This is the 'Song of the Volga Boatmen'.
It portrays the working-class people
oppressed by the Tsar,
yet striving to survive.
No wonder.
Hearing this song
reminds me of our current life.
These damn invaders,
and the Tsar who oppressed the people back then,
what's the difference?
Good.
Encore! Great!
Encore!
Then I'll play another song for everyone,
'Riding the Wind and Waves'.
Great.
We should let the Japanese
hear this song too.
Yes, great!
Wait.
Miss Qin.
Xiaoxiong.
The song 'Riding the Wind and Waves' is controversial.
We won't play it today.
Welcome everyone
to our harmonica club's open-air concert.
Our harmonica club was founded by a German,
Mr. Schiller.
Our mission is
to welcome all music-loving friends
to learn the harmonica at our club.
Music gives people armor
to withstand life's pressures and blows.
It also allows you to enjoy the beauty of life
and create a bright future.
It can also become your life companion,
accompanying you throughout your life.
When words fail,
music speaks.
Next, we bring you a
joyful piece,
'Ode to Joy'.
Business is booming lately, Boss Shen.
What good stuff
is loaded in the back?
Just some samples for the firm.
Come on, let's take a look.
Why check Boss Shen's goods?
There's no need.
Thank you, Section Chief Qian.
I'll get going if there's nothing else.
Boss Shen, actually,
I have a favor to ask you.
Tell me.
I don't know if Chen Yu told you.
About what?
Zhu Tianyou from the Gendarmerie.
I remember now.
About that killer, right?
Believe it or not, I actually asked around for you.
I heard that person
is missing his
left pinky.
And he killed Japanese
in Fangzheng County.
No, how tall is he?
What does he look like? How old is he?
I don't know about that.
Don't worry.
I'll go to Chairman Wang's place later
and ask him to ask around for you.
Chairman Wang is great.
He knows a lot of people in the underworld.
He might find something out.
He definitely will.
Okay, I'll go now.
What's wrong now?
What are you doing?
Buy something for Mr. Wang,
and say it's a token of my appreciation.
Buying things for him,
I shouldn't let you pay.
Take it, Mr. Shen.
Otherwise I won't feel at ease.
Got it.
Don't worry.
My stuff
is definitely worth the money.
Okay.
Wait for my news.
Got it.
Captain Matsuda, what brings you here?
I came to see
what's going on here.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Shen from Datong Trading Company.
We do a lot of business together,
and he's Chen Yu's older brother.
This is our dear
Captain Matsuda.
I've heard a lot about you.
What's in the car?
Some samples from my trading company.
Open it.
Sister Qin,
why did you stop us from playing "Pioneers" just now?
Did you see the audience's reaction?
The light in their eyes
is hope.
Drink some water first.
Sister Qin,
now is the time to strike while the iron is hot.
Come here.
Sit down.
You saw Li San today too.
The way he looked at us
was like eyeing prey.
He's already targeting us.
So the upcoming performances
must be suspended.
Xiaoxiong.
The Japanese are watching any signs of anti-Japanese resistance
very closely.
That's exactly why they're watching so closely.
We need to let more people
hear our music.
Outdoor performances have a limited reach.
Think about how wide a radio audience could be.
How many times have we contacted
Kong Xuzhou from the broadcasting station?
They are a commercial radio station,
not controlled by the Japanese.
Playing there
can let more people hear our music.
Even if the broadcasting station is independent in name,
can they really avoid their eyes and ears?
Going there now is like throwing ourselves into a trap.
Our music is the bullet,
and the broadcasting station is the best gun barrel.
If we don't do this,
we can't turn our harmonica club
into the second gun of anti-Japanese resistance.
Our club's anti-Japanese propaganda requires strategy
and the right timing.
If we go now
and the Japanese target us, what then?
The club will be finished.
Sister Qin, if we keep hiding like this,
when will we ever drive the Japanese out?
The broadcasting station is a rare opportunity.
If we miss this, who knows how long we'll have to wait.
Think about it.
Those working in the factories,
those farming in the fields.
They can't see the outdoor concert,
but they can hear the radio broadcast.
We need to let them know
there are still people fighting for this land,
so they won't continue to stay silent.
Xiaoxiong,
I know what you're going to say.
I understand your thoughts.
But right now,
I can't risk your safety and the safety of the team.
The banner of the Harmonica Society cannot fall.
So we can only wait.
We can't wait anymore, Sister Qin.
Every day, our compatriots
are being killed and bullied.
If we wait one more day,
there will be more despair.
The broadcasting station.
We must go.
Gu Xiaoxiong,
if you insist on going,
can you bear the consequences?
I have to bear them even if I can't.
We formed the Harmonica Society
to resist the invaders.
Captain Matsuda,
this is a special Bizen ware black pottery
I got from Bizen City, Okayama Prefecture.
It's very rare.
The glaze color will change with the tea.
Interesting.
Do you like it?
A Bizen ware black pottery tea set
is too precious.
I can't accept it.
You might have misunderstood.
This is not a gift from me.
Chief Qian asked me to buy it for you.
Isn't that right, Boss Shen? I...
Look,
Chief Qian is embarrassed.
Actually,
he even paid for it.
If you don't like it,
my business deal will fall through.
Boss Shen,
you're very good at doing business.
You flatter me.
Captain Matsuda,
if there's nothing else, I'll get going.
President Wang is waiting for me.
Are you friends with President Wang?
We've been friends for over 20 years.
Thank you.
Boss Shen,
thank you.
Take care.
Let them pass.
Hold the harmonicas in your hands when we take the picture.
Come on.
Alright, everyone,
we're getting ready to take the picture.
Thanks for your hard work.
Go up those stairs.
I know.
Brother,
why are you so late?
President Wang had something to do, so I was delayed.
I didn't delay your plans, did I?
Brother Shen.
Look,
is this the only thing missing?
Heming,
check it.
Yes, this is it.
Just in time. Let's install it right away.
Thank you, Brother Shen.
You and Lingzi go back first.
Leave this to me.
Come here.
I'll leave Ajin here.
Tell him if you have any problems.
I will help you solve them.
Don't push yourselves too hard.
Okay, Brother Shen.
We'll be leaving now.
Okay.
Be careful.
Lingzi, let's go.
Okay.
Be careful.
You guys go back first.
It's installed.
I will notify you when to activate it.
Close the gate as soon as the three minutes are up.
Be careful.
Understood.
Sir, sir.
Tonight's performance was great.
Thank you, sir.
Not bad.
Go to bed early, sir.
Don't move. Don't move.
Behave yourselves.
Stand still and behave.
Mr. Gu.
Long time no see.
What are you doing?
The broadcasting station's 'Trailblazer' was played well.
Please play it again at the Special Service Department.
Take them all away.
Let go.
How dare you resist arrest?
Beat him up.
Don't move. Stop.
Stop.
Move. Behave yourselves.
Take them away.