Sent.
Let's go save them.
Leave this to us.
You go first.
No.
Hurry up and leave.
No. If we leave, we leave together.
Listen to me.
We can't leave anything here for the Japanese.
You go first.
We'll be right behind you.
But...
Go!
Be careful.
Bastards!
You won't get anything.
Shoot him!
Come here.
Go.
Captain Matsuda.
The underground party members upstairs are all dead.
What is this old lady doing here?
I'm asking you. What are you doing?
Do you have any accomplices?
What are their names? Where are they?
Speak!
Section Chief Qian.
It seems this old lady...
doesn't understand you.
Are you mute?
Speak up quickly.
Or I'll shoot you dead.
Child.
His father.
The sound of radio waves
is so beautiful.
I know.
That's our son's soul speaking.
Our son is saying...
The Japanese...
won't last long.
Won't last long.
Sister Qin.
The route map has been converted to code and sent.
Received receipt at 8:50.
The comrades
have all evacuated safely.
The radio at the ad agency was destroyed.
Comrade Lin Heming also sacrificed his life.
From today on,
this is the battlefield.
You two are the main force.
We will fight together.
Sister Qin.
We've been ready for a long time.
Do you know
why our telegraphers
are called by comrades
'starlight in the night sky'?
We know.
Because although there are many stars in the sky,
most don't shine for more than two years.
But there will always be new stars rising.
You have to be the star
that shines longer.
Sister.
We promise to complete the mission.
You just got married not long ago.
I haven't had time
to wish you a happy marriage.
Happy marriage.
Thank you, Sister. Thank you.
Every successful transmission
involves great danger,
and requires immeasurable sacrifice.
This is your last transmission point, right?
Yes.
How long do you think
this place can hold out?
I don't know.
If it weren't for Suzuki Ko,
maybe we could have held out longer.
Suzuki Ko.
Do you have any ideas, brother?
I don't know either.
If I cast this line,
I don't know what kind of fish I'll catch.
Next month,
Manchukuo is holding a concert in Harbin.
They need a harmonica band
to play "Kimigayo"
and the "National Anthem of Manchukuo".
I've always
wanted to enjoy Miss Qin's harmonica performance.
As long as you agree to lead the band in the performance,
those children
can go home right away.
I'm a person
who values old ties.
For the sake of
my past business relationship with your father,
I'll give you three days to think about it.
No need.
I promise you right now.
But
please keep your word, Mr. Matsuda,
and release the children now.
Very well.
I hope to see as soon as possible
those children
rehearsing in the harmonica club.
No problem.
Those two songs
are relatively easy to play.
I hope to give them time
to heal their wounds.
Extra.
Harmonica band captain assassinated,
famous writer denounces the killer.
Here, give me a paper.
Extra.
Give me one.
Miss Qin.
Everyone has suffered.
Zhou.
How are your injuries recovering?
Ms. Qin.
The physical injuries are nothing,
but mentally...
Although Captain Gu is gone,
the harmonica club is still here.
Everyone must be ready to leave at any time.
Leave?
Where to?
To the rear area.
Carry on Captain Gu's legacy.
Use the harmonicas in your hands
as a second gun in the resistance against Japan.