=Forbidden Love Between=
(Adapted from "System Forced Me"
written by Xiaomanyao)
=Episode 11=
This is...
Where did you get this?
Did you go to Tian Yuxue?
Ye Wuming.
I've said it before.
I'll definitely get
anything you want for you.
Ye Wuming,
what's wrong?
Ye Wuming.
You've been poisoned.
♪The flutes and the wine
dissipate into nothingness♪
♪It matters not,
because this love will last forever♪
Tian Yaoge.
What's wrong, Palace Master?
You can't hold the sword steady.
Give me the antidote.
What antidote?
Don't play dumb with me.
Ye Wuming has been poisoned.
Give me the antidote.
Ye Wuming has been poisoned?
Are you serious?
(Ye Wuming's blood)
(is the best material
for nurturing a Love Bug.)
The Ten-day Love poison
only affects those who're in love.
When the illusion breaks in ten days,
one'll die of a broken heart.
Hei Lian, you really have skills.
You really made him fall in love.
I don't want to waste my breath.
Will you give it or not?
Why would I give it to you?
Tian Yaoge,
does His Highness know
it was you who instructed Ye Wuming
to steal the sacred relic?
Are you threatening me?
If you kill me,
His Highness won't let you off.
I believe His Highness
keeps me around for a reason.
But if he finds out
you resorted to such methods
to make him lose the sacred relic
because you couldn't
kill Ye Wuming,
I wonder if he'll still protect you.
Use your blood
to administer this medicine.
You're not lying to me, are you?
Why would I lie to you?
So you could go to my brother
and tell on me?
Wait a moment.
That was a love potion just now.
This is the real antidote.
Tian Yaoge,
I'm telling you.
I'm racing against time to save him now.
If you dare toy with me again,
I'll spare no expense
to kill you.
You haven't returned the love potion.
You're fine now.
I had a dream,
in which you wanted to kill me.
Are you afraid?
I'm not afraid.
I'm more afraid of you leaving me.
Master, please don't leave me.
No.
Ye Wuming,
stop pestering me.
I'll leave you eventually.
♪Wind, wrinkles brows not by my will♪
Pestering?
In your eyes,
is that what I'm doing?
Yes.
You're just a killing tool I trained.
My kindness towards you
is merely taking advantage of you.
No matter what you do,
it won't change our relationship.
No,
I don't believe it.
Your gaze just now
showed you care for me.
And master, you clearly said...
No matter what I say,
it doesn't matter.
I've already signed
a marriage contract with King Ling.
I already belong to Tian Yuxue.
I'll soon marry him.
What are you saying?
I already signed a marriage contract
with King Ling long ago.
When?
The day after I tried on
my wedding dress.
So,
while I was doing
so many things for you,
trying my best to please you,
you signed a marriage contract with him?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why?
In your eyes,
I was like a fool,
begging you, pleasing you,
bothering you,
and you didn't tell me?
I've already told you
I was going to marry King Ling.
That's different.
Do you know
what that piece of paper means
to the Xuanling Clan?
It's a lifetime vow.
No matter what it means,
it's the same to me.
I want to be the queen
of the Xuanling Clan.
My intention won't change.
Do you really care so much
about King Ling?
Yes.
So I hope you can let me go.
Let you go?
After all I've done for you,
all I get is
"let you go"?
I won't let you go.
Nor will I let you marry him.
The King of the Xuanling Clan?
Whatever he can give you,
I can as well.
♪When will the warm wind
of our encounter blow again?♪
♪Sharing a drink with you,
and watching the fireworks together♪
♪If you would run to me,
I'm fine with waiting three lifetimes♪
♪If in the end it's you,
the pain is worth it♪
♪Love, deep in the heart,
thickens like ink♪
♪Yet it's hard to paint you again♪
♪Two souls, close
but fearful of feelings♪
♪How can they escape the fate♪
♪Maybe because of too much love
in a past life♪
♪This life is full of twists and turns♪