=Forbidden Love Between=
(Adapted from "System Forced Me"
written by Xiaomanyao)
=Episode 13=
Hei Lian,
have you ever considered
if Yaoge is a master of using bugs,
then surely I am too?
Why do you think
you could deceive me?
I...
I just wanted
Your Highness to treat me a bit better,
so that's why...
Even if you used the finest materials,
a Love Bug brewed by a mere maid
from the Moon Palace
won't work on me.
(Now is the best opportunity.)
Your Highness won't kill me, right?
We're about to be married.
How could you bear to do it?
If you wanted me dead,
you'd have done it long ago.
Please, out of consideration
for my momentary foolishness
and deep affection for you,
forgive me.
Ye Wuming,
come out!
No need to bother.
Let me continue to drink
with Your Highness.
I'm not in the mood now.
Get lost.
(I was so close.)
(Ye Wuming,)
(if you gave me a little more time,)
(maybe I could find the chip.)
Ye Wuming,
why did you come?
You took my blood
just to do this?
Yes,
your blood can brew the best Love Bug.
I just wanted His Highness to love me,
and to be close to me.
Is that not allowed?
You sacrificed yourself,
pretended to care for me,
used me,
made me fall in love,
and then took my blood,
all just to make him love you.
I've signed
the marriage contract with His Highness.
He's my future husband.
I hope he loves me.
What's wrong with that?
You're right.
Then,
no matter what I do,
don't hate me.
Ye Wuming,
don't do anything foolish.
You'll die.
That's none of your concern anymore.
Is Ye Wuming
going to retrive his meridian?
You told him the location
of the seal?
I dare not deceive him.
He wanted to kill me.
This is your reason for betraying me?
Rest assured, Yuxue.
I warned him.
If he goes for it now,
he won't withstand the thunder curse.
He'll wait a few days.
Get Hei Lian over.
I want to inform her,
tomorrow I'll marry her.
Tomorrow?
Yes,
tomorrow.
Hei Lian,
since we've already signed
the marriage contract,
why delay further?
Tomorrow is an auspicious day.
I want you
to become my queen sooner.
Why, don't you want to?
I know,
once the marriage contract is signed,
I belong to Your Highness.
I can't break the vow.
It's good that you know.
I've been waiting for this day
for a long time.
Today, you should rest well
and prepare to become my queen.
Alright.
Yuxue,
Ye Wuming really
went into the Mystic Void Realm.
What did you say?
He's a dead man.
(Did Ye Wuming really
go to retrieve his meridian?)
(He was just poisoned.)
(No way,)
(I must go see.)
Ye Wuming,
do you know what you're doing?
I do.
Even if you defeat us,
you still have to withstand
99 thunder curses.
The pain of the thunder curse
far exceeds skinning and muscle pulling.
No ordinary person can endure that.
You'll die.
Even if I die,
I won't let anyone harm her.
Fine,
I'll grant your wish.
Your Highness,
tomorrow we'll be married.
I still need to prepare.
Prepare?
Aren't you anxious?
Knowing Ye Wuming went
to the Mystic Void Realm,
are you rushing to see
how he's doing?
Since Your Highness knows
Ye Wuming went to the Mystic Void Realm,
why are you so relaxed?
Aren't you afraid he might
retrieve his meridian?
Retrieve his meridian?
Even if he can withstand
the 12 witches
and the 99 thunder curses,
he'll suffer severe harm.
Moreover,
I've already taken back
the physical form
of his meridian long ago.
The one in the Mystic Void Realm
is fake,
and it's poisoned.
Ye Wuming is undoubtedly doomed.
Doomed!
I can't believe you set a trap!
Let go of me!
I have to find him.
You're not going anywhere.
Once the marriage contract is signed,
you're forever mine.
Mine!
Even if we sign the marriage contract,
I won't share the meridian with you.
I never intended to share
the meridian with you.
I only want your heart.
What do you mean by that?
At this point,
I won't hide it from you anymore.
Years ago,
I met a woman
named Liu Rushuang.
Liu Rushuang?
We truly loved each other.
I thought
we'd be together forever.
Unfortunately,
someone from the Ninth Heavens came.
Ever since his appearance,
she never woke up again.
Someone from the Ninth Heavens?
She's the tourist you need
to bring back,
Liu Rushuang.
So you've really met my dad?
♪Listen, drifting clouds
turn flowers to fall♪
♪Wind, wrinkles brows not by my will♪
♪Departed, like a bird
in the heart's crevice, flies over♪
♪Close yet unable to touch♪
♪Is love all like
an unpredictable dream?♪
♪The tighter you grasp,
the more it slips away♪
♪It's said that the heart-piercing
farewell song♪
♪Still has a place
to rest even in drifting♪
♪Meeting is like the warm wind♪
♪Forgetting is like a knife cutting♪
♪The once moonlight
is now like a frozen river♪
♪If you would run to me♪
♪I'm fine with waiting three lifetimes♪
♪If in the end it's you,
the pain is worth it♪