=Forbidden Love Between=
(Adapted from "System Forced Me"
written by Xiaomanyao)
=Episode 2=
Ye Wuming,
what do you want to do?
Master, you climb into my bed at night.
And you ask me what I want?
What,
do you want to make me your boy toy?
Do you think you're qualified?
If you don't want to favor me,
then...
Do you want to kill me?
You think you can kill me?
(Such a terrifying killing intent.)
(Is he really going to kill me?)
(I need to find a way
to get out of here.)
Do you want to be
my boy toy that badly?
I'll grant your wish.
Take off your clothes.
Are you serious, Master?
I'm serious.
Don't you want me to favor you?
♪Wind, wrinkles brows not by my will♪
(Ye Wuming,)
(don't be so smug.)
(When I find the chip,)
(I'll completely destroy you.)
♪Is love all like
an unpredictable dream?♪
♪The tighter you grasp,
the more it slips away♪
♪It's said that the heart-piercing
farewell song♪
♪Ultimately, it didn't spare you or me♪
♪Meeting is like the warm wind,
and forgetting is like a knife cutting♪
Enough.
♪The once moonlight
is now like a frozen river♪
Ye Wuming, you're overthinking it.
You're far worse
compared to my boy toys.
Who's there?
It's me, Hei.
Come in.
Ye Wuming's data
fluctuated just now.
How did it go?
Did you succeed?
No.
I scanned him twice
but couldn't find the chip.
The greater a virtual person's
mood swings,
the stronger the chip signal.
Ye Wuming is basically emotionless,
so his signal is weak.
Think of a way to make him emotional.
Emotional?
Should I seduce him?
At critical moments,
you have to step up.
(Moon Palace)
(Ye Wuming was here.)
(When?)
(How did I not notice at all?)
Palace Master,
King Ling is summoning you.
King Ling?
(That notorious killer?)
Tell Ye Wuming
to wait outside King Ling's hall.
If I don't come out
in half an hour,
he should come in directly.
Yes.
(Xuantian Palace)
Your Highness.
(Tian Yuxue is the king
of the Xuanling Clan.)
(Why is he...)
(Tian Yuxue, Xuantian Palace)
You're my betrothed princess.
Since when did you become so distant?
(I see.)
You must be joking.
Ye Wuming wiped out
the entire Zhaoyao Sect.
Are you aware of that?
I know.
Since you know,
why don't you kill him?
Why is that brat still alive?
(King Ling wants to kill Ye Wuming.)
(No way.)
(I need to find a reason
to keep him alive)
(until I get the chip.)
Your Highness, you didn't know.
I sent him to destroy the Zhaoyao Sect.
You sent him?
Why?
Your Highness,
Nangong Jue had a body
of extreme yin and yang,
with the aura of Asura.
He came from an ancient sect
and was very talented.
His presence in this world
would be a threat to you.
What did you say?
A threat to me?
Let me tell you,
no one in this world can threaten me.
No one can defeat me either.
Compared to Nangong Jue,
Ye Wuming is the only one
that disgusts me.
His existence is a mistake.
You said
once we used him
to cultivate the Chaotic Demon Art,
we would kill him.
I can't tolerate his survival.
How much longer must I wait?
Soon, Your Highness.
Soon.
We can't kill him now.
Don't make me wait too long.
Alright.
What,
don't you like it anymore?
Your Highness,
I've been cultivating recently...
Hei Lian,
this isn't like you.
Master,
it's time for your cultivation.
Who allowed you to come in,
you brat?
Hei Lian,
he spoiled my mood.
Tell me
how he should be punished.
(He endured being stabbed before,)
(so a bit of whipping
shouldn't be an issue.)
How about
whipping him a few times?
You really know how to torment people.
The Wuji Whip
depletes one-tenth
of one's power with each lash
until bones are shattered.
(He won't die like this, will he?)
(I haven't found his chip yet.)
♪Listen, drifting clouds
turn flowers to fall♪
♪Wind, wrinkles brows not by my will♪
♪Departed, like a bird
in the heart's crevice, flies over♪
♪Close yet unable to touch♪
♪Is love all like
an unpredictable dream?♪
♪The tighter you grasp,
the more it slips away♪
♪It's said that the heart-piercing
farewell song♪
♪Still has a place
to rest even in drifting♪
♪Meeting is like the warm wind♪
♪Forgetting is like a knife cutting♪
♪The once moonlight
is now like a frozen river♪
♪If you would run to me♪
♪I'm fine with waiting three lifetimes♪
♪If in the end it's you,
the pain is worth it♪