=Forbidden Love Between=
(Adapted from "System Forced Me"
written by Xiaomanyao)
=Episode 23=
Lu Ning.
Ye Wuming,
it's you, right?
Lu Ning,
listen to me.
Go back immediately.
Don't stay here.
What's going on?
All the clans are attacking.
The immortals and demons
are all coming at us.
Let me out.
I beg you.
Go away.
Don't come back again.
Hurry up and go.
Ye Wuming.
I don't want to go.
Let me out.
Ye Wuming.
Tian Yuxue.
You must've been
waiting for me for a long time.
While Ye Wuming was busy
saving the world,
my old followers broke into the dungeon
and rescued me.
What?
You've become the queen.
You don't even bother
pretending anymore?
I haven't come looking for you,
yet you deliver yourself to me.
Have you forgotten
how your father died?
I forgot to mention,
Ye Wuming
is also in my hands.
On stormy nights,
my spiritual power is strongest.
Why haven't you left yet?
It's still not too late
if you go now.
I told you,
I came back
to be with you.
Enough.
No need to act lovey-dovey
in front of me.
You probably don't know.
Although Ye Wuming removed
the Love-cutting Bug,
the poison has already
penetrated his bones.
His spiritual power is only a tenth
of what it used to be.
Thanks to you,
I no longer need to rely on his meridian
to defeat him.
Ye Wuming,
ever since I was young,
father left my mother and me
for your mother.
The first time I saw you,
I hated you to the core.
You took away my father,
my queen,
destroyed my beloved woman,
and even snatched my throne.
Why?
I possess the purest bloodline
of the Xuanling Clan.
You, a demonic bastard,
snatched my throne.
What qualifications do you have
to be the king?
Now,
you'll watch your beloved woman die
with your own eyes.
Lu Ning.
There's not much time left.
She wouldn't really be foolish enough
to stay there, would she?
By the way,
this world is so dangerous.
Haven't you thought
about shutting it down?
Five years ago when Lu Ning's dad died,
we did consider it.
But then the data returned to normal.
Returned to normal?
Don't think I don't know.
Back then, a guy hacked in
and then fell into a coma.
You suppressed that incident, right?
That guy is an expert in our area.
You didn't open a channel,
so he hacked his way through.
If he weren't still in a coma,
perhaps we could ask him for help.
What was that guy's name again?
Xu...
Yi...
Chi...
Lu Ning.
Ye Wuming,
you're always the same in every life.
You refuse to beg for mercy
until the last moment.
Why?
If only you just begged me once.
Tian Yuxue,
I only have a tenth
of my spiritual power left.
But you forgot, we Demon Clan
are born with the ability
to gain strength
through Soul-consuming Art.
You're destroying yourself.
Ye Wuming.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Why aren't you leaving yet?
Where do you want me to go?
Home.
Didn't you always want to go home?
Didn't you say
this is my home?
♪Listen, drifting clouds
turn flowers to fall♪
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have made you come back.
It was my decision to come back,
because I needed you.
Ye Wuming,
there's one more day
before this world restarts.
This last day,
I want you to spend it with me.
♪It's said that the heart-piercing
farewell song♪
♪Ultimately, it didn't spare you or me♪
♪Meeting is like the warm wind,
and forgetting is like a knife cutting♪
♪The once moonlight
is now like a frozen river♪
♪I can't bear you forgetting me,
yet fear causing you to delay♪
♪How can the heart be separated
even when apart♪
Why?
Why is your chip different
from Tian Yuxue's?
Have you ever considered
we might be from the same world?
Son, stop running.
Get out now.
The system is about to restart.
She's Liu Rushuang.
She also hacked in.
Liu Rushuang?
Hurry up!
Rushuang.
You remember something,
right?
Yes,
we're from the same world.
♪Still has a place
to rest even in drifting♪
♪Meeting is like the warm wind,
and forgetting is like a knife cutting♪
♪The once moonlight
is now like a frozen river♪
♪I can't bear you forgetting me,
yet fear causing you to delay♪
♪Mountains and seas separate us,
but how can our hearts part?♪
♪When will the warm wind
of our encounter blow again?♪
♪Sharing a drink with you,
and watching the fireworks together♪
♪If you would run to me,
I'm fine with waiting three lifetimes♪
♪If in the end it's you,
the pain is worth it♪