This is my shoot and my cast member.
I'll do what I want.
You can't even take care of yourself.
What do you think you're going to do?
Jun-mo, don't you get it?
CEO Byun and Cindy are at war,
and you might get sucked in.
I'll get sucked in then.
Afterward,
I'll find my place again.
That's what I'll do this time.
I'm sorry.
It's too frustrating.
We don't have time to look out for others.
This isn't some college club.
This is a place where things are done
according to market logic.
Cindy and the show are kind of the same.
When they were both popular, they didn't
see that it can come to an end.
It's like a man and a woman.
Once you're over the person,
you don't want them back.
It will be a relief
if nobody files a lawsuit.
Everyone is saying that
our show is getting canceled.
Why does Producer Ra
have to be so determined
at a time like this?
He's usually so indecisive.
I know, right?
Our show's in trouble as it is.
How can he still want us to shoot with
Cindy when she's hated by everyone?
He's trying to kill us all.
But do you know what's really scary?
What?
Nobody is stopping him,
not even the higher-ups.
Our show is really going to get canceled.
Producer Ra is so irresponsible.
-Hello.
-Hey.
-Writer Son.
-Yes?
How long have you been working
with Jun-mo?
Around five years.
And nothing has worked out well
during that time?
When his shows were failing,
do you think the higher-ups
didn't tell him to change writers?
-Producer--
-They told him to do that. They did.
But that indecisive Jun-mo,
the guy who always has issues
with his shows,
defended you guys
by arguing that you're part of his family
and shouldn't be replaced.
I just don't know what that responsibility
you're talking about is.
Come to the roof.
I'm worried about your team.
You keep running into trouble.
What is it?
You told me to come up here.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Last night,
I walked home.
You walked?
From there to your house?
Hey, that's really far.
Did it take you all night?
No. Not all night.
I got home around 5:00 a.m.
Gosh, you're nuts.
May I keep talking?
Yes, sorry. Keep going.
As I walked,
I thought about it.
I want to shoot it again.
What?
Shoot what again?
If my life is a show,
and I'm the main character...
And if someone is shooting me--
Nice analogy.
You're a true producer now.
Keep going.
Then...
I would like to shoot it again.
I don't know where to start over again.
Maybe I shouldn't have
recorded my feelings
in that stuffed animal.
Maybe I shouldn't have left you in my room
when my dad told me to come out
and play chess.
Or maybe I shouldn't have
come to the playground
when you told me to come out.
If not that,
I should have kept you from rejecting me
by not going on that date
yesterday.
If not that...
maybe I should go back way earlier
to when I started to like being around you
and started to hate
how you looked at Producer Ra.
Maybe I should go back to that time.
I don't know where I should start over,
but the point is
I want to shoot it again.
Why?
Why do you want to shoot it again?
Do you think it would've been better
if you didn't like me
because that way, you wouldn't be hurt?
No.
I wanted to like you more properly.
I was
too awkward.
I was too lacking, and I rushed it.
I was young and lame.
Maybe I could've acted cooler
or more mature.
Maybe there was a more sophisticated way
for me to get closer to you
without making you this uncomfortable.
That's why
I want to stop the filming here,
edit everything out,
and start the shoot over again.
That's what I thought of as I walked.
Would that be impossible?
For one last time,
I just wanted to ask you.
Shouldn't you submit a complaint
at the district office
about those street lamps?
I don't know.
The street lamps all turn on now.
I think that Seung-chan
might have filed a complaint
at the district office.
But maybe it wasn't him.
Maybe the lights were scheduled
to come on tonight.
Because Seung-chan
has been so good to me recently,
I thought it could have been him.
I can't expect that at all from Jun-mo.
He isn't detail-oriented
and not that kind.
But Seung-chan is like that.
-Hello. This way.
-Okay.
Cindy.
What are you doing?
It's time for the shoot.
Here.
You have to drink it.
Why do you keep looking at me?
Cindy.
You going to a shoot
feels like a dream to me.
Don't do that again.
Don't plan with the staff
and hide things from me.
I probably looked really weird earlier.
Hey, that was the prettiest
I've seen you look.
What are you going to do about CEO Byun?
What if she slaps you again?
I'm not that scared of CEO Byun.
You're the scariest.
I'm the scariest?
Of course.
When someone I don't like gets mad at me,
it's no big deal.
But when someone I like
is disappointed or mad at me,
that is what's really scary.
Are you an idiot? Why do you like me?
Cindy is going to the shoot?
Yes, they woke her up in the morning,
and now she's going to a shoot.
Then, what about Jinie?
Two Days and One Night.
-Right.
-Two Days and One Night!
She's been practicing that
since yesterday.
I talked to the chief director...
Ra Jun-mo still doesn't get it.
Him doing that won't help Cindy.
Two Days and One Night!
So, is Cindy coming today?
No way. Would she really come?
If she does, she's one strong person.
But why would she tell a lie like that?
I think she's always been a liar.
Didn't you all sense that?
I think she's all right.
She seemed a little stuck up at first,
but she's cool when you get to know her.
You're a terrible judge of character.
She didn't even blink an eye
whenever she addressed me in a way
that made me look like an old person.
I don't like her!
But you are much older than Cindy.
Anyway, people should be honest.
Do you think it's okay to lie
when you're a celebrity?
Oh, Cindy!
We were worried about you.
Right? Weren't we?
Those articles aren't true, right?
It was a misunderstanding, right?
Tell us.
Thank you so much for worrying about me,
Sandara.
Thank you for coming all this way.
Today is a "Going Home" special.
You will each be spending the night
with an elderly lady at her house.
Here are the ladies
you'll be spending your time with!
Goodness, look at that.
How amazing.
Oh, that's a helicam.
It's a camera that shoots from the sky
like a helicopter.
It's a camera.
It's filming you ladies.
You look pretty right now.
Seung-chan, what are you doing?
Bring them here.
We got some great locals to join the cast.
The old ladies live with simplicity...
That's a drone, right?
There was one of those during the shoot
for Hometown Report.
Mr. Producer.
Will you pay our appearance fees
in cash or in gift certificates?
Well, let me talk to the writer.
I'll check and let you know.
Thank you.
They know what a drone is.
Ma'am, you can walk slowly.
We have plenty of time.
So, who's the singer?
Excuse me?
Which of you two is the celebrity?
Ma'am, don't you know who I am?
The only celebrity I know is Song Hae.
I'm on TV a lot too.
What's your name?
Cindy.
What?
That's a strange name.
Do you think that's funny?
It sure is.
Was that supposed to be funny?
Was that a joke?
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I was flustered.
I've been in the industry for ten years.
I've been in commercials, dramas,
and all sorts of awards shows.
I've been on TV plenty of times.
I thought everyone in Korea knew me.
But she doesn't know me.
But...
I didn't dislike that.
I like that she doesn't know me at all.
I feel comfortable.
I feel free.
Ma'am.
Are we going to cook rice in a cauldron?
A cauldron?
This isn't the war era.
We use rice cookers here too.
You don't grill fritters
on a cauldron lid?
I have a frying pan.
I see.
Ma'am.
When did you wash this?
It's brand new.
You've never washed this since 2002?
2002 FIFA WORLD CUP
KOREA/JAPAN
It's new.
The blanket...
Yes?
No, it's just that...
It's bigger than I thought.
I see.
How long have we been shooting?
Producer.
Can't you stop filming now?
Okay, we have plenty of footage anyway.
Then stop filming and help me out here.
Oh, okay.
Turn it the other way.
No, the other way.
Producer, how can you be weaker than me?
It's not that I'm weak.
It's because my timing was off.
See? You are weaker than me.
I'm really not.
We were out of sync.
Where did you watch the 2002 World Cup?
I went out in the streets
with my older brother.
Me too.
I watched it in Seoul with my dad once.
We spread out a mat in Yeouido Park
and watched it on the big screen.
I went there often too
since I live in Yeouido.
Do you remember what game it was?
There was a shoot-out...
Against Spain!
Wow, this is interesting.
Right.
So many people were there.
Well, it's not a big connection,
but it's still a connection.
You've known Producer Ra
for a longer time,
but we have this small connection too.
Just so you know,
I know that you didn't lie.
Of course!
You'll hang this out to dry, right?
In the sunshine, so it gets nice and soft.
Of course.
I was worried,
but it's a relief
that she's handling this so well.
I heard what's going on
at the other houses.
They're performing for the ladies,
and visiting neighbors,
and getting good footage
with stuff like that.
But Cindy's just doing housework
like a maid.
It's a bit of a problem.
We're not getting enough good footage.
Didn't I just sound like a real producer?
"We're not getting enough good footage."
There's an issue
with the amount of footage.
Don't you think?
He really took Cindy along?
Yes. Articles about it are already out.
They're badmouthing the show too.
"Why would a reality show use a liar?
Are you ignoring public opinion?"
CEO Byun must know too.
I think she will come and barge in.
We'll have to talk to her for a while,
so how about we go eat first?
Right, we should.
What's the special at the cafeteria today?
It's good that both of you are here.
We're so upset.
We were just talking.
That Jun-mo...
Is this a joke?
We were trying to help you out
by taking out the problematic child
and giving you the one with potential.
Producer Ra just doesn't understand me.
You know how he is.
In our department,
people do say he jinxes things.
He only goes for what won't work.
So, the thing is...
About the new program, Star Wars.
I heard it will take the time slot
currently occupied
by Two Days and One Night.
I'll let you have Jinie for that show.
Get rid of Two Days and One Night,
and start Star Wars.
Wow.
You coming here yourself
and telling us that
offends me.
If we got rid of a show after one mishap
or after one mistake,
what show would last over six months?
Right. That's true.
If we were going to let
the agencies decide
who to cast in our shows,
why would we need producers here?
Sir--
Whether we cancel a show,
start a new one, or add a cast member,
we will be the ones to decide that,
CEO Byun.
That's why I have this job.
Oh, really?
I see.
I hope you two don't regret this.
If you do,
it will be a headache.
Sir.
Are we no longer canceling
Two Days and One Night?
I don't know.
I just said that because I was angry.
Let's go eat.
The line will be long if we're late.
Okay.
The pre-recording for this week
won't be played during the rehearsal.
We don't have time.
Noted. Will check that.
It's a good thing Cindy is out
after doing her last show last week.
It would be hard for her
to win first place this week.
The competition is tough this week.
It's going to be a close game.
There are so many popular singers.
Even if she did rank first,
I don't think she'll want to be
on television for a while.
I heard she's filming
Two Days and One Night.
What is Jun-mo going to do?
Good question.
But I don't think Cindy lied on purpose.
She's still at fault
for not confessing sooner.
She kept it to herself.
It's not like that.
Back when I was a cameraman...
When was that again?
When Cindy was in Pinky4,
I interviewed her for some show.
She said so back then.
That she was an orphan.
If that was true,
this wouldn't have happened.
People would've watched the show.
You must be confusing her
with someone else.
I'm right!
I distinctly remember
because she cried so much.
What did she say as she cried?
That her parents died because of her.
She was so sad back then.
Did that footage air?
Probably not.
One of the managers cut it short.
New artists should all look pretty,
but her makeup came off
because she cried so much.
That's why we cut it.
They asked the producer not to air it.
When was that?
Well...
I think it was around
seven or eight years ago.
What show was it for?
Was it Entertainment Weekly?
Or some special show for singers?
It's been so long that I don't remember.
Ye-jin, we have to organize the seats.
It's almost time.
Right. Okay.
Organize the seats, please.
Who are you?
She's Jinie, a rookie singer
of Byun Entertainment.
You're the youngest writer
for Music Bank, right?
Yes.
Why aren't you getting up
when the singer is here?
This is the singer's green room,
not the writer's green room.
Oh, is she the singer?
What do you mean?
I thought you were a stylist.
She doesn't look like a celebrity.
CEO Byun.
What are you talking about?
Of course, she looks like a celebrity!
Goodness...
My bad.
I really thought you were a stylist.
Goodbye.
What's with everyone
at the broadcast station today?
What's their deal?
This is so annoying!
Jinie, you better lose some weight.
Where's your willpower?
Cindy starved for days when I told her to.
-General Manager Kim.
-Yes?
Watch her starting today.
If you see her eat anything
that's not on her diet,
tell me right away, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, are things going well?
I don't know.
Why don't you know?
Did you get fun footage
of her and the old lady?
Well...
it wasn't awkward,
but I don't know if it's that interesting.
Where's Cindy?
How long is she going to
clean and organize?
Did she get a job at a restaurant?
She keeps moving around,
but she hasn't really said anything funny.
The footage isn't great either.
I don't know if it will help
during editing.
Producer Ra,
don't I kind of sound like a producer?
Jeez.
Yes, you sure do.
But...
is our show really going to get canceled?
You know what?
No variety show ends on a high note.
Variety shows end when they fail.
For dramas,
the number of episodes is determined
from the start.
A successful one ends with an applause.
It goes out with a bang, a happy ending.
But that's not the case for variety shows.
If people clap for it, it keeps running.
But they can't clap forever.
It eventually gets old.
It eventually gets obvious.
People eventually stop watching it.
It becomes a nuisance.
That's when it's over.
That's why it's hard
to end on a high note.
It's always bitter and sad at the end.
A sad ending.
I would like it
if the show doesn't get canceled.
Do you think I would be happy?
This is a long-running show
that's been on air since 2007.
The more long-running a show is,
the worse you feel when it ends with you.
Do you have the original footage
for report shoots?
We do. Which one are you looking for?
It's from seven to eight years ago.
Stuff that old isn't on the computer.
You'll have to look through the tapes.
They should be indexed.
I see.
Pinky4 was in it.
I need footage from Entertainment Weekly
and singer specials.
We're off work in an hour.
Okay, I'll be quick.
This is a lot.
Forget this! I quit!
I'm so tired. What am I doing?
How will I go to the bathroom later?
I think it will be scary.
It's true that we see ghosts often
when we shoot in the countryside.
Excuse me?
Don't lie.
Why are you so surprised?
We really see a lot of ghosts.
You'll see one soon.
We even have nightmares
and sleep paralysis.
Last year...
What was the name of that mountain?
Anyway, up on a high mountain,
we slept outdoors.
I saw a strange woman in my dream.
She had long hair
and was dressed in white.
Oh, come on.
Stop it.
Why? Just hear me out.
Yes, this is getting interesting.
I couldn't tell if the woman
was human or a ghost.
Then I talked to the cameraman
in the morning.
He said he saw that woman
in his dream too.
We talked it over,
and we had the same description of her,
down to the mole on her nose.
That's it.
I was going to do it later,
but we should do
a horror special immediately.
That sounds like fun.
Isn't that for the summer?
We don't know if we'll be around
in the summer,
so we have to immediately
do things we think of.
We should do it right away.
Let's have a horror special.
It's because of me, isn't it?
You're getting canceled because of me.
They've been talking about it
for a while now.
You made the decision
to take responsibility for me.
I know that.
I came to this shoot
knowing that it could cause you trouble.
Cindy.
Yes?
There's the term "the price of fame."
Fame isn't just about fortune.
You must pay your dues emotionally.
"Why do I have to go through this?"
Feeling uncomfortable and oppressed.
Those things,
you have to accept them more naturally.
Think of it as a tax you have to pay.
That will make you feel better.
You try going through this.
It's not easy.
Well, good point.
I saw Yun-a recently.
Yun-a?
Yes.
How is she doing?
She's doing great.
She runs a flower shop.
She's a florist.
I see.
Maybe I should run a flower shop later.
No.
I'll run a moving company.
I'm great at organizing things at home.
I bet I would get great customer ratings.
Right, that would be perfect for you.
What's wrong with him?
I hate it when guys do this.
This kid...
The cast member isn't even asleep.
How can the producer fall asleep first?
Cindy, go to bed.
Get some sleep. It's late.
I'm fine.
The wind is cool and nice.
I just want to stay like this
a bit longer.
Really?
Yes.
Just a bit longer...
Why are the dogs barking so much?
I'm sorry.
Seriously.
Do you know that you slept
for over half an hour?
You should've woken me up.
You were sleeping so peacefully.
I also didn't want to wake you.
I know who you like.
Even though I can't be happy for you,
I don't want to get in your way.
But...
I don't want to lie
about my feelings.
I heard that
having a one-sided crush
is like building
and destroying a house by oneself
and that it's very tiring.
Oh, my.
Are you worrying about me?
Are you telling me not to bother
building and destroying?
That I shouldn't waste my time?
No, it's not like that.
Are you looking down on me
because I have a crush?
No!
No, I wouldn't dare.
It's actually an honor to be liked by you.
It's an honor, and I like you...
You like me?
No, I mean...
I don't mean in that sense.
Do you hate me then?
No, that's definitely not the case.
How can I not like it
when someone likes me?
Wow, so you're just happy
if anyone likes you?
No.
No, it's really not like that.
Just remember me.
The heroine of the Cindy fan club.
The star everyone used to love.
Even though everyone hates me now.
Anyway...
I'm nothing without my pride.
I never got crushes.
And I used to not care at all
if someone liked me.
But despite the fact that
you don't like me enough
to give me a bag of stuffed pancakes,
I still really like you.
From afar,
I'll be keeping myself busy
building and destroying a house,
so, if you happen to think of me,
if you want to see
what kind of house it is,
if you're curious,
then you can look back.
This really makes me
sound like a beggar.
I'm not begging for your affection here,
so don't misunderstand.
Right. Of course not.
Thank you.
You said you felt bad
for making me a beggar, right?
Yes, I didn't mean to.
You said you would
make it up to me, right?
When I go back to Seoul,
I have a lot of things to take care of
on my own.
It's possible that no one
will give me a helping hand.
Can you hold my hand just once?
Your hands are really warm.
Oh, just my luck.
I shouldn't have heard that story.
Why did I listen?
Hello.
Oh, you're here.
What is it?
Producer, did you pull an all-nighter?
Goodness. How did you know?
You're wearing the same clothes.
Oh, right.
I had some work to do.
Hey, what's with that smile?
Looks like you made your decision.
I guess something good happened.
No.
It's not like that.
Hey! It's not what you're thinking.
Then what?
Look at these tapes.
I spent all night in the editing room.
I see.
But don't change clothes.
Why not?
Somehow...
you look really hot.
Really?
Do I look like
I have a complicated personal life?
Thank you.
You're a big girl.
Follow her from afar
until she gets in the car.
Her expression looks good now.
-Seung-chan.
-Yes?
Ms. Lee Myeong-ja said
she's a fan of Song Hae, right?
Yes.
Get a video message from him
so we can edit it in.
A video message?
A video message to Ms. Lee Myeong-ja.
It will be good to use it for the ending.
Song Hae's office is in Jongno.
I'll call him, so go there now.
Take a cameraman along.
-Oh, right now?
-Yes, right now.
Got it.
Good.
Will he be okay?
What do you think?
He should say hello.
He's a newbie
in the entertainment department.
It's his initiation rite.
Ready...
action.
This is to Myeong-ja.
I can tell if you're my fan.
You must have high standards.
How old is she?
She's 78.
-What? She's 78?
-Yes.
That's a great age.
An exciting age.
Myeong-ja, enjoy your life.
You've lived long enough to know that.
Time really flies.
Ten years can go by
in the blink of an eye.
We can only live our lives once.
So enjoy your life!
I'll go to your neighborhood soon.
So stay healthy until then,
and let's meet when I go there.
I'm a pretty good guy.
Let's make a promise.
Sir.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I'm doing that so you know where it ends.
Wait a minute.
Are you a new employee?
Yes, sir.
Oh, I see. Okay.
So you're a new employee?
Do you drink?
I can't really hold my liquor.
Good, I wasn't planning
on drinking much today.
How about having just one drink with me?
You're about to pass out. Goodness.
Hey, man.
Hae!
What? My goodness.
I really...
-Oh, my goodness.
-Hae, I...
I...
I really don't want our show
to get canceled.
Oh dear...
Why is a fine show of seven years
getting canceled
after I joined the team?
Did you say seven years?
Gosh.
I've been doing my show for 35 years.
Oh, 35 years?
Seven years is nothing.
Hae.
Why are you being so informal?
-Gosh. Hae!
-What?
You're the best, man.
You're awesome.
Jeez...
Wow, 35 years...
People still say this to me.
They say I've been doing my show
for so long,
I could do it with my eyes closed.
How could I do it with my eyes closed?
When I shout, "National,"
the crowd shouts, "Singing Contest!"
My heart still races,
and I feel like I'm in a hurry.
Why?
Because I think of whether or not
they shouted louder
than the previous episode.
You must be wondering
why I'm doing something so difficult.
Because I love it.
That's why I've been doing the show
for 35 years.
Goodness.
You should know that.
Hey, Hae.
I love you, man.
Did you get a tan?
I told you to be careful of UV rays.
Thank you for worrying.
I'll be careful during the next shoot.
The next shoot?
Cindy, you're always so optimistic.
You should learn from her.
Cindy.
The agency suffered a big loss last week.
Our stock has plummeted.
We tried our best to keep you on board.
I don't know why we have to
officially apologize
for the mistake that you made,
but that's what we're going to do.
You can reflect on that for now.
Jinie, you should learn.
This was the biggest news this week.
It's about top singer, Cindy.
We found out that Cindy has been working
while lying about her background
and her parents.
I'm sure many of Cindy's fans
are disappointed.
We were going to air an interview
by Cindy's agency CEO
with her official statement,
but we got different news
right before the shoot.
This is the point.
Cindy's exaggerated family background.
Was it Cindy's lie,
or was it made up by her agency?
But even if Cindy's agency
had been the ones
to fabricate her background,
Cindy's failure to come forward
with the truth
left many people feeling betrayed.
But if you see this exclusive footage,
you will discover a different truth.
This is an interview
from when Cindy was a rookie.
Let's watch it now.
My parents
drove from Chuncheon to Seoul to see me
-and got into an accident.
-What is this?
-Why are they showing this?
-It's all my fault.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Just a moment, please.
I told you not to talk about that,
didn't I?
I told you not to talk about that.
They're in the United States.
"My home is in the States.
My parents are there."
Is that so hard?
How high is your IQ?
Producer, please edit this out.
She's still too young.
Stop. Let's start again, okay?
Hey, General Manager Kim!
Call the chief director!
Sue all of them!
I told a senior at Entertainment Weekly
and just gave him the tape.
How did you find it?
One of our cameramen said
he shot that footage in the past.
That's why.
How did you find
that original unaired footage?
It was easy. I'm a producer.
I found it in no time.
Things will be okay soon.
I'm telling you this
so you can have some peace of mind
for a few hours.
Tell CEO Byun to get a cleaning service
for her agency's front door, okay?
BYE, EVIL CEO BYUN
Wow, how did you find that?
Look at me.
I stayed up all night.
Look at how bad my dark circles are.
You were...
You were worried about her.
You didn't tell me why,
but I know you're sensitive
about CEO Byun.
I knew you cared about
what happened to Cindy.
Isn't that why you still used Cindy
in your shoot?
Yes.
If you hadn't found that footage,
our show and Cindy
would've been in big trouble.
You saved us.
-Are you thankful?
-Yes. Thank you so much, Ye-jin.
Hey, I'm really tired.
Sleep over at my house tonight.
Keep your voice down!
Someone might hear you.
-Spend the night.
-Forget it!
I have a house.
Why would I sleep at yours?
But you're tired.
It's dangerous for you
to drive on the highway.
And your brother
sleeps over at my house
once every couple of days.
That brat drives me nuts.
Jun-mo, Seung-chan isn't back yet.
He's not picking up his phone.
Leave him be.
He will come back eventually.
He's not going anywhere.
Are you looking for me?
Are you people looking for me?
Yes, we were.
Who made him drink so much?
He did an interview with Song Hae.
Oh, is it his initiation?
Yes.
You, Ra Jun-mo.
All right, just do what you want.
For real?
I'm going to do what I want.
Whatever I want!
Go ahead.
Producer Tak.
Oh, my.
Hey, Seung-chan.
Jun-mo, you jerk!
You guys...
aren't you curious about Jun-mo's secret?
Hey!
Jun-mo has a woman.
Hey, Seung-chan.
-A woman--
-Goodness, Seung-chan.
-You're way too drunk, Seung-chan.
-A woman...
Did he even do the interview properly?
-I'm a bit uneasy.
-Seung-chan.
Get it together.
Oh, it's Tae-ho.
Kim Tae-ho.
Is he talking about me?
Good old Tae-ho...
He sure is funny when he's drunk.
I have an important announcement to make
in front of you all.
It's that--
Hey.
My goodness.
Producer Tak, this isn't right.
Producer Tak.
You should walk straight.
Stop walking from side to side.
Like this?
Happy?
Yes, that's good.
Now you won't fall.
Jeez, this guy.
It's a shame
we're the only ones seeing this.
Producer Tak.
Seung-chan wants a second round of drinks!
I want live octopus!
Let's go get live octopus!
A second round!
Oh, my goodness.
Jun-mo, is he imitating someone?
Do you remember?
I only heard.
This is my first time seeing it.
This is terrible. Oh, no.
I'm like the living Gandhi.
Gosh, he's coming.
Please do this for me.
What will we do with him? Do something.
Should we take him to a hospital?
Jeez.
What is this?
This is what you always do.
-Me?
-Yes.
Seung-chan wants chicken gizzards.
Chicken gizzards! I want chicken gizzards!
-What should we do?
-Chicken gizzards.
Chicken gizzards!
Hey!
Why, you...
That freak!
You're here too?
-Do you want some water?
-No, I'm fine.
Did you sleep well, Producer Ra?
Did you sleep here too, Producer Tak?
Yes. It was late last night.
Do you remember what you did yesterday?
No.
It's better if you don't.
Don't try to remember.
Oh, really?
Is it better if I don't remember?
Don't try to find out.
Hey, you get over here.
Do you think you still live here or what?
Look who's talking!
Oh, right. You haven't heard.
Cindy's all good now.
CINDY IS CLEARED OF HER FALSE CHARGES
CINDY WANTED TO REVEAL THE TRUTH
CEO POOP KICKED OUT
PROTECT OUR CINDY
VAMPIRE BYUN EXPLOITS HER ARTISTS
Shall I introduce you
to a good cleaning service?
When people thought I was lying,
they wrote on my car a few times,
so I found a good service for that.
They will give you a discount
if you say my name.
Have lunch with me, Cindy.
Here. This is your contract cancelation.
It's proof that I'll leave you alone
until you're done.
I know you won't believe me
if I just tell you.
I can't believe the last thing
I can do for you
is to cancel your contract.
All this time,
I don't know what I've been doing.
Stamp your seal on it.
Cindy.
Before you stamp your seal on something,
make sure you read it first.
Check if there are errors.
Don't just take your seal out.
Got it?
Yes.
Don't think I'm canceling your contract
because I'm afraid
of what people are saying.
I wouldn't just surrender over
something like that.
I know that.
For the last ten years,
you were my joy.
I wanted you to shine alone,
so I eliminated any potential competitors.
If anyone tried to hurt you,
I chased them down
and put them in their place.
Before you turned your back on me,
I really thought of you
as my daughter.
That's the truth.
I know.
You used the wrong methods,
but I know you loved me...
Mom.
I want to be free of you
because I know that.
You, too,
shouldn't be afraid of people leaving you.
There's a limit
to using their weakness
by making them sign an unfair contract.
You can't get people
to stay with you that way.
I know that you won't change easily.
But still...
I wish
you could think about why people leave you
even when you're so devoted to them.
Just once.
Think about it just once.
I...
I don't want to live like you.
That's why I'm leaving.
Okay.
The food will get cold.
Let's eat.
Hello, Chief Kim.
Come on. Do what you did yesterday.
You patted me on the head.
I did?
You even called me by my first name.
I'm going to quit drinking now.
How will you do that?
Someone will always force you to drink.
Just keep asking for forgiveness
when you make mistakes.
I'm sorry.
Yes. Just like that.
Oh, right. Seung-chan.
About that preview you made...
Yes?
It was kind of random but pretty funny.
My daughter said it was insane
and kept laughing.
Even when I was in school,
I never made someone laugh.
Even when I memorized jokes
and tried telling them,
my friends told me it wasn't funny
and that I should stop.
But to know that the preview I made
actually made a stranger laugh
feels exhilarating.
I'm happy.
You're addicted now.
It's like a drug.
You go crazy about entertaining people,
about getting applause and cheers.
That's why I'm so happy that I entertained
even one person
with a 30-second clip.
To think that my own show will gain
recognition in the future is just...
Congratulations.
But...
this is bad for your health.
Which is why I compared it to a drug.
It's bad for my health?
It will suck the life out of you.
Look.
This is a room
filled with that kind of stuff.
Look at the stuffed husky, Brownie.
It used to be a huge hit.
Almost every kid in preschool
had one of those in their house.
But now?
It's just a bag of cotton.
And this unicorn.
It was used in Experience of Life.
When one rode this and rose upward,
they were shone with lights
and there would be smoke.
People clapped at that.
It was great.
But now, it's not even close to being
what a merry-go-round horse is worth.
Because popularity fades.
Eventually.
That's why I don't mistreat the props
whenever I come in here.
It's somehow a little sad.
I never thought about that.
I have a question.
Why aren't you ever
at our meetings or our shoots?
Hey, what are you doing in here?
I'm talking to the floor director.
Who?
Oh...
What?
You shouldn't drink so much.
You're too young to be hallucinating.
Some people lie and say they work here.
They use a fake pass to get in and stuff.
Maybe he could have been one of them?
You're right.
If not, it could be a ghost.
Please don't do that.
You talked with him?
Yes.
-And ate with him?
-Yes.
And went to the park with him?
But...
there's never been
a third person with you.
It was always just the two of you?
-Hey!
-You startled me!
You're going to be successful!
He met the broadcast station ghost!
Goodness.
I'm a very scientific person,
and I've lived my life thinking that
for every effect,
there is a cause.
My seniors all think that I hallucinated
or that I'm malnourished,
or that I'm faking it to go home early.
They even asked me about their futures.
But I definitely didn't see a ghost.
Then what was it?
A fairy?
The broadcast station fairy?
That sounds a lot nicer.
A fairy.
Like Tinkerbell.
KO YANG-MI
You didn't respond to my message.
Aren't you taking this too far
over just one mistake?
You startled me!
Do you have time from now until midnight?
Why?
You should be thanking me right now.
What is it?
The chief director and the CEO
are having dinner.
They were wondering who to bring,
and I strongly recommended you.
-Really?
-Of course.
-You better do a good job today.
-Of course!
As you know, Hong-sun is great
with the protocol.
He's a pro.
The CEO is very strict.
He holds grudges.
He's also in a bad mood these days
because of the budget.
Leave it to Hong-sun.
Okay.
The CEO likes to drink.
I'll pull out all the stops today.
I'll do my best today!
Sir.
Thank you so much for inviting me
to such an honored occasion.
It's nothing.
Sit comfortably. Why are you so stiff?
Producer Kim Hong-sun exercises a lot.
His body is very hard.
Show him, Hong-sun.
This is embarrassing.
Wow, you do exercise a lot.
Muscles like this
come from years of exercise.
I guess things are relaxed
in your department.
People have time to exercise.
Allow me.
This is my turf.
Ta-da!
The taste of North Pole.
It's the Aurora drink!
That's delicious.
Sir, you must take care of your health.
Please remember.
This contains red ginseng extract.
Drink up, sir.
I'm sorry.
I should've turned my phone off.
That's okay.
He's quite a guy.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
Your 30 minutes of destiny.
If you don't get here by then,
it's really over between us.
Come to that spicy rice cake restaurant.
Producer Kim, take a shot.
I...
I think I must be crazy.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's been an hour.
You missed the deadline.
It's a miracle that I got here this fast
all the way from Gangnam.
If you knew what I had to give up to come,
you wouldn't be saying that.
What did you give up?
Don't try to find out.
You'll feel terrible if you do.
Can we get some rice here?
Allow me.
This is my turf.
Here.
I can't believe
I'm using all my skills here.
I already regret it.
I must've lost my mind.
After I came to my senses,
I realized that
I lost the chief director and the CEO.
Yes, I did get Yang-mi,
but it's not like
she's the CEO's daughter.
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message.
The chief director is refusing my calls.
Hello.
-Yes, hello.
-Hello.
It's so nice that the street lamps
come on now.
Oh, yes.
They're supposed to come on
in a certain order.
The lights back there
were supposed to go on first.
But we got a lot of complaints.
-Complaints?
-Yes.
Some guy kept calling
from morning to night, all day long.
And he didn't just call us.
He even made a big fuss
at the district office too.
Is he a resident here?
No, he doesn't even live here.
I don't understand
why he was so persistent.
I see.
So, I asked him what he did for a living.
He said he was a TV producer.
He threatened that
he would show up with cameras
if we didn't get the lights here
turned on first.
Oh, I see.
Seung-chan.
Yes?
Listen up.
I'm your senior,
and you're my junior, right?
Yes.
I don't want things to get awkward
between us
because of what happened.
I feel the same way.
Then why did you do that?
Excuse me?
Listen.
You did something
a producer must never do.
That was the worst thing ever.
Excuse me? What did I do?
Thanks to you, it got resolved.
The lights come on now.
Lights? Where?
It's an amenity for residents,
so filing a complaint is fine.
But why did you tell them
that you're a producer?
Who taught you to do that?
You don't even have that authority,
but you abused it anyway.
-Producer Tak, I have no idea--
-You threatened to show up with a camera?
What were you going to do?
Were you going to take a selfie?
By any chance,
are you talking about the street lamps?
Yes.
Oh, they light up now?
Did someone file a complaint?
Yes.
And that person said he was a producer?
Yes, he did.
It wasn't me.
It wasn't you?
It wasn't.
Then who was it?
You got all aggressive last time.
So, it totally...
I shouldn't have done that.
-What is it with me?
-I don't know.
You know, you sometimes
stare at people in a weird way.
What is it this time?
It's nothing.
I'm going to edit now.
-Be aggressive.
-Okay.
Hey, Seung-chan.
Yes?
I have good news.
What is it?
Our show is still safe.
The viewer ratings went up a bit,
thanks to Cindy
and thanks to your preview.
Thank you.
Make this week's preview too.
I'm not going to touch it at all.
It's all your responsibility.
Got it.
Okay.
Producer Ra.
What?
How did you manage
to be friends with Producer Tak
for so long?
What?
Did I know my show would last that long?
Oh, of course not.
Nobody knows
if a show is going to last a long time.
You just think,
"Maybe I'll give it a shot."
Or, "I'll do my best,
but I'll end it if it doesn't go well."
A lot of shows like that
have become long-running shows.
Nobody thought 30 or 40 years ago,
"This show is going to last a long time."
It's the same for
National Singing Contest.
When I first started,
we visited every county.
Since there are only
around 230 counties in Korea,
I thought the show would end
after two years.
But there are so many places to go now.
It's the same with human relationships.
You just happened
to become friends somehow,
but the friendship lasts a long time.
That happens often.
It's exactly like that.
I had no idea about
how things would unfold
in the short span of time this spring.
On that rainy night,
I realized that
all the things I had learned in school
were useless.
And I thought working here
was a mistake.
I didn't know when the show
would get canceled,
so it always kept me nervous
and on my toes.
This is what I thought every night,
"Let's try it today,
and I'll quit if it doesn't work out.
I'll work tomorrow
and run away if it's not right."
As I got through each day
living in the present,
spring has been passing by
equally for everyone.
Is it funny? Pretty good?
Wasn't that caption good?
Yes.
One person got to rethink
his relationship with someone
he thought would always be there.
And one person gave up many things
to set out on her own.
Some experienced the unlikely miracle
of hate turning into love.
Another is trying every day
to protect something
that has grown more precious over time.
12. UNDERSTANDING LONG-RUNNING SHOWS
DON'T FORGET THE BEGINNING
As the season passed by like that,
I'm trying not to forget the beginning.
My beginning that seems
so long ago already.
I thought I was
the most useless person ever,
just trying to get through one day,
and having fears about
not getting through tomorrow.
I'm trying not to forget that.
You've really grown up, Seung-chan.
And...
there was the connection that formed
without me knowing.
I was happy this spring because of her,
and I'll try not to forget that.
Hello?
Jun-mo, there's a huge mosquito
in my house.
-What?
-Is it because I live near a mountain?
-It's a huge mosquito--
-So what?
You need to catch it for me.
I tried using
the electric swatter you bought me,
but I can't even see it.
Are you kidding me?
So, you want me to come
all the way to Gyeonggi-do
to catch a mosquito?
Hey, I already got bitten twice.
Just let it bite you.
They need to eat to live too.
You're really not going to come?
No. Bye.
This is annoying.
Man...
Just to catch a mosquito,
do I have to go to Gyeonggi-do?
This is nuts.
I told her to stay in Yeouido.
Why did she have to move here?
This is only inconveniencing me!
What are you doing out here?
What do you think about the lights?
They're bright, right?
Yeah. Does look so.
Someone filed a bunch of complaints.
-Really?
-Yes.
He said he was a producer
and threatened to use his power
and barge in with a camera.
Hey! I never said that!
The guy kept asking me what my job was,
so I just answered
and told him I was a producer.
Right.
So it was you.
Yes!
That's right!
You called me all the way here
in the middle of the night
just to ask me that?
You were lying
about the mosquito, weren't you?
Is that really important now?
You...
The lazy, selfish sleepyhead.
You came all the way here at this hour
after I called you.
Why did you come here?
Why did you file complaints like a madman
to get the street lamps turned on?
If you're not going to answer,
I'm going home.
Wait!
Tak Ye-jin.
Listen carefully.
When we were students,
it was tough for me
because you got such good grades.
It was hard because I had to get
in the same university as you.
When you suddenly wanted
to become a TV producer,
that was a huge pain too.
I had to study for that mass media exam.
It was a huge pain, and it was tough,
but I followed you around.
But...
even as I spent half my life
following you around,
I didn't know.
I didn't know that I wasn't following you
out of habit.
I was following you out of love.
I was worried
that if I told you this
and if we started dating,
you would get sick of me
being so lazy and stupid,
which would make you break up with me.
That's why I kept hesitating.
But you never left me.
You always...
stuck by my side.
Thank you.
Producer Baek!
Hi.
Why are you alone?
My manager is on the bus.
There's some traffic.
It's a one-person agency.
We're still a bit inexperienced.
I see.
Good luck, Cindy.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll leave then.
Do you want to play rock, paper, scissors?
Excuse me?
The loser carries the luggage.
But I don't have any luggage.
I'll play scissors.
Don't play, and you lose!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Wow, you sure are competitive.
Fine. I lose.
I'll beat you one day though.
Go ahead.
Wait up!
We've been given three months.
We have to really make it work
by this fall.
A lot of people say we've changed.
Come up with some ideas!
-A producer special.
-Will you be responsible for that?
-It had better not fail!
-Okay.
I won't be so indecisive anymore.
I'm going to be more firm and pushy.
Putting all my chips on the table.
I think out teamwork has grown stronger.
I have a good feeling about this.
What?
Me and Ye-jin?
Oh, we're doing great.
Wait. Let's be serious.
I don't think it's a good idea
to have footage
of this kind of thing.
Nobody knows
what will happen in the future.
I wondered why people
obsess with homeownership,
but now I know since I own an apartment.
I feel like my life has changed.
It's like my quality of life is higher.
Jeez, every morning is such a hassle.
It's like saving a file
under a different name.
I turned a friend into a boyfriend.
Now that I have so much,
I feel a lot more relaxed.
Now, I don't get
all bent out of shape about things.
I just go with the flow.
Excuse me.
Hello.
An order from the chief director?
What kind of nonsense is this?
No way.
I won't allow
a crummy performance like that!
I don't care if it's an order.
I'll talk to you later.
We may be a one-person agency,
but nothing has changed.
A rookie might be nervous
about this situation,
but I'm Cindy.
We parked the car to do an interview.
Why would you leave the engine running?
Gas doesn't grow on trees, you know!
Now that I'm out on my own,
things aren't all that easy.
The toughest thing, of course...
is Baek Seung-chan.
The preview I made is ranked eighth
in the search engines.
I got up to sixth last time.
I made a screen capture.
It's not like I'm trying to get famous,
but so many people like my previews
and call me the Bong Jun-ho
or Park Chan-wook of previews.
They give compliments.
It's a bit excessive,
but I keep it in my heart...
Excuse me?
We're missing receipts?
But I made sure everything was there.
Hey, get it together with these receipts!
And you call yourself a producer?
Just a moment.
Producer Ra.