♪Memory is like reflection in the mirror♪
♪Ephemeral yet lasting in the heart♪
♪I let go of worries and face the road ahead♪
♪The vast land stretches far and wide♪
♪My heart remains strong, spirit unbroken♪
♪May this life remain unscathed,
till we meet again♪
♪With calm laughter, I vanquish evil♪
♪Together, we walk through life hand in hand♪
♪Dust rises♪
♪The melody continues amidst the turmoil♪
♪We stand firm in the wind side by side♪
♪I dream as if all is but a fleeting moment♪
♪Yet life rarely follows our desires♪
♪With the totem of strength,
I endure many trials♪
♪Cross love and hate, life and death♪
♪We fight with heads held high♪
♪Facing the chasm of life♪
♪We stand tall fearlessly♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 26=
Open the door.
You geezer.
Sha, open the door quickly.
Shh.
Be quiet.
I told you I would not
take any patients.
Just go away.
Sha, I am Baili Weisheng.
Baili Weisheng?
Are you getting senile?
Pharmacist Changning
introduced me to you.
We've met before, you forgot?
How many times have I told you?
Human doctors and veterinarians
are very different though they have
similar healthcare science.
Though Changning recommended you,
I have nothing to discuss with you.
Just go away.
Not to discuss.
I need you.
You idle around all day.
It can't be good news.
Go away.
It's really good news.
Great news.
What good news?
Complex disease.
Complex disease?
Human or animals?
If it's an animal, why would I need you?
I can keep it to myself.
It's a human being.
A human being?
Tell me about it.
A complex disease
that only allows living up to 30 years.
Only live up to 30 years?
Let's go to take a look.
Look,
I said it's a human being.
Pick him up, and follow me.
- Let's go.
- Don't touch me.
- Put me down.
This way.
- You haven't paid yet.
- Later.
Wait for me to come back.
Sha, are you hiding someone
in your house?
Where did you bring us?
- Here?
- Here.
Are you sure?
Fine.
Don't run around.
Where are you going?
Take his pulse first.
I'm busy.
Such a geezer.
Don't mind the place being shabby.
It's good enough that he let us in.
Though he's a geezer,
his medical skills
are very advanced.
I'm the best veterinarian,
and he's the best doctor.
On Longyuan Continent,
we are equally famous.
Look at this wall.
It's full of prescriptions
for complex diseases.
I've never seen them before.
Your illness is a minor issue.
It can be cured quickly.
Don't worry.
Cheer up. I'll get you something to eat.
Wait for me.
Your Highness.
That's great.
It's finally cleaned up.
A special membrane covered the face.
Although it was corroded by poisons,
it did not damage the underlying skin.
But is there a good way to cover it?
(Sha)
Ziqing,
I didn't expect
to see you again.
How have you been?
That person
didn't take good care of you,
did he?
He made you suffer so much again.
Ziqing,
before I die,
I can see you one more time.
I feel content now.
But why?
Why
am I a person who is about to die?
I really
want to
be by your side
and accompany you forever.
Who are you?
Gu Xi,
he is Xuanyuan Lige,
the Crown Prince of Dongling.
He saved Fourth Princess.
No matter who he is,
trespassing here is a capital offense.
I just want to check
how she is doing.
Why did you come out?
Sha Qiuzi,
what's going on?
Didn't you say
that we're your only patients here?
Get out.
This is my clinic.
It's not your place to speak.
Didn't I tell you not to run around?
You really caused me trouble.
If Fourth Prince blames me,
how can I bear the responsibility?
Doctor Sha,
can you tell me
how she is now?
You two know each other?
We're old acquaintances.
But you still can't...
She's fine.
She'll wake up soon.
What about the mark on her face?
Is there a way to cover it?
I'm also worried about that.
Unless I can find suitable human skin.
If I want to cover it flawlessly,
I can only take skin
from a living person.
Taking skin from a living person
is not easy.
Doctor Sha,
use mine.
You?
Use the skin from my body.
Is that feasible?
No, no.
Taking skin from a living person
is excruciatingly painful.
You are already seriously ill.
How can you endure it?
Anyway, I'm a dying person.
If I can be of some use before I die,
wouldn't that be a worthy death?
No, no.
I can't do something
that trades one life for another.
Doctor Sha,
if you don't agree,
I'll die here in your clinic today.
Losing a valuable case is nothing,
but if people find out
that the Prince of Dongling
died in your clinic,
can you bear the consequences?
Fine.
I agree.
Xuanyuan Lige,
you are terminally ill now.
If you hurt yourself like this,
you'll die.
That's my business.
If Ziqing knew you were doing this,
she would never agree.
That's also my business.
You...
Baili Weisheng,
we are just ordinary friends.
You don't need to feel sorry for me.
I don't have much time left.
This is my last wish.
Baili Weisheng,
Doctor Sha,
I have one more request.
Go ahead.
My body is beyond cure.
Staying here
is unnecessary.
After I'm gone,
don't tell Ziqing this.
I don't want her to know
and feel guilty towards me.
Alright, I promise you.
There's one more thing.
Chu Feiyan took my Xuezheng.
If there's a chance,
please help me get it back.
Aren't we just ordinary friends?
If we can't meet again in the future,
please give it to Ziqing, okay?
Alright, I promise you.
I will help you get it back.
Thank you.
Doctor Sha,
let's begin.
Alright.
Have a drink?
No need.
Have they searched all the places?
The Crown Prince secretly
sent out hundreds of people
to search around the city.
But we haven't found any trace
of the Fourth Princess of Tianque.
That's strange.
Where could Jun Beiyue have hidden her?
Did they get any information
from Nangong Qianqian?
Princess Qianqian
seems to know nothing about it.
She only wants to see Situ Haonan.
She's about to marry into Xiling,
yet she's still thinking about
another man.
Such a woman is not fit
to be the Princess Consort of Xiling.
Keep a close eye on her.
Report any news to me immediately.
Yes.
Your Highness,
you guessed right.
Chu Feiyan has been keeping an eye
on Princess Qianqian.
Every word and action of hers
is reported to Chu Feiyan.
Good.
Then let them hear this news.
Yes.
Haonan,
everything is arranged.
Arranged?
Arranged what?
Arranged for you
to help Qianqian regain her freedom.
What are you hesitating for?
If you miss this chance,
you will regret it
for the rest of your life.
Take her away.
Really?
Does he really want to meet me?
Mr. Situ asked you
to keep it quiet
and be careful.
Also, tomorrow at noon,
I will take you to the agreed location
to meet Mr. Situ.
Alright, don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Then I will take my leave.
I heard it with my own ears.
When Nangong Qianqian heard
that Situ Haonan
privately invited her to meet,
she immediately agreed.
Situ Haonan
should know where Han Ziqing is.
Why not go and listen to
what they will say?
As you command.
You may leave.
Yes.
(Linze Gate)
Everyone, please look.
This is Mingsha Mountain.
It is the holy land of Xiling,
and also our pride.
Everyone, listen carefully.
This is the sound of singing sand.
It sings once a year,
and the sound is loudest
on the Jiazi day of the month of Jiazi.
Distinguished envoys,
our country's Sand Worship Ritual
will be held in three days.
Please return to your residence first
to take a short rest.
When it's auspicious time,
please join us in the ritual.
Everyone,
please feel free.
The sound of the singing sand
of Mingsha Mountain is the loudest
on the Jiazi day of the month of Jiazi.
It will appear this year.
The Sand Worship Ritual is held
at this time,
which is quite a coincidence.
How is everything?
Your Highness, everything is ready.
Go ahead.
I am a bit worried about Ziqing.
You should return to the clinic
immediately
and check the situation.
But Your Highness, what about here?
I have my plan.
Mr. Situ,
this is the entrance to Sand Cave.
Princess Qianqian
has been waiting inside for a long time.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you are awake.
Her Highness is awake.
Fourth Princess, you are awake.
That's great.
Are you feeling better?
Where am I?
This is my clinic.
Who are you?
I am a doctor.
Thank god,
you're awake.
I've lived up
to Fourth Prince's expectation.
Where is Jun Beiyue?
His Highness is in Xiling
to attend Sand Worship Ritual.
He instructed us
to take good care of you.
If he knew you were awake,
he would be very happy.
Ziqing, do you remember what happened
before you fell unconscious?
Your Highness, look.
What is going on here?
I have made a human skin mask for you
to completely cover the original mark.
Others won't be able to see it at all.
Fourth Princess, please rest assured.
Whose skin is it?
An old acquaintance of yours.
Someone who was willing to die for you.
Who is it?
Tell me quickly.
Someone who wouldn't live
past 30 years old.
Your Highness.
Stop searching for him, Ziqing.
Don't pull me.
Stop searching for him.
He is already gone.
He said he wouldn't live long anyway.
He just wanted to do something
for you one last time.
He was also the one who saved you
on the ship in Dongling.
I was just wandering around
and heard something happened
in the East Sea.
I happened to save him.
(I heard you were captured by Chu Feiyan,)
(so I wanted to rescue you.)
(But I ended up saving him instead.)
Your Highness,
you're better now.
Where is Fourth Prince?
Why did you come back alone?
His Highness
went to capture Chu Feiyan himself
to retrieve what was snatched.
What did you say?
Qianqian.
I'm here.
Right here.
Why are you there?
Why did Beiyue choose such a place?
Don't you have anything to say to me?
What do you want me to say?
Don't you know what I want to hear?
Don't you know
what's on my mind?
Situ Haonan,
I regret knowing you.
Chu Tiange treats me well too.
I will have many children with him.
I will be very happy.
I also wish you happiness.
Qianqian,
I don't want you to marry Chu Tiange.
I don't want to marry Chu Tiange either.
You adulterous couple,
since you like being together so much,
then stay in there forever.
What's going on?
Open the door.
Who is it? Open the door.
- Open the door.
- Is anyone there?
Is anyone there?
- Open the door.
Open the door!
Chu Feiyan,
you finally appeared.
Jun Beiyue.
Open the door.
It seems like Beiyue's voice.
Beiyue, we are here.
- Beiyue!
- Fourth Prince!
What if I don't?
You're still so stubborn
at the brink of death.
Then today, let's settle
both new and old scores.
What scores
do I have with you?
You don't know what scores we have?
Under your arrangement,
Situ Haonan had a secret meeting
with Nangong Qianqian.
Princess Qianqian is supposed
to marry into Xiling.
If this matter gets out...
At this point,
do you think
you can still leave here alive?
This is Xiling.
If something happens to me in Xiling,
my father
will not let it go.
Are you threatening me?
Take her down.
Kill me
if you have the guts.
Do you think I will let you die
so easily?
Fine.
Since you won't let me go,
let's perish together.
Why did it suddenly collapse?
Let's get out first.
Oh no, what about Fourth Prince?
Didn't see him inside.
Quick, call someone to help search.
Go.
Catch them.
- Catch them.
- Oh no.
- Don't let them escape.
- Someone's coming.
If they discovered
I was meeting with you in private...
Don't be afraid. We can elope together
- to wander the world.
- I can't.
This will implicate you all.
Father will hunt us down.
I can't betray Tieyan.
Silly girl,
do you think
that by marrying into Xiling,
Tieyan will no longer have any wars?
Once the western defense line
is established,
your father will definitely
plan an eastern expedition.
You are just a pawn to them.
Go with me. I will never abandon you.
Go.
Be careful.
That way.
Catch them.
Qianqian, come on. Get up quickly.
Hurry, hurry.
Chase them.
Quickly.
Ziqing?
Chu Tiange,
hello again.
Han Ziqing.
What are you doing here?
Surprised, aren't you?
Release them immediately.
What if I don't?
Han Ziqing,
you dare to blow up
the walls of Xiling's border?
Does Tianque want to declare war
on Xiling?
So what if we declare war?
Do you dare to accept the challenge?
You are
simply too much.
What exactly do you want?
What do I want?
You and Chu Feiyan kidnapped me.
What did you intend to do?
- Shadow.
- Here.
Take them away.
Yes.
- Capture them for me.
- Go.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Go.
You...
Stop.
If you don't want your walls
to be blown to pieces,
ask Chu Feiyan to see me.
If you want to find her, go to Nanzhao.
Why come to me?
I know
she is in Xiling now.
If you refuse to admit it,
I will find her on my own.
What is this place?
The ancestors of Xiling
built this secret chamber
to imprison rebels.
I knew before I activated the mechanism
that we wouldn't be able to get out.
Do you see those bones?
It has only one passageway here.
It's the way of coming in
but not getting out.
Your Highness,
this is the place Mr. Situ mentioned.
Master, I have arranged for them
to set off the firebombs
to delay Chu Tiange.
I can't open it.
Explode it.
Come on.
Everyone else, retreat.
Do you think I'll spare you?
You're blown out.
Where is Jun Beiyue?
Why are you here?
Your face.
Your face...
Surprised?
Han Ziqing,
you are an Islander.
If you have the guts, don't rely on men.
Fight me one-on-one.
You're in such a state
and still want to duel?
Where is Jun Beiyue?
You should be torn to pieces.
I will kill you.
I will kill you!
Beiyue,
are you alright?
I'm glad to see you're fine.
She is
from the Isolated Island.
The totem on her face...
Why is your totem gone?
What totem?
What are you talking about?
I saw it with my own eyes.
I saw a big and ugly totem
on your face.
I saw it with my own eyes.
When did you see it?
That day
when I kidnapped you.
Shut up.
Chu Feiyan,
haven't you caused enough trouble?
Just now, Chu Feiyan admitted
she had kidnapped Ziqing.
Prince Xiang,
how should we
settle this?
Fourth Prince,
Fourth Princess just blew up
the walls of Xiling.
I think it can be even.
Even?
Do you think I don't know
why you kidnapped Fourth Princess?
That's right.
We did kidnap her and intended
to use her to blackmail you.
But so what?
It seems
you don't have any leverage
to negotiate with us.
After all, we hold a huge secret
about Han Ziqing's identity.
So, Prince Xiang, tell us,
what secret do you know?
♪Memories drift afar♪
♪Gather into love, opening our hearts♪
♪Like the sweet scent of flowers♪
♪It heals old scars♪
♪May we brave through life's trials together♪
♪Time flows peacefully like a stream♪
♪Into the sea it merges, where desolation goes♪
♪Washed by time's endless cycle♪
♪Old sorrows fade away♪
♪May time reach through longing♪
♪To where you are♪
♪No matter how long, I'll never forget♪
♪Crossing the night sky,
with the moon so bright♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪Through time♪
♪And beyond♪