♪Memory is like reflection in the mirror♪
♪Ephemeral yet lasting in the heart♪
♪I let go of worries and face the road ahead♪
♪The vast land stretches far and wide♪
♪My heart remains strong, spirit unbroken♪
♪May this life remain unscathed,
till we meet again♪
♪With calm laughter, I vanquish evil♪
♪Together, we walk through life hand in hand♪
♪Dust rises♪
♪The melody continues amidst the turmoil♪
♪We stand firm in the wind side by side♪
♪I dream as if all is but a fleeting moment♪
♪Yet life rarely follows our desires♪
♪With the totem of strength,
I endure many trials♪
♪Cross love and hate, life and death♪
♪We fight with heads held high♪
♪Facing the chasm of life♪
♪We stand tall fearlessly♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 37=
(Sheng Manor)
Your Highness,
two urgent military reports.
What's going on?
There is a civil strife in Tieyan.
The Eighth Prince has rebelled.
The Eighth Prince has rebelled?
How could this be possible?
After Qianqian and Haonan got married,
they have been
in charge of Tieyan's affairs.
How could the Eighth Prince
have any opportunity?
Now Tieyan is also at war with Xiling.
This can't be a coincidence.
It must be premeditated.
Will Qianqian and Haonan be in danger?
We have to go back
to Tianque immediately.
- Then we can make further plans.
- Alright.
Xiaosheng,
you must listen to your mother,
and focus on your recuperation.
You must come back to see me.
Don't worry.
Do I have to promise you
for you to believe me?
Yes.
I told you I would come back.
Xiaosheng, you should
focus on your recuperation first.
Once we finish our business,
Weisheng will come back to see you.
You must not deceive me.
When have I ever deceived you?
Chief,
we have to leave first.
Your Highness, be careful.
- Alright.
- Take care.
- You too.
Be careful.
- Please.
- Let's go.
Bye.
Your Highness.
(Xiling Army Encampment)
Your Highness, bad news.
The Tieyan army is counterattacking.
Our army is struggling to resist.
We have now retreated
from Tieyan's border.
You are useless.
Tieyan is dealing with its civil strife.
How could they possibly have the chance
to counterattack our forces?
Your Highness,
it is the Snow Region.
Snow Region?
Tieyan's attacking is extremely fierce.
When our troops retreated,
they were intercepted by Snow Region,
resulting in heavy casualties.
Could it be...
Your Highness,
the Tieyan army has already
reached the encampment.
What about our defensive line?
It didn't hold.
Tieyan is attacking at the front.
Snow Region is flanking from the rear.
They have already entered the city.
You are so useless.
(Xiling)
How
did you get in here?
Your people let us in.
Our army is fighting against Tieyan.
What does it have to do
with your Snow Region?
You were bullying the weak.
Our tribe can't stand by to watch it,
so we lend a helping hand.
What?
Can't we?
Chu Tiange,
if you know what's good for you,
you should end your life
to atone for your sins,
so as not to sully tour sharp blades.
Except for Chu Tiange,
our army accepts the surrender
of all Xiling soldiers.
I will count to three.
If anyone does not surrender,
they will be treated the same
as Chu Tiange
and face the same punishment.
Well...
Let's go.
Go.
- Hurry up.
- Go.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Look at you all.
I have treated you well.
Is this how you treat me now?
You have always been
arrogant and conceited.
You have never shown us any respect.
It serves you right
with such a situation.
What are you talking about?
If you're smart enough,
you'd better take your own life.
At least it would leave us a way out.
Yes. Your Highness,
you should take your own life.
- Yes.
- Please take your own life.
That's right.
You should just take your own life.
You should end it yourself.
Your Highness,
if you don't die,
we will have to die.
Sorry about that.
Good.
Good!
(Linze Gate)
Xuanyuan Lige,
today
even if Xiling perishes with this city,
I will never let you set foot in Xiling.
Ms. Qin,
do you want to go in and take a look?
Just like you, Your Highness,
I've been dreaming of going back
to our old capital.
Your Highness,
we're not going in,
but going home.
Alright.
Let's go home.
Archers, get ready.
(Linze Gate)
Release the arrows.
(I finally did it.)
Beiyue, you are finally back.
Something happened in Tieyan.
I have already heard about it.
Madam, this way, please.
Is there any detailed information?
The battle of Tieyan and Xiling
is indeed peculiar.
Snow Region, the small tribal nation,
has intervened in it unexpectedly
and defeated the Xiling army.
More strangely, Dongling
has occupied the Xiling Royal City.
I find this truly unbelievable.
Our army was stationed
in the Sanjie Region,
but they didn't notice any news.
Which route were they taking
to directly get to the Xiling Royal City?
Wherever they took the path from,
we would have noticed it,
unless they have wings
to fly over Wuxie Gorge.
Wuxie Gorge?
That was the only passable place.
This is impossible.
We have been to Wuxie Gorge.
It is extremely difficult
for one person to pass through it,
let alone an army of thousands.
No matter how he managed
to get through,
but now
they have occupied Xiling,
which poses a threat to our Tianque.
We need to come up with a plan.
Uncle, don't panic.
I will gather the generals immediately
to discuss this matter.
I will go with you.
Alright.
Ziqing,
you've had a long journey.
Relax yourself
and have a good rest.
But I'm still worried about them.
Why didn't we get any news
about Tieyan's battle?
Don't worry.
As soon as I have news about them,
I will inform you immediately.
Don't worry.
Uncle,
let's go.
Your Highness,
Princess Qianqian has arrived.
Let's go.
Qianqian.
Ziqing.
Qianqian, what's wrong with you?
What happened?
Haonan…
Haonan has died.
What happened?
Haonan.
- Qianqian.
- Haonan.
You horrid woman.
Chu Tiange, what do you want?
You never expected that one day
you would become my prisoners,
did you?
Princess Qianqian,
look at your husband,
the supreme commander of Tieyan.
Now
he is so imposing.
- Bah.
- Chu Tiange.
If you have the guts, let me go
and let's have a duel.
You're
still showing off, huh?
Let me ask you.
When you forced me
to break off the engagement,
have you ever thought about today?
Chu Tiange,
you don't dare to compete with us
on the battlefield,
yet you resort to
such insidious tactics.
You are simply despicable and shameless.
Princess Qianqian.
Chu Tiange, what are you doing?
Don't touch her!
Chu Tiange!
You horrid woman.
Chu Tiange, you...
Do you think you're so great?
I'm telling you,
I will not let you die.
I will make you watch
how your loved one dies.
What are you going to do?
No!
No.
Mr. Lige,
you should show yourself.
Xuanyuan Lige, you...
You are all in this together.
That's right.
This civil strife in Tieyan
is the handiwork of Mr. Lige.
This battle
is also the result of the cooperation
between Dongling and Xiling.
Xuanyuan Lige,
we are friends, aren't we?
I have
never had friends.
Fine.
We mistook you, you scoundrel.
Kill me or torture me,
as you wish.
Look at him.
Of course, I will kill you.
And this horrid woman will know
what a consequence it is
after she brought disgrace upon me.
No.
Mr. Lige,
how about
you do it?
So that I can believe
your sincerity in cooperating with me.
Xuanyuan Lige.
Xuanyuan Lige,
even if you don't take us friends,
what about Ziqing?
If you kill Haonan,
how will you face Ziqing in the future?
If Haonan dies,
Ziqing will be very sad.
Will she be sad?
If she is sad,
Jun Beiyue will be there to comfort her.
Well said.
There are only interests among countries,
but not friends.
Just like that Mr. Xuanyuan and I
were sworn enemies,
but with Jun Beiyue as our common enemy,
we can still cooperate.
Rest assured.
This time you have helped me
attack Tieyan.
I guarantee not to advance eastward
for the next five years.
Dongling and Xiling
will be in eternal peace.
Dongling is weak in national strength.
I hope you can show mercy.
Please go ahead.
Xuanyuan Lige,
I'm begging you. No.
- Qianqian, don't beg him.
- Come on.
Watch him!
No, Xuanyuan Lige!
No!
Please!
Isn't it just a life?
- Take it.
- No!
Haonan.
Good job.
Why did he kill Haonan?
How could he be so heartless?
Because he wanted
to gain Chu Tiange's trust
to delay Xiling's withdrawal
and increase Tieyan's hatred
to gain more time for attacking Xiling.
This person is truly insidious.
Qianqian, tell me,
how did you manage to escape?
Xuanyuan Lige asked Chu Tiange
to release me.
He told Chu Tiange,
if he truly wanted revenge,
he should make me live
to feel the pain
of losing a loved one in every second.
Ziqing,
Xuanyuan Lige is a monster.
Calm down first.
What happened next?
Then I fainted.
When I woke up,
I have already been sent back
to the Tieyan border.
In the Royal City, the Eighth Prince
has ascended the throne.
Father has been imprisoned.
But why would Snow Region help you?
I don't know.
But later I heard
Xuanyuan Lige
has occupied the Xiling Royal City.
All of this must be his plan.
Qianqian,
don't be sad.
When we find out the truth,
I will avenge Haonan.
No, I don't believe it.
Xuanyuan Lige
is not that kind of person.
- I don't believe it.
- You shut up.
I saw this with my own eyes.
Xuanyuan Lige, why did you do this?
Why?
I have to ask you in person.
Stop! Who are you?
I am friends with your master.
It's alright.
How did you get in?
It's not your fault
that the guards here are lax.
After all, you just occupied the city.
It must be hectic.
It's not your fault
that the guards are lax.
Why are you staring at me?
After all, we are friends.
It's fine if you don't
offer me a cup of tea.
Why are you staring at me?
What do you want to do?
Make a deal with you.
Give you this Xuezheng.
Tell me the truth.
Was it really you who killed Haonan?
Why?
Didn't I ask you to give it to Ziqing?
She asked me to bring it back to you.
Well...
Ziqing told me to ask you.
About what?
Were you the instigator of the battle
between Tieyan and Xiling?
Yes.
What about Situ Haonan?
I did all this.
What else do you want to know?
Have you ever thought about...
I haven't thought about anyone.
I only consider myself
and the restoration of Dongling.
Xuanyuan Lige,
Jun Beiyue
won't let it go easily
and will deploy troops against you.
I have always
been waiting for his troops.
Xuanyuan Lige,
is the restoration of Dongling
that important?
Is it even more important
than lives and friendship?
Do you know that I am worried about you?
I'm sorry.
Please go back and tell Jun Beiyue.
I am waiting for him here.
Xiaomeng,
send Mr. Baili out.
Yes.
Sir, please.
Take the guqin away.
Ziqing would never want it.
I'll go by myself.
When did he become like this?
Was he bewitched?
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
Han Ziqing and others
request an audience.
She said if you refuse to meet,
they'll blow the city gate open.
Finally, they came.
Let them in.
Yes.
Xuanyuan Lige, I will kill you.
Ziqing, help me kill him.
Lige,
is there some misunderstanding
about Haonan's matter?
As long as you say it,
I will believe you.
Do you have any difficulty?
We can solve it together.
Why did you kill Haonan?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Why are you still listening to
his explanations?
I never regret
to what I have done.
I only regret that it was done too late.
My great cause of national restoration
has been delayed for too long.
Now I have finally completed it.
Shouldn't you congratulate me?
How would you become like this?
I have always been like this.
You...
I will ask you one last time.
You killed Haonan.
Is there another hidden truth?
Have you found
all the music scores of Lishang?
It's none of your business.
♪The emptiness left in me♪
♪Light and shadow intertwine,
no time to escape♪
Nothing is hidden.
Tell me the truth!
I am the one who killed him.
Well said!
I've been waiting for you to say that.
Han Ziqing,
I taught you the Sound Strike.
Is this how you repay me?
I won't stop you
from restoring your country.
But you hurt my friend.
So don't blame me.
It's a Barrier.
Qianqian.
Who is it?
Come out.
Mother.
Beiyue, my son.
It's been a long time.
Aren't you supposed
to be on Dream Island?
How did you end up here?
You have teamed up with the outsiders
to bully your mother.
How can you still ask me what I'm doing?
What are you trying to do?
You bratty girl!
You will soon find out
what the consequence
of taking my son away from me
and making him go against me will be.
Let him go.
What are you going to do?
Put Xuanyuan Lige down.
Stop arguing, all of you.
A Barrier has already been set up here.
We need to wait a little longer.
What are you going to do?
How did your mother escape?
Would Grandfather be in trouble?
Let's go.
We'll figure out a way later.
Ziqing,
I still need to make a trip
to Dream Island.
I'm so worrying about Grandfather.
Don't worry. Go ahead.
I will be in Tianque.
I will also send someone
to look for Lige.
Shadow, let's go.
Yes.
Your Highness, all have been arranged.
Good.
Everyone, look.
If we go from here
and come over here...
(Meng Mansion)
Why would you pass away suddenly,
Father?
Brother.
Beiyue,
you're here.
Your grandfather passed away suddenly.
What happened?
He
liked to take a walk
in the back mountain after dinner.
The doctor has checked on him.
It was a sudden heart attack,
so he fell off a cliff.
Yes, indeed.
My grandfather has always
been in good health.
How could he suddenly
have a heart attack?
Beiyue,
your grandfather was getting old.
It's all our fault
for not taking good care of him.
We didn't notice his illness.
That's why such an incident
happened today.
It's our fault.
He died suddenly
and didn't leave a single word behind.
Yes.
Can I see my grandfather one last time?
Alright.
No way.
Brother.
Beiyue,
you are close to your grandfather.
There is nothing wrong
that you want to see him one last time.
However,
our Meng Tribe has its own rules.
Now that he has been laid to rest,
if the coffin is opened again,
it will be extremely inauspicious.
Yes.
That's inauspicious.
Grandfather,
I arrived late
and couldn't see you for the last time.
It's my fault.
Father.
Oh Father.
Beiyue has come to see you.
You can rest in peace.
Father.
Shadow,
we'll stay
to handle
Grandfather's funeral arrangements.
Yes.
(In Memoriam)
Father.
May you rest in peace.
(In Memoriam)
Who is it?
Brother.
Who?
- Shadow.
- Beiyue.
Beiyue, what are you doing?
Let me ask you two.
How did my grandfather die?
Beiyue, didn't my brother tell you?
He had a sudden heart attack.
- Yes, right.
- And he fell off the cliff.
Yeah.
Heart attack?
Then why did the person
who fell off the cliff
not have a single scratch,
but a bite mark from a poisonous insect
on the neck?
Well...
I don't know.
Yes. We don't know.
Speak the truth!
We don't know.
Speak!
I don't know, Beiyue.
Beiyue.
I'll speak.
Brother, speak quickly.
It's
the Minister.
He wanted to go to Momentary Tower.
He forced us
to take him to see the Chief.
Are you referring to
the Minister of Nanzhao?
- Yes.
- Yes, it's him.
It's the Minister of Nanzhao.
What is his purpose
of going to Momentary Tower?
He said he was looking for
some kind of magical artifact
and its instructions.
Yes, yes.
- We didn't dare to resist him.
- We didn't dare.
We just watched as he killed Father.
You two monsters.
Considering you are the descendants
of Meng Tribe,
I will grant you a swift end.
- Beiyue.
Fourth Prince.
We are a family, Beiyue.
You can't do this.
♪Memories drift afar♪
♪Gather into love, opening our hearts♪
♪Like the sweet scent of flowers♪
♪It heals old scars♪
♪May we brave through life's trials together♪
♪Time flows peacefully like a stream♪
♪Into the sea it merges, where desolation goes♪
♪Washed by time's endless cycle♪
♪Old sorrows fade away♪
♪May time reach through longing♪
♪To where you are♪
♪No matter how long, I'll never forget♪
♪Crossing the night sky,
with the moon so bright♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪Through time♪
♪And beyond♪