♪Memory is like reflection in the mirror♪
♪Ephemeral yet lasting in the heart♪
♪I let go of worries and face the road ahead♪
♪The vast land stretches far and wide♪
♪My heart remains strong, spirit unbroken♪
♪May this life remain unscathed,
till we meet again♪
♪With calm laughter, I vanquish evil♪
♪Together, we walk through life hand in hand♪
♪Dust rises♪
♪The melody continues amidst the turmoil♪
♪We stand firm in the wind side by side♪
♪I dream as if all is but a fleeting moment♪
♪Yet life rarely follows our desires♪
♪With the totem of strength,
I endure many trials♪
♪Cross love and hate, life and death♪
♪We fight with heads held high♪
♪Facing the chasm of life♪
♪We stand tall fearlessly♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 25=
Why isn't Prince Xiang coming with us?
He has returned to Xiling
to wait for us.
When will our ship arrive?
Don't worry. It's coming.
If you need to pass through
Yaoshun Island,
you must get Dongling's approval.
We have to go to Dongling Royal City
to get my mother's consent first.
Crown Prince Xuanyuan,
are you planning to
make a move against me in Dongling
and use the opportunity
to rescue Han Ziqing?
Without Dongling's approval,
you cannot pass through Yaoshun Island.
But I'm here.
I can represent Dongling.
You're doing this behind Mother's back
and betraying Dongling.
You will face retribution.
Don't worry.
Regarding borrowing the route
to Consort Yun,
I have already obtained Mother's decree.
I am acting under the decree.
Brother,
you don't need to worry about it.
Brother, it seems your illness
has come back,
you should return to Dongling
for treatment.
Don't stare at me like that.
I'm doing this for your good.
I'm also doing this
so you can get the antidote.
That's why I'm working for them.
You two, stop arguing.
Both of you will be credited
once the task is done.
As for who gets the credit,
that's not my concern.
Consort Yun, the ship has arrived.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, this way.
Under the nose
of the Tianque Royal Family,
someone has built
such a massive secret chamber.
Clear.
Beiyue, look.
Yaoshun Island.
Could it be that they plan
to take the water route?
Let's go
to check the dock.
Yes.
(Xuanyuan)
As an Islander,
you don't deserve to live in this world.
You took away Jun Beiyue
and ruined my life.
Han Ziqing,
this is the price you should pay.
Enjoy it well.
Princess Zhaoxi,
be careful of your brother.
He has deep feelings
for Han Ziqing.
As long as I'm here,
he won't have a say
in Han Ziqing's case.
If you want to clear obstacles,
you must be decisive.
Don't let him cause trouble.
What did she tell you?
Consort Yun said
you have deep feelings for Han Ziqing
and told me to be wary of you.
What are you doing?
From now on,
we will increase the dose of poisons
for Han Ziqing
to torture her
and make her life worse than death.
No.
Your Highness,
they are setting sail.
Trying to escape?
Blow up the bottom of the ship.
Don't let anyone escape.
No.
Zhaoxi,
Chu Feiyan is deceiving you.
She just wants to use Tianque's soldiers
to attack Dongling.
Don't be fooled by her.
You should think
about how to save yourself first.
Do you think if something happens to me,
Mother will spare you?
I won't let you die so easily.
Mother is right.
Your value
is to pave the way for me
to become the queen.
At least I have some value.
But you
are worthless.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, there's a situation.
What situation?
A lot of men in black
suddenly appeared on the sea
and started fighting with our people.
They are ruthless.
Could it be Jun Beiyue?
Quick, set sail.
Release the falcons
and send out the message
that the Fourth Prince of Tianque
is attacking Dongling's ship.
- Yes.
- Stop.
Xuanyuan Zhaoxi, stop.
You are no match for Jun Beiyue.
The only solution now
is to release Han Ziqing
and tell him about Chu Feiyan
and Chu Tiange.
There is no other way!
The only solution now
is for both of you to die together.
Xuanyuan Zhaoxi!
Quickly notify Consort Yun.
Ziqing.
Ziqing, don't be afraid.
Go.
Leave me and go.
Don't be afraid.
I won't go.
♪A fleeting dream, afraid to wake up♪
♪Yet it's a love I never imagined♪
Row faster.
♪Time flows downstream without stopping♪
♪The story lingers and turns♪
♪Turning into a segment of longing♪
♪Your love falls like the night♪
♪The moon and sparse stars illuminate♪
♪The emptiness left in me♪
♪Light and shadow intertwine,
no time to escape♪
Hurry up and go.
Don't be afraid.
Leave me and go.
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still looking from afar♪
♪For love, why fear walking alone♪
♪Willing to abandon the vast world♪
♪The return journey is desolate♪
♪Just to have you by my side♪
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still hanging on and worrying♪
♪Not wanting regret to stay with me♪
♪Why not love recklessly♪
♪After countless twists and turns♪
♪You are by my side♪
Hurry up and go.
Leave me.
I won't leave you.
Ziqing, I won't leave you behind.
- Hurry, go.
- Ziqing.
Go.
I won't leave you alone.
Open the door.
Open the door!
Help!
Is anyone there?
Open the door!
Someone, help!
♪For love, why fear walking alone♪
♪I'd abandon the world's chaos♪
♪And barren path♪
♪Just to have you by my side♪
♪Still can't forget♪
Have you found Fourth Princess?
No.
- No.
Your Highness, we haven't found her.
The lower deck is flooded.
We can't go down.
- The ship is sinking.
- Let go of me.
♪After all the twists and turns♪
♪You're still here♪
Where is she?
She's dead.
I'm telling you,
if she is dead,
I will cut you into pieces.
- Lock her up.
- Yes.
- Let go of me.
- Move.
I am the Princess of Dongling.
♪Still looking from afar♪
♪For love, why fear walking alone♪
Someone, help!
♪And barren path♪
♪Just to have you by my side♪
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still looking from afar♪
♪For love, why fear walking alone♪
Help!
♪And barren path♪
♪Just to have you by my side♪
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still hanging on♪
Ziqing.
♪After all the twists and turns,
you're still here♪
Ziqing.
Ziqing!
- Ziqing.
- Come on.
Xuanyuan Lige is still down there.
Hurry and save him.
The boat is sinking.
You all go quickly. I'll save him.
Lige!
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still looking from afar♪
♪For love, why fear walking alone♪
Shadow, send someone to stay
and assist them.
Yes.
♪Just to have you by my side♪
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still hanging on♪
♪Not wanting regret to stay with me♪
♪Why not love recklessly♪
♪After all the twists and turns♪
♪You're still here♪
Mother,
why will I die?
The crown princes of Dongling
never live past 30.
You must remember your mission
is to assist Zhaoxi
in reviving Dongling.
I can never return
to Dongling again.
Don't speak.
It will hurt your spirit.
You did a terrible job.
Don't you feel ashamed to come back?
I didn't expect Jun Beiyue
to catch up so quickly.
Luckily, I escaped in time
and didn't face him directly.
Do you think that's the end of it?
Xuanyuan Zhaoxi will expose you.
By then, you will have to
be held responsible for that.
I won't admit it.
What can he do to me?
Forget it.
After all, Jun Beiyue doesn't have
any substantial evidence.
The Sand Worship Ritual
is coming in ten days.
If he dares to provoke us then,
I will have something to say to him.
What do you plan to do?
Han Ziqing has been confirmed
to be an Islander.
If Jun Beiyue remains stubborn
and dares to provoke us,
you should write to the King of Nanzhao
and unite with other countries
to declare war on Tianque.
Declare war on Tianque?
What?
Are you reluctant?
Let me tell you.
You kidnapped Han Ziqing.
Are you still dreaming that Jun Beiyue
will fall in love with you?
You must abandon all your fantasies
about him now
and defend yourself from his revenge.
Also,
if the King of Nanzhao
finds out about this,
you won't have a good time either.
You must actively show your loyalty
to the King of Nanzhao now,
so that when we need it,
we can leverage Nanzhao's power
to achieve our goals.
If I had known
things would turn out this way,
I wouldn't have gotten involved
in this mess.
Shouldn't you take the blame?
It was a flawless plan,
but you messed it up.
You are more of a hindrance than a help.
Open the door.
No clinical services at midnight.
Get lost.
Sha!
Fourth Prince, what brings you here?
Quick, save her.
This way.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I will do my best
to treat Fourth Princess' injuries.
It's not just her body.
Is there a way
to treat her face as well?
To completely cover the mark
on her face,
I'm afraid it will be difficult.
You all may leave.
Yes.
I don't care how you look.
♪Only then will you understand
the pain of partings♪
I will always love you.
♪But it's hard to bear the weight
of longing♪
You are my princess consort forever.
♪Our encounter was too brief♪
♪Even if I have to
go through fire and water♪
♪I will still persist♪
♪A promise♪
Sorry to make you suffer.
♪Riding to the ends of the Earth♪
♪Crossing the desert sands♪
♪Deceiving me with a promise♪
♪What kind of punishment is this♪
Don't be afraid.
♪Like quicksand falling through fingers♪
I will always be here.
♪As if in a moment, only the fragrance
remains on the fingertips♪
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
you must seek justice for me.
Your Majesty.
What happened? Tell me.
My sister and nephew's death
is suspicious.
How could they suddenly die
from a sudden illness?
You must seek justice for me,
Your Majesty.
How could such a thing happen?
Well...
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
according to the intelligence report,
Chu Feiyan entered Tianque
without permission
and kidnapped Han Ziqing.
Jun Beiyue chased her
to Dongling's ship
to have rescued Han Ziqing
and captured Princess Xuanyuan Zhaoxi.
The situation is quite complicated.
Chu Feiyan suddenly left the palace
that day.
I knew she was up to something.
I didn't expect her
to interfere in Tianque.
What exactly is she trying to do?
Chu Feiyan has always hated Han Ziqing.
If she kidnapped her
out of personal vendetta,
it's not hard to understand.
I'm just afraid there's something
that we don't know about.
Why did you come back so late?
- Is he awake?
- Yes, he's awake.
He didn't say a word.
Such a mute.
He refused to take the medicine either.
Here.
Xuanyuan Lige,
you are seriously injured.
Take the medicine,
or you won't get better.
Come on.
There's a saying that the body and skin
are received from one's parents.
Why make things difficult for yourself?
Right?
You need to recover from the illness.
Baili Weisheng, I won't take it.
You don't need to worry about my body.
Let me go.
That's not possible.
I went through a lot of trouble
to save you.
I spent so much money
to buy you new clothes
and the good medicinal herbs.
What if you jump into the sea again?
Then my effort would be in vain.
It took me a lot of effort to save you.
Fine.
I promise you.
I won't seek death.
I just want to leave.
Where to?
Han Ziqing has already been rescued.
Jun Beiyue saved her.
She's fine, and so are you.
Isn't that good?
Come on, take the medicine.
Who exactly are you?
I am a veterinarian.
You are a Golden Merfolk.
What is a Golden Merfolk?
Go away.
Get well first,
and you can say I'm a Golden Merfolk.
You can also go wherever you want.
I won't stop you, okay?
Golden Merfolk
is a branch
of the Nanzhao's Merfolk Tribe.
But their status and position
are much more noble than other merfolk.
Though you're young,
you know quite a lot.
The Golden Merfolk
was extinct decades ago.
So?
You are the last surviving
Golden Merfolk.
What? Are you investigating me?
Even though I'm a veterinarian,
I can still take a human pulse.
Xuanyuan Lige,
you have a hidden illness.
Moreover, you've been soaking
in seawater for so long.
The cold has invaded your body.
No way.
I need to change your prescription.
- Stop grinding.
- Baili Weisheng,
where are you going?
Unlock the acupuncture points
on my body.
I'll change your prescription.
You should rest well.
Why did you
save the Crown Prince of Dongling?
I saw injustice and acted to help.
What's wrong?
Could it be
because he saved Han Ziqing,
you consider him a comrade?
So what if I do?
Then you're in trouble.
So many people like Han Ziqing.
Even if you wait for 300 years,
it won't be your turn.
Get lost.
Brother, you are here.
Brother, please sit.
Brother,
since the Queen
and Second Prince passed away,
my health has been deteriorating.
Thank you
for managing the state affairs, Brother.
But you are the King of Tianque.
Han Ziqing has gone missing,
and Beiyue is in conflict
with Dongling again.
It will cause much discussion.
Tianque must take a stance
on this matter
to stabilize
the people and the situation.
But the imperial edict
must be issued by you.
Your Majesty,
I believe
we should send a letter
to Fourth Prince
to inform him of the situation
in the Royal City.
Alright,
let's do as you say, Brother.
These are troubled times.
I wonder
how Beiyue is doing.
Beiyue
is busy with Ziqing's matters.
I believe
no matter what changes occur,
he will not forget his responsibilities.
That's good.
Your Majesty,
just focus on the recuperation.
Alright.
Take care, Brother.
She's starting to sweat.
That's good.
She should wake up soon.
Sha, don't forget.
Don't receive other patients these days.
I wouldn't dare break my promise
to Your Highness.
Don't worry.
Alright then.
Sha, thank you.
Ziqing,
you must get well soon.
For all the suffering you endured today,
I will make them pay back double.
I will go to Xiling right now
to retrieve
what rightfully belongs to you.
I wonder if Prince An
can stabilize the situation
in Tianque Royal City.
As for the Royal City,
I have already made arrangements.
(Xiling Territory)
Fourth Prince, long time no see.
It is a great honor
to have you here.
I apologize for making you wait so long.
I am truly sorry.
You must drink a few more with me later.
Sure.
Well,
please.
(Linze Gate)
Your Highness, will you attend
the welcome banquet tomorrow night?
Jun Beiyue is here for me.
I cannot let him see me for now.
Tell them I am unwell.
I will not attend the welcome banquet.
Yes.
Your Highness,
His Majesty has instructed
that you should not wander around
after arriving in Xiling.
I came to Xiling
to attend the Sand Worship Ritual,
not as a prisoner.
Why can't I go out for a walk?
Your Highness, it's His Majesty's order.
Please follow it,
and do not make it difficult for me.
Then bring Situ Haonan to me.
If His Majesty finds out
you meet Mr. Situ privately,
I will be doomed.
At least bring Fourth Princess to me.
She is my friend.
Can't I see her?
I have asked around.
Fourth Princess did not come this time.
Ziqing didn't come?
Impossible.
Could it be
something happened?
I didn't expect Jun Beiyue
to dare come to Xiling alone.
How do you think he will deal with us?
We have known
the secret of Han Ziqing's identity.
If Jun Beiyue dares to provoke us,
I will not be polite to him.
But where did he hide Han Ziqing?
Has he sent her back to Tianque?
No, it can't be.
Now Jun Beiyue is like
a bird on a wire.
He would never let Han Ziqing
return to Tianque alone.
She must be hiding somewhere
to heal herself.
Even if she recovers from her injuries,
so what?
That ugly mark on her face
won't just disappear, will it?
Han Ziqing was right.
You are jealous of her.
So what if I am?
I don't care about your petty thoughts.
Just remember this,
Han Ziqing must not
fall into anyone else's hands.
We must find her as soon as possible.
(Xiling Palace)
King of Tieyan,
I have heard that Princess Qianqian
is an exceptional dancer.
Do we have the honor today
to watch her dance?
King of Xiling,
I come here with my daughter.
We have no grand gifts to offer.
So let my daughter perform a dance
to express our gratitude.
Qianqian,
please dance to the song.
Princess Qianqian is indeed
a beautiful and great dancer.
It is our fortune to watch this today.
Additionally,
I have another announcement to make.
My youngest son, Chu Tiange,
will marry Princess Nangong Qianqian
of Tieyan.
Congratulations, King of Xiling.
Congratulations, King of Tieyan.
Since it is a joyous occasion,
I have also prepared a gift
for Prince Xiang.
Bring it in.
Jun Beiyue,
what is the meaning of this?
Fourth Prince.
Fourth Prince,
I was wrong.
Everything I did
was under the orders
of Chu Tiange and Chu Feiyan.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have colluded
with the Chu siblings.
Please forgive me, Fourth Prince.
Please let me return to Dongling.
Prince Xiang, I wonder
if you are satisfied with my gift.
As to the despicable things
you and Chu Feiyan did,
I will make you repay them doubly.
Sit down.
How did you feel
when you saw Qianqian today?
She seemed
very unhappy today.
You are worrying about her.
Have you ever thought about
meeting her alone?
Meeting her alone?
If you can't let go,
I can help you.
Are you just going to watch
she marries Chu Tiange?
Beiyue,
what do you plan to do
with Xuanyuan Zhaoxi?
In my opinion,
if we send Xuanyuan Zhaoxi back now,
firstly, we can avoid
a diplomatic conflict,
and secondly, it would
give the Queen of Dongling a favor.
Currently, Tianque should not
make too many enemies.
Alright,
let's do as you say.
Look at the fog and the wind.
Can we arrive before dawn?
It's going to rain.
Baili Weisheng,
why did you
abduct me?
What do you mean by "abduct"?
That's such an unpleasant way to put it.
I'm taking you to find a doctor
to save your life.
I don't need you to save my life.
I've told you before.
Put me down,
and let me walk on my own.
Didn't we discuss this already?
Look at you.
Even if I leave you halfway,
you would still die.
Just lie down here.
Be good.
Once you're cured...
I don't need treatment.
How about
unlocking my acupuncture points first?
Oh,
can't you just listen to me for once?
Do you know how much effort
I've spent to save you?
Can't you be a little considerate?
Well,
just do me this favor
and be sensible.
What favor?
Baili Weisheng, unlock me.
Unlock my acupuncture points.
Alright. It's right here.
Sha.
Sha, Sha!
I will not take any patients these days.
Go away.
What?
Don't take patients?
I need to see you.
Open the door,
or I'll break the door
and break the window.
Sha.
Fine.
You geezer.
Open the door.
Sha, open the door quickly.
Shh.
Be quiet.
I told you I would not
take any patients.
Just go away.
♪Memories drift afar♪
♪Gather into love, opening our hearts♪
♪Like the sweet scent of flowers♪
♪It heals old scars♪
♪May we brave through life's trials together♪
♪Time flows peacefully like a stream♪
♪Into the sea it merges, where desolation goes♪
♪Washed by time's endless cycle♪
♪Old sorrows fade away♪
♪May time reach through longing♪
♪To where you are♪
♪No matter how long, I'll never forget♪
♪Crossing the night sky,
with the moon so bright♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪Through time♪
♪And beyond♪