♪Memory is like reflection in the mirror♪
♪Ephemeral yet lasting in the heart♪
♪I let go of worries and face the road ahead♪
♪The vast land stretches far and wide♪
♪My heart remains strong, spirit unbroken♪
♪May this life remain unscathed,
till we meet again♪
♪With calm laughter, I vanquish evil♪
♪Together, we walk through life hand in hand♪
♪Dust rises♪
♪The melody continues amidst the turmoil♪
♪We stand firm in the wind side by side♪
♪I dream as if all is but a fleeting moment♪
♪Yet life rarely follows our desires♪
♪With the totem of strength,
I endure many trials♪
♪Cross love and hate, life and death♪
♪We fight with heads held high♪
♪Facing the chasm of life♪
♪We stand tall fearlessly♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 10=
Princess, go!
Your Highness!
- Prince.
Are you okay?
Chase her!
Stop!
Who are you?
How dare you harm the Prince's men?
Prince, be careful.
What are you trying to do?
- Prince!
Your Highness.
What kind of skill is this?
Shall we chase them?
This is the legendary Sound Strike.
Retreat!
Stop the carriage.
Stop, stop, stop.
Your Highness.
Let's go.
Open the door.
Get in.
Who are you?
The Fourth Prince's inspection.
Move aside.
Princess Feiyan.
The Prince's guards need a search.
Darn it.
We're suspected.
Routine inspection.
Please forgive us.
Why search the envoy's convoy out of nowhere?
Did our Xiling offend
the Fourth Prince's mansion somehow?
You misunderstood.
You're near the city gate.
It's just a routine check.
Please step out for inspection.
Prince Xiang got drunk yesterday.
He can't get out.
Then may we take a look inside?
That would violate diplomatic protocol.
Are you
treating Xiling's envoys like thieves?
I'm just following orders.
If you have objections,
you can file a complaint.
His Highness will
give your country an explanation.
He got drunk yesterday
and still hasn't woken up.
Is the search over?
Sorry for this.
Please continue.
Sir, the princess isn't in Xiling's convoy.
What do we do now?
Keep following them.
Yes.
Alright, everyone, get out.
- Father! Father!
- Yes.
Father!
Father, you must stand up for me.
I was sent by you
to the Tiger Army to take command.
Beiyue returned.
He had someone point a sword at me,
accusing me of seizing
military power, Father!
The order to take command came from me.
The Tieyan army is invading.
The situation is urgent.
General Ouyang's troops...
His uncle is
probably drinking
and making merry at Xiguan right now.
Nonsense!
Father.
Uncle is loyal to Tianque.
Beiyue is slandering him!
There's no war at Xiguan.
Is it wrong for your uncle to drink
and make merry?
What?
No war?
What's going on here?
Beiyue, you...
Jun Beichen.
Take a good look.
Tieyan's 100,000 troops aren't at our border.
They have only 10,000,
bluffing their way in.
As for the so-called Dugu Xianyun
leading 3,000 elite soldiers,
only fifty miles from our western border,
that's pure nonsense.
Your uncle falsely reported
the situation from the border.
What is his crime?
And you colluded with him
to seize my military power.
What is your crime?
What on earth is going on?
Father!
I only knew the situation was urgent.
I requested command
for the safety of Tianque.
I don't know anything else.
Please investigate!
- Father!
- Please investigate, Father!
My Tiger Army got the most
accurate military report from the frontline.
Please, Father,
give me justice.
How dare you!
Father.
I truly don't know.
I only knew the situation was dire,
so I asked for command.
I know
nothing else, Father!
Jun Beichen.
This was all your uncle's doing.
Without your help,
he couldn't have succeeded.
And now you're trying
to wash your hands of it?
Father.
I'm also a member
of the Jun family.
How could I do something
that would ruin the kingdom
and disgrace my name forever?
I...
I did it for Tianque
and the people of Tianque,
so I didn't stop
to discern the truth.
Father, see this clearly!
Please see this clearly!
Ouyang Yibo dared
to falsify military reports!
Eunuch!
Go to Xiguan at once,
bring him back to the royal city,
and execute him publicly!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Father.
What should we do
with Second Brother?
You reckless fool!
Guards!
Take him away!
Father!
Quickly!
I'm innocent, Father!
Father!
Forgive me.
Endure it.
Come on.
Let me help you up.
Drink.
Drink some wine.
It'll ease the pain.
One more sip.
Come on.
Rest a bit.
(Something's off.)
(Why does her blood smell fragrant?)
(Moxun?)
(She's been poisoned?)
(But)
(if she's really poisoned with Moxun,)
(how is she still alive?)
Can you hear me?
Calm down.
Han Ziqing.
Don't hurt yourself.
Don't move. Hold on!
You've been poisoned with Moxun.
Cold water can ease the toxin.
♪The memory lingers, though we're far apart♪
Just hold on.
It'll be over soon.
♪I'd abandon the world's chaos
and barren path♪
♪Just to have you by my side♪
I know.
I know you're suffering.
But hang in there.
♪Not wanting regret to stay with me♪
It'll be okay soon.
♪After all the twists and turns,
you're still here♪
(It must have been the strong liquor)
(that activated the residual toxin.)
(The cold water is)
(suppressing the toxin temporarily.)
(But)
(how did she)
(survive this poison?)
(Could it be)
(she's immune to all poisons?)
(Is she...?)
(Prince Yao's Mansion)
The Princess was abducted.
I believe Xiling is the most suspicious,
so we immediately searched their convoy.
But we didn't find her.
If it wasn't Chu Tiange who did it,
could it be the Second Prince?
It shouldn't be.
Our men surrounded
the Second Prince at that time.
No time for him.
Shadow, you said Chu Tiange was injured.
How did he get hurt?
What about the musician?
Isn't he just a musician?
Is he also a suspect?
He left right after the music gathering.
It's hard to trace him.
Your Highness.
The Princess has a unique constitution.
I worry that someone with ill intentions
might use her to threaten us.
With her abilities,
she shouldn't be easily exploited.
Now, Xiling is still the most suspicious.
Spread the word.
Say that our Fourth Princess
was abducted
by Xiling's Prince Xiang, Chu Tiange.
Your Highness, we have no evidence
to back that up.
I'm going to Xiling to find the evidence.
Old traitor!
Traitor!
Execute him!
Old traitor!
- Old traitor!
- Traitor!
He should be cut to pieces!
- Smash him!
- He should be cut!
Traitor!
Smash him to death! Smash him to death!
Smash the traitor!
Eunuch Yin.
Well.
Is the King still unwilling to see us?
Eunuch Yin, please.
Go talk to the King again.
Please let us see him.
We beg you, Eunuch Yin, please.
Eunuch Yin, please help us.
Queen.
Princess.
It's not that I don't want to help.
But the King is in a rage.
I truly don't dare to persuade him.
It's best if you both return for now.
Wait until the King calms down.
If we wait,
the lives of the dozens of people
in the Ouyang family
will be long gone!
My father has already been beheaded.
His life was taken for a great crime.
Can't the King spare our family?
Lower your voice, Princess. Stop crying.
Your Highness.
Fourth Prince, Fourth Prince.
We wronged you in the past.
I now offer my apologies.
Please, speak to the King
on our behalf.
Spare the Ouyang family.
Beiyue.
You're a noble person. Don't hold grudges.
We were wrong in the past.
Please don't take it to heart.
My father was guilty,
but the dozens of people in the Ouyang family
are innocent!
With the Fourth Princess now missing,
you have no right to ask me for mercy.
From now on, you'd better pray every day
that the Fourth Princess returns safely.
If anything happens to her,
you'll all join her in death.
Guards, take the Queen and the Princess back.
Your Majesty.
The Fourth Prince has arrived.
Greetings, Father.
Beiyue.
That old traitor Ouyang Yibo
has been executed.
The military power has been returned to you.
As for your brother,
Ouyang Yibo confessed
to everything before his execution.
It was all his doing.
Your brother knew nothing.
What do you think?
Father, no need to worry.
As long as Ouyang Yibo has been punished,
justice has been served for the kingdom.
My brother and I
are blood brothers after all.
He would never harm me.
Well.
I understand this.
I'm relieved that you can
consider the bond of brotherhood
and forgive your brother this time.
Father.
I now face a difficult matter
and seek your guidance.
What is it?
Ziqing has been kidnapped
by Xiling's Prince Xiang, Chu Tiange.
Have you heard about this, Father?
I've heard about it.
Chu Tiange is too outrageous!
He must resent the Fourth Princess
for defeating Chu Feiyan,
which caused Xiling to lose face.
That's why he did something so despicable.
Tieyan's surprise attack
was also a trap set by Chu Tiange
and Ouyang Yibo.
Chu Tiange dares
to humiliate Tianque like this.
I can't
stand it.
You're right.
We, Tianque,
cannot tolerate this.
Father, I ask for your permission
to lead the troops and punish Chu Tiange.
Very well. Do you need me
to send reinforcements?
My Tiger Army will be enough.
But I have one request, Father.
Could I take my brother
with me on this campaign?
Your brother?
Though he's stayed
in the royal city for a long time,
he's always had a heart
for serving the country.
This campaign would be
a good opportunity to train him.
When brothers work together,
they can accomplish anything.
I approve.
Thank you,
Father.
Goodbye, Your Highness.
You're awake.
It's you.
You remember me.
Why am I here?
I saved you.
Saved me?
Why did you save me?
For a musician,
the hardest to find
is a kindred spirit.
Your talent.
I witnessed it myself.
So I want you
to stay and learn from me.
I won't learn it from you.
I want to go back.
It's just a temporary retreat from the world.
From what I see, the troubles at your home
aren't really worth clinging to.
And your injuries
need time to heal.
Since I've chosen you,
I won't change my mind.
So you'll learn,
whether
you want to
or not.
It's not up to you.
Your playing can even influence the mind.
Fourth Princess, don't worry.
With your talent,
you won't be controlled.
Do you wanna imprison me?
I only want to teach you about guqin.
I've said I won't learn it.
How about this?
A month.
In one month,
I'll teach you
everything I know.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Listen carefully.
(This melody sounds)
(like the one I heard
before I fell into the cave)
(and passed out.)
Mother, what is this melody?
You'll know when you're older.
(Han Ziqing's mother used to play this.)
(How strange.)
(Why did I hear the same melody)
(when I fell?)
So?
Do you like it?
Come on.
I'll teach you.
To be honest,
I'm dying.
Before I die,
I want to pass on my skills
to someone worthy.
Han Ziqing.
You must understand.
I have no choice.
Do you know why I gave you Wuzheng?
Why?
Because that guqin
can only be played by you.
What do you mean?
Sit down.
Come on.
I'll show you some skills.
I'll play.
You listen.
(This melody.)
(Is it the key to my return?)
Mr. Lige.
How about this?
I'll learn from you,
but you must agree to one condition.
For every song I learn,
you have to answer one of my questions.
Alright.
I agree.
Good.
Now,
learn this technique first.
For every song you play later,
I want you to use this technique.
Show me first.
Let me play, and you listen.
What is this?
Sound Strike.
Sound Strike?
Killing with sound.
You're very talented.
Want to try it?
Give it a try.
Don't rush.
Try a few more times.
I told you you were highly gifted.
Once you've mastered Sound Strike,
you won't even need a guqin.
What's the difference
between it and Wind Strike?
Are you talking about the Wind Strike
that Jun Beiyue uses?
To the untrained,
they might seem the same.
But Sound Strike comes
from the sound of the strings.
It harms not only the body
but also the mind.
Practice more, and you'll understand.
Yiqing Palace said
the Second Prince accepted the order
and was ready to follow you.
He's learned to behave.
Keep an eye on him.
Yes. I'll make sure to follow him closely
and ensure his moves
are under our control.
Could it be that you've suspected
the Second Prince,
and that's why you've acted this way?
Issue my order.
The Tiger Army will fully mobilize.
We won't return
until we capture Chu Tiange.
- Yes.
Mother, now,
you should avoid coming here
lest Father gets suspicious.
I'm just worried about you.
I fear that Beiyue will
make things difficult for you.
Uncle has lost his life.
All the members of the Ouyang family,
except for you and Jingqin,
are gone.
What I've suffered is nothing.
But don't worry, Mother.
I'll definitely avenge this.
But, Beichen,
you must take more men with you.
Don't worry, Mother.
I've spent all my time in the palace.
It's been difficult to act freely.
This is an opportunity.
By the way, Mother,
have you asked Nanzhao about Han Ziqing
surviving the poison?
I wrote to them a long time ago.
In Nanzhao,
they're alert to the idea
of being immune to poisons.
They will investigate it for us.
Plus, your aunt has her plans.
All we need to do
is wait patiently.
Mother.
Though there have long been rumors
about the Isolated Island,
this matter is too strange.
Are the rumors true?
It doesn't matter.
As long as the King of Nanzhao
wants to eradicate
those immune to all poisons,
we can benefit from it.
Mother, you're right.
Once it's confirmed that Han Ziqing
is immune to all poisons,
there will be quite a show.
Indeed.
We can't deal with Beiyue,
but surely the King of Nanzhao can.
You truly are gifted.
I'm very pleased.
My mother
used to play this song.
I know.
How do you know?
Your mother was my master.
Is that true?
When you played just now,
you looked like your mom.
What else do you know?
You promised me.
For every song I learn,
you'd answer one question.
Once you've mastered all ten volumes,
you'll know everything.
Humph.
Jun Beiyue believes
Han Ziqing is in Chu Tiange's hands.
In a fit of rage, he has
already declared war on Xiling.
He even personally named me to go with him.
How do you think Jun Beiyue
will deal with me?
Fortunately, I was prepared.
With Han Ziqing in my hands,
why should I fear Jun Beiyue?
Your mission is complete.
Hand Han Ziqing over to me.
I'm taking her.
Didn't you bring her down?
I can't give her to you now.
What do you mean?
We had a deal.
Are you getting attached to her?
So you want to quit?
Helping you ascend as Crown Prince
is not a problem.
But Han Ziqing is now my bargaining chip,
not yours.
Your bargaining chip?
Your Highness, our army is ready.
We await your orders.
Got it.
Who exactly are you?
My surname is Xuanyuan.
Xuanyuan?
You're the Crown Prince of Dongling?
So you've been deceiving me all along.
If you're the Crown Prince,
then our cooperation...
We can still work together.
But
how we cooperate
is up to me.
You...
What are you planning to do with Han Ziqing?
That's my business.
Your Highness,
it's best if you return now.
Lige is Dongling's Crown Prince.
Her Highness is in his hands.
It's not good.
Should we attack now?
For now, she should be safe.
Did you
know his identity all along?
Issue my orders.
Mobilize 20,000 troops
to attack Xiling.
Let Jun Beichen lead.
Yes.
I gave you Wuzheng
because Wuzheng and Xuezheng
originally belonged to your mother.
I was returning them to their owner.
Besides that,
there's one more thing
I want to tell you.
What is it?
Your constitution is special.
Are you aware of that?
What do you mean?
Do you know
that you're poisoned with Moxun?
Moxun Poison.
I discovered it in your body
the night I saved you.
It's quite unique.
The victims
have no cure
and are certain to die within four hours.
Someone poisoned you.
(That's what happened.)
(It couldn't have been Han Xi'er.)
(Her goal was to be the Princess.)
(It's Jun Beichen.)
(He's truly vicious.)
(I must catch him.)
I've always been weak.
I've searched everywhere for good physicians.
I accidentally learned about this poison,
but I never expected to find it in you.
The strange thing is
despite being poisoned,
you're still alive and well.
The only explanation is
you're immune to all poisons.
So what if I'm immune
to all poisons?
Immunity to all poisons
is a unique trait of the Islanders.
The Islanders?
What are you talking about?
Stop being mysterious.
What's going on?
Explain everything.
The Isolated Island
is a tranquil island in the South Sea.
The Islanders
have always been reclusive,
rarely interacting with the continent.
But twenty years ago,
the reclusive Islanders
suddenly became puppets somehow.
They went on a rampage in Nanzhao Royal City,
killing countless people.
They were indestructible.
The Nanzhao royal family
had to mobilize all their forces
to drive them back to the Island.
Since then,
the Islanders have become a source of fear
on Longyuan Continent,
a presence as ghostly as a specter.
Are you saying
that these Islanders
were living peacefully on the island
and one day suddenly became puppets
to kill people?
Exactly.
That's too strange.
I also
find it very strange.
How are the Islanders now?
No idea.
After that,
the island mysteriously
disappeared overnight.
Could such a large island
disappear just like that?
What happened?
Nobody knows.
Over the years,
King of Nanzhao has sent people
to search for the Islanders,
but they've returned empty-handed.
However, it's heard
that they haven't given up.
If they find you,
it'll be very serious.
Don't worry.
It's safe to practice the guqin here.
What else do you know?
Practice one more piece.
I'll tell you another secret.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, there's news.
- There's news.
- Hurry!
Your Majesty, there's news.
The Fourth Prince has sent the Second Prince
to attack Xiling.
Unexpectedly,
the Second Prince
was defeated
and has retreated twenty miles
outside Xiling.
This is bad.
This is terrible.
If Tianque is defeated,
will Xiling take the opportunity
to attack our royal city?
Shut up.
What is
Beiyue doing?
You're
immune to all poisons.
Immunity to all poisons
is a unique trait of the Islanders.
The Islanders have become a source of fear
on Longyuan Continent,
a presence as ghostly as a specter.
King of Nanzhao has sent people
to search for them.
If they find you,
it'll be very serious.
Mother,
why do you always play this song?
Because
it can take us home.
Isn't our home here?
I can't give you much.
I only hope
you grow up safely and healthily.
But you must remember.
Never reveal this mask.
Never let others
see your true face.
(So, I am truly an Islander.)
(Why does the dagger have this pattern too?)
(What connection does it)
(have with the Islanders?)
♪Memories drift afar♪
♪Gather into love, opening our hearts♪
♪Like the sweet scent of flowers♪
♪It heals old scars♪
♪May we brave through life's trials together♪
♪Time flows peacefully like a stream♪
♪Into the sea it merges, where desolation goes♪
♪Washed by time's endless cycle♪
♪Old sorrows fade away♪
♪May time reach through longing♪
♪To where you are♪
♪No matter how long, I'll never forget♪
♪Crossing the night sky,
with the moon so bright♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪Through time♪
♪And beyond♪