♪Memory is like reflection in the mirror♪
♪Ephemeral yet lasting in the heart♪
♪I let go of worries and face the road ahead♪
♪The vast land stretches far and wide♪
♪My heart remains strong, spirit unbroken♪
♪May this life remain unscathed,
till we meet again♪
♪With calm laughter, I vanquish evil♪
♪Together, we walk through life hand in hand♪
♪Dust rises♪
♪The melody continues amidst the turmoil♪
♪We stand firm in the wind side by side♪
♪I dream as if all is but a fleeting moment♪
♪Yet life rarely follows our desires♪
♪With the totem of strength,
I endure many trials♪
♪Cross love and hate, life and death♪
♪We fight with heads held high♪
♪Facing the chasm of life♪
♪We stand tall fearlessly♪
=Fateful Love=
=Episode 22=
It's time.
Go and invite His Majesty.
We should set off now.
Yes.
Be careful.
Haonan,
Ziqing is still on the valley floor.
What should we do?
I'll go down to find her.
You wait here for me.
Wait.
Crown Prince Lige.
What happened?
Where is Ziqing?
Ziqing is still on the valley floor.
- The valley floor?
- Brother.
Why are you here?
Ziqing is still on the valley floor.
What are you doing here?
We just fell into the valley floor.
We encountered a swarm of scorpions.
Ziqing saved Qianqian.
She is still down there.
Please help take care
of Princess Nangong.
I need to go save her.
You can't go down.
This is Miasma Valley.
Every day at 3 to 5 p.m.,
poisonous miasma will arise.
It is deadly if you go down there.
What did you say?
Poisonous miasma?
Look.
The poisonous miasma is already rising.
But just now Mr. Situ said
Fourth Princess is still down there.
What? She is still down there?
Oh no, she will be poisoned.
What should we do?
Brother, you can't go down.
- Let go.
- Do you want to die?
She is down there now.
Let go.
This is Nanzhao.
If something happens to you,
how will I explain to Mother?
It's none of your concern.
Let go.
No one is allowed to go down.
You are all my honored guests.
I am responsible for your safety.
(Alright.)
(If Ziqing's identity is exposed,)
(I will kill the King of Nanzhao)
(and all these who wish her dead.)
(None of them will live.)
How long has Fourth Princess
been down there?
Almost two hours.
Once the poisonous miasma in the valley
has been inhaled,
she is likely to be dead.
Doesn't that mean...
We have to wait for the poisonous miasma
to completely dissipate
before we can go down to rescue her.
Exactly.
Otherwise, not only will we fail
to save Fourth Princess,
but even the rescuers
won't make it back.
(Oh no.)
(If Ziqing comes up
from the valley floor)
(and isn't poisoned,)
(everyone will know)
(that she is immune to all poisons.)
Ziqing,
there's poison down there!
Don't shout.
If you disturb the poisonous creatures,
they will attack in swarms.
The Fourth Princess' situation
will become even more dangerous.
What are you doing?
If Han Ziqing dies there,
it's her fate.
You can't save her.
With so many of us here,
why only Han Ziqing
keeps encountering danger?
It seems that she should be punished.
If you keep talking,
I'll push you down too,
and let you ascend to eternal damnation.
Do you mean to suffer?
That's what I meant.
You can't even speak properly.
Just shut up.
You dare say one more word...
Enough.
The Fourth Princess is in danger.
His Majesty and I
are already extremely anxious.
You should stop arguing.
The poisonous miasma is getting thicker.
I'm afraid Fourth Princess is...
What are you looking for?
With that look in your eyes,
are you looking for me?
Ziqing, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Just a twisted ankle and some scrapes.
Thanks to you,
for saving me and Haonan.
Otherwise, we would have been a feast
for the scorpions.
It's a hearty meal.
You just appeared from nowhere,
and you seem unscathed.
We worried for nothing.
Did you worry about me, Princess Feiyan?
I didn't notice.
Fourth Princess,
I'm quite curious.
You were down there just now.
How did you suddenly appear
in front of us now?
The original path was blocked just now.
So I took a detour.
I came from the back mountain.
Is that hard to understand?
Such a trivial matter,
yet it alarmed the King of Nanzhao
and Consort Qin.
My apologies.
Fourth Princess, you are mistaken.
Do you know that there is
filled with poisonous miasma?
It can be fatal if you inhale it.
You have stayed there
for a long time,
yet you are unharmed.
Even the poisonous miasma
can't harm you.
It's truly strange.
You are unaffected
by the poisonous miasma.
Why is that?
Fourth Princess,
could it be that you have
some miraculous elixir
that can neutralize all poisons,
or are you immune to all poisons?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand a word.
Someone saved me just now.
My head is still a bit dizzy.
Someone saved you?
Yes.
As the saying goes,
better to save one life
than build a seven-storied pagoda.
I saved Fourth Princess.
It's a kind of fate anyway.
Sorry, Fourth Princess.
Pharmacist Changning.
My master is old,
and walks slowly.
I almost got you to be misunderstood
by others.
Pharmacist Changning,
you...
Greetings, Your Majesty,
and Consort Qin.
Consort Qin,
and all the distinguished guests.
Pharmacist Changning,
why are you here?
Your Majesty,
Pharmacist Changning and I
were gathering herbs down in the valley,
and we happened to find Fourth Princess
unconscious from the poisonous miasma.
Fortunately, Pharmacist Changning
had an antidote,
which revived her.
Indeed,
if it weren't for me,
the consequence
would have been disastrous.
Thank you both.
I will visit to express my gratitude
when we go back.
Fourth Princess, don't mention it.
You are a distinguished guest from afar,
and I am serving
to put Your Majesty's mind at ease.
There was a misunderstanding earlier.
I hope you can forgive us.
You all are so concerned about me.
How could I hold a grudge against you?
As soon as you had danger,
someone happened to rescue you.
How could it be such a coincidence?
When Fourth Princess was in danger,
I rescued her.
Although it was a coincidence,
it is the truth.
I dare not lie.
Please believe me, Your Majesty.
You are highly respected
in Medicine Tribe.
How could I not believe you?
Thanks to your timely rescue,
Fourth Princess was able to survive.
Otherwise, I really wouldn't know
how to explain
to the Fourth Prince of Tianque.
It's getting late.
We should all go down the mountain.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
This time, she can't escape.
This Deer Ear Grass likes damp places.
Weisheng, we should go.
Coming. I'm coming.
Baili Weisheng?
You,
you...
What are you doing here?
I-I am gathering herbs.
Ziqing,
ar-are you alright?
Shouldn't I be alright?
How come after a few days,
you've become a stutterer?
You-you still say that about me.
Look at this.
What is it?
I'm looking for a way out.
I don't know why a thick fog
suddenly appeared.
It made me lose my way.
Do you know the way?
Thick fog?
Miss,
this is miasma.
Miasma is poisonous and fatal.
Miasma?
Then why are you not affected?
My master has an antidote.
No wonder I feel so dizzy,
and nauseous.
Alright, stop pretending.
Really.
- I feel terrible.
- In front of me,
you don't need to hide anything.
I feel terrible right now.
I can't take it anymore.
Someone up there is waiting for you
to reveal your true identity.
How do you know that?
Come on.
- What are you doing?
- Playing dead.
Playing dead?
Smart move.
Thank you.
Master, come quickly.
Master!
- Who is she?
- Well...
Look, she's dressed like this.
She's a distinguished guest.
She fainted.
It-it's miasma. Quick, quick.
Give me an antidote.
It seemed suspicious.
What's suspicious?
Is it that Han Ziqing doesn't die,
and you are very disappointed?
Aren't you disappointed?
If she doesn't die,
your brother will always think of her.
That's not good for you, is it?
Sorry
for the disturbance.
May I ask who you are?
Oh no.
Has Beiyue returned?
I don't know either.
Do you really believe Jun Beiyue
is staying in because of a cold?
Could he be pretending to be sick,
but actually plotting something else?
We'll know once we go to check it out.
If he takes action in Nanzhao,
let's see how Tianque will explain it.
There will be a good show to watch soon.
His Majesty has arrived.
Fourth Princess,
this time you encountered danger,
it was our Nanzhao's lack of care.
Your Majesty said
he wanted to personally explain
to Fourth Prince
to ask for his understanding.
Consort Qin, you are too kind.
My husband has caught a cold.
For the sake
of the King of Nanzhao's health,
it's better to avoid contact.
Fourth Princess,
since you came to Nanzhao as guests,
we should take good care of you.
But today, you were in danger.
Is this not important?
If we don't personally explain
to Fourth Prince,
it would be
against diplomatic etiquette.
Could it be that Fourth Prince
is not in the room?
Otherwise, how would he know
that His Majesty is here,
yet not come out to greet him?
Fourth Princess,
please announce our arrival.
Physician Gu,
how is His Highness?
Fourth Princess,
His Highness just took the medicine
and was asleep.
He's sleeping.
Sleeping?
When we left,
he was bedridden.
Now he is still sleeping.
Is it more serious?
Let's go and check on him.
No, no.
His Highness has caught a cold.
Han Ziqing.
He's afraid that you may get infected.
Let's wait...
Han Ziqing.
Until His Highness recovers.
How could he be so weak?
It's just a cold.
Fourth Princess, please
let us go in and visit him.
There's an assassin!
Someone, come quickly!
Shadow,
go catch the assassin.
Yes.
- Go.
This way.
Your Majesty,
there is an assassin in the courtyard.
Please step outside the courtyard
for safety.
No need.
I want to see
what this assassin looks like.
Stop!
Don't run!
Stop pretending.
Your Majesty, they are blocking us.
They must be hiding something.
Let's force our way in.
Move aside.
Princess Zhaoxi,
your face.
My face.
My face!
Jun Beiyue,
how dare you hit my face.
I have caught a cold
and have said I won't see anyone.
Princess,
I apologize.
I thought you were the assassin.
You...
King of Nanzhao,
there was an assassin
at the envoy's residence.
Isn't this a bit too negligent?
Well.
Have you caught the assassin?
Your Majesty,
we have searched the entire residence
and found no assassin.
It's my fault
for startling you, Fourth Prince.
How are you feeling now?
King of Nanzhao,
Jun Beiyue injured my face.
Shouldn't you seek justice for me?
Your Majesty,
Fourth Prince has caught a cold.
Although he will recover
after a few days of rest,
this cold is contagious,
and you should be careful.
Since you are unwell,
let's wait until you recover.
We will take our leave for now.
You...
Be careful. I might infect you.
Ziqing.
It serves you right.
How is it?
Did you find anything?
I found many corpses below,
hideous corpses.
They all have the totem
of the Isolated Island on their faces.
Totem?
And some are red,
while others are black.
Those with red totems on their faces
all have hideous expressions.
They must be related to the Island.
(Since they have the totem
on their faces,)
(they must be the Islanders.)
(But why do some have red totems?)
Beiyue, my face...
And this,
take a look.
What is this?
You found it after all.
If we follow the totem to find the place,
we might find the remaining scores.
How many are left?
Six volumes.
Previously, we found some
in Qinse Valley,
and you brought some back
from Ice Pool.
We have a total of four volumes.
They correspond
to the first four volumes we have.
So we can know
that Lishang has two major chapters.
Each chapter consists of ten volumes
to correspond to each other.
Besides the scores we already have,
we are still missing six volumes.
As long as we find all the music scores,
we can find the answer.
(Music Scores)
Sis,
where are you going?
When did you arrive?
I came by Father's order,
to discuss important matters
with Nanzhao.
Father sent you?
To take me back to Xiling?
It's about your marriage
with the King of Nanzhao.
I don't agree.
Father has already agreed.
Does it matter if you disagree?
I have fought battles all over
for Xiling
and have mediated in court affairs.
In the end, Father just agreed
to have just sold me off.
Am I really that worthless in his eyes?
It's because you are worth something
that Father made this decision.
Why don't you understand?
What did you say?
You know it too.
Ever since our battle
with Dongling and Tianque,
Xiling's national strength
has greatly declined.
Now that the King of Nanzhao is willing
to ally with us through marriage,
this is a great opportunity
for Xiling to rise again.
Do you really want to see your country
keep declining
and not be willing to sacrifice yourself?
Why should I sacrifice
for your kingdom?
Because you are a princess of Xiling.
Sis,
I know you are frustrated
and I know you like Jun Beiyue only.
But now Father has made up his mind.
Moreover,
your marriage directly affects
the survival of Xiling.
So you have no choice.
Fine.
I agree.
I know you are a sensible person.
It is Han Ziqing
who got me into this situation.
I want her dead.
Rest assured.
Once there's an opportunity,
I will kill her for sure.
(Lishang)
This marriage alliance
between Xiling and Nanzhao
is like grabbing a lifeline
in a desperate situation.
No wonder the King of Xiling
agreed so quickly.
He even sent Chu Tiange
to make preparations.
Beiyue,
this is not good news for Tianque.
Even if Xiling convinces Nanzhao
to be enemies with Tianque,
so what?
I will prepare for the war.
If the King of Nanzhao is smart enough,
he won't start a war easily.
Stop.
Princess Feiyan,
is there something you need from me?
I'm about to marry the King of Nanzhao.
You must be very happy, right?
Not really.
I don't feel much about it.
Don't be smug.
For what you have done to me,
one day I will repay you
a hundredfold, and a thousandfold.
Han Ziqing, just you wait.
Alright.
Princess Feiyan,
you will settle here for now.
After the wedding,
you will move to the official bedroom.
My beloved,
tonight you look
even more radiant and captivating.
Tomorrow is the wedding.
Your Majesty, you came over
late at night.
Is there something you need?
Nothing.
I just came to see you.
My beloved,
I know you are unwilling,
but I admire your beauty and talent,
I can't help myself.
In time, you will understand
my sincere intentions.
Don't be afraid.
From now on, I will love you,
protect you,
and ensure you a life of glory.
Your Majesty,
I have a request.
Please grant it, Your Majesty.
Speak.
I grow up on the grasslands,
and I dislike being confined.
After the wedding,
please do not treat me
like the other concubines
and imprison me in the palace,
but allow me to have the run of Nanzhao.
Do you intend to escape back to Xiling?
With Xiling's national strength,
I doubt they would dare to shelter me.
I just don't want to be a caged bird.
Your Majesty, if you agree,
I can run your errands,
and I am willing
to bear children for you
to continue the lineage.
Alright.
I agree.
However,
I want to know one thing.
Do you still think of Jun Beiyue,
and that's why you oppose Han Ziqing?
To be honest with you,
I did have feelings for Jun Beiyue,
but now I no longer have such thoughts.
As for Han Ziqing, I just detest her.
I detest her arrogance and conceit.
I don't want to see her so pleased.
Please allow me to ask a question.
Does she concern you?
Why do you ask?
At Lingshui River and Miasma Valley,
you and Consort Qin
seemed to be testing her intentionally.
Please don't misunderstand me,
Your Majesty.
I am not trying to pry into anything.
I just hate Han Ziqing.
Therefore, I pay special attention
to everything that happens to her.
That's why I find it peculiar.
Your Majesty,
I'm about to marry you,
so I want to share your worries.
I'm willing to help if you need me.
You may rise.
I'm glad to see your keen perception
and observation.
I won't hide it from you.
I do suspect Han Ziqing
is special.
Do you know...
What's the matter?
It's Lishang.
This music.
I heard this piece in Qinse Valley.
So he recognized it too.
It seems so.
You two really are kindred spirits.
♪A fleeting dream, afraid to wake up♪
♪Yet it's a love I never imagined♪
♪Can it be relied upon♪
♪Time flows downstream without stopping♪
♪The story twists and turns♪
♪Turning into a segment of longing♪
♪Your love falls like the night♪
♪The moon and sparse stars illuminate♪
♪The emptiness left in me♪
♪Light and shadow intertwine,
no time to escape♪
♪Enter the dream with the feelings♪
♪A hint of entanglement spreads♪
♪Still can't forget♪
Let's go.
♪For love, why fear walking alone♪
♪I'd abandon the world's chaos
and barren path♪
♪Just to have you by my side♪
♪Still can't forget♪
♪Still hanging on♪
♪Not wanting regret to stay with me♪
♪Why not love recklessly♪
♪After all the twists and turns♪
♪You're still here♪
Greetings, Fourth Prince
and Fourth Princess.
By the way,
there is something I would like
to ask you.
What does this totem represent?
I have seen this totem
in Guyue Cave.
And the Guyue Cave
has always been a forbidden area
of the Earth King Religion in Nanzhao.
Unless there is a major event
to pray for protection
from the Earth King,
no one is allowed to enter.
What if we want to go there?
You also recognized
the tune played
at today's wedding ceremony.
It is Lishang.
The music scores I currently have
for Lishang
does not include this tune.
I came to tell you,
no matter how talented a musician is,
it is impossible to write
so many music scores at once.
Unless...
These music scores came
from the sounds of nature,
and were recorded.
So it's a fact
that we must find all the music scores
and play them completely.
Otherwise, we cannot decipher Lishang.
Alright. Thank you for telling me this.
His Majesty has arrived.
♪Memories drift afar♪
♪Gather into love, opening our hearts♪
♪Like the sweet scent of flowers♪
♪It heals old scars♪
♪May we brave through life's trials together♪
♪Time flows peacefully like a stream♪
♪Into the sea it merges, where desolation goes♪
♪Washed by time's endless cycle♪
♪Old sorrows fade away♪
♪May time reach through longing♪
♪To where you are♪
♪No matter how long, I'll never forget♪
♪Crossing the night sky,
with the moon so bright♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪May light cut through the darkness
of the night♪
♪To where I found you♪
♪No matter the distance♪
♪I'll fly to your side♪
♪Through time and beyond♪
♪Through time♪
♪And beyond♪