THE CHARACTERS, INCIDENTS,
GROUPS, ORGANIZATION,
AND LOCATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH REALITY
AND ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
WE STRICTLY FOLLOWED COVID-19
QUARANTINE REGULATIONS AND CHILD
ACTORS AND ACTRESSES AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
We will now begin. Say your name,
official rank, and affiliation.
9 DAYS AGO
There's something else
I'm really curious about.
It's about Won Ki-choon's leg.
It's been cut off.
I cut it off.
You
cut his leg off yourself?
I didn't expect for you to get blood
on your own hands. That's unexpected.
It's my fault that I dared to think
that I know you well.
I don't care about getting blood
on my hands. I just need to wash them.
It's better than to just sit
and watch everything go wrong.
You can go now. I need to rest.
I have an important report.
-What is it?
-It's about Cha Woo-in's identity.
You'll be surprised.
Will I?
She's the daughter
of the late Cha Ho-chul.
Did you think that I didn't know?
I'm sure Cha Woo-in couldn't even imagine…
that I've been watching her since the day
she became a military prosecutor.
Then why are you letting her be?
I'm just observing her for now.
And it's ridiculous for me
to let one petty captain bother me.
CEO Noh's trial, his desertion,
and Lieutenant Colonel Won Ki-choon…
She keeps getting involved with you.
And she's a military prosecutor,
who can bring a charge
against a serviceperson.
And so is Doh Bae-man.
Doh Bae-man only pursued money
while working for me,
but he totally changed
after he met Cha Woo-in.
I'm sure they're intertwined
through something.
We must be careful of those two.
But I'm actually worried about you.
You only realized
Cha Woo-in's true identity now.
You just realized now
that there's a spy right under my nose.
How will you
run IM in my place like that?
You can go now.
Cha Woo-in has been
preparing for a long time
to stand in front of you.
You must never underestimate that.
And now,
please address me as the CEO of IM.
I do not want
to be called a lawyer anymore.
You only realized
Cha Woo-in's true identity now.
You just realized now
that there's a spy right under my nose.
PERSONAL DETAILS
CHA WOO-IN
A spy.
She's been
thinking of Cha Woo-in as a spy?
A monster that's beyond our imagination.
People say monsters and devils
are created because they can't accept
that a human being would do such a thing.
If she cut off his completely normal leg…
Then Noh Hwa-young
truly is a monster.
In order to fight a monster,
we must make the first attack.
Schedule a press conference for tomorrow.
Press conference?
Let's make the public sentiment explode
with Sergeant Koo's confession.
The testimony is important,
but we also need evidence
to use as a smoking gun.
Kim Han-yong's brother is
getting brain surgery tomorrow.
Wait. They said the surgery
will be difficult
because of the material in the brain.
And Medical Officer Jo Soo-chan
gave that diagnosis.
And he's their accomplice.
So it's a wrong diagnosis?
We can infer that
they've stopped the surgery
to cover the truth up.
He's a rotten doctor, who even
switched the CT scan images.
We already found a brain specialist
to operate on him.
Prosecutor Doh, please meet Kim Han-yong
and get his consent for the surgery.
Is it…
really okay for my brother to get surgery?
It's taking out what's stuck in his brain,
so we must prepare for the worst.
Consenting is completely up to you.
-I know it's not an easy decision to make.
-No.
The choice is up to my brother.
He always told me to make a choice,
if I have 1% of courage.
Though it's 1%,
it's totally different to zero,
which means doing nothing.
That's why I fired a gun
at the bookstore, too.
-Did you meet Kim Han-yong?
-Yes.
Did he consent to the surgery?
Let's do it with 1% of courage,
not 1% of possibility.
What?
That's what Kim Han-yong said.
Did he?
We must expose the one
behind this Won Ki-choon case,
for Kim Han-yong's brother.
Yes, and for Kim Han-yong
who made a difficult decision.
We must find evidence
and damage Noh Hwa-young.
Prosecutor Cha.
Put it on video call mode
for a moment, okay?
What? All of a sudden?
Is something wrong?
What…
Come here.
Isn't that Bolt?
Yes. I couldn't help but take him in.
Gosh, that jerk CEO Kang.
I was actually worried about him,
but I'm relieved to see him there.
Why?
Tomorrow is the day of the surgery
and Sergeant Koo's press conference.
It'll be such an important day.
We will either overturn the situation,
or the situation will overturn us.
It'll be the day of a decisive battle.
Yes, sir.
Now, I shall go to bed.
-Good night and sweet dreams.
-Good night, Prosecutor Cha, and…
Gosh, she's so damn rude.
Come here. Time to sleep.
Come, it's time to sleep.
Is this the east?
I should sleep like this.
Come here. Yes.
Bolt, come up here. No?
Yes, let's go. What are we doing here?
Let's go. Bolt, come. Let's go.
Let's go.
Hey.
Hey, this is trespassing, okay?
And this is the house of a detective!
Why should I suffer outside
when there's my beloved aunt's house here?
Wow. Soybean paste stew.
Auntie, hold this.
Hey!
A home-cooked meal
without side dishes is the best.
I'm hungry.
Auntie.
-Wash his feet for me, please.
-You little…
That was doggone scary.
Auntie, you make good stew.
It's lonely to be alone.
We found the witness
of the Won Ki-choon case.
We'll expose it
at a press conference tomorrow.
But you got punished.
Will it be okay?
So I'm going to face it head-on
with a press conference.
Auntie, you know that I'm a fighter.
A fighter who doesn't let go once I bite.
And I was a witness, too.
The only witness
of Mom and Dad's accident.
Bae-man, do you
really believe there's a different reason
behind the car accident 20 years ago?
Yes.
I'm convinced.
As soon as I get a search warrant
for Won Ki-choon's house,
that's the real beginning for me.
The beginning?
Noh Hwa-young must've designed
the hero of mines,
but there's no physical proof.
We only have strong suspicion for now.
That's why I'm going to interrogate him.
An interrogation in a patient's room…
I hate this probation.
You're alone, so be extra careful.
It's okay even if I fail because
the second purpose is the real deal.
I will turn the hero of mines
into a real mine
that explodes when stepped on.
You bastard!
How dare you come in here?
I'm here for a visit.
Salute.
It's been several months
since you had your accident,
but you still cannot get used to it.
Like your leg was cut off
not too long ago.
What?
Gosh
You reject the nurses
and inject the painkiller yourself.
You must have a lot to hide.
Well,
you're suddenly starring in a show
someone scripted as the main cast,
I guess you can't help it.
But the problem is,
that show, which seemed
it just required you
to play along just as it was scripted,
suddenly turned into a horrible reality.
You don't need to play a hero anymore.
Because you've become a real hero now.
I will
put an end to that show today.
Don't try to play any dirty tricks!
Get lost!
There was a witness that day.
He saw you shooting
the Search Company Commander
in a friendly fire.
I said, who's there?
What?
Sergeant Koo is going to expose everything
at the press conference today.
"Expose?"
What if you take all the blame?
If the story says
that you cut off your own leg
and made up the heroic tale…
You'll fall
from being Korea's favorite hero
to Korea's craziest bastard overnight.
Think about it.
You only did
what that person told you to do.
And that person cut your leg off, too.
They're the designer and perpetrator
of this case, and you're the victim.
You, Lieutenant Colonel,
just had to play along against your will.
So just say one thing. Either
that person's name, rank, or position.
Then I'll help you
through plea bargaining.
Noh…
No wonder you're a jerk! You don't even
knock on the door! Get out!
Get this bastard out!
Leave, please.
You're missing
such a great chance like this.
Then, Search Battalion Commander
Won Ki-choon,
I'll come see you again,
with an arrest warrant.
Salute.
The one who planned everything
was indeed Noh Hwa-young.
you're suddenly starring in a show
someone scripted as the main cast,
I guess you can't help it.
What? A show?
Doh Bae-man, that lunatic!
Do you think
I'll be shaken by what you say?
I'm a hero!
A real hero!
DIVISION COMMANDER NOH HWA-YOUNG
I hereby report regarding the progress
of the investigation on corruption
in military supply.
According to the investigation, some of
the supply provided to the 4th Division,
including 257 daily…
Daily outdoor uniform…
The 257 of them, and 419 berets…
The 419 of them were confirmed
to be of low quality, below standards.
The person in charge of supply
and the company exchanged bribes…
I'm in a meeting right now.
Division Commander.
It looks like…
Doh Bae-man knows everything.
There was a witness
among our Search Battalion members.
He said he'll gather all of the reporters
and expose everything.
If that gets revealed…
I'm dead.
Let's talk later.
Division Commander!
It seems Doh Bae-man also figured out
that you cut my leg off.
Okay.
-Keep going.
-Sure.
And due to the connection
between the food supply company
and the supply officer,
some of the bases--
Those who gave money
and who got the money…
Arrest all of them.
I'll hear the rest of the report later.
You can leave now.
Yes, ma'am.
Salute!
The phone call saved me.
It really saved me.
The materials were not ready yet.
That was really close.
I got away with it today, again.
The military clock still ticks,
though it's upside down.
By the way,
did something happen
to the Division Commander?
I have a bad feeling about this…
Anyway…
Where's the foot bath tub?
Since Doh Bae-man isn't here,
I have no one to give me a massage.
If you're on probation, just sit
at your desk! Why are you here?
Get out!
I have a report
about Battalion Commander Won Ki-choon.
Are you feeling itchy
because of your probation?
I was feeling great today,
so why did you have to
stop the military clock?
Battalion Commander Won Ki-choon
committed friendly fire.
Hey, do you have a grudge
against Battalion Commander Won
or something?
The Company Commander was
injured by gunfire, not by a mine.
That's enough of your nonsense!
The actions after the friendly fire
were even worse.
He won over a medical officer, too.
This is impossible
without involvement of a superior.
What? Win over? Involvement of a superior?
You're going overboard, aren't you?
Do you want me to charge you
and get you sacked?
Just tell me. I'll get you
out of here right now!
You must issue a warrant
for Battalion Commander Won Ki-choon.
What?
A warrant?
Okay, sure.
I will tell you my decision
as the Staff Judge Advocate.
Listen carefully.
Based on any possibilities
to vindicate the main criminal charges,
I can't acknowledge the necessity
of confinement. Got it?
Staff Judge Advocate.
Cha Woo-in, you're a great example
of confirmation bias.
When a prosecutor targets someone,
even without evidence,
anyone can become a criminal.
That's why the people are
criticizing prosecutors,
calling them dogs and perverts!
That's not something I should hear from
you, who doesn't even read my reports.
You…
Get lost right now!
Get lost!
Yes, sir.
But I did give you a chance.
Please keep that in mind.
What?
A chance?
In 30 minutes, the search battalion
member who was at the scene
will have a press conference.
What?
Sergeant Koo Hyun-seok, the only witness
to Battalion Commander Won's
friendly fire,
will tell the truth
in front of all people of Korea.
When the truth gets revealed,
the public opinion will be in turmoil,
and you'll be completely responsible
for a poor investigation.
Why will I?
Because you just rejected
the chance I just gave you.
You always told me to be
a serviceperson than a prosecutor.
Yes, right now, I'm a serviceperson.
Because a serviceperson never bends,
and would rather break.
Hey, Cha Woo-in.
Stop right there!
I will ask you one last time.
Issue a warrant for Won Ki-choon
and lift my probation, please.
And request the corps to lift
the suspension on Captain Doh.
Why are you making so many demands?
Make your decision now. We have no time.
All right.
I'll make a judgment
after watching the press conference.
Yes, sir.
Gosh, seriously.
Hold on.
What if I get in trouble, too?
DMZ MINE EXPLOSION
PRESS CONFERENCE TO REVEAL THE TRUTH
There are many reporters here.
Can you do it?
Yes!
I'll be there soon, sir!
Your voice sounds great. You sound
totally different from yesterday.
I decided to think
only about the Company Commander today.
He must be in surgery now.
I hope it goes well.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Bang!
It's Battalion Commander Won.
What should I do?
Keep your phone on call mode.
Military Prosecutor.
SERGEANT KOO
It's almost time.
Aren't you getting started?
Ah, I have to finish my call first.
Please wait.
SERGEANT KOO
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message…
DOH BAE-MAN
DMZ MINE EXPLOSION
PRESS CONFERENCE TO REVEAL THE TRUTH
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message…
I must go outside of the base now.
-Why?
-Prosecutor Doh isn't picking up.
Something must've gone wrong
at the conference.
Subsection Chief Yoon,
Subsection Chief Ahn.
Can you help me, please?
It's time for your red-haired
alter ego to come out, right?
You knew?
When I come outside and see red hair,
I get startled without realizing it.
Don't worry.
I only use it for hunting.
I see. Hunting.
What are you doing?
Her cough won't stop!
I'm sorry, Subsection Chief
Ahn Yoo-ra. Please be well.
Goodbye. Salute.
-Salute.
-Let them pass.
-Military Prosecutor.
-Nice!
Yes!
We're busy people, you know!
Sergeant Koo is coming.
If you wait for a moment…
It's obvious
that he either changed his mind or hid.
The press conference won't happen.
-Move. Let us go!
-Reporter.
You're that military prosecutor
who got punished!
How can we trust you?
Sergeant Koo?
Where are you?
Gosh, I told you not to take that road!
That road always has a traffic jam!
Go 50 more meters
and look at 1 o'clock, and there's
a byroad. Take that byroad--
What?
There's something bigger?
Prosecutor.
Where's Sergeant Koo?
Yes. Good grief.
That's not the place…
Have a seat and wait. I'll go bring him.
Yes.
Yes, turn right there…
Sergeant Koo took the wrong road.
But that's not the problem.
There's something bigger.
-Something bigger?
-Something bigger.
-What is it?
-A scoop.
-Are you sure?
Go have a seat. I'm sure.
DETECTIVE DOH SOO-KYUNG
Prosecutor Cha, it's me.
Won Ki-choon snatched
Sergeant Koo on the way.
So it was Won Ki-choon's doing.
I'm outside the base now
and I'm on my way.
What?
How did you know?
How did you get out of there
without Staff Judge Advocate knowing…
I guess you could.
Then I'll go to Sergeant Koo.
-You…
-No.
I'll send him there safely,
so please give me the location.
And keep the reporters there.
That's an order.
Since it was a special order
from the hero of mines,
I only sent the boys who served
in the Special Warfare Command.
You'll feel reassured.
Tell CEO Yong Moon-goo I said thank you.
You dared to expose me?
Me, who was your superior?
This is mutiny, you bastard!
I'm not a serviceperson anymore!
I'm not your subordinate!
I will tell them everything,
everything I saw!
You got bribed by Doh Bae-man, didn't you?
How dare you do this to me, you bastard!
You're not well,
so don't waste your energy.
We have methods for bastards like him.
A video call with his family
will change his mind.
What the heck? The call was on?
So this situation aired live.
MILITARY PROSECUTOR DOH BAE-MAN
Gosh, this is because
mobile carriers sell unlimited plans.
There's only one thing left to do
to this bastard who lost
his sense of fear.
Boys, get to it!
What the heck?
Is that a girl?
She has a gun!
Come out here.
No, you can't!
There's a car out there, so take off now.
-What?
-Don't hesitate. Just go.
So many people are waiting
for you right now.
-And close the door when you leave.
-Stop!
-Boss!
-What the heck?
-What's this?
-It's a BB?
-What?
-Stop!
-That stings!
Sergeant Koo!
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Everyone, if you're busy,
you can leave now,
but if you do, you're going to miss
a huge exclusive story.
You know who Prosecutor Doh is!
Remember the "Imperial Military Service?"
He's a goose that lays golden eggs!
If you all leave now, you'll regret it!
Hey, old woman!
Old woman?
Yes, old woman, which means you!
Hey.
How much do you get paid for doing this?
You shouldn't do this.
You must be all busy, so please leave.
Today's press conference
has been canceled!
-No, it hasn't!
-It's been canceled!
-Please leave, all of you!
-What? Do I get paid?
I'm Detective Doh Soo-kyung
from the Gangnam Police Station.
You don't look very…
You're not a journalist, are you?
Show me your journalist ID.
You don't look normal, either.
You look suspicious, okay?
Why would a detective be here?
This is a military case.
And this case was already
proved in the military court,
and the military prosecutor who broke
the prosthetic leg got punished!
Yes!
That military prosecutor is my nephew!
Happy now?
He's your nephew?
-Hi.
-Just wait and see!
My nephew will reveal the truth
behind this case at all cost!
Because he's like a Doberman!
See? I told you!
I…
I am Koo Hyun-seok,
discharged from the Search Battalion
of the 4th Division.
I'm here to expose the truth
of the hero of mines--
Forget it!
How can we trust someone
who lacks the least amount
of common sense
and is late to a press conference?
How can we trust what you say?
The mine exploded quite a while ago,
so why are you blowing the whistle now?
Isn't it because you have
some other purposes?
Prosecutor Doh.
It's because I was scared.
I was so scared that I was the only one
who saw him being shot.
Company Commander!
If I exposed
what happened inside the military
when I was about to get discharged…
I thought I'd die a mysterious death,
without being able to see my mom's face.
I just thought I should
keep it to myself and leave.
That I should leave what happened
in the military in the military.
Yes,
I turned a blind eye
and kept quiet for myself.
But,
someone who must be punished
turned into a hero,
and the moment of Company
Commander being shot
has not left my head.
I left the letter in the patient's room
to reduce my guilt.
And…
Military Prosecutor Doh Bae-man
gave me the courage.
Is there evidence
that can prove what you witnessed?
I'm Captain Doh Bae-man,
a military prosecutor.
I will speak, starting now.
First, I will show you the evidence
as the answer to your question.
It was a bullet, not a fragment?
This bullet was taken out
of the Company Commander's head,
who just had surgery.
From what I see, as a military prosecutor,
this is clearly a bullet,
not a fragment of a mine.
Of course, the credibility
will be announced after
a precise authentication process.
In addition,
the Company Commander's
brain surgery was successful.
They said, once he recovers,
he'll be able to testify
about the accident, and live his
daily life without any difficulties.
Then what happened to his leg?
Why did Battalion Commander
Won Ki-choon lose his leg?
That's the question I've been waiting for.
Did he cut off his own leg
to complete the heroic tale?
Or is someone behind it?
We confirmed that there was an attempt
to kidnap Sergeant Koo while he was
on his way to the press conference
to stop him from exposing the truth.
I'm sure there's someone behind it.
This case isn't just a made-up story
of the hero of mines.
It's a trailer for a colossal gate.
Also, I have a request for
Corps Commander Hong Moo-seob.
Please reconsider the punishments
for me and Military Prosecutor Cha Woo-in
so we can re-investigate this case.
Salute.
Who the heck are you? You wench!
Don't come any closer!
Don't you dare come any closer!
It was Noh Hwa-young, wasn't it?
The one who cut your leg off.
And she's the one who ordered you
to commit perjury in court
six years ago
to get rid of CEO Cha Ho-chul.
Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
Don't tell me
you are going to hurt me who--
When we meet next time,
I will tell you
who I am.
This bullet was taken out
of the Company Commander's head,
who just had surgery.
From what I see, as a military prosecutor,
this is clearly a bullet,
not a fragment of a mine.
Yes, Minister.
Was I wrong to give you that position?
The issues with your son quieted down,
but now, your subordinate
caused a trouble.
I'm now doubtful about
if you're truly capable
of commanding a division.
I trust Lieutenant Colonel Won.
Didn't you watch the press conference?
If a superior cannot trust
their subordinate, then who would?
What?
Sergeant Koo was won over by Doh Bae-man,
who was displeased about his punishment.
Then what about the friendly fire?
And the bullet found during the surgery?
You know military prosecutors
can exaggerate cases
and make up evidence that does not exist.
Shut up!
I'll take all members
of the Patriotic Society to you tomorrow,
so stay right there, come up
with a solution, and report it!
I really cannot let it slide
this time, understood?
Who's that crazy red-haired wench?
Who on earth is she?
How come she knows everything?
How?
What nonsense are you talking?
I did everything you told me to do.
I even gave you
this leg of mine.
And I played dead when you told me to.
For the past 20 years,
I was like your dog.
Calm down.
I have a plan.
When you got rid of CEO Cha Ho-chul,
I took the lead
and lied in court.
And it was for you.
That's not all.
That truck accident
you caused 20 years ago.
The accident in which you hit that young
military investigator couple with a car.
Don't act like you don't know!
Because I remember it clearly!
Doh Bae-man said
that the only thing I did wrong is
doing what you told me to do.
That's enough.
Once you cross the line,
your fate will change.
All right.
I now crossed the line.
What are you going to do now?
We have stepped on a real mine now.
I will not self-destruct.
I will not die alone.
Because I got my insurance
in case this would happen.
You ungrateful bastard.
You, Noh Hwa-young,
Hong Moo-seob, and Lee Jae-sik…
I have a bomb that will blow all of you.
Now, your fates are up to me.
So,
use your brain
and find a way to save me. Understood?
Staff Judge Advocate.
Come to my office right now.
Salute.
Process the arrest
for Battalion Commander Won Ki-choon.
I know we have to
due to the circumstances,
but I'm worried
that it might cause you damage.
Lieutenant Colonel Won came and confessed
that it was all made up.
So everything told
at the press conference was true.
He's willing to be investigated.
And he asked me to help him protect
his last pride as a serviceperson.
I understand.
I'll have him arrested tomorrow morning,
with the minimum number of members.
And…
It's about the punishment
on Captain Doh and Captain Cha.
Maintain their punishments
regardless of the arrest.
You see, actually…
What happened is…
-Stop hesitating and spill it.
-Yes, ma'am.
Their punishments are already lifted.
What?
Corps Commander Hong Moo-seob ordered it.
He did it without telling me?
Yes, he came to the office of justice
and ordered it himself.
He said that Captain Doh Bae-man
and Captain Cha Woo-in
must be rewarded, not punished.
It looks like
he couldn't ignore the public opinion
formed due to the press conference.
I got it, so you can leave.
Yes, I will carry out your command.
Salute.
The arrest warrant will be out
tomorrow morning.
And he'll be put on the no-fly list.
Yes, sir.
Though your punishment is lifted,
send Subsection Chief Ahn
and Subsection Chief Yoon to the scene.
I will do so, sir.
You were impudent for disobeying me
and going around during your probation,
but the result is good, so…
Well, it can't be helped, right?
Thank you for believing me,
and I'm glad that you're fine.
It's because I'm flexible, that's why.
You know,
I could've stopped
the press conference until the end.
-But--
-I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Gosh, that little…
Subsection Chiefs Yoon Sang-ki
and Ahn Yoo-ra are on their way.
Now we can reveal someone who's
behind the case of the hero of mines.
But it seems like Noh Hwa-young
lowered her tail too easily.
She ordered the Staff Judge Advocate
to arrest him herself. I think so, too.
What if she's cut off her tail,
not lowered it?
He must be inside.
I think so.
Shall we just go in?
Damn it.
Good grief.
Damaging my pride for punishing
the military prosecutors is something
I can just let slide with my generosity,
but the incident with Won Ki-choon.
If that broke out
along with her son's trial…
Then she must resign immediately!
She always said that the direct boss
must be responsible
for the faults of the subordinates.
She dishonored
your graciousness, Minister,
when you even skipped her seniors
to make her a division commander.
And so many male generals resigned
because they were against it!
Minister, I'm worried
that the criticism may attack you.
That's right, Minister.
So, are you saying we must sack
the Division Commander?
She is shaking up
the Patriotic Society, too.
I will
only follow your decision.
Division Commander.
I told you to come up with the solution.
Tell me.
I will do as you command, Minister.
I will take my uniform off.
I do not have any regrets or fear
in taking responsibility
for what I said. But,
I will make this clear to you two.
Stabbing a junior and a fellow soldier
in trouble
in the back when not all of the truth
behind the case is revealed.
Do you call that a military spirit?
Noh Hwa-young, are you nuts?
How dare you behave
so impudently to a superior…
Salute!
Division Commander,
I have something urgent to report.
Say it.
Search Battalion Commander
Won Ki-choon is dead.
-Are you sure?
-I am sure.
Our military investigators
confirmed it just now.
How did he die?
We're not sure yet,
but we're assuming it's a suicide.
We found a revolver
owned by Battalion Commander Won
at the scene.
It has been more than a week
since the death
of Battalion Commander Won,
who became famous
as the hero of mines
that turned out to be fabricated.
After the three-day investigation,
there was no sign of murder,
and they only examined
the exterior of the body
as his family is against the autopsy.
Today's star is the icon of justice
who has the characteristics of a Doberman.
Gosh, Doh Bae-man, that doggone bastard.
As soon as I get discharged,
I'll kill you first.
He's Military Prosecutor Doh Bae-man.
Thanks to him…
New soldiers are not allowed to watch TV.
The truth that
could've been hidden forever…
You can't touch the remote control.
Be careful, okay?
You know I'm your direct superior, right?
Yes, sir.
This is my gift to you, our newbie.
What is this?
It's my soldier's notebook,
but I memorized it all.
Everyone's names, their service numbers,
the specs of guns,
and the levels of the Jindo Dog
DEFCON. Everything's in it,
so you memorize it within a week.
Memorize all of this?
I don't even know my service number.
Want me to give you a tip?
Don't stand out. Never stand out.
Then your military life will be very easy.
Follow me. I'll teach you.
Never wear the winter jacket in layers.
Never let it shown over your pants.
Never watch TV while cleaning your rifle.
Never lean on the lockers.
Never shine combat boots with fire.
Never go on your sleeping floor
without organizing the shoes.
Never do these
until you become a corporal.
But you can put a towel around your neck
once you become a corporal.
Never do this, never do that…
What is it that I'm allowed to do?
What about the phone?
Can I use my phone?
Yes, once you become a sergeant,
after your daily tasks are complete.
That makes no sense.
When I become a sergeant,
I will get rid of all of these,
so hang in there until then.
But you and I are only a few months apart.
That's true.
Here.
Always turn your head and smoke
in front of your superior.
It's okay when you're with me,
but be careful
when you're with other superiors.
But you can exhale smoke through your nose
once you become a private first class.
Forget it. I don't want to smoke.
Salute!
I was teaching the new soldier.
Are you Noh Tae-nam? You're
the Division Commander's son, right?
Wow, that's some background.
But here in GOP, we don't count that.
Everyone works hard and suffers equally.
I never asked you to count that.
What's your point?
What?
Look at the way he speaks.
I'm sorry, sir.
I will educate him properly.
Do it right.
You're responsible for his behavior.
You know it, right?
Yes, I know it, sir.
Hey, by the way, you…
You look pretty.
It's been a while
since we got a pretty boy.
Let's go!
How dare he touch my face? That…
Hey.
He might hear you.
Your military life isn't going to be easy.
What's wrong with that bastard's gaze?
Damn it.
Good job running
the office of justice without me.
Good job going around
outside the office without me.
I remember when you came in
through that door for Noh Tae-nam's trial.
You did expect
that I'd be back, didn't you?
I never doubted, even once,
that we were fated to fight together.
I told you back then
that I'd be your loyal hound dog.
You did.
Then did I fail to hunt Won Ki-choon?
You have failed.
That really hurts
when you actually say it.
Gosh, it hurts.
You should've made Won Ki-choon sit here.
You should've
made me sit there.
So, did you tell me to come here
so you could say
that I lost the game?
It's sad,
but I wanted to share
the end of our first hunt.
THE ACCUSED
We have a lot more bastards left
to bring to this seat.
Hong Moo-seob,
Lee Jae-sik,
Heo Kang-in,
Yong Moon-goo,
and…
Noh Hwa-young.
Yes.
I will try harder, Trainer.
But you know, hound dogs are
so aggressive that
even their owners cannot pet them easily.
No.
True hound dogs can only be petted
by their owners, not anyone else.
You said I failed to hunt
Won Ki-choon, right?
I have something to show you.
Follow me.
ITEMS CONFISCATED
FROM WON KI-CHOON'S RESIDENCE
Won Ki-choon wore bullet proof vests
when he went on search and patrol.
Such a coward wouldn't have been loyal
to Noh Hwa-young
without any kind of insurance.
That's my hunch.
You and your hunch again?
You really lack experience, okay?
To military prosecutors like me,
a hunch is
like big data built
through tons of criminals and cases.
Well, you've been a skilled
military prosecutor for five years,
so I guess that data isn't useless.
I really searched
his residence thoroughly.
You failed in the hunt,
but you brought a lot of trophies.
Now, use your hunch and pick out
any good possible clues.
I picked them out already.
Bankbooks.
DAHYUN AIRLINES
JIHWAN AUTOMOBILE
PARKING PERMIT
The car key is out of battery.
The car is being kept
in a long-term parking lot.
It seems like nothing,
but there must be something to it.
You learned a lot from my hunches, right?
Division Commander Noh is on her way
to be questioned as a testifier.
INTERROGATION ROOM
We will now begin.
Your name, official rank, and affiliation.
It's a formality.
Noh Hwa-young.
Major General.
Commander of the 4th Infantry
Division of the army.
It has been confirmed.
Thank you for your cooperation
with the investigation
on the suicide of Won Ki-choon.
Division Commander.
You brought a lawyer
for a simple questioning.
Do you have a reason?
You're rude.
Like you said, this is
a simple questioning.
Please be polite.
I only asked the reason.
You two prosecutors
broke the prosthetic leg
of your superior in court.
I'm here to prevent such an incident.
But you're the one overreacting to this.
That's enough. Please ask questions
related to the matter.
Military Prosecutors.
You were the last person
Won Ki-choon met before his death.
What did you talk about
with him in your office?
He confessed his crimes.
I told the Staff Judge Advocate,
so check with him.
Yes, ma'am. We will check
with the Staff Judge Advocate.
Did you secure evidence
of Lieutenant Colonel Won's confession?
Are you saying I should've recorded
my subordinate repenting
and asking for forgiveness in front of me?
Unfortunately,
such evidence does not exist.
Won Ki-choon's arrest warrant was
issued quickly thanks to me.
I didn't expect you to thank me,
but I didn't expect
to be treated like this.
What were you doing
at around 11:00 p.m. that night?
Why are you asking her that?
She is now being questioned as a witness.
It's okay. I can answer.
I got off early, because I was troubled
due to Won's confession.
And after that?
I went to the residence
and went to bed right away.
Why?
Can't you believe me?
Can you prove it?
Gosh, those jerks.
Please check the entry and exit records
of the division's guardhouse
and the military residence.
The entry and exit records of
the guardhouse can be easily fabricated.
We will check it.
Lieutenant Colonel Won
placed a silencer on his revolver
so the sound wouldn't be heard outside
when he committed suicide.
What do you think about that?
You don't need to answer that.
No.
I should satisfy
the military prosecutors' curiosity.
I'm sure that he didn't want
others to see him dead
right after he pulled the trigger.
He must've wanted
to delay it as much as he could.
I can understand him,
as a fellow serviceperson.
Don't you two?
What do you think about
Lieutenant Colonel Won Ki-choon's leg?
Someone who cut his leg off is in here.
That means it's either one of you two.
Which one is it?
It's…
you two, sitting in front of us.
This is interesting.
So you're saying our investigation made
Lieutenant Colonel Won Ki-choon…
Cut his leg off,
and made him die.
With a forced investigation.
Ask yourselves
if what he did
really had to be paid by death.
We should go now.
I'm sure Medical Officer Jo Soo-chan
cut Lieutenant Colonel Won's leg off.
Put Medical Officer Jo on the wanted list.
This is my tip for you two,
as a former prosecutor.
I need to talk
with the military prosecutors.
I'll be at your office soon.
Good job, Mr. Yong.
Salute.
No more questioning as a testifier.
She agreed to this one to show
respect for Lieutenant Colonel Won,
so I will not accept any more rudeness
even if it's for the investigation.
And after today, Mr. Yong, you should stop
coming into the interrogation room.
Didn't you give up on being a lawyer
when you became the CEO of IM?
I'm glad you brought that up.
I had something to tell Prosecutor Cha.
Giving you my business card,
I wanted to tell you
that the name "IM" will disappear forever.
Because I'll change
the name of the company.
The former CEOs Cha Ho-chul
and Noh Tae-nam
all ruined the reputation of IM
to the lowest.
I'm going to change
the shadows of the past.
Well, then.
Yong Moon-goo…
knows all about it.
Thank you for lifting my punishment,
Corps Commander.
Did you make an appointment
just to say that?
Gosh, I wouldn't have another chance
to talk to you like this.
You were just working hard
as a military prosecutor.
Keep up the good work.
Yes, sir.
I heard that you used to
be a military prosecutor, too.
That was 20 years ago, I think.
Stand straight, you bastard!
You bastard!
Lack of evidence!
Clear from suspicions!
Non-indictment!
You damn worm!
Hey, you bastard!
MILITARY INVESTIGATOR ID
DOH SUNG-HWAN
I will serve you with loyalty,
Corps Commander.
Madam.
Our next game is…
Corps Commander Hong Moo-seob.
There's one weird thing.
That his residence soldier changes often.
I can smell it already.
The foul stench of power tripping.
You're working like a servant
at the residence, right?
Don't you remember me?
Have you ever defended a victim
of power tripping before?
-Salute!
-Power is like a drug.
A drug that's even more
addictive than money.
All of those who bear a grudge against me
or harbor hostility toward me
must be all locked up
under my surveillance.
I'm sure you can do it, Prosecutor Doh.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee