THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION,
CREATED SOLELY FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES,
WITH NO INTENTION TO INCITE VIOLENCE
OR DISCREDIT ANY ORGANIZATION.
Who are you really,
Thicha Insaree?
What are you planning to do?
PHATCHAI
Come on. Answer me!
So, how did that audio clip get leaked?
Your voice was so loud and clear.
It must've been leaked from your side!
- Relax.
- How the fuck can I relax?
I couldn't get more bribe money from you,
and the audio clip
got leaked the next day!
What great timing!
You really think I did that?
When Mathee called you that day,
where were you?
At home.
- In my office. Alone!
- Are your sure?
Any listening devices
or cameras in the room?
Have you checked?
Mr. Mathee sent the sweets for you.
Phoo!
- Come here.
- Come here, bitch.
Get in there.
Hello.
They took Phoo in there.
Where's Uncle Chi?
I'll ask him.
Stay put. Don't do anything yet.
Yes?
Chi, you must act fast.
Yes, Ma'am.
- Ready?
- Go!
Who did you record my voice for?
Help me!
Help!
Wait.
Careful. Don't let anyone see you.
- Yes.
- Sak.
If things are not looking good, just run.
Looks like you two knew
you were being followed.
You're fucking paranoid.
What are you doing?
I can do anything.
I'm a police officer.
And if someone plans to get rid of me,
I won't go down alone.
Get a good look that way.
I'll go this way.
Yes.
What the fuck is this?!
- We need to run.
- Go! Run!
The fire department
will be here soon. So will the police.
Buss.
Who did you tell about this?
Who's helping you?
Buss!
Time to run!
I'll question this bitch myself.
Pick that cigarette up. It's your DNA.
Hey, wait!
He has a gun.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
What is all this, Ma'am?
Let's talk at home.
Fine.
But Thicha must come with me.
Whatever we're going to talk about,
however it ends up,
I love you.
There are reasons behind everything.
There are stories.
Talk nicely to each other.
How do you want to start?
Who are you?
What did my mother do?
Okay.
Let's start over.
Let's start with this hairpin.
Who are you?
Who are you,
Thicha Insaree?
Whose hairpin is this?
How are you related to them?
How did you get it?
You did say it's your mother's.
Who is your real mother?
Who is your mother?
I asked who the hell are you?!
My name is Phatchai.
I'm sick!
Depression.
Panic attacks.
I've been sick like this for ten years.
It all started from one night.
That night,
I flew back from England
and arrived home.
Instead of seeing my mom,
I saw a girl.
That girl was being carried away.
In that moment,
she used all the strength
she had left to grab this hairpin.
The thing is, this pin
fell right in front of me.
But the worst part
was watching her being brutally assaulted
and dragged away.
You can't imagine how bad
what I saw really was.
How horrifying it was.
And then there was my mother.
Usually, she was so well-dressed.
I don't even know
what fucking mess she was covered in.
I've had nightmares
about that night for years.
I tried to find answers
about what happened that night.
Those stains could be my mother's blood.
That must be my mother's blood,
all over your mother.
And…
When I was assaulted,
it…
It didn't hurt.
It was like
I had lost all feeling.
It didn't hurt
from the moment
I saw my mother in that pit.
It just felt like I was
dying,
but I didn't die.
There was no pain.
No exhaustion.
No hunger.
Nothing.
It was like
I wasn't human anymore.
No!
My mother
worked so hard for years,
saving up to bring me here.
She said
we'd have a better life.
We're about to be born again.
And it seemed like we had.
We had a bathroom in our bedroom.
I can even sleep here.
Everything was so clean and tidy.
I did my best
to endure,
even when your mother
hit me right here.
On my back.
She told me not to make a sound.
Yeah.
Don't make any noise.
If I did,
she'd hurt my mom.
So I stayed quiet.
I never made a noise.
But my mother died anyway.
My name is Ou Yi.
That hairpin
belongs to my mother.
Thicha.
Please don't do
what you did last night again.
You're pregnant.
Last night
was necessary.
Ou Yi…
Would you love me
more than you hate my mother?
That depends
on whether
you will let your mother's injustices
continue or not.
Your mother sends girls to Mathee.
That night, I tried to run away
because Mathee was about to rape me.
And last night, I had to risk everything
to help Phoo.
Your mother is a big agent
who traffics our people into Thailand.
Your mother
has done so many horrible things.
I don't know how many.
But what I do know is that
my mother
is now under the tree
in your mother's office.
I lied…
and I know it's unforgivable.
But I had to do it.
I never thought I'd fall in love with you,
but I love you so much.
No matter what you decide now,
I'll understand it all.
You have the right to choose.
But I won't stop what I'm doing.
I didn't do it for myself.
I did it so countless others
won't have to suffer the same fate as me.
My mother…
is now under the tree
in your mother's office.
Whether you will let
your mother's injustices
continue or not.
When will this be done?
If I'm doing it alone,
it might take two days.
Find someone to help.
Someone you can trust.
Yes, Ma'am.
But…
The room will be a bit messy for a while.
I had to leave this pile of soil here.
Once we get the bones, we'll put it back.
What?
Listen carefully, Buss.
Niwarin used to be an immigrant worker.
And Thicha is using a dead person's ID.
I'll send you
all the documents I can find.
You can see for yourself
who the hell they are.
I think this is
part of a bigger operation.
But we stil don't know
what the hell they're after.
Hello, Buss?
Buss?
I think it looks fine here.
It's empty now anyway.
Hi, Mathee.
Buss. Accident at the construction site.
Three dead, five injured.
- Thicha was the one who released the clip.
- Huh?
She worked with Phoo!
Force the answer out of that bitch.
Find out exactly what the hell they want!
Fuck you!
Sorry, there is no acknowledgement from--
They must have taken Phoo's phone away.
No one is answering.
Mae also told me
Mathee's house is quiet.
His car is gone too.
Does he have another safe house
we don't know about?
- A condo or…
- From how he dragged Phoo,
it doesn't seem like a condo.
It must be somewhere else.
I'll tell Mae
to ask someone from Mathee's firm.
Good, Uncle Chi. Keep us posted.
Wherever we have people,
- find out where Mathee is keeping Phoo.
- Right.
Another person who must know
is Bussara.
I'll try to get Phatchai
to call his mother.
Go ahead.
Sorry, the number
that you've dialed cannot be connected--
Phatchai didn't pick up.
Maybe he doesn't want anything
to do with me anymore.
Give him some time.
It's hard for him to process all this.
Right now, let's focus on
finding a way to help Phoo.
Where are you going?
Mathee's house.
His car isn't there,
but he might have parked somewhere else.
He must be somewhere.
You can't do that, Yi!
I can't just sit and wait.
Yi!
Thicha…
Who is…
Thicha, Dear?
And…
what did she
ask you to do?
Speak.
I told you to speak!
Change your clothes then!
Please don't do this to me.
Say that again.
Say it again. What did you say?
Please don't do this to me, Sir.
If you say that
in a Japanese schoolgirl outfit,
you would be so cute.
Don't you think?
Change your clothes.
Hurry, get changed.
Get changed.
And say it again.
Say it.
I told you to say it!
If you don't wanna say it,
go get changed.
Go!
Take it all off.
Now!
MRS. NIWARIN INSAREE
CERTIFICATE OF SURNAME CHANGE REGISTRATION
She really did change her nationality.
MISS WASSANA MEEBUNYANG
Her name is Ou Yi.
CERTIFICATE OF FIRST NAME CHANGE
THICHA
Thicha Insaree.
I've been busy looking up that word.
It means "the one who was born twice."
MISS THICHA INSAREE
MISS WASSANA MEEBUNYANG
Ou Yi?
You and Phatchai
will leave this place in no time.
Why do you care about what happens here?
A girl was about to be raped.
Stop!
She's just a maid.
A Maid
is a human too.
Human.
What are you trying to achieve
from all of this, Thicha?
I just want to be a good daughter-in-law
and make my husband happy.
How dare you lie to my son?
Phat.
When did you come back?
Thicha has been deceiving you.
All the things she told you,
her education and her work,
were all a lie.
She was nothing more
than a low-life alien.
She assumed the ID of a dead person.
Look. This girl is dead.
And this.
This is Thicha!
Thicha is Ou Yi.
Her mother is Yoaw,
your maid when I was in England.
Let's talk in the office.
Wait, wait. No. We can't.
Right now, my office
is so messy.
Sak is changing the fertilizer.
Phat.
Hey! Phatchai.
- Get out, Sak.
- Don't.
Go on.
- Uh, I…
- Keep working.
Go on.
If Mom told you
to dig the soil or whatever,
just do it. No need to go anywhere.
I said keep working!
Phatchai! What is this?!
Is her mother under that tree?
I asked you,
is the body of Thicha's mother under here?
What?! There's nothing like that in here!
Who told you this?!
Was it your wife?
You know she's a liar,
and you still believe her!
She doesn't even love you!
She never did!
She lied to you to get revenge on me!
- She never loved you!
- Then what did you do to her?!
What did you do to her?
Didn't you hear me?
Answer me.
She's just a low-life.
A little punishment,
and she acted all weak
and so fragile!
All weak?
So fragile?
A little punishment?
How was it little?
Beating?
Sending her to your friend to rape?!
You killed her mother
for protecting her own daughter.
Then, you stripped
half-naked in front of Sak
and burned your dress!
Yes.
Thicha didn't tell me.
But I know
because I saw it.
I was here that night.
I saw everything
but didn't understand what happened.
The only thing I know is that
it must have been horrible.
But I kept lying to myself
that it wasn't.
It wasn't horrible.
My mom is a good person.
I tried to find the reasons
and excuses for you,
why you did it.
And you know what?
Who has ever done anything to you?
Did they hurt you?
Why did you do it?!
Is it for me?
I don't know.
Now, tell me the truth.
The truth
has many sides to it, Phatchai.
Your version of truth and mine
are different.
You will never be able
to accept my truth
and what I did my whole life.
Just know that
what you are and have now
are the results of my efforts.
I went through a lot.
I did it for you, and for myself.
We can do anything for others.
But we shouldn't hurt anyone.
Let's do it this way.
I'll talk to Thicha.
We'll talk about all that happened.
And I'll ask her that
if the three--
No.
The four of us,
including my grandchild.
If we have to live with each other,
how should we handle it?
Money? Take it.
How much? You tell me.
Marriage certificate?
Have it.
I won't stop her.
But about what was done,
she must stop.
And then,
if you want to live with her in England
and never come back to see me,
I'm okay.
Let me see my grandchild sometimes.
The only thing Thicha wants
is justice.
Is that what you want too?
Yes.
You can start
making it right at this moment.
Where is Phoo, Mom?
You think that maid bitch
is more important than me?!
Mom.
You're blinded by love
and believe everything she says!
She'll send me to jail,
and you're helping her!
You want me to leave everything behind
just to save that alien bitch?!
- I am your mother!
- You need to stop now.
And admit you're wrong.
You ungrateful brat!
Why did I even have you?!
I'll fucking show something to you.
The Gossip Fanpage, at your service.
This is Buss.
Oh, hello, Ms. Buss.
I was about to give you a call.
About the audio clip, right?
Could your page
hold off the posts about this news?
I think someone is using AI to frame me.
I need some time
to clear it all up.
Yes, Ma'am. We'll post some news about
celebrities fighting in the meantime.
We can go with that for a few days.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Let's have dinner sometime.
Do you think
people really care about justice?
Celebrities fighting.
Actors breaking up.
Someone sleeps with another person.
Most people
don't pay attention to what they should.
You know what?
You made it so much easier for me.
What?
Phat.
Phatchai!
You choose it yourself, Phatchai!
How is that bitch?
Phoo?
Feeling good, I think.
But didn't say much.
Probably afraid I'll like her too much.
Bring her to my house tonight.
Hey, Buss.
I just had her. I'm not done with her yet.
Take a photo of her and send it to me!
Bring her to my house tonight!
What are you-- Hello. Buss.
Damn it, Buss.
Smile.
I'll just use filters then.
I'll be back, Dear.
Almost forgot.
I happen to be a collector.
Wait here.
Smile.
Smile…
If you don't, I'll make you.
Come on. Smile.
No one has ever smiled.
143 LAWYER MATHEE'S HOUSE
Phoo!
Are you in there, Phoo?
Open the door! Phoo!
BUSSARA
What?
Why don't we find the best solution
between a mother-in-law
and a daughter-in-law?
If anything happens to Phoo…
She's alive,
as you can see in the photo.
If you want to help her,
meet me at my house
alone.
I think Thicha's going to see your mother.
What did you say?
Where is Phoo?
I'll send you to jail, bitch.
You're a fucking illegal alien.
It's your fault!
I'm your mother-in-law.
Did your son really choose you?
Don't try so hard to save the world.
I'm not even the most horrible person
in this fucked-up world.
Thicha! I'll kill you!
Subtitle translation by: Anan Pratchayakul