(The Escape of the Seven: Resurrection )
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(All child actors were shot under supervision.)
System unlocked. Escape now.
Medusa is helping us.
Ki Tak, jump!
They survived.
Gosh darn it!
How dare you ruin my plan?
Medusa is among you.
Who is Medusa?
Who's the traitor?
(Episode 6)
Do Hyuk.
Do Hyuk!
Who dared to pretend to be on my side and tricked me?
Who lived off of me like a parasite,
enjoyed riches they didn't deserve,
and gained honour as they lived in luxury like a rat?
Who was it that rang the emergency alarm,
manipulated my tablet PC,
and saved Min Do Hyuk and Kang Ki Tak...
as if they knew no fear like a crazy psycho?
Who is Medusa?
Matthew, I...
only just found out about the existence of Medusa.
The same goes for me.
I don't want to hear that garbage!
Just find out who Medusa is!
Then, I'll let you live!
Nam Chul Woo, do something. You're a police officer.
Why should I have to do it?
Well...
What about testing the tablet PC for fingerprints?
If I get caught now,
all my plans will go up in smoke.
The people that Medusa wanted to kill were you and me.
Who among these people would want to kill us the most?
A person who might dream of revenge because of desperation and rage.
If I had been Medusa,
I would've already killed you.
It's not me.
Then,
what about the possibility that the tablet PC was hacked?
Hacked?
Thanks to Medusa, I found out Han Na's location,
and I also found out that Yoon Ji Sook was in trouble.
And how does Medusa know that?
I don't know.
All I know is that Medusa uses Save's server to contact me.
Save.
Hwang Chan Sung?
Did you just say "Hwang Chan Sung?"
Medusa contacted Min Do Hyuk using Save's server.
Then, Hwang Chan Sung is Medusa.
Save has criticized and talked badly about Chairman Lee...
since the very beginning.
It's also suspicious that they made...
Min Do Hyuk a national hero through a Save vote.
I am sure...
Hwang Chan Sung rigged the vote.
That's right. I'm sure Hwang Chan Sung is Medusa...
or on Medusa's side, one or the other.
What if...
Mone is on the same side as Medusa?
Among us, the person who's the closest to Save...
is Mone.
Indeed, you're the only person...
who'd come up with this kind of scheme.
You have lost...
your mom.
I don't know anything about Medusa!
But anyone could be the traitor.
Joining hands with the devil...
is something any of us would do, as long as it benefits us.
Don't trust me either.
Doubt over and over again.
Gosh! I'm so sick and tired of all the doubting!
Oh, this might also be...
Medusa's big picture.
An impure intention to split us apart.
Right.
The seven of us must stand united.
We can't be jerked around by Medusa,
whose identity we don't even know.
As Jin Mo said,
the tablet PC being hacked seems to be the most likely explanation.
We'd know if we do some digging on Hwang Chan Sung.
Han Mone.
This has been decided as your second mission.
Go and find out!
Whether Hwang Chan Sung is Medusa...
or just simply helping out.
If you don't find out,
you'll be the first to die.
And if Hwang Chan Sung is Medusa?
Of course I'll kill him!
Do Hyuk.
Are you awake?
Ki Tak, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm just a little sore.
How about you? Are you okay?
Ki Tak.
I'm sorry.
I only thought about wanting to meet Medusa.
I should've doubted it at first.
From the moment it said to come with you.
Don't blame yourself.
What's important is...
that Matthew also knows about Medusa's existence.
And we missed that.
It's okay.
What's this?
Oh, right.
The person who brought us here was Mr. Hwang.
You would've been in serious trouble if I had not gotten there in time.
Wait a minute.
How did you know to come to us?
That we were in an accident?
I guess I have to tell you.
I am...
Medusa.
Darn it.
Min Do Hyuk and Kang Ki Tak are already gone.
Darn, those lucky punks. All right.
Why didn't you...
discuss this matter with me?
That person called Medusa is targeting my life too.
I also have a right to know!
Are you still hanging around here to nag me about that?
I should try to avoid being killed senselessly.
Both you and I.
More people will go astray from now on.
That will never happen.
I will really start to push ahead from now on.
What do you mean?
Getting your hands on Save?
Before that, we have to make Yang Jin Mo the mayor of Seoul.
That way, we can get the development rights for the Gagok District.
Then,
even if Min Do Hyuk and Kang Ki Tak act like crazy punks,
they will never be able to beat me.
Why is the Gagok District...
so important?
That is...
You said...
to doubt over and over again.
Before we catch Medusa, I won't trust anyone.
You're Medusa?
You clearly said you weren't last time.
When did you know that we were back?
Why did you help us?
Do you know that Save's security program is installed...
on Matthew's system?
I'll answer your first question first.
I've been checking the facts on the Bang Da Mi case the whole time.
And when I found out that K appeared...
at the première event of the movie, "Dear D,"
I instinctively knew that you had returned.
That's because Matthew...
is K.
You knew?
About Matthew's real identity?
Everyone denounced Chairman Sim Yong's sincerity as a lie,
but I believed the Chairman's last words.
So,
I analysed Matthew and Lee Hwi So through Save's big data.
The result was a mismatch.
Why did you do all that?
Do you have some kind of resentment towards K?
This could be the answer to your second question.
I was once duped by Sim Jun Seok's lie.
What's certain is...
that we have the same goal.
K's...
death.
I will kill K with my own hands for sure.
I can do that without your help.
I'll answer your third question.
The person who passed Save's security program through Mone...
was me.
Of course, K thinks that Mone stole the security program.
That's for Mone's safety.
For her safety...
LUCA is a masterpiece of the century created by Lee Hwi So.
Taking away that kind of weapon from K...
is the way to save humanity.
LUCA's secret key.
You know it, don't you?
Now is the time for us to join forces and get LUCA.
So,
I'd like to scout you to work at Save, Mr. Min.
Won't you join me...
in fighting against Matthew?
(Beasts who deserve to die)
Min Do Hyuk, Kang Ki Tak.
After all I did to help you, you lost to Matthew like fools?
I warned you...
not to tell Kang Ki Tak.
But you believed the message that Matthew sent?
I don't need you two anymore.
I'll do it on my own.
Ki Tak.
How much do you trust Hwang Chan Sung's words?
To a certain degree.
If we join hands with Hwang Chan Sung,
we can get LUCA sooner.
Do you really think Hwang Chan Sung is Medusa?
I'm not sure about that.
I'm not sure either.
The fact that he was watching us...
and that he asked us to join forces...
Do you still think...
that Park Nan Young is Medusa?
The man who worked at the cemetery definitely said it was a woman.
She had a limp and had something...
wrapped around her face.
Anyway, what we know for certain...
is that she has something to do with Da Mi.
Do Hyuk, wait.
Could it be...
Why?
No, it's nothing.
Min Do Hyuk.
Why isn't he accepting my offer right away?
It's a golden opportunity to grab Matthew by the neck.
(Beasts who deserve to die)
(K, Han Mone, Cha Ju Ran)
(Nam Chul Woo)
(Yang Jin Mo)
(Go Myoung Ji)
I will destroy what's precious to you,
one by one.
For Matthew, it's Children Home and the Gagok District.
For Han Mone, it was your mom.
Next is Cha Ju Ran.
It's your turn.
Gosh, I can't stand this.
Matthew is the one who always causes trouble,
and I'm the one who cleans things up.
If it was going to be like this,
I should've been named president, not a mere director.
Look here! Drive carefully!
You're not supposed to drive here.
It is a nice car, though.
Ju Ran!
Cha Ju Ran.
This voice is...
Ju Ran.
I've missed you, honey.
("Escape")
It's dangerous here right now.
Everyone has gone crazy.
If you want to go,
go by yourself, Mom.
I'm going to stay here.
If you stay here, you'll die!
I don't know what it is, but everyone is possessed by something.
We have to run away.
Erica.
Mom!
Goodness, have you been a good girl?
Erica, the election campaign for the mayor of Seoul will begin soon.
Then, can you help Dad, Erica?
If it's for Dad, of course, I should do it.
Dad will be the mayor of Seoul, and I'll be a superstar.
Oh, just a moment.
You're No Han Na, right?
Yes, she is. She's No Han Na.
She lives with us in our house.
Can we take a picture with you?
My niece is a huge fan of yours.
- Let's take a picture. - I want to be in it too.
Come on. Let's take a picture.
One, two, three.
- One, two, three. - Why, that little...
Who does she think she is?
Two, three.
One, two, three.
Mom.
Can you lend me your shoes?
What? Why do you want my shoes?
Just give me them.
Ladies.
Gentlemen.
You're working so hard.
Have something to drink while you work.
- I think I broke my ankle! - Erica!
- Mom, it hurts so much! - Did you hurt yourself?
Where? Here?
Where does it hurt? Here?
I'm dying!
You can tell her ankle is broken.
- Take her to the hospital. - It hurts.
What about the shoot? Today's the first shoot of the movie.
We'll have to switch to a different actor.
But where will we find a child actor this instant?
Oh, Han Na.
I saw her running through Erica's lines with her earlier.
She's as good as any actor.
No! I'm going to do it!
I'm going to act!
Hey, No Han Na!
Don't you dare take my spot!
I won't let it slide!
Please help me out! We have to hurry!
Please help.
No, I'm going to do it!
It's mine!
Please watch Han Na for me.
Phillip! Let's go!
- Erica! Director! - Mom!
- Let's go! - Mom!
Do you have a reservation?
Mr. Kim Do Jin.
Are you a guest of Mr. Kim's?
She's with Mr. Kim.
Hello!
- Hello. - Hello.
Ju Ran!
Honey!
You're here, Mr. Kim.
Yes.
This is my wife.
I'm sorry I didn't know, ma'am.
I'll escort you to a private room.
Have a good time.
Since I'm with a special guest today,
please take extra special care of her.
Also, for our meal,
bring it in after ten minutes.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Please excuse us.
As soon as I saw you, I wanted to do this so much.
Stop that mouth.
I fell for it once, but not twice.
Ju Ran, you haven't aged at all.
You're so feisty.
It reminds me of the old days.
When we were together.
We danced like this a lot.
What are you trying to pull?
Goodness.
Why did you want to meet?
What are you after to show yourself again?
I'm a dreadful man.
This reaction of yours...
is only natural.
I asked to meet to give you this.
What's this?
The money I stole from you before our divorce.
With some interest.
(2 million dollars)
How many zeroes are there? One, two...
Two million dollars?
I regretted it so badly.
In order to come back to you, I worked like a dog.
My business in Dubai was a success.
I owe it all to you.
Don't you dare try to dupe me.
Stuff like this can easily faked.
Don't you know how things are now?
And me? I have a boyfriend.
A boyfriend?
What a relief.
I thought I'd hurt you so bad, you'd gone off men completely.
That means...
there's still hope for me.
What hope?
Hope that Ju Ran...
could become mine once more.
Ju Ran.
Let's get back together.
I started a construction company in Korea,
and I got a huge investment.
Soon in Gagok District...
Gagok District?
Oh, that's it?
You showed your cards too soon.
In exchange for just two million, how much will you take from me?
"Hope?" "Reconciliation?"
That's just stupid.
I really...
don't care about your money at all.
I have more than enough people...
who are willing to invest.
Whenever you're ready,
come and see me.
I fly out in three days.
I hope you don't wait too long.
I'd like to see your smile again.
Think about what I said and call me.
The likes of him can't run a business.
Come this way.
How are things with your ex-wife?
I wronged her so badly, she won't come round.
Oh, dear.
Where's my guest?
Waiting in the private room.
- Thanks. - Sure.
Wait. Excuse me.
The man who just went upstairs. Kim Do Jin.
Mr. Kim the CEO, you mean?
Yes. Mr. Kim the CEO.
I have business with him.
I'm so sorry.
Mr. Kim said he'd no longer meet with investors.
As general manager of this hotel,
I respectfully ask you to leave.
- I... - Escort her out.
Do you know who I am? Don't treat me like a peddler.
I'm Mr. Kim's...
wife. I'm his wife.
Oh, my goodness.
How insolent of me. I apologize.
Please don't tell Mr. Kim.
I'm very sorry.
I'm so very sorry.
He's in there.
This laughter...
Don't worry too much.
Geum La Hui?
What is she doing here?
It's perfect. So admirable.
Thank you.
You must keep this investment a secret as well.
From Chairman Lee too.
Don't you worry.
The list of investors will never get out.
We've done business before.
Just like last time, I guarantee a 300-percent profit.
I trust in you.
- Don't worry. - She has lost her mind.
Why is she holding my man's hand?
- Shall we leave, then? - Sure.
- Don't forget this. - Thanks.
After you.
Three hundred percent?
Yes.
(CEO Geum La Hui)
It's time to leave.
Thanks.
My skin looks so much brighter.
("Seoul City to Resume Redevelopment of Gagok District")
It must be somewhere here.
(Gagok District Investment Agreement)
"Gagok District?"
Gagok District.
That's where Bang Chil Sung died.
("Seoul City to Resume Redevelopment of Gagok District")
(Gagok District Redevelopment Site)
What he said was true.
How much is she investing?
(10 million dollars)
"Ten million dollars."
Ten million?
I forgot some papers. I'll be a little late.
Geum La Hui, that sly wench.
She'll make a fortune on her own?
I won't let you do that.
What are the results?
They found just your prints...
and no one else's.
- But... - But what?
There were signs that someone wiped it down.
They wiped their prints off in that short time?
Keep looking until you find something else.
- I don't care how long it takes. - Okay.
Wait.
Let's keep this between us this time.
Don't even tell Ju Ran.
Yes, sir.
If you bring me something good,
I'll consider promoting you.
Thank you. At your service.
At your service!
What are you doing here?
I was just passing by.
I said hi to the chairman.
What about you?
Aren't you on a break for a while?
Oh, well,
I had some sorting out to do at Children Home.
By the way,
we're meeting for dinner today.
I'll take you somewhere amazing.
Dress up nice.
Oh, no.
Something important came up.
Sorry. Cancel dinner for me.
I can't.
I rented out the whole place and paid for the full course.
You won't do something silly like propose, will you?
Goodness, how did you know?
Since it came to this, I can't wait any longer.
Darling.
Will you marry me?
I'll make you real happy.
I might become...
the Police Commissioner of Seoul.
It's beautiful. And the jewel is huge.
Whenever you're ready, come and see me.
I fly out in three days.
I hope you don't wait too long.
I refuse.
I'm leaving the country.
I won't live in fear as Matthew's dog forever.
Can't I live happily now?
Why are you suddenly doing this?
Are you...
seeing someone else?
I am.
Someone cool and capable.
Someone who doesn't know what I did...
and will make my life rosy.
This time,
I want to get a shot at a good life.
Forget witches like me, Chul Woo.
Darling. Ju Ran!
That girl...
will play my daughter?
Erica dropped out due to an injury.
Han Na's a genius when it comes to acting.
Do you hate it that much?
She memorized the script already.
The director gave the green light right away.
Because you abandoned me,
can you leave that easily?
Mone.
When did you get here?
It's your first shoot. I had to come.
As a surprise, I also brought a food truck.
I'm excited already.
Thank you.
- Take good care of Mone for me. - She's awesome.
- Help her out. - Thank you.
Is she the girl playing your daughter?
No Han Na.
Right? The girl from the news.
Yes. I think so.
I see the chemistry.
I thought this before too,
but that child looks oddly similar to you, Mone.
Her gaze especially.
What?
Thanks for driving me home.
I'd like to come in for some tea.
Next time.
Okay, then.
You must be tired. I'll hold back.
Excuse me.
What's your decision, Min Do Hyuk?
Your offer.
It'll turn it down.
You turned me down?
If that's what you say, fine.
Call me if you change your mind.
Darn it.
When did you get out of the car?
Just now.
Who was it?
It was just business.
I got boring news.
It's a shame to part like this.
Sorry.
I know you're a great guy,
but I'm not prepared.
It's not your fault.
I was hasty.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Get back safely.
Can I trust Chan Sung?
Yes.
He even gave me the security program.
I must trust him right now.
But...
what did Do Hyuk refuse?
- Long time no see. - Yes.
I was going to call you.
Who is this?
A guy I work with.
Don't mind him at all.
I'm Han Kyung Soo.
Yesterday evening, they all got together for a movie.
I don't know what movie it was.
- They watched a movie? - Yes.
But suddenly the alarm sounded, and it turned into a total mess.
What's important is...
that none of them fled or even left the room.
Do you remember what time that was?
The movie started at 7pm,
and that happened about 20 minutes in.
7:20pm.
System unlocked. Escape now.
Medusa is helping us.
Are you sure all seven were there?
Yes. I saw them myself.
Then one of them is Medusa.
There's one more thing.
Han Na will appear in Mone's movie.
Come on.
I know you're upset, but you must eat.
I don't want to eat!
I hate Han Na.
Why did we take in that beggar?
I lost my role to her and all the attention.
You're pretending to be pitiful on purpose, aren't you?
To steal my dad from me too?
Han Na. Leave that and get out.
No one will take your dad from you.
I hate how he's nice to her.
I hate how he only looks at her.
Mister.
I'm okay.
I see why Erica is upset.
Han Na.
I'm sorry.
I brought you here for my own selfish reasons.
No.
If I didn't have you,
I'd really be all alone.
Thank you.
I'll go read a book.
Don't you dare think of scolding Erica.
Even if it's you,
I won't put up with anyone who hurts my kid.
Even as an act,
can't you hug Erica or say something nice to her?
Is it that hard?
She yearns for your love. This is too cruel!
A father role was never part of the deal.
Han Na living with us wasn't part of the deal either.
Do you think I took her in because I liked her?
It was what you wanted.
Because she's the daughter of the woman you loved!
- Go Myoung Ji! - What, Yang Jin Mo?
You're not the only one who's holding back.
I'm holding back too.
So as much effort I put into caring for Han Na,
I want you to put into caring for Erica and Phillip.
What was the love we had?
Did you toy with me?
Did you use me?
Were you even worth...
Well, fine.
Let's say I toyed with you.
If that's what you want to hear,
I'll say it a thousand times.
This is your last chance.
If you go inside like this, you'll never...
see me again.
Can you live without me?
Will you be okay with that?
Will you?
- You were making a wish. - Yes.
I never took you on a decent date since we met.
Sorry.
In the future, let's go on a great date.
I'll treat you to a full course.
Get out of here.
Darling!
Why are you so darn cool?
I can't live a day without you.
Why couldn't I?
Our love wasn't that majestic.
You're a drug addict.
I swear I'm clean.
For you.
Did you? How commendable.
But I don't care.
Darling. Ju Ran!
Cha Ju Ran!
You can't do this out here.
- Leave. - Don't leave me!
Darling. Will you please explain?
Why are you doing this?
Honey, Ju Ran!
Ju Ran! I can't live without you.
- Please! - We'll call the police.
Calm down.
Cha Ju Ran is on her way up.
- Be prepared. - Okay.
I got it.
You're the woman who wanted to see me?
What do you want?
You need money, right?
Seduce Cha Ju Ran.
Get her life savings in a week.
Then you get a million dollars.
A million dollars? An actual million?
We have Yang Jin Mo,
the former Deputy Mayor for Political Affairs.
You recently stepped down as deputy mayor...
to run for office as mayor.
Is it true you'll run as an independent candidate?
Yes.
The mayor who appointed me ended up losing his job,
and joining a party...
to take his place just didn't seem right.
Isn't it because you weren't sure any party would nominate you?
No.
I think the mayor should be a servant to his people.
I will not be loyal to any party.
Can I ask you an aggressive question, then?
Sure.
Seoul National University...
law school professor Choi Mi Nam is your opponent,
and he raised the issue...
that you only have a middle-school diploma.
Would you like to refute that?
No, I don't.
My family was poor, so I dropped out of high school.
I joined the workforce earlier than most.
Is that illegal?
Does that disqualify me as a candidate?
I was an entertainer, a so-called clown.
But unlike someone else, I don't use an SNU degree...
to pathetically beg for votes.
I like your spirit.
I guess that must be why this person fell for you.
Let me introduce our secret guest.
Come on out.
Honey.
Are you surprised?
I saw you off this morning, and I'm still pleased to see you.
My dear wife Go Myoung Ji.
Welcome.
- Thanks for inviting me. - We're honoured.
Hello.
You used to teach high school art.
Yes.
Our viewers would love to hear exactly how you fell in love.
Who proposed to whom?
He proposed to me.
She had to be exhausted as a single mom of twins,
but we volunteered together,
and when I saw her care for the orphans so lovingly,
it was love at first sight.
(I love Yang Jin Mo)
- Thank you. - Good job.
You put on a good act.
So did you.
What are you doing here?
I'm here...
to support Yang Jin Mo, the future mayor of Seoul.
Did you identify Medusa?
We'll know in due time.
Can you...
excuse us?
When you become mayor,
make Gagok District a government-run project.
So TIKITAKA can buy the land for a dollar per every 3.3m².
You can do what you want with the budget.
Do you think that's even possible?
That's why I'm trying to make you mayor.
Before the public bid,
I'll make up a lie that TIKITAKA's the company...
to build a futuristic city.
What's your plan for this place?
I'll make the world's best data center complex.
A data center complex?
TIKITAKA, Save, Sungchan.
The data of all the country's major companies...
will be here.
Then I'll have all the information and power.
It's the dream my father couldn't realize.
How about working with me on it?
I'd be honoured.
Once I get what I want,
you and that kid will be gone forever.
Do you think I'll be satisfied with becoming mayor?
I'll go further and higher.
So you can never touch Han Na.
I want to withdraw every cent.
- I'm in a rush. Hurry up. - Okay.
- It was all deposited. - Okay. Thanks.
Thanks for doing business with Euddeum Bank.
(Receipt)
You'll lose a great deal if you sell so urgently.
It's none of your business.
Let's sign the contract fast.
(Contract of Property Sale)
That's it?
You're a small-scale business.
More.
Are you sure you can handle it?
(Standard Loan Contract)
I have the money. 30 million dollars in total.
Thirty million?
Darling.
Did you forget what I said last night?
I can't take more than ten million.
It's me, not just any investor.
Will you take it all?
Where did you get all this money?
The bank, people I know, even loan sharks.
I went everywhere I could.
Right.
I even maxed out the cash loan on my credit cards.
Why did you go to that extent?
I really don't want to spend your money.
You wanted us to get back together and leave the country.
Take the money and make me a profit.
You promised a 300-percent return.
Don't worry.
Let's throw a party.
We should have some fun.
Come on.
- You, wait right here. - Okay!
I'll get some champagne and snacks.
Okay.
Thirty million dollars?
Ju Ran will do anything for money.
She even went to loan sharks.
- Good job. - But...
now I'm thinking the one million dollar pay...
is a bit too little.
Can you give me a little more?
You're a mere insect wanted by Interpol.
I smuggled you into the country.
Do you have a death wish?
What did you say?
Are you out of your mind?
You're a piece of trash...
and even a cent is a waste on you.
What's going on?
The money. Take it all.
What are you doing?
What do you think...
Hey! Stop where you are!
Hey! You!
My pay!
A million of that is mine!
("The Romantic Future Seoul Mayor and Single Mom of Twins")
(Candidate Yang Jin Mo and wife Go Myoung Ji...)
The photo came out so nice.
I owe you all a great deal.
Please don't hesitate to ask if you need our help.
We're ready to support you.
I'll leak some positive stories on mom blogs next week.
Thank you so much.
I'll invite you to a luncheon soon.
I have cars ready for you, so please use them.
- Thank you. - No problem.
Take care.
Please write a lot of good stories about us.
Now, let's check who the popular mayoral candidate is.
(Mayoral Candidate Popularity Poll)
(Citizens cannot understand the election pledges...)
(Sixth place: Yang Jin Mo)
What happened?
What?
This is impossible.
Where are they hiding it?
(Deokseon Appliances)
(No to redevelopment)
How did you know Hwang Chan Sung would show up here?
Someone tailed us...
after we met with Hwang Chan Sung.
I'm certain that he's searching...
for Lee Hwi So's flash drive.
He almost fooled me.
The person who passed Save's security program through Mone...
was me.
Of course, K thinks that Mone stole the security program.
That's for Mone's safety.
It wasn't for Mone's safety.
He's trying...
to take advantage of Mone.
I'll be right back.
Do Hyuk.
Are you thinking of seeing Mone?
Mone has to know...
what kind of person Hwang Chan Sung is.
He approached us acting like he was Medusa.
It means he's plotting something big against Mone.
I also have to check on something.
I'll call you.
(Deokseon Appliances)
Hello?
It's Min Do Hyuk. Where are you right now?
Why do you care?
Let's meet right now. I have something important to say.
Did the suite room guest go somewhere?
They already checked out.
That's impossible. We're supposed to meet here.
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message...
Could you call the general manager? Please hurry.
You know, the man with the funny moustache?
It's against our hotel policy to have a moustache.
Hurry up and call the general manager now!
Hurry it up.
Tell them to come now!
My goodness.
Call them!
May I help you? I'm the hotel's general manager.
You're not the general manager. Call the real one.
To avoid disturbing other guests,
shall we speak somewhere else?
That...
That's impossible.
What?
Geum La Hui?
Please keep this new investment a secret.
Even from Matthew.
Let's get back together.
Soon in Gagok District...
Gagok District?
(Gagok District Investment Agreement)
"Gagok District?"
Geum La Hui plotted everything.
Geum La Hui...
Geum La Hui!
Open the door.
We received a report of drug use.
We're going to force it open.
(Nam Chul Woo)
Nam Chul Woo,
you're under arrest for using drugs.
Thank you for cooperating.
- Let go! - What are you doing?
You punks. Do you know who I am?
I'm a detective.
Sure. I'm a detective too.
- Get him. - Okay...
Okay...
I'm a detective... Cha Ju Ran, my love...
Ju Ran...
Are you sure you're okay?
Are you absolutely sure?
I told you to mind your own business.
I'll be doomed if I get involved with you.
Watch out for Hwang Chan Sung. He's a dangerous man.
To me, you're the most dangerous.
My mom wouldn't have died if it hadn't been for you.
You saved Han Na. Why didn't you save my mom too?
You said Medusa contacted you.
Why didn't you save her?
Why didn't you?
(Thank you once again for protecting Han Na.)
Thank you once again for protecting Han Na.
I thought leaving Mone and Han Na...
would be the best for my daughter and granddaughter.
Will you please stay out of my life?
You got me in a huge mess.
Please, just leave me alone!
Just stay out of my life!
I'm sure there will be a chance to see Han Na and Mone again.
I'll look forward to that day.
Mom...
She came to see me...
She came to see me before leaving.
What have I done?
What have you done to Mom, Mone?
Thank you...
for handing my mom's last letter to me.
(Chan Sung)
Yes, Chan Sung.
What are you doing right now?
I'm taking a quick walk in front of my home.
I'll read scripts too.
I see.
On your own?
Yes.
Do you want to have dinner together?
You won't decline again, will you?
Sure.
Where should I meet you?
Okay. See you later.
Don't go.
If you go, break it off with him.
Mr. Hwang,
Ms. Han Mone is here.
It took you longer than I thought.
Was it difficult to find?
There was a bit of traffic.
I see.
Dinner's already set.
Come with me.
Are you afraid of me, Mone?
You're shaking right now.
Of course not.
Maybe it's because it's chilly out.
Let's hurry up and eat.
I hope to set some rules between us from now on.
No lying.
And...
No to meeting Min Do Hyuk.
He's a very dangerous person.
Let me ask you one more time.
Who were you with earlier?
I'll ask you for the last time.
Why...
did you meet with Do Hyuk?
Were you tailing me?
That doesn't answer my question.
All right.
Let me repeat the rules. One...
Get up.
La Hui!
You...
Are you...
Medusa?
You are, aren't you?
You're Medusa, right?
Answer me!
It's you!
What are you thinking to have started this?
Why did you approach Do Hyuk?
How did you get the information from Save?
Why do you care if I'm Medusa or not?
You should go on your way,
and I will mine.
What are you thinking, La Hui?
Don't tell me...
you saw Da Mi's video that day.
I mean the last record of Da Mi...
that K had.
I'm being punished.
Punishment for what I did to my daughter.
La Hui.
Don't touch me.
I don't need your help.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm the heartless...
Geum La Hui.
(Beasts who deserve to die)
(Cha Ju Ran)
Is this working?
Hi, Mom and Dad.
I was going to call you,
but I figured you might want to see me.
Look. I'm doing well over here.
I'm eating well and sleeping well,
so now my cheeks are chubby.
My mom here is a great cook.
Even yesterday,
she made me stir-fried anchovies and braised beef.
They were so delicious.
Now that you know,
you can stop sending me food.
My mom is a really cool person.
She works hard, and she's passionate.
I wish I could be more helpful,
but for now, I still fall short.
However, I promise to become a daughter who is loved.
Right, the aquarium.
Thank you so much for that.
I'm so happy to have little siblings.
You can stop worrying about me now.
I want the two of you to take care. Okay?
You believe me, don't you?
Geum La Hui,
you don't have the right to cry.
You have no right to punish.
You have no right to live.
You don't even deserve to die.
You...
You're not a human.
(Beasts who deserve to die)
(K, Han Mone, Cha Ju Ran...)
(Geum La Hui)
(Thank you to Jang Hyuk Jin and Kim Hyun Wook...)
(for their special appearance.)
(The Escape of the Seven: Resurrection)
Geum La Hui is Medusa.
She plans to ruin all of us.
She has our twins!
Geum La Hui and Hwang Chan Sung are planning something.
If you keep breaking the rules,
you don't know what I'll do.
Your mom died because you neglected her.
Let me kill Geum La Hui...
with my own hands.
Are you hiding?
I came all the way here in person.
You can look forward to it.