I know your obsession is to hand the evidence
to someone who can punish him,
to overturn the Su family's case,
and restore your father's reputation.
What is the meaning of this, Vice Minister Zhou?
General Xie, my servant reported that rebels infiltrated the building.
I was worried about Miss Adeng's safety,
so I brought my men here.
You come in alone.
All of you, step down.
Adeng.
What are you standing there for?
Hurry up and get rid of this evil ghost!
An official must keep his original intention,
be upright and honest,
so as not to fail the people's trust.
We must replace the guards at these border fortresses
with our own men.
Once our power completely infiltrates the imperial court,
the world will be in our pockets.
Don't worry, Master.
I have already taken care of it.
The Ministry of Revenue's military pay and provisions
are entirely under our control.
All supplies and personnel transfers
are completely at your command,
without any deviation.
Wanniang, I have stumbled upon a shocking conspiracy.
They won't let me go.
Remember, an official must keep his original intention,
be upright and honest,
so as not to fail the people's trust.
You must live well.
By imperial decree, we are here to search the corrupt traitor Su's residence
and execute everyone in the family!
Miss, go!
I want to make the last trace of the Su family
completely disappear from this world.
You all must die!
The Su family's grievances have finally been cleared.
Wanniang didn't let you down.
Mr. Su's lifelong reputation for honesty has been preserved,
but justice still came late.