Hahaha.
The matter at the Liu residence was botched.
Not a single weasel found out the true nature of the Soul Lantern.
Spare me, My Lord.
I already have a countermeasure.
I will use the vengeful soul of Su Wanniang as bait
to lure her into the trap.
She will definitely be consumed by the resentment,
deplete the spiritual power of the Soul Lantern,
and disturb her and Xie Jingchen's peace.
Su Wanniang is the daughter of the imperial censor
who discovered our plot back then.
Remember,
your life is in my hands.
If you mess up again this time,
I wouldn't mind letting you
end up like that old man from the Su family.
General Xie, please save me,
save my whole family.
Vice Minister Zhou, speak plainly.
Don't dirty my eyes with these gold and silver items.
Something happened at the Yanyu Pavilion in the city.
The pavilion's top courtesan, Su Wanniang,
refused to submit to me a few days ago
and burned herself to death in her room.
But since then,
any woman wearing red
is haunted by resentment.
If this continues,
my whole family will die.
You forced a civilian woman to death for your own selfish desires,
and you dare to come asking for help?
Men, arrest this scum who treats human life like dirt.
Wait.
Why are you stopping me?
I'll go to the Yanyu Pavilion case.
The Soul Lantern reacts.
In Su Wanniang's obsession,
there might be clues related to my background.
If I find out you're lying even a little,
I'll directly strip you of your official position
and send you to the government office.
Thank you,
General, for sparing my life.
General Xie, you're finally here.
It's too weird in there.
Several girls fainted right after entering that room on the second floor,
and no one dares to go up again.
Wait for me outside.
Thank you for saving me, miss.
May I ask who you are
and why you are here?
I am Qinghe
from Yaowang Valley.
I noticed a trace of resentment outside Yanyu Pavilion,
so I was looking for the source in this room.
I didn't expect someone to barge in.
I am Adeng.
Thank you for saving me just now.
I'm also here for this.
Ah.
Help me.