♪Hey, why is it happening♪
♪My heart is racing♪
♪The world has fallen silent♪
♪Hey, when I imagine you♪
♪What kind of look♪
♪Attracted me to you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
=Love Me, Love My Voice=
=Episode 32=
(I bought an apartment
next to the studio.)
I will not lie to you.
Qiang Qingci won't lie
to Shengshengman either.
♪Hey, why is it happening♪
♪My heart is racing♪
♪The world has fallen silent♪
♪Hey, when I imagine you♪
♪What kind of look♪
♪Attracted me to you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
(Two years later)
(The ending of this story is a bit long.
Are you ready?)
- What are you looking at? Your studio again?
- You scared me.
No. This is our recording studio.
This is the registration form.
Everyone, please fill it out.
Our dubbing class this summer
has a total of 60 trainees.
And you are the last batch. Welcome.
- Off Key.
- Mr. Zhou Zheng.
You and Xiyou go sort out this material
and print the schedule in the afternoon.
These new trainees
are all in your care now.
- Okay? Go ahead.
- Just rest assured.
- You should take good care of newcomers.
- Don't worry. Leave it to me.
Come on, everyone. Fill out the form.
If you have any questions, just ask me.
- Alright?
- Okay.
I've prepared red date tea for you all.
You can take your time.
Before the third year of Tianqi,
I lived in the heart of Shu.
Until one afternoon a few months ago,
a child delivered a folding fan
and a place name to me.
I remembered that fan.
I would never forget it in my lifetime.
Feishao, you need
to re-record this part.
Alright. Come out and have some water.
I'll tell you what the problem is later.
Okay.
Take a look at this notification
for a commercial dubbing this weekend.
I can't do the weekend.
I'm working overtime.
- Zhou Zheng, are you free this weekend?
- I should be. What's up?
- Then you'll be the director.
- Okay. Leave it to me.
The actors this time
are all from other studios.
Only a few newbies are from our studio.
I'll feel more at ease with you there.
- Okay. No problem.
- Then I'll put you in it.
- Sheng.
- Happy early...
- Graduation!
Thank goodness you came quickly,
or the pretending couldn't go on.
- Come on.
- I don't know how to open it.
Are you still surprised?
I was wondering why you guys ignored me,
as if you didn't see me at all.
- How is that possible?
- Here, Sheng.
Thank you.
- The Golden Piglet enters the society now.
- Bravo!
Now that you're a member of the society,
you need to act like one.
Sheng, you should carry him home tonight.
Mo was planning to sneak on anyway.
Don't expose him.
It's just a graduation celebration.
Don't make it look like a wedding night.
- Tone it down.
- Be gentle, will you?
- Cheers?
- Okay. Cheers!
- Let's all wish Sheng...
- Happy graduation!
Thank you.
- Let's cut the cake.
- I want some cake.
- It's quite strong.
- Come on.
Help yourself.
- I still need half an hour.
- It's okay. Keep working. I'll wait.
Everyone, hurry up and eat.
After we finish recording this part,
Feng Yasong has to go on a blind date.
Don't make him late.
What? Given Feng Yasong's look,
he can't even find a date himself?
- I can't believe it.
- Exactly. He is not that bad, right?
The blind date was arranged
by my landlady.
She is over 90 years old.
I don't want to make her upset.
Shouldn't you wear a shirt, then?
It'll make you look a bit more formal.
Isn't it just going to be
a regular meal?
He is dressed like this on purpose,
afraid that his date will fall for him.
Alright. Stop talking about me,
as I'm the easy target here.
Let's get to work.
Feng,
I've prepared a suit for you in Room 2.
It's ironed. Go and change.
- That won't be necessary.
- Go change.
You are the only single man
among the Top Three.
Try to look good on the blind date.
Formalism? Okay, then I'll go change.
- You look good. Who are you going to see?
- I've said it many times. I'm leaving.
Come back.
This shoulder bag
doesn't go with your outfit.
Just take your cellphone with you.
- I'm leaving.
- Take a cup of milk tea with you.
Are you sure?
By the way, Doudou,
- Mu has a favor to ask.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- We are friends. Just say it.
My company is
organizing a pairing activity
for singles this afternoon.
Men can bring a girlfriend
if they have one, so...
What are you doing?
Do you want my partner
to pretend to be your girlfriend?
Yes, that's what I'm asking.
Sure, I'm free today anyway.
Who says you're free?
We've just recruited some trainees,
and there is a training class and such.
There's a lot to be busy with.
Doudou didn't say no. You...
That's right. Mu can't go alone, right?
Am I not a friend to you?
No. It's just that she is a single girl.
And you guys...
Never mind. Do whatever you want.
I'm leaving. It's too sweet.
You...
What's wrong with him?
- Do I need to prepare anything?
- Xiyou, have some milk tea.
Just change into something formal.
- Thank you for agreeing to do that.
- When did you buy these?
I'm not very familiar
with my female coworkers.
It's okay. We're friends.
There's no need to be polite.
Rest assured. I will change into
something nice. I won't embarrass you.
I-It's not necessary.
Why are you back?
I'm back for the car keys.
It's getting late. I'll drive there.
You don't have to do anything.
We'll leave after a while.
I'm leaving now.
Are you coming back?
I will come back after the date.
Don't wait for me for dinner.
Actually, I don't really want to go,
but I have no choice.
- Then send me the time later.
- I'm really leaving.
Just go ahead. Aren't you in a hurry?
And drive slowly.
Goodbye.
- Come on.
- Happy weekend!
- How do you know Mu?
- Yeah, tell us all about it.
- We just...
- Are you a cosplayer too?
- Yes, I am.
- No wonder. That explains it.
- Right.
- They're such a good match.
- Mu is nice. He just doesn't talk much.
- Right. Just be more patient with him.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- How long have you known each other?
- Why are you so curious?
- Let's eat.
- Okay. Let's eat.
(Where are you? What are you doing?)
Would you like to eat something?
Okay.
(Seafood)
I'm sorry. Honestly,
I came as I didn't want
to disappoint my landlady.
You can order whatever you'd like today
and consider it my treat.
- I got it. So you have a girlfriend?
- How could that be possible?
If I had a girlfriend and still came,
what kind of person would that make me?
Then you...
I don't know either.
Maybe I'm just destined
to be alone.
Well, let me see.
King crab? Or maybe a lobster?
Are you starting
with the expensive items?
Having you come all this way,
I should treat you something nice.
A steak will be fine.
- Who chose this place? It's nice.
- Okay.
- Then, hurry back.
- Come back soon. We're waiting for you.
If not, let's watch a movie.
(Dear friends, after saying farewell
to tonight, we'll reunite in the spring.)
(Here, a 5,000-year-old dream
glimmers and blooms resplendently.)
- (This is our 5,000-year-old home.)
- Feng Yasong?
- (It's prosperous and full of life.)
- Why didn't you go home for the Festival?
I only have one day off this year.
And I have to be on call. I'm staying.
It's quite a meal you ordered today.
- The Spring Festival is once a year.
- So I'm lucky to catch this.
You are here in time. How about we
celebrate the Spring Festival together?
Okay. Wait for me to get a cup.
- Cheers!
Cool.
So,
do you have a secret girlfriend or not?
If I had a girlfriend, I'd make it public.
Why would I have a secret relationship?
Well, it's quite funny for both of us.
We are pretty good-looking,
yet we have been single until now.
You had a few suitors, and they were good.
Why didn't you accept them?
I had no feelings for them.
Feelings are too elusive, aren't they?
Only you girls believe in them.
Feelings are important
in a relationship, alright?
Feelings are not reliable.
They might come, and they might leave.
Hurry up. It's the countdown.
Come on. Come on.
- Five! Four! Three! Two! One!
- Happy Chinese New Year!
I drank a bit too much.
I'll go home now.
- Can you do that?
- I...
Sure.
Then, take care.
I'll clean this up.
No need. Let me do it. I can do it.
Okay, then I am leaving.
I'll come back tomorrow morning.
Let's have breakfast together.
Okay.
- My cellphone.
- Here. Take it.
Then, I'm off.
- Goodbye.
- Take care. Let me know when you're home.
- Okay.
What's wrong? If you don't like this,
I can take you home first.
Not at all.
Your coworkers are all quite funny.
I probably didn't get enough rest
yesterday. I'm a little tired.
- I thought you were upset.
- No.
I wonder
how Feng Yasong's blind date is going.
He's finally decided to find
a girlfriend. He should take the chance.
Dates introduced by acquaintances
are more likely to work out
as they know each other better.
Don't worry.
That's good.
You are quite experienced.
It's what others say.
I'll go in first.
I'll be there soon.
(Mo Bai)
- Hello?
- Hello, this is Feng Yasong.
- Is everything okay with Doudou?
- What could possibly go wrong?
Going out with one of our own people
is the safest.
- Alright. I'm hanging up now.
- Wait. She...
Is there something urgent?
You seemed pretty anxious
when you were paying the bill.
If you have something urgent,
you can go first. It's okay.
I do have something urgent. I'm sorry.
If your friends' or relatives' children
need medical attention in the future,
you can tell me.
- I have to go now. Bye.
- Bye.
You and Mu
look better and better together.
He's never mentioned having a girlfriend
when he's at school.
We always thought he was single.
- We're usually busy, so...
- I understand.
Is he your friend?
He is
my younger brother.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Why didn't you respond
to my WeChat messages?
You sent me WeChat messages?
I didn't check my phone.
Why didn't you answer my call?
Would you come over so quickly
if I answered?
Your brother really cares about you.
You must love him a lot.
Let's hurry up and leave
before it starts raining heavily.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
- Doudou, you have worked hard today.
- What's hard about being with you three?
- I'll sit in the back row.
- Why?
Mo Bai, come in.
Why are you jostling for the back row?
I can't believe him.
What?
Why are the two of you here?
To watch the show?
I...
Feng said he's worried about you.
He insisted on coming to have a look.
I am not 'single' today.
What's there to worry about?
You're too deep in character.
Mu didn't take it seriously. You did.
- What's the attitude? I'm your sister.
- Who said you were my sister?
Haven't you been calling me that
for so many years?
I came to pick you up,
and you didn't even thank me.
Thank you. Alright?
Childish.
They two...
Let's go as soon as
we get out of the car.
It smells good.
- Bring over the tomatoes for me.
- The tomatoes?
Careful. It's hot.
Check my phone for me.
Is it the hospital?
It's Mu. He said Doudou didn't eat well
tonight, and we should cook her share.
I guessed it.
You could even guess this?
Open the refrigerator.
Take out the breaded pork chops in it
- and the vacuum-packed steak.
- Okay.
- Then...
- It's okay. You can keep my phone.
Keep an eye on my messages and calls.
If it's from the hospital, let me know.
So transparent?
Aren't you afraid I'll look?
Feel free to look.
Okay.
You haven't told me how you knew
Doudou didn't eat well tonight.
Maybe you'll know in a moment.
Wait. Don't go in yet. Come over here.
What's up?
I've been putting up with you.
I've been putting up with you all day.
What did I do
to make you put up with me?
You know what you did.
- Did I mess up your blind date?
- No.
You pretended to be other's girlfriend.
What's wrong with that?
I was willing to.
Besides, it's none of your business.
D-Didn't you say I was your brother?
Of course, I have a say in this.
- Wait a moment.
- Stop it. I'm tired.
You thought it wouldn't be tiring
to eat and drink with strangers all day?
I told you not to go,
but you insisted on going.
Mu and Mo Bai are my friends,
and they simply asked for a favor.
Besides, I have nothing better to do
this afternoon.
You can tell me if you want
to go somewhere. I can accompany you.
Feng, have you forgotten
where you went this afternoon?
- I can't believe you.
- Wait.
I haven't finished yet.
Why are you in such a hurry?
- Go inside if you have anything to say.
- There are other people inside.
- What can't we say in front of others?
- I...
Sheng.
I saw you two coming back.
I wanted to get something from the car.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Then we'll go inside first.
- Okay.
Welcome back.
- Have you eaten?
- Yes, I have.
I guess you didn't eat enough.
How about we eat some more together?
Mu said that Doudou didn't eat well
and asked me to make more food.
There were too many people.
I was just busy talking.
He really cares about you.
Sheng.
You should've told me to get the drinks.
It's okay.
We heard you two quarreled,
so we dared not let you get them.
- No, we didn't.
- Right, we didn't.
- We are getting along just fine.
- Who is getting along with you?
- Don't touch me.
- Well...
So you went to
pick her up after your date?
Yes, I picked her up on the way.
That's right. Mu and Mo Bai
were supposed to come back with us.
But they got off just before we arrived.
Right.
- The four of us came back together.
- Yes, together.
You two are quite in sync today.
You quarrel and make up quickly.
We didn't quarrel.
Well, I'm going to wash a few cups.
I will help you.
Did Feng Yasong get jealous
because he likes Doudou?
- When did it begin?
- I don't know.
- Are you keeping from me again?
- I really don't know.
Well, it was just a hunch.
I've known them for too long.
I can sense if something is off.
When was the earliest time
you sensed it?
It was on the first day
of the Chinese New Year.
I saw them have breakfast in the studio
when I came back from working overtime.
It should be that time.
No need. I'll wash these.
Don't tell people
that I'm your younger brother anymore.
I have been calling you that
for so many years.
Then don't do that starting today.
Did you hear me?
Give it to me.
Starting now,
if you call me your brother again,
I'll get mad at you.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
I'm scared of you, alright?
Give me.
Why are you smiling at me?
I'm not Gu Sheng.
Perhaps you know better than I do
why I'm smiling at you.
I...
You have something to say?
Even if you have something to say,
it's no use telling me.
I don't have anything to say.
Even if I do, I won't say it to you.
Smart choice.
Aren't there bowls outside?
Why do you get more?
They're for drinking soup.
Here come the bowls.
Okay.
You went away for a long time.
My grandma often makes
borscht during the Spring Festival.
It goes perfectly with rice.
Like this?
Thank you.
Let me serve you some.
You can also soak the rice in it.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Eat it while it's hot.
Come on, get ready.
Smile. Three, two, one.
One more. Three, two, one.
Okay, it's my turn now. Come on.
- Wait a moment. I haven't finished yet.
- Hurry up and help me take a picture.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Why did you two start hugging?
Just hurry up and take the picture.
Okay. Three, two, one.
- I'll take a wide shot for you guys.
- Okay, be quick.
Three, two...
Which one is your boyfriend?
Today, we can finally
meet your boyfriend.
Both of them look pretty good.
- What brings you here?
- I came to see you.
- Congratulations on graduating!
- Thank you.
Aren't you going to take a photo
with him in your cap and gown?
- Hurry up.
- Then I'll go ahead.
Come down now, Sheng.
- Just go.
- Go.
I'll take a photo for you.
Don't you think it's hot?
Just ignore him.
- Let's go. I'll take photos for you.
- Okay.
Forget it. There are too many people.
Wasn't it you who jumped at me?
- I was too happy just now.
- You are not happy anymore?
Now, I can't out-talk you.
When were you ever able to out-talk me?
Would you like to come over
and take a picture with me?
Happy graduation!
(Flight to Guilin)
- When did you buy these?
- Last night.
When is the flight?
- This afternoon.
- Today? I will be taking photos then.
I go pack my stuff ten minutes after this.
Will that be too late?
No. I have to go and pack now,
or I'll be late.
Xiaoxing, will you help me pack?
My flight to Yangshuo is this afternoon.
Wait, I've agreed to take photos
with them. They are waiting for me.
Alright, then I'll go back
and pack up first.
- I'm going back to the dorm now.
- I've packed up for you.
Mo has already arranged everything
in case it's too late.
I've missed you guys so much.
Sheng, you really are my lucky star.
Only you can make the Perfect Voice
accompany you on a graduation trip.
- Do you want to eat beer fish?
- Yes!
- Let's go and check in first.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
What are you thinking about,
smiling so happily?
The river snails rice noodles,
stir-fried river shrimp, and that hotpot.
- Spotted fish hotpot?
- Yes, the spotted fish hotpot.
Come. This way.
Everything is arranged.
Just check in with your ID cards.
- Where is my ID card?
- Here it is.
For you two.
A private place only for you.
You're so thoughtful, Mr. Zhu.
Of course. This is your second visit.
I have to perform well.
- Just take it.
- No, thank you.
We can stay, just like everyone else.
Don't make it special for us.
I let him book it. It's peak season now.
You need to book a villa
a month in advance.
- That's right.
- A month in advance?
- Yes.
- And he said it was a spontaneous idea.
- You shouldn't believe what he said.
- You guys check in quickly.
- Mr. Zhu.
- Stop fussing.
Isn't there one for the two of us?
It should be this one.
We all came together.
Is it good if we live here alone?
Of course, it is.
Aren't we telling the whole world
that we are living together?
Aren't we supposed to live together?
We're here.
Please come in, Ms. Shengshengman.
Okay, Mr. Qiang.
Allow me.
- How is it?
- Not bad. There's also a yard.
- I forgot to tell you something.
- What's it?
I bought a place
next to the studio.
I wanted to tell you
after the renovation is done.
I want you to decide on decoration styles
since it will be your home too.
I've already found a designer.
Let's meet with them when we go back
and tell them the style you like.
Really? Are you serious?
A duplex with three bedrooms,
one living room,
an open kitchen, two bathrooms,
and a walk-in closet.
So big?
It's not bad.
It's bigger than the one
Zhou Zheng and I rented.
Considering our future living needs,
three bedrooms are necessary.
And it has two balconies.
That's about it.
Anything else you want to know?
Let me think.
Take your time.
I'll go inside and take a look.
When did this happen?
- The idea, or the time looking for it?
- When did the thought first occur?
It was two years ago. It was the day
I first told you I wanted to marry you.
- That early?
- I have been busy with work.
So I looked for condos
on and off for a long time.
It's not scientific. I didn't notice
that you were looking for a place.
How isn't it scientific?
But I did not contribute a penny.
But even if I want to, I can't.
I'll have to work for at least two years.
It's so embarrassing to have you
buy the apartment all by yourself.
How about
we buy another one
after I earn a lot of money?
So we can live in one place for some days
and the other days in another.
On the weekends,
we can either go to your place or mine.
I am serious.
Okay.
Your call.
Are you happy?
Yes.
It's just indescribable.
- Suddenly, we have our own place.
- "Suddenly"?
Isn't it so?
I waited for you from your senior year
till you graduated from graduate school.
Is this "suddenly"?
That's true.
Thank you, Mr. Mo.
It's not easy to have a love marathon.
- Is two years a long time?
- Isn't it?
You've made a perfectly good young man
in his twenties wait until he's 31.
I will be responsible for you
until the end.
♪Where should I start
about millions of dawns and dusks♪
♪Depict a stroke of rain
before the mountain, stars beyond the sky♪
♪Bit by bit, it outlines
yesterday and today♪
♪And you with picturesque eyebrows and eyes♪
♪Jointly create the mood♪
♪The rain and fog
over the mountains are intriguing♪
♪It seems I can't get enough of seeing
the once inexhaustible journey♪
♪On this journey, the stars accompany me
along thousands of miles♪
♪I walk down with you♪
♪Spending dawns and dusks together
for a hundred years♪
♪Just like it rains
when the clouds are low♪
♪I was moved
when you were singing softly♪
♪Since then, I hear stars every night
and rains at midnight♪
♪I could hear you
among millions of voices♪
♪All other voices fade away♪
♪I hear your monologue♪
♪Saying I miss you so much♪
♪Like knowing the implied meaning
of a picture♪
♪Knowing your happiness and sadness♪
♪Love comes in time again and again♪
♪Among the millions of people♪
♪I hear your voice♪
♪Saying I miss you so much♪
♪Tangled love for millions
of dawns and dusks♪
♪Kisses like pouring rain♪
♪Lightly falling
outside and inside the dream♪
♪All other voices fade away♪
♪I hear your monologue♪
♪Saying I miss you so much♪
♪Like knowing the implied meaning
of a picture♪
♪Knowing your happiness and sadness♪
♪Love comes in time again and again♪
♪Among the millions of people♪
♪I hear your voice♪
♪Saying I miss you so much♪
♪Tangled love for millions
of dawns and dusks♪
♪Kisses like pouring rain♪
♪Lightly falling
outside and inside the dream♪
♪With you in this life♪
♪Tangled love for millions
of dawns and dusks♪
♪Kisses like pouring rain♪
♪Lightly falling
outside and inside the dream♪
♪With you in this life♪