♪Hey, why is it happening♪
♪My heart is racing♪
♪The world has fallen silent♪
♪Hey, when I imagine you♪
♪What kind of look♪
♪Attracted me to you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, we fall in love♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I can't leave you♪
♪Slowly, slowly, I am with you♪
♪I love you♪
=Love Me, Love My Voice=
=Episode 23=
(Don't worry. I'm here.)
I wanted to have oden.
But there wasn't too much left.
I'm not full with the small portion of
river snails rice noodles just now.
I was in a hurry to come here.
I didn't eat much either.
I'm okay.
Are you hungry?
How about
filling our stomachs first?
Do you have a rice cooker?
You want to cook?
We have the stuff right here. The soup.
It's easy if you want to eat something.
Yes. I'll get it.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
- Hop pot noodles or vermicelli?
- Noodles. It can absorb the soup.
Okay. Let's go.
The rain eased off a little, right?
Let's see.
It smells so good.
- So many hearts.
- Yes. So many.
Draw it again.
Okay. It's done.
Give me this.
It looks so good
with your casual cooking.
Let's open a small restaurant.
A small one with several tables.
I can assure you they have to wait
for a few months to reserve online.
Okay. You can be the lady boss.
Try this.
This is for you.
- Is it good?
- So good!
- Okay, enough. I can't eat them all.
- Give me if you can't eat.
This helps digestion.
Feel free to eat.
It's good indeed.
This meatball is so good.
I'll let my mother buy more.
There's one here. The last one.
You can taste it.
You like it. You can eat it.
Let's eat together.
Stop. Don't give me. Eat.
It's hot.
That's right. We have plenty
in the freezer. Anything you want.
Help yourself. It's my place.
I can afford it.
- Okay. Eat.
- Right.
(Bad guy, how dare you
infiltrated into the demon world again?)
(You had some guts to break into
the forbidden area of Yanbo.)
(How did you sneak in?)
(You are threatening me?)
Go have some sleep.
- I really have to get some sleep.
- Go.
Take your time.
(Juemei Shayi, My Chat Room)
- Is it still raining?
- It's raining here.
I'll go to Suzhou tomorrow.
We have no class tomorrow.
But the school wants us to stay home.
- Me too, but I board at the school.
- (Geng Xiaoxing.)
I live near the school. I'm at home.
We can chat longer today.
I can't sleep with the thunder.
Right. And there's no class tomorrow.
We can chat all night.
- (I heard it wrong.)
- Chen, you are a fan of Perfect Voice.
You must know a lot. Where were we?
Juemei. When I was in dubbing circle,
he was popular.
Now there are new voice actors. Current
famous actors are all unknown to me.
But Perfect Voice is
still invincible in the circle.
- Will we be heard by them?
- I hope they can join us.
- They should sleep by now.
- It's fine. We can still talk.
- Chen, you go on.
- (It should be Geng Xiaoxing. Which one?)
I remember the dubbing actors
of Perfect Voice were scattered.
Then the main dubbing actors
moved to the same place.
Yes, a main actor talked about this
at one of their anniversaries.
- It was a Golden Age with Top Three.
- It's a pity that I've never seen it.
It's this one.
Miss, you must be a new one.
You've missed a lot.
- Have you heard about Juemei's scandal?
- He has a scandal?
Who? Juemei? No way.
He loves to make jokes
but never talks with anyone
except posting ads on Weibo.
I've never seen a real couple.
But I like him with Doudoubing.
A leader and a vice leader.
They've known each other
since young and fought together.
Me too. They fit so much.
I'm already picturing it.
Their voices also fit.
- (I don't think they fit.)
- Why are you typing?
- (My headset is broken. I'm on computer.)
- Then type.
How does it feel with only you
typing on the screen?
I think Feng Yasong has many partners.
He's easy-matching.
He goes well with anyone.
I like Feng Yasong. He's a doctor.
I like someone in a white gown.
- Me too. I liked his voice at first.
- He has many fans.
And I liked him better
when I knew he is a doctor.
In regular shows, and at
the anniversary in Yangshuo,
he kept helping newcomers proofread
manuscripts backstage. He's kind.
He cures people as a doctor
and helps the new as a dubbing actor.
- He's such a perfect youth. I love him.
- No way.
- He is a good person, and so handsome.
- Feng Yasong.
- A perfect man in the Perfect Voice.
- (He seems to have a girlfriend.)
Who is it?
It's such a big news. Tell us about it.
(It's just a rumor.
I don't know if it's real.)
Let me clarify. That's not true.
- That's actually him.
- I knew someone's listening.
- No way.
Is it Feng Yasong?
Yes. It's me. Pretend I'm not here.
You can continue. Anything is fine.
I'm just saying I'm single.
Where did you hear it from,
that typing guy?
Don't disgrace my idol.
- You bad guy.
- What else can you say with him here?
(You told Juemei on one of anniversaries.
I'm not lying.)
Juemei?
Feng Yasong told Juemei about it.
How did you know this?
Mr. Feng, are you still there?
Say something.
- Really? I don't remember I said this.
- He's serious.
Juemei must have made it up
or remembered it wrong.
(He said that.)
I don't remember. That's not true.
I have to work overtime.
- Mr. Feng, don't go. Let's talk.
- Don't go. It's rare to see you.
It's clean. I'll put it there.
It's almost 4 AM.
Shall we get some sleep?
I'll just go to work from here.
It's convenient to live here.
We can come more often.
You can go to work by crossing the road.
I'm fine. It's the same as
sleeping in the hospital.
Never mind. We have our homes.
We don't even have a bed here.
My father or my brother
sometimes sleeps here.
If it's too late after checking
and stacking, they would sleep here.
So it's a single bed.
Your father works so hard.
The bed was here before the decoration.
And we didn't want to throw it.
It's a bit small,
but I think we can get by with it.
How? It's smaller than a single bed.
What happened?
It's okay. I'm here.
The electricity is off?
But the lights across the street are on.
So something is wrong with wires here.
Let's find someone tomorrow.
It's not okay to stay here
without electricity.
How about going to the hospital with me?
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
The rain eased now. And the beds
in the duty room are all available.
It's a special occasion. It's okay.
Alright.
Mr. Mo, thank you for having a feast
with me and inviting me to the hospital.
In return, I'll get you some food.
Enough, enough.
What will you say to your mother if she
asks you why the supermarket is empty?
Every time I go to my friend's,
she would stuff me with many snacks.
She likes to see people eating.
The snacks for the recording studio
last time were given by her.
It's really enough.
Right, we have to put this bed away.
Or she will think someone sneaked in
and slept here.
Okay. Let me put it away.
Dr. Mo,
your shift is at the branch hospital.
Why are you here since it's late?
Yes. I came back.
Why don't you go back home
with such heavy rain?
I passed here. My house is too far away.
It's not safe to drive now.
Here.
This is my duty room.
Feel free to take a look.
I went to my grandpa's office
when I was young.
It's my first time to come to
a duty room of doctors since I grew up.
Do you sleep here
when working overnight?
This is my bed.
I will wash and sleep here
after surgeries
if I'm too tired to go home.
If it's too late in the recording
studio, I'll sleep there.
You've been staying up all night.
How about having sleep here?
I'll go to the office next door.
It'd be awkward if someone got in.
Lock the door.
I'll call you
when I'm back tomorrow morning,
then you can open the door.
Okay.
I'll go. Lock the door.
Wait for my call.
- Bye.
I was scared.
You haven't left?
(Yes. I'm working overnight.)
You...
(What do you want to ask?)
You know so many rumors about
Perfect Voice. You must be a loyal fan.
(Yes. Since their foundation. No,
specifically, before their foundation,)
(when Qiang Qingci and Juemei Shayi were
slightly famous, I was there.)
I see.
(You are a student?
I heard you talking about university.)
Yes.
(It's so late. Aren't you afraid
of disturbing your roommates?)
She's watching a film. She's afraid,
so she asked me to stay awake with her.
But I'm too sleepy.
I'll go to sleep. Bye.
With the thunder and the rain,
it's a perfect night to watch this film.
It would be more perfect
if you don't let me stay awake with you.
- I thought you were asleep.
- I promised you. I have to keep it.
You are so nice.
- You've been chatting with others?
- Mostly listen to them.
They were talking about rumors
in a chat room. I thought it was fun.
Why didn't you call me
to hear the rumors?
- You were watching the film.
- What's new? Tell me.
- Feng Yasong has a girlfriend.
- No way. He's known for being single.
He denied it, but he left after a while.
He was online?
- In the chat room?
- Yes.
He listened to his fans chatting in his
own chat room. Was it fun?
A strange habit.
Why did I watch the film? I'll wait
for him in the chat room tomorrow.
- Alright. Go to sleep. Good night.
- I'll wash and sleep too.
- Good night.
(- Geng Xiaoxing?
- Did you make it home safely?)
No way.
(Reply tomorrow if you are asleep.)
(If I can reply when I'm asleep,
I must have been woken up by you.)
(But then I see you asking me to reply
tomorrow. How do you think I would feel?)
(It's my fault.)
(How to make up for me?)
(Say it.)
(Record an audio for me.)
(You are a dubbing actor.)
(Record counting sheep.
It's the simplest.)
(How?)
Listen. I'll teach you.
One sheep, two sheep, three sheep,
four sheep, five sheep,
six sheep, seven sheep, eight sheep,
nine sheep, ten sheep,
11 sheep, 12 sheep, 13 sheep, 14 sheep,
15 sheep, 16 sheep, 17 sheep, 18 sheep,
19 sheep, 20 sheep, 21 sheep,
22 sheep, 23 sheep, 24 sheep,
25 sheep, 26 sheep, 27 sheep,
28 sheep, 29 sheep, 30 sheep.
(First People's Hospital)
(Outpatient)
Dr. Mo, Pediatrics wants you.
Okay.
Dr. Zhang, don't get in the duty room.
Dr. Mo brought his girlfriend here
due to the typhoon yesterday.
She's still asleep.
Morning.
Dr. Mo was called away.
He'll be back soon.
Okay.
You are sleeping?
You can go on. I have to make rounds.
I'll close the door for you.
Lock the door.
(Mo Qingcheng)
Hello.
I thought you asked me
to open the door just now.
I'm in Pediatrics. I was called here
temporarily. Get more sleep.
Okay.
That was awkward.
It's a good day.
Morning, Dr. Mo.
Dr. Mo,
your girlfriend was awake and looked
for you. I told her you'll be back soon.
Thank you.
Hello.
- Is it you knocking at the door?
- Yes.
Coming.
How did you sleep?
Great. Your bed is so comfortable
to sleep.
It's 6 AM. My shift hasn't begun.
Let's get some sleep.
Let's go.
(It's the duty room at the hospital.
He probably wants to get some sleep.)
It's the duty room at the hospital.
I just want some sleep.
I'll sleep here. You can go on.
Do you need an alarm?
I already had one.
Let's sleep.
I'm so sleepy.
Morning.
Who is it?
It's me.
What's the matter? I'm sleeping.
Let's discuss the case.
Coming.
I'll go home first. You can come and
find me when you are done with this.
Okay.
I'll open the door.
This...
- Sorry. I forgot you were here.
- It's alright. You can go on.
I...
- Bye.
She's gone. Have a seat.
Sheng.
- Grandpa, why are you here alone?
- Come. Have a seat.
It's dangerous to come upstairs.
Don't come alone.
You can tell me if you need anything.
- I just want to take a sunbath.
- Okay. Do whatever you like.
- Were you frightened by the storm?
- No.
Right.
You won't be afraid
with someone by your side.
Right.
Your mother asked your father to pick
you up from your schoolmate's house.
- Then?
- Then I told her
you are mature enough
to keep yourself from the storm.
And you should know better if she
doesn't want you to go, right?
Sheng,
are you getting along well with Dr. Mo?
- Yes. Very well.
- Okay. Let me meet him someday.
I have sharp eyes though they are small.
I know about a doctor.
I can rest assured when you do,
and we can all rest assured.
- No rush. We have plenty of time.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Sit, grandpa.
- Okay.
- Mr. Feng, when did you come back?
- This morning. I was delayed by storm.
I should have come back last night.
I stayed at the airport the whole night.
The whole night. Then you were bored
and went to the chat room.
How did you know?
I- I heard it from others.
It doesn't matter.
- You don't look good. You didn't sleep?
- I don't look good?
Really? Let me see.
It's okay.
- Come. I'll feel your pulse.
- Okay. You haven't felt it for long.
You can apply what you learned.
Why didn't you study Chinese medicine
in college? It's popular now.
Don't disturb me.
What's wrong? I was caught in the rain
last night and now I have a sore throat.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
You are pregnant.
Nonsense.
You know you were caught in the rain
and had a sore throat.
Why don't you take medicine?
- How would you dub later?
- I'm finding it.
But your eyes are bright and there is
light on your forehead. A lucky sign.
- Is there progress in your love life?
- Why is it so hard to talk to you?
It's not hard. You've become stupid.
The wise never fall in love.
You and Qiang Qingci
could compete with me before.
Now you all fell in love. Of course,
you are not as smart as me.
Where do you learn that from?
I'll take a shower and do the laundry.
Do you have some clothes to wash?
Why do you have to
wash your clothes with mine?
To save money. It will charge
the same water and electricity fees.
It's better to wash them together.
- Okay. You are good at saving money.
- Good at living.
Here's the milk tea for the best saver
of Tianzi No. 1 Recording Studio.
- Thanks. How much?
- Free. Your style. Two for one.
I'll use the milk tea as wine
to welcome you back.
- Where's mine?
- You have your medicine.
Are you jealous? My friendship with Dou
is beyond yours.
Yes. I'm jealous. Beyond mine.
Cheers for my friendship with Dou.
- Cheers.
- Okay.
Sheng, I like to eat a pomegranate.
It's just quite difficult to peel.
- I'll peel more for you.
- Okay.
(See at the lane entrance.)
- Grandpa, I have to go out for a while.
- Okay.
- Gu Jia.
- What's wrong?
Grandpa wants you
to peel pomegranates for him.
Peel pomegranates?
Then what would you do?
- Grandpa likes it. Peel more for him.
- How could you leave this...
- Where are we going?
- Where do you want to go?
Go to the studio with me if you don't
have any other arrangements.
The sewer was blocked,
so I asked someone to come and fix it.
Okay.
But you've been working all day.
And I just ask you to do this with me.
I feel bad.
I just want to see you. It doesn't
matter where to go or what to do.
Let's go.
It feels like taking you home.
Off Key.
I thought I was in the wrong place.
You thought you were still
in Tianzi No. 1 Recording Studio?
Yes. I didn't see Mr. Mo at Tianzi No.1,
but I see him here.
Guai, your guest of honor is here.
- Come.
- Who is it?
I didn't know you and I thought
you were our senior last time.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- Speak normally.
- I am doing that.
He's a senior. I have to respect him.
- You don't have to be so polite to me.
- Right.
Mr. Mo, have a seat.
I was sleeping.
I forgot to clean this up.
Mr. Mo, sit here.
Why are you so serious and tense?
I don't dare bring him here anymore.
Mr. Qiang is here as a guest.
We have to be polite.
But I'm on your side.
I have to be polite as well.
Okay.
Then I should say,
"Relax, I'll be good to Sheng."
- You are joking again.
- It's not a joke.
It's definitely not a joke. I saw
sincerity in Mr. Qiang's eyes.
I wanted to say it last time
I went here. It's a good place.
It's bigger than the first studio
of Perfect Voice.
Our leader found this place.
She works at a nearby beauty salon.
This used to be
children's art classroom.
The teacher happens to be
a guest of our leader.
- He moved out and we rented this place.
- I see.
I forgot to introduce myself. I'm Guai,
an English teacher in a primary school.
I'm Off Key, an official employee
of Perfect Voice.
You are so proud.
I'm just being honest.
Senior, what do you do?
It's okay if you don't want to say.
It's okay. I'm a doctor.
A lot of rumors
on the internet didn't say it.
Feng Yasong and you are both doctors.
Haven't you told her?
There are confidentiality agreements.
Doudou said we can't disclose
personal life of anyone in Perfect Voice.
- She never asked.
- Right.
I know you have privacy concerns,
so I never asked Sheng.
You are good friends. That's different.
I haven't poured you some water.
Tea or drinks?
- We have coke, ice tea...
- It's okay. I can help myself.
- Is it okay? I'll go to the kitchen.
- You went there before.
Okay.
I'm on their side today.
I won't be with you.
Right.
He's so nice.
Yes. I'll show you around
Perfect Voice someday.
They are all seniors in the industry
and all of them are kind.
You just show off.
I'm not. Sheng should be
the one showing off. Right?
It's 5 PM.
I have to work this afternoon.
- Mr. Mo, I'll go back to Tianzi No. 1.
- You are leaving?
- Bye.
Bye.
Drink orange juice.
- I... I have a class later.
- You said you didn't have any classes.
I ch-changed.
It's not our first meeting.
You don't have to
find an excuse to leave.
- Yes. Sit.
- Okay.
It's your place. I'm just a guest.
Ri-right.
Let me.
Coming.
- Hello.
- Hello, I am here to repair the sewer.
Yes. The drain next to the washing
machine in the kitchen is broken.
- Okay...
- This way.
Sit. I'll watch.
- Where? This one?
- This.
Okay.
He's not arrogant,
and he's a reliable good man.
- Doudou, there is toast.
- Thank you.
It smells so good.
Does Mr. Feng's family need money?
Why does he have to save like this?
You can see.
He has to spend
less than 15 yuan on takeout.
And he has to let us throw the empty
bottles in cardboard boxes to sell them.
He has used his phone for five years.
It's always unresponsive.
He used a lot of coupons
when buying things,
but he never hesitated
to treat us to meals.
He doesn't look poor.
He's rich.
He's a famous dubbing actor,
a pediatrician from a tertiary hospital
and he can save.
How could he be poor?
He's saving to get married. I seldom see
someone who could save money like him.
It's his habit. He's generous to
his friends, but he's frugal to himself.
He was like this when he was in school.
We were not so familiar at first
and we went to lots of expensive places.
It's rare to get out of school.
He was so generous
when we split the bills.
But then Mr. Mo told me that
he earned his living expenses
by doing temporary jobs.
He's so frugal at usual times.
What a good man.
He's famous and popular,
he has a lot of works
and he never had a scandal.
And he has a good temper.
I've never seen him angry with anyone.
He was born with a good temper.
He is more patient
after he became a pediatrician.
What do you think his future wife
will look like?
♪Turning the years into a drifting boat♪
♪Sailing through
the tumult and winding sorrow♪
♪I fear that the past will be crushed
by the coming cold wind♪
♪And stirred into
a piece of tranquil river water♪
♪Touching the crack with my fingertips♪
♪I dare not look at the haggard faces
and gray hair in the mirror♪
♪After many years,
the longing remains as sharp♪
♪And our shadows are thinner♪
♪Grinding the memories into ink♪
♪And writing them on the paper♪
♪The mirror and the person
are both gone♪
♪Where could I ask for the return date♪
♪The bronze mirror shatters at farewell♪
♪It's hard to convey the lovesickness♪
♪Over millions of miles♪
♪I laugh at the fame
and wealth of my life♪
♪I picture it as a flower in the mirror♪
♪It's hard to rival
a cup of tea in your hand♪
♪We drink from the same cup♪
♪And we share joy and sorrow♪
♪We drink down the past memories♪
♪Or alone in the corner of the world♪
♪Frost whitens the hair
in front of the forehead♪
♪Looking at the world, where is my home♪
♪I wish the clear frost
glitter in the moonlight♪
♪Reflecting the couple in the mirror♪
♪Return with you♪
♪After being separated for half a life♪