THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
Mom, no.
No, Mom.
Mom…
Kang-ho…
Kang-ho.
Kang-ho, you're…
You're…
Kang-ho…
You just
stood up, right?
Honey…
Our son… Thank you.
Thank you.
Kang-ho, do it again.
Stand up again.
Kang-ho, that was…
Kang-ho.
Kang-ho!
EPISODE 8
Let me see your fingernail.
I fixed it for now
but it could chip again.
Here.
I'll mark it with this nail polish,
so be careful with this fingernail, okay?
My mom abandoned me.
She took me to an unfamiliar place
and left without me to go somewhere nice.
Your mom
would never abandon you.
However,
if she really
did such a thing,
I'm sure she had a reason.
A reason?
Yes.
She may not be able to tell you now,
but one day, you'll understand everything.
Mi-joo, how do you know that?
Because I was abandoned too.
You were?
Why?
I'm not sure.
I also really want to know
why I was abandoned.
But I'll never know.
Kang-ho!
Kang-ho.
About what happened--
What's the reason?
What?
Why did you abandon me?
Mi-joo told me
that there must be a reason for that.
Kang-ho.
I never
abandoned you.
Kang-ho, look at me.
Look at me. Please?
I'll be honest.
Kang-ho, the thing is…
I'm actually
a bit unwell.
You are?
Where?
Here.
My stomach hurts a bit.
Because I'm unwell, I need to
take medicine and go to the hospital.
Someone needs to cook,
do the laundry, and look after me.
But…
I didn't want to burden you.
That's why.
Was I a burden to you…
because I'm unwell?
What?
You fed me medicine
and took me to the hospital.
You cooked and did my laundry too.
To me, you're just my mom.
But I must've been a burden to you.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
You're right.
I'm your mom,
and you're my son.
I was so stupid to think that way.
Besides, you're no longer unwell.
You definitely stood up earlier.
And soon enough,
you'll be able to walk and run.
And…
you'll be able to take care of me.
That's right.
I also have a guardian now, don't I?
"Guardian"?
Yes.
You're my guardian now.
Your guardian.
So Kang-ho,
try to stand up
like you did earlier.
It's okay. You can do it.
Take your time and try it again.
Okay.
Don't give up. You're almost there.
A bit more.
I can't do it.
No, you did. You already did.
Get up, Kang-ho.
Get up.
Don't leave me, Mom.
Mom, where are we going?
No. I don't want to go.
Can't I just live with you? Please?
Mom.
Mom!
Mom! Save me!
Do you want to live?
Do you?
-Mom!
-Then get up.
Stand up like you did earlier!
-Mom!
-Get up!
-Kang-ho, look!
-Mom!
If you stand up,
the water will be only knee-deep!
-Mom.
-So get up!
Stand up!
Mom.
Mom!
The wheelchair is gone.
So get up.
Get up and walk!
I can't…
It's not that you can't. You just won't.
That's not true.
I can't do it, Mom.
-Really?
-Mom!
Really?
Mom!
-Get up.
-Mom!
-Get up!
-Get up and walk!
Mom!
Get up!
Mom…
Hold him by his pelvis…
Get up.
All right.
It's okay. You can do it.
Get up.
-You're doing well.
-A bit more. Your left foot.
That's it.
Your legs.
Move your legs!
I can't move them.
Slowly. Good.
Well done.
-Well done.
-You're doing well.
Slowly.
Gosh!
-Move them.
-Mom.
I can move them, Mom.
Mom.
Well done. More.
-I don't want to!
-Oh Tae-soo of Jeilmirae Party
-Come here.
-received the highest votes
-Kang-ho!
-in the preliminary elections.
Mr. Son!
Come here, Kang-ho.
Kang-ho.
She's already been through
so much hardship.
With her son in that state
and now her farm in ruins,
she must be in so much distress.
I can't believe I made such a fuss
trying to get rid of her pig farm.
I deserve to die.
That's true.
What?
Don't say that.
We're all to blame.
No one here is innocent.
I should visit and console her,
but I feel too shameful to do that.
Speaking of which,
as her neighbors,
we should be doing something to help her.
Then should we all pitch in
some money for her?
You know her. She'd never accept it.
I agree. Instead of giving her money,
how about we give her a gift?
Perhaps, some nice sheet masks,
clothes, or a luxury bag.
She's been giving away
everything she owns.
I doubt she'll be happy.
What is she giving away?
Did she give you something?
-Did she give you something?
-No.
That's not it.
What I mean is that
she's not the type
to want nice clothes or bags.
Her only desire
is to dote on her one and only son.
Why don't we get Kang-ho a gift instead?
Goodness, that's a great idea.
Right.
Then what about a new wheelchair?
I saw that she had thrown out
his broken wheelchair a few days ago.
Then don't you think
she would've bought a new one already?
-Right.
-You think so?
Since he can't go anywhere without it.
That's true.
Then how about
we get him a mobility scooter?
It won't break since it's sturdy.
The roads here are very rough.
It's perfect!
You sure are an early adopter.
I'm all for it.
-Me too!
-We all are!
-Then let's get one already.
-Okay.
JIN YOUNG-SOON
CHOI KANG-HO'S MOTHER
JUNG GUM-JA, LEE MI-JOO
PIGSTY
OFFICE
Mr. So.
You startled me.
You jerk. I told you
not to barge in like that.
-We finally have it.
-What?
Are you serious?
Where?
Where is it?
Look at this.
We finally have…
a lettuce leaf.
So…
you didn't mean evidence.
You meant lettuce leaves.
Oh, the evidence?
But sir, look. We went through
the effort of planting them.
At times, we forgot
to water them or spray pesticides.
But look how they've grown.
So,
you're elated.
Right?
Yes, sir. I'm very happy.
It's the first time
I've planted something and seen it grow.
-Take a closer look.
-Don't come near me.
Don't!
Get out!
Go!
You punk!
Leave!
What are you talking about?
We're not qualified?
We're young, healthy men
who decided to farm in the countryside.
We've completed the required course too.
I'm sorry.
But both of the applicants
are employed in a conglomerate
and covered by social insurance,
therefore are not eligible for this loan.
What on earth are you talking about?
Then what about me?
What should I do?
Sorry?
What are you…
I'll die if I don't pay them back soon.
And it'll be messy.
They'll tear out my liver, kidneys, eyes,
lungs, intestines, duodenum,
and everything else
piece by piece
and that's how I'll end up--
I should just die.
What are you looking for?
Are there any pesticides?
I want to kill myself.
It's down there.
What?
Mix two tablespoons of this
in one mal of water.
Okay.
This one too.
Here's your insecticide.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
-Bye.
Goodness.
What is this? Is this for me?
Are you senile?
What? What's wrong with me?
Is looking for romance at my age so wrong?
Jeez.
This countryside has been teeming
with old ladies.
-All the men around here are excited
-Does it hurt?
to see such a young, pretty lady.
Mi-joo has been treating everyone
in this village well.
Thanks to her, I have more customers now.
She's my lucky charm.
Hey, young lady.
Are you interested in opening a nail salon
in a bigger and cleaner place?
I could easily get you
the best spot in this area.
What do you say?
Thank you for the offer,
but I like this place.
I have many regulars,
and the owners here are so lovely.
Did you hear that?
Don't you even dream
of stealing her from me.
Shouldn't you get going?
Excuse me.
Hi, Mom.
Mom, Dad is here.
What? What are you talking about?
Why would he be here?
-I'm working, so call me later.
-I'm not lying. I know his face.
He drove a Banz here.
I'm certain it's him.
Stop here please.
Mom!
Mom, hurry!
-Hurry up!
-Okay.
You need to hurry!
Grandma is beating Dad up right now!
He's getting beaten up!
You darn son of a gun!
I know it's you! Stop lying!
-What's wrong?
-You're the guy
who abandoned my daughter!
That's not me.
Don't you dare lie!
You don't think I know your face?
I set a picture of you
as the wallpaper on my phone.
I wanted to make sure to recognize you
so I can beat you up.
I only took that because she asked me to.
Stop lying!
Darn it. And that's not even the US.
We took that in Seoul.
Be quiet.
The kids will hear.
-Dad!
The kids think you're their dad.
You can't show up like this.
Pay me back.
-Sun-young borrowed that money.
-I don't want to hear it.
You have until the end of the month.
If you don't,
I'll tell those ladies
who are dying to find you
that you're here.
What? What's wrong?
Where's Dad?
Dad?
He left.
He left?
Where did he go?
To the US.
The US?
Something urgent came up, so he had to.
He said he was sorry for leaving
without saying goodbye
-and that when he returns--
-I hate you both.
I won't go to kindergarten anymore.
Ye-jin.
There's this boy named Park Jun-seo
at our kindergarten.
He always teases her for not having a dad,
so they always get into fights.
So we were going to
bring Dad along tomorrow
and teach him a lesson.
But not anymore.
Seo-jin.
It's me.
The hen I told you to prepare,
I don't need it anymore.
Darn it.
The kids kept saying that
they wanted to see their dad.
So I asked my friend's boyfriend
to video-call them a few times.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
It's not like I've been
a model parent to you anyway.
I'm the one who started all this,
so you don't have to apologize to me.
It's just that
those kids
will be going to school soon.
Once they see the family register
and find out they don't have a dad,
they'll be so heartbroken.
I thought of telling them
that you guys got a divorce
or that he died of an illness.
I thought long and hard too.
But…
I just can't do it.
I can't bear the thought
of making them cry.
Both of them will bawl.
How can I possibly watch that?
They must be so heartbroken right now
and bawling their eyes out.
My babies…
-No way!
Is this for Kang-ho?
Yes, what do you think?
Isn't it incredible?
It's a bit small for three.
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't ride it!
It's just for him!
Don't raise your voice at them.
-They could get hurt.
-He's right. You could get hurt.
Kids, this is very expensive.
So you shouldn't ride it, okay?
-Okay.
-Good boy.
The wheels are huge,
and it looks so sturdy.
Kang-ho will love it.
-Right.
-Of course.
This will save Young-soon the hassle too.
I'm glad we got it.
-Right.
-Hey, it's Mi-joo.
-Hi, Mi-joo.
-Gosh.
Look who's here. It's Mi-joo.
Did you close your salon today for this?
Sorry?
Goodness, you must be busy
with so many customers.
How considerate of you.
But then again,
she's always cared for Kang-ho
-since they were kids.
-That's true.
And Sam-sik always bullied Kang-ho.
What…
What on earth are you talking about?
Sam-sik never bullied Kang-ho.
He did. Be quiet.
Anyway, now that
everyone's here, let's go.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-Move aside.
-Let's go!
-You're going to hurt yourself!
-Go.
All right.
-Look at him.
-Goodness!
I need to go back to the salon now.
After they complimented you?
-What?
-Be quiet and follow me.
Mom…
We can't make any mistakes this time.
Do something stupid once again,
and you'll see lettuce roots
instead of leaves.
Roots?
But the roots are underground…
Yes, sir.
Hey, hide!
Over there!
Where in the world are they
after screwing me over?
And why aren't they picking up?
Darn it.
All right.
Gosh, it's so fascinating.
-Be careful! You'll trip and fall!
-Make way!
Make way!
Hey!
All right.
-Make way!
-Let's go!
-Come on, let's go!
Wait, why am I hiding?
I'll ask her to open the gates.
Why aren't you picking up?
-Hey--
-Wait.
-What is it?
-Hold on.
Don't you think it'd be too boring
to just hand it over to him?
-Boring?
-What do you mean?
-Yes.
-How about
you all line up in two rows?
-Both ways?
-Yes.
-Like a wedding.
-I see.
-Go on.
-Like this?
I'll be hiding in that corner, okay?
Once Kang-ho comes out,
I want you to shout out his name.
That'll be my cue.
-Then I'll appear with this scooter.
-What are they doing?
-I love it.
-Great.
You sure are the brains around here.
You're flattering me.
Anyway, give me my cue.
All right. "Kang-ho!"
Jeez, they're so over the top.
Young-soon!
Are you home?
Young-soon.
I'm coming.
What brings all of you here?
Goodness.
Mr. Son.
It must've been so tough for you.
As the old saying goes,
"Neighbors are worth a thousand homes."
But none of us are well-off enough
to help you out.
We also thought you'd need some time
to cope with your loss.
It may sound like an excuse,
but we finally mustered up
the courage to see you.
We're truly
sorry.
Don't say that.
I'm the one who should be sorry
for inconveniencing the village.
-I'm sorry.
-Not at all.
-We're sorry.
-Enough.
We apologized,
and you accepted our apology.
We're good now, okay?
Sure.
Where's Kang-ho?
We haven't seen him in a while.
We miss him.
-Kang-ho?
-Yes.
One minute.
Kang-ho.
Kang-ho, come on out.
All right now.
-Should we go get him?
-We should.
No, stay here.
-Goodness.
Goodness.
-Goodness…
-This is great.
I'm so happy for you!
Goodness!
-Goodness…
-This is unbelievable.
Kang-ho!
I'm coming!
Goodness.
Goodness, this is amazing.
I'm so grateful.
Goodness…
-Goodness!
-Hey!
Mr. Bang!
Dad!
-Dad!
-No! Move aside!
Honey, where does it hurt?
Where?
-My legs!
-Your legs?
Are you okay?
-Goodness.
-What do I do?
-Hi, Sam-sik.
-Are my legs okay?
Hold on. No.
-Call 911!
-Hurry!
They say sunshine comes after the rain.
God must've been moved
by your mom's perseverance and love.
That's why He's given you this miracle.
I agree.
And He's given me this mobility scooter.
You should be grateful for it.
That was a close call.
You two from Seoul, eat up.
Thank you.
-Eat up.
-Thank you.
Hey.
Focus and look around carefully.
We didn't come here to drink makgeolli.
Yes, sir.
A little bird told me that
you work at a conglomerate.
How did you know
we work for Woobyeok Group?
What?
I didn't know that.
Jeez, you work for Woobyeok Group?
Then you should've told me sooner.
Hold on.
If that's the case,
why do you want to farm?
We've retired.
Did you?
I see.
Don't you usually receive severance pay?
You see, I have
a really great business idea.
Listen up.
Look who's here.
It's Mi-joo, my love.
Say hello.
These two are my future business partners.
And she'll be my future--
Can't you see everyone is working?
Go get some makgeolli from the kitchen.
Enjoy.
That's her charm.
The straightforwardness and jabs.
I'll invite you to our wedding,
so make sure you come.
-We'll talk about our business later.
-Okay.
I'll give them to the kids.
Kids, there's more.
Eat up.
Wait.
Look.
I'm all better now.
You're right.
You're all better now. I'm glad.
Wait.
My mom said that
she didn't abandon me.
So I'm sure
that person didn't abandon you either.
Here you go.
We used to be similar in height.
But you're much taller now.
Tell me about it. You're like an adult.
Here.
If I do this, you're taller than me.
All right.
What is this? Why do I have butterflies?
Me too. Lift me up too.
Should I?
Come here, Seo-jin.
Here we go.
-Get a good look at the view, Seo-jin.
-And again.
Good boy.
You got a good view.
Sam-sik.
Come and eat.
Congratulations, Young-soon.
Now that Kang-ho can walk again,
I'm sure only good things
will come your way now.
That's right.
Once you open the farm again,
Kang-ho will help out. This is just great.
It's so fascinating.
Her pigs have been around
for the past 30 years,
and now that I don't smell them,
a part of me feels empty and strange.
I'll be honest. She used to give us
free meat every now and then.
We also got manure for free. It was nice.
Of course.
A pig farm is far better
than some trot concert hall.
Look at those despicable humans.
By the way,
I haven't seen Hoon-ah around lately.
You're right.
We grilled some meat.
So what? Are you rubbing it in my face?
If you haven't eaten yet,
you should come over and eat with us.
The villagers are all there.
No.
I'm allergic to pork.
It's beef.
These darn flies.
I hate them!
Go.
-Darn it.
-Sir.
I won't be alive for long.
I have terminal cancer.
Since I won't be running
the farm for long,
I told my lawyer
to hand it over to you after I die.
But…
my son can walk again now.
That pig farm
is the only thing I can leave him.
It's also the only thing I can teach him.
So please.
Please…
don't take it away from us.
I knew you wouldn't join us,
so I brought some meat.
Here.
Please keep my illness
a secret from the villagers.
-Thank you.
-Not at all.
The meat just melts in my mouth.
-It's like ice cream.
-It's tasty.
Everything's so good.
Gosh.
-I need to use the bathroom.
-It's so tender.
Gosh.
The vegetables are good too.
Hey, don't drag your feet. It's so dusty.
Where are your table manners?
-Where's the bathroom?
-There's dust everywhere!
Is this it?
This isn't it.
It's here.
Thank you.
-Gosh, thank you.
-It's so good.
-Use both hands.
-Just eat this.
Come on.
We finally have it.
What is it this time?
-Poop?
-No.
The evidence.
All his files and belongings
are in the shed back there.
What?
Are you serious?
-Let's go.
-All right.
Right!
I finally remember who you are.
Damn it.
We met before, right?
You were hiding in my closet,
and then came out and started fighting
with a knife with a guy.
What? With a knife?
-Yes.
-Are you thieves?
Why were you hiding in their closet?
What are you talking about?
They're my business partners.
Then they are thieves.
Hey!
-Wait.
-Come on.
You're wrong.
They recently moved here
from the city to farm.
-Remember my cornfield?
-Yes.
They bought it.
They're growing lettuce with Sam-sik now.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Then come here
and have some makgeolli with us.
-You won't be driving.
-Come.
I'm afraid we need to leave.
We need to water the lettuce.
Right. We should.
-Excuse us.
-Bye.
-They're so hardworking.
-Wait.
Make sure you let the water run first.
The water in the hose is lukewarm,
so it'll kill the lettuce.
-How cute.
-Lion, come here.
Lion, come here.
Lion.
Sit down, Lion.
Over here.
Now I can play soccer
and hopscotch with you.
Right, Kang-ho?
Don't call him like that.
He's all grown up now.
Right, Kang-ho oppa?
It's okay. We're friends.
You're an adult so we need to
treat you like one, okay?
Then do we need to use honorifics too?
All right. I got it.
I actually always thought you should.
Is it tasty, Lion?
They look like one happy family.
Goodness, I'm sorry.
I can wrap up here.
You should go home with your kids.
Ms. Jin.
I stayed behind
because I had something to ask you.
Do you remember
when we met by the pond
when it was raining?
Kang-ho said something…
I won't do it again.
Never again.
Okay.
Then I won't worry anymore.
Thanks.
Likewise.
-"I love you"
-Is such
-A great thing to say
-I really like
-These three words
-I love you
-I love you.
-I love you, Mom and Dad.
I'm sorry about getting mad earlier.
I guess Dad must've been very busy
if he had to leave without saying goodbye.
I'm sure he'll come
to our elementary entrance ceremony.
I can teach Park Jun-seo a lesson then.
But tell Dad to look good that day.
I don't know
if he was dressed the way Americans do,
but he looked quite shabby,
and I didn't like it.
I agree. Kang-ho looked great today.
He was tall and strong.
What if we pretend that
Kang-ho is our dad?
-No!
-No.
Goodness. All right.
You guys didn't have to get all worked up.
You. I told you
not to treat him like a friend.
-Treat him like an adult!
-Mom!
-Stop it.
-Hello.
My babies.
It's Mr. Sam-sik.
Why do you call me "Mr. Sam-sik"
and Kang-ho "oppa"?
Come here.
What are you doing? Put me down.
I'm scared of heights.
-Don't do that!
-All of a sudden?
You liked it when Kang-ho lifted you up.
Baby.
Answer me, will you?
You reek of alcohol.
That's enough. Go inside and wash up.
-Let's go!
-No.
My babies!
Goodness. You should go home
and sleep if you're drunk.
You're embarrassing yourself.
Go home.
Mi-joo.
What is it?
I'm going to be
straightforward with you.
Okay.
Do you like Kang-ho?
What?
Does seeing him walk
stir up your emotions?
Is that why you didn't go to work today
and stayed behind
and helped them clean up?
Just go home.
Why can't you say you don't?
I don't. I don't like him.
Happy?
If that's true,
let's get married.
Let's live a happy life
and raise the kids together.
Let's do that.
They need a dad.
I promise to make you guys happy.
Should we?
What? What did you say?
Are you serious?
-You'll marry me?
-Yes.
Let's do it.
But you know I'm broke, right?
I have a ton of debt too.
A creditor came by today as well.
We can struggle together every single day
to pay off our debts.
We'll get chased around pathetically.
But amid all that,
let's live happily together.
Sure.
"Stir up my emotions"? "Get married"?
I work like a dog every day
to pay off my debt bit by bit.
It's tough to make ends meet
while taking care of my family.
I can't afford to have
my head in the clouds like you.
Bye.
Is the debt the only issue then?
Mi-joo, listen carefully
to what I'm about to say.
I will be back.
This used to be your room.
You'll be sleeping here from now on.
But I don't want to be alone.
No.
You need to learn to be independent.
That's how you become an adult.
I'll teach you one step at a time. Okay?
Okay.
Who is this?
Hello?
Excuse me.
I'm Prosecutor Choi Kang-ho's…
Goodness, you're here. Please come in.
This way.
-Have this.
-Thank you.
On the day
you dropped off the side dishes,
Prosecutor Choi came by late at night.
If my mother comes by
to pick up my belongings
when I'm not here,
please give her this.
TO MY MOTHER
Are you moving?
No.
But I might have to.
Please give it to her and nobody else.
Please.
But I was off duty that day,
so I didn't even know that he had moved.
Fortunately, you gave me
your number last time,
so I'm finally giving it to you.
Sorry it's so late.
To my mother whom I miss dearly.
Are you healthy and well?
I got the side dishes
that you left at the security office.
I had always missed
your home-cooked meals.
I had a lovely dinner
for the first time in a long time.
I'm sorry that my work keeps me
from calling or visiting you often.
But Mother,
I want you to know this.
We may be apart,
but I still live
in the memories
I shared with you and Father.
I'll see you next week on your birthday.
"September 7.
From your beloved son, Kang-ho."
"Kang-ho"?
Did I write this?
It's just so odd.
You've never spoken to me
in this manner before.
Why did you leave this
with the security guard?
How did you know
I'd be packing your stuff without you?
Tell me.
Did you know you'd end up this way?
Were you trying
to tell me something with this letter?
You were, right?
I'm sorry, but I don't remember.
And then…
Again.
INVESTIGATION OFFICER
Hello?
It's me, ma'am. You called.
I was attending a trial earlier.
I see. One minute.
Fill it out, and when they call number 25,
go hand them the bankbook and the seal.
What's the password again?
The password is
zero, nine--
Zero, nine, zero, seven. My birthday.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo?
Do you mean
the assemblyman
who's running for president?
The former prosecutor?
Correct.
Prosecutor Choi was engaged
to his daughter.
You didn't know?
Goodness.
How could this be?
That's a relief.
I've been acquainted with Assembly Oh.
Could you give me his number please?
Sorry?
His daughter's number
would be even better.
I have a few things to check about my son.
And I think she'd know best
since they were engaged.
Gosh.
Ma'am.
There's no way for me
to know their numbers.
And she's getting married soon.
I think it'd be best
if you didn't call them.
Here comes the bride.
Where's the groom?
He's taking a call outside.
He's taking a call inside.
Is he serious?
He's in the room next door.
Make sure the baby is dressed warmly.
It's pretty windy near the sea.
I'll pick you up at 8 p.m.
Kang-ho.
What baby?
It's nothing.
Are you done?
I was going to surprise you
with a grand appearance.
Is the other one better?
Or is something fancier better?
You already look pretty enough.
Whatever.
You do. Let's go.
Kang-ho.
We're visiting your mother tomorrow.
Do you really have to go out tonight?
It's work-related. I won't be long.
You're such a workaholic.
Let's stop by the department store.
We need to make a move first.
I heard about your daughter's wedding.
You'll become in-laws with Dosang Group.
Yes, that's right.
What can I do? Our children are in love.
I understand.
Parents are always bound
to give in to their children.
Though there are parents who kill them.
Mr. Song!
Gosh, you startled me.
It's about time you dropped it.
It's all in the past.
I believe
my men found something in Kang-ho's house.
Do you mean
the original copy of the DNA test result?
As you said, it's just a piece of paper.
What if I claim that you colluded
with Bareun Hanguk Party
and fabricated it to take me down?
Then how will you prove its authenticity?
So why did you have to take it so far
as to kill the poor woman and her child?
What did you say?
I hope we never see each other again.
Goodbye then.
Right.
I expected nothing less from him.
How did it go?
We finally located the file.
In two days,
Oh Tae-soo will become in-laws
with Dosang Group.
And you just managed to locate it?
-Are you kidding me right--
-Choi Kang-ho
is walking again.
What do you mean?
See? What did I tell you?
I told you he'd walk again.
Where should you record
the pig feed that you purchased?
Pig feed.
Pig feed…
Here. "Pig Feed Management."
Good.
What about their medicine and injections?
Medicine
and injections…
Here.
Well done.
You're so smart.
You need to check
and record them every day, okay?
Okay.
What am I learning tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
COPIED DOCUMENTS
-Are these all mine?
-Yes, they're all yours.
Mom, this too?
Yes.
Awesome.
I'm going to show it
to Seo-jin and Ye-jin.
Found it.
Kang-ho oppa!
Hello, you cuties.
You must be here
to hang out with Uncle Kang-ho.
But we need to go into town.
It's okay.
Ye-jin only came to congratulate him
on walking again.
She brought a flower.
Go on.
They said yellow was your lucky color.
Thanks, Ye-jin. It's so pretty.
But of course, you're prettier.
We'll be back.
I'm going to beat up anyone
who tells me to wash my hands.
Did you see how we were
wearing matching colors?
This is fate.
I'm going to marry him.
One, two, three.
Okay, it's all done.
Please wait in the waiting room
while it gets printed.
-Okay.
Excuse me, but could I take one alone?
Sure. Please sit in the middle.
Is it for your passport or ID?
I need a photo much bigger than those.
Those who come to pay
their condolences will see it,
so please make sure to take it well.
"Condolences"?
Yes.
Okay, ma'am.
One minute please.
All right. Let's try it again.
Mom.
Why are we doing this?
Do it.
Now.
Goodness.
Go on.
I don't want to. I'm scared.
There's nothing to be scared about.
Kang-ho.
I'm just teaching you
things you don't know.
Just like teaching you how to cook
and what to do at the bank.
I'm teaching you things that
you'll need to know in life.
When will I need to do this?
Later.
Much later.
So let's try it.
Goodness.
What did I tell you to do?
You need to get up too.
You must be heartbroken.
-Mom.
-You must be heartbroken.
Thank you for coming here
and offering your condolences.
Did she have an illness?
"She had cancer."
She had cancer.
Well done, my son.
-Done.
Let's put him in there too.
What? Who?
Dad.
Dad?
Yes.
Just like that photo,
let's add him to the new photo too.
Then we'll be together.
Sure, let's do that.
But I still live
in the memories
I shared with you and Father.
"In the memories."
Inside?
Mom, what's wrong?
THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
I want to find out the reason why
I had to attend law school.
Beg him, or you'll go to jail!
Once you study hard
and become a prosecutor,
no one will be able to
look down on you or bully you.
That's true power.
You want me to become a cowardly snob
who'd do anything to get my way.
He hasn't even been appointed yet.
It's too soon to think about marriage.
Do you want to know…
what it is that I want to do?
Oh Ha-young
is Prosecutor Oh Tae-soo's daughter.
The moment Chairman Song
accepted me as his son,
she became a stranger to me.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim