THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
-Mom!
-My babies!
-My gosh! Have you been well?
-Mom!
-Oh, my!
-Goodness, come here.
-Mom!
I came for you!
Mommy came to get you both!
Goodness, look.
Ye-jin, how are you?
Seo-jin, how about you?
-Mom!
-You've both grown so much!
-My babies!
-Mom!
Did you miss me?
Who could it be? Is it someone scary?
Let me check. Stay here.
Who is it?
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday dear Kang-ho and…
-Happy birthday dear Mi-joo
-Happy birthday to you
What did you wish for?
For you to complete your training
at the top of your class.
And for us to live happily
for a long time.
What about you?
Me?
That I won't be nervous.
-Nervous?
-The candles are melting.
-Right.
-One, two, three!
-Happy birthday, Mi-joo!
-Happy birthday, Kang-ho!
What is it?
I made it myself.
It's a limited edition, one-of-a-kind.
-Really?
-Yes.
You have to wear it
to your appointment ceremony, okay?
Okay, I will.
Good.
But what's this? Ten square root of two?
-Love.
-I see.
I ten square root of two you.
The gifting portion is over.
Let's move on to the next part.
Let's sit and wait.
-Oh, my!
-Wait.
I taught myself,
so I'm not that good.
But still, listen to the end.
Okay.
Pray for me.
Don't let him be nervous.
Don't let me be nervous.
A tiring day passed by
Two are under the moonlight
As one shadow
That distant happiness is
Still there seemingly within my reach
When I close my eyes
-Open up.
-Okay.
You're back!
What took you so long to tell me that?
Am I your first love?
Yes.
You're my first love, Yeong-min.
-You have to brush vertically.
-What?
Careful.
-You're bleeding.
-What?
Got you.
-Gosh, your hair is long.
-Okay, I'll stay still.
You're so good.
Is there anything you can't do?
One more coat, and we're done.
Eat up.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
What a cute couple.
What is it?
I'm home.
-Hey.
How have you been?
KANG-HO'S VISIT
Of course, I should come.
You're beautiful.
-Am I? I'm relieved.
-Yes.
-Let's take a picture.
-Okay.
KANG-HO'S VISIT
KANG-HO'S APPOINTMENT CEREMONY
Congratulations on your appointment
Congratulations, my dear Kang-ho…
DEAR KANG-HO
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR APPOINTMENT
What are you waiting for? Make a wish.
I did.
What did you wish for?
That I won't be nervous.
Tell me.
There's something I want to do.
And it's something…
you need to do on your own.
It's money I've saved up.
BANKBOOK
This is it?
I thought I would get much more
for devoting myself
to making you a prosecutor.
It's not as much as I thought.
All right.
In any case,
set me up with a colleague
or whoever else that'll take
the bar exam.
This time, someone richer.
You know that
I'm good at cooking and chores.
Right.
And at giving love.
Who was it?
It was nobody. Let's go.
Let's go.
Who was it?
Wait…
There's nobody here.
If you wanted to find
that bouncy ball so badly,
you should've taken me with you.
It's dangerous for you
to go out alone without telling me.
I was really worried.
Where's your phone?
Wait.
Where's my phone?
My phone is gone, Mom.
Goodness.
Mom, are you sick?
Yes.
Because of me?
Goodness.
Do you feel sad when I'm ill?
Yes.
I feel sad when you get hurt too.
So don't let this happen again, okay?
Okay.
-By the way, Mom.
-Yes?
Why am I in pain?
You bruised and scraped yourself
so of course, you're in pain.
No, not there.
Right here.
What?
You feel pain there? Why?
When did it start?
After seeing that pretty lady.
Pretty lady?
Who?
Someone I don't know.
But it hurts right here.
What?
You never know what will happen in life.
Who knew that would happen to him?
His mom was thrilled
and even threw a feast
saying her prosecutor son
would be an assemblyman's son-in-law.
Mom, is Bar Exam a bad guy?
Is that why he's behind bars?
BAR EXAM MEALS
Give it to me.
Why did you go through her things?
I wanted to see
if she got us anything from America.
Actually, Kang-ho lost
the bouncy ball she got for us.
You little rascal!
Don't refer to him like that!
He's your mom's friend!
What do you mean?
Kang-ho is Mom's friend?
He's our friend.
You rascals!
They keep doing this.
I feel bad whenever I see his mom.
You two.
Don't do that again.
Then what do we call him?
Kang-ho oppa? Uncle Kang-ho?
Don't call him.
Don't ever meet him
or play with him again.
Okay?
But…
Do you both understand?
-Yes.
That's enough.
They're excited to see you again
so stop scolding them.
Wait.
Why did you suddenly come home?
Is something wrong?
Goodness, nothing's wrong.
I just decided to stop by.
My babies, I have presents for you.
Let's see what I got for you. Where is it?
MY FIRST KOREAN WORDS
You should've bought them
comic books, slime, push pop,
or other things like that.
Then again,
you left as soon as you weaned them.
You couldn't have known.
Sorry.
I didn't get you anything.
This is plenty.
My hands never looked this fancy
in my 60 years of living.
You'd always look at my hands
and get angry saying,
"Why are your hands like this?"
I had to pay for your dad's dance craze,
and my hands were covered with dirt
from farming all the time.
I never even imagined
getting my nails done.
Back then,
although you were the youngest,
you were the most considerate.
You always knew
what was going on
just by looking at my face.
That's how it is
between a parent and a child.
You don't have to say a word.
You can tell just by
the look on their face.
My daughter suddenly shows up one day
and she has
the look on her face that I had
when my husband had an affair
and ran away,
creditors came and destroyed my house,
and my future seemed so grim.
So…
how can I not recognize it?
It must've been so tough for you.
Your children will start school soon,
and I'm now too old and tired
to look after them.
I don't know what's going on,
but seeing how you came back
with all your stuff,
it looks like you've come to stay.
I know it wasn't easy for you to come.
And it might not be easy,
but let's live together.
I once heard this singer sing on TV
that if you live on,
you can continue to live.
-Okay.
-All right.
You feel pain there? Why?
When did it start?
After seeing that pretty lady.
Who could it be?
Ms. Jin!
I made it according to your instructions.
Okay. Put it there.
-Give it to them in there.
-Okay.
I know how much you care
for your own piglets.
But this piglet has lost its mom.
Please share your milk, okay?
Goodness.
You must've been hungry.
-Ms. Jin.
-Yes?
It was scheduled
for sawdust to arrive today,
but the forecast says
there is an 80% chance of rain.
Let's push it back then.
Ask them to come when it's dry.
Okay.
Kang-ho.
It's forecast to rain today.
We have a hospital appointment
so stay home, okay?
Don't go outside.
Okay.
Ye-jin! Seo-jin!
Hello.
You're so adorable!
What's its name?
-Tiger.
-"Tiger"?
That's a unique name.
May I hold it?
Here. Careful.
-Tiger, careful. Come here.
-There we go.
Hello.
By the way, who are you?
I've never seen you here before.
Ms. Jo, it's me, Mi-joo.
Mi-joo?
Goodness! Gum-ja's youngest daughter!
-Yes.
-Yes, it's you!
You've grown really old,
so I didn't recognize you.
I thought you were in America.
Did you come back?
-Yes.
-I see.
How have you been?
I've been busy.
Life is really busy over there.
Mi-joo.
INTRUSION UPON HABITATION
I'm feeling it. Wait.
"Criminal Act, Article 319,
Intrusion upon Habitation."
"A person who intrudes upon
one’s residence, guarded building,
structure, ship, or occupied room,
shall be punished
for up to three years
or by a fine under five million won."
"Intrusion into My Heart"!
When did you come in?
Into my heart?
Into my tightly shut heart?
It'll sound good with a bit of work.
Oh, my.
Darn it.
Excuse me. Outsiders can't come in here.
Lady, why are you here?
How did you…
I get it now. This poop-smelling truck.
This is where the poop smell comes from!
What will you do about this?
-What is that?
-My clothes.
They're all ruined
because of the poop smell!
I'm sorry if the smell caused
any inconvenience.
It's usually fine,
but when it's windy and rainy,
it gets a little worse.
"A little worse"?
No one can breathe around here.
We're doing our best about that.
We have a smell reduction system
and sprayed ozonated water,
but no matter how clean we keep the place,
they're still livestock.
It's impossible to get rid of
the smell completely.
If you can't get rid of the smell,
you should get rid of the pig farm!
You're ruining other people's careers
just to make a living for yourself.
Isn't that right?
What are you talking about?
I didn't ruin anyone's career!
I'm a composer. An artist.
But I'm unable to do anything
because of this poop smell.
What if I can never write songs again?
Are you going to provide for me?
I'm warning you.
Stop being disrespectful.
Or what? What will you do?
Then I'll stop being polite too.
So you're a composer?
But you can't write a song?
Let me tell you why.
It's not because of the smell of the poop.
It's because you're an awful person!
You have no basic manners for others
and zero authenticity!
Forget it.
My business is legally registered,
and I'm operating my farm
without any legal problems.
So if you have any issues,
go file a complaint or sue me!
Do whatever you want.
I have no manners?
I'll show you what I'm made of.
You're dead.
Livestock Division!
-Livestock Division!
-How may I help you?
Livestock Division…
How may I help you, sir?
Is this
the Livestock Division?
It's the Livestock Division.
I thought you'd like pizza.
But you didn't even finish half.
It's too greasy, and it tastes bad.
Wait.
When we go to America, do we
have to eat food like this every day?
It's awful.
Can you just ask Dad to live in Korea?
Right, when will he come?
Well…
Things are busy at the beauty salon,
so he can't come for a while.
What a relief.
Right? I was scared that he might come.
-What?
-Look, there's a clothing store.
The nail salon next door?
It's been closed for a while.
They picked the wrong business.
Most of the customers
around here are elderly farmers.
Who would get their nails done
in this rural village?
I'm about to go bust too.
It's a hassle to do it every year,
but once we cut and dry them,
we can eat pumpkin seeds,
porridge, pancakes,
and rice cake all winter.
It's the best snack, isn't it?
I mean,
I always tell her
we should all come and work together.
How come she never shows up?
Don't be so harsh on her.
It's not easy to raise pigs.
I'm not talking about Young-soon!
Let me ask you something.
Mr. Son, when, where, how, and why…
did you meet someone like her?
I've never heard the story either.
I haven't been able to tell you
for the sake of our village's safety.
But I think it's finally time.
She was actually…
a daughter of a newly rising yakuza boss
in Japan.
-What?
Her family had to disperse
to avoid their enemies' attacks.
And that's how
she ended up coming to Korea.
She wandered around,
then she collapsed in a valley
at Mount Gyeryong.
I found her and saved her.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Wake up.
Are you all right?
If her true identity is leaked,
there will be…
-Goodness!
-Goodness.
…bloodshed in this village.
So if you don't want to die…
-Goodness!
Get the porridge ready.
Pumpkin porridge.
You totally got us!
You scared us!
It's not like you to make such jokes.
"Get the porridge ready!"
-Goodness!
-My gosh!
Good grief!
You scared me!
I'm sorry.
I'm late, aren't I?
What?
Which one should I cut open first?
-My gosh!
-What's up with you?
-My gosh.
-Look at this.
I don't want to die.
Your nails are so pretty!
Mi-joo did it for you, right?
I already know you take
great care of your farm.
But we're civil servants,
so we must deal with complaints.
I'm sorry my farm
is taking up your busy schedule.
Don't mention it.
I should speak with you in person,
but it's foot-and-mouth disease
control period
so farm visits are restricted.
Yes, I'm well aware.
I'll do what I can to take care of it,
so don't worry about it.
Yes.
Okay. Goodbye.
Mom, look.
I can fully squeeze this now.
You're the best.
See? All the exercise
is paying off, isn't it?
Yes.
If you continue to practice walking
and treat your legs,
you'll be able to walk very soon.
Gosh.
Mom.
There's something I want.
-Something you want?
-Yes.
There's something you want?
Tell me. I'll buy anything for you.
A dog.
-A dog?
-Yes.
We have a dog at the farm. Yellow.
No, not like Yellow.
A dog that I can keep in the room
like Ms. Jo's dog.
A dog that I can carry in my arms.
No, you can't have that.
And in the room?
What about all the fur?
And who will pick up after it?
Who will feed and wash it?
I will! I'll do everything.
Kang-ho, who made you breakfast
this morning?
You did.
Who bathed you and helped you get dressed?
Goodness.
And you have rhinitis too.
So, no.
Come on, Mom. Please.
-Please, just this once.
-No.
You can't have a dog.
HAPPY FARM
We're here. Let's go.
Good. One second.
Kang-ho, great job.
Let's try moving your feet.
How…
can I live with this?
Don't get discouraged.
Kang-ho. Look at me.
You're doing great right now.
You got this.
You're a miracle.
A miracle in our hospital.
Not everyone can recover so quick--
-No, dog.
-Yes, dawg, you're tough!
Tougher than anyone!
No, not that!
That dog! I want that dog!
Oh, my Happy?
You can't have Happy. That's my dog.
The foot-and-mouth disease also broke out
in North Gyeongsang.
Quarantine authorities are doing
everything they can to prevent the spread.
Next story.
-Ms. Jin Young-soon.
-Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo
-Come to the endoscopy room.
-of the Jeilmirae Party
-Yes.
-declared candidacy
for the primary presidential election.
Park Min-hui reports.
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo,
with the highest approval ratings
as a potential candidate,
-held a press conference
-That's…
in his office in Yeouido,
-officially declaring
-"Oh Tae-soo…"
his presidential candidacy.
-His first schedule
-He's that prosecutor.
-was visiting a nearby market
-Oh, my.
-to encourage businesses.
-He must be running for president.
-The marketplace was packed
-Ms. Jin.
-with reporters and supporters.
-Come in.
-Okay.
-Assemblyman Oh
promised the revitalization
of local marketplaces
and took his first step for the campaign.
-I need to make a bathroom run.
-Okay.
What's this?
He was with another woman.
He even had a child with her.
He wanted to marry you,
so he killed her and his child.
I can't believe this.
Do you expect me to believe this?
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Fine.
Let's say this is true.
Why didn't you
report him to the police then?
It was 30 years ago.
He knew I was involved
in his father's death.
He's trying to use you
to take revenge on me.
Jujubes are said to be
natural tranquilizers.
You said your symptoms weren't severe,
so don't take any medication.
Just have some jujube tea before bed.
I went to the marketplace in the morning
to get them, so don't throw them away.
If I report him to the police
and an investigation is launched,
everything will be exposed to the world.
And that'll be the end of me.
Ha-young.
We should end this first.
If news of his
son's draft evasion breaks out,
people will turn their backs.
This is why
it's best to have daughters
since they're free of military service.
-Cheers.
Ha-young.
-What happened to your hand?
-Hello.
Goodness.
I gave him the pills to kill him.
What are you saying?
-Take her upstairs.
-Please come upstairs.
Dad.
I did it.
-Ha-young!
-Wait.
I did it, Mom.
Dad.
Dad?
-Please come upstairs.
-I did it.
Dad?
I'm telling you, I did it.
Kang-ho ended up like that,
so he must be like a dog off its leash.
He needs to be squeezed tight
to realize who's holding his leash, right?
I'll find Yang Gu-man's suicide note.
Mr. So, that's not a card we can play.
Who'll believe
what's on a criminal's suicide note?
Even if we do find the water bottle
with Kang-ho's blood on it,
how are we going to prove
Ha-young did that?
Oh Tae-soo knows all this.
He was once a prosecutor.
So we need to secure
a hidden ace up our sleeves
to use in unforeseen situations.
Bring me that.
I already know you take
great care of your farm.
But we're civil servants,
so we must deal with complaints.
What are you doing there?
I want to see you.
Mom.
Why are you so pretty?
You're prettier than people on TV.
You're much prettier than IU, Mom.
I said no.
Why not?
Mi-joo likes dogs.
Mi-joo?
Oh, my.
Do you remember her?
I keep thinking of her.
So please, Mom.
Buy me a dog so that I can show her.
But Mi-joo is married
and lives in America now.
So even if you had one,
you couldn't show her.
No, Mi-joo lives at Ye-jin's house.
I'm going to go to visit our neighbor.
Don't go out and stay home.
Don't go out.
Yellow.
Come here, Yellow.
Good boy. Yellow.
All right, come here. Good boy.
Come here. It's all right.
Good boy.
All right. One second.
Stay still, Yellow.
-No!
This can't happen! Yellow!
-No, Yellow! Gosh.
-Kang-ho.
Hold this. Halt immediately!
FROM THE PIG FARM
PLEASE ENJOY
You surprised me.
This isn't your first time seeing me.
Why are you so surprised?
You're right.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, to get my nails done.
I see.
-See you around.
-Okay.
Wait.
What kind of dog is that?
Canine.
Yes, I know that.
I meant the breed.
Bi…
Bickering?
It was something like that.
Bishop?
-Bi…
-Bichon?
Yes, that's right.
Bichon.
I understand what you're saying,
but to be precise,
the farm was in the village first.
You moved in after.
There's nothing we can do
in this situation.
I already spoke to the farm
and provided guidance.
Guidance?
Even a street dog could
give them this much guidance.
What did you say?
I mean, a citizen is suffering from it.
My rights to the pursuit of happiness
are being violated!
And who provides your paycheck?
You're paid by our tax money.
I'm the reason why you're making a living!
You're crossing the line.
The farm owner is a citizen too.
She pays taxes too.
Or has she done anything illegal
at the farm?
Why are you giving her such a hard time?
What's your name? Where's your name tag?
And why are you yelling at me?
I'll call the Minister of Agriculture,
Food and Rural Affairs
and make sure you get
the biggest lesson of your lifetime.
I'll end your life!
Go ahead.
Even the old villagers don't say anything,
and you roll in and do this?
"Roll in"? I'll show you how I roll.
I will defend
my right to pursue happiness!
Bichon.
Goodness.
How can I work with these hands?
They're so pretty.
Right? Goodness.
Forget working.
I don't even want them to get wet.
How can I cook?
Make your husband cook.
What are husbands for?
Should I do that?
My hands are as pretty as my maiden days,
so maybe he'll do it for me, right?
Oh, my.
Were your hands
as huge as a caldron lid back then?
-Caldron lids?
-Never mind.
Caldron lids are at least shiny.
You little…
-You and your mouth.
-Stop it.
When did he come and leave this here?
I don't think he came and left it.
It was in the drain.
Does this mean
we can't see Kang-ho anymore?
No way. We live in the same village.
We'll run into each other sometimes.
Do we pretend he's a stranger?
I'm sure a little nod will be fine.
Poor Kang-ho.
He must be bored without us.
But why do we seem more bored
than he might be?
Kang-ho!
I mean, Kang-ho oppa.
I mean, Uncle Kang-ho.
Seo-jin, Ye-jin. What brings you here?
This is our home,
so we're usually here.
Right.
Anyway, what's that?
My goodness.
Is that a pig?
This is my pet pig,
Lion!
A dog named Tiger
and a pig named Lion.
What an odd village.
May I hold the pig?
Sure.
Be careful.
By the way,
are there any other people in the house?
Other people?
There are lots of people.
Lots?
No, Lion!
-No!
-Lion!
-Catch it!
I have to give it to Mi-joo!
What?
Kang-ho left with a pig?
I deserve to die, Ms. Jin.
That punk.
HAPPY FARM, PIG FARM, OFFICE
-Wait, Lion!
-Hurry up!
-Hurry up and catch it!
-No, Lion!
-Lion!
Lion!
Choi Kang-ho!
-Catch it!
-Lion!
-Run!
Yes.
You said you know
the Minister of Agriculture,
Food and Rural Affairs, right?
How do you know him?
Yes, the minister has a daughter.
The daughter's friend? Yes.
And…
Hey, if that's the case,
I might be closer to him, you punk.
-Hey, listen.
-Lion!
-Where are you going?
-I'll really kill--
-Lion!
I just had an accident.
Yes, I was driving!
I'm sorry!
Hey, stop right there!
You rascals!
Damn it!
Damn it! Hey!
-Lion!
-No!
-I can't.
No!
Guys, come on.
I can't run anymore!
Yes, we're done.
You should go.
Come here.
If your mom catches
the three of us on that,
we're dead meat.
We're already dead because of Lion.
Come quickly!
Kang-ho!
-Ye-jin!
-Seo-jin!
-Assemble!
Seo-jin!
Ye-jin!
-Move!
-Lion!
-All right!
-Let's go!
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
-See you later.
-Thanks.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
-Bye!
-Goodbye.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Should I open a nail salon here?
You saw how thrilled they were.
Women will be women
even in a rural village.
They all want to be pretty.
What do you think?
Do you have
enough money?
How will you open it?
Just go set the table.
Come on, Mom.
Stop right there!
Mom, catch it!
-Catch Lion!
-Catch the pig!
-Mom, hurry!
-Mom!
-Catch the pig!
-Catch it, Mom!
-Mom, catch it!
Lion!
Mom, catch Lion!
-Catch Lion!
-Mom, hurry!
-Lion!
-Catch it!
She caught it! Mom!
-Yes.
-What a relief.
What a relief.
Thank you.
Lion.
It's…
Choi Kang-ho!
Run! Now!
Stop right there!
-Hurry up!
-Hurry!
That little…
Darn it.
Hello?
Yes, Director.
Yes, regarding the dog
you asked about earlier.
Let me call you back right back.
Stop right there!
Mi-joo?
Oh, my.
Kang-ho really was talking about you.
Goodness, he mentioned Mi-joo?
He kept saying he had to show her a dog,
and I had no idea what he meant.
Anyway, are you back for good?
What about your husband?
Well, the thing is…
He owns a huge beauty salon in America.
Right.
She's back for the children.
It's just her for now.
I see.
But isn't it wonderful?
Your husband is successful,
and you have adorable children.
Right.
Is Kang-ho back?
Yes, don't let him into the piggery.
I'm sorry. I have to get going.
-Come by for a visit.
-Okay.
-Bye.
-All right.
If I catch them, I'll kill them.
What is this? What's this water?
Wait a second.
It smells like disinfectant.
ALL INCOMING CARS
MUST BE DISINFECTED
Do you know how sensitive pigs are?
When one of them is infected,
they all get sick.
This one ran all around the village,
so who knows what it caught?
What are we going to do with it?
I'm sorry.
It lost its mom
and is the runt of the litter
that gets pushed around by other pigs.
I had to feed the poor thing
through a surrogate mom.
Mom.
Can I keep this one?
I'll feed it,
wash it, and put it to sleep.
What?
I have you,
but this pig doesn't have a mom.
I'll be its mom.
Nonsense.
How will you raise
a dirty and smelly pig at home?
"Everyone thinks
pigs are dirty and smelly,
but that's not the case."
"They not only
do their business in one place,
but they also only sleep
where it's clean."
"But humans started to lock them up
in tiny pigsties."
"Isn't that so sad?"
That's what you said.
Who could it be?
All right.
Come here.
Let's go inside.
Go in. I'll be right back.
Coming!
Who is it?
Hey. Are you kidding me?
Oh, no.
Are you bummed about the food?
Then look at my car.
I almost totaled the car not long ago.
But you let out the darned pig again
and made me drive it into a ditch.
I'll have to scrap it!
I don't know what happened,
but I'll compensate you if you were harmed
in any way because of us.
Okay, good.
Then give me a billion won a year.
What?
I'm a composer.
I write at least 60 songs a year
for 10 million each,
so that's 600 million won.
Plus the royalty
and album sales.
You haven't even released
ten songs altogether.
And they're off the market
because of plagiarism.
You were sued for the newest song
because it was the same as
"Ripe Persimmon" by Na Hoon-a.
-What's your problem?
-Goodness.
Are you a detective or something?
-Who the heck are you?
-What's with you?
-Let go!
-What the…
-Who are you?
-Hey!
Hey!
Darn it. Hey!
So you're saying
Mr. Choi Kang-ho here attacked you first?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I won't do that again. I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You did nothing wrong, okay?
I mean,
there's no son who would hold back
when he sees his mom
being grabbed and hurled on the floor.
I was grabbing her,
but he suddenly rushed at me,
then pushed me, so I let go of her.
I'm not going to settle.
Just arrest him.
All right, don't be like this.
Ms. Jin here is
a woman of great character,
and she has a great relationship
with everyone here.
You've become neighbors now, so--
"Neighbors"?
I'm a civil man,
so I haven't done anything,
but I can sue them for a lot of things.
Hey, tell them.
You intruded on my house,
and then you brought
that pig out on the road.
That's why I'm in this mess.
Isn't that so?
It's Lion.
It was a pig, you idiot!
Hey!
"Idiot"?
My son is much smarter
and has much better judgment than you do!
Then you tell me
with your better judgment.
Did you see me get into a car accident?
-Did you or did you not?
-I did!
Game over.
-He saw me.
-That man…
I'll really kill--
He saw Lion, tried to dodge it,
and then the car swerved and crashed.
And he said this into the phone.
"I just had an accident."
"Yes, I was driving!"
Then he got out of the car and fell down.
Hang on.
Hold on.
That means
you used your phone while driving.
Were you even wearing your seatbelt?
Well…
I mean,
well…
Phone use is a violation
of Article 49, Paragraph 1,
Item 10 of the Road Traffic Act.
Neglect of a seatbelt is a violation
of Article 50, Paragraph 1
of the Road Traffic Act.
-I'll fold.
-Another one.
-Give him one.
-I'm done.
Hey, bring me a pack of cigarettes!
-Yes.
-Here we go.
Bet big, will you?
I'll take one.
Enjoy your cigarettes.
-Hey, a pack of cigarettes.
-Yes, sir.
-Goodness.
-What now?
Okay.
Good work.
-Gosh.
-That's your paycheck.
You little…
You bastard.
Let go!
I've been looking everywhere for you.
-Bang Sam-sik?
-Yes, that's me, you asshole.
You knew it was stolen, right?
You sent me there knowing it was stolen.
I rotted in prison for months
because of you!
Your friend is a prosecutor!
I thought he would get you out.
He was never my friend, you punk.
Goodness!
This afternoon,
a violent fight between gangs broke out
at an adult entertainment business
in Ilcheong-dong,
-resulting in 2 deaths and 17 injuries.
-Goodness.
It must be heartbreaking news
for the parents of those punks.
You know, Sam-sik may have quick hands,
but he doesn't get into fights.
Isn't that a relief?
Don't I look different today?
My head hurts. Oh, my.
Wait.
These fell off your nails.
How did those end up there?
No, it's all right.
My wife looks
so sexy for the first time in 40 years.
What's with you? Gosh.
Oh, my.
-Just eat your meal.
-No.
Oh, my.
Next story.
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo, the presidential
candidate of the Jeilmirae Party,
volunteered to do laundry
at the temporary shelter
for flood victims in Anseon,
now designated as a special disaster area
due to the typhoon.
Assemblyman Oh
made his visit with his family
and was surprised to see
how the situation seemed worse in person.
You're banned from going out
except for official occasions.
Don't schedule any performances
for the time being
and don't meet anybody.
Is that my next job?
Sure, I'll do as you say.
If you're still worried, take this.
You never know
when I'll start acting crazy again.
Ha-young.
Listen to me carefully.
If you ever get in my way,
I will not condone it,
even if it's you.
Dad.
Don't worry.
Nothing in Korea can threaten you.
-Hello, Assemblyman Oh.
-Hello.
-Are you doing okay?
-I'm fine.
Unless…
he regains his memories.
Let's get rid of
Choi Kang-ho.
Hey, Kang-ho.
Yes?
Well…
About what you said at the police station.
You know, the Road Traffic Act.
How did you remember that?
Road Traffic…
What? What's that?
Kang-ho.
You go in first.
I'm going to stop by Mr. Son's place.
I'll go too.
No, I'll be quick.
But still…
Right, what about Lion?
Lion didn't have dinner.
It must be hungry.
Right, Lion.
Okay, then. Come home quickly.
-Okay.
-I'll feed Lion so come back quickly.
Goodness.
What kind of a jerk made a scene
and made you suffer like this?
Goodness, it's okay.
It's just a stomach cramp.
The medicine will help me feel better.
This is bad. You're sick so often.
Our medicine cabinet
is empty because of you.
Goodness, woman. Stop talking nonsense.
You and that red face mask!
I'm just saying.
Don't worry about it,
although it's costing us a fortune
to refill the medications.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll go to town and refill
your medicine cabinet tomorrow.
Goodness, no.
It's all right.
Anyway, if you're this sick,
shouldn't you get a checkup?
I got a gastroscopy yesterday.
I'll get the result next week.
It's because you have
too much on your plate.
I'll meet with that composer or whatever,
so don't worry about him.
Thank you, Mr. Son.
Will you do something
about that red face thing?
Take it off or turn it off!
Damn it. It's yellow now.
I'm relieved that Mom
is at Mr. Son's place.
Gosh, Lion. What are you going to do now?
You're going to get kicked out.
Mom.
Mom?
No!
No.
Who are you?
THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
Promise me you won't
get into trouble like last time.
-Promise.
-Mi-joo!
Mi-joo!
Do you know him?
No, I…
I don't want to see you anymore.
This is the last time
I'll be helping you out.
Mom.
Please help me, sir.
-Help me.
-Sam-sik.
Are we friends?
How dare they say that to our friend?
The pig farm was kind of an inconvenience.
We can't deny that.
And now, she'll be betrayed
by the villagers she trusted.
Mom.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon