THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
-You punk.
-What the…
-You punk. How could you do that?
-What's wrong with you?
-How could you?
-What's with you?
-Calm down.
-I mean,
of all people,
how could you do that to Kang-ho,
that poor kid?
Why do you pity him?
-What?
-He got all the attention
for being smart and getting good grades.
And now he's getting all the attention
because he's become an idiot.
As if his mom's love isn't enough,
even the lady next door dotes on him.
You were always too busy with the mill
to make me a birthday meal,
but when Kang-ho got into SNU,
you even closed the mill
and threw him a feast!
Darn it, I'm your kid, not him.
Why do you think I did that?
I thought you'd benefit a little
if you were around a smart kid like him.
It was humiliating and frustrating,
but I still put up with everything.
That's…
That's how I held out.
Why are you crying?
You're breaking my heart. It's all right.
Hey, you punk.
Why are you making my woman cry?
I needed some money.
I wanted to work,
but I couldn't get a job anywhere
with my criminal record.
How much do you need?
Tell me!
-Two…
-What? Two million won?!
Two million won?!
You cursed punk! Two million won?!
Look who it is.
My love Mi-joo…
Mom, where are we going?
Where is she going this early?
Hello?
What?
Kang-ho.
Let's eat and get ready.
We'll be having a guest soon.
You're upsetting me right now.
Mom, where are we going?
This is Kang-ho oppa's place.
Ye-jin.
Seo-jin.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom.
Excuse me.
Is this Mr. Choi Kang-ho's place?
Yes.
This is it.
Don't give out
his personal information to a stranger!
Who are you
and why are you looking for him?
My name is Hoang.
I'm supposed to meet him today,
but I couldn't get in touch.
Mom.
Mi-joo, my mom…
-What?
-Mom…
What's going on?
Mom.
Ms. Jin!
-Mom, please.
-Ms. Jin, wake up.
-Mom.
-Ms. Jin!
-Oh, no.
-No…
-Don't shake her like that. Please move.
-Sorry?
Okay.
She's in hypovolemic shock.
Hello? I'm calling from Jou-ri.
We have a medical emergency.
Kang-ho, bring me a thick blanket
and pillows.
Okay, a blanket and pillows.
-A blanket…
-How long will it take?
It's an emergency.
Please come quickly.
-Yes.
-Lift up her legs so the blood
-can get to her heart.
-Legs.
-Higher.
-Okay.
-You two go wait at home.
Is Ms. Jin dead?
No. Don't worry.
Seo-jin, go home with Ye-jin.
Okay?
Good. Get home safely.
Ms. Hoang.
-Can you stay with her for 20 minutes?
-Yes, of course.
Kang-ho, where's the car key?
The car key?
HAPPY FARM
License plate 6169, pink truck.
Pull over to the right. You're speeding.
License plate 6169, pull over!
-Pull up next to them.
-Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
-Pull over.
-Can't you hear me?
You're speeding!
Sir! Please help us!
-What?
-My mom just collapsed.
It's hy…
Hy…
Hypovolemic shock.
Hypovolemic… What?
-Hypovolemic shock.
-Hype?
What are you saying?
Hypovolemic shock!
-What?
-She's in hypovolemic shock!
-Hurry up and go.
-Yes, sir.
We're escorting an emergency patient.
Please make way.
-Put her on IV.
-What's wrong with my mom?
Why is she ill?
I'm sorry, but please wait outside.
No, I want to stay here.
Let's wait outside
so that she can get treated.
Thank you.
We arrived safely
thanks to your first aid.
I should thank you.
You drove her here
without waiting for the ambulance,
so my mother-in-law
could get treated quickly.
I see.
-Hey.
-Here.
You must be in shock.
We're at the hospital now,
so you can relax.
Thank you.
By the way, who are you?
I didn't get to introduce myself
in the midst of this chaos.
My name is Hoang,
and we were supposed to meet today.
Ms. Jin Young-soon's guardian?
-Yes?
You wanted to open
a clothing store, didn't you?
I'll open one for you,
but make a small space in a corner
for a nail salon.
It's not for you!
It's for Mi-joo!
I'll sell my garlic field
and whatever else to fund it,
so take Mi-joo and the twins
and look after them.
Your sister
will be ruined if she stays here.
Goodness.
Goodness, it smells rotten.
It smells like an old man.
Hoon-ah?
Are you here?
My goodness, this place reeks.
What's all this?
Baek Hoon-ah!
Goodness! What the hell are you doing?
Serves you right.
You're getting punished.
Right, that pig lady.
How's she doing these days?
The foot-and-mouth disease
took a toll on her,
but she's doing better now.
Not that.
Then what? Her son?
That woman.
Good grief, how frustrating!
What?
She hasn't told anybody?
She's still keeping it a secret?
What are you talking about?
A secret?
She's critically ill?
She has stage four stomach cancer.
The cancer cells have metastasized
to her peritoneum and lungs,
so there's…
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Doctor,
but please speak with me.
It's tough for him to understand
what you're saying right now.
I'm a friend of his and--
No.
Please speak with me. I want to hear it.
I'm…
I'm my mom's guardian.
Kang-ho, wait.
Kang-ho!
Mom, get up.
Mom, get up. Come with me.
Mom, let's go home.
Kang-ho, don't do this.
Come home with me, Mom.
Mom, open your eyes!
Mom…
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'll do as you say from now on.
I won't…
I won't be a prosecutor anymore.
Mom, please get up.
-Kang-ho, stop it.
-Mom.
Mom, I won't like Mi-joo anymore,
just as you wanted.
I won't like Mi-joo anymore.
Mom, so please, wake up.
Wake up, Mom.
Hey, Andrea.
I think
you set me up with the wrong guy.
Is anybody…
up there?
Is anyone…
really up there?
I know you can be cruel,
but this is way too harsh.
Wasn't it enough
to take her husband
and make her son like that?
What did that good woman ever do?
Goodness.
How could you try to take her life too?
Grandma!
Grandma, where have you been?
We looked everywhere for you.
Ms. Jin collapsed!
She collapsed?
When?
This morning.
Mom and Kang-ho oppa
took her to the hospital.
YOUNGEST DAUGHTER MI-JOO
Gimbap with no carrots.
Eat some.
Everyone Mom made gimbap for
never returned home.
Grandma, Grandpa,
and Dad too.
That's why she never let me go
on a school picnic.
She was afraid I wouldn't return.
So my mom isn't a bad person.
You're right.
She's not a bad person.
Then why is she ill?
I'm getting punished
because I'm a bad person.
But why is my mom being punished?
No, Kang-ho.
Neither of you
is getting punished.
This is…
something that nobody wants,
but something that can happen to anybody.
Just as Ms. Jin was there for you
when you were unwell,
it's your turn
to stay strong by her side.
Okay?
She's going to be fine.
She'll be okay.
Hey!
Hey, get away from him!
What are you two doing in broad daylight?
Mom.
Hello.
I'm afraid I don't have time
to exchange greetings.
Where's your mom?
I'll stay here.
You should go home
and look after your kids.
Listen, Mom.
Go home.
You darn brat.
You crazy bitch.
I ought to…
Lead the way.
Ma'am, what are you doing?
You can't do this.
Let go of me!
Doctor.
Will I live if I get this IV shot?
Will I live if I stay in bed?
If not, let me go.
Help me make the best use
of the time I have left.
I have…
I have no time to be here.
I was supposed to meet
my son's future bride today.
What time is it right now?
Goodness.
Oh, no.
My goodness.
Goodness.
My goodness, why is this happening?
My goodness.
My goodness. Oh, no.
Things were finally beginning to
look up for you.
Do you see the tear here?
And you dare sell this
as an authentic item?
I thought of reporting you
but decided to refrain.
I want a refund.
I'm so sorry,
but how do I know if there was
something wrong with the stitch work
because of what I did
-or what you--
-I'll report it.
I'm not looking to nitpick over that.
I need cash to give you a refund,
but as you can see, I don't have…
You have exactly two million.
Sorry?
BALANCE 2,000,000 WON
PARK SUNG-AE
I'm busy. What do you want?
Why did you deposit money
without my permission?
-Pay it back.
-Okay.
Mom, while you're at it,
can you lend me some more?
Gosh, my mom can be so cool.
It looks brand new.
Who did this to the bag?
What is this?
What the…
"DNA Test Result"?
Hello, Ms. Hoang.
It's me, Kang-ho's mom.
I didn't have my phone with me
so I couldn't call you.
I'm so sorry about this morning.
I heard from my son
that you came to the hospital with him.
Sorry?
What do you mean?
Nonsense.
It's a misunderstanding.
Mi-joo is just a childhood friend.
Don't be like that. Let's meet.
Let's talk in person.
Ms. Hoang?
Mom, where are you going?
Stay here.
No, Mom. You're very ill right now.
Yes.
You heard it from the doctor, right?
I'm very ill right now.
So please,
just stay here.
Did you tell him?
What?
Didn't you go to tell him
that he's Ye-jin and Seo-jin's father?
I did.
At the very least,
I thought Ms. Jin should know.
Goodness.
This is bad.
But…
I couldn't tell her
because she collapsed.
You couldn't?
Wait.
You didn't tell her?
Goodness gracious.
Thank you, deities of heaven and earth.
What a relief.
You should
take the kids
and go live with your eldest sister.
I talked to her, and she agreed.
You can open up a nail salon there.
Listen.
It's not just Kang-ho anymore.
His mom is unwell too.
Do you want to waste your life
looking after people?
-Mom, come on!
-Yes.
I'm your mom.
And my daughter is about to ruin her life,
so what wouldn't I say to stop you?
Mom.
You must be mistaken.
Listen carefully.
I'm
never getting back with him.
What you're imagining right now
will never happen.
Yes.
I plan to live happily with my kids.
Right?
You will, right?
But…
I won't run away either.
Why should I?
Why should Ye-jin and Seo-jin do that?
Mi-joo.
Mi-joo, are you there?
-Mi-joo.
-Yes?
Do you remember that young lady
who came to the hospital?
Yes. Ms. Hoang, right?
Yes, that's her.
She's going to
marry Kang-ho.
Yes, I know.
You do?
You already knew?
Then why did you do that?
Sorry? What did I do?
I mean,
what did you do to make her say
she won't marry him because of you?
Mi-joo.
I asked you to help me.
I told you about my situation
and asked you to help me.
Then you shouldn't have ruined this.
Why do you
always ruin Kang-ho's future?
Who's ruining whose future?
Mom.
Don't you think you're crossing the line?
How could you torment my kid
for the sake of your kid?
Mom, stop it.
You also did that
when she got into that accident!
How was it her fault
that Kang-ho didn't take the exam?
She was hurt badly!
Why do you blame everything on my child?
But I still put up with you
because I knew
what you went through raising him.
Yet you're going this far?
Do you have any idea
-who ruined whose future?
-Mom! Stop!
Go back inside. Please!
-Darn it.
-Go inside.
Go.
Go inside.
Take a good look.
Don't you remember this bag?
I don't know.
Hey, sit back down.
Don't be so half-hearted again. Goodness.
You gave this bag to your mom
on the day you brought
your fiancée to introduce to her.
Assemblyman Oh's daughter.
Why do you have the bag
I bought for my mom?
Did you steal this too?
Of course not.
Your mom gave it to my mom.
I'm serious!
You don't trust me?
-Should I call my mom?
-So what is it that you want to say?
Yes, right.
What I wanted to say was…
Do you know what this is?
Take a good look.
I do.
-Do you know whose this is?
-No.
Right, you don't.
Well, while we're on the subject…
Ta-da!
We're about to look at this together.
Why should I do that with you?
Well, because…
Kang-ho, you said
you wanted to be a prosecutor.
Take a look.
"DNA Test Result."
It's a test result.
It's a test that shows if you have the DNA
to be a prosecutor.
And the result is right in here. Got it?
I'm not going to be a prosecutor anymore.
-My mom doesn't approve.
-Darn it.
Yes, right.
You won't, right?
So let's find out if your DNA says
you don't have to be a prosecutor.
Please just do the damn thing.
When I click this file here,
I have to type in a password.
-Do you know it?
-Zero, nine, zero, seven.
Zero, nine, zero, seven?
I didn't expect it'd go so smoothly…
I knew it, you punk.
-That's not it.
-Zero, three, one, two.
Zero, three… Okay, zero, three, one, two.
I have a good feeling…
ENTER PASSWORD
…about nothing.
Damn it, that's not it either.
Get it together!
Think again. Hurry.
CAPTAIN BAE
Keep trying.
Goodness, sir.
I was about to give you a call just now.
I'll let you talk alone then.
ENTER PASSWORD:
DKQJWL
Darn it, what the heck?
Move aside.
Sam-sik, look.
What?
-No way! You opened it?
-I…
My gosh, Kang-ho! My dear Kang-ho!
My smart fiancée.
Good.
All right, let's take a look.
Before we do that,
we should get rid of everything
-that can hurt us.
-What?
It's a voice recording, not a video.
Will you get rid of the original
DNA test result in front of me?
-Come on. Getting rid of that paper
-This guy.
-won't change anything.
-Who's this?
This guy.
He'll get rid of them
as if they never existed.
My son will do that.
Right?
I'll take care of it.
That's your voice, Kang-ho. Right?
I'll let you talk alone then.
Is that all?
Are you suggesting that
we kill Hwang Soo-hyun?
We can't just get rid of the mother.
The kid must go too.
This won't cause trouble, right?
The mighty Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo
is scared of something like this?
Don't worry.
Even if it does cause trouble later,
Kang-ho will take the fall.
That's why I keep him around.
Then I'll be counting on you,
Chairman Song.
Sure.
What are they talking about?
So this
belongs to Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo?
Yes!
This is it.
Sam-sik.
What is this?
Who are they? Why am I talking about
this stuff with them?
I already told you.
You were going to marry
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo's daughter.
Then who's Hwang Soo-hyun?
Did I do something to her?
You said you'd take care of her.
So what did you do to her?
You didn't
kill her or anything, right?
Hey.
What are you doing?
-This is mine.
-So what will you do?
I don't know.
But I feel like
I need to find out what this is.
-My mom might know.
-No.
Hey, you idiot. Are you stupid?
If your mom knew about this,
would she have given this bag to my mom?
I understand how you feel.
Of course, you'd want to know.
Okay.
Let's do this.
I'll find out for you.
-You will?
-Yes.
I'll meet and ask them myself.
Think about it.
There's a possibility
that you really did something very bad.
And if you did and your mom finds out,
she'll be greatly shocked.
Don't you think so?
-What are you doing?
-Listen up.
I have to know what this is.
So if you deceive me
and do something weird again,
I won't let it slide, okay?
Okay.
Here's the password.
D, K, Q…
That spells "father."
Mom is ill.
By the way, Dad,
who are you?
Why was I reminded of you
when I heard those scary words?
I've never even met you.
So why do I miss you?
Why does my heart…
ache so much?
Who are you, Dad?
And who am I?
What do I have to do?
There you were, Kang-ho.
How are you?
Are you happy?
Your dad was really in love with me.
What? It's true.
He used to follow me around
asking me to hug and kiss him.
Gosh, it was so bothersome.
He'd never spend a second away from me.
Just like you, Kang-ho.
Come to think about it,
you take after your dad a lot.
Your stubbornness
and strong determination
all come from him.
But your dad
wasn't always that strong.
He cried very easily.
He'd always
rub my big belly while you were in my womb
and cry saying he missed you,
that he loved you,
and that he was sorry.
Then you'd begin to kick in there.
"Mom, Dad, I'm here."
"I can see everything from here!"
It was as if you were answering.
I wanted to
grow old together with him.
But our time was cut very short.
Kang-ho.
Later on,
when I die, please bury me
next to your dad.
I want to be with him for a long time.
-Mom.
-Kang-ho.
When you get married and have kids,
will you visit us with them?
I'm sure they'll be adorable.
Your child will grow up,
go to school, and get married.
And you'll grow older
and become a dad, and then a grandpa.
Mom and Dad
will watch over you
from this round mound.
No, we'll protect you.
So Kang-ho,
don't feel lonely even when I'm gone.
You aren't alone.
Okay?
Mom, why are you so mean?
I know, Mom.
I know everything.
But do you have to say that?
Just say,
"It's all right. This is nothing."
"I can fight this and win.
I'll get better."
Why can't you just say that?
Why do you always…
Why…
Why do you always say things
that hurt me right here?
Why do you always make me do tough things?
Why do you always do everything your way?
Cooking, doing the laundry,
farming, and banking.
After you teach me everything
like a mother pig,
you'll go somewhere nice without me.
I don't want that!
No!
Then I won't do anything.
No, I'd rather not know
how to do anything.
I'm just going to
live my life like an idiot.
So Mom, you can't leave me!
Mom, please.
Please don't leave me, Mom.
Mom.
Mom, just…
Just a little…
Just stay a little longer.
Mom…
Okay.
I'll take my time.
I will leave…
very, very slowly.
So let's not be sad
and let's not cry.
Let's not be like that.
I want to spend
every minute and second I have left
being happy with you.
Okay?
Who is it?
Gum-ja.
I'm sorry.
I felt sorry for Kang-ho
for growing up without a dad.
I didn't want him
to feel his dad's absence,
so I've been selfish.
After he became the way he is,
I finally realized
my love for him was misguided.
But I haven't really changed.
You were right.
Your child is as precious as mine.
I've hurt Mi-joo…
very deeply.
Even after everything you've done for me.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
Please forgive me.
Goodness.
There's no need to kneel.
You aren't even well.
Get up.
Stand up.
Stand up already.
Get up.
Gum-ja.
Am I really going to die?
I'm scared.
What do I do?
What do I do, Gum-ja?
Please let me live.
Please help me live.
Goodness, you poor thing.
Please let me live.
One day, you're going to die by my hands.
I'll probably die of anxiety before then.
-Goodness!
-Hey!
-This is amazing!
-Excuse me.
Please give the brewery
-a lot of time on air.
-Are you wearing makeup?
I heard you need to put on makeup
to be on TV.
We've never had
such a joyous occasion before.
I can't believe our village will be on TV!
I'm sorry to say this,
but I don't think we can be seen on TV.
See?
I knew it. I was right, wasn't I?
I was suspicious of you
from the moment we met.
They're here to hide
because they did something bad.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Don't say something so dreadful
about these wonderful men
who brought honor to Jou-ri.
Look at them.
Does he look like someone
who's up to no good?
His eyes are so kind, just like cow eyes.
And his last name also means cow.
See? He's just like a cow.
Anyway, we don't have a particular secret.
All we ever did was water them.
Right?
We didn't…
just water them.
"As makgeolli ferments,
the soil becomes aerobic
and grows many beneficial bacteria
and prevents diseases."
You were so cool.
How did you come up with that?
Just pack up.
We have to beg the chairman
for forgiveness
before the program goes on air.
Otherwise, we'll become manure
for the lettuce.
Let's go
Let's go to Seoul
Just go.
Just drive by.
Just go!
Mr. Cha!
We'll look suspicious if we just go.
Let's say bye before we go.
Hello.
So and Cha, where are you going?
We have to go to Seoul for business.
-Seoul?
-Yes.
Should I play some music?
Sorry, sir.
I was on my way to Seoul too.
Isn't this great?
Do you know where Seongbuk-dong is?
I know it rather well.
Are you headed there?
Yes, to Assemblyman Oh's place.
What's wrong with you?
You scared me.
Why are you going there?
I'm a huge fan and supporter,
so I wanted to show him my support.
Right here. This is where I'm going.
Hey, fiancée.
What happened? Did you meet him?
Yes, I just met him.
I'll call you once I'm done.
Sam-sik.
You better not screw it up.
I won't.
Congratulations on your wedding tomorrow.
Help!
Are you all right?
-I'm sorry.
-Help!
-Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
-Goodness.
Should I call an ambulance?
DNA TEST RESULT
This is going to scar.
My mom never let
anything like this happen to me.
What's this?
It says it right there.
"DNA Test Result."
Even an idiot can read it.
Exactly.
So what is this?
I'm about to let you listen to
what this is all about.
Will you get rid of the original
DNA test result in front of me?
She's using earphones,
so I cannot confirm the content.
I was torn
between giving this to your father
and handing it over to Bareun Hanguk Party
who's dying to take him down.
I pondered it deeply.
But I decided to give you
a chance to be a good daughter
right before your wedding.
Hey.
What are you trying to pull?
What are you doing? That's mine!
You just said it was my dad's.
Choi Kang-ho had this.
A prosecutor like him
wouldn't keep a fake, would he?
What the hell do you want?
So I had to mention him
to get your attention.
I want 200 million.
Right, I have to pay Mom back.
And two million.
I want 202 million won in cash.
You know what will happen
if you have another copy, right?
I'll probably be found dead
in some mountains.
I'll see you here in an hour.
Hey, fiancée.
I just talked to her.
She was taken aback at your name.
There's definitely something going on.
I'll look more into this and call…
Damn it.
Okay, Sam-sik.
Okay, bye.
What are you doing?
Sam-sik.
Sam-sik?
Mom. I'll do it.
Let me.
Okay.
Mom, I'll do it.
Mom!
What's the number?
All right.
You said you wouldn't do anything.
But you're unwell.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
Ms. Jin!
You're here. I was about to call you.
What did the vet say?
Those are signs of MMA.
Give them these anti-inflammatory shots,
and the prospects are that
they will get well in a couple of days.
-That's a relief.
-Mom.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
But you're afraid of giving shots.
I'll just grit my teeth
and stick it in at once.
I'll go with you.
Excuse me.
Have you seen the man
who was sitting there?
No, I haven't.
Please don't hit me!
RECENTS
FIANCÉE
I didn't hit you.
Oh, you didn't?
I'm…
I'm sorry.
So Choi Kang-ho had this?
Yes.
That idiot wouldn't have sent you here.
Who was it?
Who sent you here?
You must be Woobyeok.
No, sir.
I'm Sam-sik.
Samsik?
Hey, what's Samsik?
Look it up.
No, sir.
My name is Sam-sik.
Bang Sam-sik.
So you will keep your mouth shut?
Okay, take it to the grave.
-Sir.
-Get rid of him.
I just opened my mouth! What do I…
Knife!
So…
So and Cha?
What the hell?
What the…
Darn it!
So and Cha?
Damn it.
Drop the weapons.
Drop the weapons!
Damn it.
Are you okay?
Damn it!
My goodness.
I'm sorry you're hurt because of me.
Why did those damned bastards
have to use knives?
I was scared to death.
I almost wet myself.
Goodness, speaking of which,
let me go take a leak.
Kang-ho will take the fall.
That's why I keep him around.
Are you sure it was Song Woo-byeok?
Yes, sir.
I saw Mr. So.
That wicked old snake.
Where's Ha-young?
What's that?
I won't make excuses.
It was a mistake.
Killing an innocent woman
and her baby was a mistake?
Choi Kang-ho did that.
You put him up to it.
You're a terrifying person.
You kill and get rid of everyone
who gets in your way.
And Kang-ho…
He ended up like that
after being used by you.
Ha-young, you must be quite scared.
Yes, of course, you are.
Since you slipped Kang-ho sleeping pills
and tried to kill him.
-That was--
-Are you going to say
that I put you up to that too?
No.
You took
revenge on him because you felt betrayed
when you found out
he was using you to take me down.
It was your decision
to do it.
But Ha-young,
it's all in the past.
Besides,
the evidence that could be used against me
is now in my hands.
With Kang-ho in that state,
no one can prove it
as long as you keep your mouth shut.
Do you understand?
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
You came.
Thank you for coming.
Goodness, congratulations.
You came. I didn't invite you
thinking it'd be uncomfortable for you.
Right?
If you texted me the wedding invitation,
I would've just wired you
the congratulatory money.
I didn't know how else to give it to you,
so I brought it here myself.
The husband is quite
tall and handsome, isn't he?
So do you like
your future son-in-law this time?
Yes.
Good, you should.
That way they can live happily
without getting into
an unexpected accident, right?
I'll be heading inside now.
The steak here is amazing.
You must know that.
-Hello.
Thank you for coming.
The bride looks so stiff.
Please relax and smile a little.
Come on, smile.
Here comes the groom.
-Congrats!
-Looking good!
Congrats!
Next,
please welcome the beautiful bride.
Here comes the bride!
Excuse me!
When will you serve the steak?
Goodness gracious.
Ha-young, here.
Oh my, Ji-u.
Is this for me?
Thank you so much.
It's not from me. It's from that man over…
What? Where did he go?
The bride is gone.
I'll look for her once again.
Are you ready?
I just need to get dressed.
By the way, where are we going?
On a date.
-A date?
-Yes.
So you need to look your best.
-My best.
-Yes.
Ma'am?
-Yes?
-Your payment went through.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Please leave your message after the beep
and press the asterisk once you're done.
Sam-sik, why aren't you picking up?
Is something going on?
Give me a call, okay? I'll be waiting.
What's this?
Kang-ho.
Mom, you look…
What do you think? Don't I look pretty?
Yes.
Very pretty.
It's cold.
-I'm fine.
-It's not fine.
You have to keep warm.
Like this.
All set. Let's go.
Did you want to go on a date with me?
I realized
I never had a chance to eat out with you.
We've never been to the movies,
a karaoke room,
or on a trip.
So we're going to do everything now.
Look.
I made a list
of everything I want to do.
THINGS TO DO WITH MY SON
What do you think?
Will you do them with me?
Yes, I'll do everything.
Okay.
Excuse me!
Give us two more servings
of your best ribeye please.
And also a bottle of makgeolli please.
What?
Come on, Mom.
I'm an adult.
I'm your guardian.
But you can't drink.
Never.
Okay.
Yes, you're my guardian
and an adult.
-Yes.
-Gosh.
We'll take a large bottle of makgeolli.
Then just one glass
with the large bottle please.
-I want some too.
-No, just have the meat.
Kim Min-jeong reports.
The body discovered by Lee,
who was fishing at night
on Jemyeon Island on the 8th,
was highly decomposed and…
Honey!
Honey, wait!
You damn brat.
Stop it!
-Have you gone insane?
-That bitch is the insane one!
How dare you tarnish my reputation?
Get in here!
Lock her up in a hospital
and keep her there
until the election is over!
Yes, sir.
-Sir.
-Yes?
We checked,
and it was Hwang Soo-hyun.
The police began the investigation
as a possible murder case.
Damn it!
-Hey.
-Yes.
We need to do something.
FIANCÉE
Your call could not be completed
and will be transferred to…
I was a fool to trust him.
Darn it.
Mom?
I want to sleep here tonight.
I have to protect you.
I'd love that.
Come on in, Mr. Guardian.
Mr. Guardian.
Yes?
Thank you for our date today.
It made me very happy.
Your wish is my command.
I'll do everything for you.
Really?
Yes.
In that case,
sing for me.
Sing?
Yes.
But I can't sing.
I can't.
What? You said you'd do anything for me.
It was always my wish to hear my son sing.
Sing for me.
Please sing for me.
-Okay.
-Please.
Okay.
A tiring day passed by
Two are under the moonlight
As one shadow
That distant happiness is
Still there seemingly within my reach
When I
Close my eyes
-My wounded heart…
-My wounded heart
May cast a shadow
Upon your dream
Please remember…
Why are you singing
such a heartbreaking song?
You're not asleep?
Let me check your fever.
What a relief. It went down a little.
I'm sorry.
It must be because
I brought you out in the cold
before I dried your hair properly.
-Mom.
-Yes?
I already know.
About what?
About Dad.
-Dad?
-Yes.
So you can be honest with me.
Did you hear something?
I don't have to hear it to know.
It's obvious to me.
Ye-jin.
Well, the thing is…
Dad
had an affair, right?
What?
This is why a married couple
shouldn't live apart.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing like that.
It is.
He's never called us once
since that brief visit.
Doesn't he miss us at all?
Ye-jin.
That's because…
But you know,
I don't miss him that much either.
What?
Maybe it's because
we've been apart for so long.
He feels like a stranger.
I don't feel attached to him.
So I wanted you to know that
you don't have to put up with him
because of us.
Just get a divorce.
Being divorced is not a big deal nowadays.
There are three divorced families
in my kindergarten.
At first, they threw a fit
and even refused to eat,
but now they run about happier than ever.
It's such a mess.
So,
stop worrying about us
and start living your own life.
If there's one thing
I learned in all my years,
it's that there isn't much to life.
You just have to live happily
with the people you love, right?
You love us.
And we love you too.
So please,
let's just live happily by ourselves.
I'll marry Kang-ho oppa in the future
and take good care of you.
Come here, my baby.
Goodness, come here.
You little thing.
You must've been worried sick.
It must've been so hard for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm…
such a bad mom.
I'm such a bad mom.
You're crying again.
-What?
-You haven't smiled once
since you've come back here.
I want to see you smile.
Because you're not a bad mom,
but a pretty mom.
Hello?
What?
There's smoke coming from the farm?
Yes, okay.
Yes, I'll check now.
Kang-ho.
Kang-ho, wake up.
There's smoke coming from the farm.
Mom.
Oh, no!
-Mom.
-Our pigs!
Guys, wake up!
We need to leave.
-We have to get out.
-No.
We have to get out!
-Mom, no.
-Our pigs.
-Mom, we have to go!
-Let go!
-We have to go!
-No!
-We have to go now!
No!
Mom.
-No!
-It won't open.
Why won't it open?
Mom.
Mom, come here. This way.
Mom, we have to get out of here.
-Mom, get out of here. Now.
-No.
-Mom, we have to leave now!
Come on.
Mom!
Kang-ho, you go first.
-You go…
-No, Mom.
You have to get out first. Mom!
You have to leave first.
I'll follow you out, okay?
Come on.
Hurry.
Mom.
Yong-yong, have you been well?
Yong-yong.
Do you copy, Yong-yong?
Do you remember Daddy's voice?
What are you up to?
Are you still asleep?
It's time to get up.
Wake up and play with me.
My dear son,
it's time to wake up.
THE GOOD BAD MOTHER
Fire!
Are you saying Kang-ho is in there?
Was it you? Were you the girl
he wrote about in his journal?
Sam-sik, you know something, don't you?
I really need to see Ha-young.
Did you have that much fun with her?
Mr. Choi, you're under arrest on suspicion
of murdering Ms. Hwang Soo-hyun.
I'm going to protect Kang-ho.
Kang-ho was only able to endure
those lonely and painful years
because of you.
Do you think she's really here?
She has to be. For Kang-ho's sake.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon