[English subtitles are available]
♫I'd like to invite you to talk about yourself♫
[Hello, I'm At Your Service]
♫Do you dare to come?♫
[Episode 17]
Liu?
Lou.
Sit. Sit.
Uncle, Auntie, I'm not sitting.
Sorry for the misunderstanding just now.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm En's boyfriend.
My name is Lou Yuan.
I'm 30 years old.
Do you know what you did wrong?
In public,
you were
being lovey-dovey.
That's ridiculous.
What do you think you were doing? Filming a movie?
If others see you,
they would think you are ill-educated.
Keep your voice down. You scared her.
Well, Uncle, Auntie,
don't blame En. It was my fault.
Just blame me.
It's okay.
What do you do?
I'm Peony Corporation's president.
His driver.
When he is free, he would provide ride-hailing services.
Provide ride-hailing services to get extra gains?
The son of our neighbor Ms. Wang
also provides ride-hailing services.
He can earn tens of thousands yuan a month.
Making money by working, right?
It's reasonable and legal.
You get as you give.
Yes, especially boys.
Boys should be independent early
and be responsible.
Can you cook?
Yes.
Dad, why did you ask that?
It's okay.
Uncle, Auntie, I can cook.
I usually cook when I'm not busy.
You can cook?
Not many boys can cook nowadays.
Lou
is quite good at living well...
Why... Why are you staring at me?
Did I say anything wrong? Did I?
Well, Uncle, Auntie, here's the thing.
Since childhood,
I've been helping my mom cook.
So I can cook some dishes myself.
Don't worry.
I will cook more frequently for En in the future.
Have your parents met En?
Dad.
What?
I'm sitting here, right?
Well,
this boy
wants to have my daughter.
Can't I ask him some questions?
Can't I?
You can.
They haven't met En yet.
But don't worry.
They can meet her anytime.
No, no, no.
They haven't met her, right?
That's better.
Good. Good.
Liu.
Lou.
It's getting late, right?
Go back.
I'm going to walk him out.
No need.
Doesn't he have legs?
Can't he walk by himself?
En.
En, well,
where's the fridge?
Your dad brought you a lot of food.
Let's... Let's put them in the fridge.
Well, Lou,
s-sorry.
It's okay, Auntie.
Uncle, Auntie,
I'll visit you at home next time.
I'm leaving.
What's wrong with you?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you so much.
The director said
you look more suitable
for the character.
It will be decided in several days.
Get prepared
-these days.
-Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
I will be well prepared.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
What... What...
What... What happened?
Honey.
Guess who called me just now.
En?
The producer. The producer!
She said I passed the second audition.
They will choose between me and another girl.
But the director is more interested in me.
Really?
Gosh.
Look. Look.
My heart is beating so fast. I'm so excited.
-And she said...
-Calm down.
she'll introduce more resources to me in Beiqing.
Gosh, I'm so lucky.
The characters they introduced are all good.
I'm so happy.
I'm so excited. So excited.
Are... Are you going out?
No. No.
Come here.
What's wrong, Mom?
Sit there.
Where's Hai?
Her boyfriend is sick and hospitalized.
She went to accompany him.
Are you sure you two live together?
Yes, right here.
These are hers?
They are not her size.
They are...
Mr. Lou...
No. Lou
left them here as spare clothes.
There is his toothbrush in the bathroom.
Because he needs to brush his teeth after eating. He's a neat person.
Keep making up stories.
Turn around.
Look at me.
Tell me the truth.
Are you living together?
What... What are you talking about?
No. No.
I'm serious.
No matter what,
you must take safety precautions.
Okay. Okay.
Mom, don't tell my dad.
He'll have hypertension if he knows.
This is a serious matter. Why would I...
Why would I tell him?
But judging from the fabric,
the business suits are quite expensive.
How much does a driver have to earn
to afford this kind of suit?
Mom, if I tell you
he is the president,
do you believe it?
President?
A president came to this shabby place to date you?
Who would believe that?
En,
you should be cautious.
Don't be deceived by a liar.
Don't forget
when your cousin got married last year,
she thought she married a big boss.
Now she has lost everything.
Your uncle was so angry
that he was sent to the hospital.
Your dad was furious too.
Your dad said
if he meets such a liar,
he will definitely beat him up.
You must be cautious.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Are you cold?
No.
Your parents are asleep?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Your hands are freezing.
No need to apologize.
Right,
why did you tell your parents
that I'm a driver?
My...
My parents don't like presidents.
If you tell them you are the president,
they won't even let you in.
I'm not joking.
I don't want your parents
to think I'm an dishonest person.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I... I will explain to them later.
Then it's a deal.
Don't bully me.
All right.
Go back.
If your parents find out,
they will really think
I'm an unreliable boy.
And I won't be able to clear my name no matter what I do.
You should go back and rest early too.
Take this back first.
Okay.
Good night.
♫Wait, my heart, don't beat so fast♫
♫Wait, I'm afraid to fall alone♫
♫Slow down, let me feel♫
Sorry.
♫Your eyes and sight♫
♫Stay by my side, be worried♫
All right.
Go back and keep them company.
♫Wait, a deeper understanding♫
Bye.
♫Wait, memories overlapped♫
♫Keep moving forward until I see♫
♫You and I gradually become intimate♫
♫Unchanging vows through the elapse of time♫
♫Missing you gradually♫
♫Little by little♫
What are you looking at?
You look dedicated.
How much can a president's driver make?
Seriously?
Do you believe what they say on the Internet?
Our daughter is in a relationship.
Are you more nervous than her?
I'm not nervous.
But I can't
let my daughter be deceived.
How old is she?
You should learn to let go when you need to.
If everyone treats their future son-in-law like a criminal
like you,
who can marry off their daughter?
Look at me. Look at me.
Turn around. Turn around.
Come on. Take a look.
What's there to look at? I see you every day.
Focus on me.
Am I really scary?
Horrible?
Yes.
I think I usually
talk very politely and nicely.
Very politely.
Like this.
What are you doing?
Do you know Bai Wuchang?
You'll look just like him if you wear a white coat.
If our daughter can't find a husband,
it will be your fault.
You scared that boy.
Even if she can't find a husband,
so what?
I'll support her.
What's the big deal?
You scared me.
I can't just
let my daughter
marry a random guy, right?
I need to know his background.
What do you know?
I have to find it out.
You scared me! What are you doing?
Listen.
Our daughter has asked for a leave tomorrow.
She will take us out to have fun.
You should behave well. Don't cause trouble.
Alright.
I hit my head.
It's all your fault.
What are you doing?
Get up.
No.
Why are you shy?
It's not like I haven't seen it before.
No.
Listen.
After this period of time,
I've figured out something.
Get up.
In this world,
there are so many problems.
Living is too tiring.
But only when I'm with you,
am I truly relaxed.
At first, I didn't realize
that this is love.
I was quite confused for a while.
But now I've figured it out.
Staying where I am is not my style.
I want to try to be with you.
Try?
You're talking like...
You're talking like a scumbag.
Is it too easy for you to have me?
I should have made it more difficult.
Pursuing you properly is romantic.
If you deliberately make it difficult for me, it'll be annoying.
Come here.
What's that sound?
Your heart is beating so fast.
My...
My... It's always like this.
I like you, Wang Zijian.
I...
I like you very, very, very much.
Cao Ya,
I like you too.
Everyone knows they're in a relationship now.
They're still pretending.
Now everyone in Peony
is pretending that they don't know.
But
actually, everyone knows they are together.
It's just that they don't know
we all know they are together.
Have you been
practicing tongue twister recently?
I just think they are very funny.
They look great together.
A perfect match.
Besides,
I think since my grandmaster met my master,
he has been very lucky.
My master must be very auspicious.
But my master's hard work
also played a significant role.
My grandmaster mentioned once
that he wanted to run a dining saloon.
Later, I saw my master
searching information
on buffet dining saloons several times.
Dining saloon?
You mean Lou Yuan wants to run a dining saloon?
I... I shouldn't have said that, right?
Are you his sister?
You are my sister.
Why can't you tell me?
Brother, my lunch break will be over.
I'm leaving.
I'll talk to you next time.
Bye.
Dining saloon?
Peony wants to run a dining saloon.
Come in.
What is this?
[Internship Certificate]
Internship certificate?
Your internship is going to end, right?
After Mr. Wang transferred me to the Marketing Department,
I was transferred to Shanghai to do things.
[Internship Certificate]
Look at me.
I've lost weight.
Get some nutrition after you go back to your campus.
After graduation,
welcome to our company.
Miss Cao, do I still have a chance?
The gate of our company
is always open for excellent talents.
I'm talking about you.
My gate is locked.
I'm not as good as Mr. Wang,
but
I can also be very nice to you.
And I'm very young.
I think he's better.
You're late.
Fine.
I wish you happy.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
Come on.
I'm really leaving.
Don't miss me.
Mr. Su.
How did it go with Eighty-two Studio?
You're right.
They took the initiative to come to me.
We've reached an agreement.
I've sent the contract.
It should be signed soon.
Okay, good.
What should we do next?
I have my own plan.
Is it Lou?
Lou
looks handsome, right?
Your mom and I like him.
But he's a driver.
Although he's a president's driver,
it's not promising, right?
Dad, Mom,
I have something to tell you.
Actually, Lou Yuan is not a driver.
He is...
Mr. Lou, this way please.
Please.
Lou?
Isn't he Lou?
How about this? Mr. Li,
please wait for me upstairs.
I'm going there to say hello.
Mr. Li and I will wait for you upstairs.
Okay.
He's a driver?
He's not a driver.
Sorry.
Hello, Uncle, Auntie.
Why are you eating here?
I was talking about you with my parents,
and you showed up.
He's my client.
He's a real boss.
Don't be angry.
Last time, I didn't have time
to explain to you.
Well,
I happen to have time tomorrow.
I'll drive and show you around
to have fun.
Okay.
Go back to your work.
Take good care of your parents.
I'm going.
Uncle, Auntie, I'm going.
Okay.
President?
If you are with him,
aren't you worried?
What's wrong with you?
A president's driver is not okay.
A president is not okay either.
Why are you so picky?
I... I think he's good.
Can't you be more positive?
What... What do you know?
You're shortsighted.
He's a president.
His family is rich.
So what?
If something bad happens,
it doesn't matter even if he fails.
What about my daughter?
My daughter is with him.
It will influence the rest of her life if he fails.
Dad, can you say something auspicious?
Right.
Can't you just hope for good things for her?
In times of peace, prepare for war.
-Thrive in calamity and perish in soft living.
-You...
He is pessimistic. Ignore him.
He's always been like this.
[Chunlai Teahouse]
This way, Uncle, Auntie.
This is your first time here.
Let me introduce.
This place
is called Luodai Ancient Town.
It dates back
to the Three Kingdoms period.
It's time-honored.
This ancient town is situated in Longquanyi District, Chengdu.
This street
is also a time-honored street.
It's well preserved.
This street
has
7 alleys.
And it features an obvious
architectural style of Ming and Qing dynasties.
Why is it called Luodai Ancient Town?
It is said that
back then, Liu Shan
left his belt here.
So it was named
Luodai Ancient Town.
I see.
Look how great Mr. Lou is, right?
Uncle, Auntie,
If we keep walking,
we can see Luodai Clubs.
There are many clubs including Guangdong Club
and Jiangxi Club.
How about this?
Uncle, Auntie, let me
take a photo for you here.
-Okay.
-Let's take a picture together to mark the occasion.
Okay.
Is my tie ready?
This is great.
Take a photo here.
What? What are you doing?
Just keep walking.
Otherwise, when can we finish the trip?
Mr. Lou, don't you have a meeting this afternoon?
Can you make it?
Why don't you go first?
Is there enough time?
Well...
Yes. I do have a meeting this afternoon.
How about this?
Uncle, Auntie, you keep walking around.
I'll pick you up when you're done.
No, no, no.
No need to bother you.
We can take a walk by ourselves.
Okay.
Work is more important.
-Well...
-Don't worry about us.
Okay.
I wanted to say
your commentary was very good.
You were very serious.
I want to hear more.
Don't take it to heart.
My dad has always been like that.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
What are you doing?
[Second People's Hospital of Huaze Community, Nandu]
Can't you be nice to him?
I think Lou is a good kid.
Why don't you like him?
I've raised En for more than 20 years.
I haven't seen him several times,
and he has her just like that.
Why?
How about this?
Show your parents around.
I'll go back first.
Okay.
-Go.
-Love you.
Bye.
Daughter,
did Lou
tell you anything?
En,
I'm going over there.
Go.
Just go.
Walk around.
Did he say anything?
What can he say?
You treated him like that.
My attitude was so obvious.
Didn't he complain to you?
Didn't he get angry?
Mr. Lou is not that kind of person.
He's very generous.
If he stands in your shoes,
I'm sure he can understand you.
Tell me the truth.
How much do you like him?
Do you really like him?
Do you really want to marry him
and spend the rest of your life with him?
Do you?
I really like him.
But I haven't thought about those things.
Don't. Don't.
You have to think about the future.
You are not young anymore.
I...
I just want to make money for you.
And I'm an adult now.
Dad, don't worry about me.
Yes, actually,
I didn't mean to force you.
But I'm really worried.
-You two…
-Dad.
I know what you said.
Yes. We are different.
-Yes.
-It's an objective fact.
But...
I like him.
And I like him more than I know.
He is a president.
He is cool.
But
he is willing
to be with an ordinary customer service staff member like me.
He would take me to eat
my favorite hairy crabs.
He would make me happy when I'm unhappy.
He would also act cute to me
and ask me not to bully him.
Anyway,
you should trust me.
Don't you trust your daughter?
Peony's dining saloon
is a comprehensive food experience store
combining product traceability with on-site cooking.
Our current plan
is to lay a foundation
in Beijing, Shanghai, Guangzhou, and Shenzhen first.
And then we'll make adjustments
according to the local flavors.
-First-tier cities are not enough.
-So the cities...
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
You should also pay attention to middle-sized and small cities.
What is our concept?
The taste of home.
So
we must
expand the retail channels.
We must let more people
eat our sauces.
If so,
it's going to be a big plan.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
What's wrong with being big? Being big is right.
If you want to do it, do it big.
As the saying goes,
problems can never be overcome without taking risks.
I've made up my mind.
We have to spend the money when we need to.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
Okay. Okay.
-Chairman, bravo.
-Good.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
What are you two looking at?
Well...
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
My eyes don't feel well.
Enough.
You just want to know
why I have changed, right?
Yesterday, I went to a supermarket with my neighbor Ms. Wang.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
In front of me,
she bought Triangle's sauce pack.
And she said
her grandson asked for it.
That was embarrassing.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
I thought I have to do something.
If I don't teach Triangle a lesson,
they won't know who is the sauce ancestor.
Of course it's you.
Everyone knows that.
This is so annoying.
Triangle Group is nobody.
I've decided.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
We will offer enough budget this time.
Do it big.
Son, you...
I'll support you no matter what you do.
Okay.
Since you said so,
this time, our project's budget
is at least 5 million yuan.
Five million yuan?
-Five million yuan.
-Okay.
Wait.
It's good.
It's not easy to make money.
Money should be spent in the right way.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
We can't waste money, right?
So, I've thought about it.
We need to cooperate with Eighty-two Studio.
Because the company knows us better.
Right?
They will help us
spend the money in the right way.
So call En.
Tell her to come here.
I'll talk to her.
Okay, leave it to me.
Okay.
It's settled then.
[Localized layout in first-tier cities]
Okay, Chairman.
No problem.
Okay.
[Executive Office]
Hello, En.
What?
Did your parents enjoy themselves?
They had fun.
They are tired.
They are resting in the room.
That's good.
Right,
did your parents tell you anything about me?
Are they very dissatisfied with me?
No. You are so perfect.
They just didn't expect me
to find a boyfriend as brilliant as you.
Right, I have something serious.
It's good news.
My mom wants to promote the dining saloon.
She wants to collaborate with Eighty-two Studio.
Really?
If you're free tomorrow,
come to the company.
Okay, no problem.
Tonight,
should I come
and take your parents out
to have dinner together?
I know what you mean.
But I think
we should give them some time to accept it.
Let's not rush it, okay?
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
Love you.
Okay, bye.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
-Don't drink if you can't drink.
-It's fine.
What kind of person is that?
Why did you come here to drink?
Why?
Tell me why.
Why are you nervous?
I can't run away.
Who's nervous?
I...
I'm just afraid
you would run away
with some other man.
I just want to have a drink here.
What's wrong with you?
You have no confidence in yourself?
Who said that?
I... I really don't care about others.
But to you...
What?
Tell me.
I'm addicted...
to you.
Let's go. It's more fun at home.
Let's go.
♫You're like a beam of light♫
♫A warm light♫
I know what you mean.
But I think
♫Imprinted the distance we've been looking at♫
we should give them some time to accept it.
♫For many years♫
Let's not rush it, okay?
♫If a message♫
♫Can also imprint the time♫
♫Please don't forget♫
♫There's also me standing here♫
♫I just want to be your sun♫
♫I'll leave a beam of light in your heart♫
♫One day♫
♫You will follow the light and come to me♫
♫Even if I'm not by your side♫
♫I'll do my best for you♫
[Peony]
You first.
En.
You are
at your best age.
Look.
You are not married and have no children.
There is nothing to worry about,
so you can focus on your career.
Right?
A girl
must have a successful career.
In this way,
she can have anything she wants.
Right?
Yes.
You're right.
But...
Auntie, this project is really big.
You skipped bidding and competitive presentation.
Of course,
I'm very grateful for your trust in Eighty-two Studio.
But do you want to think about it again?
I was right about you.
I've thought about it.
The price you offer is reasonable.
And you're capable.
This time,
we have a lot of ideas about this dining saloon.
I guess only you
can meet our requirements.
So
after thinking about it,
I think you are the most suitable.
Thank you, Auntie Lou.
As for the budget this time,
2 million yuan. Do you accept it?
Two million yuan?
Accept it. You must accept it.
En, listen.
You are the light of Eighty-two Studio.
[Eighty-two Studio]
Again?
This time, our direct Party A
is Auntie Lou.
So we must do it well.
We can't let Auntie Lou down.
[Eighty-two Studio]
Of course.
Eighty-two Studio is lucky.
We have two projects at the same time.
Well, how is the contract with Dongshi going?
[Eighty-two Studio]
Zhenzhen is responsible for it. I'm going to ask her.
[Forbidden Forbidden]
Zhenzhen, where is the contract with Dongshi?
Here.
Take a good look at it.
[Eighty-two Studio]
What do you think?
Is it suitable?
[Eighty-two Studio]
Yes.
The offer is reasonable, right?
Very.
Two projects at the same time?
Let's do it simultaneously.
Fatty, what do you think?
Undertaking two projects at the same time?
Don't we need to rest?
We should work harder.
You have to face the difficulties.
But why are there supplementary terms
based on the responsibility for the breach of contract?
Dongshi is a big company.
[Eighty-two Studio]
The process is quite complicated.
I asked Mr. Tong before.
He said instead of reviewing it again,
[Eighty-two Studio]
it's better to make a new contract.
So they have stamped the seal on the supplementary agreement.
The liquidated damages are much less.
Yes.
But the process is a bit strange.
Is there any problem with the contract?
No.
That's good then.
Don't waste time. Fatty, get to work.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm gonna stamp the seal then.
Go ahead.
[Eighty-two Studio Advertising Co., Ltd.]
Two projects.
[Supplementary Agreement]
Okay, Zhenzhen.
Put one
in the archive
and deliver the other to Dongshi.
Okay.
Why does Qi need this?
I might need your help this time.
It's not a big deal.
I just want you to deliver
Eighty-two Studio and Dongshi's two supplementary agreements
to me.
If they ask you,
you can just deliver a copy to me.
I don't have to do this.
But I promised him.
He will be angry if I don't.
But my master and the others are good too.
I can't make him angry.
No, no, no.
[Wonderful Space] [Architecture Twins]
Maybe I should deliver it.
Are you the one who wants to deliver a parcel?
Maybe I shouldn't.
But I promised him
I'll be on his side.
Are you sure you want to deliver a parcel?
Yes, my brother is the most important.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
[Wonderful Space] [Architecture Twins]
Forget it.
Mr. Su, I just signed a contract with Eighty-two Studio.
Isn't it too hasty
to ask them about the progress of the design draft now?
You are Party A.
Is it illegal
to ask them and rush them?
Okay, I see.
Mr. Su, may I ask
you and Eighty-two Studio...
Why don't I understand
Dongshi's accounts last month?
Shouldn't you explain
to the board about some items?
I see.
I'll contact you again if there's any news.
[Forbidden Forbidden]
Hello, Mr. Tong.
How's the design draft going?
We're in the end stage.
If everything goes well,
we can submit the draft this week.
No, it's too slow.
It's only Tuesday today.
There are five days left this week.
What's the problem?
Didn't we just sign the contract?
And we've agreed on the time limit of 7 days, right?
I chose to cooperate with Eighty-two Studio
because you are efficient.
If you do everything as we agreed in the contract,
is it necessary to continue our cooperation?
No, that's not what I meant.
Don't be angry.
I mean...
It seems I can't cooperate with a small company.
Submit the draft quickly.
I'm hanging up.
Fatty.
[Forbidden Forbidden]
Come and take a look at this.
Is this one okay?
The color.
Adjust it again.
Adjust it.
[Mr. Lou]
[Honesty makes you the winner]
Here.
The delivery time is around this time.
[Details determine the result]
Okay.
Zhenzhen.
-Let me confirm
-Mr. Guo.
the paper size with you again.
2,200x1,200mm.
[Nandu Guankai Advertising Production Co., Ltd.
Production Process Sheet]
Right?
Yes. Start producing. It's good.
The material you require is a little special this time.
We need to buy it in advance.
We've received the payment.
Please thank Ke for me.
Ke paid for it?
Yes.
Ke is nice.
He knows it is not easy for our small factory.
He always paid us in advance.
To express our gratitude,
we only charged the cost price.
It's not easy for us to make money.
We should understand each other.
Thank you.
Okay, do your things.
-I'm going there.
-Okay.
That's why you always have crises.
Honest men shouldn't do business.
I'm working.
Can you be quiet?
It's late.
Don't sit in front of the computer.
Come, exercise with me.
You'll get sick if you sit for a long time.
I have to finish the draft and submit it to Party A as soon as possible.
I have to stay up late.
Turn off the sound.
Well, I'm exercising for work too.
It's fine if you don't exercise with me.
But why did you blame me?
I don't want to argue with you.
I just said what I was thinking.
I'm gonna turn it off.
I'm not exercising.
Alright, let's not argue.
Let's go out
for a walk.
Okay?
[Believe in the strength of the team. We're always making progress.]
Mr. Ke,
your project is bigger.
I always have faith in you.
Mr. Guo, I'm flattered.
Thanks to En.
Yes.
Look.
This time, new materials
[Crispy Ice Cream]
have been used for these billboards.
Have you noticed this?
Although they are brighter than before,
they won't glare.
And I have used the latest materials.
They definitely meet environmental protection standards.
You can rest assured.
Mr. Guo.
Is this made based on the bleed size?
Yes.
I made it after checking with workers three times
according to the size you gave me.
Mr. Guo,
don't install it.
We gave you the wrong size.
♫Wait, my heart, don't beat so fast♫