[English subtitles are available]
♫I'd like to invite you to talk about yourself♫
[Hello, I'm At Your Service]
♫Do you dare to come?♫
[Episode 16]
[Peony]
The previous client we were dealing with
was too demanding.
Indeed.
We need to come up with a solution quickly.
Morning, everyone.
Good morning, Mr. Lou.
-Hello, Mr. Lou.
-Okay.
[Meeting Room]
[Marketing Office]
Hey, Baby,
you seem a bit different today.
You seem a bit different today too.
What do you mean by different?
I feel like
you're shining all over,
like every cell in your body is singing a joyful song.
Is it that obvious?
It's like you've unblocked the Ren and Du meridians.
You are you,
but not quite.
I am me,
Are you and En...
Don't be so nosy.
Let's keep the brotherly love in our hearts.
You should share this kind of thing with me.
You want me to share it?
You want to hear?
If you want to hear, you have to first share with me
what's going on between you and Cao Ya.
Why do I feel like you've been avoiding her lately?
What could possibly be going on between me and her?
I've thought it through.
I'll just be friends with her.
We'll be bros
and homies.
Just friends?
Just bros?
Do you believe it?
Well, I don't believe it.
You don't believe me?
As a love guru,
I won't be troubled by love.
I'll soon make a comeback, you know?
I'll showcase the charm of a man,
displaying masculine charisma.
Whether you display it or not, it's up to you.
I already did.
I'm leaving.
You already did?
[Marketing Office]
Bye.
Hello, Mr. Lou.
[Peony]
♫Kiss me now♫
♫The atmosphere is just right♫
Hello, Mr Lou.
♫The temperature is also helping♫
Mr. Lou.
Okay, understood.
♫Oh, I'm getting closer to you unconsciously♫
♫Honey, please give me a signal of love♫
♫My heart is pounding♫
♫How can I run away?♫
♫I just want to see your smile every second♫
♫The sweetness is in every corner♫
♫The simple me and the unpredictable you♫
♫Kiss me now♫
♫It's the declaration of love♫
[Peony]
Can this piece of junk
really get over 200 million views?
Mr. Su, please take a look for yourself.
This is...
Do I still need to look at it?
What's our current market share?
What are their next steps?
Mr. Su, I've written it all down here.
Take a look.
[Peony Sauce New Product Corporate Promo Video Estimated Platform Views]
If it keeps going like this,
we'll be really in danger.
This job is impossible to do.
With this little pay, who's going to do it?
En.
We want to use a basic salary to select people
who truly love this industry.
Miss,
can you please give me back the resume?
It's expensive to print it.
May I ask
what is the basic salary here?
What's the commission?
Your place is quite cool.
Do you need any guard?
Trust me. If you give me this job,
I'll do it well.
I have a question.
Trust me.
Miss.
Your place is cool.
[Lan Zhenzhen]
Hello.
Is this where the interview is being held?
Yes, we are recruiting.
But we offer only a basic salary and social benefits.
No commission.
The environment is as simple
and basic as you see.
The only advantage here
[Lan Zhenzhen]
is that there is no workplace social pressure
because the people here
are all a bit quirky.
That's okay.
[Lan Zhenzhen]
My main goal is to gain work experience,
and I really love this industry.
So when can I start working?
[Lan Zhenzhen]
Now.
[Ba'er Creative]
Are you okay?
Well.
Are you sure there's really no problem?
It's okay. It's just a little shaky.
Fasten your seatbelt.
Okay.
Ke.
Your van keeps
having issues.
When are you going to get it fixed?
An old horse in the stable still aspires to travel a thousand miles.
I'm just carrying forward the fine revolutionary tradition
of being thrifty and frugal.
Otherwise, where am I going to save money
for your concert ticket?
I've been deceived by your sweet talk again.
This...
Zhenzhen.
This roller coaster
is still very enjoyable.
En is used to it already.
Yeah.
After a while, it feels like riding a cradle.
If it doesn't shake, I can't sleep.
You talk too much.
[Ba'er Creative]
[Peony]
The video you all just watched
is a quirky video advertisement
that we, Ba'er Creative,
created for Peony.
This advertisement has currently
210 million views.
Many young people really like this advertisement
and have spontaneously shared
and created their own versions on social media.
As a result, the sales of the Peony sauces
are continuously rising.
Zhenzhen, are you okay?
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Excuse me.
We've prepared
two design proposals
for your company's viral cake beverage.
They are on your tables.
You can take a look.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
I need to take this call.
Hello, Mr Lou.
What did you call me?
Zhuang, what's wrong?
Didn't you say we would have dinner together?
I'm really sorry.
I need to go back to Ba'er
to sort some things out.
It will definitely be late.
It's okay.
So, Ba'er Creative
cozied up to Peony like this.
No. Really...
Be good.
Let me give you a kiss.
Master.
By the way,
Ke and the others are having dinner with clients.
Do you want to join them?
I think I'll pass. I don't feel like going.
Then let's go back to Ba'er together.
Master, I'm off work.
I'm leaving.
You can go back on your own.
Bye.
[Fire Hydrant]
[We're a family]
Do you guys think
Zhenzhen doesn't like this job?
She looks like
she comes from a well-off family.
I think she's just working
to pass the time.
I think
maybe she hasn't opened up to us yet.
We haven't spent much time together.
Give her some time.
I think this apprentice is quite cute.
She is quite cute.
Comrades, good news.
Did you win the lottery?
I'll never have the luck of something
like money falling from the sky.
I've been navigating the world for so many years
relying on my true skills.
That's right.
You do rely on your skills to deceive people.
Look.
Trouble Ma understands me.
Oratory skills.
You don't trust me, do you?
Then I won't tell you about the collaboration
with Dongshi.
Wait.
Is it the famous Dongshi Entertainment?
Is there a second one?
You're really something.
You managed to connect with such a big company.
I've been working for so many years.
It's not been in vain.
Ke, eat this bowl of noodles.
Here, eat it.
Isn't this inappropriate?
Just eat it.
Well, then I won't hold back.
Sit down and eat.
I have more if it's not enough.
You've worked hard.
You are sensible.
Ke, tell us more.
Give us the details.
Yes.
Wang Zijian!
Open the door, Wang Zijian.
I need to talk to you.
Wang Zijian.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed is powered off.
Lou Yuan.
Can you help me ask where Wang Zijian is?
Cheers.
Come on.
Bro.
What's wrong today?
Is something wrong with work?
Forget it. I know him.
Most likely, he's so infatuated with some girl
that he's lost his mind.
Even when you're drinking, you can't stop talking.
Come on. Cheers.
Come on. Cheers. Cheers.
You guys are drinking, huh?
I'm late.
Who are you?
I'm the girlfriend of the person whose arm you're holding.
Bro.
You have such a beautiful girlfriend.
Why didn't you bring her out for us to meet?
That's not what a good friend would do.
Come on.
-Cheers.
Sorry for being late.
Come on.
Thank you.
I must punish myself with a drink.
Let's drink.
A toast to everyone.
I'll take this.
I'll take this drink.
Alright, you drink.
Why are you here?
You still care about me.
Last time, I went too far with my jokes.
Don't be mad, okay?
I mean,
how did you come to this place?
I drove here.
It's okay. I'll call a designated driver later.
I didn't ask how you came here.
I meant, how did you know I was here?
Here, here, this place.
How did you know to come here to find me?
Let's talk.
For business,
we can talk at the office,
but there's nothing to discuss for personal matters.
You guys go ahead and have fun.
I'm leaving.
I'll see you next time.
Okay.
See you. See you.
See you next time.
[Bar]
Be careful.
Could you please not make a scene?
Don't touch me.
I want to go home.
Okay, let's go home.
Then, can I come to your place and comfort you?
Cao Ya.
[Bar]
I can have
any kind of woman I want.
Do I need you to comfort me?
We are adults.
Is it meaningful for you to pretend
to be clueless here?
Do you find it meaningful?
Wang Zijian.
I came all the way here to find you and coax you.
When have I ever done this for someone else?
You should stop.
I thought
we could maintain
this physical relationship before,
but this time I lost.
I lost completely.
I can't stand seeing you
with other men anymore.
It makes me unhappy,
upset,
miserable, and uncomfortable.
So,
let's end this kind of relationship.
It's over.
-It's over.
-Alright.
I promise you,
from now on, I'll only keep you by my side. Is that okay?
You...
You clearly know
that this isn't what I want, right?
If you can't give me your whole heart,
please don't hurt mine anymore,
okay?
[Four Seasons Flower Street]
I just don't want to lose you.
Now the information has all been given to you.
[Ba'er Creative]
Quyue Technology
is actually
a subsidiary
of the publicly
listed company, Ireader.
It specializes in the production of original online
[Quyue Technology]
literary content
and the development of intellectual property rights.
Its original works have won numerous awards
and have great potential for development.
So impressive?
[Ba'er Creative]
Why haven't I heard of it before?
Their audio work
[Original Online Literature]
Supreme Martial Deity
has been played on the platform
[Quyue Technology]
nearly 196 million times.
The revenue from their self-produced short films exceeded 30 million,
[Quyue Technology]
breaking records
on various platforms that year.
Of course,
this is just the tip of the iceberg.
30 million.
The tip of the iceberg.
[Ba'er Creative]
[Quyue Technology]
That's impressive.
Even if they're impressive,
what does it have to do with us
if they don't do advertising?
I also have a question.
They wouldn't take on all kinds
of projects like us, would they?
You are ignorant.
Big companies like them
have all kinds of projects.
You don't even know that?
[Quyue Technology]
Right.
They have
a very complete industrial chain.
They own
quyuewang.cn,
shenqiwang.cn, and pinyuew.com.
These are their three major literary websites.
They also have iciyuan.com,
[Quyue Technology]
Quyue Audiobooks, Quyue Films, and Quyue Animation.
These are their four major business brands.
[Quyue Technology]
I'd like to praise En.
Well said.
[Quyue Technology]
Successful advertisements
are meant to be remembered by the times.
Yes.
We need to closely follow the pulse of the times
and seek more diversified collaborations.
[Original Online Literature]
[Ba'er Creative]
[Exquisitely Crafted]
So,
I've decided to go meet with the boss
of that company.
Sure.
I happened to get their boss's WeChat account,
I'll share it with you later.
Okay, dismissed.
Dismissed.
I just organized this information this morning.
When did she memorize it?
Probably just before the meeting.
So quickly?
She only glanced at it.
Your master
has a very strong ability to quickly memorize things.
She's good at catching the point and summarizing.
Let me tell you.
Your master is quite outstanding
as a customer service representative.
You should learn from her more.
She's not just a sweet talker.
She's really capable.
[GAI GE]
Master,
how much does the company pay you in a month
to make you work so hard?
I'm doing this for passion and ideals.
Besides,
no one stays in the company
for money, right?
You're just talking big.
It's boring.
You'll understand in the future.
I believe
Ba'er will get better and better.
By the way,
could you help me organize this customer information?
Master, it's already eight o'clock.
I'm sorry. Go back now.
I didn't check the time.
I can handle it myself.
Be safe on your way home.
Send me a WeChat message when you get home.
Well, Master.
Can you handle all these materials
by yourself?
I do it often. It won't take long.
Don't worry. Be safe.
Alright.
[Ba'er Creative]
Mr. Lou.
You scared me.
Why are you here?
My girlfriend is so busy she doesn't even have time for meals,
let alone thinking about me,
so I have to come personally.
Here.
Have you forgotten about me?
Look at you.
You don't have the demeanor of a domineering CEO at all.
You should be more reserved.
Reserved?
Being reserved
won't earn me the reward of a public boyfriend status.
The one who's eager for an acknowledgment is Mr. Lou?
I thought it would be Master.
Do you really want to make it public?
Of course.
I just want to be able to
pick you up from work when you're busy,
and, of course,
I hope to gain the approval of your friends
and family as well.
Here.
How about having dinner
with Ba'er colleagues tomorrow night?
Really?
Well, now that we're not in a working relationship anymore,
going public doesn't matter.
Besides, you are so nice.
I definitely shouldn't mistreat you, right?
It sounds pretty good.
Here.
Qi, you're back.
Dad.
You're late.
Sorry.
I had a meeting that ran late.
Don't make excuses.
If you're capable enough,
[Finance]
no matter what unexpected situation arises,
you should be able to handle it well.
Qi, I'm starving.
Come and eat.
Let's eat.
Qi, all these dishes
were prepared by Uncle for you.
They are all your favourites.
Really?
Then you should eat more.
Thank you.
Uncle.
Recently, when I was watching videos on my phone,
I keep seeing Qi's company's sauce advertisements.
Really?
All my friends have been interested in it.
Triangle is lucky
to have Qi.
Good marketing
is indeed a part of a company's success,
especially if it can adapt
to market changes.
Speaking of that,
Lou Yuan is doing very well.
Since he returned to Peony,
not only has he tapped into the youth consumer market,
but he has also upgraded the products.
He has truly excelled in both aspects.
What's wrong?
Are you not convinced?
If you are not,
then strive to surpass him.
Don't just focus on superficial advertising
and promotion.
Good products are what really matter.
Uncle.
Uncle...
Uncle was just gaving an example.
How can Lou Yuan compare to you?
Don't take it to heart.
It's fine.
I've been used to it
since I was a child.
Forget it.
Qi.
I actually have something to tell you.
What is it?
Just tell me.
I found a job at Ba'er Creative.
You went to Dong Dong En's company?
It's just that you mentioned it,
and I thought it sounded fun, so I went.
Plus,
those people are all very open-hearted.
They're always having a happy time.
You know what?
On my first day of work,
they dared to take me to the client's office
and tell me everything.
Besides,
they're so poor that they only have one power strip left,
and they might go out of business with a gust of wind.
Their biggest advantage they could possibly rely on
is the relationship between Dong Dong'en and Lou Yuan.
Qi.
I really don't think they're worth your concern.
Zhenzhen.
You like them too?
I don't.
I really don't.
Truly.
Zhenzhen.
I'll agree
to whatever you want to do.
I promise.
But you also have to promise me one thing.
What is it?
That no matter which day in the future,
you'll choose to stand by my side.
Okay, that's for sure.
[Peony]
Mr. Wan.
You're back.
You don't look well.
You didn't sleep well last night?
I'm fine.
Mr. Wan, are you watching the advertisement of Peony?
It's quite interesting.
The operation of Peony is quite interesting.
Is this what they call
going viral?
These kinds of trends usually have a limited lifespan.
They're forgotten once the hype dies down.
The future development of Triangle
should still rely on solid new projects,
those that revolve around the consumer.
Very good.
You have your own judgment.
I'm relieved.
Although Peony Company is currently on a strong momentum,
with you
in Triangle,
I feel we're not inferior than they are.
We also have young talents.
Mr. Wan, you're flattering me.
This is just what I should be doing.
Young man, don't belittle yourself.
When I was as young as you,
I wasn't as capable as you are.
Young people have enthusiasm and drive,
qualities that older people like us
wish we still had.
Seeing you now
reminds me of my younger self.
I'm about to retire.
Come on.
Mr. Wan.
Sit.
Have a seat.
The future of the company
will rely on young people like you.
Do you understand what I mean?
Mr. Wan, don’t worry.
I won’t let you down.
Good luck.
I'm going to work.
Just thinking that I won't see you
when I go to work later
makes me not want to go.
Well, aren't we going to have dinner together tonight?
I'm leaving.
Give me a kiss.
I have to go to work.
You...
That's more like it.
It's great to have a boyfriend.
They are actually showing affection at the company entrance.
Why doesn't Lou Yuan publicly acknowledge his relationship with En?
En, that silly girl.
En.
Sit down.
What's wrong?
Tell us if you're wronged.
We can help you vent your frustrations.
Don't suffer alone.
What did I do?
Stop pretending.
We all know
Lou Yuan is with you
and he doesn't want to reveal your relationship.
Don't be fooled by his sweet words.
All scumbags are the same.
Can he be irresponsible if he doesn't make it public?
When he leaves without a care,
and you're left alone,
crying and suffering,
we'll feel sorry for you.
You've misunderstood.
It's me who didn't want to go public.
Earlier, we were business partners,
and I was afraid of gossip.
But now that we're no longer collaborating,
I can be open about it.
Tonight at 8 o'clock,
the two of us will treat you to dinner.
But
you're not allowed to make him drink,
not allowed to bring up my past,
and
no mischief, understood?
If we can't say anything,
it's just like having dinner with a client.
He truly is our client.
But let's be clear from the start.
If he's inviting us to dinner
in his capacity as our client,
then he's the boss,
and we certainly won't
create any trouble.
But if he's inviting us to dinner
as your boyfriend,
then he's a piglet
who got a free lunch from all of us.
We must make him eat, drink,
smile, and foot the bill.
There's no escaping it for him.
Do you believe
I'll send this message to him exactly as it is?
Let's see if this piglet will give us orders in the future.
Dong Dong‘en.
You've only just started dating,
and you're already siding with your boyfriend?
It's settled then.
Remember,
no messing around.
En has changed.
Actually,
you don't need to worry too much.
En isn't the type to be
emotional in a relationship.
Just let things flow naturally.
I think
that any romance that En is missing,
Mr. Lou can make up for.
As long as En is fine.
Piglet, mind your own business.
Who is it?
Yuan.
Coming.
Surprise!
Why are you here?
I'm here to hide from Cao Ya.
Why are you dressing
so provocatively and going out at this hour?
Listen.
I have dinner plans with people from Ba'er tonight.
I don't have time for you.
En doesn't give you a proper status,
why are you still so proactive?
You have to earn your status.
By the way,
have you resolved things with Cao Ya?
She was just in the mood for some eye candy,
admiring my beauty,
nothing more.
You are so narcissistic,
claiming to be a beauty.
I'm versatile,
cute, and domineering at the same time,
active like a fitness enthusiast,
and calm like a charming gentleman.
Which of my ex-girlfriends didn't give me a five-star rating?
Tell me.
But even with all your talents,
don't you still seek refuge from me?
Also,
you know Cao Ya's temper.
Be careful.
I suggest you two should have a face-to-face conversation.
I'm leaving.
Are you just going to watch me suffer here alone?
Lou Yuan, I was wrong about you.
What you're doing now
is like a scumbag who forgets his old love
when he finds a new one.
How about I call Cao Ya over for you?
Mr. Lou, have a safe journey.
I can stay here alone.
Good luck.
Are you really leaving?
You put romance before friendship.
[Cao Ya]
[Decline] [Answer]
[Voice call]
[Cao Ya]
Cao Ya.
Wang Zijian, let me tell you.
If you are a man,
come here right now!
Did you drink?
Come here right now!
You...
Hello?
[THE BALVENIE]
Sir, let me ask you a question.
What is love?
I'm asking you
what love is.
I don't know what love is.
But I know
if you throw up here, you have to pay 800 yuan.
-I won’t.
-Cao Ya.
Is she your girlfriend?
My friend.
-Okay. I’ll leave her to you.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Wang Zijian.
Yes.
Why are you avoiding me?
I couldn't even see you.
You're drunk. I'll take you home.
I'm not drunk.
No, I'm not drunk.
Listen.
I don't want to lose you.
You know what?
While you were hiding from me,
I was so upset.
I've thought about it.
I tried not to think about you.
I tried to find someone else.
I tried to let everything go back to the beginning.
But I found that
I couldn't make it.
You know what?
Here.
Here,
there's no room
for anyone else but you.
[Bar]
Wang Zijian.
Let's be together, okay?
Are you serious?
Can I be your girlfriend?
Don't go back on your words when you're sober.
[Bar]
Well...
First,
thank Mr. Lou for your hospitality tonight.
You have prepared such a feast for us.
We're flattered.
It makes me feel like a client.
To Mr. Lou.
Let's not drink for now.
Have a seat.
Don't call me Mr. Lou today.
Just call me Lou Yuan.
It's just a common meal.
Since you said so,
I won't stand on ceremony.
En's parents are in her hometown.
We are
like her family.
So if En
is bullied
or wronged,
we wouldn't like it.
He's our client after all.
Chunhua is so cool.
I'll propose a toast to everyone.
How about this?
Let me propose a toast to you.
Ke and Chunhua are kind of En's elders.
The rest of you from Ba'er
are like her family.
We've been working together before.
This is the first time
we're having dinner in private.
I don't know
how to say pretty things.
But there's one thing.
I hope you can rest assured.
I really love En.
En is like a little sun.
She brings warmth and happiness
to everyone around her.
But there are times when the little sun is tired.
So I want to
be the shoulder that En can lean on.
I want to do my best to take care of her,
protect her, love her,
and be someone she can rely on.
I'll drink this.
Ma Chengshu.
You have to confess to me like this in the future.
I will.
Mr. Lou said it so well.
Since we've come to this point,
for the time being,
we'll rest assured to leave En to you.
From now on,
we are Party A and Party B at work.
We're family in life.
One more thing.
Tell me.
Think about us more if there's work.
Aren't you ashamed?
Why did you say that here?
It doesn't matter.
Mr. Lou, a toast to you.
OK.
I'll drink. You drank too much.
-En..
-It’s OK.
You're protecting him before getting married.
It seems that
it'll be hard for us to make Mr. Lou drink in the future.
He's a big boss.
What's wrong with having one more drink?
Right, Lou...
Mr. Lou?
It's okay.
Let me drink it.
How about this?
Let's drink together.
Cheers.
A toast to Mr. Lou.
This wine is good, Mr. Lou.
Let's eat.
What do you want to eat?
You did a good job.
I thought you would be nervous.
Did you practice a lot?
I didn't.
It's all true feelings and emotions.
Walking with you,
just like this now.
Walking with you...
I can sing for you.
I said you ordered too many dishes.
What a waste.
It won't be.
I can go back and reheat these dishes
for a late-night snack.
I'm going upstairs.
I don't want you to leave.
Give me a hug.
I won't sleep at your house tonight.
Nose bump.
Rest early.
En.
You know them?
My parents.
Your parents?
Uncle, Auntie.
♫Wait, my heart, don't beat so fast♫