Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim
An age of injustice.
Please, save my father!
My father was here first!
Honey... Please someone help.
He came after my father!
An age of inequality.
An age full of dissatisfaction and doubt.
8:23 PM. Kang Won-hyung has passed away.
Father...
Father!
Honey!
Thankfully, the surgery ended well.
The assemblyman is safe.
Thank you, Doctor!
My father got here first though.
My father...
My father got here
way before that person did!
Let go! Let go of me!
My father got here before that person did!
He should've been treated first!
My father... Let go of me!
It became an age in which patients
were discriminated against...
...based on who they were
and how much money they had.
Why the heck did you play
with a person's life, huh?
Hospitals and doctors
shouldn't be doing that!
This is the police, right?
This is the emergency room
at Geosan University Hospital.
But at that moment...
...there was someone who came out to us.
My father!
Let go of me!
Let go.
One.
Two.
Three.
BU YONG-JOO
Are you awake now?
Do you feel a bit better now that you
came and bashed a couple of things?
It has nothing to do with you, mister.
Don't get it wrong.
Just because you vented
your frustrations,
it doesn't mean you've gotten revenge.
Even if you go around swinging
a baseball bat for 100 days,
those people probably
won't even remember your face.
If you really want to get revenge...
...become a much better
human being than them.
Don't get revenge with anger,
but with skill.
Understood?
If you don't change,
nothing else will either.
Doctor!
Doctor.
Don't get revenge with anger,
but with skill.
Understood?
How is someone like me
supposed to do something like that?
Especially someone like me?
If you don't change,
nothing else will either.
KANG DONG-JOO
Dr Kang Dong-Joo?
HOW TO PUT AN ELEPHANT IN A REFRIGERATOR
SEPTEMBER, 2011
Hey, hey, hey.
Have you heard that there's a real monster
among the new medical interns?
Monster?
I heard he doesn't care about seniority
and treats his seniors like garbage.
He gets sassy with them,
and even gets in their faces sometimes!
Dr Lee said that his blood pressure
went up so much because of him
that he almost had to declare himself dead!
Apparently, he's also never missed
a first place in his life...
...and apparently, he's so great
that the chief surgeon wants him so much.
In other words, he's untouchable!
But still, he's only an intern.
I don't want to.
What?
Hey.
Why is it that you never do any favors
for your senior and always give me sass?
I didn't become an intern
to be your coffee boy.
Why did you become an intern then?
To fix people.
Did you hear that?
An intern said he's going to fix people!
Hey, how about you work
on your nasty personality first, Intern?
You think that someone
who doesn't even obey their seniors
will be able to treat patients well?
Don't say that as if those two things
have anything to do with each other.
Getting coffee and treating patients
are two completely different matters.
What did he say?
You know, it doesn't take much
to get a gist of someone's character!
Then don't send me
to get your coffee for you.
I won't run stupid errands for others
unless it's related to hospital work.
Stupid errands? Hey, what did you say?
-Hey! Hey!
-Oh, come now.
Just ignore him, Senior!
He's untouchable, isn't he?
Just leave him alone.
Untouchable, whatever.
There was a huge accident
at a construction site!
Four injured patients
will be here in two minutes.
Make an emergency call to Dr Won first!
Got it!
Bring them in this way.
His BP and heartbeat is regular.
And there's an injury on his right wrist.
He said that the area near his thumb
is numb.
Can you feel that?
-No.
-Feels numb?
-Hey, Intern!
-Yes?
He seems to have broken something.
His circulation is okay, but I think
his median nerve has been damaged.
so get him a hand splint
and perform a wrist series.
Take the X-ray in as a forearm
anterior-posterior view lateral.
And perform a reduction
as soon as possible.
Yes, ma'am.
Dr Yoon!
-Over here!
-Okay!
He barely has a pulse.
I think we'll have to perform
a popliteal artery dissection.
Perform a low extremity angiography
on him, please.
Yes, sir.
Hey, where the heck are all the interns?
Get the heck in here, already!
My mom got here first though.
Dr Kang.
They need you.
My mom got here first.
And she's quite ill too!
Can you come by for a second?
There's a patient
with a respiratory problem.
How much fluid did you give him so far?
About two liters.
Preparing for emergency surgery.
-And the tests?
-Negative.
-And nothing else is definite yet.
-Doctor...
How long was he kept waiting?
The conditions at the scene were bad,
so it took over an hour to get to him.
Hey, Intern. Get him a Foley catheter.
There's a patient in critical condition
that came first.
She has a history of COPD,
and she currently has SIRS.
I'm afraid that
she may have pneumonia sepsis.
How are that patient's vitals now?
She's at 100/70 so she's stable
for now, but...
Then get a Foley catheter
in this man first!
Please check her chest
and perform an ABGA.
Don't you see this patient's
blood pressure dropping?
Isn't it clear who needs help right now?
I told you, she might have pneumonia sepsis!
-Hey, Intern!
-Yes?
Get over here and replace
this annoying jerk!
Get out of my way!
Move, move!
This patient is in a critical state!
Doctor. It's Dr Yoon Seo-Jung from the ER.
They say there's a patient
from the construction site...
...with an abdomen penetrating injury.
Sure. Give me the phone.
How's the patient's condition?
He's a 45-year-old man...
...and has a one meter long metal rod
stuck inside his abdomen.
On one side of the rod is a slab of concrete
that they couldn't remove.
Focus!
Where is the rod, exactly?
The rod is running through his lower...
...back to his upper abdomen
and is angled upward.
And his vitals?
Thankfully, his blood pressure is at 119,
so it's normal and his pulse rate is 130.
No massive bleeding.
He may have internal bleeding,
so perform a FAST on him
and stabilize his vitals.
I'll take care of it.
Yes, sir.
Did you all hear that, right?
We're ending this in 30 minutes.
Get your heads in the game.
-Get him hooked up.
-Yes, ma'am.
Put the Cline in like this
and prepare a Foley to put in him too.
Yes, ma'am.
6Move! Please move!
Here's the monitor!
No!
-Get Dr Nam, quickly!
-Yes, sir!
His BP is 90/60!
Levels are dropping quickly!
Give him an emergency transfusion,
and pump two more RBC in him.
-And tell them to prepare 20 more!
-Yes, sir.
-Get him some oxygen!
-Yes.
Sir, it's the ER again.
I think there's been an accident.
Put them through.
Doctor, the steel rod in the patient
has fallen out accidentally.
His BP is falling fast!
Idiots.
Where's Yoon Seo-Jung?
Yoon Seo-Jung!
What are you doing, Yoon Seo-Jung?
The doctor is on the line!
Seo-Jung! Yoon Seo-Jung!
Can you hear me?
Answer me, you little brat!
What are you doing?
Yes, yes, yes, sir! I'm here!
Go ahead!
10 minutes.
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
So just have him hang on for 10 minutes!
You understood?
Yes, yes. Yes, I understand!
His blood pressure is at 80/50,
and it's still dropping!
Hey, Intern! Get more gauze!
Yes, sir!
-I need a draper.
-Yes, ma'am.
Hey, what are you planning to do?
At this rate,
he can injure his thoracic aorta.
We don't have any time.
So you're going to open him up,
here and now?
If we lose any more time, he'll have
too much internal hemorrhaging.
Then we won't be able to see...
I'll do the best.
Seo-Jung...
-Scalpel.
-Hey, Seo-Jung!
Give me a lot of gauze.
Hey, Dr Yoon. Seo-Jung!
Stop!
Shut your mouth for a bit.
Wait, is she looking for the artery?
Here it is.
You got it?
Yes, I did.
I don't think it's a main artery,
based on its location.
I think it's a splenic artery.
The patient's condition is stabilizing,
Doctor.
Oh, it's the doctor!
Seo-Jung! Dr Moon.
What happened?
Oh, his vitals
are being stabilized again, sir.
What about the bleeding?
There was some bleeding from
his splenic artery but I'm holding it down.
What do you mean you're holding it?
With what?
My index finger.
You crazy girl.
Okay, send him up
to the operating room right now.
Yes, sir!
We're moving him
to the operating room now.
Yes, ma'am.
Doctor!
-Hey, move out of the way!
-Yes, sir!
Excuse us! Please move!
Please move!
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your hard work, sir.
Take it easy.
I'm sorry that there was an accident,
Doctor.
It's fine.
I'll take care of things from here on out.
Good job.
Okay.
Hey, Yoon Seo-Jung.
You were so awesome today.
Awesome!
No, I was just lucky.
Crazy Whale!
I have a new nickname for you now.
Queen of the Index Finger!
How can you manage to eat
in this situation?
What do you mean, sir?
There was a patient
with pneumonia sepsis.
Why didn't you call me?
Oh, I had to send that patient
with the steel rod in him to the OR.
But that patient came in
before the construction workers did!
Her vitals were fine
and she only had a slight fever so...
So a slight fever isn't an emergency?
Does someone have to be bleeding out
on the floor with their artery torn...
...for them to be in critical condition
to you?
No, that's not what I meant.
That patient had ARDS.
She would've been dead if...
...Kang Dong-joo had been even
five minutes late!
I heard that he asked you to check
her chest and perform an ABGA!
And twice, at that!
Why did you ignore him?
I didn't ignore him...
If you didn't ignore him,
were you not aware of her condition
even though a mere intern was?
I'm sorry.
Go and apologize 1,000 times
to the patient instead, you idiot!
How dare you be stuffing your face
like this, as if you deserve to be?
This is our first meal of the day,
though!
Geez, he's really too much!
That darned Kang Dong-joo.
Now he's even telling on his seniors?
What do we do about this?
What should we do, Seo-Jung?
Hey, you. Intern.
Are you talking to me?
-Your name is?
-Kang Dong-joo, ma'am.
Yeah, you. Intern.
My name is Kang Dong-joo.
Yeah, your name is Intern.
I saw that you told on me to Dr Park.
All I did was call him to report
the situation since it was an emergency...
...since you couldn't be bothered,
with the bleeding patient and all.
So?
The patient with ARDS is fine, then?
Fortunately, she's been stabilized
and has been put in a room.
Geez, amazing.
You even saved a patient's life
when you're a mere intern.
You really did something amazing.
Looks like I'll be able to relax a bit
for the next month, thanks to you.
Right?
Well, I'll do my best.
Really?
You all heard him, right?
Our intern here said he'll do his best.
From now on, let's have our intern
deal with the MA patients.
What are you talking about?
You see, the TMs who come through
our ER are quite delicate.
So this experience will be really helpful
for you to grow as a doctor.
So do your best.
What does she mean by TM?
It's an acronym for Trouble-maker.
She means the worst kind of patient.
Worst kind of patient?
Hey, miss.
How much is it for two hours of karaoke?
They're there now, I think.
Let me take a quick look at you, sir.
You have quite a deep wound
in your forehead.
Let's disinfect that first with alcohol...
What do you mean, disinfect?
Alcohol is for drinking!
You don't even know that
and yet you're a doctor?
Let me disinfect your wounds...
-No!
-Just a moment, sir!
I said I'm not doing it!
What's wrong with the doctors
in this country?
Oh, my goodness!
Geez, you pervert!
Hey, you'd better do a good job,
did you hear me?
Our boss really hates needles.
You have a death wish, don't you?
Well, is it okay?
It's not too hard, is it?
Yes, it's not bad.
I heard you were the best of the best,
and you really are a cut above the rest.
So keep doing your best, okay?
And thanks for the coffee.
Seriously!
That's good.
It's an anal foreign body.
I think they were having too much fun
and the object got lodged in there.
Take it out for them.
What's in there, exactly?
Can't you tell?
Um...
About four anal beads
the size of golf balls got in there...
...but they got twisted up or something
and they won't come out.
What?
The rest of the string of beads
is coming out of his anus,
but some are stuck and the patient
is in excruciating pain.
Thankfully, there's no free air
in there, according to the x-rays.
Oh, yeah. Have you eaten?
Well, it can't be helped either way.
Take care of it and remove them for him.
Wait. How am I supposed to get them out?
Think long and hard about it.
What do you think you'll need
to remove something that's stuck?
Hey, aren't you being too tough on him?
Yeah. What if he ends up running away?
Well, that can't be helped then.
Sir, please relax!
How am I supposed to relax? It hurts!
-There you go!
-One, two!
Okay, we're almost done now!
-Breathe! One, two!
-Happy thoughts!
You really are a doctor, huh?
I got everything out.
The patient was screaming
quite loudly, though.
He got some anal fissures.
Are you sure he didn't tear
his sphincter too?
I did a thorough examination
and thankfully it's not too bad.
What a relief! Good job, Intern.
You're trying to piss me off, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
You're giving me the worst patients
on purpose to piss me off.
-Am I wrong?
-Geez, stop talking nonsense.
I didn't do anything.
Are you discriminating
because they're bad patients?
No, I'm complaining
because you're being ridiculous.
Hey, Intern.
How do you put an elephant
in a refrigerator?
What?
The answer is get the intern to do it.
Here, interns have to do
whatever the heck we tell them to.
And you can't discriminate
against patients and refuse to see them.
That goes for patients...
...who have shoved worse things
up their butts than just golf balls too.
You understood?
And if you can't handle it, leave.
I won't beg you to stay.
What did I do so wrong?
While you put on a show
with that bleeding patient,
I got someone to see a patient with ARDS
who got here before that guy.
Was that so wrong of me?
What did you just say?
"Put on a show?"
You do all that so that you can be
called things like...
"Crazy Whale" and "The Queen of
the Index Finger," don't you?
You have a big ego, but you're still
so thirsty for others' acknowledgement.
The medical term for that
is histrionic personality disorder.
Am I wrong?
And the medical term for what you have
is narcissistic personality disorder.
You're a darn psycho
who thinks he's great and has no respect!
What did you just say?
What? "Darn psycho?"
"Histrionic personality disorder?"
That crazy little...
He never acknowledges me.
Thirsty for acknowledgement, huh?
Maybe he was right.
Geez!
Wait, really?
They even cried!
Hurry up and eat.
You don't even have friends to eat with?
What about a girlfriend? Do you have one?
No. I don't have time.
What do you even live for then?
How boring.
You have no friends and no girlfriend.
That's probably why you were at the top
of your class for five years straight.
While acting all high and mighty too.
Right?
At the ER, it's not about
who got there first.
It's about who needs help more.
That day, I thought that the pneumonia
patient wasn't in critical condition.
So the issue was with my judgment.
I didn't ignore her
so I could put on a show.
You understood, Intern?
Thanks for the drink.
For the coffee I got from you last time.
I'm repaying you for that.
You were with him, weren't you?
Get over here already.
-What is it?
-You surprised me.
Are you teaching him a lesson,
or low-key flirting with him?
He may be a jerk, but he does
pretty admirable things.
Admirable, huh?
Even though he said
that you were hysteric?
Look how well he's enduring
even though he literally got crapped on.
There aren't a lot of people like that
among our interns nowadays.
Oh, geez.
You practically have hearts in your eyes.
Say what now?
I've had a fever since this morning.
And I feel kind of blocked up inside.
It feels like there's a weight inside
of me.
Should I get Dr Yoon Seo-Jung?
I'll do some preliminary checks first.
I'll take your temperature
and do a chest X-ray.
Okay.
Please get him an ECG as well.
She's not trying to spite you.
I mean, Dr Yoon Seo-Jung.
I know her well
since I've worked with her for a while.
She's just showing her interest
and affection toward you since you're good.
Her nickname is "Crazy Whale," but she's
actually quite a tenderhearted whale.
I'll get the ECG ready.
Oh! Oh, no! Honey!
Honey...
What happened? What's wrong with him?
He has no pulse.
I think he's going into cardiac arrest.
-Patient!
-Doctor, perform CPR!
Yes.
Call Dr Yoon Seo-Jung! Quickly!
What's going on? What happened to him?
The patient had a fever
but suddenly went into cardiac arrest!
Fever?
Maybe it's myocarditis?
How long has he been in arrest?
A bit over a minute now.
Shall I call the thoracic surgery specialist?
He's at an all-staff dinner tonight!
It'll take him at least 30 minutes!
Please prepare the defibrillator
and intubation for me.
And get the AP for me
within three minutes.
-Quickly.
-Yes, ma'am.
What are you doing? Do it harder!
Hey.
Move. Go over there.
Where's the defibrillator?
Let's give him ventricular fibrillation.
Charge it up, please.
Move back.
Go!
One more time. 200 joules!
Move back.
Go!
Let me see.
I'll check his pulse!
PEA compression!
This won't do.
It's not working, Doctor.
How many minutes has it been?
Four minutes and 30 seconds.
I'll do it.
Let's bring ECMO.
Are you out of your mind?
The chief doctor isn't even here!
I've called the thoracic surgery specialist.
I think it'd be best for us to wait
until he gets here.
If a younger man has a fever
and then goes into cardiac arrest...
...there's a high chance
that it's myocarditis.
We can save him
through extracorporeal membrane oxygenation.
If we wait any longer, we'll lose him!
It won't be of any use even if we get
his heart beating again then!
So hurry and get the ECMO machine!
But if something goes wrong
while you do that, you...
...you'll be blamed for all of this,
Dr Yoon!
Didn't you hear me? Get the ECMO machine!
What happened last time
with that artery was due to sheer luck.
You said so yourself that it only worked
because you got lucky!
You're not going to get lucky
like that all the time.
Let's just do CPR, okay?
Let's try it for 10 minutes.
And if it doesn't work,
it can't be helped. Okay?
How do you think you'd feel then?
How do you think you'd feel
if you were lying here...
...but the doctor in charge of you
was saying stuff like "it can't be helped?"
How do you think you'd feel then?
That's not the problem right now, though.
If something goes wrong,
you could cause medical accident!
I agree with that doctor, Dr Yoon.
Please wait.
Are you all really going to be like this?
I said that I'll take responsibility!
So go and bring it, right now!
Oh, darn it!
I brought the ECMO machine.
Hey, are you out of your mind?
You should be trying to stop her,
not enabling her!
Okay. Let's move the patient
to the hybrid room.
Are you confident that you can do this?
This was covered
in my clinical skills class last term.
I assisted at least 10 times per month.
One false move and he'll die.
Compression please, A-Ra.
You're driving me crazy!
Let's begin.
Get the probe.
Wire.
Blade.
Forceps.
Dilator.
12 cm wire.
24 cm wire.
Close it.
Tube.
Get the wire.
Tie.
Cut.
Turn the dial now.
Oh, we did it!
What's the patient's name?
Mr Lee Myung-woo.
You can hear my voice, right?
I'm Yoon Seo-Jung who performed
the surgery on you just now.
We're oxygenating your blood now.
I have no doubts that you'll be okay.
You have to hold on
until the very end, okay?
Okay, then.
Monitor his progress
and give me a call back.
What are you doing over there, Dr Moon?
Sit down and eat!
How long has this been running?
About 30 minutes.
The patient is fine too.
Call me if anything happens.
Yes, sir.
You, come with me.
Hey, are you out of your mind? Huh?
Who the heck do you think you are,
getting the ECMO?
Who's supposed to take responsibility
if something goes wrong?
The surgery went well
and the patient is still holding on.
Hey. If you're working in the ER,
just focus on ER-related things.
If you want the right to decide whether...
...or not patients get the ECMO
go and get a specialist's license!
He was dying, so we weren't
in a situation to be arguing about that.
At any rate, don't think that you'll be able
to get off the hook easily for this.
Prepare yourself.
It's okay.
It's okay!
You saved him. That's all that matters.
You did the right thing.
You did the right thing, Yoon Seo-Jung.
What is it?
I'm sorry. This is all because of me.
It's due to my own shortcomings.
I was a mess when I had to step up
and I acknowledge that I came up short...
...when I had to deal with the real thing.
Oh, stop. It's fine.
At any rate, the patient survived
and we did what we needed to do.
I can write a 1,000 page long letter
of apology if they want.
So don't be scared.
You weren't that bad either.
Your assisting skills were great.
Really?
Looks like you managed to get one of
the elephant's feet into the refrigerator.
Good job, Intern.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
Am I not allowed?
Am I not allowed to fall
heads over heels for you?
You're crazy.
Hey!
I have a boyfriend, you know!
I have someone I'm seeing already!
How dare you?
Crazy little brat... I can't believe him.
Seriously!
He's crazy!
Are you leaving?
Crazy. Crazy.
Oh, yeah.
Dr Moon is here.
About what happened before,
that was just an accident.
You know that, right?
An accident?
Well, you know...
We just saved a patient on the brink
of death, so...
So...
you and I were just really emotional,
is all.
There was an overproduction
of hormones in me at that moment
and I couldn't react properly,
so regarding what happened...
...I froze up for a moment
and couldn't react.
What do you mean?
I'm just saying that it didn't mean anything.
You understood?
For me, it was since that time...
...since that time you found
that patient's artery and held it down.
You were clinging on to that patient's bed
and heading to the OR.
I thought you looked so cool then.
Didn't you hear what I said?
I told you that I'm seeing someone.
I want to date you.
I told you that I'm seeing someone
and we're in a serious relationship!
And I want to sleep with you.
What?
What did you just say?
I like you, Senior.
I want to sleep with you.
That's him.
He's the one I'm dating.
I'm leaving now.
What are you thinking about?
Is this the finger that blocked off
the artery?
Yes.
This is your last year
as a medical resident, right?
Let's get married
as soon as your residency is over.
Doctor.
Let's do that.
Yes, this is the ER.
What? What is it?
Yes, I understand.
It's Dr Moon from the surgical department.
There's been a traffic accident
and Dr Yoon Seo-Jung is in the ICU!
Dr Yoon!
Her BP is bad.
She hit the right side of her head
and she's fractured the right side of her...
...skull as well as her right arm
so get her X-rayed first.
And make the necessary arrangements
to run tests on her.
Yes, sir.
Over here.
Get her hooked up!
Jelly.
It's a hemoperitoneum.
Get her up to the OR
as soon as her CT scan is done.
I'll operate on her myself.
And we have to take care of her right arm
and her fractures at the same time...
...so call Orthopedic and see
if we can do a combined operation.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Did you drink?
I'll call someone else
to handle the operation.
-Let's get her a CT scan first.
-Yes, sir.
Dr Moon?
I'm not Dr Moon.
I'm just that jerk intern.
We're on our way to get a CT scan
done on you now.
Where's Dr Moon?
He's in the ER.
He hasn't shed a drop of blood
and is completely fine.
So don't worry about him.
Go down there and check on Dr Moon first.
Are you out of your mind?
You're the one in critical condition
right now.
It wasn't me, but him.
He's the one who hit his head.
What are you doing?
I told you, hurry up and go!
-Dr Yoon...
-Kang Dong-joo!
Please.
Go to Dr Moon.
Please?
What is going on?
What happened with Dr Yoon?
Kang Dong-joo. Kang Dong-joo!
That jerk.
Kang Dong-joo!
Oh, Mr Tae-hwa! Mr Tae-hwa! Mr Tae-hwa!
Mr Moon Tae-hwa! Mr Moon Tae-hwa!
What do I do? He's not breathing!
He's not breathing!
It's not me, but him.
He's the one who hit his head.
What do we do? What do we do?
Mr Moon Tae-hwa!
Mr Tae-hwa!
It was a blood hemorrhage
due to trauma from a car accident.
Dr Yoon.
Dr Yoon, what's wrong?
Was my proposal too sudden?
In fact...
...I received a confession today.
Was it that fellow from before,
by any chance?
But...
...I was a bit swayed by that, Doctor.
I'm sorry.
Doctor!
She's not picking up?
Her phone is off.
She should've told us
where she was going, at least!
She's making me so worried!
Can't we call her family, or something?
She doesn't have anyone
like that we can contact.
What do you mean?
Doesn't she have parents?
No. She doesn't have any family
or relatives.
She's completely alone in this world.
I didn't know that.
Where could she have gone?
I like you, Dr Yoon.
Crazy little brat...
So she's still somewhat conscious.
Geez, she must be out of her mind, huh?
Who are you?
How could she think of hiking up
a mountain in her current state?
Is he a pervert?
Oh, your hip seems fine.
So it's your leg, of all things.
Geez. It's completely busted.
I can't leave her behind though.
Okay. Let's get your ankle realigned first.
It's going to hurt a bit.
One.
Two.
Three!
But what do I do with her now?
Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim
You should've been prepared for that much
if you were going to take the chance.
Doldam Hospital? Where is this place?
It's a sister hospital in Jung-sun.
Maybe he doesn't really like
our hospital?
Are you people crazy?
Are you sure you are real doctors?
I'm going to escape this wretched hospital
as soon as I can!
Since when have you been here?
I don't know how long you'll stay at...
...Doldam but let's pretend that we're
strangers while you're here, okay?
Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim