Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim
Dr Kang, are you okay?
Doctors are people, too.
Doctors can get MERS, too!
And sometimes, unfortunately,
we can die because of that.
Are you aware of that?
Dr Kang!
Mr Go.
Get me a surgical mask and a gown.
I'm going in.
You can't, Teacher Kim.
You're the control tower
at this hospital right now.
Please reconsider just one more time.
I'm going in.
I'll go in there, Doctor.
I'll go in there.
Please allow me to go in.
Look at you...
The doctor that the people in there
need right now... is me.
I...
...will go in.
Please allow me to go in.
Dr Kang.
Wake up, Dr Kang!
His BP is 100/70, with 120 bpm.
But his fever is 104.
Oh my goodness.
And he was treating
patients in this state?
What should we do, Nurse Oh?
TEACHER KIM
What did you say
his body temperature was, again?
Dr Seo-Jung!
Please tell me his vitals and
his temperature one more time.
His BP is 100/70, with 120 bpm.
His temperature is 104.
Dr Seo-Jung.
Give him 200 cc of normal saline per hour
and give him some fever medicine.
Will that be enough?
It's just a syncope.
I think it was because
he was severely dehydrated...
...so let's get him rehydrated first
and give him tons of fluids.
He'll be fine after getting some sleep.
What about the patient
with the acute appendicitis?
Where is she?
This way.
But shouldn't Dr Seo-Jung not be here?
If they confirm that
the patients have MERS,
then she can't participate in
Chairman Shin's surgery!
You're right!
Oh no!
She prepared so much for it, too.
Could you lie down flat, please?
I'm going to press on your stomach a bit.
You may regret what you're doing.
That still doesn't matter to you?
I did think that it didn't matter.
At that very moment, anyway.
I'll go in.
I wanted to be with him.
I wanted to stay by him.
At that very moment, anyway.
EPISODE 14
The Effect of Paragonimiasis
Here you are. I'll entrust this to you.
Section Chief Jang!
I heard that some potential
MERS patients came in?
We're only assuming for now,
but the ER has been closed off.
So why aren't you
all wearing hazmat suits yet?
Well, that's...
Are you there?
Sir!
Are you home?
Oh! Over here, sir!
Please open up!
Oh, hello!
Who are you?
How's the situation in there?
The patient with acute appendicitis
is getting worse.
Her fever is rising,
and her pains are growing worse, too.
I think it's turning
into peritonitis, Doctor.
When will it be possible to
perform surgery on her?
I'm not going in without a hazmat suit.
No way!
Hey, what happened with the hazmat suits?
Do we still not have them?
Teacher Kim!
They just got in touch with
the manager of the health center!
They'll be here with the hazmat suits
within the next 30 minutes!
You heard that, Dr Song?
They said 30 minutes.
Hurry up and get ready to
perform surgery!
-Darn it.
-Oh!
Do we finally get to
see Dr Song in action?
It seems like you'll be performing
your first surgery here.
Congratulations.
Well, don't!
Darn it, why did Kang Dong-joo
have to go into the ER?
Okay, then.
I'll head in first to make preparations.
Okay, Yoon Seo-Jung.
Keep that patient stabilized
for just 30 minutes.
We're going to head into surgery
the moment we get the hazmat suits.
Yes, Doctor.
Give this patient propacetamol via IV
and some antibiotics, too.
Yes, Doctor.
Over here, Dr Yoon!
Just a moment.
The chairman has gotten a lot better now.
His temperature is back to
normal levels now...
...and the sound of his breathing
is a lot better now, too.
What's the matter, sir?
Did you come up here yourself,
or did Yoon Seo-Jung send you up here?
I'm not sure what you mean...
I'm curious as to how Yoon Seo-Jung
knew about Kang Dong-joo passing out.
That news wasn't relayed to
the staff on the second floor.
It seems that Kang Dong-joo
passed out in the ER.
I'm not too sure.
I merely came up here because
Dr Yoon Seo-Jung called me up here.
So are you saying that
Yoon Seo-Jung called you first?
Yes, that's right.
Is that right?
Oh, look who it is!
Looks like our super important
VIP is finally here now!
How are you feeling?
That unpleasant female doctor
stuck a bunch of things in me,
and I'm feeling better, more or less.
She's good at what she does.
And she'll be my main assistant
during your surgery.
Really?
So why did you switch
my doctor to someone else, then?
Did she get upset because of me,
by any chance?
To be frank, there's trouble
at the hospital right now, Mr Chairman.
What?
Excuse me.
Can't I go in there too?
You cannot, ma'am.
Please sit and wait.
My kids are still young.
My eldest is barely in middle school.
When the people
from the health center come,
they'll tell us what to do.
So please sit and wait.
Excuse me.
Please take a seat here
and wait for a bit.
Do you guys want this?
You must be hungry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Soo-Jung.
What were the results of the
pulmonary function tests?
They're being maintained at around 90.
And his temperature is 96.
He's gotten a lot better,
but his temperature is still low.
Please cover him with one more of these.
Yes, Doctor.
Excuse me.
I told you, you can't do that!
Please let me go in.
My kids are in there.
Please move aside!
Sir, calm down!
Let go!
Please move!
Please allow me to be with my children!
You cannot act like this here, ma'am.
I cannot break the rules.
Please allow me to be with my children!
Let go! Let me go, you little brats!
I don't want to die!
Let go!
Excuse me.
Nobody is dying, here!
Nothing has happened yet,
and we haven't even confirmed
that it's MERS!
Please calm down, already.
What if they really do have MERS, then?
What are you going to do then?
That's more of a reason
why you shouldn't leave!
It's not like you'll die here and now...
...so to run out now would be
wishing death on everyone!
Do you really want to
do something like that?
If you cause a commotion one more time...
...I'm going to tell
your girlfriend everything...
...as soon as she wakes up.
It'd only be your own fault for
doing something humiliating.
Dr Yoon!
This patient's BP is dropping!
Soo-Jung.
Soo-Jung!
I see.
So how long will it take for
them to know for sure?
It'll take at least 24 hours for...
...the first round of test results
to come out.
Let me know when you know for sure.
Then I'll get discharged or go to
a different hospital, or something.
Aren't you scared, Mr Chairman?
Why would I be scared when you're here?
But MERS isn't something
I can do anything about as a surgeon.
And the case fatality rate is very high.
If I were fated to die,
I would've been dead 20 years ago.
But considering
I'm still alive like this...
...I don't think I'm someone
who's fated to die that easily.
Right?
TEXT MESSAGE
Go on.
It seems that they're looking for you.
Yes, sir.
20 years ago, huh?
When are you going to tell Teacher Kim?
When my surgery is over.
Don't you dare say anything until then.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
I received word about this too late.
Don't worry about it.
How many hazmat suits
did you bring in total?
We have 20 in total at our health center,
and I've brought them all.
Okay.
Hey, Dr Song!
Dr Song!
Aw man.
Wait, but how am I supposed to
do this alone without an assistant?
Even Dr Do In-bum
got assigned off to Chairman Shin!
You want me to do this myself?
Don't worry, I'll assist.
Wait... you will, sir?
Yeah, me.
Open the door, Nurse Eun-tak.
Dr Nam.
How are the anesthesia levels?
They're okay. Go ahead and start.
Hey.
Don't be nervous.
Who's nervous?
Scalpel.
Are you not going to do it?
There you go.
His fever has gone down quite a bit.
Yes.
Dr Kang has been
overworking himself, after all.
It seems so.
Your attention, please.
We've received word that someone
from the health center has just arrived.
They will now escort you home,
one by one.
But until we receive word about...
...whether or not this is MERS,
you should not leave your home.
And you will be monitored by
the health center until we confirm this.
The health center only has one vehicle...
...so we'll have the
hypothermia patient go home first.
What about those kids?
We'll take care of them ourselves,
so please stay out of it.
I mean, in all emergency situations,
shouldn't children be the priority?
What is this? It doesn't make any sense.
A patient with diabetes is the most at
risk when it comes to MERS.
And we're planning to
send the children out after him.
Oh, really?
I see.
Then... what about me?
You'll probably be among
the very last, I believe.
Goodbye.
He's sleeping so well.
Kang Dong-joo.
What? What is it?
Here's some disinfectant.
And put this mask on.
Hurry and head in there!
Mr Go, what's going on?
Teacher Kim!
Teacher Kim.
Huh?
The results just came out.
It's...
It's not MERS!
Our hospital's record is clean now,
Teacher Kim!
Dr Song!
It's not MERS!
Our hospital's record is clean now!
Hooray for Doldam Hospital!
THERE WERE NO TRACES OF THE
MERS CORONA VIRUS IN THE SAMPLES.
What is it then, if it's not MERS?
Hey, give me the blood test results.
The blood test results.
Oh... oh yes, of course!
Oh... oh, Teacher Kim!
Have the results come out?
Yes.
Firstly, the test results were negative.
Oh, really?
Yes!
Thank goodness!
What a relief.
But... what is it, if it's not MERS?
I'm trying to figure that out now.
Hey, why are their
eosinophil levels so high?
What?
Eosinophil?
Eosinophil? You mean...
By any chance,
have you eaten any raw freshwater animals
in the past couple months?
Freshwater?
Yes.
No, we haven't eaten anything raw.
We don't even eat sashimi that often.
Oh. Mom.
What about fermented soy crabs?
Do you cook fermented soy crabs?
Fermented soy crabs?
Was that made out of
Chinese mitten crabs, by any chance?
Oh, yes!
My mother brought some
since my husband likes it.
Remember?
She brought it just before your trip,
saying they were in season.
How long ago was that?
It was before I went on
my business trip...
...so about two months ago.
But why are you asking about that?
Nurse Eun-tak.
Let's do a sputum test on them.
A sputum test?
I think it may be paragonimiasis.
That's probably why their
eosinophil levels came out high.
Oh, I'm an idiot!
Why didn't I see that before?
Despite everything,
you still sent Dr Yoon in.
She could've lost her chance at
operating on the chairman, too.
Well, I couldn't hold her back.
I see.
And thus, the MERS scare
that had all of us in a frenzy ended...
...when we discovered
that it was actually paragonimiasis...
...caused by fermented soy crabs that
hadn't been fermented long enough.
And...
When did you wake up?
Not too long ago.
Oh, really?
Oh, your fever is gone now.
And you're not as pale anymore.
Are you dizzy? Do you have any ear pains?
You were severely overworked.
You lacked sleep,
were dehydrated, and malnourished.
Why are you so stubborn?
And you've been eating and sleeping only
in the staff room for two months.
It's true, right?
What are you talking about?
That you stayed by
my side the whole time.
And you even held my hand.
You must be hungry.
I'll go and get you some food.
It's true, isn't it?
Did you have a dream, or something?
I didn't do that.
So that didn't happen?
Nope. It didn't.
So you're really saying
that it didn't happen?
Probably.
Really?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to find out for myself
whether or not you're lying.
Oh, you avoided my gaze just now.
What do you mean? When did I do that?
Oh yeah.
The patients ended up
having paragonimiasis.
They didn't have MERS.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah. It was because of some soy crabs
that weren't fermented long enough.
So... it was paragonimiasis.
Isn't that funny?
Yes, it is.
Oh, fine, fine! Yes, it was me!
I was by your side!
You were, right?
And you even held my hand.
Well, that was just to check
if your fever was gone or not.
Hey, do you know how high your fever was?
104!
Your fever was that high.
What are you doing?
Hey...
It's only because I feel a bit dizzy.
I'm going to lean on you
for just a little bit.
If you're dizzy, you should eat.
You... should eat.
I no longer had the strength to
push him away.
Oh, this paragonimiasisish little...
Ms Woo Yeon-hwa?
Hello.
I'm a government-contracted doctor
assigned to Doldam Hospital.
Woo Yeon-hwa.
I'm pleased to be working with you all.
What's going on, Director Yeo?
Oh, she was a resident at
Gangwon University Hospital.
Wait, but I thought you were Chinese.
I'm a foreign exchange student.
A foreign exchange student?
Oh, wow!
I guess your family
is quite well-off, then.
My mother is Korean.
I see.
Then why did you show up looking
like a bum at our hospital before?
I was in my residency course,
and then ran away.
Then you should've
told us from the start!
Because I wasn't planning on
being a doctor ever again.
Because it was so hard.
So why the change of heart
all of a sudden, then?
Because of the staff here.
I watched the staff here work hard...
...and felt that I wanted to
become a real doctor, too.
At any rate, I'm happy to hear
that a familiar face will be joining us.
Isn't that right, Teacher Kim?
So?
What's your specialty?
General surgery.
Wow, general surgery, huh?
That's great!
Even foreigners are choosing to
go into general surgery.
This is the problem with
medical students in Korea.
They want to go into plastic surgery
or dermatology for the money.
Nobody wants to go into general surgery
or cardiothoracic surgery anymore.
Does that make any sense?
Here, in our great nation of Korea.
Oh geez.
Look here.
That may be true,
but that's not something
to be bringing up now, is it?
Oh... is that right?
I apologize.
I'll think of myself as starting over
as an intern and work hard.
I'm looking forward to your cooperation.
Wow, so you were a resident, Ms Yeon-hwa?
I'm here as a
government-contracted doctor...
...but it's fine to think of me as an
intern and use me however you'd like.
Really?
Well, your mindset is good.
But, are you fit?
Yes, and I'm very determined!
Oh, you're even determined, too!
Hello, Doctor.
Oh, Ms Yeon-hwa!
Apparently, she was a resident at
Gangwon University Hospital.
And a general surgery resident, at that!
Oh, really?
General surgery?
Yes.
That's great.
From now on,
I'll give you sage advice
that will become integral to you.
So you, Yeon-hwa...
It's okay if I just call you
by your name, right?
Yes, that's fine.
You can call me whatever you'd like.
Okay, then!
All you have to do, Yeon-hwa,
is trust and follow me.
Yes.
Be careful, Ms Yeon-hwa.
Dr Yoon Seo-jung's
nickname is "Crazy Whale."
How dare!
What, It's true, though...
Hey, Dong-joo.
Want some pizza?
-Whoa!
-What?
-Where did this pizza come from?
-I bought it yesterday.
I just reheated it and
it's nice and warm.
Eat up, okay?
Eat as much as you want!
I'll buy all your snacks from now on!
I mean it. 100 percent!
Thanks, Dr Yoon.
Would you like some too,
Section Chief Jang?
No, I'm on a diet.
Yeon-hwa, come over and have some.
We have to eat a lot when we can.
Because if you don't...
We have traffic accident patients!
All three are middle-aged.
Oh... you saw that, right?
This is how it is around here.
They'll be here in three minutes.
Oh, three minutes!
Please take your time to unpack and
come over when you're finished.
-Yes, I will.
-Goodbye, then.
It's nice to see you again, Ms Yeon-hwa.
Yes.
She was in a car accident!
She's a 35-year-old female...
...and we believe she hit her
head hard on the steering wheel.
Her BP is normal and
she seems to be a bit nauseated.
She also feels severe pain and dizziness.
What are her vitals?
BP is 100/65, with 120 bpm.
She may have some hemorrhaging,
so give her some maxeran
and take a CT scan of her brain.
Yes, Doctor.
One, two, three!
She was in the passenger seat
when the window shattered,
and she hurt her arm.
Ma'am, please don't cry!
I'll be examining you for a second.
Does anything else besides your arm hurt?
No. Please take it out.
There may be more glass
more deeply embedded,
so we'll take an x-ray first.
Nurse Park, take an x-ray of her, please.
Yes, Doctor.
-Where is he hurt?
-He has shoulder pain.
Oh, it's dislocated.
Sir, we believe your shoulder is
dislocated so we'll take an x-ray first.
-X-ray him, please.
-Yes.
-Can you take care of it?
Oh, you're back?
Please lie on that bed over there...
Teacher... Kim. Teacher... Kim.
Please call... Teacher... Kim.
Oh!
Excuse me!
Sir!
Mr Go?
Is it heart attack?
This patient has a pacemaker.
What are his vitals?
BP is 60/40, and he's not breathing.
What should we do?
Please call Teacher Kim.
And intubate him.
Let's move the patient.
Hey, why are you still
using the Ambu bag?
You have to hurry and
put a ventilator on him!
Oh... I was just about to do that.
Nurse Oh.
Mix dopamine and dobutamine together...
...and give him 10 cc per hour.
And prepare some isoket,
and only give it to him
when his BP goes up.
And put a Foley in him,
and check his urine.
Yes, Doctor.
Here are the ABGA results.
I think it'd be good for you to
go over there.
All right.
Here are the results for the ABGA.
It's respiratory acidosis.
I'll do a echocardiogram on him.
Oh... the ejection fraction in
his DCMP is dropping a lot.
It's only about 25 to 30 percent.
You said you've done
an ECMO before, right?
Yes, I have.
No, not you.
Hey!
I'm talking to you, Do In-bum.
Yes, I have, but...
Okay. You take care of it today, then.
And you assist him, Yoon Seo-Jung.
And call Dr Nam Do-il.
Call him before the ECMO machine's here.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing, sir?
Could you help me a bit?
With what?
What's this?
I want to give a gift to a woman
whose name I cannot tell you.
Which one do you think is better,
this one or this one?
A Christmas gift?
Isn't it romantic?
A present given amidst
a white blanket of snow.
A warm, cozy hug.
Yes. And...
Oh, I'm sorry.
If you also have a woman
whose name you do not wish to reveal...
...how about making a move by
giving her a Christmas gift?
No thanks.
I'm okay.
Really, though?
Man.
Is this better?
Oh, this is nice.
Start.
Needle, please.
Guidewire.
Scalpel.
Gauze.
Give me the smallest dilator you have.
The next smallest one.
I'll put the cannulas in now.
Are you sure about this?
What?
I asked you if you're sure
this is the right one!
I think that Dr Do In-bum
got confused for a second.
The infusion line is the red one.
Oh.
I was too focused.
I guess I got confused for a second.
Stop.
Yoon Seo-Jung.
Switch spots with Do In-bum.
Nurse Oh, please assist.
Yes, Doctor.
Do In-bum.
Follow me outside.
Answer me honestly.
What's the difference between
the venovenous and venoarterial in ECMO?
The venovenous is used
when there is only respiratory failure...
...and the venoarterial is used
when there is heart failure as well.
And what we did before?
Venoarterial.
And why did you put a drain line
all the way up to the right atrium?
Because there could be an IVC collapse
when the ECMO flow increases.
And why is that a problem?
Because there won't be
enough blood in the return drain.
You know that so well!
And yet you got the cannulas mixed up?
I'm sure it seemed
as if anyone could do it...
...as long as they knew the technique.
But there's something you overlooked.
When it comes to ECMO surgeries,
there is an intricate awareness of
physiology involved.
It's not just about simply
sticking cannulas in the patient.
You may be able to
deceive me with your words...
...but you can never deceive me
with these hands of yours.
Because a surgeon's hands can
only move with purpose and precision,
if they have experience and effort.
As for why you lied to me about
doing something you've never done,
how far you thought
you could trick me with your imitations,
and why you even went so far to do it...
I won't ask for the reason.
However.
Don't degrade yourself by
becoming an expendable person.
Did you head straight here
from the airport?
I had to, after hearing
the chairman was hospitalized.
Where is he now?
Is he in critical condition?
He's currently not at this hospital.
Didn't you say
he was hospitalized, though?
He's at a small hospital
called Doldam in Jungsun.
Actually, that's the reason
for the emergency meeting.
What?
Is there something wrong with me?
I think what I'd feared has happened.
Don't try to scare me,
and just give it to me straight.
I believe that there's an issue
with your artificial heart.
In this case, I'll have to change...
...out the artificial heart itself
and not the batteries.
But this isn't that
simple of a surgery, you see.
Does it make any sense?
Why would he have...
...such a dangerous surgery done
at that tiny hospital?
I, too, tried to talk him
out of this many times.
But he was resolute in his decision.
And this is why I asked you
to come all this way.
To ask this favor.
I'm well acquainted with
my old man's stubbornness.
He'll never change his decision
once he puts his mind to it.
So, who's the doctor in charge of him?
Is it a skilled doctor?
It's someone they call "Teacher Kim."
Teacher Kim?
I don't know if you remember...
...but he once went by the name
Bu Yong-joo and worked at Geosan.
Bu Yong-joo...
Are you talking about
that crazy little brat?
What, are you wussing out now
that the time has finally come?
We should remove and
discard your old artificial heart...
...and put a new artificial heart
inside of you.
That in itself is quite a rare case.
This is so rare that
there aren't even survival
statistics published about this.
What an honor this will be for you, then.
I'm even giving you an opportunity to
perform that kind of surgery.
What, do you have no confidence?
If that's not the case,
I want you to do it.
May I ask you the reason
why you trust me this much?
I already told you.
I'm someone who tries to survive,
no matter what.
And you're someone who tries to
save people, no matter what.
And since those two stubborn
little brats have come together...
I'm sure my chance at survival
will go up by that much, too.
All doctors do their best to
save patients, Mr Chairman.
Do you think they'd really do that...
...if they were receiving
billions of dollars not to?
-Pardon?
-Be quiet and you do it.
At the very least,
I'll die without suspicions or regrets
if I die in your operating room.
I'll do a CT scan of your chest tomorrow.
And we can continue with...
...the rest of the tests we couldn't do,
due to the MERS scare.
I've scheduled Chairman Shin's
surgery, nine days from today.
We'll be discarding the artificial heart
that's currently in his body,
and replacing it
with a new artificial heart.
-Kang Dong-joo.
-Yes, sir?
You'll be in charge of discarding
the batteries on the old model.
They were placed in him two years ago...
...so there will be a lot of
fibrous tissue on them.
Once you've discarded them,
I'll start with
the removal of the old model.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
-Yoon Seo-Jung.
-Yes, Doctor?
You'll be my main assistant,
as I said before.
Speed is key here, so make sure
you can keep up with me.
Yes, sir.
Do In-bum.
This time, you will assist Kang Dong-joo.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
Okay, I plan on doing three simulations...
...prior to the real surgery.
I'll let you all know the schedule
as soon as I choose the dates and times.
So be aware of that, and be prepared.
Okay, that's all!
Okay. Are you all ready?
Yes.
Scalpel.
Until we proceed with
the artificial heart,
we'll allot three hours from the initial
incision and insertion of the cannulas.
And 45 minutes for
the subcision in the abdomen,
the removal of the battery,
as well as the controller.
So there are only 45 minutes allotted
from the subcision to the removal?
No. That 45 minutes includes
suturing up the subcision, too.
You shouldn't forget that
the patient is a 72-year-old man.
We have to shorten the length
of the surgery as much as we can.
Yes, sir.
Change positions!
We'll give two hours for
the removal of his current model...
...and another two hours for
the installation of the new model.
Then one hour for hemostasis,
and one hour to close up his chest area.
So the entire surgery will
take 9 hours and 45 minutes, then.
No, no.
We have to make it even shorter.
We need to finish in seven hours to
minimize the damages done on the patient.
First, let's shorten the starting of
the artificial heart by one hour.
And let's shorten the time for removal
and installation by 30 minutes each.
We'll still be 45 minutes over
our ideal time, though.
Then, I'll try my best to
finish my part in 30 minutes.
I'll have the subcision in the abdomen,
the removal of the battery,
and controller done within 30 minutes.
30 minutes, including stitching him up.
I'll try my best.
Don't say that you will try.
I'll do it, sir.
Okay.
We'll still be 30 minutes
over our ideal time, though.
Do you have any ideas?
The preparations for the surgery
are going better than we'd expected.
Everyone still thinks that
it will succeed, for now.
And Chairman Shin
seems to think that, too.
Well, things can change at any moment.
By the way... how much longer
do I need to stay here?
Until I tell you to leave.
Until then, don't complain
and just bear it.
I'll call you again later.
Don't degrade yourself by
becoming an expendable person.
Thank you.
Huh?
One of these is mine.
But who is this for?
DOLDAM HOSPITAL TO...
Oh, this is...
Okay.
What am I doing right now?
Are you... leaving work?
Um, yeah. I'm a bit tired.
I'm going to head home early and rest.
Oh. I... see.
I'll get going now.
Dr Yoon Seo-Jung.
I have another package for you.
What package?
I don't know, but I think it may be
a gift from someone...
...who wants to spend Christmas with you.
What could it be?
Dong-joo.
See me for a second.
I thought you said she'd like it.
Everyone else usually does.
Maybe she just doesn't
like things like that?
Maybe she's more into bags than jewelry?
What is this?
A Christmas gift.
I heard that women like to
receive things like that.
Take it back.
Why?
Do you not like it?
I just don't want to accept this.
Take it back.
What do you mean, exactly...
when you say that
you don't want to accept this?
What other meaning would there be?
I just don't want to accept it, is all.
Am I that unlikable?
Do you really not see me...
...as a man?
It's not like that.
What is it, then?
How do you feel about me, exactly?
I...
...like you.
Then why?
But...
...the more I grow to like you...
...the more I remember the accident
from five years ago.
But I can't allow myself to do that.
I can't help that my feelings for you
overlap with my memories of the accident.
That's just too unfair to you...
...and I'd feel so bad
for feeling that way.
That's why.
So, Kang Dong-joo...
We...
I'm okay with that, though.
I've never expected anything
from you, Dr Yoon.
And I heard the answer that
I wanted to hear just now.
That's all you have to do.
I'm fine with everything,
as long as you like me.
So, please...
So, Dr Yoon...
I can't?
PATIENT CHART SEARCH SHIN MYUNG-HO
Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim