Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim
Yes, hello?
It's me, Oh Sung-jae.
So, if I tell you that I do have
the courage to reveal that truth...
...can you tell me the truth?
Dr Bu Yong-joo?
Sometimes, in life, it takes time
for you to be able to see the truth.
Such as the reasons why
those things happened to me.
Why I'd met someone like that.
Why I'd taken a detour like that.
Which department are
you a part of, Doctor?
Are you close with Dr Bu Yong-joo?
The countless moments that
I'd deemed insignificant...
It's you, isn't it?
The person from that time.
Dr Bu Yong-joo.
Everything starts to become
significant, one by one.
Why do you keep asking me
about Bu Yong-joo?
What is it that you want to know, exactly?
He's someone whom I respect.
I want to learn from you, Doctor.
Studying hard and becoming
someone like him is my dream.
Doing a joint surgery
with you is my dream.
And they started to pave
a path, at one point.
Will you tell me what
the truth is, already?
Will you tell me what really
happened 14 years ago,
as well as why
Jang Hyun-joo died like that,
and why Dr Bu Yong-joo quit working
at the main hospital overnight?
There's no "truth."
14 years ago, Bu Yong-joo was...
...a coward and fell silent.
And he ran away.
That's all there is to it.
EPISODE 18
Whether You Want It or Not
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
Establishing Emergency Trauma Center
Proposal by Teacher Kim, Chief of
Surgical Department at Doldam Hospital
Let's talk for a bit, Section Chief Jang.
Yes, I'll step out for a bit, then.
What is it?
Were you the one who handed over
Teacher Kim's documents to Director Do?
Why...
...do you think that was me?
Had you already been convinced by them,
when you were promoted to Section Chief
as soon as Chief Song came here?
How could you accuse me of such things?
Being promoted was, to an extent,
due to my own performance.
Oh, really?
Why did you go into Teacher Kim's
office that day, then?
What do you mean, "That day"?
When?
Section Chief.
Dr Yoon told me that you told
her you were emptying out his trash.
But that doesn't quite
make sense, doesn't it?
Why not?
Am I...
...not allowed to empty people's
trash bins for them?
You think I don't know you,
Mr Jang Ki-tae?
You said that you were
pampered as a child,
and never even sorted the trash properly!
You didn't even toss out the wooden
chopsticks you used to eat cup noodles!
And yet, you emptied out a trash bin?
And one in someone else's office, at that?
Look at me in the eye.
Look straight into my eyes and tell me!
You were the one who gave him
Teacher Kim's documents, weren't you?
No!
Are you sure?
It wasn't me!
I really am innocent this time!
Then, who?
Who handed those documents
over to Director Do?
Who?
I don't know anything.
I don't remember a thing.
Do you think you're in the courtroom?
I told you, I'm just here for udon.
Just give me some udon.
CASINO OWNER CHAIRMAN SHIN MYUNG-HO
HAS BECOME BRAIN DEAD...
after his artificial heart transplant
surgery at Doldam Hospital.
SUBMIT
BULLETIN BOARD FOR
DAEGUK INVESTMENTS AND SECURITIES
How's the chairman doing?
Is he displaying pain responses?
No, he's not responsive yet.
He should've woken up by now.
Approximately 24 hours have
passed since the surgery was done.
The fact that he still hasn't woken up yet
definitely means that there's...
...an issue with his brain.
And in the worst case scenario,
we'll have to shut down Doldam Hospital.
There won't be a need to have him treated
at a hospital that will be closed down.
But still, you're going to shut down
a hospital just because of that?
Rumors regarding the chairman have already
begun to circulate in the stock markets.
FROM: SUNG IN-CHUL OF
DAEGUK INVESTMENTS AND SECURITIES
Brain dead?
Who's spreading these baseless rumors?
People care more about
thrilling rumors than the facts.
You have to think of what's best for
the chairman from this point onward.
We don't have a moment to lose.
Yes, this is Doldam Hospital's ER.
Where did you say you were from?
Well...
...I'm not sure.
One moment.
Nurse Oh, it's a reporter.
They asked if Chairman Shin's
surgery was performed here.
Hello, this is the hospital's ER.
We don't know much about things like that.
It'd be best for you to direct your
inquiry to the Administrative Office.
Yes, this is Doldam Hospital's ER.
Oh, just one moment.
These people are asking about
the same thing, Nurse Oh.
They say that they're reporters and
are asking about Chairman Shin.
Hello, this is the hospital's ER.
We only take calls regarding
emergency patients!
What if your call prevents a call about
an actual patient from getting through?
I said I don't know.
Don't call back.
What's going on, Nurse Oh?
I think that there's a rumor
going around online, Nurse Oh.
A rumor going around online?
CASINO OWNER CHAIRMAN SHIN MYUNG-HO
HAS BECOME BRAIN DEAD...
What do you mean?
What's going on?
A post saying that the chairman is
brain dead is spreading on social media.
How could a groundless rumor...
No, it's not like that at all.
I told you,
we can't tell you such things!
Good day, sir!
What is going on?
I'm not sure, either.
I feel as if we've been hit by a bomb!
What's the commotion about?
I told you, it's really not!
What's going on?
It's nothing.
There are some bad rumors
regarding Chairman Shin's surgery...
...spreading on social media.
Reporters have gotten wind of it
and are calling us to confirm.
Don't worry.
I'll block them like an iron barricade.
Oh, you're here, Mr Director?
Is Director Yeo in his office?
Well,
is Director Yeo upstairs right now?
The director is out right now.
Yes, Section Chief Jang? What is it?
Director Do from the main hospital is
here right now.
Just a moment.
It's me, Director Yeo.
What brings you to Doldam
without any prior notice?
I've come to give you one final message.
The Doldam branch of our hospitals
will soon be shut down.
We'll make that decision at
the provisional board meeting tomorrow.
So stop stalling for time, and get
Chairman Shin to the main hospital.
If you want a position at the new assisted
care facility we'll be building,
it'd be best for you to do as I say.
I've said what I needed to say,
so I'll be hanging up now.
I'll go see Chairman Shin
since I'm already here.
Director Do. Director Do?
Has it really been decided that
Doldam will be shut down?
This means I can go back to
the main hospital, right?
Right?
Teacher Kim.
What do you mean, they've decided to
shut Doldam Hospital down?
Apparently Director Do just
came by and said that.
Nurse Oh and everyone else
are in a state of panic right now.
What will we do, then?
And what will happen to
everyone at the hospital?
Come back to Seoul now.
Tomorrow, the decision to close
this place down will be made,
and the decision will be implemented
as soon as it is made.
Why...
...do you have to go so far?
What is the reason you
must go to such lengths?
Because the Foundation feels that
this place is an old and useless hospital.
Useless?
Chairman Shin will be transferred to
the main hospital by the end of today.
It'd be nice if you came with him
and watched over him.
I'll assign you to him, so...
...come back
to the main hospital now, okay?
Shutting down the hospital?
What on earth are you trying to do, here?
You locked my father up in there
while waving that document in my face,
so as his daughter,
I can't just sit and watch.
I have to move Father to
the main hospital,
even if I have to
shut Doldam down to do it.
Look here, Ms Director.
Do you even know how many
flock to Jungsun...
...just because of the casino
that you people built here?
Approximately 8,500 per day!
On top of that,
there are at least 30 to 40 traffic
accident patients per week in the ER.
So what are all those people to do
if you get rid of the hospital?
Are you telling them to go from hospital
to hospital because there's no ER here...
...until they just die on
the side of the road?
Director Do told me that
you people cost us...
...over a million dollars in
deficits every year.
And this year, there was
a 1.5 million dollars deficit.
So you're going to talk about some money
when I'm talking about the injured?
The Geosan University Foundation no longer
wishes to cover Doldam's deficits.
Your father received
surgery at that hospital.
And it's at that hospital where he lies,
still unconscious.
72...
No, you can't even wait 48 hours?
48 hours?
They said that the longer
he remains unconscious,
the greater the chance of him
becoming brain-dead!
And who told you that
he'd become brain-dead?
I, his primary doctor, never said so,
so who the heck told you that?
Is money the only thing that you
people care about right now?
Are you weighing the pros
and cons of having him die,
versus having him hang on for
a bit longer?
And wondering which scenario
would help you inherit his fortune?
Aren't you out of your mind?
If that's not the case...
...shut your mouth and just do as I say.
You can decide to shut down the hospital
or whatever after I save your father!
They're not really going to shut
this place down, are they?
Geez, this is driving me crazy.
It's looking quite grim.
What do we do?
Do I need to find another job?
Oh, it's Nurse Oh.
What happened, Nurse Oh?
Is our hospital really shutting down?
Nothing has been decided yet.
Just focus on work and
act as you always have.
How could you focus on work
at a time like this, Nurse Oh?
I told you that it doesn't hurt!
I'm going home!
You told me that your
stomach hurt a lot before, sir.
We have to get you a CT scan, at least.
What's going on?
He had too much to drink and
he kept saying that his stomach hurt.
So I told him that we'd get
a CT scan of him, but he refuses.
I told you, I'm not getting a scan!
Why would I waste money to
get that kind of thing done?
If I had money for that,
I would've gotten another drink instead.
Sir.
Please listen to what
the doctor is saying.
I told you, I'm not a patient!
Get out of my way. I'm going home.
Sir.
Let go! Get out of my way!
Get out of my way!
What should we do?
Shouldn't we prevent him from leaving?
Just leave him alone.
We get plenty of
drunken patients like that.
What are you doing?
Well, I was just resting for a bit.
I should go back in there now.
Are you okay?
The hospital may be closing down...
...so of course I'm not.
What's this?
It belongs to Teacher Kim.
This was the big picture that
Teacher Kim was working on.
Did you know about this too?
No.
I had no idea.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
Establishing Emergency Trauma Center
So this is what he was thinking about.
Yes.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
Director Yeo.
Are you okay?
Well, this won't really affect me.
I'm just a powerless person
who has taken a back seat, after all.
But still, I wanted to become an adult,
who sided with justice and give
that justice some strength to act.
What do you mean by that?
Just a moment ago,
I just received word that
Doldam Hospital will be shut down.
From Director Do Yoon-wan.
Isn't it strange?
We all know that
Do Yoon-wan is in the wrong.
Everyone knows that what
he's doing right now is wrong.
So why does he still maintain
a position of such power?
Thank you for the udon.
Looks like you were off somewhere.
Geosan is sending an ambulance
and some staff to escort Chairman Shin.
Oh!
They should be here any moment now.
With whose permission?
Who else's? Director Do's, of course.
Just give up now.
The decision to have this place
shut down will be made tomorrow, anyway.
You don't still believe that
Chairman Shin will wake up, do you?
Oh, come on.
Section Chief Jang.
Yes, Teacher Kim?
Take out this trash, will you?
What? Trash?
Also, make sure that none of
those guys from Seoul get in here.
Did you just call me "trash"?
Of course you are.
Since the one who calls himself a doctor
is praying for a patient to not wake up!
I'm just letting you know that
it's game over for you!
I just feel bad watching
as you desperately insist...
...on trying to extend his life
when there's no hope!
I don't care who they are.
Just see what happens
if they come near the ICU.
I'll sue them all.
Got that?
Yes, sir.
Look here, Section Chief Jang!
"Yes"?
You can't be saying that!
You'd better hurry up and choose
your side properly, now!
Figure out who you're loyal to
Doldam or Geosan!
Okay?
Yes, sir.
Seriously!
I'm so angry.
It took so much hard work
and effort for us to get this far.
Teacher Kim and the rest of us...
...worked so hard to get this far.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
Establishing Emergency Trauma Center
I'll be checking your pain
response now, Mr Chairman.
I can't just give up, right?
So please, wake up.
Please, Mr Chairman.
Nurse Uhm, regarding
Patient Lee Kang Jin...
I wonder if I'll get paid
for my work this month.
I know, I really had a hard time
to get an apartment.
Nurse Uhm!
Huh?
Yes.
Aren't you going to pick up?
They've only been calls about
Chairman Shin all day, so...
But what if it's a call
regarding a patient?
Yes, this is the ER at Doldam Hospital.
Yes, I understand.
We have a patient with a glass shard
in his abdomen coming in five minutes.
Didn't you hear me say that
a patient is coming in?
What's with you all?
Why are you all just staring at me?
We heard that Doldam Hospital
may be closing down.
Nobody can seem to focus on work
because we're all so worried.
Will the hospital really be shutting down?
I want to hear it from
you directly, Doctor.
Please, tell us.
That's what I want to ask you all.
Have you all decided to shut
Doldam Hospital down already?
That's not it...
If that's not it,
why are you all acting as if
the hospital is already closed?
Nurse Oh.
Why are you hunched over like that?
I have no intention of
shutting down this hospital.
I stood here yesterday and today,
and plan to do so tomorrow, too,
and wait for the patients
who need my help.
That's what I've decided, Kang Dong-joo.
-Doctor.
-So just act as you usually do.
Let's just focus on the patients as
we all usually do, Kang Dong-joo.
We have an emergency patient!
He's a 37-year-old man and has
a piece of glass stuck in his abdomen.
What happened?
Oh, he climbed a ladder to try
and swap out a light fixture,
and he fell toward a window.
The glass got stuck in
his stomach as it shattered.
We'll move him to the hybrid room.
Okay.
Nurse Uhm.
Yes?
Yes.
Teacher Kim said that the scariest
thing to do is act as you normally do,
instead of backing down
in the face of uncertainty and fear.
Dr Yeon-hwa.
The patient's clothes, please.
Oh, of course!
His vitals are 119/70, with 70 bpm...
Oh! Dr Yeon-hwa!
This is why you don't tear
into padded clothing.
I'm so sorry!
I didn't know!
Can I get a D-set?
I'll take a look at his wound.
Yes, Doctor.
I'm sorry!
Put two lines in him and one liter of
a full drop saline solution.
Give him a tetanus shot,
some antibiotics,
and let's also get a CT scan of him.
Yes, sir.
Teacher Kim may have already known...
...that our worries and fears...
...could become
even lighter than feathers.
Yes, what is it?
Oh, come in, come in!
I got your call and was waiting for you.
Oh, good thing you're here,
Section Chief Jang.
Will you escort them, please?
What are you doing?
I told you to hurry up and escort them!
What are you doing right now?
Teacher Kim ordered us to not let
a single person pass through.
None of you may go upstairs.
What? Why, you...
Step aside.
Step aside right now!
I can't.
No, I won't.
Why, you!
Oh?
Eh?
Wow, are you serious?
Seo-Jung.
You said that the chairman is conscious?
Yes, Doctor.
He's nearly alert.
I think he's about a 10 on the GCS scale.
Mr Chairman.
Can you hear my voice?
If you can hear my voice,
please move your hand a bit.
Mr Chairman.
Doctor!
What do you mean?
They've blocked you off
so that you can't get in?
That ass Teacher Kim ordered them not to
let anyone into the ICU!
Even this Section Chief of
Administration is blocking the path!
Is that Director Do, by any chance?
Yes, Director!
We promoted him to Section Chief,
yet he's acting so ungrateful.
I'm so appalled!
We have no more time to lose,
so force your way through.
Escort the chairman out of there,
even if you have to use force.
Now!
Yes, sir.
I'll do that.
Okay, let's prepare ourselves.
You go up this way,
and you go up that way.
And you go up this way.
Man...
I really wasn't going to do this, but...
-Go!
What are you doing right now?
What else?
We're on our way to go escort
Chairman Shin,
as we were ordered to.
Are you people some neighborhood thugs?
What the heck are you people
doing at a hospital?
So why did you tell him to block us off?
You think I'm doing this
because I want to, at this age?
Shut your mouth,
And all of you,
get the heck out of here.
Wow, how frustrating.
I told you, we have to
escort Chairman Shin!
He's awake now.
Exactly!
He's awake now, so we...
Wait, he woke up?
The chairman is awake now.
So shut your mouth quietly,
and disappear from this hospital. Now.
Got it?
Father did?
The chairman...
...woke up?
Okay.
No, no... I'm heading there now.
Father is awake now.
He recognizes everyone
and he's fully conscious.
How's Father?
Go inside, ma'am.
Mr Chairman!
How are you feeling, Mr Chairman?
Did the surgery go well?
Of course.
It went perfectly well, Mr Chairman.
Good job, Teacher Kim.
Father.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Father!
Do you know how worried I was?
Thanks, Dad.
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Doctor.
That impudent little brat...
What will you do now, Director?
The chairman is awake now, so...
At any rate, we'll have
the staff who were sent here...
...return to Seoul tomorrow, as planned.
And I'll return to the main
hospital tomorrow as well.
No.
Stay here for now.
What?
This game isn't over yet.
So stay here,
and know that you'll be buried here
if Doldam isn't shut down.
Buried here?
I'm sorry, Honey!
I was told that I'd be going back to
the main hospital tomorrow,
so I'd even packed all my bags!
But the decision was reversed
all of the sudden, so...
I'm really upset, too!
You think I'm here because I want to be...
Hello? Hello?
Just who was I even talking to?
Oh no...
Looks like your wife is really mad.
I have two choices now.
Submit a letter of resignation,
or have her divorce me.
Can't she just come and live here?
She's already looking into
kindergartens for my daughter,
even though she just learned how to walk.
Oh, so she won't come, then.
I'll buy you some beer at Come and Go
when we get out of work today.
I'm in!
Me too!
Does that place even have
good food, though?
Dr Nam's ramen with
rice cakes is delicious.
His signature dish is
ramen with rice cakes?
Well, no. Maybe beer?
What do you want?
I heard that the CT scan for the patient
with the glass in his abdomen is done.
Want to come and take
a look at it with me?
This isn't really
a common case, after all.
We can look at it together, and it'd be
even better if you'd assist for me.
What do you mean?
Everyone is having a hard time
right now because of my father.
So what?
So I'm sure that people don't want
to see my face around, either.
To be honest,
I really can't stand
seeing Director Do's face.
But that's not your fault.
I'd be super embarrassed if I were you
and my father was acting like that.
Are you trying to insult me again?
Forget about that.
So are you going to assist me, or not?
The patient is waiting.
Hurry up and decide, okay?
Never mind if you don't want to!
Oh, fine! Okay!
Geez, you sure take advantage
of people like crazy!
Hey, you have to assist me
next time, okay?
You got that?
Seriously...
Dr Kang Dong-joo!
I was just on my way to see you.
A piece of registered mail for you
came from Geosan University Hospital.
Registered mail?
For me?
Yes, sir.
SURGERY RECORDS
DR BU YONG-JOO DATE: APRIL 29TH, 2002
April 29th...
Who sent this?
I'm not sure.
It's from the main hospital,
so I didn't check to see who it was from.
Did you send the thing I told
you to send yesterday?
Yes, Director.
I sent it as registered mail.
It should have arrived there today.
Okay, that'll be all. You can leave now.
The scariest thing is a seed of doubt.
If you just scatter it, it grows well
without any effort on your part.
SURGEON: BU YONG-JOO
FIRST ASSISTANT: KANG TAE-WOOK
Mr Kang Won-young has passed away.
Father...
Father!
Oh, Honey!
SURGEON: BU YONG-JOO
I'll check on him one more time later.
Borders meeting members won't
be discussing...
...the closure of Doldam
for the time being.
You know that you're only safe
as long as Father is here, right?
Yes.
Of course.
To be honest,
I still can't acknowledge you.
But I truly thank you for
what you did this time.
I mean it.
Sure.
I don't only care about my inheritance
and such because I'm rich.
As for me,
I just want to live under
my father's shadow for a long, long time.
So I'd like it if Father lived
a long time.
I'm heading back to Florida for
a bit because of my kids,
but I'll be back early next month.
So please take good care
of my father until then.
Yes, have a safe trip.
Well, goodbye, then.
Oh, I have one thing I'm curious about.
Yes?
How did you decide on
the name "Teacher Kim"?
What's your name, Doctor?
Me?
I have a really plain and common name.
It's Kim something...
Oh, I see, Dr Kim Something.
Dr Kim Something!
Are you busy right now?
What?
When you're doing a
Billroth II gastrectomy,
do you just leave
the front part obstructed?
I'm just curious.
Dr Kim Something!
Are you leaving work now?
What is it now?
When you're performing
a Roux-en-Y gastric bypass,
you're supposed to just leave
the duodenum alone...
...when you connect the stomach
and jejunum, right?
That's a video of the surgery
you asked me about.
It has footage of a gastrectomy
and a Roux-en-Y gastric bypass.
Is this footage of surgeries that
you did yourself?
Why do you have so many questions?
Just watch the thing!
You sure are a chatterbox.
Hurry up and get better soon.
Thank you!
I'll call you "Teacher" from now on!
My child gave this to me
before she went into surgery.
She said that it was
a gift for you, Doctor.
STUDENT ID: JANG HYUN-JOO
SURGICAL DEPARTMENT
To: Dr Teacher Kim
To: Dr Teacher Kim.
I was quite a nuisance to you
all this time, wasn't I, Doctor?
But thank you for taking the time to
teach me and talk to me anyway.
To be honest, I knew from the beginning
that you were Dr Bu Yong-joo.
Mister!
Do you know Dr Bu Yong-joo,
by any chance?
I was so nervous that I blurted
that out before I knew it.
I don't think I'll ever forget the time
I spent with you at the hospital.
Thank you for being
the head surgeon of my surgery.
I'll come and visit you after
the surgery is over and I'm healthy again,
while dreaming of the day that I'll be
standing in an operating room with you.
Your disciple, Jang Hyun-joo.
I see.
Do you think that girl knew...
...that the name she gave you...
...changed your life forever?
I don't know.
To: Dr Teacher Kim
I don't think any of his main arteries are
damaged, according to the CT scans.
It does look like his intestines are
injured, however.
So this injury won't affect his life if
he gets surgery, right?
Hey, Kang Dong-joo.
Huh?
We'll only know the specifics after
we go into surgery and check it out.
It could be that we can't see the vessel
that was damaged by the glass.
Oh, I see.
Let's move him to the OR first.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
It's nothing.
We have a patient!
Get him to bed number three, quickly.
What happened to him?
Chest pains that began
right when he called us.
Chest pain?
We gave him two doses of antibiotics,
but his pain didn't get any better.
How are his vitals?
BP is 160/100, with 100 bpm.
Please check his vitals
one more time, Nurse Oh.
And run an EKG test on him, please.
Understood.
His BP is 100/60 now.
What?
Why did his BP change so suddenly?
Can you take his vitals
from his right side, please?
Of course.
Weren't you in the ICU?
I'm just on my way back from there.
What about the EKG results?
Here you are.
It's not a STEMI.
His BP is 160/60 on his right side,
and 100/60 on his left side.
Really?
What kind of pain are you
experiencing in your chest, sir?
It feels like it's being torn to shreds!
Could it be...
-An aortic dissection?
Excuse me! Over here!
My husband will die at this rate!
Oh no!
Where does it hurt, sir?
He says that it's his stomach!
He was defecating blood and everything!
I'm going to die!
Oh, ow!
Geez!
Oh, this is the patient who refused
treatment before and discharged himself.
Discharged himself?
He was completely drunk before.
His BP is 90/60, with 130 bpm.
You said that he had bloody stools?
Yes, he went to the bathroom
because his stomach hurt,
and didn't come out for a long time.
And when I went in, his face was
pale and he couldn't move!
And when I stood him up,
in the toilet, there was...
...tons of blood!
Geez, Geez!
How could he do this to himself?
What are we going to do now?
Oh, my stomach!
His wall motions are okay,
but I can't see his aorta root very well.
Oh, it is an aorta dissection.
It is?
Yes, it is. Right here.
I can't see his abdominal aorta.
It seems like a Stanford type A.
How are you feeling?
I feel good.
Great, even.
And I think that it's become
easier for me to breathe, too.
But...
...when are you planning to
take all of these...
...annoying tubes off me?
You sure are impatient, Mr Chairman.
I'll get all of these things and the chest
tube out of you within two days.
Good work.
Thanks.
No, I should be the one thanking you.
We almost got this hospital
shut down because of you.
What?
Really?
I guess I really am a big shot, after all!
Geez.
The ER staff are asking me to come down.
Sure, sure. Go on now.
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
We have three patients who
need emergency surgery.
Three? Really?
One patient has
an abdomen-penetrating injury.
The glass is lodged in there
and there's internal damage,
but he isn't bleeding much.
I think that the patient with
the aortic dissection takes priority, sir.
We have a patient with
an aortic dissection?
What about the CT scan?
We just got it.
It's a type A aortic dissection.
What about his BP?
Initially, it was 160/100
on his right side,
and 100/60 on his left side.
But it has fallen to
120/80 on his right side.
Did you do an echocardiogram?
Yes.
Any AVR?
A bit, but it's not severe.
What about the last patient?
His CT scan is being uploaded right now.
But he has ischemic colitis.
Ischemic colitis?
The CT scan for the patient
with ischemic colitis is now up.
Geez, what a headache...
I even see pneumatosis intestinalis here.
Geez, we'll have to cut this out.
Yes, it does appear that way.
Geez, what a complicated situation.
What should we do?
We can't even transfer at least one of
them to a different hospital, either.
Doctor.
Let's take care of
the aortic dissection first...
It'll take a bit of time to prepare for
that surgery, even if we start now.
I think we should take care of
the patient with ischemic colitis first.
But the patient with
the dissection is the most critical.
He's the one who came in first, too.
If we're going by the order
in which they came,
the abdominal patient should be first.
But the patient with the dissection
needs care the most right now!
Am I wrong?
Why are you so fixated on
the dissection patient,
when you're a general surgeon?
What's wrong with you?
Let me know if you need anything else.
Yes, thank you.
I have a question.
Yes?
Your son wreaked some havoc at
Geosan Hospital's ER 14 years ago, right?
Who are you?
Who are you that you're suddenly asking
me about something from 14 years ago?
Well, I'm trying to collect some
information about someone.
Here you are.
REPORTER OH SUNG-JAE
But there are some pieces of
the puzzle that don't quite seem to fit.
I've suffered quite a bit
while going around...
...and collecting more information.
I know that your late husband died
in the ER at Geosan University Hospital...
...within an hour of arriving there.
That was due to an issue
with his aorta, correct?
How long will it take for us to
prepare for surgery, Yoon Seo-Jung?
About 30 minutes in total.
Okay.
Then maintain that dissection
patient's condition until then.
Have the colitis patient treated first,
and move him to the OR.
Yes, Doctor.
Doctor!
You're a general surgeon, Kang Dong-joo.
Just focus on the patient
whose fate lies in your hands.
Yoon Seo-Jung and I will take care of
the cardiothoracic patient.
Is this how you lost him last time, too?
On that day...
...a VIP patient was prioritized
before my father,
who'd come in before him.
And I heard that the surgeon
who did that was you, Doctor.
There's no need to be so nervous.
What I'm curious about is the bill
for the damage that was caused then.
I heard that the damages cost
about 200,000 dollars in total.
So who helped you repay
all that back then?
Can you tell me who it was?
Can you tell me, Doctor?
Why...
...did you push back my
father's surgery back then?
Kang Dong-joo...
Please tell me the reason.
Who was it?
Why can't you answer me?
I asked you why you pushed back
my father's surgery back then.
Why?
Do you know what the easiest thing is?
Destroying relationships.
All you need to tell them is,
"You're being deceived."
Yes, I remember perfectly.
I made the decision about that surgery.
He blamed the incident from 14 years ago
on Bu Yong-joo alone and now,
you can't find that name anywhere.
What do you mean you're
going to fight the hospital?
Do you think you can win this fight?
Why?
Are you nervous?
Romantic Doctor, Teacher Kim