EPISODE 9
What brings you here?
I heard that you were being interrogated.
I'm sure that it hasn't ended yet.
How dare you try to do the chairman's
surgery in your lowly position?
Look at you...
Looks like you'll lose another precious
disciple because of your stubbornness.
Geez...
Why, you little brat...
Doctor!
You have a guest.
A guest?
Teacher Kim!
I'm here.
I heard you told me to admit
myself to the hospital.
I contacted the chairman with the
news just as you told me to, sir.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up and escort me to my room.
Who told you to do something
stupid like this?
I'm sorry, Mr Chairman.
I think that there's been a mistake here.
We're not ready to accommodate
you here yet.
What?
Dr Kim...
You've come such a long way.
I'm sorry to have to send you
back like this.
We'll admit you as soon as we're ready.
What are you doing right now?
Didn't I tell you that you're suspended?
Suspended?
Hey... hey.
I cannot allow you to treat any patients
until we're done with our investigation.
And if you disobey us, you could
suffer an even worse punishment.
Who the heck are you brats?
What do you mean, he's suspended?
Says whom?
Let me explain, Mr Chairman.
What happened is...
Look here, Teacher Kim.
You explain this.
Tell me what's going on here, exactly.
And who are they?
The hospital is under investigation
right now, Mr Chairman.
Hey, hey, hey, Kang Dong-joo!
We have no idea why the main
hospital sent investigators down here
to us and we have no idea why
they're putting pressure on us, either.
Hey. Be quiet.
Why should I be quiet?
We're the ones being treated unfairly
when we didn't do anything wrong.
Kang Dong-joo!
Sir...
You're the Chairman of the Geosan
University Hospital Foundation, correct?
Could I possibly complain about the
main hospital pressuring
Doldam Hospital like this for no reason?
Manager Joo.
Yes, Mr Chairman?
Call Director Do, now.
Mr Chairman...
Tell him to come down here now and
explain this situation to me in person.
Right now!
Yes, sir.
Tell me what I did wrong.
Why did you call the chairman here?
I couldn't just sit and watch while
Seo-jung was being treated unfairly.
And I figured that we needed someone
to resolve this situation for us.
Do you really think that Chairman
Shin will be the one to resolve this?
To be honest, the only one who can
pressure Director Do is the chairman.
Furthermore, Chairman Shin is
on your side.
If I'd known that you were such
an idiot before...
But you know, you really are ignorant
to the ways of this world, aren't you?
You're really naive, huh?
What?
Chairman Shin has summoned me?
Yes, but...
You needn't put yourself through
the trouble, sir.
I'll just watch over the situation
and do as I deem fit, sir.
No, there's no need.
Pardon?
What do you mean by that, sir?
Our opponents just gave us a light
jab to see how we'd respond but
you took that as an opportunity,
and thus escalated the situation.
I was actually wondering how that
old man would find out about this.
Good.
They've set the stage for us themselves.
All I have to do now is go and
report the facts to him.
Well, this might actually end up
being a good thing for you.
You'll score some points with
Director Do, at the very least.
Even though Yoon Seo-jung is screwed...
Aren't you being a bit too harsh, sir?
What do you mean, she's screwed?
You have no idea what kind of
person Director Do really is, do you?
He'd be willing to do anything and
everything to get what he wants.
And Chairman Shin is someone
who made a guy like him the
hospital's director and sits idly by
while reaping the benefits from that.
He's on my side? Give me a break.
He doesn't need me.
He needs my operation.
That's all he cares about!
You fool.
We received word that Director
Do Yoon-wan is on his way here.
What are you planning to do?
I'll just have to bear it.
And if worst comes to worst,
I'll let them do what they want.
Well, there's not exactly anything
that I can do for you...
But have this when your blood
sugar gets low.
How did you come to know Bu Yong-joo?
Were you introduced to him
by someone, or...
He saved me. Twice.
Can you be a bit more specific?
One time, he saved me while I was
passed out in the mountains.
And one time, he treated my wrist
when it had almost lost functionality.
That's how he saved me twice.
Wait, no.
He saved me one other time, too.
I survived this time around
because of him, too.
So he's saved me three times now, then.
Do you still have random moments
in which you feel like you wish to die?
I'm asking you if you still get sudden
urges to commit suicide.
An age in which people ignore
others' pain.
People who don't care about others'
pain as long as they can get what
they want.
People who don't care about such
things, as long as they can maintain
authority, and...
I asked you if you still have any
suicidal urges.
It's all your fault.
It's all because of you that I died.
People who can't even get a good
look at the nature of their own pain.
I'm sorry.
Because all of them justify themselves,
saying that they didn't have time to
worry for others when they had
their own situation to deal with.
EPISODE 9
The Limits of Goodness
It's bad enough that those inspectors
barged in here so early in the morning
but now the Chairman of the Foundation
and Director Do are involved, too.
What in the world is going on?
Maybe that Chairman Shin guy
called Director Do to yell at him?
I have no idea.
We even heard that Teacher Kim
isn't allowed to work for the time being.
I heard that this all happened
because of Dr Yoon Seo-jung.
Return to your positions and get
back to work!
Don't make things worse
when the situation is already bad.
-Got it?
-Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry.
All you need to do is act as you
did before, as if nothing happened.
You know that, right?
Why do you keep doing these
unnecessary things?
I told you to send equipment here,
not some darned inspectors.
Please don't misunderstand my
intentions, Mr Chairman.
I've even sent important people from
the main hospital down here to obey you.
However...
However, what?
I heard that things at this hospital are
a bit messier than we'd realized.
Go on.
They must have managed this place
so poorly that a person broke into the
OR and held someone hostage with
a sickle.
That's not all.
They even left that criminal alone with
a patient who had been operated on.
And because Teacher Kim was the
one to handle the situation,
nobody was hurt.
And they performed an expensive
treatment on a patient who cannot
pay for it.
Saving the patient is our priority.
The hospital bill can be taken care
of after that, Director Do!
And how are you going to explain
the fact that the doctor who ordered
the treatment has PTSD?
PT what? What's that?
It refers to post-traumatic stress
disorder, sir.
Dr Yoon Seo-jung made a full
recovery two years ago.
I heard that there was a drug overdose
incident involving her recently.
And Director Yeo and Bu Yong-joo
were both aware of that.
Yet, they were keeping it hidden.
As such, these two have been
negligent of their duty.
Stop beating around the bush
and get to the point.
What is it that you truly wish to say?
I can't just sit by and watch as
these abnormalities occur at this
poor excuse of a hospital.
That's what I truly wish to say.
You mustn't entrust such an important
thing as your surgery to this sorry
excuse of a hospital, Mr Chairman.
Please reconsider entrusting your
surgery to Bu Yong-joo, sir.
So that's what it is.
You caused an uproar just to stop
Teacher Kim from performing the surgery?
Watch your words, Director Yeo!
Oh, whatever.
That's enough.
Mr Chairman.
This is my surgery, and I've already
made up my mind regarding this.
So stop arguing about it, already.
I'll have things proceed as originally
planned, so just be aware of that.
And let's end things here by firing
that doctor who caused all this trouble.
Now stop causing such a ruckus
at this hospital.
We can't, Mr Chairman!
Dr Yoon Seo-jung is...
Let's just end things there.
Okay, Director Yeo?
Geez....
You really don't get what's going on
here, do you, Mr Chairman?
What did you just say?
Hey.
The one Director Do really wants
to fire is me.
That's what he really wants.
Isn't that right, Director Do?
At the very least, you must take
responsibility for letting a PTSD
patient treat people.
Oh, you got the neuropsychiatrist's
clinical notes already?
PTSD, huh?
Or did you already decide the results
of her evaluation from the start and just
have her interviewed as a formality?
You won't be able to avoid shouldering
your part of the blame, either.
The duty of ER doctors is to save
dying people, no matter what it takes.
Asking them why they used an
expensive treatment on a patient is
the same thing as asking why someone
falling from a plane used a parachute.
So?
Do you even know how much the
hospital will suffer in losses?
Stop giving a doctor lessons in
business administration.
You can't get by nowadays by
merely being a skilled doctor.
A doctor can only survive if his
hospital does.
Wow, you say these things and yet
you call yourself a hospital director?
No, the order is all messed up there.
The patient needs to survive for
the hospital to survive.
Those are the basic principles of
being a doctor!
Oh, really?
I didn't realize that you valued
fundamentals and principles so much.
Fine, then. Let's do things that way.
We'll maintain our hospital's principles
and continue with the investigation.
And we'll issue proper punishments
for employing a doctor with PTSD
after the official diagnosis comes out,
as per our principles.
Look here, Director Do.
As the one in charge of Geosan Hospital
and in an attempt to rectify this wrong
I'll do what I must to defend our
principles until the very end,
Mr Chairman.
Have you finished your conversation,
Director?
Make sure you get them good this time.
No matter how long this may take.
Yes, sir.
What is it that you wanted to say?
I'm sorry for continuing to
disappoint you.
The reason I became a doctor was
because I wanted to be acknowledged
by you, above all else.
Because you saw potential in me and
made me want to become a doctor.
And yet, you went ahead and
back-stabbed me instead.
Just let him have this one, Teacher Kim.
I understand that you
treasure your disciple
but you can't have this
hospital shut down just because of her.
What should we do?
I really don't see a way out of this
one, Teacher Kim.
Why did it have to be Bu Yong-joo,
of all people?
Why were you hiding behind
someone like him, of all people?
There was an incident.
And he helped me through that.
And did he tell you to hide the
fact that you have PTSD?
I received treatment for 3 years
and thought I made a full recovery.
I'm asking you what the heck
he told you to do!
Teacher Kim didn't do anything wrong.
It's all my fault that the situation
got this out of hand.
It's because I'm lacking and incompetent.
So... if someone needs to take
responsibility, I'll do it.
I...will quit working here.
That's too bad.
At the very least, I thought of you
as my own daughter.
I guess you never saw me as
a parent, though.
If you had really needed help, you
should've come and sought me out.
Director.
Regarding Doldam Hospital,
I'm going to go by the book
to resolve this.
And as for you...
I don't know you anymore.
Are you looking for something, sir?
Do you want me to help you?
No, it's fine.
Um... you haven't seen Seo-jung,
have you?
Seo-jung?
I haven't seen her since she
dropped by the ER a little while ago.
Oh... really?
All right.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Do you want me to call you if I do
end up seeing her?
Could you?
Thank you.
Excuse me, have you seen
Dr Yoon Seo-jung?
No, I haven't.
Oh, really?
Has his condition improved at all,
Doctor?
Not yet, we'll have to keep
monitoring his progress for now.
How much longer does he have
to remain like this?
It almost feels like I'm clinging to
false hope.
The fees for this treatment and for
the ICU are overwhelming enough.
I feel like we'll only end up being
a burden to our kids.
I'm sure that things must be hard,
but please don't give up until the end.
And continue talking to the patient
and telling him pleasant things.
Am I really doing the right thing
right now?
Did Dr Yoon Seo-jung come by
here, by any chance?
It seemed that she stopped by
the ICU for a bit.
I'm not sure if she's still there, though.
I see.
Are we ever making the right decision
in front of our patients while they
waver between life and death?
Yoon Seo-jung!
What brings you here?
Am I someone who is perfectly
prepared to take responsibility for
someone's life?
What do you mean, you don't see
Yoon Seo-jung around anywhere?
We looked everywhere for her
today, but we can't find her anywhere.
She won't pick up her phone, either.
I think she heard about you being
suspended from duty back in the ER.
-Oh, Teacher Kim.
-Yeah?
Yoon Seo-jung stopped by my
restaurant not too long ago and
wanted me to give you this.
Letter of Resignation
A letter of resignation?
When did she give this to you?
About 10 minutes ago.
TEACHER KIM
Where are you headed?
She's not picking up?
Of course she wouldn't.
If she even wrote a letter of resignation
she's really made up her mind about this.
Go and get her back here.
How would he know where to look?
Regardless of that, we have to
start searching first.
But...bring her back by the end of today.
If you can't bring her back by
the end of today,
I really will accept this letter.
You got that?
Oh, Dr Kang Dong-joo!
Good thing I ran into you.
Your car just got here, so...
That's great.
Well, actually...
I'm busy right now. Let's talk later!
That's... a new car.
We're here.
Where are you planning to go?
I don't know.
I did come all the way out here,
but I feel a bit lost now.
Maybe I should take this chance
and go to Seoul?
Or maybe I should go to the East Sea
and enjoy the Oceanside?
You have nowhere else to go?
No, I don't.
And there's nobody for you to meet
up with?
No, no one.
What a hard life you have!
I know, right?
It seems bad from the surface,
but it's actually a lot worse than
you'd think.
Can you not say things like that
so casually?
That makes you look so insensitive.
Isn't it better to seem that way
than to seem pitiful?
Well, if you're going to Seoul,
I'll drive you.
Aren't you going to the hospital?
I'm taking my monthly day off.
Your monthly day off?
His monthly day off?
Dr Do In-bum is taking the day off?
Yes, that's what he said.
Then call Kang Dong-joo and tell
him to take over.
Dr Kang was on duty last night
so he's not working today.
Call Teacher Kim, then!
Did you forget?
Teacher Kim was ordered to be
off duty from today.
Wait, then I'm the only general
surgeon at this hospital now?
Yes.
Looks like things ended up this
way somehow.
Dr Jung! Please come here.
Geez, it hurts!
Wait just a bit, ma'am.
Doctor, over here, too!
The caller you are trying to reach
is unavailable...
Seo-jung?
Hey, how would I know?
I just saw her for the first time in
five years!
Hey, Dr Jung!
Are you done treating the patient
with the right lower quadrant pain?
Hey, I'm busy with a patient.
Talk to you later!
I'll check right now!
JERK KANG
Do In-bum. It's me, Kang Dong-joo.
Go ahead.
What do you want?
You said that you knew Seo-jung
from before, right?
I have to find her right now.
Do you know where she might have gone?
She's next to me right now.
You're on speakerphone.
Say what you need to say.
Where are you right now?
We're on our way to Seoul.
Turn your car around right now and
come back to the hospital.
That's going to be a bit difficult.
I'm already on the highway.
Are you listening?
I know it's hard for you right now.
I know that, but... come on.
A letter of resignation?
You wrote a letter of resignation?
Turn the car around right now.
Come back. Dr Yoon!
Hey, why did you tell him that
I was with you?
Well, you didn't tell me not to.
And why did you tell him that
we're heading to Seoul?
Well, he asked me where I was.
Why did you write a letter
of resignation?
None of your business.
Just drive properly.
Wow, you sure are coming
on strong, Sister.
I told you, I'm not your sister!
Seoul?
Where in Seoul?
I don't know the details.
I'm just following them there for now.
Hey, aren't you a bit too tight on
time to drive to and from Seoul?
But still, I have to do as much as I can.
All right, then.
But you know, things are kind of
crazy back here, too.
We all forgot because of Director Do,
but today is Friday.
What are you doing?
I told you to bring a suture set and
lidocaine here!
It's been barely 10 seconds since
you asked me to do that.
Ugh, seriously.
I'm not someone to be treating
people like this!
You should take off your necktie.
You concern yourself with doctors'
neckties now, too?
Nurse Park!
Whoa, whoa!
Are you okay?
Please lie down.
Do you think that it may be
something you ate, ma'am?
I had cold rice and soup this morning.
But I guess I ate it really fast.
My insides are killing me.
And you didn't have any diarrhea?
My stomach is rumbling,
but I haven't had diarrhea yet.
I just vomited a couple of times.
Are you feeling pain anywhere else?
My chest hurts a little.
It may be due to esophageal
damage from vomiting a lot.
It seems to be just stomach pain for
now, so we'll give you an injection.
Give this patient some metoclopramide
via IV, and hydrate her.
Yes, sir.
It's okay. I can do it.
I'll get her cleaned up.
You hurry and give her the injection.
Thank you, Ms Yeon-hwa.
What are you doing?
Oh, I thought there was something
on her neck.
We have an emergency patient
who was in a traffic accident!
She's bleeding from her right calf,
and her BP is 90/60.
And it's falling quickly!
Darn it, I'm going to go crazy!
Yes, this is Doldam Hospital's ER.
Yes. Yes, I understand.
A person who attempted suicide
will be here in 5 minutes.
They jumped off the Yeong-gye Bridge.
What?
Ms Woo Yeon-hwa?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
You're not working today?
Well, the folks from the main hospital
told me not to.
You do know that today is Friday, right?
We have an ER specialist from the
main hospital here now, too.
And even the chief of the surgical
department is down here now.
So why are you so worried?
Those people are doctors, too.
It's a patient who attempted suicide!
He fell off a bridge!
Doctor!
Please come over here!
You call yourself a board-certified
ER doctor?
Do your job properly!
Oh, yes.
Do you think that Dr Yoon Seo-jung
will come back?
Well, I did what was necessary though...
I'm so happy!
Don't you feel an endorphin rush
just from looking at this?
Are you serious?
You're eating pizza with a fork and knife?
Come on, you're being rude to the pizza!
You're supposed to hold pizza in
your hand, like this.
And give it a big old bite!
Got it?
You're a mama's boy, aren't you?
You've never just rolled in the dirt to
have a good time or disobeyed your
parents, have you?
My gosh, "disobedience"? What's that?
Is it something you can eat?
Were you always this chatty?
Me?
No.
I tend to be more quiet and stoic.
Who's the one who's been talking
all by herself for all this time, then?
Well, that's because you chose not
to say anything.
I didn't want there to be an awkward
silence.
I'm just being considerate to you,
to help you avoid feeling awkward.
Are you sure it's not because you
feel uneasy?
Um, why would I feel uneasy?
Aren't you worried, now that you've
left after writing a resignation letter?
And I bet that you're concerned that
Kang Dong-joo called, too.
And the fact that you're here with
me now concerns you a bit too, right?
And you're just saying anything that
comes to mind so I don't find out.
Whatever. Let's eat.
Yeah, I'm worried to death.
I couldn't even say a proper farewell
to those people, who were like family
to me and I feel so bad about running
off after just leaving a letter behind
that I feel like I'll die.
Why did I do that?
I should've been more persistent
and begged him to spare me.
Why did I go and write that letter
of resignation?
I have nowhere to go but Doldam Hospital.
I... really have nowhere else to
go but there.
So why did you get scared and run off?
Nothing has been decided yet.
It's not like that psychiatrist's
report has been released yet.
And that patient undergoing TTM
hasn't died yet, either.
Am I wrong?
DIRECTOR'S SON
JERK KANG
Hello?
Where are you?
Are you still with Dr Yoon?
Give the phone to Dr Yoon.
Hurry up and give the phone to her!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
What?
She ran off while we were eating.
She said she suddenly remembered
something that she had to do.
GEOSAN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Hello, Doctor.
What brings you all the way here?
I came here because of the question
I couldn't answer for you before.
You're a bit too late for that.
I just sent my report to the Director.
I've never had that though.
I've never once thought that
I wanted to die.
Not when my mom died.
Not when I got into the accident
with Dr Moon.
I...wanted to live,
even through all that.
That's why I was so miserable.
Because my desire to live was
stronger than the guilt I felt for being
the only one to have survived.
Because, despite all that,
I wanted to live.
And I felt so bad about feeling this way.
Dr Yoon Seo-jung, why did you
become a doctor?
Because I thought that, if I became
a doctor...
I'd be able to have my existence
acknowledged by someone.
Did you ever have a moment in which
you wanted to quit being a doctor?
Every single time...
I had to make a decision for the
sake of the patient.
I see.
Could you give this to Teacher Kim
at Doldam Hospital?
It's my report regarding your
mental health evaluation.
I thought it'd be good for your
hospital to have a copy, too.
Goodbye, then.
This patient's outburst was due to
stress from this past year.
She does not exhibit the DSM5
defined symptoms related to PTSD.
Furthermore, there is no need for
her to be supervised closely.
This little brat...!
I've handed my report over to
Dr Yoon myself.
Fortunately, I was able to hear the
answer that I wanted to hear from her.
I almost did something quite
immoral as a doctor.
Is Hyun-ji doing well?
You still remember my child's name?
Hey, of course I do.
She was the youngest patient that
I'd ever had.
You know, about Doldam Hospital...
I think I understand why you're
remaining there.
Please do a proper evaluation of her.
This is a life-and-death issue for
Seo-jung, as a doctor.
Please give her a proper evaluation,
despite what Director Do said.
Dr Yoon is someone we must have
at Doldam Hospital's ER.
Please don't screw her over with
a false evaluation.
Here.
These are thank-you-letters that
Dr Yoon's patients have given her.
I thought you may want to refer to
them as you write your evaluation.
We'll entrust our Dr Yoon to you,
then, sir.
If you write anything strange,
we'll file an appeal against you.
Please don't do something to make you
ashamed to face her, doctor to doctor.
Well, they're all such strong willed
people.
Don't lose to Director Do this time.
I'll be going, then.
Thank you.
How did you know I'd be here?
I just received word, so I rushed here.
What about you?
Did you take care of everything you
needed to?
Yeah.
All right, then.
Let's head back now.
You're not coming?
Are you crying?
No!
It's just so cold out here.
You know how if you suddenly walk
into a bright or cold place...
You know how it is. You tear up.
It's just that, is all.
Oh man, it's so cold! Right?
Huh?
Is this the first snowfall of the season?
It seems that way.
It's pretty.
Yes, it is.
Your hands are cold.
I'll hold your hand just until it
warms up.
That's okay with you, right?
But you know...
Isn't today Friday?
Ugh, seriously!
Why did they bring me to the hospital?
Just let me die, already!
Darn it, I want to die!
Hey, how can you say that when
we barely brought you back?
Geez, I have lost my inspiration.
I want to draw something,
but I haven't been able to for
three years now!
If you can't help me draw again,
just leave me to die!
-Why?
-Hey.
Mr Go!
Please let go!
This is why I told you to take off
your necktie in the ER.
-Hey, Dr Jung!
-Yes, Chief?
You take care of him.
I can't do this anymore!
Sir!
Teacher Kim is in the ICU right now!
Why? What's he doing in there?
He's... just sitting there.
What should we do?
What do you mean?
He's just sitting.
What do you want me to do?
-Hey, Nurse Ji.
-Yes.
Can't you see what's going on here?
Don't you see how chaotic it is in
here right now?
Not a single person is helping me out.
Ma'am. Ma'am?
I'm going to die.
It seems that she has a lot of gas
trapped under her skin.
Miss. Miss, please...
What's the matter? You can't breathe?
Miss!
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor!
Miss.
Doctor. Doctor!
Ms Yeon-hwa.
Nurse Park.
Go and get Teacher Kim.
He should be in the ICU.
Go get him now.
Quickly.
The Seoul region, Gyeong-gi-do
Province, and in the mountains of
the Gang-won-do Province have
seen their first snowfall of the season.
The snow stopped after an hour or
two but there will be
a chilly breezestarting tonight...
I'm glad that there won't be
a heavy snowfall, at least.
Isn't that right, sir?
You can't be too sure.
Snowfall at night is the worst!
The roads just freeze over, like icicles!
Man, what's with this snow?
It's making it harder for us to work!
Let's just finish this up quickly and go.
Oh man, it's quite slippery!
Be careful.
Why is the road this slippery?
-The ER?
-Yes, Doctor.
There is a problem there.
I think you'll need to head there
for a bit.
This seems like subcutaneous emphysema.
And this young lady did this?
Yes, we believe so.
What were the doctors doing that
they missed this, huh?
All right.
Give this patient antibiotics first.
Call Chief Song and contact Dr Nam, too.
Tell him that we've scheduled
an emergency surgery.
Yes, sir.
Hey, you punk!
Keep it down!
I can't diagnose the other patients
properly because of you!
Oh... you're here, sir?
Just receive treatment quietly and
head home, all right?
Yes, sir.
What... what just happened?
This guy is a regular at our ER.
He says that he's a webtoon artist,
but I've never seen his work.
Oh man, what do I do?
Um, I think you'll need to disinfect
this spot here.
Get me a dset, please!
-Ms Woo Yeon-hwa.
-Yes?
Can you explain to me what
happened with that patient out there?
We should be there in 20 minutes.
I wonder what Teacher Kim will say.
Isn't it obvious?
He'll probably say, "You idiot."
"How are you going to be a doctor
when you're so weak like this?"
"You still call yourself a doctor
after doing this?"
"Wait, no, you're not.
You're just a helper!"
"How dare someone like you just
hand me a resignation letter?"
What are you doing?
Oh, that was bad, wasn't it?
Don't ever do that again, Yoon Seo-jung.
Don't disappear without
a word ever again.
Okay?
Look at you, messing with me
again, I am your senior.
Don't do it, okay?
Fine, whatever.
I'll let you off the hook just for today.
Huh?
You said that you were Chinese.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Are you a medical student?
Ms Yeon-hwa, we're not
trying to scold you.
We just want to know the truth.
You must answer our questions honestly.
Doctor, Chief Song won't
pick up our calls.
He won't pick up his cell,
and he's not at the hospital, either.
To the city. To the city, please.
I think he's left work.
Left work?
What is wrong with him?
He's well aware of the situation
at the hospital right now, too!
So how could he just leave?
All right. I'll take over for today.
Please prepare the patient for surgery.
Will you be all right, sir?
We're not in a situation to be
discussing that now.
Get her ready, please.
So you disobeyed us.
I definitely told you what would
happen if you ignored our command.
Nurse Park.
Get the patient to the OR, now.
And prepare her for surgery.
Yes, sir.
Stop right there!
Are you going to take responsibility if
something bad happens to the patient?
-Get out of the way!
-It seems that you're trying to wiggle
out of this by using the patient as
an excuse but I can't let you do that.
I told you to get the heck out of the
way, now!
And I told you that I won't!
Why, you little brat...
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. I'm not hurt.
What about you? You're not hurt?
Stay in the car.
I'm going to check what's going on.
What's the matter? What is it...
There's only one way to know if
a doctor is doing a proper job.
Through the way they
treat their patients.
That's the only way.
So is this the "painting" that you
were working on, Teacher Kim?
It's just a sketch for now.
What do you think about Bu Yong-joo?
You think he's a good person?
Or do you think that he's
a genius doctor?
Are all of those people going
together, too?
What do you think?
Want to team up with me?
I'll have to look into it starting now.