EPISODE 5
PAN RESTAURANT
Say that again, I dare you.
Master Fan, let's talk this over.
For my sake,
please let him go first.
The Li family?
They're nothing special.
With just a beckon,
they'd come running into my arms.
You…
drunk yourself silly.
This is Fuhui's husband in front of you.
What nonsense are you spouting?
Stop pretending.
Don't you know?
Those perfume sellers,
those so-called Jinnu and Yunu,
are all from the Li family!
Mr. Fan,
which sister-in-law of yours
might that be?
You're asking for it!
Master Fan!
Just hold your tongue.
You heard this bastard's words.
Don't stop me!
What's new?
Every time he drinks,
he spews such drivel.
Yesterday, it was Lady Zhang,
today, it's Lady Li.
Tomorrow, who knows?
Maybe someone from the palace.
Exactly.
He's clueless, rambling on like a fool.
He'll forget it all when he sobers up.
If you take him seriously,
you'll be the real joke.
Right.
Isn't that so?
In his drunken dreams,
forget the maidens of Bianjing,
even the moon goddess
and fairies of heaven aren't spared.
It's just his lips flapping.
Talking nonsense at will.
Liang Junqing, stop dreaming.
What did you say?
I'm telling you the truth…
Clearly drunk!
Hurry and get him back.
Take him away!
Apologies, everyone.
My deepest apologies.
Excuse me.
Everyone.
Everyone!
A drunken guest caused a scene
and disturbed your peace.
- Deqing.
- Yes?
Two more dishes and a jar of Jade Wine
for every table.
Many thanks, Master Chai.
- Come with me.
- Master Chai, you're too kind.
If not for you stopping me,
I'd smash his head into a pulp!
He brought his insults right to me!
If I didn't stop you,
you'd brawl in Pan Restaurant
and make it known to all.
After that, the Li daughters
would even be shamed
just stepping out the door.
They're delicate girls.
How could they bear such disgrace?
Tomorrow night,
I'll get some men
to teach that filthy dog a lesson.
If you hit him today
and he's harmed tomorrow,
wouldn't that make it clear to all
it was your doing?
I can't care about that!
A son-in-law is half a son.
The Li family's in trouble.
I can't stand by
or let people mock me
as a coward without guts.
Stop there!
His father and brothers are commoners,
but his uncle serves in the court.
The Liang family can't harm you directly.
But can they not go after the Li family?
Her family has just found some peace.
One cannot act on impulse alone.
If this won't do and that won't work,
must we just endure it?
Endure, but enduring
doesn't mean not avenging.
Go back first. Let me think about it.
Brother!
Get lost!
SIFU HOUSE
What are you doing?
I finally get it now.
Sir,
what can you achieve
by meddling in their matters?
You only get slapped or splashed.
And the water smells like plum blossoms.
Who knows what it's even for?
Why do you always have to speak?
You delivered all the wine today.
Don't pass it off to someone else.
Yes, yes.
I'm just trying to help you.
That Kangning is fierce.
Always up to no good.
Haode and Leshan are watching over her.
She's wildly scared and agitated.
In the end, it's all Chai's fault.
You're wrong.
Liang Junqing's the one to blame,
not Master Chai.
I've told you already.
Master Chai took the fall
for someone else.
He's been wronged.
He's in with bad people,
so it means he's not different.
Why lend the jade comb
to him of all people?
If we don't expose him now,
he'll keep calling everyone his brother.
Only because it didn't harm
the Chai girls.
Even if he's wronged,
he can't escape the blame
for poor judgment.
And that Pan Restaurant,
it's a den of vice.
Drunken men come and go every day.
It's either old lechers or young rakes.
- He's bound to face some retribution.
- You're wronging an innocent person.
In business,
one must deal with all sorts of people.
There's no telling who you'll meet.
He's not a sage with all-seeing eyes.
I don't want to hear his name again. I…
Just hearing his name makes me feel like
all the old grudges
are rushing to my heart.
I can't help but wish
I could kick him again!
Alright, I won't bring him up again.
Alright?
Shouhua, what should we do about Qiongnu?
Mother's furious.
She nearly came over.
I had to stop her.
This must not be made public.
That bastard won't dare
offend the other families,
but he's bold enough to bully us,
strangers in an unfamiliar land.
The Fan family is just a trading family,
not one to push too far.
I think we should deal with Qiongnu later.
Sir, take it easy.
You know where to send news.
Don't worry, sister, I know.
Go on.
Kangning.
Let's go.
Master Chai?
Kangning.
May I have a word with you?
Chunlai, you may leave.
You two, come with me.
I wonder if Master Chai is here
to settle the score for that slap.
Or…
Aren't you going to teach
Liang Junqing a lesson?
I'm here to lend you a hand.
I slapped you, yet you bear no grudge.
And you are willing to help me?
How strange.
He tricked me out of my jade comb
and accused me of indecency.
I can't forgive him for that.
Kangning, I am truly here to help you.
Don't miss this chance.
I wonder how Master Chai
plans to help me.
That depends on your sincerity.
There have been misunderstandings,
hence my offenses.
You are a noble man.
Please do not blame my rashness.
I apologize once more.
Kangning,
you're quite adaptable.
May I ask,
how would you take revenge?
Let him enjoy a few more days.
We'll deal with him at Chongyang.
- I'll pick this one.
- Here you are.
- Do you have any in white?
- Alright.
- So fragrant! Here you are.
- Here's the money.
This one looks nice too.
Yes.
Come see the Chongyang cake,
fresh from the oven!
Put them out.
Place them there. This one's good.
Alright, go quickly!
Come see the Chongyang cakes,
fresh from the oven!
Twenty coins per box.
Just out of the oven.
Madam Li.
Your Chongyang cakes,
aren't they just sugar and flour?
Why are they pricier than others?
That's right.
But my cakes come with meaning!
This box, "All Things Well",
it's blessed
by the Lion-Taming King of Bodhisattvas.
If a scholar buys it,
Manjushri will grant wisdom.
It'll boost talent
and bring honor to their ancestors.
But the uncle I'm gifting it to
is an official.
Don't you have something else?
Of course, we do! Come!
Look at this one.
See the little deer?
"Eat the Deer,
Feast on Fortune."
Officials who take it home
will rise step by step.
Your second uncle,
isn't he the oil merchant Master Wang?
- Yes!
- Then, take this one.
Prosperity Cake.
It ensures luck and wealth,
I promise!
I'll take one!
I want one too!
Just a cake
with deer and elephants
and endless meanings!
Kangning, typically you.
We've been at this for seven days.
Shouhua,
shouldn't you let us out for a break?
The family business is booming
and you just want to play.
Look at Fuhui.
She's been helping all morning.
Didn't I come early too?
Shouhua, please let us out!
Even the lion is saying,
"Let me out! Let me play!"
Shouhua, look.
This one's done too.
I heard of a lion meeting
at Kaibao Temple.
I'd like to hear the master's sermon.
May I go?
Shouhua?
Please let me go.
Please.
Kids will be kids, always wanting to play.
Let them go.
But…
no causing trouble.
I never cause trouble!
You? Never?
Go on, go on.
- But be careful!
- Let's go!
- Hurry up!
- Wait for me!
- Be back early!
- Coming. Wait for me!
Take it slow.
Do you still remember,
during the Chongyang Festival that year,
Haode went to the temple with Mother?
She met a handsome young monk
and secretly followed him.
Thankfully, someone noticed
and brought her back.
They said he came from
a long line of officials,
sent there fearing he'd die young.
So, they had him raised as a monk.
Qiongnu, do you remember
which family it was?
I just can't recall.
Yes.
I seem to remember that.
But I can't recall, either.
She was only seven that year
and already fancied a handsome man!
Didn't you say Master Chai was here?
That's what the servant said.
Maybe he's not here yet.
Give me two bowls.
Coming right up.
METAL AND STONE ANTIQUES
This golden Mahoraga is so cute!
It's perfect for Fuhui.
Sharp choice, young lady.
The others are clay,
but this one's gold.
A fine symbol of blessings and fertility.
It's just too pricey.
Left unsold after the Qixi Festival.
So, I thought I'd bring it out
to try and make some money.
Would you like
to try your luck, young lady?
- How?
- Five coins a turn.
Get all five coins to land face up
and the golden Mahoraga
is yours.
I'm good at this. Let's try!
Here we go.
Young lady, you…
Go ahead.
All coins are face up!
The golden Mahoraga is ours now.
Wait, wait!
A bet's a bet.
What's wrong with you?
It's just gold-plated
and you can't even let it go.
Believe me,
I'll flip your stall over.
I wouldn't dare!
It's just that
this Mahoraga
was already won by a young man.
He said he'd come back for it later.
I thought
I could get a few more bets in.
How can you gamble the same thing twice?
Shameless!
No, no, please!
I won it first.
It's mine!
Kangning, don't act on impulse.
Don't forget why we're here today.
Go ahead.
Follow me.
This…
I've long heard of your beauty and wit.
But I think
you're good at everything,
except for one thing.
After crossing paths a few times, I think,
aside from being shrewd and wealthy,
you lack in almost everything else.
I wonder what's the purpose
of this invitation?
Kangning, take a look.
Him?
Master Chai, what does this mean?
Don't rush.
You'll know by tonight.
Don't trick me, Master.
Chunlai, go home and inform them.
Say I've gone to attend the sermon.
Don't let Mother worry.
Got it.
I'll be back soon. Don't go anywhere!
- Great!
Wonderful!
Excellent!
Kangning,
these shrimp dumplings are delicious!
- Take them.
- The market's crowded.
We must come here more often.
Master Chai, it's already dark.
How long are we waiting?
So eager for revenge?
If not for someone's vanity
and disregard for propriety,
things wouldn't have come to this.
And yet you defend her.
So foolish.
Seeking fortune and status
is human nature.
A girl with no family support or dowry
just wants someone to rely on.
How is that unforgivable?
Why blame her instead of the culprit?
If it were your own sister,
could you still say that?
Fine, I was wrong.
If you leave now,
today will have been wasted.
The righteous Kangning indeed.
But your stubborn pride will never change.
One day, it'll cost you dearly.
He's here.
Let's go! Come on!
- Kangning.
Please.
What, think I'd trick you?
Do visit again!
Take care!
Didn't you say you have two sisters?
Both beauties.
Please bring them out!
I'd like to pay my respects.
Why is this room so dim?
I'll have someone light a lamp.
Gosh.
- Who's there?
- Bitch!
I've heard the rumors
that you've been unfaithful.
- Caught you red-handed! Tie them up!
- Let me go!
Sir!
A brute climbed in
to commit a vile act!
I'm innocent!
Let me go!
Spare me!
Quit pretending!
I'll deal with him first,
then you.
Do it!
Let me go!
Enough.
This?
Stop playing dead!
Keep going!
Then strip him
and dump him in the mass grave.
Hit him!
- He won't…?
- Don't worry.
They're trained. They know his limit.
Break his leg,
so he won't harm others again.
It won't kill him.
Aren't you afraid he'll come after you?
He attacked a married woman
and ruined her name.
Caught in the act, beaten by the wronged.
Even if he takes it to court,
he won't dare speak of it.
Besides,
by dawn, we're gone. Who will he find?
It's just bad luck for him.
He ran into the wrong crowd.
This honey trap feels familiar.
I just wanted to remind someone.
Kangning,
act cleanly and thoroughly.
Leave no loose ends.
It's for you.
Really?
We attended the sermon
and wandered around the market.
We came back empty-handed.
This is raising suspicion.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Here, have some.
You've lost weight.
And you don't go out much lately.
- Qiongnu, you--
- Shouhua.
I'm fine now.
Don't worry about me.
She's loved roasted goose since little.
Let's visit the night market tonight.
That five-flavor almond goose
from Granny Ma.
It's so delicious.
One bite
and all your troubles will vanish.
I heard that Liang
offended some lady
and got his leg broken.
Afraid of more trouble,
he fled to his hometown
Shouzhou overnight.
We won't see him again.
What are you sewing?
That looks fun. Give it to me!
It's for Fuhui.
Oh? Let me see.
Look at you,
clinging to your little treasure.
I'll get her something better next time.
This…
A golden Mahoraga.
I can't accept this.
Next time, just bring a clay one.
Feeling better?
Kangning said we're going
to the night market tonight.
Sounds great. Let's go together.
I heard from my husband
that there's been some thieves
in the city.
They target
wealthy children and young women
in the chaos.
Last month, they took the only daughter
of Master Jiang from the east side.
The authorities have posted notices,
but she's still missing.
You believe that?
He's just scaring you.
I'm on the streets every day
and never heard of such a thing.
Just rumors.
Let's go.
Shouhua, come with us.
I'm not going. You guys go ahead.
But to be safe,
have the Fan family
send a few guards along.
Please, come on!
Alright!
Haode, please! Let's go play!
Drink it while it's hot.
Slowly.
Master Chai, please wait.
No need to see me off.
Fire!
A fire at Cross Street!
What's going on? Look, it's a fire!
Fire's spreading!
Whose place is it this time?
Must've started in the kitchen.
Last time at Shouning Temple,
it was the stove catching the walls.
Look at those flames!
That area's packed with houses.
- Exactly.
- One house after another.
Half the city might go up in flames.
This is bad, really bad!
What are you standing here for?
Our house is at the end of the street!
Hurry and check on it!
- Mother's out traveling.
- Your big house is still there!
Your wealth is going
to be burnt in a flash.
Hurry! You're driving me mad!
- Deqing!
- Yes?
Bring everyone from the restaurant.
Get all the silver from the safe.
No.
It's not enough, not nearly enough!
I'll exchange more silver first.
We'll meet up later.
- Got it!
- Brother!
The fire's at Cross Street,
near your house!
Why are you leaving the city?
- Get ready!
- Yes!
You four, come with me!
You're going the wrong way!
Have you lost your head in the panic?
- What are you doing running off now?
- Move! Mount up!
Let go!
Your pancake, madam.
- Thank you.
- Let's have more fun next time.
- Smells great!
- Good idea!
Madam, have a taste.
- No, thank you.
- Tasty roasted goose.
Look, roasted goose! Let's go!
Hurry!
- Take a look, ladies.
- Let's go look.
- Not full yet?
- Tasty roasted goose!
No, I just want one!
You've already eaten so much.
No more.
Good and cheap!
- Fine, do what you want.
- Please.
- Just one more!
- Suit yourself.
Steamed buns for sale!
I'll buy it for you.
Which one do you want?
- Qiongnu, let's go.
- I’ll take this one.
Fine pearl necklaces!
I want one too.
These are South Sea pearls.
Each one is dazzling.
Look at this one.
This little rabbit suits you.
See if there's one you like.
- I like this one!
- I like this one too.
- Let me see that.
- Okay.
- Why not buy one?
- Here, madam.
- Sir.
- Pick your favorite!
Here, you can always get more.
Thank you, Fuhui!
What about mine?
It's all together.
Young lady, I have even finer ones.
Take a look.
I'll take what my sister picks.
Young lady, you have excellent taste.
My lady,
the cart is ready.
If we don't head back, Master will worry.
It's late. We should go home.
Let's come back another day, alright?
Alright.
Paid!
Let's go.
But I don't want to leave yet!
Come on.
Take care. Come again!
But I'm not done playing!
You're not done? None of us are!
Sister,
there are shadow puppets
and snake charmers over there!
- Let's just take a look!
- Another day.
- How about another day?
- Go. Go home first.
We're heading out first!
- Leshan!
- Great!
- Go with them and keep watching.
- Got it.
Come back early!
Let's go!
Fire!
A fire in the north!
Fire in the north! Clear the way!
Qiongnu, get in the cart!
Qiongnu!
Kangning!
Fuhui!
Stop!
- Fuhui!
- Kangning!
- Not good!
- Someone! We've been attacked!
- Go report this.
Got it!
- Fuhui!
- Kangning!
Careful. Someone's coming!
- Don't move!
- Stay still!
Quiet!
Brother.
You're the clever one.
The soldiers will handle the fire there.
Even if you go,
you'll just get in the way.
After this fire,
the north will need countless repairs.
I control most of the city's
construction supplies now.
This is the real way to profit.
A single house means nothing.
Later, take the goods to the warehouse.
I have a guest to meet.
Who?
Take less from the common folk.
Don't let them call you
a heartless rich man.
I'll make a fortune.
Not just from the nobles,
but by having someone
report the fire to the palace,
so His Majesty knows the damage,
and I'll have the taxes
on my materials waived.
Impressive.
Please, help me!
My sisters have been kidnapped!
The cart's not far.
We can still catch it!
Please, help me!
We have orders to head to the north.
We can't delay.
Go report it to the authorities.
- Please!
- Master Congyi, let's go!
Save them, please!
Kangning.
Someone, help me!
You're from the Li family?
Master Chai, Kangning…
She's been taken!
Please save her!
Fuhui…
She's on the cart too!
- What?
- Quick, where's the cart?
Over there! That way!
That's the one!
Deqing, take her back.
- Got it.
- Rest of you, follow me!
Sir, it's to the right.
Cousin.
Lives are at stake. Don't mess this up.
They've traveled far and wide with me,
faced countless bandits.
Their skills are decent.
No mistake. Let's go!
Hurry!
Stay here and watch them.
Got it.
Rest of you, keep this place secure.
Let's go.
Stay put!
Find somewhere to hide.
Cousin, they're all caught!
Spare us, sir! Spare us!
Mercy!
Bandit, where did you take my wife?
I only thought they looked lovely.
I wanted to offer them to my leader
or sell them to a wealthy lord,
but I never laid a finger on them.
Take her back.
- Please spare us!
- Yes.
Gag him.
Sir.
Seems to be a small band
taking shelter here.
Tie them up, hand them to the authorities.
We'll find their lair soon.
No rush.
Save my wife first and we'll talk later.
If your wife asks later
why you didn't guard her,
knowing there were bandits,
what will you say?
And if she asks
why you abandoned your ledger
to drink at Pan Restaurant
the moment she left,
what will your excuse be?
Instead of gratitude,
you'll get blamed.
If you want to live at her mercy forever,
then go ahead.
Kangning, listen to me.
If we can escape, it's a blessing.
If we can't,
don't throw your life away.
Do whatever they demand.
Gold and jewels mean nothing.
Even chastity is meaningless.
Our lives are what matter.
Only then can we return to Mother.
That's the wife I know.
If it comes to the worst,
I only want her alive.
No matter where she's sold,
I'll find her.
Fuhui is wise and resolute.
Not one to be swayed easily.
Are you still trying to scare her?
Of course, I am.
If she had obeyed,
she wouldn't be suffering like this.
An obedient wife is the best wife.
Then you'd better steel yourself.
If you regret halfway…
Don't worry, brother.
I swear, no regrets.
I've heard that a thousand times.
- Remember.
- Got it, brother.
I'll never tell, no matter what.
Come here.
Don't move!
Mr. Zhang, outside Guangli Gate,
offered 200 strings.
He wants a young and pretty one.
Follow my plan.
Send her tonight. No delays.
Great. Better we split it for drinks
than give it to the boss.
But 200 strings is too little.
This work risks our heads.
We should extort more from him.
Don't talk nonsense.
No drinking or sleeping tonight.
Keep your eyes open.
Watch this woman closely.
So we can explain to our superiors.
There's one more thing.
The boss hasn't picked yet.
Don't you dare touch her first.
Get up!
Move!
Make another sound
and I'll toss you down the cliff.
I haven't run.
I'm doing as told.
Why torment me?
I've been frail since I was young.
If I die on the way,
wouldn't your efforts be wasted?
Behave and listen.
Once the deal's done, we part ways.
I overheard in the bag.
How much are you selling me for?
That's right. Two hundred strings.
I can brew tea and light incense.
Even sold for thousands, it's fair.
But for just a few strings?
Isn't that an insult?
You're from nowhere.
Easy to explain, hard to hear.
Let me be honest.
I'm the third daughter of the Li family
from Sifu House on Pan Street.
Across from us is Master Chai,
the new owner of Pan Restaurant.
He's ruthless and shameless.
I despise him
for ruining my family's business.
So, I tricked him out of a fortune
and hid it somewhere safe.
I've kept it hidden ever since.
If you spare me,
I'll give you 380 strings
for my freedom.
Are you just stalling to escape?
Why would you think that?
I knew you'd doubt me.
That's why I didn't speak until now.
Master Chai is furious over his loss.
He even smashed his prized jade comb.
He's been seeking someone to repair it.
How could that be a trick?
And look around.
This place is deserted.
I could scream and no one would come.
How dare I lie to you?
A headless ghost would be my fate.
Then tell me where it's hidden.
I'll send someone to fetch it.
Come closer, I'll tell you.
Closer.
Kangning, it's me.
- You deserve this--
- Ruthless and shameless one.
Enough already?
Aren't you just toying with me,
you scoundrel?
So,
you can mess with me,
hit me, scold me,
but I can't tease you back?
When did you figure it out?
What kidnapper uses Four Harmonies?
- And Fuhui?
- Guarded safely by her husband.
He even asked me to keep it secret.
So he can play the hero later.
Come. Let's get you home.
Hold tight. We're heading back.
Here we are, right up ahead.
Okay.
Take care, sir.
Thanks for your patronage.
Hire from me again!
Safe delivery guaranteed.
Not good.
If someone sees me
walking with a man at night,
there'll be plenty of gossip.
Mr. Zhang, this job's not done yet.
We'll need another trip in a few days.
I'll count on you.
No problem.
Isn't that Master Chai?
The owner of Pan Restaurant, Master Chai?
I haven't greeted you in a while.
When free,
visit my shop sometime.
Been too busy lately.
I'll come by another day.
I'm rushing to send a maid for service.
Don't want to miss the hour
or ruin my mother's banquet.
I must go ahead. We'll talk another day.
Alright, Master Chai, take care.
A maid?
Kangning.
I didn't do this to tease you.
Not for any other reason, just because…
I wanted to spend more time with you.
I'll be going.
Hold on.
If your sisters return, all's well.
If not,
I'll act like you two never existed.
Mother!
I was wrong!
I'll never play around again,
Mother.
You're wrong, Mother.
Even if we were there,
we'd just be tied up too.
It's the bandits' fault, not ours.
Why blame us?
Mother's just angry.
If they don't return,
I'll give my life for theirs.
You still won't admit your fault?
- You're to blame!
- Mother!
I'm older than Leshan.
Don't punish her alone. I'll take half.
Mother.
They're already missing. Don't hit them.
What have I done to deserve this?
My two daughters.
How am I supposed to go on?
Madam, they're back!
They're back!
Mother!
- Kangning!
Kangning!
I'm home.
- Kangning!
- It's alright now.
Kangning!
I'm back.
Good. It's okay.
It's fine now. All fine.
Don't cry.
As long as you're back.
You scared me.
It's over now.
Quickly!
No!
Come here. Come!
Hit me once.
Hit me!
Hurry!
Harder!
Give me a good punch.
Good punch!
My lady, I've come to save you!
Careful!
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Are you alright, my lady?
Are you hurt?
Were you frightened?
My lady?
My lady.
Why did you come so late?
Don't be afraid, my lady.
It's all my fault. I came too late.
Don't be scared.
Subtitle translation by: Jiayi Xu