EPISODE 28
KAIFENG COURT PRISON
Mr. Huang.
Mr. Xue.
Bring the person up.
Last night, I wanted
to interrogate an important prisoner.
Kaifeng Court's Official Qiao Du
lied about a malaria outbreak in prison
to escape with the female prisoner.
I caught them on the spot.
The incident occurred suddenly.
Sorry for not informing you
in time, Lord Shen.
I hope you would not blame me
for overstepping my duties.
I dare not.
Qiao Du, what's going on?
Lord Shen asked you a question.
Why don't you answer?
Where are you taking this female prisoner?
Fang.
You tell me.
Yes.
It was Qiao Du who had someone
send me the drug,
teaching me to feign malaria
to escape from prison.
Drug? What drug?
Mr. Du.
These were all Mr. Qiao's order.
What's wrapped is Semen Cannabis.
After one takes it, they vomit
and have diarrhea, appearing delirious,
just like having malaria.
After the prison physician's diagnosis,
we wouldn't dare keep the patient.
According to regulation,
we must send the patient away.
- Where do you send her?
- To the infirmary.
To find a corpse with a similar appearance
to deceive everyone
that the patient has died.
I have also heard rumors in the past
that people often bribe prison officials
with large sums of money
to secretly release prisoners,
but report them as dead from illness.
I never would have thought that,
Lord Shen, under your jurisdiction,
such outrageous things would happen.
Shen Huizhao.
Qiao Du is your subordinate.
How do you explain this?
There is no need
for further interrogation.
I believe that Lady Fang
is wrongfully accused,
- so--
- Nonsense!
You have no relation to Fang.
Without someone's instigation,
how dare you take such a risk?
Things have come to this.
Yet you still attempt to use excuses
to hide the truth.
Mr. Xue.
You seem to imply something.
Fang attempted to escape the prison,
which is doubly guilty.
She should be sentenced to death
by dismemberment.
I'll give you one last chance.
- Tell us the truth.
- I…
Do you think Shen Huizhao
can help you escape?
Let me tell you the truth.
Tonight, that Lu Jiulang
died of serious injury,
and the Lu family
is busy preparing the funeral.
Shen Huizhao has committed false judgment
and intentional prisoner release.
He's in trouble himself.
Now, I'm the only one in the world
who can help you.
Say it.
- Say it.
- It's my cousin.
I have been engaged to my cousin
since childhood.
But due to mourning,
we missed the wedding date.
I didn't expect he'd called off
the engagement and marry another.
When I went to the Shen family,
they threatened me with their power,
seducing me to conduct adultery.
He feared that someone would expose him
and his reputation would get ruined,
so he forced me
to marry into the Lu family.
He told me to use the excuse of a wedding
in mourning period to escape the crime.
And it was my cousin who asked Qiao Du
to enter prison and save me.
Stop slandering against the official.
Mr. Huang, this woman is holding grudges
for the engagement being called off,
so she seeks revenge,
lying and framing the innocent.
Every word I say is true. I dare not lie.
I hope you can be lenient with me.
Shen Huizhao.
His Majesty holds you in great trust,
allowing you not to avoid cases related
to your relatives, to judge fairly.
Yet you are sanctimonious,
with unfaithful actions and words.
You first forced the girl
to conduct adultery.
Later, you covered up for your relatives
and committed the major crime of
releasing prisoners without authorization.
You committed a crime beyond forgiveness
and can't hold the position
as the Chief Official of Kaifeng Court.
Today, with Mr. Huang as witness,
you don't have a chance
to argue with that.
I must purge the imperial court
of treacherous scoundrels
and petition His Majesty
to severely punish you.
I have judged cases impartially
and never practiced favoritism.
I have no guilt towards
His Majesty, the imperial court,
or the world.
If you two believe what she said,
you are free to petition His Majesty.
I am willing to remove
my official rank and accept…
all interrogation.
You! I've been considerate of you,
but look at you.
Colluding with that woman
and creating such a scandal.
Let me ask you when you love her
and how much you love her.
Don't you still want your future
and reputation?
And you don't want me, your lawful wife.
- Haode, listen to me.
- You shut up.
Let me ask you. Did you teach that Cui
to come to me?
- How would she know where the entrance is?
- What's happening?
How dare she cause such trouble!
Marrying during the mourning period?
What a ridiculous excuse!
Doesn't she feel ashamed?
And that Qiao Du… Don't touch me.
And that Qiao Du…
I wonder why he's so anxious,
like his own wife's
on the execution grounds.
So, he did it all for you.
In the end, I've become a pawn
to be used by others.
All my good intentions wasted.
Do you know?
During tomorrow's court interrogation,
in public,
you not only will be dismissed,
but sent to prison for the crime.
You'll implicate the whole family
and become a laughingstock to others.
Shen Huizhao, let's part ways.
Haode.
Get lost!
- Go.
- Leave.
We had an agreement.
Just do as you said, and my lady
will be given a lighter sentence.
Don't lie to me.
Be patient. That day will come.
I can't wait.
If she can't get a lighter sentence
tomorrow, I will tell the truth at Yamen.
Easy.
Lady Fang has a message for you.
Come closer.
KAIFENG COURT
Shen Huizhao.
That day you sat here
and sentenced my son to death,
did you ever think that one day
you would be dismissed
and put on trial, becoming
a prisoner?
I really never thought
that my upright and unyielding teacher
would become like this today.
What? To go on trial,
yet you still don't want
to take off your official robe?
Lord Shen, after today's hearing,
you, who were once known
as the upright official
trusted by His Majesty,
will become the villain who's despised,
condemned, and cursed by everyone.
By then,
there will be many things
you'd never expect.
Xue Guang, for your own self-desires,
you've rashly judged a lawsuit,
set all sorts of traps
to frame an imperial official.
Do you confess your crime?
Shen Huizhao, have you lost your mind?
Today, I am judging your crime.
Why are you instead questioning me?
Mr. Huang has arrived.
Mr. Huang.
Mr. Huang,
please make a fair judgment in court.
No, I am here on His Majesty's order
to attend the trial.
Lord Shen.
You have promised to His Majesty
that you'd certainly
make a fair judgment on this case.
I shall wait and see.
Hold court trial!
Bring in the prisoners.
My lady.
Mr. Xue, do you recognize them?
These two are witnesses accusing Lord Shen
of practicing favoritism.
But I don't recognize the two of them.
The servant, Mao Chun,
is the one
who cleaned up outside my study.
After Fang Yuchan was imprisoned,
he incited Lady Fang's wet nurse, Cui,
and lied that Lady Fang's mourning
for her father was over
so she could escape punishment.
Last night, he even attempted to kill Cui,
but I caught him on the spot.
Cui, he wanted to kill you?
My lady, I almost couldn't see you again.
Lord Shen, it was Mao Chun
who convinced me
that marrying during the mourning period
would result in a lighter sentence.
I was eager to save my lady,
so I slipped the information
to Madam Haode.
I made up all these lies.
I deserve to die.
Lord Shen, I was merely talking nonsense
after being drunk,
and I didn't expect
this old lady to believe it.
When it didn't work out,
she blamed me.
Thus, we only had a quarrel.
I had no intention to kill her.
Take him away and punish him
with 50 strokes of the cane first.
- Yes.
- Lord Shen, please spare me.
Lord Shen, please spare me.
- Lady Fang, it'll be fine.
- Lord Shen.
You practiced favoritism
and judged the case for personal gains,
and found others to take the blame.
Trying to escape the crime
of judging falsely?
This is just too childish.
No rush. Qiao Du,
why did you secretly release the prisoner?
All my words and actions
are all out of loyalty to you.
Nonsense!
Ever since I got attacked by an assassin,
I suspected that someone close to me
was leaking information.
I told you to go to Hangzhou again
to investigate the Fang family.
It was to find out your intentions.
But two days later, the man you sent
is still in the tavern
30 miles from Bianjing.
What is he waiting for?
Naturally, he's waiting for me
to be dismissed and interrogated.
I asked you
to covertly protect Lu Jiulang,
yet you didn't do what I said again
and went to the Li family
to stir up trouble.
Don't you ever wonder
why things have gone so smoothly?
If that Fang Yuchan dies,
then this case
would be resolved immediately, right?
I asked Li Shouhua of the Li family
to cooperate with me
and secretly push the progress.
I just wanted to see
how this mastermind behind the scenes
framed me and accused me.
Regarding the prison escape, I had already
reported it to His Majesty early on.
I set this trap
to wait for you to be caught
by your own scheme.
Qiao Du, I have given you chances
again and again.
If you had realized your mistake
and mended it in time,
you wouldn't end up as a prisoner.
I didn't know.
But do you know
that the person behind this
for his own selfish desires
even tried to kill Cui and Lu Jiulang?
As a chivalrous martial artist
with a tender heart,
you have become an accomplice to murder.
Don't you regret it?
I didn't know.
- You!
- Kneel.
You promised me you wouldn't kill again.
You promised me
that you would only
deal with Shen Huizhao alone
and never kill anyone again.
You lied to me!
- Xue Guang, you…
- How dare you!
I have been an official for decades.
I don't care about any rumor or slander.
Xue Guang, you still refuse to confess.
- I have no crime to confess.
- Fine.
I have two witnesses to come forward.
Haode.
Lord Shen and my husband have discussed
and set up the plan.
How did you know it?
Huizhao's expression and tone
towards Qiao Du
seemed a bit strange,
so I paid attention to it.
Besides, you are so shrewd and careful.
How could you easily agree
on the prison escape?
The quicker you agreed,
the more suspicious the matter.
Don't be mad.
I asked the two of them
to keep it from you and Leshan.
Only then could we fool the others.
Shouhua.
Haode.
Do you think that Qiao Du will confess?
You…
You're still alive?
Qiao Du, since I have suspected you,
how would I entrust
the important witness to you?
Lu Sheng, is Lady Fang kneeling here
the one who stabbed you?
Yes.
That night, she saw my ugly face
and was unwilling to marry me.
She pulled out the dagger from her waist,
wanting to commit suicide.
I stepped forward to stop her.
In the struggle, I was mistakenly injured.
It was a suicide attempt, not murder?
It was a suicide attempt, not murder.
Fang Yuchan, do you hear it?
Tell the truth.
I heard it. Please discern the truth.
I am trapped in prison,
with no means to appeal.
Xue Guang told me
that Jiulang was already dead,
and the Lu family
would certainly not let me go.
He asked me to do as he said,
to frame Lord Shen
for practicing favoritism,
then he would seek His Majesty's pardon
to reduce my sentence.
Otherwise, he would charge me
with the murder of my husband,
and the crime of prison escape,
and put me to death
by dismembering the body.
Xue Guang, as the Minister
of Dali Supreme Court,
how dare you bend the law to extract
confessions and frame a colleague?
A prisoner on death row
who tried to escape prison
accused Shen Huizhao firmly yesterday,
yet shifted all the blame onto me today.
How can you trust her?
I do not accept this.
You instigated the Bianjing physician
Liu Zaichang
to poison Lu Jiulang to death.
I caught the person and got the drug.
You can't deny it anymore.
You are slandering me!
I've heard how marvelous
this physician Liu's medical skills are.
Yet I haven't met him.
How dare you slander
the Minister of Dali Supreme Court!
Xue Guang, if it weren't for you
threatening me with the evidence
of my pharmacy endangering other lives…
I've been practicing medicine
and saving lives for 40 years.
Why would I poison my patient to death?
Lord Shen, I know
that I deserve punishment.
Everything I said is true.
I am willing to accept the punishment
and sign my confession here in court.
- I hope you won't let the mastermind go.
- Shut up.
Shen Huizhao, that servant Mao Chun
is from your Shen family.
Li Haode bought the Semen Cannabis.
The Kaifeng Court Official
secretly released Lady Fang.
They are all related to you.
What does it have to do with me?
With clear evidence presented,
how dare you still deny!
I might have bribed one.
Could I possibly bribe
all these witnesses in here?
Our ancestors made laws
after careful consideration,
and we should enforce the law
with fairness and justice.
If for one's self desires
one disregards the law and justice,
harming the innocents,
even if one had much achievement,
they would vanish in an instant.
The imperial laws couldn't tolerate you.
Even the world couldn't tolerate you.
Teacher…
wake up.
I have lost.
- I didn't expect it to be true.
- What is it?
- I have also heard about it.
- Yes.
KAIFENG COURT
Lu Jiulang bears in mind the favor
of being saved by you,
so he's willing to plead for Lady Fang.
What will happen to them?
The Minister of Dali Supreme Court wields
great power. He violated the law.
Only His Majesty
could judge his punishment.
As for Qiao Du,
he is sentenced to 30 canings
and to be exiled to Cangzhou.
What a pity.
- Let's go.
- Where to?
To the Li family and bring back my wife.
Jingwei.
Lord Shen, my apologies. You can't go in.
I'm here to pick up Haode.
Leshan, please let me in.
Qingshi.
Haode said
you didn't complete the bride fetching,
wedding ceremony, and the temple visit.
Thus, you two are not considered
as a married couple.
Lord Shen, please leave.
You are so rude.
Lord Shen, what should we do?
Go back.
Lord Shen, aren't you
taking Lady Haode back?
He's left?
So, he's really left and never returned?
He came here to pick you up.
I told you not to put on an act.
Now, this is great.
You can't go back now.
So, he could collude with
my elder brother-in-law to deceive me,
but I couldn't fool him?
It's not fair.
He got the cold shoulder
and didn't want his wife anymore.
I haven't heard of anyone nearby
having a wedding.
Who is this for?
Coming.
- Coming.
- What?
You silly girl!
What are you waiting for?
Your bridal sedan chair has arrived.
Huizhao.
W-What are you doing?
Of course, I'm here
to complete the bride fetching,
wedding ceremony,
and the ancestral temple visit.
I would marry you
into the Shen family in glory
and make you my wife.
Huizhao, so you knew everything all along.
I'm so delighted.
Just hold on
and change into your wedding attire.
Old Lady is waiting
for her daughter-in-law to offer tea.
Haode.
You girl!
The makeup isn't even finished yet.
Wait for me. Coming.
Hurry up.
You can't catch up.
- Congratulations, Lord Shen.
- Congratulations.
- Bravo.
What a joy.
Congratulations, Lord Shen.
Mother, sister, where are you?
Where are you?
Why are you here all alone?
My mother is so biased.
I don't want to see her.
But I miss home so much,
and I miss my mother.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
SECOND DAY OF THE THIRD MONTH
This won't do.
Yesterday, I was busy preparing the room.
Didn't I ask you to replace
the fruit on the tray with the best?
Mom, Lamian tea costs 200 coins a catty.
We don't bear drink it ourselves,
yet you say it isn't good enough.
You don't know anything.
Change it to the best Hunan Mountain Tea.
Can't let the He family look down on us.
- Hurry!
- Alright.
Wine.
A jar must hold four catties of water.
Mom, it was you who mixed the water in it.
And you even complained
that it was too little.
I mixed it myself?
The new son-in-law comes to visit us,
can it be the same?
Madame He is a meticulous person.
We can't let the He family
look down on Leshan.
Hurry up. Go.
- Go change it.
- Okay.
Go change it.
Two, four…
Hurry up. Mother-in-law.
The groom's family is coming
with the betrothal gifts.
The person urging the bride to dress
is near the alley entrance.
Qiongnu, Chunlai.
Double-check the gifts in return.
- Okay.
- Leshan.
- Have you finished your makeup, Leshan?
- Come over.
Lianghan, you go with An
to the gate to welcome them.
Don't slight the bride's fetching team.
- Go now.
- Okay.
Leshan, my dear, are you done
with your makeup yet?
Leshan.
- The bride's fetching team is already--
- Mother. Alright, don't rush her.
They are all waiting.
- If we make them wait too long…
- Coming. Look.
Are you still
my dear Leshan?
She got up to do her makeup
early last night.
You said
we have to let all the relatives, friends,
and neighbors know how great Leshan is.
This also brings honor to the He family.
Nothing good comes too late.
The bridal sedan chair is about to arrive.
Mom, are you afraid
your son-in-law will run away?
Exactly.
He is marrying such a beautiful bride.
Why can't Mr. He wait?
I guarantee that once he sees her,
he'll be fascinated.
Mom.
Are you that eager to send me off?
You won't even let me
stay at home for a bit longer.
You girl!
Alright, everything is fine.
I'm just worried about your temperament.
He Guangyuan is gentle and soft.
The He family is also quite well-off.
They have a simple family.
After you marry into their family,
your mother-in-law is kind,
and the sister-in-law knows etiquette.
And you won't have to worry
about household affairs.
You won't get wronged.
But you must learn to control your temper.
From now on,
you should be kind to your in-laws
and considerate to your husband,
becoming a nice wife
who supports her husband
and teaches her children well.
Do you hear me?
Can you make me proud?
You can't do whatever you want
like you do at home.
Mom.
Don't worry. I understand.
Even if I marry,
I will always be a part of the Li family,
upholding the instructions
of the Li family.
As the old saying goes,
kind parents and filial sons,
virtuous husbands and wise wives.
The kind elders
and the virtuous husbands come first.
After I marry off,
if they respect me, I will be forgiving.
I will never hit my in-laws
nor bully my husband.
I will never bring shame
to the ancestors of the Li family.
But if someone provokes me,
I'm not a timid person,
I might just beat him.
If it happens, don't blame me
for being rude or un-filial.
You! You girl!
Mom, don't.
On such a joyful day,
we can't make a scene and be laughed at.
Wait. As her elder sisters, you should
manage her well. What…
Mom.
The groom has arrived.
Clean my room every day.
I'm just taking a look.
If I'm not happy with the He family,
- I'll come back.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- I'm just taking a look there.
If I'm not happy with the He family,
I'll come back.
Hey.
Leshan.
- Take it slow. Your bridal veil.
- Leshan.
- Leshan, put on your bridal veil.
- Mother.
I wonder what day today is.
The dresser stands on the balcony
is getting closer.
Some people say
that hibiscus grows in water,
but it blooms in the bronze mirror.
Good. Okay.
What? It's not acceptable
to pass off with another's poem.
Right, Yuanming is correct.
It's not difficult
to invite the bride out.
It depends on whether
you're sincere or not.
Mr. Du, don't make things difficult.
You're the third-ranked scholar.
- No one shows off in front of you.
- Right.
For the sake of me, please let him pass.
No way.
- No way.
- No.
On this wedding day,
there's no distinction between us.
Moreover, Mr. He is different now.
Do not act shy like a lady.
If you have any skills, show us.
You must show them off anyway.
- Yes.
- Compose a poem and you'll pass.
Greetings to you all.
I pay my respects to you all.
No, compose a poem.
- Compose a poem.
It's noon.
The auspicious moment is about to pass.
Please, please let the bride come out.
- Poem.
- No.
- You have to compose a poem.
- You can't get in otherwise.
- Hurry up.
- You have to compose a poem.
- Try.
- Give it a try.
Joy fills the gate
- Brightness illuminates the silk
- They have searched all the talents
in Bianjing and chose this man,
who's even shyer than Leshan.
Look at him blushing all over.
He's become like the bride.
Brightness…
I heard from Haode
that the Li family is choosing a husband
for Leshan differently.
They choose one
that won't fight or talk back…
- Brightness illuminates the silk
- …and never complain.
Madam is discerning. Hurry up.
Rouge brings color
Green varnishes the palace
- Alright, move.
- It's out of rhyme.
- It's not a poem.
- No way.
- Let me in first.
- The bride's come out.
- Let me in.
- Let him in.
The bride has come out.
- She's out.
- Forget it, Yuanming.
- Here she comes.
- She's here.
Wonderful.
He's truly blessed.
Such a great daughter-in-law.
Bride, please go onto the sedan chair.
Let's go.
Mom.
I'm here. Don't worry. Just go.
- Let's go.
Welcoming happiness, dispatching joy.
The bride sets off.
- Good.
- Congratulations.
- Bravo.
Look how shy he is.
May you have a child soon.
Live a happy life.
- Live a harmonious life forever.
- Bravo.
- Congratulations.
- Great.
Look how happy he is.
- Congratulations.
Leshan.
Remember what I told you.
- Give me two.
- Okay.
Whose family is having a wedding?
What a good day.
I wonder whose family is having a wedding.
Master.
- Tell him to make way.
- Yes.
Stop, stop.
Whose bridal sedan is this?
You are not discerning at all.
Make way.
- Make way.
- Let us go through.
- Move.
Which Yang family is it? So dominant.
Master, his aunt is Concubine Yang,
who personally raised His Majesty.
He's related to the Empress Dowager,
he has a sister in His Majesty's favor,
and just got promoted to imperial consort.
We must not offend the imperial kins.
Perhaps let them go first.
Right, move way!
Go, hurry!
- Move.
- Move to the side!
Hurry, to the side!
- Master.
- Come.
To the side.
- Stand firm.
- Be careful.
Be careful not to jostle the bride.
Matron of honor, what happened?
Do not fear. Everything is fine.
Don't let the bridal veil fall.
The road's wide,
yet you bumped into us?
You are too outrageous.
- Put it down first.
- Put down.
You!
- What do you want?
- Fight him.
- Being unreasonable, right?
- Leshan.
Don't fight.
- Don't fight.
- Stop it.
Stop it.
Leshan, are you alright?
Master.
- Master.
- Why did you hit me?
- Don't hit Master.
Stop.
Stop hitting, Master.
It's a day of great joy.
Stop it.
- Stop it.
- Beat him.
Stop it.
Don't unveil it.
- Help!
- Stop fighting.
Matron of honor!
- I'm here.
- Stop it.
Before the ceremony is complete,
don't unveil it.
Let me help you back into the sedan chair.
- Come on.
- Be careful.
- Over there, hurry up.
- Get him.
- Careful.
- Watch out.
- Make way!
- Hurry up.
Right, this way.
Be careful with the bridal veil.
Hit them.
- This way.
- Get out of the way!
Help!
Everyone, stop fighting!
Both families are anxiously waiting.
If we miss the moment,
we'll have to pick another.
Stop it.
- Let's go
- Stop!
Stop fighting!
Don't miss the auspicious moment.
Let's go.
- Go
- Let's go.
- Master.
- Matron of honor.
Matron of honor.
- Hurry up and get in.
Why are you coming out?
Hurry up. Let's go.
- How can there be such rude people…
- Hurry.
- …in this world?
- Yes.
- How dare you!
- You are outrageous.
Master.
All the relatives
are all waiting for the ceremony.
It would be a pity to delay it.
- No way, I must sue them.
- Let's go.
- You are outrageous.
- Sir.
Alright, let's go.
Master, that punch you threw
just now was amazing.
This silly girl.
Mom.
You've been busy all day. I've made you
a bowl of dumplings.
Please eat some.
Why haven't you gone back yet?
Yangxi is coming to urge you.
I told him to go back to pack up
and move back here early tomorrow.
Move back here?
Did you two have an argument?
Mother-in-law insists on returning
to the hometown.
There are no elders at home.
We're only separated by a wall.
I might as well move back.
Besides,
Yangxi said he marries into the Li family.
It's only right for him to come over
and take care of you.
Seriously?
Of course.
How about we all come back
and stay with you?
Well, you all!
What's going on?
After Leshan gets married,
you must feel a bit lonely.
We sisters have decided
to take turns coming back to live here.
How about one in turn for a month?
- Is it?
- Nonsense!
No married daughter comes back
to live with her mother all the time.
If you come back,
what about your husbands?
Your in-laws will complain.
Mom.
We grew up without a father
and have been raised by you.
If we forget our own mother
once we are married,
who would want
such ruthless daughter-in-laws?
Exactly.
I'll go home and fulfill my filial duties.
If Fan Lianghan dares to object,
I'll beat him.
Next month, I'll bring Joy back
to keep you company, okay?
No need.
Mom, of all virtues,
filial piety is the greatest.
In the Song, all mothers without sons
have been supported by daughters.
If we don't even have this right,
we don't deserve to be your daughters.
Exactly.
Good.
The house is all ready.
Every night,
I go around each room
and clean them all thoroughly.
Okay, Mom. It's getting cold. Eat now.
- Eat now.
- Eat up.
I wonder how Leshan is doing.
I hope this He Guangyuan
makes fewer mistakes tonight.
If he annoys Leshan,
then he has to suffer tonight.
Why are you like this?
That's the truth.
- Eat up.
- Mom.
YANG MANSION
Li Leshan, how are you?
Do you still remember me?
You're a woman,
so I won't make things difficult for you.
As long as you kneel and beg for mercy,
swearing to be my maid for three years,
to help me change clothes,
grind ink, and serve by my bed,
then I will save your sister.
How about that?
Master, I beg you to save my sister.
I'm willing to be a maid.
Whatever will do.
Li Leshan, you promised me so
when you begged me
to save your fourth sister.
I went through great hardships
to destroy the thieves' den,
kill the bandits,
and save your fourth sister.
But you've hidden
in the Li house ever since,
going against your promise.
Now, I don't need you to bother coming.
I'll personally bring you here
in a bridal sedan chair. How about it?
You exchanged the bridal sedan chair?
Yes, I did.
Yang Xian.
You bullied me, such a vulnerable girl,
and took advantage of me.
The Shen and Li families
brought you generous gifts as thanks.
You thought it's not enough.
Marriage is an important event.
This affects my whole life,
yet you dare pull such a trick.
Yang Xian.
You are arrogant, despicable,
inhuman, and lowly.
You are the one who's ungrateful.
How dare you scold me here!
I don't want jewels as thanks.
I want you to keep your promise.
Now, we've bowed to the heaven and earth
and completed the wedding ceremony.
We are a couple now.
- You can't regret it.
- You!
The wedding night
is a rare beautiful night.
Have a cup of wedding wine with me.
From now on,
if you respect me
and serve me well,
then I will spare you.
If you dare to lose your temper,
speak disrespectfully,
or provoke me again…
Li Leshan, how dare you hit me?
I…
- You shrew!
- You heinous man!
I…
How dare you mess with me?
I must beat you until you crawl.
- I--
- Go away.
You heinous man!
What's wrong?
Xian.
- Xian.
- Don't come over.
MADAM LUO
YANG DEMAO
I am Li Leshan from Sifu House
on Pan Restaurant Street.
On my wedding day,
your son snatched me away,
forcing me to be his wife.
Hurry and inform the Li family.
If you dare delay,
- I'll take his life.
- Don't.
- Mom.
- Go to the Li family.
Go!
Don't act rashly.
Crying, that's all you know.
Your son has caused big trouble.
The Yan's daughter is from a distinguished
family, virtuous and upright,
praised by everyone in Bianjing.
What is there for him to nitpick?
He insisted on switching to a shrewish
and fierce girl
who pays no respect to her elders.
He just wants to drive me crazy.
It's not my son who made the switch.
It was the heavens' doing.
You are the cousin of Concubine Yang,
yet you can't even deal
with such an ignorant girl.
Just have the servant go tie her up.
Wouldn't that solve everything?
You stupid woman!
The Li family is a humble family,
but her fourth brother-in-law
is Shen Huizhao,
the ruthless judge of Kaifeng Court.
And her eldest sister got married
to the third-ranked scholar Du Yangxi.
Who are they?
They are the intimate officials
to His Majesty.
If the Li family accused us
to His Majesty,
even with Concubine Yang as a guarantor,
we can't escape the punishment.
But she has already
married into our family.
She has become one of us.
Not to mention
upholding women's virtues and integrity.
She wouldn't accuse us.
If she makes a scene,
she'd be so ashamed.
You are a faithful widow,
having shame and dignity.
But that shrew
doesn't fear being humiliated.
Enough. Stop it.
Chaozong.
Father, I have already asked someone
to go to the Li family.
Of course, you must go to the Li family.
Prepare a generous gift.
You go visit the He family.
Also, send someone
to the palace immediately
and ask for instructions from the Consort.
Subtitle translation by: Wina Huang