EPISODE 30
The new son-in-law visits his in-laws.
As tradition,
he must serve tea to the elders.
Please.
Easy tests. I've got it.
Madam, please.
Mom.
He's seven or eight days late.
The Yang family
must've brought lavish gifts.
Why don't we take a look first?
Okay.
Qiansheng.
Sure.
Quite thoughtful.
Take them.
Mom.
Have some tea.
Get up.
Mom.
I was naive and arrogant in my youth.
I was misled by others,
which led to foolish mistakes.
Thanks to your forgiveness,
I married Leshan.
Since our marriage,
my wife has guided me tirelessly.
I've reflected on my past mistakes.
I vow to turn over a new leaf
and leave my faults behind.
I hope everyone here
can forgive me. I'm truly grateful.
It's not late, not late at all!
It's good that you've changed.
Who hasn't made mistakes in their youth?
But what if they disagree?
You're from a rich family,
- and you're young
- Mom.
- and easily misled by other evils.
- Sit down.
- But he regrets his mistakes now.
- I really miss you.
That's good.
We're family. There's no room for grudges.
Right, my lord?
My wife is right. Absolutely.
He…
Thank you, Madam.
Something feels off to me.
You better sort this out.
What's that burnt smell?
I've got pork simmering on the stove.
Yang Xian, I am cooking today. Try it.
- You all sit with him.
- Thanks, Madam.
We'll join you.
Let's go too.
- And me.
- The soup.
Kangning makes it the best.
It's rare to have such a guest.
We need your help.
- Let's go.
- Kangning, just go.
Yang Xian, excuse us for a moment.
Of course.
Wait…
Good luck.
- Yuanming.
- Chai.
Leshan, tell me the truth.
Are you conspiring with him to fool Mom?
Change?
He'll never change.
Not even if pigs climb trees.
That's nonsense.
Fuhui tamed her husband.
Why can't I do the same?
Kangning,
you underestimate me.
What are they up to?
You're new here,
so you don't know our family rules.
It's not hard to marry into the Li family.
First, remember three things.
The first, when your wife is upset…
You must soothe her.
- What about scolding from Madam?
- Endure it.
My wife reminded me many times.
I won't forget.
Did she tell you
before joining the Li Family,
you should first pass the tests
from us, the brothers-in-law?
What kind of tests?
Yuanming.
Back when we chose a husband for her,
we followed our wives' orders.
We searched the entire capital
for the best talents.
No one dared approach Li's house
without exceptional skills.
Today, I see you handsome and charming.
His look matches with Leshan.
But to know how he matches her
on the talents,
it will depend on your learnings.
- Lord Shen.
- Don't look at me.
Outside, I have some authority,
but in this house,
my wife is the fourth sister.
She's one of the younger ones.
Even if I'd like to help you,
I don't have a say here.
Master Yang,
you can only rely on yourself.
Stop it!
Take a break. Don't move.
What kind of test?
Yuanming.
A martial challenge?
We know you're not skilled.
- So, let's test academics.
- Yeah.
Instruments, chess, calligraphy,
and painting. Pick one.
Show us what you're good at.
Master Yang,
if it's decent,
we'll accept you.
Old grudges will be forgotten.
But if you fail,
don't blame us for being harsh.
Give him a tough lesson,
so he knows the Li family isn't easy.
Being a Li son-in-law is even harder.
- I should check on them.
- Where to?
Stay out of it. It's men's business.
Oh no!
I forgot how tricky
my brothers-in-law are.
I studied painting in my youth.
Though not as skilled as Mr. Du,
my strokes are decent.
Do it.
Excuse me.
Too much ink bleeds the lines.
Haven't you learned this?
It's said, strength gives grace.
Speed gives stiffness.
Reflect on yourself.
Don't defend your flaws.
Tension creates vigor.
Act recklessly
and there will be consequences.
Straighten your back.
The ink needs some water.
Stay humble and self-aware.
Aim high but avoid arrogance.
Be grounded but ambitious.
Face life with a calm smile.
There.
All done.
After all that, your mouth must be dry.
You outnumbered and bullied me.
How shameful!
Who can respect that?
Cousin, he is not convinced
and speaks of bullying.
You oppressed others and forced marriage.
Are you not shameful?
If you say no,
we will beat you until you agree.
Count me in.
- What are you doing?
- This…
I told you not to act so rough.
- It's disgraceful.
- Shameless.
- This is too much!
- Enough, enough.
Just a friendly spar.
Stop!
- Come back!
- Leshan.
Stop!
Dinner's ready.
Mom. What?
- Nothing.
- Nothing at all.
Nothing.
- Mom.
Yang Xian wants duck.
He's too shy to ask.
I just finished the duck soup. Let me--
I heard the two cooks
were borrowed from Pan Restaurant.
Let's check if everything's set.
- It's all ready.
- Mom.
Wine-flavored snails?
Didn't you just prepare some?
You want that?
Sure, I'll make them for you.
Dear brothers-in-law,
stop fighting already.
Enough is enough.
Once he passes this test,
he'll truly be one of us.
I was wrong.
Don't mess this up for me.
Eat more. It's good for you.
Here, wife.
Put it there.
- I want that.
- This one?
Have some meat.
A round face means good fortune.
Shouhua,
we should settle the match soon.
We need time to prepare.
Got it.
Madam, Kangning loves me.
This is my favorite.
The acting might get a bit exaggerated.
They'll give themselves away
before mother-in-law.
Silly.
My lord, here.
- What?
- Look around.
Is it good?
- This.
- Sour?
- Not bad.
- Try this.
Take this.
I'm full.
My lady, have this.
Yang Xian.
This cured meat has orange peel and herbs.
Leshan hates this flavor.
My wife said she follows my lead now.
Whatever I like, she likes too.
She's even fixed her picky habits.
That's what true harmony looks like.
My wife loves it.
It must be dipped in vinegar,
then ginger and garlic.
That's the best way. Try it.
Take this.
Thank you, my lord.
Taste it.
If you like it, have some more.
Fan, I'm so sorry. It slipped. My mistake.
I'm sorry.
Alright, alright.
You think I don't know
what mischief you're up to?
Young rich boys
always have bad friends.
They always trick him into being evil.
It's hard not to go astray.
But if he were truly wicked,
he'd never save others.
Haode, Qiongnu,
and the old lady.
He saved all their lives.
Marriage makes us family.
No matter the past grudges,
for that alone, he deserves a break.
Let's not dwell on old wrongs.
That's how family should be.
Making peace to his face,
but scheming behind his back.
Is that how the Li family acts?
From birth till now,
even my parents never said this to me.
Madam, you're right.
Since Yang Xian regrets his past,
we should bury the hatchet.
Get along well.
All grudges aired,
all anger gone.
Let's drink to move on.
- This one's on me.
- Me too.
Thank you for saving my granny
and my wife.
- Yuanming.
- Come.
- Drink it.
- Yang Xian.
- And me.
- Together.
- Drink this.
- Drink one.
- Come on.
- Madam.
- Mother.
- Let's drink.
Madam.
- Here.
- I heard that.
- Arrange a match for Qiongnu?
- Madam.
- I'm going too.
- Yes.
Mom.
Don't make it too grand.
You'll scare them off.
I'll check on the food.
It's a match, not a battle.
- Madam.
- Mom.
- Eat up.
- Sit here.
- Not this.
- You barely ate.
- Have this.
- Good.
- Try this.
No.
This one helps circulation.
This one heals bruises.
This one is nice.
And this is for swelling and pain.
I twisted my ankle once,
and it healed in seven days.
According to Yangxi, there is ginseng
and galangal in it.
Lots of good stuff inside.
Thanks for thinking of me.
It's just a small injury. I'm fine.
No, you're not fine.
Make sure to apply the medicine.
If you can't reach your back,
let Leshan help you.
- Did you hear that?
- I heard that.
Yang Xian,
you didn't eat much at dinner.
Was it not good?
No, no, not at all.
Well, it's your first time here.
I can't let you sleep hungry.
Tell me what you want.
I'll make it for you.
I'd like some steamed egg custard.
Isn't that too much?
Not at all.
My custard's smooth and silky.
Even Leshan loves it.
Mom.
Don't listen to him.
It's too late for custard.
Such a hassle.
None of your business.
It's no trouble. I'll cook it now.
It'll be ready soon.
- Thanks, Madam.
- Mom.
Do it.
Done.
My back too.
Ask your servant.
You're my lawfully wedded wife.
Why let someone else do it?
Your mother said--
Stop making a big deal out of nothing.
Did you forget your forced wedding stunt?
I was promised to the He family.
Who's your wife?
Good thing you got into my bridal sedan.
Look at your four sisters.
They either married
to successful young men
or wealthy gentlemen known in the capital.
If you'd married that loser,
how could you hold your head up with them?
I forced the wedding to help you.
You should be thanking me.
Custard?
Medicine?
You want me to thank you for that?
You're such a shameless jerk!
I have to remind you.
Be careful if the Li family hears this.
Lose your temper, and it's all over.
Left in the carriage, right?
Using this laundry stick to hit a thief
is better than using a rolling pin.
- Take this!
- Madam, save me!
Your proud creation.
You better keep it.
Change is easier said than done.
Kind words can't beat showing the stakes.
We're not doing this to vent anger.
It's to show that Yang guy.
He must follow the rules
and treat his wife well.
If he acts up again, a line of people
are ready to teach him a lesson.
You don't even thank me for this.
Why are you blaming me?
Yes, yes. I appreciate your effort.
Thank you very much.
I owe you one, okay?
- Help!
- Stop it!
Help me!
- Stop! Help!
- What? What
Don't run!
Qiongnu.
- You!
- Qiongnu.
What's going on here?
I've put up with you all day.
If not for my mom,
why would I be kind to a kidnapper?
Fine, fine.
Qiongnu, did you see that?
- Your sister's so feisty.
- You!
Couples bickering is normal.
Holding that isn't right.
Put it down. Okay?
Why all the noise
in the middle of the night?
Madam, help me!
- Madam.
- Come here.
- Leshan.
What now?
- Drop it.
- Shouhua's here.
Leshan, the new son-in-law's here.
The neighbors can hear you yelling.
- You're embarrassing Mom.
- Exactly.
He wants me to thank him
for kidnapping me.
What a shameless thief!
Nobody stop me today.
If we indulge his arrogance,
he'll keep bullying me forever!
I won't take that from him. No way!
- Mr. Du.
- Be the judge.
- You…
- You're wrong.
- Come here.
How could you say this?
He deserves it.
Leshan, let him go for my sake.
No way!
Drop it!
What did I do in my past life?
You're a troublemaker.
You've been married just a few days.
You scare him with this?
- I--
- Doing this for everyone to hear?
Put it down!
Put it down.
Leshan.
Madam.
- That's okay.
- I can't handle this wife anymore.
- I'm truly sorry this time.
- Good kid.
Be patient. I'll have her change.
- Okay.
- How miserable.
You can't take it.
Write a letter of divorce.
We're done today.
- Leshan.
- Hey.
- Drop it.
- Yang Xian.
This kid.
A royal marriage can't be dissolved.
Divorce? Not a chance.
- Stop it.
- Mom.
I'll marry someone better.
You'll die alone here.
Spend your life as a lonely widow!
- Calm down, Madam.
- Mom.
Mom.
Fine. I was wrong, okay?
Wow! You admit you're wrong?
You scared him half to death.
I must've raised a warrior, huh?
You're braver than most men.
Mom.
He fell on his own.
It's not really my fault.
Still arguing with me?
Even if you didn't chase him,
you still scared him.
I…
Shouhua.
Mom.
Yang Xian broke his leg.
He needs someone to care of him.
Let her make amends.
Besides,
if you really hurt her,
you'd regret it yourself.
Today, I'm putting my foot down.
From now on, you're staying home.
Focus on taking care of your husband.
No one else is allowed to help.
If there's even a slight mistake,
you won't set foot in this house again.
- Mom.
- Don't even call me mom.
Mom, please calm down.
I've sent Qiansheng to the Yangs.
I told them you're keeping her longer.
So, the couple can stay a few more days.
Once his leg heals,
we'll send him back.
To avoid alarming the Yang family.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.
What a mess.
- Go take care of him.
- Sure.
We're off.
It hurts.
I'll be gentle.
You're suffocating me.
No, no, not at all.
Be gentler.
You're so clumsy.
- I'm hot.
- What?
I said I'm hot.
Water.
Anyone? I need water.
Coming, coming.
Here, here. Water's here.
Madam! Leshan--
No, nothing happened.
What are you doing? Keep fanning.
Chunlai.
Boil the medicine longer.
Chunlai, why are you taking over?
Chunlai.
My lord, time to drink your medicine.
I know you're mad at me.
But I've stayed up caring for you.
Up at midnight to make your medicine.
My eyes are red, fingers burned.
Please, consider my effort.
At least drink a little.
Such care and effort,
just so I'll take the medicine?
Afraid your mom will scold?
What's your real motive?
You're misunderstanding me again.
If you don't drink, your leg won't heal.
It'll hurt more than just you.
It'll ruin my peace too.
Seeing you in pain every night,
I can't bear it either.
My lord.
Do you know what's in this medicine?
It's arsenic.
In less than an hour,
you'll bleed from every pore,
your insides will rot.
Who says I can't refuse an imperial match?
I'd rather be a widow
than stay married to you.
You vile woman.
What's wrong?
- What's going on?
- Mom.
- Shouhua.
- Good kid.
- It's okay?
- He insists I poisoned him.
He even spilled the medicine bowl.
He's clearly wronging me.
Kid,
you've really wronged her this time.
I got the medicine myself.
After it was brewed,
I made her taste it first,
fearing bitterness.
Besides, you're her husband,
and this is her family home.
If anything happens to you,
she'd be the first to blame.
Li Leshan.
Naughty girl.
He's being dramatic, refusing medicine.
Ignoring my intentions.
If he dares next time…
You little troublemaker.
Mom, the Yangs sent someone to fetch them.
Weren't they staying more days?
Why?
They said Lady Jieyu is visiting home.
They rushed to escort the newlyweds back.
Li Leshan,
your doom is near.
YANG MANSION
Your sister-in-law
isn't virtuous at all.
She lacks grace, manners, and decorum.
Other daughters-in-law
respect their mothers-in-law.
But her?
She fears nothing.
Rules and customs mean nothing to her.
You won't find another
like her in Bianjing.
True.
She defies her mother-in-law,
bullies her husband,
and is terribly fierce.
I say take her to court.
Let them deal with her as an example.
But we care
about Lady Jieyu's reputation
and our family name.
That's why we endure this.
Sister,
is she truly this vicious?
If not completely,
at least mostly true.
My brother is so lawless,
yet he's afraid of her.
It's strange.
With others, he shows no mercy.
But with her,
he even softens his tone.
Like they say, everyone meets their match.
Why blame my son?
Anyone facing her would be wary too.
Why don't you try taking her hit?
Seems she's fiercer
than I heard in the palace.
Enough.
She rarely visits her family.
You keep pestering her with complaints.
It's all just trivial household matters.
Aren't you worried she'll get annoyed?
Don't worry. These are all my confidants.
Daughter,
you've always had your own mind.
Since entering the palace,
you've gained His Majesty's deep favor.
I shouldn't say much,
but palace life changes rapidly.
I can't help but worry about you.
Her Majesty has no child, no favor.
They say Shang's rising fast.
Even her brothers gained noble titles.
A mere merchant's family
rose so quickly in a few years.
I wish to help you,
but I lack power.
My rank is too low to intervene.
You must plan ahead, daughter.
Don't let others steal your glory.
That Li came from
a low tea-seller's family.
She relies on ties
to the Shen and Du families.
She's become arrogant before me.
Now that you're back,
it's time to teach her a lesson.
Don't let her bring trouble to our family,
or we'll have no way to escape it.
Lady Jieyu, Master,
they have returned.
Carry me back to my room.
My lord, Lady Jieyu is calling for you.
I need to go back.
I don't care who it is.
This…
Hurry, hurry, go back.
Quickly, now!
My lady, Lady Jieyu is calling for you.
Don't keep the noble waiting.
Greetings, Lady Jieyu.
Why don't I see Xian here?
I didn't report earlier to spare worry.
Since you asked, I'll tell you the truth.
My husband returned home with me.
He drank too much at the feast.
He fell down the stairs.
We asked Liu, a renowned bone physician,
to see him.
His injuries were swollen.
Liu realigned his bones.
He prescribed an ancestral remedy.
One topical ointment to wash daily
and an internal formula taken with wine.
His skilled hands worked wonders.
After three days, he improved a lot.
But today's travel made him worse.
I tried to convince him,
Lady Jieyu is his sister.
She'll never blame him.
That's why he's resting in his room.
I apologize for his absence on his behalf.
How could he fall for no reason?
Clearly, the Li family caused this.
Don't misbehave in front of Lady Jieyu.
We're all family. No need for formalities.
My poor son.
He married such a woman.
It's truly a family misfortune.
Daughter,
you must punish her for your brother.
Please seek justice for us.
Don't let this evil wife get away with it.
Slap her 50 times to teach her respect.
Oh no, she's going to accuse me later.
I might seize that weak one
before she retaliates.
There's no going back to my home.
Worst case, I'll cut my hair and be a nun.
Your imperial family rules everything,
but not the world outside.
Bring it.
Open it.
This golden rod is from His Majesty.
It's yours now.
This…
Thank you, my Lady.
Lady Jieyu,
you're not here for justice.
You're encouraging her arrogance.
His Majesty mentioned promoting my father.
I told him
officials should earn promotions.
It can't just be
because of his favor for me.
Making exceptions and asking for favors
would cause criticism.
This cannot happen.
You…
You don't care about me
or our family?
I care for the family.
That's why I refuse.
The Yang family
already has wealth and honor.
Not from the great talent
of my brother and father,
but from the ladies
who married into the palace.
If your fate
relies on fragile connections,
how can you forget what you have
and dream about more?
You're accusing your own father?
That's out of line.
Apologize to Lady Jieyu.
Forgive us, Lady Jieyu.
Since ancient times,
family disgrace
starts with neglecting rules.
Leshan, this golden rod is for you.
Use it to set the Yang family straight.
One day, if someone ever
commit crimes and bully others,
no matter if it is your husband
or your brothers-in-law,
even your parents-in-law,
you have the right to discipline them.
This is not only my decision.
His Majesty approves.
Lady Jieyu, you're so just and wise.
I'm deeply grateful.
Get up.
GENTLE BREEZE AND PLEASANT MOON
Master.
But your injuries…
Sure.
SPRING BREEZE AND AUTUMN MOON
Lady Jieyu, why don't you go in?
He doesn't want to see his sister.
Out of the four of us siblings,
he was always closest to me.
When Father sent me to the palace,
the family was overjoyed,
except him.
He came at night,
trying to help me escape.
Father nearly broke his legs for that.
He was bedridden for six months.
Leshan,
my brother wasn't always this way,
spoiled by Mother, beaten by Father,
but no one ever
taught him right from wrong.
Let me ask you a favor.
Guide him in the future.
Don't let him go astray or get ruined.
Lady Jieyu,
teaching morals
is a family's responsibility.
I'm just a taken woman. I wouldn't dare.
If you can reform him,
a year from now,
if you wish to leave the family,
I'll request His Majesty personally
to grant your divorce.
You mean it?
Let's make a deal.
Okay, deal.
Since you care about him so much,
why not go in and see him?
Lady Jieyu, it's time to return.
Li Leshan.
Don't forget your promise.
If you fail,
you'll stay here forever.
I'll leave here, no matter what.
What an ungrateful girl.
She's never been on my side.
If she wasn't sent to the palace,
she wouldn't have such glory.
We worked hard for her future,
but she repays us with resentment.
Helping that wicked woman to bully me.
Unbelievable. Absolutely unbelievable.
Father shouldn't have sent her
to the palace.
He should've sent me instead.
She is talented in music and art,
smart, poised,
and favored by Her Highness.
What about you?
Sister, I'm better at many things.
- Enough.
- So--
Instead of finding a solution,
you two are having squabbles.
How useless.
Mom,
what if she loses that rod?
An imperial gift. She'd guard it fiercely.
How could she lose it?
Bad idea. She wouldn't fear that.
But this could be serious.
She could be charged
with disrespecting the royal family.
It's a big deal.
Once we have this against her,
we control her life or death.
Even a fierce tigress would bow
before Mom after that.
Go, bring Yinping here.
Master, does it still hurt?
I don't mean to meddle,
but you and the lady just don't mix.
Even the smallest thing causes trouble.
It's better to stay away from her.
Master,
my brother once broke his leg.
I massaged him often
to make walking easier.
Would you like me to help?
My lady.
If I see you acting like this again,
I'll cut off that hand first.
Qiansheng!
Qiansheng.
Where did everyone go?
My lady, Master.
Listen up, everyone.
From now on,
only male servants may attend here.
Maids in the courtyard must obey me.
No one enters here without orders.
If he bothers a maid, let me know.
I'll handle it.
But if anyone
flirts or oversteps
or ever tries to lure him out for treats,
bully others, and act immorally…
If I hear that,
I'll smash them
with this golden rod.
Li Haode,
do you dare interfere with me?
Don't tell me you're jealous too.
I've always been dominant.
Even my dog
must only wag its tail for me.
No one else is allowed.
And my husband is mine to control.
So, naturally,
I'll watch over him closely, always.
You…
What?
From today,
you're under my care.
Got a problem?
Whatever.
Everyone, clear?
Sure.
Master Jiang.
Madam is calling you.
Sure. I'll take my leave now.
Don't take it too fast.
Honey cakes are delicious.
The sesame outside smells amazing.
And the inside is so soft.
Better than what I eat here.
Of course.
I made these myself.
I didn't let them do it,
worried they'd overcook it.
I'm glad you like it.
My mother came to visit me.
Even your mom left.
She wants us to have some private time.
Why are you here?
Don't be naughty.
Mom.
Enough.
Yang Xian, tell me.
Has she treated you well?
If she has been neglecting you,
I'll handle it.
Mom, who is really your child?
Don't worry, Madam.
I'm getting better.
Don't be careless.
Injuries to bones take time to heal.
If you don't take care,
it could get worse.
When you get older, it will hurt terribly.
- Bone soup.
- Okay.
I also made you some bone soup.
Drink some.
Subtitle translation by: Yi Yang