EPISODE 3
SIFU HOUSE
I can't believe you.
Why are you being like this?
I kindly let you consign your zither here.
Now that the zither has been reserved
and the deposit has been paid,
you want to take it back?
What am I supposed to say to the buyer?
In three days, the buyer
will come with the money.
Can't you wait another three days?
I planned to stay in Bianjing
for two months
but ran out of money.
That's why the zither is for consignment.
I received a letter from home yesterday,
saying my mother has fallen ill
and is eagerly waiting for my return.
Let alone three days,
I can't wait one day more.
You seem to be educated.
How can you go back on your word?
We received the buyer's deposit
and waiting for them to pick up.
If we can't hand over the zither,
how can we continue to do business
on this street?
- I…
- That can't happen.
I won't allow that.
- Give it to me.
- Stop that.
Well, Mr. Liao.
Why are you quarreling
with a customer in the street?
Madam.
- That man's outrageous. No credibility.
- Gentlemen, may I have your attention?
I put my zither Bingqing here temporarily
for consignment.
I don't want to sell it,
but they won't let me take it back.
I am the owner.
What they are doing is simply robbery!
Bingqing? Isn't it a Lei zither
from the Tang dynasty?
It's by the Lei family
in Shu prefecture.
Exactly. Please take a look.
It says, "On the third day of the third
lunar month of Dali Era's third year,
made by the Lei family in Shu prefecture."
It is indeed the genuine famous zither,
Bingqing.
- It's a fine zither.
- Madam.
- Can you--
- Here is the thing,
I thought that shabby zither
- was worth 30 strings.
- You shall see it for yourself.
But just yesterday, a rich customer came
and offered this amount right away.
- Fifty strings?
- Fifty?
No, 300 strings.
That shabby zither is worth 300 strings?
I heard the buyer has been collecting
items from 40 or 50 years ago
for the family of the Transport Envoy
of Guangdong.
He has also collected
many paintings and calligraphy arts.
He insisted on having this zither.
I told him that the seller
had made it clear beforehand
he wouldn't sell
if they don't appreciate it.
We made a deal
that the seller must be notified
before the zither was picked up.
The buyer set the contract,
left 30 strings, and left.
This shabby zither
isn't worth that much money.
Who are they trying to fool?
What the heart cherishes
can't be bought with a fortune.
This is my first time seeing Lei zither.
How about you sell it to me
for 40 strings?
- Forty?
- Sell it to me for 40 strings.
Sixty-five.
Sixty-eight.
- 68 is a good price.
- 80.
- That's a lot.
- You…
- 100 strings.
- How much?
- That much?
- You…
This is an exorbitant price.
Do you have the money?
This is an astronomical price.
Sir,
doing business is all about reputation.
We have received the buyer's deposit.
- That's right.
- We can't just go back on our word.
How about this? Name a price.
I will make the decision to buy it.
Well…
Just name a price.
I like this smell.
Lady, look at this.
This one has a unique design.
This one looks even better.
OFFERING ALL KINDS OF TEA
It matches the color of your clothes.
- Here.
- Not bad.
- It smells good.
- Have a try.
You can try this.
It smells so good,
and the scent is quite special.
This one also smells very good.
Then, I'll take this one.
- I want this one.
- Alright.
Young lady, take a look
at this indigo-colored sachet.
- It suits you more.
- This scent is quite nice.
SIFU HOUSE
This one is good too.
Mother, why are you crying?
What's going on?
- Why are you crying now?
- Mother!
- What's wrong?
- What happened?
Mother, why are you crying?
What's wrong? What happened?
Just tell us.
Everything can be shared between us.
Mother, just tell us.
The dowry…
- What about the dowry?
- The dowry…
I think I know.
The shop brought in a famous zither
at a high price.
Mother has been waiting for days, but the
customer with the deposit hasn't shown.
Mother, could it be
that you have been scammed?
Yes, they were a bunch of scammers!
How much did you spend?
- One hundred…
- What?
It's just a zither.
It's worth ten to 20 strings at most.
You spent 100?
No one will be fooled like that.
It's 180 strings.
Hundred and eighty strings?
Mother, last time I asked you
for a hairpin,
you even thought 180 coins were too much,
and now, we are talking about 180 strings.
Mr. Liao said someone
would pay 300 strings for that zither.
And those scammers kept saying
that it was a treasure
and a cherished item
that's worth a big fortune.
As soon as I heard them,
I got dizzy and my vision blurred.
It's like my mouth wasn't even my own.
I just asked the price directly.
Most of the money from selling the land
has been spent on the shop.
Now I lost 180 strings.
That's the dowry for all of you.
Those scammers should be cursed.
It's like stabbing my heart
with a knife.
- Every time I think of it…
- Alright, alright.
…it's like another stab.
Mother, we are familiar
with perfumes and flowers.
But not antiques, paintings,
and calligraphy arts.
Last year, we set up a counter
for the trend,
and it attracted many regulars
who love the flea market.
Didn't we agree
not to buy in valuable items?
How could you change that so easily?
I bet those few are all in cahoots.
Where is Mr. Liao?
And the zither?
I gave Mr. Liao
a bout of scolding and drove him away.
Afterwards, I still felt angry.
I wanted to find an axe
and cut that zither into firewood,
but I couldn't find the axe.
So, I just threw the zither away
at some place.
You threw it away?
Chunlai, go over there and look.
Kangning,
maybe someone has already taken it.
Maybe we should stop looking and go back.
Mother said when she threw the zither,
the night market hadn't ended yet.
Maybe it's still here.
Mother saved up for a long time
to get those 180 strings.
How could we just give up like this?
This is strange.
Mother said she threw it here.
Where could it be?
Do you hear that?
Kangning, are we not looking anymore?
Chai,
don't think you can get away with this.
XIANGGUO TEMPLE
Come and take a look at the flowers.
They are here.
Do you think it will work?
Mother, I've heard that Madam Chai
always prays on fasting days.
Be it monks or Taoists, none are spared
her devotion. She is very pious.
Just do as I taught you.
It will work.
Alright.
- Then I'll go.
- Go.
Thank you for blessing us, Bodhisattva.
What's going on?
Thank you.
- Thank you, Bodhisattva.
- We have
- five girls waiting for marriage.
- Please, Bodhisattva.
- A few days ago…
- Thank you.
…she came
to worship the Bodhisattva and pray for
good marriages for her daughters.
Her prayers have been heard.
Now, we are here to thank the Bodhisattva.
Thank you, Bodhisattva.
Is it true they've all gotten married?
Is this a deception or what?
- I'd be a donkey to deceive you.
- Thank you.
Is it really so effective?
I don't know how many times I've kowtowed,
how many bridges I've repaired,
and how many roads I've paved.
My wishes have not been answered yet.
How could a commoner have such blessings?
- Go ask her again.
- Yes.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you for fulfilling my wishes.
- Madam, can you tell me more?
It's a magical encounter
that our lady had.
I don't know more.
Madam, please.
Alright.
Since you are so sincere,
I'll tell you, but only you.
Okay.
That day,
after we prayed to the Bodhisattva here,
we were guided by the Bodhisattva.
We met an old immortal.
- An old immortal?
- Yes.
Thank you for blessing us, Bodhisattva.
Thank you.
Thank you for fulfilling my wishes.
You have suffered, Mother.
Are you alright?
How is it? Will it work?
Let's wait and see.
And we got this.
Stop here.
Hurry. Stop here.
Make way at the front.
Why are you blocking the way?
Our lady'd like to ask you
some questions.
Is it the Third Lady Kangning
in the sedan chair?
Master Chai,
- have our families had any feuds?
- No.
- Have we made enemies recently?
- No, we haven't.
If that's the case,
why did you conspire with Mr. Liao
to deceive my mother?
Didn't you and your sisters
also deceive Fan Lianghan?
Master Fan and my second sister
are a married couple.
We are a family.
There is no such thing as deceiving,
but understandable humor.
Fan Lianghan is my cousin.
He is also my family.
It's only right and proper
that I seek justice for him.
Master Chai, are you determined
to give my family a hard time?
That's not true.
Although I am no gentleman,
I disdain to trouble women and children.
Deqing.
What are you doing in broad daylight?
Be careful, or we'll report you.
Third Lady, the antique business
is often fraught with deceit,
and your family is new here.
You'll inevitably attract jealous eyes.
I did this just to remind you.
Business is not easy in Bianjing.
You must be extremely careful from now on.
Do not be credulous or greedy for money.
You need to stay grounded
and avoid being rash and impulsive.
If someone employs tricks
on you again in the future,
presumably, you won't fall for them.
You still don't get it?
My master heard that someone
was going to target your family,
so he warned you in advance.
Now that you've learned your lesson,
you can have the money back.
Let's go.
Chunlai, give it to me.
That man is so strange.
Why are there 40 strings less?
My master said that the 30 strings
of interest money must be repaid,
and you have to pay the rent for our
shopkeeper, calligraphy, and paintings.
Villain!
We don't need you to give us the warning.
It was clearly deliberate mockery.
We didn't go to you,
yet you came to me.
Fine, then bask in your pleasure
a little longer.
Let's see if you can
stay this way afterwards.
Mother,
I'm back.
You are finally back.
You run around all day.
Even I have to send someone
to fetch you when I want to see you.
I got held up a few days ago.
Please forgive me, Mother.
Has anything good happened?
I haven't seen you this joyful in a while.
With you always striving for better,
I don't worry a bit about the businesses,
except for one thing.
- You know it.
- Mother.
Why are you bringing it up again?
I have my own plans
about my marriage.
What plans could you possibly have?
Stop putting me off
by making excuses.
It's been years.
Even that good-for-nothing Fan Lianghan
got married before you.
How can I be at peace?
I know you're with high aspirations.
When your father was here, he wished you'd
marry a lady from a scholar's family.
Since you agreed,
you will keep your promise.
Rest assured. That wish will be fulfilled
at the latest by next year.
Why is that?
I met an old immortal
on my way out yesterday.
He travels to all places,
only to raise money
to repair a Taoist temple.
As long as I donate some money,
you'll be able to marry a wife next year.
Mother, immortals
are supposed to be in temples.
Since when do you see them
running in the streets?
Why have you started
believing in such street swindlers?
The streets are bustling
with ordinary mortals.
He couldn't be an immortal.
He was a true immortal.
Before I even spoke, he knew my wishes
and the situation of our family.
Every word he said was precise.
I don't care.
I promised to donate money
for the temple's building.
I've already made the donation.
Giving out wealth is a blessing.
If you wish to donate for inner peace,
then let it be.
Okay.
How much did you donate?
I wanted to donate more,
but he wouldn't take it.
I didn't donate much. Only 180 strings.
PAN RESTAURANT
Sir.
- That Third Lady sent a message.
- What is it?
She wants to thank you
for your generous donation.
It only took 100 coins
to thank the immortal.
The rest has been returned in full.
She wants you to remember
that however clever you are,
there is always someone more clever.
- You shouldn't…
- Shouldn't what?
You shouldn't act pompous and arrogant,
which makes you a person of narrow view.
Move closer.
SIFU HOUSE
My lady,
they've returned the money to us,
saying it's just a tad of money,
and it's not significant.
They even said that if you fancy it,
you can buy yourself some flowers with it.
That's cheeky.
They can't admit defeat,
but mock us instead.
This is sarcasm
about my family being poor.
We can't take a coin
of the ill-gotten wealth.
Otherwise, for what you take today,
they'll take a hundredfold back
from you later.
Come here.
- Come.
- Young lady!
- Thank you, young lady!
- There's enough for both.
- Okay.
- Don't fight over the money.
- Thank you!
You have the heart of a Bodhisattva.
Thank you, young lady!
Alright.
They are giving away our money, my master.
Let's go. Hurry.
Let's go buy something tasty.
Young master!
What? You could deceive her,
but she couldn't deceive you?
Anyway, I gave her the money.
Besides, Mother wants that money
to be used for good deeds.
Weren't they just doing good deeds?
So, that's it? You will do nothing?
As a lady of the inner chamber,
she knows not to touch unrighteous wealth.
It makes me admire her a bit more.
However,
acting so rashly and impetuously will lead
to great losses for her in the future.
Master Chai.
I went to Dongji'er Lane to see Lu Yanyan.
I begged and pleaded,
offering all sorts of jewelry,
brocades, and fine gauze.
Finally, she agreed
to attend the banquet at Pan.
You need to buy me
half a year's worth of liquor.
Young master, Master Yang came again.
He cursed away three, four companions
and drank two jars of wine quietly.
I wonder if he will cause trouble.
YANG XIAN
Leave him be.
Master Chai.
Master Chai,
when the Mid-Autumn comes…
Please hear me out.
I see. I have things to do today.
Let's talk another day.
Master Chai.
What's going on?
It's purely bad timing.
My master is in a bad mood.
He can't get the bellyful of anger
out of his chest.
- What happened?
- My master is magnanimous.
He doesn't stoop to fight with a woman.
Forget about it.
You didn't hear me saying anything.
Tell me about it. You never know.
I may be able to help him
get this sullenness out.
It's her again.
I still have that slap
on my account.
The beef wasn't settled yet.
Exactly.
Even if you search all Bianjing,
you won't find a second one
as shrewish as she is.
I don't think that's true.
There are six tigresses in the Li family.
A profound family heritage.
What on earth are you singing?
There is no strength in your singing.
Get lost.
No hurry. I'll go take a look.
Deqing. Deqing.
Yes, sir?
Give the order.
I want the new wine gathering
before Mid-Autumn to be grand and lively.
I'd like all of Bianjing to come and see,
so we can take down the arrogance
of Sifu House.
Okay.
SIFU HOUSE
MID-AUTUMN DAY
THE 15TH DAY OF THE EIGHTH LUNAR MONTH
They are washed quite thoroughly.
Our business is starting
to look promising.
We must be more attentive
during the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Be careful.
Be a bit more careful.
Everyone, be quick about it.
- Here.
- We know, Mother.
Come on. Be quicker about it.
- Careful.
- There won't be mistakes.
- Alright.
- Just rest assured.
Chunlai,
put these in place neatly.
This area needs to be sorted out.
Okay.
Jiang.
You need to trim the tree and the flower.
- Trim them to make them look nicer.
- Okay.
This area is done.
This needs to be taken care of.
You can't take down this painting.
Many people come for this genuine piece.
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Scholars will be inspired to write poetry
after drinking some wine.
We can offer some cheap brushes and ink,
so that they can
write a poem or compose a verse
on this blank wall.
During next year's Spring Examination,
if someone becomes the Number One Scholar,
this will become
the Number One Scholar's Wall.
To write a poem on it,
you must be a famous or talented scholar.
That's a good idea.
They're full of boasting on ordinary days.
Now I'd like to see
which of them has genuine talent.
I will take them as my son-in-law.
Dear daughter, you are so intelligent.
I'll listen to you.
What are you doing?
I'll keep this painting for you.
Mother, we need to return this painting.
Well, he openly steals my business.
So what if I keep his painting?
Mother, we can't keep this painting.
Mother.
PAN RESTAURANT
It's a rare sight.
We did the right thing coming here.
Exactly.
It's a feast for the eyes.
That's right.
It is so different.
It's thanks to Master Chai
- for coming up with the idea.
- Yes.
We've waited for this for a long time.
Raise the signboard.
Nice move.
Truly impressive.
- Bravo!
THE BEST IN BIANJING
Great move.
Good skills. Such talent.
I wonder whether the wine is good.
Right. How's the wine?
Ladies and gentlemen, the host
doesn't boast about
whether the wine is good.
You can taste and find out yourselves.
This year, as the new owner
of Pan Restaurant,
not only do I invite you
to taste the wine,
but I also invite everyone in Bianjing
to come and try the Jade Wine
to see whether it's good or not.
- Bravo!
Please welcome the best courtesan.
- Bravo.
- It's the best courtesan.
She is here.
Lu Yanyan!
- Lu Yanyan!
- The best courtesan.
She's looking at me.
- She's looking at me.
- Lu Yanyan!
- She is so beautiful.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Over here.
Pan Restaurant is launching
its new wine today.
Come on.
Come to Pan Restaurant
and try the new wine.
This method isn't bad.
- The smell of the wine disperses fast.
- Pan's new wine!
Pan Restaurant is launching a new wine.
- Come and taste. Try it.
- Come on.
- Pan Restaurant is launching a new wine.
- Here. Try it.
Here. Try it.
- Pan is launching a new wine.
- Pan is launching a new wine today.
Everyone, come and show support.
Pan Restaurant
is launching a new wine today.
Everyone, come and have a try.
- Look.
- Try some.
Here. Try some.
- Try it.
- Okay.
- Here, try it.
- Thank you.
Everyone, come and try it.
You're welcomed to come and try!
Pan Restaurant is launching a new wine.
Come and try it.
Master Wang, you are here.
- Got a pot of Jade Wine for you.
- Good.
Been expecting you. Come.
- Congratulations.
Welcome.
- It's so grand.
- Let's go out and see.
No wonder they are so extravagant.
Sir, you always have good ideas.
With the parade going around the city,
all hear the news.
Please come in.
Deqing.
Take down the wine sign in the afternoon.
Tell the guests
today's Jade Wine is sold out
and they can come early tomorrow.
Okay.
Mother, stop watching.
Let's go back to business.
There is no business at all.
We got up before dawn
and have been busy until now,
all for today's business.
All the people on this street
have been lured away by him.
There is no business at all.
Liang was right.
She somewhat resembles the portrait.
It's just she's too far away.
I can't see her clearly either.
Haode and Leshan
have gone out to play again.
Kangning,
you stay for the business.
I'll go look for those two.
Chunlai, go with her.
Please.
Congratulations.
- Please.
- Congratulations.
Please come in.
Young master,
Master Liu from Daming Prefecture
ordered 200 jars of Jade Wine.
He is the most anxious to get it.
I feel we can't reason with him.
- I'll go take a look.
- Okay.
Deqing.
My mother will come too.
Wait at the door.
Then lead her to the pavilion,
to avoid the crowds.
Understood. Rest assured, sir.
- Please come inside.
- This way.
Good idea. You are the most ingenious one.
- Hurry and ask the cook to prepare.
- Okay.
Our shop has a new shuanglu game.
No, thank you.
- Master Wang, a game of shuanglu?
- Let's go drink up front.
It's harmful to your health
if you drink too much wine.
- Been a long time. Why--
- No. I'm going to Pan Restaurant.
Come here. We have shuanglu.
- I'll go to Pan Restaurant too.
- There's nothing there.
We have set up a shuanglu game
at our place.
We have a new shuanglu game at our place.
- Come, join us at Sifu--
- I'm heading to Pan Restaurant.
What's so good about it?
It was her. She swindled my money.
This is bad.
Take her to the officials.
What are you doing?
What's going on? What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What?
Fellow citizens, come and take a look.
Relying on her money,
someone here is bullying us
because we are not locals
who have no backing or support.
What's going on?
In broad daylight, how can you bully her?
Yes, indeed.
Listen to me. Let's not get physical.
Let me reason with you.
It's not too late to get physical
if words fail.
Exactly.
You shameless vulgar woman
and lying swindler!
Shut her mouth!
W-Who's the swindler?
Go shut her mouth quickly.
- You say I'm a swindler?
- What's going on?
I'm not a swindler.
You say I'm a swindler?
- Quick, stop her.
- I'm not a swindler.
Who are you calling a swindler?
You say I'm a swindler?
Who's a swindler, huh?
Say it.
Who are you calling a swindler?
- You say I'm a swindler?
- Mother!
- What's the matter?
- It's alright.
- Let's go home.
- Go away.
Listen to me.
I am naturally fierce.
Even if ten of your men come at me,
when I'm provoked,
I will make you
turn into clawless crabs one by one.
- Who is the swindler, huh?
- Move aside.
- Who is the swindler?
- Enough, Mother.
What are you doing? Let's go back.
- Mother!
- Stop fighting.
Mother! Mother!
Mother, stop fighting.
Calm down, Mother.
My apologies. Don't take offense.
Stop fighting.
- Mother, let's go back.
- Calm down.
Third Lady, quickly take your mother.
Mind your own business.
- Enough, Mother.
- Let's go.
Let's go back to the pavilion first.
- This isn't over!
- Let's go back to the pavilion first.
Mother, our own business
is more important.
She is right.
Let's go.
- Disperse.
- Let's go.
- Disperse now.
Stop looking.
You gave me a fright.
Let's go.
There's a new trick again.
Come on.
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Baifan Restaurant, Taiping Restaurant,
and Chunfeng Restaurant all sell new wine.
As the saying goes,
"One cup of wine and the fierce tiger
lie in the mountains,
and two cups and the dragon sleeps
in the sea depths."
If you have three cups,
I assure you your guts
will be turning upside down.
To those passing by,
have a bowl of our shop's hangover soup.
I guarantee you'll get less scolding
when you get home.
The dark plum and osmanthus hangover soup
quenches thirst and refreshes you
with a fragrant aroma.
It costs only three coins per bowl.
It's very cheap.
It smells good. I'll have a bowl.
- I'll have one too.
- Please, come this way.
Three coins per bowl.
- It's very cheap.
- Only three coins per bowl.
Madam Li,
you've hidden away
such a beautiful daughter.
Willing to let her serve drinks,
you must be earning a vast fortune.
Exactly.
If you keep spewing nonsense,
I'll gouge out those toad eyes of yours
and put them in the hangover soup
to boil them together.
- I was kidding.
- My third daughter.
Hangover soup! Hangover soup!
The incredibly aromatic hangover soup!
Osmanthus hangover soup!
There is enough for everyone. Be patient.
It looked so bad
in the middle of the street.
Mother.
Mother, come on.
Sit here.
Well, well.
How dare you do business trampling us?
Send some people quickly
to take down that vulgar woman.
Mother, it's not a big deal.
Doing that will make us all look bad.
Just let it go.
I've lived for most of my life
as a decent and respectful person.
Today, because
of that ignorant, vulgar woman,
I've lost all my dignity.
If you take yourself as my son,
quickly send out people
- to smash her shop…
- Mother.
…and immediately take her to the officials
to vent my anger.
Have you forgotten?
It's Mid-Autumn Festival.
The officials are celebrating
the festival. Sit.
There's no reason in involving
the officials over this trifle, right?
Madam Li has been a widow for many years,
raising several daughters by herself.
It's said she was bullied by relatives
in the countryside of Luoyang.
That's why she had to sell her land
and come to Bianjing.
If you truly take issue with her,
it'd seem as if our family
is bullying them with our power.
Besides, the Li family
is Lianghan's in-laws.
You should consider him and his family.
If you had them arrested,
how would Aunt Fan feel about it?
- But she…
- Mother.
Upon seeing her, I can't help
but remember the years
when my father just passed away
and how you endured hardships
to raise me
and manage the family's affairs.
So, I always feel
a bit of compassion for her.
She is someone with a crude manner,
while you're a well-educated
and mannered person known far and wide.
Considering the hardships
of a widow and her daughters,
please do not take issues with her.
Alright?
All right, Mother.
- She has daughters waiting to be married.
- Right.
And she doesn't accumulate virtue
for their sake.
She was that rude, fierce, and indecent.
Within two days,
the whole of Bianjing will know.
- Yes, you are right.
- If it were me,
I would rather die without an heir
than to ever seek such a daughter-in-law.
You're right. Calm down, Mother.
Take my mother home.
- I'll go back when I'm done here.
- Yes.
Just calm down.
Don't be angry anymore, Mother.
Don't be angry anymore.
Stop there.
Under the Emperor's feet,
in a clear and civilized age,
who are you scoundrels
dare to tease a respectable lady?
The Emperor?
Coincidentally,
the one sitting on the throne
happens to be my brother-in-law,
if it comes to that.
You tell me,
what kind of "scoundrel" am I?
Don't bother with him. Let's go.
- You…
- Don't be afraid, young lady.
Women are not to my liking.
Even the most beautiful woman
is just a piece of wood in my eyes.
I made a bet that within ten days,
I must find the person in this painting.
Otherwise, I would lose a manor to him.
Young lady,
let me take a good look at you.
I won't give you any trouble.
I'll give you ten taels of gold instead.
- Come, don't move.
- What are you doing? Let go.
- He has money on him.
- Young lady!
- What are you doing?
- Don't touch me.
Let go of your dirty hands.
- Young master!
- Get off!
- What are you doing?
- Are you all blind?
Do you know who I am?
- Don't touch me.
- Let go!
- Careful, sir.
- This is fine material.
I want that jade pendant!
- My belt!
- It's mine now.
- My belt.
Stop.
- Be careful, young master.
- You've torn my clothes.
Sis, let's go.
All of you, back off. Go after her.
- Don't touch me. Hands off.
- Take the clothes.
- Young master!
- Don't touch me.
Let's go. Quickly.
Young master, are you alright?
Sir?
What are you laughing at? Stop looking.
Go away.
You with the veil, stop right there.
Pah!
Stop looking.
What are you looking at?
Give me your clothes.
Stop looking.
- Hurry up.
- Sir.
All of you, go away.
Stop laughing, all of you.
What are you still waiting for?
Go after her quickly.
Hurry up.
I have always been the one
bullying others.
Li family, I'll remember you.
- Slow down.
- It's truly beautiful tonight.
- I want to sit on this side.
- Then I'll sit here.
I'll do the cutting today.
- I'll cut it.
- Last time, you did the cutting.
Don't fight over it
with your elder sister.
I'll cut it.
Then you do it.
What part do you want?
- I want to eat the filling inside.
- Then who will eat the crust?
- You eat it.
- I don't want the crust.
- I want the filling.
- Cut it quickly.
This is too hard.
I can't cut it. You do it.
It has to be me in the end.
Leshan, what's that new style
on your head?
I've heard that inside the palace,
Consort Shang and Consort Yang
are the most favored.
They compete with each other
both openly and secretly.
Consort Shang loves
pearl decorations in her makeup.
It has been very popular
in the city recently.
How is it? Doesn't it look good?
Tell me. Where did you find
such fine pearls?
Mother, you've been
subsidizing her secretly again.
I want pearls too.
I'll pluck some off you.
You… Open your mouth.
Where are the pearls?
You're the worst.
Mother.
Fuhui.
Didn't you say you'd spend the Festival
with the Fan's and come back tomorrow?
Second sister.
Our beloved little five
has offended that lawless Master Yang.
Even your brother-in-law can't save you.
Get up quickly. Go packing upstairs.
I'll send you away to stay out of trouble.
Big sis, you have to go as well.
Bianjing is really different.
Anyone you bump into outside
is either rich or noble.
So, Master Yang
comes from a distinguished family.
So what if he is an official?
If he dares to come at our door,
I'll chase him away with a door bolt.
Mother.
He's far more fearsome than any official.
His elder sister
is Consort Yang,
who is most favored by His Majesty.
In the palace, she is even
more prestigious than the Empress.
His Majesty appointed their grandfather
as the governor of Guizhou just now
and will grant Master Young a position.
If he were hurt in any way,
Consort Yang will be furious.
They'll hold our family accountable.
Mother, for our sisters' sake,
promise me that you won't act rashly.
Is it really that serious?
Now is not the time to ask.
Leshan, I will help you pack.
Just leave to avoid the trouble.
If he intends to seek revenge,
I'm afraid it's too late to leave now.
Fuhui, did you look around
before you entered?
Thirty.
Forty.
Indeed, some are missing.
Master Yang,
you insisted
that you lost your pouch in our shop,
but the pouch is right here.
And no one
has touched a single pearl in it.
Make sure you count them well.
Originally, there were
a hundred large pearls in this pouch.
Now, half of them are gone.
If they weren't taken by your shop,
could they have just flown away?
You need evidence to back your words.
Evidence?
My words are the evidence.
You…
Right in front of everyone's eyes,
you took half a bag of my pearls.
Your Sifu House is clearly a shady shop.
Let's take it up with the authorities.
But I accept negotiation.
Bring me the young lady
who robbed me that day.
Have her kowtow to me.
Maybe I'll be pleased
and let you off the hook.
Otherwise, we'll see you in court.
Once this lawsuit begins,
it could last three to six months.
You'll be locked up, and the shop
will be sealed for investigation.
You all better think it through.
Which one of us are you looking for, sir?
Third Lady, don't go.
Who let you out? Hurry and go back.
Not you. Call out the one
from the bridge that day.
What? Not me that you are looking for?
Then it is my mistake.
Or perhaps you have the wrong address?
It's this canopy hat.
It was you. There is no mistake.
What exactly do you want?
Your daughter disrobed me in public
and tarnished my reputation.
She can either join my house
or apologize with her death.
But it's a life after all.
I've decided to take her as my concubine.
- These are the betrothal gifts.
- You…
Mother.
Have you forgotten what Fuhui said?
I will take it as a "yes" from you.
A verbal agreement is no guarantee.
Let's take this skirt as proof.
Three days later,
I'll deliver the betrothal gifts on time.
Young lady, you must wait for me.
Let's go.
What…
Where is Leshan?
I've locked her up.
Sis, if you do this for me,
I will never sleep tight ever again.
I don't want you to worry.
I'll go talk to him.
If you go to him,
I'm afraid there'll be bloodshed.
If you step out of this door,
you're abandoning your mother
and sisters.
You promised to hold your temper.
Are you trying to make me mad?
I'll go to the government and accuse him
of forcing a civilian to become concubine.
Now that the Yang family
is at the height of its power,
who would dare to take this lawsuit?
Even if someone takes it,
it will be delayed and hidden.
How could we be saved
from this imminent danger?
That heartless Yang Xian
took away your skirt.
If it's brought before the court,
your innocence might as well be discarded.
Third Lady, what should we do?
Let alone a pouch of pearls,
even if it were a mountain of gold,
we couldn't agree
to that kind of scoundrel's request.
PAN RESTAURANT
I have told you
all the details of the matter.
Please do everything you can
to dispel Yang Xian's
malicious intentions.
Thank you, cousin.
You want me to help her?
Will the Third Lady appreciate it?
My mother had a dispute with Madam Li.
I'm afraid she might think
I go only to mock her.
She might kick me out.
Unless she asks me for help personally,
then I will do my utmost to help her.
- If you wish to meet her--
- No, I just can't stand injustices
and want to help her out.
Previously,
she was arrogant and disrespectful.
Now that she's in trouble,
she has to seek help from you.
If you ask me, you should not
get involved in this matter.
- Let them cry out.
- Be quiet.
She's my cousin's in-law,
so she's also related to me.
If I didn't help her in a crucial moment,
what kind of person would I be then?
When meeting him later,
be patient
and say a few good words.
You must not be willful anymore
and bring trouble upon me.
- Do you hear me?
- Of course.
Subtitle translation by: Grace Zhao