EPISODE 22
SHEN MANSION
This is your second uncle's wife.
This is your third uncle's wife.
This is your fourth uncle's wife.
They are all your elders.
Just call them aunts.
STUDY THE NATURE OF THINGS
Greetings, aunts.
I pay my respects to you all.
I heard that Huizhao is seriously ill.
I am extremely worried,
so I came to visit today.
I wonder if he has gotten any better.
Right. Rumors say he has injured his head.
If there's a blood clot,
it could be life-threatening.
Is that true?
I wonder where the rumors came from,
and it has worried you all.
He just has some minor external injuries.
He'll go to the yamen
to deal with affairs soon.
Old Lady, since ancient times,
a rumor starts with one person,
but it can spread
through the city unstopped.
It's futile, no matter how much you deny.
We might as well
take advantage of this time
to make arrangements
for the Flower Festival
and show everyone
that Huizhao is fine and healthy.
Look, I have thought it through.
On the day of the Spring coming,
we would rearrange the pond pavilions,
terrace, flowers, and trees.
The peonies in the garden are flourishing.
We could get more peonies,
peach, and plum trees.
Plant bamboo in the corner of the wall.
A beautiful scene can't be without bamboo.
Other families
would play cuju and game fowl,
so it'd be very noisy and lively.
But it actually makes others
lose interest in visiting the garden.
In my opinion, we can put
some antiques and accessories
for small betting games
in the southeast corner.
On the west side, we could set up archery
targets, pitching pots, and swing frames.
This could show
our attentiveness and hospitality.
Considering the reputation
of the Shen Garden in the capital,
we could make 20 or 30 strings
for tea money only.
During the Flower Festival,
we open our gardens to the public
in order to share the joy with everyone
and appreciate the beauty of spring.
The Shen family has never charged
a coin for tea.
Where does this vulgar commoner come from?
GUINIANG
SHENG MU
This is your aunt.
Greetings.
The gardeners and garden keepers
have to be busy for a month
during the Flower Festival.
This tea money is their reward.
Guiniang.
Hurry up. Come over here.
Come to me. Come here.
Grandmother, may you be in great health.
Spend more time with me this time.
Don't rush to leave.
- Yes.
- Liu.
Order someone
to clean up the Wutong Yard
where Guiniang lives.
We've cleaned it up every day.
- Rest assured
- Good.
It's been not even two months.
Guiniang has become even more beautiful.
Last year,
at the Jinming Pool Flower Festival,
many people wanted to know you.
That embroidered screen with flowers
you sent to my house
was seen by Madam Zhang
of the Imperial College.
She insisted on taking it away.
You'll have to embroider another one
for me later.
Yes.
Mother.
Why did you choose
such a wife for Huizhao?
Madam, please have some tea.
It's not me being picky.
The wedding was arranged too hastily.
They all look elegant but are mean inside.
Who are they trying to impress
with their pretense?
They are aiming against Haode.
If it were me,
I'd drag them out and beat them up,
these old hags.
Alright.
We've seen each other.
And I'm tired now.
I'm going back to take a nap.
Please make yourselves comfortable.
See you then, Old Lady.
Old Lady, I'll take you back.
You attend to the guests for me.
Guiniang.
You accompany me.
Yes.
Be careful.
I'll go see how
the preparation is for lunch.
I'll excuse myself.
She's already been
married into the family.
Why did you intentionally
make things difficult for her?
Mother has made a bad decision.
For the Li family's marriage alliance,
I've visited them again and again,
only then did they agree
to marry their daughter over.
Yet Huizhao just
called off the engagement.
I'm feeling very uncomfortable.
Fine.
It's alright if he married a lady
from a reputable family.
Out of all the girls,
he has to marry such a vulgar girl.
Tea money?
Mom, Haode is sensible,
and Leshan is clever.
They surely won't suffer a loss.
Before, I hope
my daughters to be obedient.
But after they get married, I want them
to be assertive and unruly.
A daughter-in-law will get bullied
if she's that sensible.
Haode has never been good
at arguing since childhood.
I need to see for myself to be at ease.
Tell him to hurry up.
Mom, it's right ahead.
There might be a distinguished guest.
Let's go around to the back door.
I'll just take a peek at Haode and go.
I don't want to cause any trouble.
Take a detour.
Here are the past two months of case files
organized by Judge Fang and Official Xia.
Please review.
There are so many case files.
So, I used to spend my days like this.
Is Haode still receiving guests?
What's the matter?
Today, the second, third,
and fourth uncle's wives all came.
And your aunt Madam Qiu.
She is the most difficult to deal with.
I think Lady Haode will have a hard time.
Aunt?
Those distinguished guests have arrived.
Everyone,
we have distinguished guests here.
- Invite them in now.
- Yes.
Mom told me to be tolerant.
Don't let others ridicule our Li family
not having proper family education.
When you go in there, just keep your calm
and not lose your temper.
Just let them talk. Ignore what they say.
If we talk back to elders,
we might be ridiculed.
Those despicable women! How dare they!
If you don't behave,
I'll send you back home tomorrow
and ask Mom to confine you.
I understand.
Let's go.
The Li family is selling tea,
famous in Bianjing
for their tea-making skills.
I was eager to see for myself,
so I invited you to make the tea.
Look.
She's really good at it,
much better than my tea-serving maid.
I wonder how many young ladies
there are in the Li family.
I have five daughters.
I heard that the eldest daughter
is married to a third-ranked scholar.
The second and third daughters
are married to wealthy families.
And there's no need to mention
the fourth daughter.
Madam Li, apart from
your skills in making tea,
you also have splendid strategies
to enable your daughters
to marry into prestigious families.
Why not share them with us?
Madame Qiu, didn't you
want to have some tea?
Why all the talking?
Aunt, if you'd like some tea,
I will make it for you.
Isn't your Li family the one selling tea
on Pan Restaurant?
What? Can't I have your tea?
- Haode.
- If you want to have the Li family's tea,
you must go to Sifu House
and spend some money.
Today, my mother has come as a guest.
Since you claim
to be on behalf of the Shen family,
we should treat her
as a guest with hospitality.
Please forgive me
to be humble and ignorant.
I have never heard of any host
to let the guest serve tea.
If this were to spread,
I'm afraid others might laugh at you
for being disrespectful
and lacking etiquette.
I was fully considering your position,
which is why I was bold to speak frankly.
I hope you don't mind.
H-how dare you!
How can you be so impolite to an elder?
My daughter-in-law
doesn't even dare to talk in front of me.
Do you know how to respect the elders?
What is this all about?
Huizhao, you are really recovered.
Those unpleasant words outside
are indeed just rumors.
Nothing. We are just joking.
Joking.
Aunts,
recently, the Kaifeng Court
has been ordered to arrest gamblers.
Offenders will be executed on the spot.
If Zhong and Huan dare go
to the gambling house again,
as their elder cousin,
I will show no mercy.
Dare not, definitely.
When I return,
I will strictly discipline them.
Huizhao, you are his close elder cousin.
Please take care of him.
I was unaware that you are here
and did not personally greet you.
Madam, please have this cup of tea
and forgive my rudeness.
Huizhao.
Not at all. You're always busy.
Have tea.
SHEN MANSION
Alright, there's no need to see me off.
Huizhao, save the formalities.
I can't accept this, really.
I can't accept it.
As a son-in-law,
I must pay my respects to you.
You must want to talk with Haode.
I dare not disturb you.
Since ancient times, women and men
should be matched for marriage.
Our family is indeed
not as prestigious as theirs.
I was afraid that you'll be wronged.
I didn't expect Huizhao
to be so protective of you.
Then I could be at ease.
It's okay. It's just a small case today.
I won't take it to heart at all.
But that Madam Qiu is his aunt.
She's a relative to him,
and it will never change.
Later on, apologize to her.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving, Huizhao.
I'm leaving.
- Go back.
- Be careful on the road.
Go back.
How do you remember about
the two cousins gambling?
Qingshi reported it.
I can't even recognize
who those two aunts are.
I heard it from him,
this aunt, though not
my grandmother's own daughter,
has been raised by her since childhood.
So, she's arrogant and spoiled.
I apologize for her being rude.
Considering you stood up for me,
I won't be mad anymore.
Having read the case files for so long,
you might be dizzy now.
Let me read for you.
Leshan.
Mom.
It's such a small deal.
Don't take it to heart.
What a man, Shen Huizhao.
He humiliated me for his mother-in-law.
If not for you, I wouldn't put up with it.
- What is this?
- Madam.
It's a gift sent from the Li family.
Including fine teas and hams.
I am going to send them to the storehouse.
Inferior goods.
I don't care to look. Just throw it away.
Well…
Yes.
The eldest son of the family,
Liu Zong, has passed away.
His son Liu Ting
followed his mother, Wang,
who's remarried into Liu Yu's family.
Later, this Liu Ting died young.
His second Uncle Liu Wen
wants to have his son adopted by
his brother to carry on the line.
This is simply
a case of inheritance dispute.
Why force Wang to divorce Liu Yu?
Mrs. Wang's two husbands
both shared the surname Liu.
Distant relatives
beyond the fifth generations.
It's illegal to marry a widow
from a distant relative.
Therefore, Judge Fang has asked
the two to divorce.
Huizhao, you remember it all?
Then, continue.
Do you remember
which chapter and section
the clause you just recalled
is in the law?
Take your time. No need to rush.
PENAL LAW
Take your time.
Stop it.
I was being too impatient.
The physician said that recovery
still requires some time.
It takes time.
It's alright. Don't rush.
Take it slowly.
Let's take a look at this.
This is a case of dispute over inheritance
between a stepwife and a maid.
This is about a stepson scheming to take
over the legitimate son's property.
Which one would you like to read first?
I suggest we read this one first.
It must be interesting.
Today, I wish to take Haode out.
So, I shall report to you first.
You want to go to the yamen again?
No, stay at home and recuperate.
My desk is already piled with case files.
I can't push them all to others to handle.
Besides, I already rested for a bit.
I'll follow the physician's instructions
and take the medicine.
With Haode by my side,
what is there to worry about?
Mom.
Mom, save me.
I'll go take a look.
Mother.
- Mother.
- What's wrong?
Mom, uphold justice for me.
Let me see. What happened?
Why did you become like this?
- Oh my.
- Grandmother.
After mother fell asleep last night,
someone snuck into her room.
We have interrogated
the maid on night watch.
They all said they didn't see anyone,
nor did they hear any noise.
The visitor only left this note.
"I am a born bald, enduring suffering.
Long have I heard you have beautiful hair
and disdain artificial hairpieces.
Tonight, at midnight, I'll come
by the moonlight to take your hair.
Leaving behind a coin
as a token of thanks.
The Peddler Huang San
from Bianjing market."
No need to say more.
- It was all your doing.
- Aunt. It's all my fault.
This peddler, Huang San, sold wigs
outside Xiangguo Temple.
Because he fought with others,
I punished him to receive caning,
and he made a fuss outside
the yamen for two months.
I thought that was the end.
But I didn't expect him to seek revenge.
I'm sorry to implicate you.
Huizhao, you still defend her?
Can anyone enter the Shen house at will?
Look at me and my hair.
How can I return
to the Qiu family like this?
How can I go out like this?
Aunt.
Those who deliver water and vegetables
come and go daily.
Someone must have taken advantage of it
to sneak in here and act at night.
It's my lack of vigilance. I'm so sorry.
I'll order a search
throughout the entire mansion--
No, search the entire city
and be sure to capture the villain.
Aunt, please leave
after your hair grows well.
You!
- Huizhao.
- Grandmother.
I have matters to attend to at the yamen.
I have to leave now with Haode.
Go, go.
Come back. Don't leave.
- Mother.
- Huizhao.
Mother.
I am his aunt.
Is this how he treats his elder?
Look at my hair.
Mother.
My hair.
Alright.
Guiniang.
Apply makeup and comb the hair
for your mother.
What a disgraceful look it is.
Don't forget.
Choose the best wig for her.
Yes.
Mother.
You were sleeping so soundly.
Brother.
Leshan did it to vent for me.
It's understandable.
Sorry, brother-in-law.
I really couldn't help it.
If you do anything naughty again,
at least tell me in advance,
so I can be prepared.
Haode.
Did you see her appearance?
It's so funny.
Don't do so next time.
INDICTMENT
Huizhao, don't worry about it.
Just do as we said.
You can handle it.
Judge Fang.
The case of the stepwife and maid,
An, fighting over the inheritance,
the judgment was somewhat inappropriate.
May I ask what's improper
about my judgment?
You two should sit down and talk.
An gave birth to a son for Luo Bing,
so Luo Bing divided his property
into three, giving one part to her.
The stepwife, Zou, has always been
on bad terms with Luo Bing.
They've been separated for many years.
Luo was old and confused,
so Zou came back to seize the property.
After An's son died,
Luo Bing didn't ask her
to return the property for six years.
His intentions were clear.
How can you solely believe Zou's story?
Send this case back for retrial.
Yes, Mr. Shen.
- Official Xia.
- Yes.
The case of an uncle
who kicked his nephew out of the family
and then seized his property
also requires further investigation.
Yes.
- I'll take my leave.
Mr. Shen, the Kaifeng Court
lacks an official
in charge of judicial matters.
There has been a pileup of cases recently,
and I have sent someone to urge.
The Ministry of Personnel says
the new official will come soon.
Understood.
You should also go rest.
Yes.
The medicine has been
warmed up twice already.
Huizhao, you've scared those two just now.
Why?
They report once every ten days.
And they get scolded hard each time.
They're drenched in sweat and need someone
to support when leaving the court.
I heard from Qingshi that Judge Fang
has asked for leave six times already.
Was I that scary before?
Just like a monster?
Why are they so scared of me?
You were not a monster
but cold and ruthless like chill iron.
You can even scare the children
to stop crying at night.
Then, why aren't you scared of me?
There are many people in the yamen.
Do not wander around.
Take good care of Leshan.
She has been out of sight for a while now.
Don't bother asking.
Bitter.
SIFU HOUSE
Let me tell you.
When I first went to the Shen family,
I was afraid I couldn't sleep,
so I brought some sedative incense.
Look, they have come in handy now.
And then I…
You are so naughty.
How dare she cause us trouble.
I have to show her what I got.
How arrogant you are.
You are really incredible and bold.
- You little troublemaker.
- Mom.
You were supposed to
look after your sister.
All you do is cause trouble.
What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with you?
- Mom.
What?
That mean old lady
bullied Haode first.
I've showed her some mercy.
Next time, I'll take a sewing needle
to stitch up her mouth.
I'll shut you up first.
- How dare you!
- Mom.
- Stop.
What's wrong?
PAN RESTAURANT
What's wrong? Did you see something?
You see.
Who is she, acting so secretive?
She's asking you. Tell us.
It's naturally a noble lady
who's different from us
in every possible way.
Why are you scaring me?
Haode.
You're not the same
as you were before now.
You are obsessing with
resolving the cases all day.
- What's there to look at?
- You've finally come back.
- Where's fourth brother-in-law?
- He was taken away by Judge Fang.
Let me tell you.
Recently, I've been working
on these cases with Huizhao.
I found it quite interesting.
Look.
This one is the case of three brothers
disputing over land,
lasting for 25 years. Even their grandsons
are still suing each other.
If you read many of these court arguments,
I bet your quick wits
- would be more--
- Stop.
Now, when I hear any lawsuit,
my head starts to ache.
Haode.
I have a big secret to tell you.
What is it?
Let me tell you.
Really?
My lady.
My lady, go check your room. Madam is…
My lady, I tried to stop them,
but I can't.
My lady, please go and see.
Aunt, why are you
searching through my room?
I have been wearing a string
of agarwood beads since I was a child,
which was blessed
by Master Fuji of Xiangguo Temple
to bless me safe.
But it is missing.
I have reported to the Old Lady.
The entire mansion
must be searched thoroughly.
It's in here.
You are really from a humble family.
How foolish.
She framed us so blatantly,
not pretending anymore,
this vicious old woman.
Madam, please
don't make it difficult for my lady.
I picked it up
in the garden by chance.
I thought it was Mr. Shen's.
I didn't know it's your treasured item.
Please forgive me, Madam.
You can't even distinguish
your Master's items.
If you didn't steal it,
then you'd be so confused.
You caused a big commotion
and worried the Old Lady.
Haode.
Do you think
this maid deserves to be punished?
- Aunt, actually--
- I made a mistake.
I'm willing to accept the punishment.
It's good then.
She's my maid.
You'd better let me do the punishment.
Madam, please forgive me.
I had this strange illness
since childhood.
I feel itchy being hit,
and I laugh when I feel itchy.
I didn't mean it.
Thank you for punishing me.
You mad maid!
- Give it to me.
- Aunt.
An unintentional mistake
deserves punishment,
intentionally stealing
gets punished more.
You discipline my maid so harshly.
If one day someone from your side
makes a mistake,
I hope you will be that harsh.
What do you mean?
I mean,
I'm afraid your hand would get hurt,
and it's not worth it.
Coming from a humble family,
you don't know the rules.
If it were my maid, she would have been
dragged out for a beating long ago.
Today, I just give you
a slight punishment.
Should she offend again,
she will not be let off easily.
My lady, it's all my fault
for not stopping her.
Huizhao will be back soon.
Hurry up and tidy up the room.
Yes.
Hand.
Hurry.
- Does it hurt?
- It's nothing.
You should have just admitted
you are my younger sister.
Let's see if she dares to hit you then.
If I admitted it, it would be inconvenient
for me to act here.
Then why were you laughing?
If I didn't laugh,
I might reach out
to pull off her wig then.
Haode, she's framing us boldly.
Can you stand that?
It's not gold or jade
but just a string of wooden beads.
I think she just wanted
to make me some trouble.
We must think of a way to keep her down,
so she won't dare to bully others again.
However, she is my aunt.
We can't fight her head-on
but only outwit her.
Come.
Good, amazing. Let's do that.
PAN RESTAURANT
Guiniang.
Mr. Wu.
Mother restricts me so much, I'm afraid
I may not be able to come out again.
Let's get to the point. Do you have
any plans to get to marry me now?
I've pleaded with my parents
to go for a marriage proposal.
But when the matchmaker
went to your house,
she was kicked out by your father.
He said you've been
engaged to the Xu family.
My parents were so angry and arranged
an engagement with the Lu family for me.
At this point,
I can't figure out any plan.
Go in there.
Mother.
You lowly lecher!
How dare you be so shameless
to seduce my daughter again!
I'll break your legs today.
- Mother.
- I'll break--
Don't. Mother. Don't.
- Don't.
- How dare you seduce my daughter.
Mother.
- Don't hit him.
- You did that?
Mother.
- Don't try to run.
- Mother.
Mother.
Mother. Don't hit him.
Don't.
- Don't hit him, Mother.
- Stop right here.
- Mother.
- I'll beat you up.
- How dare you!
- Don't.
Don't hit him. Mr. Wu, run!
What's going on here?
- Don't run.
- Mr. Wu, run!
Auntie?
I wonder why this building
is surrounded by people
and all bystanders
get chased away completely.
So, it's you here catching a thief.
Why didn't you tell me?
My third brother-in-law
owns this Pan Restaurant.
If you had told me earlier,
I could have helped you.
Was that person who just went by a thief?
I wonder what precious thing
you have lost this time.
Mother, it was my own will.
Just let Mr. Wu go.
You useless brat!
You've disgraced me.
What's wrong with her?
Are you okay? Go fetch some water.
Yes.
Freshen up before going downstairs.
Haode.
What's wrong?
You seem distracted all evening.
Brother, I have done something.
Something a little wicked.
How wicked is it?
Haode, terrible.
Something bad happened to Guiniang.
Guiniang, give it to me.
Are you trying to drive me to death?
Huizhao.
Uphold justice for me.
I'm going to sue him,
that son of the Wu family,
for defiling the lady
of an official family
and disgracing my family's reputation.
I will never let him go.
Mother, if you want to sue, then do it.
If anything happens to him,
I will also go with him.
- You!
- Aunt.
It's late at night.
Don't scare the grandmother.
If you want to sue someone,
then you need to explain it in detail.
Come with me to the study to discuss this.
Someone.
Aunt, please.
Guiniang, this is all my fault.
I shouldn't hold grudges against
your mother and drag you into it.
It's all my fault.
Sooner or later, this would happen.
The Wu and Qiu families live next door
to each other.
Mr. Wu and I grew up together.
We've fallen for each other and have been
seeing each other for a long time.
But there is no secret that doesn't leak.
The Xu family has heard of this matter,
but they have never had proof.
Mother brought me here
just to force me to end this relationship.
Hearing what you said,
the Wu and Qiu families
are considered equal in status.
And you two are really in love.
Why don't they permit your marriage?
Sorry about that.
This is my younger sister. She's naughty.
She often disguises herself.
No wonder you don't act like a maid.
Several years ago,
when my grandfather
was still an imperial censor,
he impeached Mr. Wu's father.
There is a deep rift
between the two families.
They will never resolve their grievances
because of us two.
If Aunt
refuses to let you two marry,
- then--
- If he doesn't abandon me,
then I won't leave him.
If she insists me to submit,
I can only seek death.
These delicate noble young ladies
are saying to seek death easily.
To seek death over a marriage,
is it really worth it?
But she does look quite pitiful.
Let's help her.
I thought you hate her mother very much.
When parents do evil deeds,
their children shouldn't be implicated.
I am forgiving.
Okay, what a forgiving girl.
Where are you going?
I haven't finished talking yet.
Huizhao, this cream dessert is so smooth.
It's very sweet and fragrant.
I learned how to make it
from the chef of Pan Restaurant.
Straining the milk took quite an effort.
I know you have a sweet tooth.
I added a lot of icing sugar to it.
Who said I have a sweet tooth?
Huizhao, are you tired
from reading so long?
I'll give you a massage
to help you relax and ease up.
What do you want? Spit it out.
Tell me.
If Guiniang can't marry Mr. Wu,
- she would seek death.
- Ridiculous.
The marriage must involve a matchmaker.
It is the parents who decide the marriage.
I hate those
who don't cherish their lives the most.
Tell her to give up.
But our marriage involved
a matchmaker and a betrothal.
It was parents who decided our marriage.
Then why didn't you just accept me?
Slow down.
Huizhao.
Guiniang is your cousin.
Do you really want
to force her to seek death?
Just help her out.
Huizhao.
Just say yes. Huizhao.
It's too late.
Aunt has quite a temper.
This matter won't be hidden.
I'm afraid this matter has been spread
to the Xu family.
They will not let this go.
KAIFENG COURT
Huizhao, Guiniang has been crying
day and night.
While we can still do something about it,
why don't you persuade your aunt?
Stop it. This is not for you to handle.
Well, I have handled so many things
that were not for me.
Why not this?
- Huizhao.
- Let me go.
- Just help them.
Sir, the new official has arrived.
He's in there.
Come on.
Mr. Shen.
It's been a while.
Eldest brother-in-law.
Please.
I've just returned
and I received the transfer order,
saying the Kaifeng Court is short of staff
and the cases are piling up.
I had been urged
to take the position immediately.
So, here I am.
Sorry for not having the chance
to inform Mr. Shen in advance.
Mr. Du comes at a perfect time.
There's a tough case for you.
Back then,
Mr. Du accused against his father,
and you insisted on sentencing him
to death in the imperial court.
Everyone knows you two are enemies.
Why would you transfer him here?
Is that so?
Hold court trial!
Mr. Du, the Qiu, Wu, and Xu families
are all either rich or noble.
As the officials' relatives involved,
they requested to listen in private rooms.
Please allow the steward to stand in court
and respond on their behalf.
Nonsense!
Once a writ has been filed,
it becomes a formal lawsuit.
According to the law of the Song,
even imperial relatives
must come for the trial.
Get both the plaintiff
and the defendant here
- to attend the trial.
- Yes.
Well…
Who is the plaintiff?
Who is the defendant?
- I'm the plaintiff.
My lord,
my husband's family name is Qiu.
We have a daughter named Guiniang,
who's 18 years old and has been
meticulously raised since childhood.
My husband and I hope her
to marry a fine man.
But the son of the Wu family
took advantage of our families' proximity
and defiled my daughter.
I am the plaintiff.
I want to sue the son of the Wu family
for adultery.
She can't discipline her daughter,
yet she wrongfully accused my son.
Separated by high walls,
with a deep courtyard,
you can never tell
who held the ladder to ask somebody in
and who held the lantern
to guide others into the room.
My son is just a frail scholar.
He can never leap onto roofs.
My lord, the shrew broke my son's legs.
- I want to accuse her of hurting my son.
- You!
Our Xu family presented a betrothal
through a matchmaker.
The gift has been delivered.
Qiu Guiniang
is my Xu family's daughter-in-law.
But the Qiu family allows
their daughter's adultery
and hides the truth.
My lord, I'm accusing Qiu Guiniang of
adultery with the son of the Wu family.
I am the plaintiff.
- I am the plaintiff.
- I am.
- I--
- Stop it. Shut up.
- My lord, I'm the plaintiff.
- I'm the plaintiff.
- I am the plaintiff.
- I am.
My lord.
- Court is adjourned.
- I am the plaintiff.
My lord.
The one causing trouble
in court is really Aunt?
Why doesn't she care about
her reputation at all?
All for her daughter.
You've seen the marriage law.
How is the adultery judged?
Male and female are each sentenced
to a year and a half of penal servitude.
If married, the female adulterer shall be
sentenced to two years.
Correct.
If Aunt does not accuse the Wu family,
the Xu family will not let her off.
Once the adultery is confirmed,
even if Guiniang
could escape imprisonment,
she can't avoid being flogged
in the court.
A lady getting stripped and flogged
in public
is much harder to endure than death.
When life is at stake,
reputation is no longer a concern.
Mr. Shen, you gave me a tough job.
One shrew is fine.
But there were three of them.
Is this case easy to judge?
Mr. Du, the one who filed the suit
is my aunt.
I have to avoid it.
Everyone knows you judge cases
only by the law but not the person.
His Majesty agreed you don't need to avoid
judging cases related to your family.
What? Encountering three women suddenly
makes it difficult for you too?
Mr. Du, how do you intend
to judge this case?
Although this case is complicated,
it's not difficult to judge.
The Qiu family shall return
all the betrothal gifts to the Xu family.
The son of the Wu family
and the daughter of the Qiu family
privately dated,
violating the marriage law.
Both shall receive 15 strokes
of the cane on the back
and cannot be married. Ask their families
to take them back for discipline.
Mr. Shen, what do you think?
Do they have to receive the caning?
Let's do it.
Subtitle translation by: Wina Huang