Can we talk for a minute?
- You know...
- Yes.
Well,
if Yurisa had gone,
in case you would...
Of course, you're good.
But there was a chance
that you might have lost,
so I decided...
to spend all my money.
But...
I was surprised to find out
that Yurisa was voted.
Our team's members talked
about spending quite a sum...
and buying about 3 to 4 extra votes.
Then, I decided to spend all my money,
so I did.
But Seong Beom said that you told him
not to spend any money...
unless it was to vote for Steve...
and said that he didn't buy any votes.
I got mad because of that.
If he had told me beforehand,
I wouldn't have spent all my money,
so I asked him why he made me do so.
Dong Min told you not to spend
any money...
unless it was to vote for Steve, right?
- How much did you spend?
- I didn't.
I thought you knew.
You should have told me that in advance.
We're a team. You could have told me.
There was a little trouble
between me and Seong Beom.
I was pretty suspicious of him.
But...
I mean,
we could use every member possible,
so...
we should be uniting as a team.
Instead,
they were telling me,
"This seems strange,"
and "He's a little suspicious."
They've been doing that,
and they should not be doing that.
Let's unite as a team!
Is that so hard?
Gosh. I've been getting a headache
since yesterday.
I...
didn't want to send her there.
I never played politics in this team.
I really...
liked that about us. When I first came,
you, Seong Beom, and Si Yoon...
were hitting it off really well...
and told me that you never played politics
because we were a team.
When I heard that, I was so glad...
and decided that I should be sincere.
- But as we lose more members,
- Yes.
we're left with no choice.
Someone had to be eliminated.
Yes, but I didn't think
it was such a bad idea to do that...
among ourselves...
when we all survived.
(Seong Beom joins them.)
They were so convinced.
If we had known that,
we should have noticed that...
in the first round.
- That's true.
- Their strategy?
Emotionally, there was tension between us.
It's true that I've been playing politics,
but I decided...
to stop doing it within our team...
after seeing how united our team was.
But...
I believe
Seong Beom is playing politics...
to be the winner in the finals.
I didn't think...
that anyone was
playing politics in our team.
That's why I participated sincerely.
But I changed my mind last night.
I spent my money...
because I could do that much for the team.
Then, Seong Beom said,
"Did Dong Min tell you too?"
"He told us to only spend money
to eliminate Steve..."
"and not otherwise."
Then... Darn it. He should have...
told me that.
I wouldn't have spent my money, then.
I suddenly got a headache.
That means he saved his money...
while making us spend ours.
He's been subtly telling me...
to buy the extra votes,
and it could have been...
because they weren't buying them.
There has to be
a strategic battle within the team.
I was so flustered.
You're supposed to play politics
when you're in this game.
But...
I was the one who suffered
when I wasn't doing that,
and it felt like a smack on the head.
In that team,
Dong Min and Seong Beom have...
a strong bond.
That's what it feels like.
Even when I present a good opinion,
it's rarely accepted.
I had been noticing that before this.
Let's have you...
- be the leader in calculation.
- Okay.
And who else is confident in calculating?
Look. Among us,
Seong Beom is the one
who can get the most points.
Let's keep assisting him.
He keeps placing first,
and the reason is...
that he calculates things
to make him the winner.
Like, "I can place first
if you help me out in this one."
Last night, Seong Beom was assigned
to the triple box,
and he said, "We need to go with the plan
to make me place first."
Okay. I might place first...
if you get minus points.
He's from KAIST.
He has the desire
to prove how intelligent he is,
so when I make a mistake
from time to time,
he points it out on purpose.
(During the third team match,
Criminal Memory)
You keep questioning me, so...
No, I'll tell you why.
Here's how you speak.
It also applies when you see a photo.
You need to explain
in the way for the listeners...
to understand at once.
(Seong Beom points out Acau's mistake.)
It would have been worth it
if Dong Min suggested something...
and I could learn from that.
But I didn't exactly understand
why other players would...
challenge me.
Because he also has...
a lot to learn from this game.
We don't point it out
when he makes a mistake,
but when others make mistakes,
he tends to point that out.
I had been stressed out about that...
little by little.
Like, "Why did you do this?"
But we don't point it out
when he makes a mistake.
We're like, "It happens."
That's when I thought,
"He's not going to win."
KAIST isn't good enough.
I've gotten too soft.
I should have played
like when I was in the Mansion.
Please gather at the Main Hall.
Where should I sit?
One, two, three, four.
Twelve people.
There is an announcement.
(Startled)
There's more.
Before the announcement,
the Evil Spirit who's been caught,
Jang Dong Min,
will leave this place
and wait in a separate room.
(Doubting)
(Dong Min, the Evil Spirit, leaves.)
From now on,
you will judge the additional Evil Spirit.
(Judging the Evil Spirit?)
Additional Evil Spirit?
There's another one?
The players will take turns...
to visit a hidden location
on the first floor...
and pick a player that you think...
is the Evil Spirit.
It must be the altar!
They did something with the altar.
You can only judge the Evil Spirit...
if five or more of you vote for them.
When you succeed
in judging the Evil Spirit,
they will instantly be
an elimination candidate...
and be exempted...
if they receive an Immunity Pass...
in today's Money Challenge.
On the other hand,
when you fail to judge the Evil Spirit,
they will be given an Immunity Pass
in today's Money Challenge.
You will now begin
judging the Evil Spirit.
We have to catch another one?
It's never easy here, is it?
I was like, "Who's the other one?"
Who would it be?
So, there's another Evil Spirit among us.
Do you have a guess?
- Do you have a hunch?
- Tell us who it is.
It's you.
- Me?
- Yes.
Seriously.
Because of the photo?
Fine. Vote for me. Do whatever you want.
That tells me that he's not.
He's not.
I'm really good at Mafia.
I poured my heart into acting.
I don't think Xitsuh is an Evil Spirit.
- We can exclude him.
- It can't be him.
To rule out the certain ones,
Xitsuh and Hye Seon can't be it.
I don't think it's Hye Seon either.
It's Steve, guys.
Stop trying to frame me.
I'm usually great at the game of Mafia.
She's framing me!
(Pouring his heart into acting)
But do you think
the additional Evil Spirit...
has the same abilities as Dong Min?
- They must.
But we need to know
what happened to the Evil Spirit.
Let's think about the people
who went through the same things...
that Dong Min went through.
If there's a storyline
of how one becomes an Evil Spirit,
we can find similar cases.
- Right.
- But the one who's gone through...
the same thing was Seong Beom.
You were the one
who's been playing with him.
Logically speaking,
I think it's fair that you vote for me.
So, I wouldn't mind
if you were suspicious of me.
But I'm clearly a regular player.
I bet my everything.
I bet my career, my real-life assets,
- and all the private funds here.
- And his YouTube subscribers.
I'm not Evil Spirit.
I think I did a good job of hiding.
The number of wins...
and the Deathmatch voting...
all match.
So, you just want to vote for me.
That's not it.
Go and stick the dagger.
That's not what I mean.
I thought...
that Seong Beom might be
the other Evil Spirit.
Dong Min was the Evil Spirit,
so I reckoned that the other one would
have the same pattern.
The one who had similar wins and losses...
and patterns on Dong Min's team was...
Seong Beom.
He's an Evil Spirit candidate.
(Seong Beom followed Dong Min's tracks.)
No matter how hard...
we try to guess,
there are too many possibilities.
We're not likely to find the one.
But what's fortunate is...
that there's no penalty, even if we fail.
Let's just give it a try...
- Let's give it a try.
- and go forward.
- One by one...
- No need to keep wondering.
Let's go one by one.
(They all move to the Purgatory
to vote for the Evil Spirit.)
Oh, it's scary.
Gosh.
Seriously. What is...
this place?
(It's their first time
seeing this mysterious place.)
It looked like a place
where Evil Spirits were possessed...
to send negative energy
to the people they didn't favor...
like they would to a voodoo doll.
That scared me.
Oh, is this what it is?
Stick the knife to the person
you think is the Evil Spirit.
It was obviously Steve.
I say it's Seong Beom.
There's a high chance that it's him.
Sorry.
Maybe it's not you. I'm not sure.
Right on the crown of the head.
I didn't know
when I'd get to stick it again,
so I stabbed it hard,
and it went all the way in.
I wasn't sure, to be honest.
I didn't have any information
on how an Evil Spirit...
was chosen.
I was especially clueless this time,
so I was frustrated.
Take this!
Darn Evil Spirit.
(The Evil Spirit enters.)
I think I'll get caught too soon.
I'll just vote for anyone.
The Evil Spirit has been judged.
(The Evil Spirit Judge ends.)
The player with the most votes is...
Steve Yea.
(Steve Yea)
(The players found the Evil Spirit
with pinpoint accuracy.)
Based on our grounds,
we can narrow it down to two people.
One, someone who has been...
experiencing
the same wins and losses as Dong Min.
Seong Beom has the most wins,
so there's a chance
that he's an Evil Spirit.
On the other hand,
the one who played the same role.
Among us, Steve...
made the most suggestions
as he was the leader.
Considering the role,
Steve was the same as Dong Min.
Then, we can pick 1 of the 2...
based on what we think.
(They narrowed it down
to Seong Beom and Steve.)
I thought
Steve would be the Evil Spirit...
if there was another one.
When we played Criminal Memory,
he made...
such a fatal mistake.
Then, what's your opinion, Steve?
Who do you think is the Evil Spirit?
I can't tell.
There was no way he would be that calm...
if he wasn't the Evil Spirit.
He would have thrown a tantrum,
like, "I'll kill you if it turns out
that I'm not the Evil Spirit."
But he was just sitting modestly.
Steve is too quiet.
When you become the Mafia in Mafia,
some people get extremely quiet
unless they're really good.
Because they don't know what to do.
Considering that, I have a feeling...
that it's Steve.
Everyone was thinking...
that it might be Steve...
if there was another Evil Spirit.
Chungju-Man's revenge!
I think we all voted for Steve...
without delay.
Oh, no.
I judge Steve as the Evil Spirit.
Take this!
(Steve Yea: 8 votes, Hong Jin Ho: 1 vote)
The success of the Evil Spirit Judge...
will be revealed
after today's Money Challenge.
- Oh, gosh.
- Gosh. I have a headache.
I think it's him.
You guys are stupid.
(Still pouring his heart into acting)
Then,
we will now begin today's Money Challenge.
What? We're starting right away?
- Right away?
Today's Money Challenge is...
Good and Evil.
(Good and Evil)
Good and Evil is
a ten-player individual match...
where players must uncover
the identities of the opponents...
through suspicion and persuasion...
while keeping their own identities hidden.
It's like Mafia.
At the start of the game,
each player enters the voting room...
to draw one of the role cards,
Angel or Devil.
Players will be assigned...
one of 6 Angels or 4 Devils.
Team Angel is composed
of Deity, the Archangel,
and four Angels.
Only the Archangel knows
the identity of Deity.
Team Devil is composed
of Lucifer and three Devils,
who know each other's identities.
After the roles have been assigned,
players can accumulate...
either Good Deed cards or Evil Deed cards.
A Representative candidate is selected...
in random order,
and they nominate...
an Executioner candidate...
to choose cards with them.
Players, then,
vote to approve or reject...
the Representative
or Executioner candidates.
If more than half approve,
they are elected.
If the vote fails, you skip a round
and move on to the next round.
Once elected,
the Representative and Executioner...
select cards for the round as follows.
A deck containing...
twenty Evil Deed cards
and ten Good Deed cards is shuffled.
Three cards are randomly drawn,
and the Representative discards
one card first.
The Executioner discards another card...
from the remaining two.
The final card is...
accumulated in that round.
As the rounds go on,
if five Evil Deed cards are
accumulated first,
the game ends with Team Devil's victory.
Each time an Evil Deed card is added,
one Devil's identity, excluding Lucifer,
is revealed to Deity.
Upon the fourth Evil Deed card,
the round's Representative gains...
the ability to eliminate one player.
The eliminated player's identity
is revealed,
and they're isolated until the game ends.
If five Good Deed cards...
are accumulated first,
Team Devil gets
one last chance to identify...
and eliminate Deity.
(Heaven)
If the Devils successfully
eliminate Deity,
they win.
If not,
the game ends with Team Angel's victory.
The losing team must send three players...
to the Deathmatch.
If a revealed Evil Spirit is
on the losing team...
due to the additional vote,
that player automatically goes
to the Deathmatch.
The other two participants are...
determined as follows.
(One player is selected through a vote
within the losing team.)
(The winning team nominates
one player after a discussion.)
If a revealed Evil Spirit
is on the winning team,
the Deathmatch participants are
decided as follows.
(One player is selected
through a vote within the losing team.)
(The voted player nominates
one additional player.)
(The winning team nominates
one player after a discussion.)
Good and Evil will begin shortly.
So, the teams are split.
- Team Devil and Team Angel.
- Yes, and we can't know yet.
I think it's a game...
where Team Angel and Team Devil compete...
regardless of the existing teams.
I was listening to the rules,
and it sounded
similar to the game of Mafia.
Every time I play Mafia,
people say, "You're a Mafia, aren't you?"
I knew I was in trouble then.
Back in college,
I played Mafia with my friends
every night in my room.
We giggled and had strategy meetings.
It was as if it was our profession.
This was my profession.
I thought I might win this.
After all, I was a champion...
of a Mafia competition.
I played pretty well,
so I knew I could play it well.
I'm confident that I can survive
in the Deathmatch,
so I don't mind going.
But there's no reason
to bring the chance...
from 0 percent to 1 or 2 percent.
It'll be essential
to win the Money Challenge.
We'll have to pick
the right Representative and Executioner.
Team Devil needs to make
its member the Executioner.
Team Angel needs to make
We'll have to accumulate the right cards.
Being picked
as Deity in the end is best for an Angel.
From the moment I heard,
"Today's game is Good and Evil,"
I understood nothing.
MJ was the one
who understood the game the least.
She's completely clueless.
Totally. I didn't get anything.
I'm bad at mind games.
I haven't properly played it before,
so I was worried.
She's innocent,
and she's a bad liar.
If such a player is on my team,
I'm doomed.
The game's over, then.
Six Angels and four Devils?
Angels must...
analyze people's patterns of behavior.
Devils know who each other is,
so there will be people
who approach and talk...
to others with conviction.
Then, you need to be suspicious of them.
The players will now take turns
to enter the voting room...
and draw a role card.
This ought to be fun.
I hope I get a good one.
I didn't mind
getting either a Devil or an Angel.
But rather than a normal Devil
or a normal Angel,
I want an Archangel or Lucifer.
I'm a terrible liar.
If I get a significant role...
or get a Devil card,
I'm worried about ruining the game.
If I can choose, I want a Devil.
I'm sure I can be persuasive,
and it's time to use that ability.
It's about time that I tricked others.
I thought it'd be more fun to be a Devil.
It's a special role, after all.
It's like being a Mafia,
so I thought a Devil would be
more fun to play.
I hope I get an Angel card...
so that I can do my best
in catching Devils.
Being a Devil sounded too arduous...
because I would have to hide...
the fact that I'm a Devil
and act like an Angel.
I wished I'd get...
an Angel with a significant role
rather than a regular one.
The Archangel or Deity.
Either one would be fun.
Keeping a straight face is
the most essential part...
of playing those roles,
so a bad player can't have it.
I was thinking...
I might be a good fit.
Xitsuh, please draw a role card.
Oh, only two cards left.
(Jin Ho enters
when there are only two cards remaining.)
Jin Ho, please draw a role card.
I will...
pick this one.
(The players randomly draw a card...)
(from the 10 cards
that have been placed...)
(to get their roles.)
Please wait at the Main Hall.
(All players have been assigned
to their roles.)
(Singing)
It looks like you're...
pretending to be excited when you walk.
You're so sharp.
Then, we'll deem you as a Devil...
if you act individually.
Devils will find out...
about each other, right?
They're sure about each other.
- Say you and I are Devils.
- Okay.
He's also a Devil,
so we need to be in private...
to come up with a plan.
Team Angel can't lose
if we work as a group.
(He doesn't want to give
the Devils a chance to strategize.)
- If we move as a group.
- Okay.
- Do you get it?
- I like that idea.
- Yes.
- You want to tie us down here.
We, Angels,
must find and kill all the Devils.
- "Kill?"
- We need to take them down,
and Angels will have to win
if we stop the Devils...
- from acting separately.
- Right.
Angels need to come together.
I don't know who Deity is,
but let's have all the Angels
move together.
We're finished
the moment Deity gets caught.
You speak like a true Angel.
Let's put handcuffs on each other.
- Don't do that.
- What?
Don't do that. It's too scary.
- What do you mean?
- What?
- I don't know.
She's being weird.
- Were you possessed by an Evil Spirit?
- She gives off a bizarre energy.
Were you possessed by one of the Devils?
When the Devils go
to check who each other is,
see if MJ is one of you,
and come out crying if she is.
If not,
smile as you come out.
You basically won.
- It's so tricky.
- Do the Devils know each other already?
- No.
- Not yet?
Didn't they say they'd tell them
when we pick a number?
The players will now enter
the voting room one by one...
to draw a card to be the Representative.
Devils will see who each other is,
and the Archangel will see who Deity is.
I'll go first.
Okay.
If we keep staying here,
we'll win, anyway.
Right. We need to keep staying here.
I think that has
the best chance of winning.
I won't even go to the bathroom.
The Archangel and Deity...
shouldn't contact each other.
- Right.
- Just don't.
If Deity finds out who the Archangel is,
they'll have a lot on their mind.
- Also,
- And you can't play as usual.
it shows.
Right. So, Angels,
the Archangel knows who Deity is,
but don't show it.
Deity, don't think, "Why isn't..."
- "the Archangel approaching me?"
- Good idea.
Archangel, don't approach Deity...
and say, "I'm the Archangel."
- That sounds too risky.
- That's a Devil playing a trick on you.
Do all Angels agree?
- Yes.
- Aren't you a Devil?
Gosh. You're hopeless.
I'll have to eliminate you.
- He's a Devil.
From an Angel's point of view,
it's better that we all stay here.
It's true that the Devils are the ones
who need to make a move.
- Indeed.
- We need to lock everyone up here...
and stay silent.
But the problem with that is...
that we'll only accumulate
Evil Deed cards...
if we pick the wrong Representative
and Executioner.
I think we'll need to find...
who picks Good Deed cards...
and keep using them.
We can find 2 to 3 of them
and keep replacing them.
- Exactly.
- Right.
We'll form a group of people
who have been verified...
and use them only.
If someone else tries to be
the Executioner, they're Devils.
Angels will have to win that way.
- Absolutely.
- Yes.
We can't lose if we keep playing that way.
I believed the Angels had the upper hand.
Because all we had to do was...
pick the verified Angels to be
the Representative and Executioner.
I thought the Angels had an advantage.
Please pick a card
a Representative order card.
(The order of being the Representative
is chosen.)
Number eight.
(Jin Ho picked number 1.)
I'm number one.
You're number one?
He picked number one?
That doesn't make sense!
There's no way you can pick number one.
- He should have been number two.
- I was doubtful as I picked it.
Like, "Why did I get number 1?
I should be number 2."
Xitsuh, did you get your number?
No, I'm going now.
I'll go last when he comes back.
Xitsuh, Jin Ho is out smoking,
just so you know.
Where is he smoking? Over there?
I won't stop by.
And I don't know who is what!
I'll find out on my way back up.
Why? What do you find out
on your way back up?
- I think he's a Devil.
- He just made a mistake.
- That was a slip of the tongue.
- "I'll find out on my way up."
Yes, he said that.
Because Angels can't find out anything.
He's too obvious.
(Is Xitsuh a Devil?)
(Sighing)
Archangel Xitsuh,
I will tell you who Deity is.
(Xitsuh was...)
(the Archangel.)
I got such a significant role
out of the blue.
This role is the busiest,
gets all the attention,
and has the most vital role in the game,
and I got that role?
I thought it was rather good, though.
I was confident
that I wouldn't completely ruin it.
I thought, "I guess it's better
that I'm the Archangel."
All I have to do is...
to keep distracting them
and confusing them...
so they don't know who Deity is.
But...
Oh, Deity.
(Team Angel: Deity, Xitsuh the Archangel)
(Team Devil: Lucifer)
Please gather at the Main Hall.
I will now announce the order
of the Representative candidates.
(Representative order)
(Jin Ho, Hye Seon, MJ, Acau,)
(Min A, Eon Kyu, Xitsuh,)
(Dong Min, Steve, and Seong Beom)
You will now pick
the first Executioner candidate.
The first Representative candidate,
Jin Ho,
enter the voting room in 30 minutes...
and nominate an Executioner candidate.
Let's talk.
Rather than picking one by myself,
it'll be better to talk about it first.
Although we don't know...
who each other is...
We don't have any information.
But who do you think is...
likely to be an Angel?
We don't have a conviction,
but let's try nominating...
the ones who we think we are.
I've played Mafia many times,
and some people...
get really quiet when they're the Mafia.
- Right.
- The Devils are the Mafias here.
Right.
How are the Devils Mafias?
Devils are the Mafias.
We'll have to think so.
No, you need to set this straight.
Listen, Angels.
Just like how we try to find
who the Mafia is,
the Angels need to pick...
who Deity is in the end.
- Right.
So, the Devils aren't the Mafias.
- Deity is.
- Yes.
Angels are the Mafias.
So, at first,
Devils are Mafias.
But the main point is Deity.
Whether Devils figure out
who Deity is or not.
I hope Deity is a smart one.
So, it's easier for Devils.
That's not exactly true. You keep...
Just throw out
all the Evil Deed cards, okay?
Yes. I know that.
I know the basic rules.
But why do you say...
that this game isn't easier for Devils?
I can't tell you that now!
Oh, right.
Seriously.
I vote for MJ as an Angel candidate.
I don't think MJ will be able to lie.
She might be pretending...
to be ignorant of the rules
while she's a Devil,
but she's not the type to do that.
- Definitely not.
- Right.
She's incapable of doing that.
She wouldn't have asked any questions
if she were a Devil.
- Right.
- We need to...
- play the game, so...
- Yes.
So, you're thinking of MJ, right?
- I agree.
I'll go, then.
(Jin Ho, a Representative candidate,
enters the voting room.)
Jin Ho, please pick
an Executioner candidate.
I pick...
I don't think...
MJ is such a good liar.
Listening to her speak at the time,
she didn't really give off the vibe...
that she was a Devil.
I pick MJ Kim as the Executioner.
The first Representative candidate,
Jin Ho,
has nominated MJ as the Executioner.
Players will now enter the voting room
one by one...
within 30 minutes...
to vote for or against the candidates.
What happens if it's 4 to 4?
It can't be 4 to 4.
- It should be 5 to 5.
- We're 10 people, MJ.
(There's a total of 10 players.)
If it's 4 to 4,
it means
that two people haven't voted yet.
So, you will have to nag them.
Was that a good enough answer?
- Go ahead and vote.
- That's so funny.
Seriously.
- That was wild, MJ.
- Oh, gosh.
Jin Ho, please vote for or against.
(The voting in Round 1 goes smoothly.)
(Approval)
I approve.
Xitsuh is too obvious.
I think so too.
There are three others.
Hye Seon is pretty quiet.
She's a Devil.
You're the type to read the room first.
She's been reading the room
without speaking.
She's taking notes of everything we do.
(She takes observation notes
without speaking.)
I'm certain...
that Seong Beom, Min A, Eon Kyu,
and either Jin Ho or Steve are...
the Devils.
Hye Seon seems strange.
I feel like she's lying.
I can't get a read on her.
It's all right to suspect people,
but try not to instigate things.
We need to be careful.
It's very risky
when an Angel suspects another Angel.
You know what happens
in the game of Mafia.
"I think Hye Seon is a Mafia."
I hate that when I play the game.
- We ask, "Why?"
- They say that I have a weird look.
I try to keep a straight face...
when I tell a lie,
but I don't know
how I look when I do that.
I'm not so good at that.
(Is this the look when he lies?)
Eon Kyu, you're likely to be an Angel.
If you were a Devil,
you would have been anxious.
It's 100 percent.
They'll tell us the number of votes,
right?
I don't think they will.
It'll be easier to guess if they tell us.
- Really?
- It gets easier. Of course.
You and I are the candidates,
and the vote is 6 to 4.
That means all the Devils voted
against us,
so you and I are safe.
We're safe?
It means we're Angels.
(She obviously didn't get it.)
What was that?
Seriously.
She's hilarious.
How did Dong Min carry her...
for eight straight days?
(Sighing)
- How did you carry her?
- I give up.
I'll make it look like it was an accident.
I'll explain.
If one of you is a Devil,
what will the Devils do?
They'll want you to be elected...
because the Devil will pick
an Evil Deed card.
If even the Angels vote for you,
and the vote is 10 to 0,
we know that one of you is a Devil.
Devils know who each other is,
so they'll approve of these candidates...
- if one of them is a Devil.
- They approve... Right!
- Now you get it, right?
- Awesome.
I got it now. Okay.
Voting is over.
The first Representative candidate,
Jin Ho,
and the Executioner candidate, MJ...
(Approved)
have been approved.
- Approved.
- They don't tell us the number.
Representative Jin Ho and Executioner MJ,
please enter the voting room...
and pick which card to discard.
Shall we?
Don't discard a Good Deed card.
You know that, right?
Gosh. I'm Jin Ho.
If you say all three of them were
Evil Deed cards, you're a Devil.
If you're going to say
that all three of them were...
Evil Deed cards,
use that...
to stab your thigh before you say it.
- "Please believe me!"
- Yes.
We need that much proof, at least.
(Then, we approve.)
But it might actually happen,
statistically.
It's going to happen
more often than you think.
It might happen twice in a row.
We'll have to count the cards well.
But it might go wrong
if we blindly trust that.
After shuffling 20 Evil Deed cards
and 10 Good Deed cards,
when the three cards are revealed...
to the first Representative,
the probability of them
being three Evil Deed cards...
is 28.07 percent,
which is close to one-third.
(Representative Jin Ho enters
the voting room.)
Jin Ho,
please pick 1 of the 3 cards to discard.
(Sighing)
(What's the outcome of the first cards?)
- We need to count them.
- Will he say it right away?
Yes, tell us right away.
Don't get me wrong. It really was...
three Evil Deed cards.
I mean it.
I'm telling the truth.
- I'm serious!
- Where's the dagger?
- It was actually three Evil Deed cards.
- Get the dagger.
It was actually three Evil Deed cards!
Then, we'll...
stab you with that from behind,
so scream three times.
I went in, and there were three red cards.
The moment I saw them, it was...
hopeless. But I didn't have a choice,
so I stepped out.
(Executioner MJ enters
the voting room next.)
MJ, please discard...
one of the two cards.
I don't have a choice.
(She has no choice
but to pick an Evil Deed card.)
In Round One,
one Evil Deed card has been accumulated.
(Heaven, Inferno)
Now,
one Devil's identity is revealed to Deity.
All players will take turns
to enter the voting room.
We might be at a disadvantage at first,
but we got to rule out
three Evil Deed cards.
It's not so bad.
Deity will now find out one Devil.
I beg you. Just pretend you didn't see it.
If you're so worried,
close your eyes as you go in.
Just keep your eyes closed. You know,
like how you close your eyes...
so that you don't see
the kidnapper's face.
Keep your eyes closed.
Even if you find out who it is,
act natural when you come back here
and act innocent.
(The first Devil to be revealed to Deity)
(Deity will pick 1 of the 3 Devil cards,)
(excluding Lucifer, and check who it is.)
(1 of the 4 Devils' identities
has been revealed.)
The Representative candidate
in Round Two is Hye Seon.
Hye Seon will now...
enter the voting room in 30 minutes...
and nominate the Executioner candidate.
I have a question.
- What is it?
- There are 20 Evil Deed cards, right?
What if we get three Evil Deed cards...
five times in a row?
Then...
- But the probability...
- That's the probability...
of winning Mega Millions.
- Wait.
- I'm right, aren't I?
- It's automatically...
- We don't have a choice, then.
(Acau is deep in thought.)
It felt like a smack on the head.
I thought, "This is bad."
"We might lose at this rate."
When the Representative picks the cards,
the chance of getting
three Evil Deed cards consecutively...
decreases significantly.
But if you include the cases...
when a Devil Representative
secretly discards...
a Good Deed card,
the probability increases significantly.
Isn't it worse for Angels
to be in the same room?
Why?
I think it's better to stick together.
We can't stop the Devils...
from being approved.
Shouldn't we be moving around freely?
Yes, we're supposed to.
- Really? Wait.
- If we all stay here...
I don't get why, though.
- Can you tell me?
- Why?
In this type of game,
the Archangel needs to carry the team.
But the Archangel can't do that
without any information.
I figured...
that it wasn't a good situation
for the Angels.
Now that the Archangel can't...
communicate with Deity,
I thought that we'd need to create...
chances for people...
to meet up in private.
That's why I said that.
Acau said,
"It's disadvantageous
for Angels to stick together."
"We can't win this way."
I didn't understand.
No, I couldn't understand.
I misjudged things.
I realized it was wrong.
Right. We shouldn't be playing this way.
Hold on. We'll be in huge trouble.
The Angels who we're sure of...
(Dong Min supports Acau's opinion.)
Those guys...
The Archangel knows who Deity is.
Those two...
and one more Angel should gather.
That way, Angels will have an influence.
(Tilting his head)
I don't get why we should move around.
At least the Archangel...
Team Angel's goal is...
to accumulate Good Deed cards
without getting caught who Deity is.
The chance of Deity
being caught goes up...
- if we talk.
- That's true.
We just need to sit here
and pick the right Executioner.
We only have two jobs, don't we?
You're right. Deity can just sit here...
without saying anything,
even if they know who the Devils are.
We add...
MJ to the list...
and find a few combinations.
- I think we can win that way.
- We can't stay still.
I don't see...
the need for the Archangel and Deity...
to be separated from the Angels.
I believe we can win this game
without finding out...
who the Devils are.
- I agree.
- If we stay here.
There's no need to expose Deity.
We, Angels, can stay here
and have a meeting...
to count the cards
and eliminate the Devils.
This isn't a mathematical game.
We can't win by counting the cards.
What are the chances
of getting two Good Deed cards...
among the three?
- He's right.
- The Devil can discard it...
when there's only one Good Deed card.
No, it's not!
- He's a Devil.
- That's why...
He's saying that because he's a Devil.
- Can't you tell?
- I can tell.
But...
(Is Seong Beom a Devil?)
When he says such things,
just observe how he behaves.
Don't try to convince him to stop.
What makes you think he doesn't know that?
Just watch.
(They'll watch for now.)
I'm not saying
that we should talk about the chances.
We, Angels, think...
that we only need...
a couple of verified Angels...
- to have them...
- But how can we verify...
the Angels in this situation?
- We can do that.
- How?
We can just tell.
That's what this game is about.
(Finding it odd)
From my point of view,
I couldn't get that.
I saw him saying
that we should stay together...
and leading the discussion,
and I knew...
he was a Devil immediately.
Who do you think the Angel is, then?
MJ and I are Angels.
That's for sure.
And maybe Eon Kyu.
How are you sure?
What's the reason?
- I just...
- I was agreeing...
- with Seong Beom's opinion,
- We can just tell.
but the moment I heard
his reason for verifying Angels...
I was like, "What is this?"
But we can't logically say,
"I picked a card,
and it said I was an Angel."
That's not logically fair.
So, we observe their behavior and words.
MJ, Eon Kyu,
and I stayed together
for quite a long time,
and we're the same.
The three of us are honest people,
so we would have acted differently
if we were Devils.
There are things that seem unusual.
That's why I'm saying it's safe...
to find the ones
who are clearly on our side...
in this room.
I get what you mean.
It seemed to me like the Devils were...
anxious to get out of here...
so that they could come up with a scheme.
But Devils know who each other is.
Should they be scheming?
Even though they know each other,
it's not like they can talk
through telepathy.
- They still need to talk.
- Right.
So, we're trying to stop that.
Seong Beom was leading the discussion...
and saying,
"All Angels,
stay right here in this hall."
But that makes no sense.
Devils know each other,
so they don't need to speak in private.
They only need to incite the Angels.
Their only job is to confuse the Angels.
On the contrary,
the Angels must spread out,
while the Archangel approaches Deity.
The Angels need to observe them...
and guess who the Devils are.
The fact that he's saying,
"We should all stay here,"
"you're a Devil if you step out..."
told me that he was trying to distract us.
(Is Seong Beom a Devil?)
- The Devils...
- You see,
I've played with Seong Beom
for a while, right?
I've been playing with him from the start.
He never makes decisions...
for such a reason.
(Seong Beom seems
particularly different than usual?)
He's the type to play the game...
- by always proceeding with caution.
- Actually,for the Angels...
- Right?
- Yes.
Can I join?
(Approaching)
- No?
- If you're in a group...
- For now...
- Devils already know each other.
- ExcludingLucifer.
- ShouldI get lost?
- What?
Because...Yes.
I...
want to believethat you're an Angel.
But how couldyou be certain
that they are Angels?
(Hesitant)
Then let me just say it to everyone. Yes.
You couldthinkthat way.
So far,
Seong Beom has been playinggames...
by always proceeding with caution.
But the style of game
he's suggestingnow...
is quite similarto gambling.
I'm not sayingthat you're a Devil.
Who? Me?
- No, Seong Beom.
- I see.
I feel threatened now.
If this continues,
Angelsmight be in a predicament.
- That's how I feel.
- I shouldput him on the list for now.
(The playersare dividedinto two groups
in no time.)
- If we just all stay here...
- If we don't do anything,
Angelsmightbe in trouble.
I want to continuewith the combination
of people who we know as Angels.
No, it's not about
the right combinationof people.
I'm sayingthat...
we have to think of a way
on how to utilize...
the good cards Angels have.
But eliminating
the Devils one at a time...
and securingthe Angels one at a time...
- No, we can't eliminatethe Devils now.
- We can't do that now.
- We can't kill them off...
- Only Deity knows.
- unlike the Mafia Game.
I've been playingwith Dong Min
for the past severaldays.
I figured out his patterns
and behavioralpsychology...
to a certaindegree.
But when we began playing,
he didn'tbehavelike himself.
He initiallysuggested
to go with StrategyA.
But he behavedthe opposite way.
He exaggeratedhis gestures
and the way he talked to people.
I foundthat suspicious.
I was 100 percentsure
that Dong Min was a Devil.
Only Deity is frustrated.
So now, Deity knows
one of the Devils' identities.
But Deity can't speak up now.
If we just sit here and do nothing,
the Angels can't share that information.
"What? Why? I thoughthe was an Angel."
That could happen.
Then can I share my opinion?
Only the Angelscan pay attention.
MJ is going 3rd. Acau is going 4th.
Eon Kyu is going 6th. And I'm going 10th.
In my opinion,
the four of us are indeedAngels.
- Why? On what grounds?
- So...
- Tell us the reason.
- So if you don'twant to believe me,
then don't.
But that's just my strategy.
So there are players
whom we deem as Angelsfor sure.
When it's their turn
to be the Representative,
we can pick another Angel
to be the Executioner.
MJ is goingthird.
We're certainthat she's an Angel.
Why?
We were certain,
so we chose her for Round One.
- That's...
- No, that can change.
- Listen.
- Just becauseyou were an Angel once,
it doesn't mean...
- you'll alwaysbe an Angel.
- Here's an example.
I would appreciate
if you can let me finish.
- Okay. Let's hear him out.
- Please.
It's difficultto voice my opinion
becausethere are people...
who are overly opinionated.
Anyway,we all agreedthat MJ was
the most likelyto be an Angel.
- Okay.
- So MJ...
is goingthird.
You go in as the Representative.
Save all the Good Deed cards you can.
But if we end up with the Evil Deed card,
one more Devil will be exposed.
We can split up then.
The Archangel and Deity can meet up.
They can exchangeinformation
about the two Devils.
But why must we wait until then?
Why must we wait
until there are two Devils?
What will you do if you don't wait?
(What will you do if you don't wait?)
I thoughtSeong Beom was a Devil for sure.
So I just left.
I boltedout of there first.
"Fine. Think of me as a Devil then."
"I don't think we shouldplay like this."
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
(Xitsuh is leavingin the end.)
The Archangel must meet with Deity.
By stayingthere,
we'll only be instigated by the Devils.
Devils alreadyknow
each other's identities.
They must be Seong Beom...
and the playerswho followSeong Beom.
The people who agree with Seong Beom.
Heo Seong Beom, Kim Min A,
Hong Jin Ho, and Joo Eon Kyu.
The four of them...
(Devil candidates: Heo Seong Beom,
Kim Min A, Hong Jin Ho, Joo Eon Kyu)
I'm consideringthem
to be the Devil candidates.
I think
we oughtto talk to peoplein private.
Are we just goingto split up? What?
No. There'snothingwe can do now.
It will be better to talk to people
in privatefor the sake of your team.
- This is so sudden. This is a bust.
- If you're an Angel,
just strike up a conversationwith people.
My firststrategywas makingit possible
for Deity and the Archangel...
to communicatein private.
But if it's too obvious
that Deity and the Archangel...
are talkingin private,
Deity can be easilyexposed.
Even if I didn't needto talk to everyone,
I invitedeveryone for a talk in private.
I keptdoingthat.
Who do you think is an Angel?
Just based on your gut feeling.
- At first, Dong Min took an activerole.
- Yes.
I thoughthe was an Angel
becausehe said all the right things.
But he talkedto Xitsuh
in private earlier.
So now, I'm certainthat he's a Devil.
I see.
But we talkedabout not sharing...
any informationwith anyone.
But you want to mislead the Devils.
That's your strategy.
In an attemptto mislead them,
we mightend up givingawaya hint.
It feelslike I'm beinginterrogated.
It feels weird.
- Dong Min seems a bit suspicious.
- Okay.
He rarelychangeshis strategy
once the game starts.
He said we shouldall stay together.
Aftertalkingto Xitsuh,
- he changedhis stance.
- Yes.
I was like, "What? Dong Min changed
his mind? It's a majorchange."
Dong Min said we had to stay together...
and shouldn'tsplit up.
Then at one point, he said...
that the Angelshad to split up,
so the Archangeland Deity could meet.
He arguedthat
we shouldtalk to peoplein private.
So I suspectedhim for it. Yes, that's it.
In my opinion,
Seong Beom is a 100 percentDevil.
I think Min A and Jin Ho
are highlylikelyto be Devils.
When we drew the cards...
- for the order of Representatives,
- Yes.
- we didn't have much information.
- Right.
But aftercomingback from it,
Jin Ho made notes.
(He made notes
when there wasn't much information?)
He could'vewrittendownthe order.
In my opinion,Acau is the Archangel.
- I thinkhe wants to lead the game now.
- He wants to lead.
That's why he wants to split up.
Then will the Archangelknow who Deity is?
Probably.But Acau thinks...
that he's super sharp.
But sometimes,he makes clumsymistakes.
If he's exposedwhile meeting up
with Deity, we'll lose this game.
I'm really at ease becauseI'm an Angel.
I didn'tdraw the Archangelor Deity.
You can totallytrust me.
Dong Min is a Devil.
- I'm certainof it.
- Yes.
I became sure of it just now.
Seong Beom is not the type
to insiston his opinionlike that.
- Right. I've never seen that before.
- Yes.
If Steve did that, I would'veunderstood.
But this kind of behaviorfrom Seong Beom
doesn't make sense.
So anyway,
it's not that we hate Seong Beom.
We just have to win the game.
- Min A and Seong Beom are together.
- What?
- Really?
I think Acau is an Angel.
Amongall the strategiesI heard,
his strategywas the only one...
that was advantageousto the Angels.
If the Archangeldoesn't do anything,
this game will be a bust.
Right now,
the Devils know each other's identities.
The Angelswill be easilyinfluenced
since they don't have the information.
But since the Devils know,
they can easily shape the public opinion.
This is the biggestproblem.
Deity cannot be exposed
in whatevercircumstances.
But Deity must do something.
So the Archangeland Deity must meet up.
Well, I must meet Deity
as soon as possible...
and sharemy identity,
so I could get some information.
So I askeda lot of people...
withoutmakingit look too obvious.
"Who do you think is the Devil?"
Whom do you suspectthe most?
(Xitsuh asked everyone,includingDeity.)
You're an Angel, right?
Of course. Darn it.
Whom do you suspectthe most?
Pick the most suspiciousplayer.
- The Devil.
- You can pick me.
Tell me the most suspiciousplayer.
- You and Dong Min.
- Okay.
So I heard from Deity.
Deity said,
"I think this person is the Devil."
So I was like, "Okay."
I was givenan oraclefrom Deity.
Be quiet, you Devil.
- I'm not a Devil.
- We're talking.
See? He's callingme a Devil
withoutproof.
- Dong Min is makingthem think I'm it.
- The first Devil.
(The first Devil singled out by Deity)
Min A.
(Kim Min A)
We have all forgottenthat
we have the Archangel.
- I know.
- And the Archangelknows...
who the Devil is.
I didn'thave to hide the fact
that I was the Archangel.
Even if the Devils find out
that I'm the Archangel...
So what?
What could they do?
In this game,
the Archangelhas to take an activerole.
The Archangelmust lead
the other Angels...
and let them know who the Devils are
while covering for Deity.
Did they meet?
Did Deity and Archangelmeet?
Let me tell you how far we've gotten.
And I think we're right.
- Okay.
- Min A is a Devil.
(He sharesthe information
with Dong Min too.)
My gosh, this is gettinginteresting.
- So you know what's goingon now.
- Yes.
- Min A is the Devil.
What if...
Seong Beom is Lucifer?
Then we're basicallydoomed.
The only person who can be this active
is Lucifer.
(The 1 Devil who was not revealed
to Deity is Lucifer.)
My gosh, this is really iffy.
This is crazy.
(The 1 Devil who was not revealed
to Deity is Lucifer.)
Anyway,
you have to lead the Angels.
If you see anyone
with suspiciousbehaviors, tell me.
Then I'll make a gesture, and you observe.
The Representative candidate,
Choi Hye Seon, for Round Two...
has ten minutes
to nominate the Executioner.
This roundcouldgo wrong.
He has somekind of plan.
He assumesthat there won't be
any Good Deed cards this round.
If we end up with two Evil Deed cards,
it will be over. That's his judgment.
(They must make an Angel
to be the Executioner.)
Choose one player
to be the Executioner candidate.
(Xitsuh)
The second Representativecandidate,
Choi Hye Seon,
nominatedXitsuh
to be the Executioner candidate.
(Representative:Choi Hye Seon,
Executioner: Xitsuh)
A vote will now be held...
for the Representative candidate,
Choi Hye Seon,
and the Executioner candidate, Xitsuh.
The combinationmakes no sense.
- I will vote againstit for sure.
- Are you an Angel?
How manytimes
must I tell you I'm an Angel?
Do you feel lonely?
(Suspectinghim)
When have I ever lied to you?
You can start today.
Lyingis not my cup of tea unlikesomeone.
You're so sly.
Xitsuh.
Please vote for or againstthe candidates.
(Xitsuh's alliancevotes
for the candidates.)
I'll vote for them.
(Xitsuh's alliancevotes
for the candidates.)
They're not interestedin hiding
that they're the Devils.
Thinkabout it. Dong Min
and Xitsuh are on the same page?
This can never happen.
The three of them
might be Devils for sure.
Xitsuh, Choi Hye Seon, and Jang Dong Min.
(Heo Seong Beom's alliance
votes againstthe candidates.)
You don't think I don't know who you are?
(Against)
I was told to vote againstthem.
- So I did.
- Who told you that?
Seong Beom.
Initially,I was suspiciousof him.
- I'm still not 100 percent sure.
- Okay.
I thinkyou're an Angel.
Well, my hunch couldbe wrong.
And earlier,Xitsuh slipped up.
(It was right after
their roles had been assigned.)
And I don't know who is what!
I'll find out on my way back up.
- I think he's a Devil.
- He just made a mistake.
- That was a slip of the tongue.
To think that he was actingthen,
what he said...
clearlygave away his identity.
Voting is over.
Accordingto the result,
the secondRepresentativecandidate,
Choi Hye Seon,
and the second Executionercandidate,
Xitsuh,
were not elected.
(Representative,Executioner)
This is crazy.
What are you doing alone?
What? I'm tryingto figurethis out.
Darn it. Nothingis working out.
Did you vote against us?
- Me?
- Did you voteagainst us?
I don't know. I'm not sure anymore.
- I thoughtyou were an Angel.
- I...
- Did you vote against us?
- No. We can't assume she's not...
- just becauseof this vote.
- I'm an Angel.
The Representativecandidate
for Round Three is MJ Kim.
(Representative, MJ Kim)
MJ Kim, the Representativecandidate,
must enter the voting room
within 30 minutes...
and nominate an Executionercandidate.
MJ. Pick Seong Beom
for the Executionercandidate.
- Eon Kyu. MJ. Could you come here?
- But...
- Eon Kyu. MJ. Come here.
- Just now...
- No. Don't leave.
- Eon Kyu...
So tell me why you voted
againstthis round just now.
All right.I'll tell you.
Here's when we have to elect
the candidates.
We must do that when we're certain...
both the Representative
and the Executionerare Angels.
That way, we have a higher chance
of getting the Good Deed card. Right?
But to be honest,
we didn't have clear proof
that Hye Seon was an Angel.
Everyonewas suspectingXitsuh
from the get-go.
(Thinking)
Yes, we'll tell you.
We votedagainst the round. Why?
Becausewe believeyou're Devils.
(Becauseyou are Devils.)
- If you have a differentopinion,
- Okay. Let me speak.
- you can speak up.
- Okay. Let me speak up.
When we were all sittinghere earlier,
we listenedto each other's strategies.
The only person to offer
any sound strategywas Acau.
All the strategiesfrom Seong Beom...
would put the Angels at a disadvantage.
"Let's try out four rounds first."
I don't understand
what he wants to do with that.
He wants us to end up
with four Evil Deed cards?
"Let's keep going
until we get the Good Deed cards."
What if this happensin Round 2?
"Wait, we got 3 Evil Deed cards?"
That's a possibility.
So tryingto waste
four rounds like that...
If you trulybelieve
this strategymakes sense,
I'll just go and blow up.
- He didn'tlistento me.
- He didn't say four rounds.
- He didn'tsay that.
- That wasn't the strategy.
No one said that.
- Earlier,you wanted to experiment.
- No. He didn'tsay that.
I startedoff by saying
that was an optionwe could consider.
- I ended up sayingsomethingelse.
- So...
- You didn'tlistento the whole thing.
- But you still broughtit up.
You broughtit up.
- Then for your strategiesafterward,
- Right.
you said we couldn'tsplit up
and shouldstay together.
Acau was the only one
who understoodthe essenceof the game.
He knew the Archangelhad to do something.
Why?
That's the mechanismof this game.
Deity is the only one
who knows the identities of the Devils.
When Deity tells the Archangel
about the Devils,
the Archangelwill talk to people
on Deity's behalf.
Xitsuh. If you trulywanted
to listen to what I had to say,
just like Jin Ho and Eon Kyu,
you would've knownexactly what I said.
You wouldhave known
what kind of strategyI wanted to play.
But you stoppedlistening.
You thought,"Okay. Seong Beom's strategy
will harm the Angels."
Then the person I suspectedthe most
was Dong Min.
Earlier,Dong Min said
he wantedeveryoneto stay together.
He made everyoneto get on board
and said we shouldn'tsplit up.
Then Dong Min was the first one
to suspect Xitsuh.
But back then,
they didn't know each other's identity.
But afterward,
Dong Min stopped suspectingXitsuh.
After exchangingeach other's identity.
Then up until yesterday,
they tried to send each other
to the Deathmatch.
But today, they're perfectlyin sync.
We all know that
they like to play for themselves.
And Hye Seon
didn't need to play with them.
Up until now, she didn't have
a friendlyrelationshipwith them.
So it's ironical
how the three of them are together.
- Can you give me a rebuttalfor that?
- So...
- A Devil...
As an Angel, I didn't mislead anyone.
- I did things that raised suspicions.
- Acau.
- That's what I did.
(CallingAcau)
If you listento me,
you'll know I'm working...
- for the Angels. Why?
- Acau. Just know this.
- You're the key player.
- Only Acau...
- What?
- You have the decidingpower.
Here's where I stand.
From what I've been hearing,
I wasn't sure about Hye Seon.
I highlythought that
Xitsuh could be an Angel.
- Xitsuh had a point.
- Yes.
But Seong Beom didn'tsay anything
about wastingfour rounds.
He was tryingto say that
we shouldn'tdo anything...
that could harm the Angels.
Then put me on trial.
If you all agree that MJ Kim is an Angel,
put me down as the Executioner
and elect me.
- It doesn't matter if we get...
- Gosh, no. We can't do that.
all three Evil Deed cards or vice versa.
She'll know what they are.
MJ will tell you what she saw.
Then see what I do.
- Then...
- See which card we end up with.
- Then you'd act like an Angel.
- That's a waste. Then pick Seong Beom.
- I'm 100 percent sure. It's Seong Beom.
- Right.
- No. Jin Ho...
- Are you a Devil?
- Why did he say, "100 percent?"
- Jin Ho,
- MJ, and Min A.
- Nothingis guaranteed.
- Let's talk.
- Okay.
I'm so angrybecausehe's being
super aggressivebut with awfulacting.
- Is Acau a Devil?
- What?
Are you sure Acau isn't a Devil?
- Hold on. Let's talk.
- Okay.
- Let me say just one thing.
- Let's say Acau is an Angel.
- Yes.
If we lose,
he will have to go to the Deathmatch.
- Yes. He's trolling.
- He's trollinghard right now.
He thinks
he's the key player of this game.
He talkedto everyonein private.
He just sat there with his legs crossed.
He's so into gatheringinformationnow.
It's either Acau or Hye Seon.
What if Hye Seon is actingstrange
like that...
becauseshe trulybelieves
Dong Min and Xitsuh are Angels?
- That could be why.
- No. Never.
- No?
- Never.
Hold on.
Dong Min could have gaslighted her.
- Exactly.
- I've made up my mind.
Acau is an Angel, but he just doesn't know
how to play this game.
He's easilyinfluencedby them.
So this is a criticalpoint.
To get the result we want with this vote,
- we need Acau and Jin Ho.
- Right.
I just want to pick Jin Ho.
Here's why. Earlier,Jin Ho said...
we got three Evil Deed cards...
and I saw two Evil Deed cards.
So I want to check...
- if he removed a Good Deed card.
- Yes.
That's a good call.
MJ. Nominate an Executionercandidate.
Here.
I'll nominate Jin Ho.
The third Representativecandidate,
MJ Kim,
nominatedHong Jin Ho.
A vote will now be held
for the Representative candidate, MJ Kim,
and the Executioner candidate,
Hong Jin Ho.
So who has the highestpossibility
of beinga Devil in your opinion?
Everyoneon the other team?
I'm 100 percent sure it's Min A.
But there are two more.
- And Seong Beom is actingso odd.
- But...
He was louder than me. All of a sudden,
- he started to laugh.
- Well, that was...
That didn'tmake any sense.
- That's nonsense.It's clearhe's acting.
- That's a bit odd.
- Well, you know me. This is me.
- But...
But what is your proof
for thinkingMin A is a Devil?
- What?
- What's your prooffor Min A?
I have my sources.
I'm not sure.
I didn'tget any vibe
even when I talked to her up close.
Givenhis personality,
he would've done something.
He would'veoffered a strategy
or figuredout a way.
But he's not doinganything.
(Realizingsomething)
(Dong Min quietlypulls Xitsuh aside.)
You know what I think?
- Yes?
- I get the feeling...
- What?
- that we're doomed.
Becauseof the Evil Deed card?
Yes, this is bad.
We needto stay sharp now.
Here's the thing with the score
of the Good and Evil Deed cards.
We must have one more Good Deed card...
- to have a somewhatof an equalchance.
- We're not doing well.
There's a risk with Round Four for us.
- We must lead by one point...
- This is so hard.
to have similarfootingin this game.
But we're actuallylosing.
It's 1 to 0 now.
The score for the Evil and Good Deed cards
is 1 to 0.
It meanswe're actually losingby two.
The requirementfor the Angels and Devils
to win is the same.
The Angelsmust end up
with five Good Deed cards.
Or the Devilsmust end up
with five Evil Deed cards.
However,for the Devils, even if
the Angels collect five Good Deed cards,
the Devils can win by identifyingDeity.
But when the Devils have
five Evil Deed cards,
the Angelswill lose immediately.
With more Evil Deed cards,
Team Angels faces a great chance
to lose the game.
- No.
- So for this round,
if they don't feel safe,
they will vote against Jin Ho.
People whom we deem
to be Angelsfor sure...
- must pair up.
- Right.
But why did they pick Jin Ho?
No, listen. MJ just picked him on her own.
She was influencedby them.
Listen.
We should'vegotten a Good Deed card
in the previousround.
Right. It's so hard to collect
five Good Deed cards.
I mean, there aren't a lot of cards,
to begin with.
The only way to collectGood Deeds
is throughthe cards.
Look. If this happens...
and they decide to come clean
and just vote for him,
then this game will be a bust.
We must stop this from happening.
I'll go and ask them how they voted.
- We must stop them.
- We must vote against them.
- You bet.
- I understoodyou.
- We must vote against them.
- Yes.
I never stopped suspectingDong Min.
- Really?
- Yes.
Did you vote?
- Yes, I did.
- Did you vote for or against them?
I voted for them.
- Hye Seon.
- Yes.
They were alreadyelected.
Go and tell Dong Min.
- Really?
- We outnumberedyou, so yes.
I see.
(Hurrying)
That's odd.
He said they were elected
becauseeveryone voted for them.
What?
- Darn it. Already?
- The other group already voted.
- Darn it. They didn'teven talk to us.
- But Seong Beom seemed happy.
- He was smiling.
- Why did they vote withoutus?
They mightend up
with two Good Deed cards.
with two Good Deed cards. I must pray.
Gosh, no.
It will be another Evil Deed card.
Unlesswe get three Good Deed cards,
we'll get an Evil Deed for sure.
- Three Good Deed cards.
- Yes.
That's impossible.
Votingis over.
The Representative candidate,MJ Kim,
and the Executionercandidate,
Hong Jin Ho, were elected.
The Representative,MJ Kim,
and the Executioner,Hong Jin Ho,
enter the votingroom
and choose the card you want to discard.
(RepresentativeMJ Kim
enters the votingroom first.)
MJ Kim. Please choose a card
you wish to discard.
I'll discard this card.
(MJ Kim discards an Evil Deed card.)
(Executioner, Hong Jin Ho
enters the voting room.)
Hong Jin Ho, please choose a card
you wish to discard.
The card selections have ended.
This is wrong.
This is really wrong.
- Why?
It's wrong because Dong Min has said so.
We'll get a Good Deed card this time.
I believe in Jin Ho.
The result of the card selections
of Round Three will be revealed.
(5 minutes ago)
(Jin Ho was deep in thought.)
If I choose this card,
that card will be registered, right?
That's right.
(Good Deed)
(Why did he discard a Good Deed card?)
I was a bit torn.
Shall I leave behind a Good Deed card...
and pretend to be an Angel a bit more?
Even if people find out that I'm a Devil,
shall I accumulate an Evil Deed card?
(It was time to choose his position.)
I think it'll be fun
to side with the Devils.
It's the Devils' role to bring chaos.
I'll choose this card.
(He chose 1 of the 2 remaining cards.)
I chose a card and got
the role of a Devil.
I thought, "What? I think it'll be fun."
Number one, Hong Jin Ho.
I got number one.
I thought that it'd be nice...
to gain a point from the start.
Hong Jin Hom please discard
1 of the 3 cards.
Okay.
I'll discard this card.
Seriously, all three were
the Evil Deed cards.
(A Devil's acting)
Seriously, all three were
the Evil Deed cards.
- Don't lie.
- All three were the Evil Deed cards.
Of course, people know...
that there's a chance
of getting three Evil Deed cards.
They don't know when it'll happen.
Even if people grow suspicious,
I'll lie that there were
three Evil Deed cards...
so that an Evil Deed card
can get accumulated in Round One.
I planned things that way.
- Can I pick you?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Go ahead. What is it for?
Then...
If there are 2 Evil Deed cards
and 1 Good Deed card,
I'll leave behind 1 Evil Deed card
and 1 Good Deed card.
Of course.
In any case, you did well to choose me.
I thought it'd be better
to accumulate an Evil Deed card...
when we can, so I chose an Evil Deed card.
As for the rest,
I'll believe in other Devils...
and look for what I can do.
In Round Three,
one Evil Deed card has been accumulated.
Currently, two Evil Deed cards
have been accumulated.
(Judgment Status)
See? What did I tell you?
- My goodness.
- Gosh, Jin Ho.
Are you going to be like that?
- What?
- Work hard.
Perhaps he discarded
a Good Deed card earlier too.
I think this is better.
- Why did you choose Jin Ho?
- I want to kill him.
(The players are confused.)
Let's beat him up.
What should we do?
It made my legs go weak once more.
We can't be certain about MJ.
- Okay.
- It's because...
I told you this earlier.
Seong Beom might be completely wrong.
This is driving me crazy.
- This is seriously driving me crazy.
- Xitsuh.
Let's think about Hye Seon.
Are you 100 percent sure?
- Yes.
- Why?
- It's because...
- Tell me about your suspicions.
She was smiling
when the result got announced.
- That's her usual facial expression.
- Really?
When she was selected
by an Evil Spirit yesterday,
she was taking notes alone
with a smile on her face.
Is Hye Seon really an Angel?
Can we trust her?
I think we can trust her.
I think we can trust her. Dong Min too.
Why?
We can trust Dong Min too.
Is it a hunch?
My judgment is based on his behaviors.
Dong Min was the one who wanted to reject
the candidates in Round Two.
Perhaps he did that
because he was a Devil.
Here's what I wrote down.
(They have different ideas
regarding Dong Min's identity.)
I think he might be a spy.
I continue to be suspicious.
- We can't be sure about his identity.
- You know,
I honestly had a reality check.
What did I do wrong?
What failed?
So...
(At that moment, someone visits Xitsuh.)
What is it?
(Acau gives them room.)
(A moment later)
(Sighing)
For goodness' sake.
What nonsense is this?
We're doomed.
Xitsuh, why aren't you persuading me?
I'm an Angel.
I'm the Archangel.
Let me tell you this for sure.
Min A isn't a Devil.
(The identity of the first Devil)
It's Steve Yea.
(It's Steve Yea.)
That happened
because Deity was thorough...
and lied to me.
Deity couldn't believe someone
who claimed to be the Archangel,
so he tested me.
Apparently, Deity lied to me.
Deity didn't believe
that I was the Archangel.
Min A's identity is a mystery.
In Round One, Steve Yea
was revealed to be a Devil.
In Round Two, Jin Ho
Round Two.
The problem is that Min A can be an Angel.
In any case, 1 of the 3 is a stupid Angel.
(At least 1 of the 3 is an Angel.)
There can't be two stupid Angels
in that trio.
Thus, Dong Min is an Angel.
Dong Min.
I'm the Archangel.
- What?
- I'm the Archangel.
- Okay.
- In Round One, Deity lied to me.
Deity belatedly told me...
that Steve and Jin Ho were Devils.
It was Steve in Round 1
and Jin Ho in Round 2.
So we need to find the other two.
Seong Beom has to be a Devil.
Right.
I don't think Min A is acting.
Only two remain.
If Seong Beom is definitely a Devil,
we're looking for the last one.
So only Eon Kyu remains.
I think we should go in there together.
Think about it logically.
Two Evil Deed cards got accumulated,
but Hye Seon and Jin Ho
are laughing out loud...
with Xitsuh.
Xitsuh is the type who often acts...
- in an emotional way.
- It definitely isn't Xitsuh.
- A Devil?
- That's right. That's what I think...
from his behaviors.
Right now, the suspicious one is...
Steve Yea is a bit suspicious.
Who else?
As for Jin Ho, we know for sure.
Yes.
Hong Jin Ho and Steve Yea. Are those all?
It's just a probability.
I can't be certain.
How many Devils got revealed?
- We're certain about one Devil, right?
- Yes.
Dong Min, Xitsuh, and Hye Seon
are alive and well,
but I...
I guess Acau knows.
- The Devils?
- Yes.
I see.
- Min A, shall we talk?
- Okay.
- Min A.
- Yes?
Are you having a mental breakdown?
- What?
- Are you having a mental breakdown?
Yes.
I guess I believe people's words
too easily.
- That's right.
- It's so...
Min A, are you really an Angel?
- Yes.
- I'll give you definite information.
Okay.
Steve is...
a Devil.
I also think Steve is a Devil.
- Jin Ho is a Devil.
- Yes.
It's Seong Beom.
We don't know about Seong Beom.
Perhaps he's trolling.
- But...
- Isn't he trolling too much then?
I think either Seong Beom and Eon Kyu
are Devils...
or Seong Beom alone is a Devil.
I see.
Why do I feel like
Seong Beom is a trolling Angel?
Seong Beom said that
you were a trolling Angel.
Perhaps you guys are mistaken
about each other.
Perhaps Seong Beom is a Devil.
I'm certain that you're an Angel.
But Eon Kyu has been behaving strangely.
Did three Devils come upstairs to talk?
(Seong Beom and Eon Kyu visit Min A.)
- Gosh.
- I see why you're confused.
Yes.
You and MJ are getting swayed...
because you guys aren't the Deity.
Deity knows who the Devils are.
That's right.
But both Eon Kyu and I are Angels.
Acau and someone else...
can be the Deity and the Archangel.
But Eon Kyu, it doesn't make sense.
Let's say Xitsuh is the Deity.
No. I think Acau is the Deity.
Is Xitsuh the Archangel?
- The Archangel?
Isn't he getting too swayed then?
- Who?
- Xitsuh.
He isn't getting swayed.
- Perhaps he has an idea.
- He has an idea.
Please excuse me.
Why? Let me join you guys.
Dong Min, can we talk for a second?
Yes.
I suspected Jin Ho of being a Devil.
But MJ said,
"I want to pick Jin Ho."
I didn't understand why
she would make such a decision,
but Seong Beom and Eon Kyu said,
"That's a good idea."
So I didn't say anything in the end.
Thus, I became very suspicious of the two.
If you suddenly behave this way,
- Seong Beom will find another target.
- You're right.
I'll tell the others that I persuaded you.
- So just pretend to listen to them.
- Okay.
- Devils did another prey.
- Yes.
So stay with them.
- Should I pretend to be on their side?
- Yes.
You know what I mean, right?
- I don't know what to do.
- That way,
- we can come from behind by voting.
- Yes.
I began to figure out who the Angels were.
I thought, "We can keep going this way."
We can approve
of the candidates we trust...
and reject the candidates we don't trust.
Since there were more Angels,
it was 100 percent possible.
I thought, "If we keep going this way,
we can accumulate the Good Deed cards."
- If you aren't a Devil...
- Okay.
- Then you're a fool.
- Then you're so mean.
- Me?
- Yes.
You're either a Devil or a fool.
Hold on. Let's talk without Hye Seon.
The number won't be right
even if you keep counting.
The number won't be right without me.
(Sighing)
Have you talked to the others?
What did they say?
Xitsuh... I mean, Dong Min is talking.
The problem is
that Xitsuh trusts Dong Min.
It makes no sense. They think I'm a Devil.
- So...
- That isn't it?
- Their number won't be right.
They'll wonder why the number isn't right
and we're making a fuss.
There's an Angel among them.
- That's why.
- Where?
- Who's an Angel?
- Xitsuh.
- Xitsuh is an Angel.
- But...
- Then why are they with them?
- Exactly.
- They believe...
- They were gaslit.
- Yes.
What do you know?
Seong Beom is totally flustered.
- Okay.
- It's obvious that he's flustered.
I don't know yet...
if Eon Kyu truly trusts Seong Beom...
or is a Devil.
There's a big chance
that one of them is a Devil.
(Is one of them a Devil?)
- Shall we talk together or...
- We were talking.
- Let's talk together.
- Together.
Okay. I can't trust you.
- Suit yourself.
- Right now,
there's one Devil we don't know about.
I have a feeling
that Seong Beom just didn't know.
(Frustrated)
- Doesn't he go to KAIST?
- Exactly.
- How could you fall for the ruse?
- You know,
I've been on the same team with him.
I've seen that side of him a lot.
- If he's an Angel, let's lose.
- Okay.
- Let's lose.
We can just lose. If he's an Angel,
- let's lose.
- I understand.
- Then we can pick him for the Deathmatch.
- But...
The fourth Representative candidate, Acau,
please enter the voting room
in 30 minutes...
and choose the Executioner candidate.
(The fourth Representative candidate,
Acau)
Acau, please select
the Executioner candidate.
The person I choose is...
Xitsuh.
The fourth Representative candidate, Acau,
chose Xitsuh as the Executioner candidate.
The game...
begins now.
My goodness.
Acau and Xitsuh?
- I'll go and talk.
- I'll approve.
Please approve.
Acau.
I wondered why
the calculation wasn't right.
It's because Xitsuh is an Angel
who has been completely brainwashed.
It's because Xitsuh is on that side.
Because I kept saying
that the Devils were...
Xitsuh, Dong Min, and Hye Seon,
- you suspected me.
- That was why I suspected you.
Then we need to come up
with a new strategy.
We need to protect you.
- But...
- Here's the thing.
Right now, Xitsuh...
- is telling everyone.
- He might be the Archangel.
No, it's okay. It's a feint.
- Is that so?
- Yes. It's okay.
- Thank goodness.
- Yes.
I was worried about...
Xitsuh getting thoroughly gaslit...
and telling the others
that you were Deity.
Then it'd be game over.
It's okay. Everything is a strategy.
- Okay. Then it's okay.
- I knew about it,
but...
Why didn't you tell us?
You kept being suspicious.
- You weren't sure about us.
- No.
- Okay.
- You kept hanging out...
with suspicious people
and saying that you were 100 percent sure.
We're 100 percent Angels. People will see.
I'll approve.
(Staring)
They know about both.
Both.
Both got caught.
I'm completely on their side.
Whenever I visited a survival show,
I always got...
the role of a civilian in the Mafia Game.
I was a bit disappointed about that.
(He chose his role carefully.)
I've always had that thought.
This time, I chose a Devil.
I was like, "Gosh, this is great."
"It'll be so much fun today."
As for me,
people think that
I have a devil-like image.
I think I can use it...
to my advantage.
And as soon as I saw the members,
I thought to myself,
"Xitsuh..."
"and Seong Beom..."
"will lead the team."
So I decided to break up
Xitsuh and Seong Beom first.
In that situation...
(Dong Min argued
that people shouldn't work individually.)
I said, "You shouldn't go someplace else."
"We should work as a group."
Seong Beom showed...
a small reaction of agreement...
by my side.
It was my cue to create a conflict.
I said to Xitsuh who was next to me,
"Hey, we're in trouble."
"We'll lose if we keep going this way."
Xitsuh bought it and began...
to argue with Seong Beom.
(Xitsuh fell for the trap.)
What will you do if you don't wait?
One Devil has been revealed.
(He even left the group.)
This is so much fun.
(Dong Min succeeded in
dividing up the players.)
There's nothing to do.
They're fighting against each other.
Gosh.
All right. Since I'm bored,
I'll guess who the Deity is.
After two rounds,
Xitsuh came to me and said,
"I'm the Archangel."
I was like, "Really?"
"Have you met the Deity?"
To me, Deity was the important one.
"Yes, I've met him."
"So who are the Devils?"
(He said that Min A was a Devil.)
Min A?
They're ruined.
There's something serious wrong
with Team Angel.
Gosh, things are getting interesting.
- You can probably see what's going on.
- Yes.
- Min A is a Devil.
- I see.
"What's going on?"
Those guys...
Team Angel is going mad.
(They even picked a Devil, Jin Ho,
as the Executioner candidate.)
(He summoned Xitsuh right away.)
I think we're in big trouble.
If it ends up being an Evil Deed card...
If he says, "I'm a Devil,"
and picks an Evil Deed card,
we'll be ruined.
That's why we need to stop him.
- But getting five Good Deed cards...
- In...
(Dong Min used Jin Ho to avoid suspicion.)
In Round 3,
1 Evil Deed card has been accumulated.
(He pretended to be an Angel.)
Dong Min is definitely an Angel.
In any case, he's strategizing...
for Team Angel with enthusiasm.
So I believe that he's an Angel.
Jang Dong Min,
please stand by for five seconds.
(He can't help but smile.)
Seriously,
I should've joined the military
and become a spy.
It's so much fun to see the team crumble.
(He's very satisfied with his position.)
(A Devil's play)
(Team Angel: Xitsuh, Acau, Kim Min A,
and Heo Seong Beom)
Round Four will begin.
(Team Devil: Lucifer, Jang Dong Min,
Hong Jin Ho, and Steve Yea)
They're giving me
all the information, so stay still.
Okay.
(Steve Yea: Rejection)
(Hong Jin Ho: Rejection)
Please vote for or againstthe candidates.
(MJ Kim: Approval)
(Xitsuh: Approval)
The fourth Representative candidate,
Acau...
and Executioner candidate,
Xitsuh have been elected.
Now, we just need to hope
that a crazy thing won't happen.
Three Evil Deed cards.
- That's right.
- Yes.
Two Devils have been identified.
We'll get the full picture
once one more Evil Deed card gets added.
Then...
Team Devil will be
at a serious disadvantage.
So we just need to protect...
the King. I mean, the Deity.
If we protect the Deity,
we can receive five Good Deed cards.
It'll be quite a feat if they guess
the Deity's identity correctly.
We used all the smokescreen strategies.
Right.
- I'll go to Min A.
- Yes. Sound her out.
Do you want to talk to Eon Kyu?
You know... Think about it.
We shouldn't give the Devils
time to gather around.
I'll protect this place, so...
All right.
Tell Eon Kyu that I want to see him.
- Tell him to come here.
- I need your insight.
Okay.
Eon Kyu.
- Dong Min wants to talk to you.
- Really?
Hey.
Right now,
- we aren't in a good situation.
- Right.
(The identity of the last Devil)
(Lucifer, Joo Eon Kyu)
The moment I got the Lucifer card,
I thought, "I'm in trouble."
(Sighing)
"What should I do?"
I was very worried.
But the members made me think,
"We might be able to win."
Dong Min gave me advice.
From now on,
you should never talk alone with me,
Jin Ho,
- or Steve.
- Okay.
- That's what I was thinking.
- Because...
we'll be exposed more.
This round is the last time
we can talk like this.
When we're exposed...
and they share that information,
we'll no longer be able to talk like this.
So completely exclude and abandon...
- the three of us.
- Okay.
- Okay? Just focus on making your allies.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Yes.
I was keeping Seong Beom only.
Actually, he was keeping me.
You're likely to be the Angel, right?
It's 100 percent.
Why don't you judge me then?
If everyone agrees MJ is the Angel...
We can't waste our chance.
Seong Beom rather should be...
It's 100 percent Seong Beom.
I thought I had to do anything
for the team.
I have no thoughts...
other than that.
I'm going...
to reveal who the Deity is.
Xitsuh is mostly leading them.
And he almost trusts me 100 percent.
I know who the Archangel is.
Okay. Who is it?
Xitsuh is the Archangel.
But he hasn't told me
who the Deity is yet.
As we keep talking,
I'm trying to figure out
the identity of each person.
I'm going to find out.
Who turned out...
to be the Devils so far?
I'm the only one who isn't exposed.
It's fine as long as I'm not caught.
So we...
can't have the third Evil Deed card yet.
- Not yet.
- Okay.
Make a decision when I say
I know who the Deity is for sure.
I'm going to find out who the Deity is
no matter what.
You should act like you're the Angel.
- Yes.
- Xitsuh is strongly suspecting me.
- But I can't act differently now.
- Okay.
I should keep acting the same way.
Darn it. If I were Lucifer,
I would've selected Evil Deed cards only.
(Angel: Xitsuh, Acau, Choi Hye Seon,)
(MJ Kim, Heo Seong Beom, Kim Min A)
(Devil: Joo Eon Kyu, Jang Dong Min,
Hong Jin Ho,)
(Steve Yea)
(Xitsuh: Archangel, Joo Eon Kyu: Lucifer)
Acau, please choose a card...
you wish to discard.
(2 Evil Deed cards and 1 Good Deed card)
I will discard an Evil Deed card.
(Executioner Xitsuh)
Xitsuh, please choose a card...
you wish to discard.
I will discard an Evil Deed card.
The fourth Representative Acau...
and Executioner Xitsuh chose...
(Judgment Status)
a Good Deed card.
Currently, one Good Deed card...
and two Evil Deed cards
have been accumulated.
(In Round 4, a Good Deed card
was accumulated for the 1st time.)
- Nice.
- Okay.
Revenge has begun.
The fifth Representative candidate,
Kim Min A,
please enter the voting room
in 30 minutes...
to choose an Executioner candidate.
Min A can skip anyway.
- And you should be skipped.
- Yes. I'll skip.
- Yes. You should be skipped.
- Okay. I will.
Let's skip Eon Kyu...
and move on to Xitsuh. Number seven.
Executioner, just choose anyone.
Okay.
- Choose Jin Ho.
- Okay.
You're crazy if you agree with it.
(Executioner candidate Hong Jin Ho)
Kim Min A chose Hong Jin Ho...
as an Executioner candidate.
Thanks for choosing Jin Ho.
It's so funny.
They can't help but reject it this time.
Jin Ho, thanks for being our card.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm thankful for being anything.
Save me, Eon Kyu.
I think it's going well now.
You can pass me.
- I got it.
- Okay.
We should do that.
There's no other choice.
- Right.
- Because...
if we follow this strategy...
- We'll win.
- Yes.
Good.
Let's play safe.
This is the line of defense.
It's Min A this round.
They're skipped.
Then it's you and me.
- And they're skipped.
- Yes.
- Then it's Hye Seon and MJ.
I absolutely reject it.
(Kim Min A: Rejection)
(Heo Seong Beom: Rejection)
(Acau: Rejection, Xitsuh: Rejection)
(Choi Hye Seon: Rejection)
(Hong Jin Ho: Approval)
(Jang Dong Min: Approval,
Steve Yea: Approval)
(Joo Eon Kyu: Approval)
I hope Lucifer...
does well.
Eon Kyu.
Everyone thinks you're the Devil.
- Me?
- Yes.
What did I do to be considered a Devil?
They think you're very suspicious.
- I did nothing.
- I asked why.
They said you were very suspicious.
Voting is over.
Kim Min A and Hong Jin Ho...
weren't elected.
(Representative, Executioner)
The sixth Representative candidate,
Joo Eon Kyu,
please enter the voting room...
to choose an Executioner candidate.
That's not it.
Please vote for Jin Ho if you're an Angel.
- Please vote for Jin Ho.
- I want to become an Executioner.
- Vote for Jin Ho if you're an Angel.
- They ignored me.
- I want to become an Executioner.
- Thank you, everyone. I'll do my best.
You should vote for Jin Ho.
Joo Eon Kyu,
please choose an Executioner candidate.
The sixth Representative candidate,
Joo Eon Kyu...
chose...
Acau as an Executioner candidate.
I definitely said,
"Vote for Jin Ho if you're an Angel."
But he was like, "What?"
He looked confused when entering
the voting room. Then he suddenly chose...
Acau.
I was like, "He's crazy."
"He's trolling so hard."
I reject it.
Why Acau?
Why did you choose me?
Why should I vote for Jin Ho?
It's to skip him.
The Angels can skip him for sure.
We agreed to vote for Jin Ho...
as we could reject it.
"Vote for Jin Ho if you're an Angel."
Even if we said so,
he suddenly chose Acau.
So I thought
he was 100 percent suspicious.
"Vote for Jin Ho if you're an Angel."
But Jin Ho is a Devil.
And Devils should choose a Devil...
as a Representative.
So I wasn't sure
if they were sounding me out or not.
I thought they were teasing me.
- Reject it.
- Reject it if you're an Angel.
Reject it.
You're not an Angel.
Jin Ho, why don't you go and approve it?
Eon Kyu is Lucifer,
so he could act like an Angel
until the end...
because the Deity wouldn't know.
So he should've listened to the Angels...
and cooperated.
The Angels said,
"You should choose this person
as an Executioner."
And he tried to play smart.
But it was the biggest mistake...
for us Devils.
I said,
"Please vote for Jin Ho
if you're an Angel."
And he chose Acau.
- It's strange.
- So...
it made us suspect him.
He's one of the Devils.
(Eon Kyu's suspicious behavior
made them think he's a Devil.)
Or he wanted to make us...
approve it no matter what.
Is Eon Kyu not an Angel?
That's impossible.
(Going crazy)
Even though he's Lucifer,
the only person...
whose identity can't be revealed
until the end,
he basically declared...
that he was a Devil.
That punk. I told him to choose Jin Ho.
I told him to choose Jin Ho. Darn it.
There's no one to believe in the world.
(Heo Seong Beom: Rejection)
(Xitsuh: Rejection)
I reject it.
(Acau: Rejection)
(Kim Min A: Rejection)
Joo Eon Kyu and Acau weren't elected.
(Representative, Executioner)
Why did you not vote for Jin Ho?
What? Because I didn't know
what was going on.
I told you to vote for Jin Ho.
I said you shouldn't do anything
that will make them suspect you.
Gosh, I was stupid.
- You guys shouldn't approach me now.
- Okay.
The only thing we can do now
is to find out who the Deity is.
That punk.
Don't approach me from now on.
They identified me as the Evil Spirit.
I had to receive the Immunity Pass...
to avoid the Deathmatch.
And Eon Kyu basically confessed
that he was a Devil.
I couldn't understand.
His identity won't be revealed
because he's Lucifer.
But he confessed he was a Devil.
I couldn't understand at all.
I was at a disadvantage after that.
(Steve Yea must have a Deathmatch
if the Devils lose.)
The things I hoped wouldn't happen...
happened.
In one word,
it's messed up.
Devils, please stay away from me.
Don't approach me.
In a situation like this,
I can show...
my true worth.
The seventh Representative candidate,
Xitsuh...
has chosen Choi Hye Seon...
as an Executioner candidate.
(Representative: Xitsuh,
Executioner: Choi Hye Seon)
Please vote from now on.
Devil.
Why do we have to choose Jin Ho?
I've known Eon Kyu...
for a while,
but I don't know what he's thinking.
(He cut ties with him
even though he's also a Devil.)
- What?
- It's nothing.
It's because I don't know well.
Gosh, I can't play Mafia.
(Devil Dong Min is working hard
by himself.)
Hey.
Xitsuh.
Dong Min. Let's talk.
Is there anyone here?
Acau and Hye Seon.
Among the seven people,
there's a spy, a Devil.
And we haven't found out...
who it is yet.
- You trust Hye Seon 100 percent.
- Yes.
I think she's the riskiest.
- Do you think it's risky?
- Yes.
Does Hye Seon know who the Devils are?
- She does.
- She does?
- So...
- Does she know?
- About Steve and Jin Ho?
- Yes.
Of course, she knows.
- Hye Seon told MJ...
- Yes?
that Steve wasn't the Devil.
- When?
- Just now.
- Gosh, I want to tear everything.
- That's why...
That's why I asked you about Hye Seon.
Gosh. Give me a moment.
- Ask MJ.
- I'll bring her.
Tell me quickly.
The key was to find out...
who the Deity was among them.
And I was sure Xitsuh was the Archangel.
So I kept trying...
to make him suspect others.
I tested him.
Are you sure?
Did Hye Seon tell you...
that Steve wasn't a Devil just now?
She said, "Why are you suspecting Steve?"
That's how she feels people out. Wait.
- That's what she said?
- Yes.
She asked why you were suspecting him.
- She didn't say he wasn't a Devil.
- No.
She was trying to feel her out.
- It doesn't sound like it.
- I agree.
- She knows I'm an Angel.
- Because MJ is so suspicious.
You chose Jin Ho.
She was feeling her out
because she suspected her.
because she thought MJ might be a Devil?
The voting will be closed in ten minutes.
Who are the Representative
and the Executioner candidates right now?
- Xitsuh and Hye Seon.
- Okay.
Please stack Good Deed cards.
I approve it.
(Kim Min A: Approval)
(Choi Hye Seon: Approval)
(Heo Seong Beom: Approval)
(Xitsuh: Approval)
(Jang Dong Min: Approval)
I approve it.
(MJ Kim: Approval)
The voting is over.
The seventh Representative candidate,
Xitsuh,
and the Executioner candidate,
Choi Hye Seon,
have been elected.
Thank you.
(Representative Xitsuh
is going to choose a card.)
I hope they're not all Evil Deed cards.
Thank you.
I'll discard the Evil Deed card.
I'll be good.
Okay. There's 1 Good Deed card
and 1 Evil Deed card.
Were there 2 Evil Deed cards
and 1 Good Deed card?
We got 2 Evil Deed cards
and 1 Good Deed card.
- Oh, yes.
- There were two Evil Deed cards?
- I discarded the Evil Deed card.
- Okay.
I will discard this.
I will choose the Good Deed card.
The seventh Representative, Xitsuh,
and the Executioner, Choi Hye Seon,
have chosen...
a Good Deed card.
(Judgment Status)
Currently, two Good Deed cards...
and two Evil Deed cards
have been accumulated.
It's a tie. My gosh.
The eighth Representative candidate,
Jang Dong Min,
please enter the voting room
in 30 minutes...
to choose an Executive candidate.
I'll choose Xitsuh.
The Representative candidate,
Jang Dong Min,
has chosen Xitsuh
as an Executive candidate.
Please vote from now on.
Let's go.
I'll approve it.
(The Angels proceed to vote
without hesitation.)
Let's hurry up.
I approve it.
- Eon Kyu.
- Yes?
Let's just smoke.
I'm an Angel.
Things will not be going well for us,
but we should keep trying to meddle in...
and find out who the Deity is.
It'll be Hye Seon, Xitsuh, or Acau anyway.
That's for sure. It's 1 of the 3.
I think Hye Seon
is either the Deity or Archangel.
I think Acau is the Deity.
Hey.
You should gather with Steve...
and whisper...
as if you were guessing who the Deity was
to make them waver.
I'll get more information then.
You shouldn't let them feel at ease.
"What?
I think they figured something out."
"I think they noticed it."
You should make them think like this.
- We'll act like that.
- Yes.
Yes.
And... Okay.
Gosh! Darn it.
- Steve...
- The voting is over.
The eighth Representative candidate,
Jang Dong Min,
and the Executioner candidate, Xitsuh,
have been elected.
- Xitsuh.
- Yes, Dong Min.
- Let's pray.
- Will it work?
- Let's pray. I'm serious.
Please give us a Good Deed card.
Please.
- Dong Min.
- Please.
Please give us a Good Deed card.
I'll be good.
We'll be good.
- See you later.
- Yes. See you.
The chance of getting
three Evil Deed cards is quite high.
No. But quite a lot
of Good Deed cards are left.
We'll get an Evil Deed card at least once.
Please.
Please give me a Good Deed card.
I'll be good. Please.
I'll be good.
Gosh.
No way.
My goodness.
Hold on. No way.
There were three Evil Deed cards, right?
Don't suspect me and go.
Okay. So there were
three Evil Deed cards, right?
- This is annoying.
- I knew it.
(Executioner Xitsuh
came to check the cards later.)
My gosh. This is annoying.
So it'll be an Evil Deed card this time.
It doesn't matter.
Because we'll get more information
about a Devil.
Why do you think
it'll be an Evil Deed card for sure?
Because he got three Evil Deed cards.
Yes. It's nice to know more about Devils.
Darn it. I knew it.
I knew it too.
I told you.
Was it a Good Deed card?
It was a Good Deed card.
- Oh, yes!
- You startled me.
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
(In the voting room earlier)
I'll be good.
Please give me a Good Deed card.
(Devil Dong Min
can still hide his identity.)
Dong Min, please choose a card
you wish to discard.
I should throw away...
all the Evil Deed cards.
You must not do bad things.
Please choose a card you wish to discard.
This is so annoying.
I'll discard an Evil Deed card.
Let me tell you now.
Whether Seong Beom is an Angel or a Devil,
I'm going to put off the plan,
so don't take anyone out.
Don't try too hard.
Currently, three Good Deed cards...
and two Evil Deed cards
have been accumulated.
(Judgment Status)
So you think...
they don't know anything...
to figure out who the Deity is, right?
If they find any clue,
we should confuse them.
- Hold on, Dong Min.
- Then you...
Let's test it.
Tell me who you think might be the Deity.
I'm not going to say anything.
- What? Do you want me to tell you?
- Guess who the Deity is.
I'm not going to answer.
You're going to test me
if I'm hiding it well.
You guess.
I was like, "What's going on?"
I think...
Gosh, this is really hard.
I thought it was Hye Seon at first.
Because I heard
she had said something strange.
Okay.
(Okay. Let's stop here.)
What was that?
I can't tell you anything.
- I know.
- I was testing...
- if I was hiding it well.
- Okay.
So you tried not to give any hint...
to anyone, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- If it's hard for you to guess,
- Yes. Okay.
- it'll be even harder for them.
It's one of the biggest roles
the Archangel has.
Even if you know something, you
should pretend you don't until the end.
It depends on
how good you are at hiding it.
The fewer people know about it,
the better.
I should be the only one who knows.
No matter how much I trusted someone,
I didn't tell anyone.
The ninth Representative candidate...
is Steve Yea.
- Hey, who should I choose?
- Choose Jin Ho.
- Who should I choose?
- Me.
Vote for Jin Ho.
Someone raised her hand to volunteer.
Choose her then.
Please choose Hye Seon.
We can't skip four times anyway.
Or Evil Deed cards won't be stacked.
For Round Ten, we have Seong Beom.
If you're suspecting me, you can skip me.
We're going to skip you no matter what.
What are you talking about?
- Okay.
- They'll skip me too.
- Okay. So that's how it is for us.
- Yes.
- We should just vote.
- Okay.
(They're guilty
of suspecting Archangel Xitsuh.)
The ninth Representative candidate,
Steve Yea,
has chosen Choi Hye Seon
as an Executioner candidate.
(Representative: Steve Yea,
Executioner: Choi Hye Seon)
Let's go and reject it.
I reject it.
(Kim Min A: Rejection)
Let's keep it this way...
if you're an Angel.
I reject it.
(Acau: Rejection)
(Heo Seong Beom: Rejection)
(Jang Dong Min: Rejection)
Where are those guys?
They don't have to participate.
Please vote.
We talked with Seong Beom.
Acau is the Deity.
Xitsuh is the Archangel.
That's Seong Beom's prediction, right?
He said so based on his predictions,
didn't he?
That's his prediction.
Let me vote.
We can talk after voting.
Okay.
Are all the Devils here?
We were just talking.
(Steve Yea: Approval)
(Joo Eon Kyu: Approval)
(Hong Jin Ho: Approval)
They started feeling nervous...
and discussing.
They will analyze the patterns so far.
Gosh, they're good actors.
Be careful until the end.
Skip three people, including Jin Ho.
Don't skip Hye Seon and MJ.
If it's not over by then...
How can it not end?
It won't end
if they're all Evil Deed cards.
Skip Acau, Min A,
and Eon Kyu. Then it's me again.
(Team Angel's plan
for selecting the Representative)
(Choi Hye Seon, MJ Kim, and Xitsuh)
- We'll win then.
- Okay?
Why do we skip Acau?
It's to exclude everything.
Every possibility.
The voting is over.
The ninth Representative candidate,
Steve Yea,
and the Executioner candidate,
Choi Hye Seon,
weren't elected.
Who should I choose?
Just choose Jin Ho.
Yes. Bother him.
(They're going to bother the Devil.)
The tenth Representative candidate,
Heo Seong Beom...
has chosen Hong Jin Ho
as an Executioner candidate.
(Representative: Heo Seong Bom,
Executioner: Hong Jin Ho)
(The Devils are reasoning.)
Okay. Now,
we don't have to think...
unless it's important information...
with a level of certainty.
- We don't have to think.
- We don't have to.
- So what I'm saying is...
- Yes.
Someone is standing over there.
Oh, my gosh.
Look at you.
You must be crazy. Hey.
I was going to open the door.
This punk.
- What were you doing?
- Excuse me.
- Doing what?
- What were you doing?
- What do you mean?
- What?
- Why do you ask?
- I heard nothing, though.
- What?
- I heard nothing.
- I mean...
- I was going to open the door...
because I heard nothing.
And you came out right then.
We were talking for a moment.
I had to guess who the Devils were.
To get at least one clue,
I needed to do all that I could.
Nice job. Goodness.
That itself indicates he's not a Deity.
What?
That's why he has such behaviors.
(Acau is an ordinary Angel?)
I might get goosebumps to know one.
I know.
I can't wait to see the result.
Once a Devil is revealed,
I'm going to hit them real hard.
(Feeling a sting)
I mean it.
- That person...
- Seriously.
Darn it.
It doesn't feel like living.
(The voting begins for another rejection.)
I choose to reject.
(Choi Hye Seon: Rejection)
(MJ Kim: Rejection)
(Kim Min A: Rejection)
I choose to reject.
(Jang Dong Min: Rejection)
(Steve Yea: Rejection)
(Joo Eon Kyu: Rejection)
(Hong Jin Ho: Approval)
The tenth Representative candidate,
Heo Seong Beom,
and the Executioner candidate,
Hong Jin Ho,
have not been elected.
(Representative, Executioner)
The 11th Representative candidate,
Hong Jin Ho,
has nominated Joo Eon Kyu
as the Executioner candidate.
- Eon Kyu?
- Oh, come on!
(A Devil was forced to reveal his identity
by another Devil.)
Eon Kyu!
Jin Ho!
Let's show something now.
Is this the beginning?
We're going to show you what we can do!
- We'll work hard.
- Support us!
- What will you show?
- Support our misdeeds.
They aren't giving up on hope
until the end.
- Let's give them a hand.
- Vote for us.
- Please vote.
- Vote for us, guys.
We'll work hard.
I'll vote against you.
- Nice.
- They deserve votes.
Support number two.
(Choi Hye Seon: Rejection)
I choose to reject.
(Xitsuh: Rejection, Kim Min A: Rejection)
(Heo Seong Beom: Rejection)
I hate people.
(Hong Jin Ho: Approval)
(Steve Yea: Approval)
(Joo Eon Kyu: Approval)
I choose to reject.
(Jang Dong Min: Rejection)
The 11th Representative candidate,
Hong Jin Ho,
and the Executioner candidate,
Joo Eon Kyu,
have not been elected.
I'm so confused right now.
Either Seong Beom or Acau
is a Devil for sure.
Acau doesn't try to convince others.
- At one point, he let go like an Angel.
- He let go.
Seong Beom is the only one
who's still making moves.
He tried to persuade MJ until the end.
It's driving me even crazier.
(Xitsuh saw the two of them
come out of the pantry.)
What is it this time? Come here.
I must win.
What did Seong Beom say?
What? Seong Beom?
Dong Min, Xitsuh,
Hye Seon, and Acau.
He asked why I was so sure
about these four.
Gosh, he's shaking us until the end.
He's a Devil.
Acau is...
suspecting me and MJ.
Well, that makes sense.
Archangel Xitsuh...
was certain he wasn't a Devil.
I saw him so sure...
and figured he couldn't be persuaded.
I decided to let him have faith
to some degree...
because I could be wrong too.
I don't think I can play
this kind of game again.
- All my trust broke.
- Right.
I was so glad that I drew an Angel...
- because I didn't have to tell lies.
- Me too.
But the bad thing is...
that I can't believe what anyone says.
- It's hard.
- Right.
It's so ambiguous.
It's so ambiguous
in the sense that Angels...
- Right.
- can't trust each other.
- Devils trust each other tightly.
- Yes.
The 12th Representative candidate,
Choi Hye Seon,
please nominate an Executioner candidate.
Hye Seon,
I choose to nominate Jang Dong Min.
(The Executioner candidate
is Jang Dong Min.)
I have a good plan.
Come here.
In any case... Look.
When Hye Seon is a candidate...
Even if she's a Devil,
just pick a Good Deed card.
There are no chances
to turn the tables anyway,
so go for a Good Deed card,
even if you're a Devil?
Even if you turn out to be a Devil,
- I won't vote to eliminate you?
- That's right.
- I got it.
- Do you understand?
It's a completely supplementary plan.
I called Xitsuh...
and said Hye Seon was suspicious
although we had a way.
I told him to say,
"Even if you're a Devil,"
"go for the Evil Deed,
not for the Good Deed."
"Then even if you turn out to be a Devil,"
"my team won't point you out."
And he said it was a good idea.
I believe that you're an Angel,
but everyone's suspecting each other,
okay?
So Dong Min suggested a deal with you.
Even if you're a Devil,
go for the Good Deed card.
Then we'll never point you out...
even if you're revealed to be a Devil.
- You know, the other team...
- I see.
- can choose a person.
- Right.
It doesn't matter. Okay.
I eavesdropped on him to check
in which tone of voice...
he spoke to Hye Seon.
The 12th Representative, Choi Hye Seon,
and the Executioner, Jang Dong Min,
please enter the voting room
and choose which card to abandon.
This is too cruel.
Gosh.
What is this?
(Evil, Evil, Evil)
Please choose 1 of the 3 cards.
This is too cruel.
It was just too cruel.
I couldn't believe it.
I knew I'd be suspected...
when I left the room.
What is this?
- That's not it.
- What is this?
I guess all three cards are Evil.
- It's okay. It doesn't matter.
- Gosh.
This is too cruel.
(Eliminating 1 of 3 Evil Deed cards)
- All three were Evil.
- Really?
- Yes.
- For real?
For real.
Goodness.
Darn it.
(Evil, Evil)
(He needs to reveal his identity himself.)
Dong Min,
please choose 1 of the 2 cards to abandon.
Come on.
Evil Deed.
(Jang Dong Min chooses Evil.)
Take a seat.
It was a purposeful fluke to give you one.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
The 12th Representative, Choi Hye Seon,
and the Executioner, Jang Dong Min,
have selected...
(Judgment Status)
an Evil Deed card.
Currently, 3 Good Deed cards
and 3 Evil Deed cards...
have been accumulated.
Now that three Evil Deed cards
have been accumulated,
one Devil...
will be revealed to the Deity.
(The players enter in turn...)
(to reveal a Devil to the Deity.)
I've come this far...
through ups and down.
Goodness.
- Gosh.
- Dong Min.
Wait five seconds.
The third Devil has been revealed
to the Deity.
(The third Devil has been revealed.)
(One of them...)
(is aware of Dong Min's identity.)
The 13th Representative candidate, MJ Kim,
has nominated Xitsuh
as an Executioner candidate.
(Representative: MJ Kim,
Executioner: Xitsuh)
The voting will begin now.
(Xitsuh moves to meet the Deity
in secret.)
I finally did all that I needed to do.
I did all that I could do, and there...
I was curious about
who the last Devil would be.
I wanted to see it too.
Who?
What? Just come and say it out loud.
Dong Min is a Devil.
Dong Min?
What is going on?
It's because he's a Devil.
Can't you figure it out?
- I'm Archangel.
- What?
- I see.
In Round One, the Deity lied to me.
You can trust me and Dong Min.
Why?
You can trust Dong Min too.
It was horrible.
What...
I had my faith in Dong Min until the end.
I thought he was an Angel...
because too many players
seemed like Devils.
In the midst of that,
he kept making plans for Angels.
Of course,
a Devil could make plans for Angels.
But in that case,
things would get too confusing.
With even more Devil candidates,
I wouldn't have anyone to trust.
It made me so confused.
I did all that I could,
but it was still not easy to the end.
(Xitsuh gathers all the Angels.)
All right. All of us here are Angels.
Now, we just need to hide
the identity of the Deity.
All of us here are Angels.
What?
Honestly speaking,
I couldn't believe it at that time.
Xitsuh trusted Dong Min too much at first,
so I just assumed he was also an Angel.
He totally brainwashed me.
He usually has such a big plan...
that it's perfect for people like me
to be played.
Dong Min doesn't even come.
Gosh, Dong Min...
I'm not made for games like this.
This is crazy.
- What do we do?
- What do you mean?
We still have the last possibility.
We can only pray.
It's going to be over soon anyway.
There's no need to drag it on.
- Let's just end this quickly.
- Let's just hold our tongues.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- Let's keep silent.
Once we win this game,
we can all say, "Good work."
- They're going to pick one anyway.
- Right.
I'm sure they're confused.
At least, I was...
confident about
hiding the Deity's identity.
I kept it from Dong Min until the end.
I believe I tried my best not to show it.
Gosh, it was darn hard.
Did you see their faces?
When did you get caught?
- Now.
- Just now?
- Yes.
- You survived so well until now.
The Deity entered the room
and found out about me just now.
- Right.
- Yes.
If the upcoming round has...
three Evil Deed cards, I'll be eliminated.
(If 4 Evil Deed cards are accumulated,
1 Devil can be eliminated.)
MJ, please choose a card
you wish to discard.
Xitsuh, please choose a card
Let me announce the card
that has been selected.
- If it's Evil...
- The 13th Representative, MJ,
and the Executioner, Xitsuh,
have selected...
If it's Evil, I'll be eliminated.
A Good Deed card.
(Judgment Status)
We just need one more. We'll win, then.
The 14th Representative candidate...
will nominate
an Executioner candidate now.
The 14th Representative candidate, Acau,
please nominate an Executioner candidate.
Nominate just anyone.
- Okay.
- You can choose anyone here.
No, except for him.
That's for sure.
(Embarrassed)
Why isn't this punk coming?
He went down there to confuse them.
Goodness.
Until now?
He's Lucifer, darn it.
Such a trick isn't needed anymore.
The 14th Representative candidate, Acau,
has nominated Choi Hye Seon
as an Executioner candidate.
(Representative: Acau,
Executioner: Choi Hye Seon)
Acau, please choose a card
you wish to discard.
I...
choose this card.
(Acau chooses an Evil Deed card.)
Hye Seon, please choose a card
you wish to discard.
I choose this card.
(Hye Seon chooses to discard
an Evil Deed card.)
The 14th Representative, Acau,
and the Executioner, Choi Hye Seon,
have selected...
a Good Deed card.
(Judgment Status)
A Good Deed card!
Five Good Deed cards
have been accumulated.
(Five Good Deed cards
have been accumulated.)
The Devils should enter the voting room
and point out the Deity...
after enough discussion.
Let's go, Angels. Let's run away.
Follow me.
(All the Angels leave.)
Let's go.
Let's stay gathered here,
and when a Devil comes,
- Let's send them out.
- just run away.
Don't even speak with them.
- Never. It's not over yet.
- Let's send them out.
It's not over.
But it's unpredictable...
because the chances are 1 in 6.
We'll have to wait for the result.
It's hard to figure out with suspicion.
I think there's a 50-percent chance.
But Dong Min has...
- such a good hunch.
- I think there's a 50-percent chance.
- So, what do you think?
- What?
My gut feeling says...
it's Acau.
- And...
- Hye Seon is faking it?
Hye Seon is an Archangel.
I've guessed it the other way.
- I think it's Hye Seon.
- Hye Seon?
But it feels like she's faking it.
What do you think?
Who do you think it is?
You don't have any concrete information,
do you? Do you?
(The Devils are done
pointing out the Deity.)
Everyone, please gather at the Main Hall.
To eliminate the Deity,
the Devils...
Please.
I honestly think they'll guess it wrong.
(Deity)
(MJ Kim)
Gosh, what do I do?
(Archangel Xitsuh is given
the Deity's identity.)
Goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
(He can't believe what he's seeing.)
It feels like the game has become
about five times harder.
I literally thought,
"Dear Deity, why would you
give me such a hardship?"
It was all that I thought.
That's why...
(After the first Devil was revealed)
Right.
I thought I should...
let her know who I was,
and get information from her
as soon as possible.
Who do you think is most suspicious?
- What?
- Who do you think is most suspicious?
I'm clueless.
Goodness. At first, I...
You know who.
- What...
- Who's most suspicious? Hurry.
- One person.
- Min A?
Okay, the first Devil.
- Yes, I'm sure of it.
Min A is a Devil.
(But the Deity is totally off guard
around Min A.)
- So anyway for now...
- But Jin Ho...
This is driving me nuts.
Why? Where are you going?
You know Min A is a Devil,
and you're the Deity.
Why do you keep acting like that?
I'm the real Archangel, and...
It's her. It's the two of them.
- You lied to me?
- Yes.
Darn it.
I didn't know what to do.
It's fortunate at least
because no one would know your identity.
- No one. Okay?
- Okay.
We must be winning from now on.
We'll talk and go inside naturally.
I honestly didn't tell MJ...
to do anything.
I'll just act like I'm clueless.
Okay.
I'll act like I still don't get the rules.
(MJ acted like
she didn't understand the rules.)
It makes no sense.
I'm an idiot.
What...
Go inside.
I'm an idiot.
- Don't get fooled, and trust my info.
- Okay.
- Please!
- Got it.
And I hardly talked to MJ.
(After checking Dong Min's identity)
Hye Seon.
Go to Xitsuh and tell him it's Dong Min.
I'm the Deity.
(MJ sends Hye Seon
in case someone follows her.)
I shouldn't get caught.
MJ is the Deity, and Dong Min is a Devil.
MJ, and... Dong Min is a Devil?
MJ told me so.
I did my best to hide it.
I just needed to confuse them
so they wouldn't know who the Deity was.
Right now...
(Acau acts like he's the Deity.)
I'm a little suspicious of Steve.
And who else?
- Jin Ho for sure.
- I see.
Acau might know.
- Who the Devils are?
- Yes.
What...
(Hye Seon approaches
the Devils on purpose.)
Who do you think is an Angel for sure?
I don't know who's foolish.
- A foolish Angel?
- Yes.
It's either Hye Seon,
Xitsuh, or Acau, right?
Hye Seon seemed a little suspicious.
I honestly think it'd be hard...
for the Devils...
to guess MJ as the Deity.
To eliminate the Deity,
the Devils...
have succeeded.
(They have guessed
the Deity's identity right.)
The Devils are the winners.
I saw you acted like crazy.
Did you think I'd fall for such a trick?
(Sighing)
It makes no sense.
I couldn't even think of anything else
that I could've done.
It was just impossible
to hide her identity...
from Dong Min.
He probably saw it.
We won thanks to Dong Min.
He lives up to his name and reputation.
I was surprised by
how he led the team to victory.
I realized how easy it was...
to team up with Dong Min.
You guys need...
to believe me 100 percent.
- Unconditionally?
- Yes, unconditionally.
The Deity is...
MJ Kim.
But why is it MJ?
Can you explain it to us?
First off,
I checked where Xitsuh moved...
and paid attention...
to his honest remarks,
which couldn't be fake.
I crossed the players out 1 by 1 that way.
First, Seong Beom...
Who are you suspecting?
- Seong Beom, for sure.
- I see.
His actions and behaviors...
- Right.
- make no sense.
He's taking the opposite direction.
Xitsuh, why wouldn't you convince me?
Why wouldn't you convince me
that you're an Angel?
He didn't deal with Seong Beom
for several rounds.
That meant he wasn't the Deity.
And Acau.
(Deity Candidate 2: Acau)
I figured out that Acau wasn't
the Deity during the first round.
Xitsuh had to talk to the Deity,
so he left the room.
I'm leaving.
(He left the room first.)
He had work to do.
But the one who started it...
was Acau.
In this kind of game,
the Archangel plays an important role,
no matter what.
But the Archangel can't do
anything without information.
The Deity can't do it.
So I deleted those two from the list.
(Candidate 3 for the Deity, Kim Min A)
Xitsuh said that the Deity
gave him misinformation,
and he heard it was Min A.
The Deity told me a lie in Round One.
- A lie?
- I heard it was Min A.
It was to sound me out.
And now the Deity says,
Steve Yea and Hong Jin Ho were Devils.
In Round 1, it was Steve Yeah,
and Hong Jin Ho in Round 2.
But what was said was all true,
so I thought, "Okay."
I deleted Min A from the list too.
Now, only two were left,
MJ Kim and Hye Seon.
I saw Xitsuh communicating
a lot with Hye Seon.
I was confused about Hye Seon all along.
From the beginning, Hye Seon and Xitsuh...
participated a lot.
I wondered if my guess was right.
I couldn't make up my mind.
So I, to make sure for the last time...
Anyway, look at this.
When Hye Seon is a Representative,
even if she is a Devil,
she needs to choose a Good Deed card.
She has no chance
of turning the tables anyway,
so she needs to choose a Good Deed card
even if she's a Devil.
If it turns out you're in Team Devil...
You won't be picked.
I got it.
If you choose a Good Deed card,
even if it turns out you're in Team Devil,
we will never pick you.
I heard him talking to Hye Seon.
I wanted to know how he said it.
He just said it
like a casual conversation.
But when MJ Kim had to come forward...
as a Representative for the next round...
Dong Min.
Don't we need to make a deal with MJ Kim?
- Will you talk to her?
- Shall I?
MJ, can we talk for a minute?
Xitsuh might have thought,
"Why is he not doing the same thing..."
"to Hye Seon..."
"and MJ?"
We have accumulated...
a lot of Good Deed cards anyway.
So we have a chance...
of winning anyway, right?
He said it intentionally
where everyone could see him.
At first, MJ was puzzled thinking,
"Has he gone mad?
Why is he saying this to me?"
Okay? I said the same thing to Hye Seon.
Now, I was sure that MJ Kim was the Deity.
The moment I was 100 percent sure...
was when my identity was revealed.
So I kept watching to catch the moment...
when she was coming out
of the voting room.
Next.
Are you drawing a moving picture?
It looked most unfamiliar.
It was a moving picture.
I'd never seen a look like that
on her face...
ever since I was acquainted with MJ.
She definitely looked
like she was betrayed...
by someone she trusted.
It was at that moment...
that I got confident.
I knew her so well,
so I could catch it.
It's MJ Kim.
(Devil Dong Min chose MJ Kim.)
Today, MJ Kim...
truly gave the best performance.
Xitsuh gave his best performance too.
If we had played the game
with me in Team Angel...
and the others in Team Devil,
I wouldn't have guessed
that it was MJ Kim.
Her performance was terrific.
But she was going...
against me.
She gave the best performance,
but she faced me.
I just feel sorry for her.
Today, everyone on the winning team
of the Money Challenge...
will be given an Immunity Pass.
Today's Evil Spirit Judgement
results will be announced.
We will judge the extra Evil Spirit.
(A new announcement
before Money Challenge)
Gosh, I'm sorry.
It seems it's not you, but I'm not sure.
(Almost a landslide vote for one person)
The player who was selected
as the extra Evil Spirit...
is Steve Yea.
(Players brought Steve Yea to justice
as the Evil Spirit.)
The players succeeded...
in judging the Evil Spirit.
I knew it!
Come on.
With Team Devil's win today,
Steve Yea won an Immunity Pass.
From Team Angel,
who lost in the Money Challenge today,
there will be
three elimination candidates in total.
By voting, a team member...
needs to be selected
as the elimination candidate.
The one selected by voting...
must select a team member
to go against in a Deathmatch.
And the last person...
will be selected by the winning team.
Voting will now begin.
Vote for one player
to send to the Deathmatch.
Voting will close after one hour.
Players can transfer money
among themselves,
but they need to execute it...
in the voting room with the butler.
(Voting begins.)
(Team Angel gathers in the pantry.)
This is insane.
We did our best today.
- You worked hard.
- You really worked hard.
- Xitsuh worked so hard.
- Totally.
Thank you for your work.
Today, I...
I hope we exclude Xitsuh.
- No, I mean...
- He worked so hard.
To be honest, I wanted to send Xitsuh.
He trusted Dong Min until the end,
and it led the team to lose.
I'll speak now.
(Xitsuh had conflicts
with Seong Beom all along.)
You should just stay here.
Don't take anyone out
or do something like that.
- Are you uncomfortable with it?
- Don't try too hard.
Okay.
Well, I don't mind it.
He can play games as he likes.
But he should win.
The result matters, after all.
So I wanted to send Xitsuh.
Anyway, I played the Deity,
and I was caught.
So I want to go to the Deathmatch.
And don't say something like,
"That's not fair."
I don't want to kill the clock.
That's what I want, first of all.
I felt that MJ Kim...
wanted to go.
I sensed it.
I didn't feel that
she was forced to say so.
So, if she had said she'd go
although she didn't want to,
I'd have protected her,
even if I had to spend money.
I was also responsible as an Archangel.
Still, when she said that first,
I pitied her,
and I felt thankful at the same time.
She might have stopped their criticism...
from coming toward me.
First of all, I played the Deity today.
Also,
I've been acquainted with Dong Min...
for a long time.
In fact, I could have predicted...
that he was a Devil.
That was my mistake,
and I think I need to take responsibility.
Actually, in the hour...
given to us, we could discuss it.
People would feel
they didn't do a good job,
but they don't want to go.
So after the hour is up,
they can't decide,
and someone is forced to leave.
I didn't want that.
I said I'd go
because there's a chance I can come back.
I'll take responsibility and go.
(The first voter, MJ Kim)
Can I transfer my money?
You can transfer money.
Seong Beom.
(MJ Kim calls Heo Seong Beom.)
She says you need to be there.
I hope you go and come back.
How much would you like to transfer?
I'll transfer everything I have.
Since the first day, Seong Beom...
has been my team member
who played with me.
He was the youngest in the team,
and he was the brain.
I hoped Seong Beom could advance...
to the final and give a good performance.
I actually didn't have
a lot of money left,
but I wanted to give it to Seong Beom.
(MJ Kim transfers all her money
to Heo Seong Beom.)
MJ Kim transferred 57,000 dollars...
to Heo Seong Beom.
Why are you crying?
It's okay.
I might come back after this.
I hope you come back.
I really can come back.
Let's go.
Why are you crying?
I don't shed tears easily.
I'm definitely a thinker.
But in that situation,
I couldn't help but cry.
I grew very attached to her.
It felt like my family was going to war,
and she might not be able to come back.
And the money she saved hard...
could be received like inheritance,
I thought.
Back then,
I really couldn't control my tears.
(Seong Beom kept crying like that
for quite a while.)
(Voting carries on.)
(The second voter, Choi Hye Seon)
(MJ Kim)
(Choi Hye Seon votes for MJ Kim.)
(Kim Min A votes for MJ Kim.)
(Xitsuh and Acau vote for MJ Kim.)
(MJ Kim)
Voting is over.
Please gather at the Main Hall.
- Already? It's done quickly.
- Already?
They made a quick decision.
Then we need to think about it now.
Let's see who is left and think about it.
Could I have more say?
Of course.
Do you have anyone in mind
you want to save?
No, I'll think about it.
Goodness, look at our baby.
- Our baby is in big trouble.
- He's crying.
People might think
we eliminated Seong Beom today.
The voting results will be announced.
The voting results say...
MJ Kim is an elimination candidate.
(MJ Kim)
My goodness.
MJ Kim,
please enter the voting room now...
and select one person
to go against at the Deathmatch.
MJ?
I guess they caught...
that MJ lied.
Gosh.
I'm sorry...
to hear...
the unfortunate news.
I feel like I sent her to the Deathmatch,
so I feel bad.
(MJ Kim goes to select
her opponent in the Deathmatch.)
MJ Kim, please select one person...
you will bring to the Deathmatch.
(5 people are left.)
I thought they would need someone...
to reinforce their strength.
I thought I'd be the first card
they'd discard.
The only people...
who didn't play games
with MJ Kim usually...
were Xitsuh and me,
so I thought it was highly probable
that she selected me.
I felt very nervous back then.
It's Bloody Game.
I think anything can happen here.
You selected your opponent
for the Deathmatch.
MJ Kim, please leave this place now,
and move to the Deathmatch place.
The result will be announced.
The player MJ Kim selected
as her Deathmatch opponent...
(Choi Hye Seon)
is Choi Hye Seon.
Choi Hye Seon,
please leave this place now,
and move to the Deathmatch place.
The time has come.
Since she hasn't played any game with me,
I guess we had...
a psychological distance.
I never thought she showed...
a wonderful individual performance.
I might survive today and come back,
but I wished...
Min A and Seong Beom
would make it together.
Today,
the winning team of the Money Challenge...
can select one elimination candidate
from the losing team.
A representative player
should enter the voting room...
and select one elimination candidate.
You should go, Dong Min.
The decision is already made.
- Oh, gosh.
- See you later outside.
- Is it me? Okay.
- Darn it.
- Why are you making us nervous?
- I'll get myself ready.
You should prepare to cry.
Dong Min won't let Seong Beom be selected.
You can't be sure.
Please select one elimination candidate.
(Xitsuh)
(Kim Min A)
(Heo Seong Beom)
(Acau)
Much to my regret,
I should pick someone
who showed the poorest performance.
The Deathmatch player
selected by the winning team...
is Kim Min A.
(Jang Dong Min chose Kim Min A.)
Kim Min A, please leave this place now...
and go to the Deathmatch place.
- I'll be back.
- Go for it.
- Yes.
- You can do it.
You can do it.
In my perspective,
in today's game...
Although I'm on Team Devil now,
I've been on Team Angel
from the beginning to end.
It's about the contribution.
That's important.
Considering the contribution,
Min A is ranked the lowest.
It's not an exaggeration
to say I'm on Team Angel.
I've put in effort for Team Angel.
Among them, she was...
the least active person.
That's what I thought.
She kept saying,
"Am I stupid? Am I a stupid Angel?"
I'm a stupid Angel.
(Kim Min A blamed herself
all throughout the game.)
Gosh, how can this happen?
Since she kept saying so,
I thought she was...
the least active one today,
so I picked Min A.
To be honest,
I wanted to play the Deathmatch...
and win.
Why can't I? I can give it a try.
We're all similar.
(The last Deathmatch candidate, Kim Min A)
Today's Deathmatch will now begin.
MJ Kim,
Choi Hye Seon,
and Kim Min A.
Three players here...
need to have a 1-on-1 Deathmatch.
I'd rather win the Deathmatch today,
and show them I'm back.
I'll show my competence.
I think that's better.
I got a chance to play by myself,
so I felt excited
but was offended as well.
Making us go against one another...
felt like everyone
was looking on with indifference.
It was detestable.
They thought I was an idiot...
that they picked me.
To be the last one standing,
I can't advance
without having a Deathmatch.
I thought I couldn't be the winner
all of a sudden.
I decided to win and come back,
no matter what.
Today's Deathmatch is...
Black Village.
(Black Village)
In Black Village, you take turns...
to place tiles.
You win scores...
according to your area.
Using your spatial perception
and strategic thinking,
you need to occupy a larger area
than the other players.
For each round, six tiles to select...
and six tiles for preview
for the next round are revealed.
Players take turns...
to select one tile left
among the ones that can be selected...
and place it on the board.
When you place a tile,
it needs to touch sides...
with previously placed tiles,
and the shapes of the fields
and roads drawn on the tiles...
must connect.
After placing a tile,
if no one owns the fields or roads...
included in the tile,
you can place your piece on it...
to make it your area.
On the bottom of the pieces,
there are numbers from 1 to 3.
Each player is given 3 pieces with 1s,
two pieces with twos,
and one piece with a three.
After all the tiles are placed,
if the whole area of the field...
is surrounded by a complete border...
or if each end of the road
meets the starting point...
or a field,
the area is considered completed,
and the piece placed on the area...
is returned to the player.
If you complete a road,
you get one point
per the number of tiles on it.
If you complete a field,
you get two points
per the number of tiles on it.
That's how players win scores.
If two or more players
have placed their pieces...
on a completed area,
each player adds up the numbers
written under their pieces,
and the one with the biggest number
wins the score.
If it's a tie, both players...
win points.
The game consists of 12 rounds in total.
After placing all the tiles,
the player with the highest score
wins the game.
The rules were very simple,
and it was such an intuitive game.
I thought it wouldn't be
very hard to play it.
Actually, I'm someone
who likes to play a game alone.
When it's a 1-on-1 or 1-on-1-on-1 match,
I can concentrate more.
So I thought
it wasn't that bad of a match.
I like that kind of game very much.
When I heard the instructions,
I felt confident.
For ten minutes, you'll check the tiles.
(Checking the shape and number of tiles)
(Road, three branches, right fork,
straight road, endpoint, L-shape,)
(corner and road, 7-shape, 3-way,
3-side field, field and road, spiral,)
(quarter, tunnel, 3-side large field,
1 half-circle, parallels, large field)
I tried to memorize the tiles...
the biggest or smallest in number.
I memorized the topographical features.
I mainly look at the fields...
because a road makes only one point.
As I see, many tiles...
were of fields bulging like a tomb.
So I thought I could complete
the fields whenever I wanted...
and I needed to expand the fields.
Frankly, I thought memorizing the tiles...
was meaningless.
It will be necessary to memorize tiles
for a big picture,
but for a small picture,
you can complete it in any way.
I devised a strategy
to keep completing small pictures...
from the beginning.
Tiles for Round One are revealed.
(Tiles for Round 1 are revealed.)
Preview tiles for Round Two are revealed.
(Tiles for the current round)
(Preview tiles)
We'll set the order.
Please pick one card.
Please give me the card at the center.
Kim Min A goes first.
Choi Hye Seon goes second.
MJ Kim is the last one to play.
Round One will now begin.
Kim Min A, please select a tile you want.
I'll have tile number three.
Place it wherever you want.
- Will you place your piece?
- Yes.
Kim Min A connected two fields...
and won four points.
In the case of a field or a road,
you think
you could win points really easily,
but once you try it, that's not the case.
I'm sure that I might not win a point...
because I'm missing one tile
after putting everything else together.
So, I went for winning small points
here and there.
I should win often
and as many points as possible.
That was my strategy.
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take this tile.
Place it where you want.
(She places a piece on the field tile.)
MJ Kim, please select the tile you want.
I'll take number five.
Place it where you want.
(She places her piece on a field tile.)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take number two.
(She places her piece on the field tile.)
Please select the tile you want.
I'll take this one.
(She places her piece on a field tile.)
MJ Kim, please place your tile.
(Kim Min A, MJ Kim)
(MJ Kim attempts to connect
to Min A's field territory.)
Anyway, in order to place over 70 tiles,
I figured they'd all get connected.
Then, whoever has more pieces wins.
So, I went toward Min A's territory,
and I tried to take the field
that Min A had connected to.
(Round 1's tile placement is over.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Three.
(The tiles from this round)
(The preview tiles)
Hye Seon, please select the tile you want.
I'll take tile number two.
(She places a piece on the field tile.)
(Round 2 tiles)
I'll take number six.
Place it where you want.
(MJ Kim, MJ Kim)
(Hesitating)
(MJ Kim tries to expand her field.)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take number four.
Place it where you want.
(Choi Hye Seon, Kim Min A, MJ Kim)
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take this one.
Place it where you want.
(The tile doesn't fit
with the field on the right.)
What?
(She takes the tile back.)
(Choi Hye Seon)
(She connects it to the road tile
on the opposite side.)
I thought Hye Seon didn't
really understand this game very well.
What's that?
I didn't think this game was that simple.
I'll take this one.
Place it where you want.
(She continues to expand her field.)
Kim Min A,
please place the tile where you want.
(Kim Min A)
Kim Min A, you connected 3 fields.
You win 6 points.
(Kim Min A currently has 10 points.)
(Kim Min A places her piece
on a road tile.)
Min A was starting to take points
little by little.
So, I was kind of wary of her.
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Four.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Tell me the tile you want.
I'll take number four.
(Choi Hye Seon)
(MJ Kim extends Hye Seon's road.)
She was placing some weird tiles,
so I thought that was strange.
(Choi Hye Seon)
(MJ Kim places a piece on the field tile.)
- Kim Min A.
- I'll take number six.
Will you place a piece?
(Kim Min A places a piece
on the field tile.)
I'll take number two.
(Hye Seon connected 6 road tiles.)
Number three.
(MJ Kim places a piece on the road tile.)
Number five.
Kim Min A, you connected 3 road tiles.
You win 3 points.
(Kim Min A places an extra piece as well.)
Small points can really build up
to be a lot.
I will take points
whenever I can take them safely.
I won't have any big picture.
Choi Hye Seon,
place the tile where you want.
(Round 3 tiles, Number 1 tile)
(Hye Seon connects her road to 7 tiles
as Round 3 ends.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Five.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Please select the tile you want.
I'll take number two.
(Kim Min A, MJ Kim)
(She stops MJ Kim's attempt
to combine their fields.)
MJ was getting too close to me.
I should never fight with her over land.
I might get pulled into it.
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take number four.
(Choi Hye Seon)
(Choi Hye Seon closed one side
of the road.)
Please select the tile you want.
Number one.
(Round 4 tiles)
I'll take the one right in front.
Kim Min A, you connected 2 field tiles.
You win 4 points.
- Will you place a piece?
- Yes, this one.
(Kim Min A places a piece
on the field tile.)
(Round 4 tiles)
(Choi Hye Seon closes off the road.)
Choi Hye Seon,
you connected ten road tiles.
You win ten points.
Your piece will be taken off.
(Choi Hye Seon currently has 10 points.)
Min A collected small points,
so I thought I might have a chance.
Please place the tile where you want.
Will you place a piece?
(MJ Kim places 3 pieces
on a single territory.)
If I connect two sides of that tile
that looks like a tomb,
I could complete this area
and take back my game pieces.
(She had seen
the next round's tile beforehand.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Six.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Please select the tile you want.
I will take number two.
(Choi Hye Seon places a piece
on the field tile.)
I'll take number six.
(MJ Kim starts to close off the land
that she had been expanding.)
MJ Kim.
You connected 2 field tiles.
You win 4 points.
(MJ Kim connects 2 field tiles
and wins 4 points.)
Is there a tile you want?
I'll take number five.
Please place it over here.
Kim Min A, you connected 2 field tiles.
You win 4 points.
Your piece will be taken off.
(Kim Min A. currently has 21 points.)
I'll take this one.
This one.
(MJ Kim is about to win 14 points
by connecting 7 field tiles.)
(MJ Kim doesn't complete her field.)
Will you place a piece?
(She places a piece on the new field.)
(MJ Kim is going after 9 tiles or more
to win over 18 points.)
I could tell that MJ was going for
one big win.
She kept expanding her field.
But that could be a bit risky.
That won't be easy to complete.
I could connect over ten tiles.
So, I thought I could win
over 20 points at once.
(Round 5 tiles, Number 1 tile)
There's nowhere to place it.
Will you place a piece?
Kim Min A, you connected 2 road tiles.
You win 2 points.
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Seven.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Please select the tile you want.
Number two.
(MJ Kim expands her land
without hesitation.)
I'll take number six.
Please place this on the field.
(Kim Min A places a piece
on the field tile.)
I'll take this one...
Please place the tile where you want.
All right.
(Their two fields are connected.)
Are we being connected?
Choi Hye Seon, you connected 4 road tiles.
You win 4 points.
Your piece will be taken off.
(Choi Hye Seon currently has 14 points.)
MJ Kim.
(Round 6 ends as they each place a tile.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Eight.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take number two.
Over here.
You connected 2 field tiles.
You win 4 points.
Please select the tile you want.
I'll take number four.
(Hye Seon connected 5 field tiles.)
Please select the tile you want.
Number three, please.
Will you place a piece?
Number five, please.
Place it where you want.
(Round 7 ends.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Nine.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
(Choi Hye Seon places a piece
on the road tile.)
Number four, please.
Number five, please.
Number one, please.
Place it where you want.
Choi Hye Seon, you connected 4 road tiles.
You win 4 points.
(Choi Hye Seon currently has 18 points.)
Place it where you want.
(Round 8 comes to an end as Hye Seon
chases after Min A.)
Place it where you want.
(Round 8 comes to an end as Hye Seon
chases after Min A.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round Ten.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
MJ Kim, please select the tile you want.
Number four, please.
(Round 9 tiles)
Place it where you want.
MJ Kim, you connected 5 field tiles.
You win 10 points.
(MJ Kim currently has 14 points.)
Your piece will be taken off.
(She takes back 2 pieces.)
Please select the tile you want.
Number six, please.
(Kim Min A)
(Kim Min A places a piece
on the road tile.)
Kim Min A, you connected 3 field tiles.
You win 6 points.
You connected 2 road tiles.
You win 2 points.
If I just keep building up
points safely...
in the beginning
without getting too greedy,
I was sure I would win this game.
Please select the tile you want.
I'll take number one.
(Hye Seon is far behind Min A.)
(With 9 tiles,
this field will be at least 18 points.)
I thought I should take those points,
no matter what it took.
The one over there.
- Will you place a piece?
- Yes.
(MJ Kim places a piece on the field tile.)
I'll take the road tile.
(Kim Min A connects 4 road tiles
and wins 4 points.)
Kim Min A, you connected 4 road tiles.
You win 4 points.
Your piece will be taken off.
Choi Hye Seon,
place the tile where you want.
(Round 9 tiles, Number 3 tile)
(She can't place the tile
in the empty spot.)
(Choi Hye Seon, Kim Min A)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round 11.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
(In order for Hye Seon
to complete her field area,)
(she absolutely needs the number 2 tile.)
(Desperate)
I'll take number two.
Place it where you want.
(Min A has the number 2 tile in her hand.)
Will you place a piece?
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take number six.
Place it where you want.
(She completes the lower side first.)
Please select the tile you want.
Number five, please.
Will you place a piece?
MJ Kim, you connected 3 field tiles.
You win 6 points.
Your piece will be taken off.
(MJ Kim currently has 20 points.)
Please select the tile you want.
Number one, please.
(Kim Min A places a piece
on the road tile.)
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
Choi Hye Seon, you connected 2 road tiles.
You win 2 points.
Your piece will be taken off.
MJ Kim, please place it where you want.
(MJ Kim places a piece on the road tile.)
I'll reveal the preview tiles
for Round 12.
(The tiles from this round,
The preview tiles)
(All 72 tiles have been revealed.)
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
(Choi Hye Seon)
(The next round's tile that
Hye Seon can use to complete her field)
(Contemplating)
(She wins 3 points for now.)
Choi Hye Seon, you connected 3 road tiles.
You win 3 points.
I'll take the first one.
(She connected the road tiles, but...)
(MJ Kim)
(But MJ Kim doesn't have
any more pieces to place.)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
The second one.
Kim Min A, you connected 3 field tiles.
You win 6 points.
(Min A doesn't allow them
to chase after her.)
(Hye Seon needs a big win.)
(She places a road tile...)
(and places a piece.)
The one on the bottom.
Place it where you want.
(She can win 6 points
if she just places 1 tile.)
(However,
MJ Kim doesn't have any pieces to place.)
I was thinking about that.
They were connected in three strands,
but I didn't have any pieces to place.
Kim Min A, place it where you want.
(Round 11 ends
with Min A's tile placement.)
Will you place a piece?
(Round 11 ends
with Min A's tile placement.)
(The tiles from this round,
The final round)
I'll reveal the tiles for Round 12.
These are the last tiles.
(Hye Seon absolutely needs
the number 2 tile to win 18 points.)
Unfortunately,
I wasn't the first player in that round.
(Choi Hye Seon is the third player.)
MJ Kim, please select the tile you want.
I'll take number five.
MJ Kim, you connected 7 field tiles.
You win 14 points.
(MJ Kim currently has 34 points.)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
Please.
(Round 12 tiles)
I'll take number two.
Place it where you want.
(Hye Seon can't complete her area
and win big points.)
Seriously. I was hoping she didn't know.
But she knew and took it so cleverly.
I resented her.
I kept looking to see
what would fit in there.
There was only one.
If she completed that area,
she would take about 18 points.
I thought I should keep her in check.
Kim Min A, you connected 3 road tiles.
You win 3 points.
Choi Hye Seon,
please select the tile you want.
Choi Hye Seon, you connected 6 road tiles.
You win 6 points.
(Choi Hye Seon currently has 29 points.)
MJ Kim, please select the tile you want.
I'll put this one here.
MJ Kim, you connected 3 road tiles.
You win 3 points.
(MJ Kim currently has 37 points.)
Kim Min A,
please select the tile you want.
I'll take number four.
(Kim Min A connects 2 field tiles
and wins 4 points.)
Kim Min A, you connected 2 field tiles.
You win 4 points.
Choi Hye Seon, place it where you want.
(Round 12 tiles, number 6 tile)
The game has ended.
This...
I was going to use this one here.
You knew that when you took it, right?
I will announce the results.
Choi Hye Seon, 29 points.
MJ Kim, 37 points.
Kim Min A, 52 points.
Kim Min A wins.
(Kim Min A is the survivor
of the Deathmatch.)
The Deathmatch is now over.
The reason
I chose the safest strategy was...
because I didn't want to go home
after gambling.
My goal was to return to Paradise,
no matter what.
I'm just happy that I won.
I think I didn't have
much combat power until now.
But honestly, I only want to win now.
I want to win so badly right now.
I want to come in first place.
The Deathmatch is over.
Please gather at the Main Hall.
The results of the Deathmatch
will be announced.
Bloody Game's
final eliminated players are...
MJ Kim...
and Choi Hye Seon.
Oh, goodness.
MJ Kim and Choi Hye Seon,
please leave Bloody Game immediately.
Eliminated players cannot return
to Bloody Game again.
Good work, guys.
- Good work.
- You did so well.
Good job.
- You did well.
- I was praying.
It's such a shame.
It had been a while
since I was on a survival game.
I feel disappointed that I couldn't...
play more boldly.
Even if I went to the Deathmatch,
I could've just done
what I wanted to do...
and go to prison.
Had I played more boldly like that,
I might not have regretted it as much.
People might think that MJ is
all about her physical strength,
but her brain works really fast too.
(In the 1st game,
MJ Kim read 1 move ahead of time...)
(and untied the rope quickly.)
(Before kidnapping Acau)
(They didn't say we all had to go.)
(Her keen insight put Hong Jin Ho,
the spy, in a difficult position.)
(The last team battle
with going to Remaining on the line)
(She contributed to their victory
with her meticulous memorization skills.)
Since she does her best
at the task she's given,
I can really rely on her.
I feel so grateful.
Since I'm a newbie at survival games,
it was kind of hard on my own.
But when things were hard,
MJ helped me out a lot.
She cherishes her teammates
more than her own self.
So, I was really grateful to her.
(Along with her great physicality,)
(she was a player with equally balanced
intelligence, morality, and strength.)
I'm being eliminated
almost at the very end.
So, I'm really sad.
I tried really hard to do my best,
but there were still sides of me
that I couldn't show off.
Still, this was a great memory,
and I really hope that Seong Beom
goes to the finals.
Hey, I'm not lying.
- Here you go.
- Hye Seon, you worked hard.
Good work, Jin Ho. I hope you win.
I feel relieved but sad to go.
When I looked back on everything
that happened in Bloody Game,
I think I was too rigid.
I thought I was good at handling people,
but I think that turned out
to be my weakest point.
(She was 1 of the 2
who solved the 1st problem.)
(And she made a huge contribution
to successfully rescuing those in prison.)
(With her persistent observation skills,
she successfully defended the looting.)
(She has both sensibility and the brains,)
(but Choi Hye Seon was always let down...)
(when it came to winning people over
to her side.)
(She was driven to be
the sacrificial player in the Remaining,)
(and the team collapsed in Paradise
in the end.)
I thought of people in such a naive way.
I think that was my greatest mistake.
There are many different kinds
of people here,
and since these are unique circumstances,
everyone will have different...
and peculiar thoughts.
But I hadn't expected that at all.
That's what I feel disappointed about.
This was my first survival game.
I was able to experience much more...
than I ever imagined.
That was really fun,
and I'm grateful for the experience.
What a shame.
(Bloody Game's final eliminated players,
Choi Hye Seon and MJ Kim)
Dramaday.me