(Bloody Mansion)
My lips are dry.
- Yes. I feel nervous.
- You feel thirsty, right?
(Kim Kyung Ran: A former announcer,
a runner-up on "The Genius")
(Xitsuh: Entered Brigham Young University,
a semi-finalist on Bloody Game 2)
(Chungju-Man: a 6th-grade civil servant,
number 1 YouTuber among local governments)
I'm nervous.
(Acau: A gaming streamer,
the winner of "Accomplice 2")
I saw a lot of people sitting around me.
I thought to myself,
"Kyung Ran will be on the show?"
I thought that the staff invited
people from the big league.
Kyung Ran. She made me feel a bit dizzy.
I know her history...
because I watched "The Genius"
so many times.
She can be very political
and use it to her advantage.
She's good at recruiting people
to her side.
She will have an influence over the others
as she had done this before.
I think she will be leading the group.
I'll follow her a bit and ditch her
when the time is right.
I was like,
"So she's the famous Dualistic Queen?"
A friend of mine was explaining
what happened on "The Genius."
She was the Angelic Kyung Ran at first.
Then she became Kyung Ran of Hatred.
Afterward, she became the Dualistic Queen.
How could she be three things?
How could she form this Holy Trinity?
The player that made me nervous?
Hyun Seo.
(Lim Hyun Seo:
Graduated as a business major from SNU)
(and Seoul National University School
of Law)
(Surprised)
So he came.
- Hello.
(It was 15 minutes ago.)
(Sighing)
Hello.
It's been a while.
We filmed one of TV shows together
a long time ago.
One of my allies fell for his tactic...
and betrayed me.
That's how I got eliminated.
He's the one who got me eliminated.
I thought, "Shouldn't I battle him out?"
There must be a sense of competitiveness
I still held onto deep down.
Xitsuh.
I think he holds grudges.
How did you two meet?
We met on a competition show.
We went head-to-head.
- I lost.
- Gosh, you can't say that.
I realized that he held grudges.
He didn't have to say that
to other people.
Since he and I are on the show together
again,
I should wait and kill him off.
Well, I did have to get my guard up
around him.
What about the rest of you?
Have you been on competition shows?
- Well, my life itself is a competition.
- I see.
Same here.
(Lee Gina: Majored business
in the University of Hong Kong)
What was that?
Hello.
Welcome to Bloody Game.
(Kim Young Kwang:
A former goalkeeper on the national team,)
(competed in the 2006 and 2010 World Cup)
(Steve Yea: A professional poker player,
number 1 on the Global Poker Index)
We will now begin the first game.
The first game is...
(Kim Min A: A former weather forecaster)
Eliminate a Player.
Seriously?
One of the players will become...
an elimination candidate
in an hour through your vote.
Now, converse with one another amply
to understand each other.
And vote for one player whom you deem...
unnecessary for your survival here.
The player chosen by the vote...
will go to the Deathmatch.
The player will pick another player
to compete against at the Deathmatch.
The player who loses the Deathmatch...
will have to leave Bloody Game.
The voting for an elimination candidate
will begin now.
Please remember that
you will pay the price for all decisions.
The voting will be closed after an hour.
(The voting begins.)
My gosh.
To be honest, it was so cruel.
We had just met, but we have to pick
an elimination candidate.
But if there was a player
I couldn't mix well with...
or a player I didn't feel comfortable
around for some reason,
a part of me wanted to get rid of them.
It's only right
to eliminate strong players.
If winning first place is the goal,
getting rid of them
would increase my chances.
Either Xitsuh or Hyun Seo should go...
since they're strong players.
Actually, I was contemplating
whom I should pick.
Hyun Seo looked like
he would be good at games.
Xitsuh was in the last season too.
He's been on this kind of competition show
many times before.
So people might want
to get rid of them first.
(Players identified as threats:
Xitsuh, Lim Hyun Seo)
It's fine as long as it's not me.
By default, if I don't speak up,
others wouldn't have chances
to turn on me.
So I didn't see any reason
to actively lead the group.
So it looks like...
there are 9 or 10 of us here.
- Is it 10?
- There are 9 of us.
This is a small group.
- It is.
- Yes.
Trying to figure out their intention,
there's no way they would keep
the same format as the first season.
- Right? Yes.
- I agree.
There's just no way.
I think there has to be another intention.
There must be a hidden intention
other than eliminating one of us.
Maybe, whoever gets eliminated
might join the other group.
And vice versa.
- Or the elimination might be real.
- That could be it.
- We can never predict that.
- It's impossible to know.
Yes.
One of us could get eliminated for real.
I thought this was the worst.
Everyone is the most careful
in the beginning.
No one's going to be aggressive and say,
"Let's pick this player."
Whoever starts that will be a target.
So it was obvious
no one was going to speak up.
I thought to myself that
there had to be a different intention.
I thought there had to be a trick.
That crossed my mind.
It's a big if.
If the score is tied...
- If the results are tied...
- If it's tied.
So if we all vote for ourselves,
all of us might be able to survive.
That could be one scenario.
There could be other players outside.
There could be another team.
I thought this could be a test.
To see how well we would work as a team.
Maybe, they gave us a chance
not to eliminate anyone.
I thought we had to try it out.
Because if it works, it would be amazing.
Since I spoke up and led the conversation,
I thought I should tell them...
I would take the risk.
I think picking ourselves
might be a good option.
But if it doesn't work,
I don't care if I get eliminated.
With that risk, I would like to try it.
"Why would he say that?"
If the vote was tied,
but one of us still had to be eliminated,
he told them to pick him then.
That's what he said.
"Why would he say that?"
"What's his hidden agenda?"
One of us was going
to be eliminated anyway.
So we're all going to vote for ourselves
for this one episode?
What's the point?
To be honest, there's a huge risk
in voting for ourselves.
I'm sure
one of us will vote for someone else.
Trusting each other naively
and voting for ourselves...
To be honest,
I didn't understand his point.
I thought, "Why would he say that?"
Then I thought, "Wait. That's not
a bad idea. That's pretty good."
I was grateful.
He said,
"If it fails, you can vote for me."
So I felt at ease.
We can try it at least once.
It won't negatively affect you guys.
- We can at least try.
- I see.
I'm on board.
- Okay.
- Then let's vote for ourselves.
- Right?
- So we should all write down our names.
- I'm curious about the system.
- Sure.
I'll go and vote for myself.
- Let's go around and do it.
- Let's...
- go around and vote for ourselves.
- Let's go with that plan.
I was certain that there would be a trick
with this game.
But I couldn't figure out
how it was inserted into the game.
Like the last season,
would there be a small number of people...
living in poor condition?
Or would there be a group of people...
managing us or watching us?
They could be betting on our decisions.
Hello.
- Will you vote?
- Yes.
(Xitsuh votes for himself.)
(The second voter, Kim Young Kwang)
When Xitsuh said that, I thought,
"Hey, he and I had the same idea."
(Kim Young Kwang votes for himself.)
(The players take turns to vote.)
(They all voted for themselves.)
(Number of votes)
(Xitsuh, Kim Min A, Acau,
Kim Kyung Ran, Lee Gina, Kim Young Kwang)
Gosh, is this right?
If I end up in the Deathmatch,
I'll win no matter what.
Fine.
(The seventh voter is Steve Yea.)
(Sighing)
I was certain that one of us
was going to betray the group...
and vote for someone else, not themselves.
So I had a lot on mind
regarding how to vote.
(Steve Yea, Acau,
Lee Gina, Lim Hyun Seo, Chungju-Man)
(Another player has the same dilemma.)
He thought there was a trick to this.
But what trick could there be?
"They'll make us take another vote."
That's what I thought.
(Contemplating)
I thought about it long and hard
in my head.
It wouldn't go as planned anyway.
That's not going to happen.
I thought a lot about what to do.
Voting is over.
Please gather at the Main Hall.
- There it is.
- My gosh.
The results will be announced.
Here are the results.
All the players received a vote.
There will be another vote.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
(Chungju-Man, Lim Hyun Seo, and Steve Yea
voted for themselves.)
It would be a lie if I wasn't hoping...
there would be something new like that.
I thought trying it wouldn't hurt.
We could try it out without risks.
Even if someone were to betray us,
that person wouldn't pick me.
The probability was 1 out of 9.
The probability of that not being me
was much higher.
"They wouldn't pick me."
That's what I had in mind
just like everyone else.
If anyone picked me to be eliminated,
that person would be a fool.
Why would anyone pick a weak player?
At first, I thought that
at least one of us would betray the group.
But it looked like they were all
going to vote for themselves.
So I voted for myself too.
If another vote must be held after this,
as per rules, one of the players
will be eliminated today.
I'm doomed. There was no trick to that?
I was certain there would be a trick.
I felt like a pathetic fool
for putting on this silly show.
I mean, without the trick,
I basically dug my own hole halfway.
Two things crossed my mind at that moment.
"This is nonsense." "I'm doomed."
These two things crossed my mind
at the same time.
So I thought...
one of us was going to be eliminated.
(The voting begins.)
(The countdown begins again.)
- I don't want to think about this.
- What should we do?
We have to think about what we should do.
What do we do?
So we have to vote for someone again?
All of us have to vote in an hour.
(Glancing)
I'll go and vote.
I thought going in to vote right away...
was the best survival tactic I had.
I thought I shouldn't hesitate.
There could definitely be external players
given the system.
Some people might try to save me.
Or some might not want to eliminate me
because they find me suspicious.
I thought, "Let's gamble."
"I'll brace myself."
That was how I would play it.
No one could be
as threatening as a lunatic...
who had given up on everything.
Seriously. This is way too harsh.
I'm done.
Let's go with the same order.
I'll go next.
Hyun Seo went after me.
He's like a machine.
He's someone who's clear
when it comes to gains and losses.
(The second voter is Lim Hyun Seo.)
I voted for Xitsuh.
He told everyone to vote for him
if his plan didn't work.
(Xitsuh)
He told us to vote for him.
I do what I'm told.
(The third voter is Chungju-Man.)
(Xitsuh)
I voted for Xitsuh.
This is a competition in the end.
We have to eliminate strong players.
Well, I had a reason to vote for him too.
(Chungju-Man votes for Xitsuh.)
(In no time, Xitsuh gets 2 votes.)
Who's next?
I was bracing myself.
I only thought about whom I was going
to pick for the Deathmatch.
- Who voted so far?
- Yes.
The three of us.
- Hyun Seo,
- Hyun Seo.
- Xitsuh, and Chungju-Man.
- I see. They already voted.
(Glancing)
(There's only silence in the mansion.)
Gosh, what do I do?
What do I do?
I don't know what to do.
People stopped talking.
And no one went to vote.
I think people were contemplating...
about voting for Xitsuh.
To be honest,
I only had one thought in mind.
"How can I play politics here,"
"so I don't become
an elimination candidate?"
This is so hard. Seriously.
It's about what you said earlier, Xitsuh.
Does it still stand? No, right?
You said we could vote for you
if it didn't work.
It doesn't matter to me.
But there will be a Deathmatch after this.
- Anyway...
- Even if I get the most votes,
- I'll have to pick someone.
- Right.
- So you can vote freely.
- I see.
Is that so?
All of a sudden,
he didn't say we should vote for him.
Seeing how he didn't say
we could vote for him afterward...
To be honest, I didn't want to see him go.
That was really tough for me.
Gosh, I don't know what to do.
It's so hard.
Telling them to vote for me
after all was said and done...
was unnecessary in my opinion.
I have a lot on my mind, right?
- Thinking about several possibilities...
- Right.
I have way too many thoughts in my head.
Right. I agree.
- I would picture what would happen.
- Yes.
- I would picture other scenarios too.
I hated seeing other people...
unable to make a decision
and pondering about it for a long time.
When other people were contemplating,
I usually took the role
of leading the group to a decision.
Shall I go then?
I'll make it quick.
I really don't know what to do.
This is crazy.
Let's go.
We're stalling way too much time.
It was tough because no matter how hard
I thought about it, there wasn't a way.
Xitsuh is like a veteran player
on shows like this.
So I didn't want him to get eliminated.
"If I'm wrong, you can eliminate me."
He clearly said that.
I thought there was a high chance
that they would pick Xitsuh.
But...
that would be a bummer.
I did think I should vote for him...
since he volunteered to be eliminated.
Voting is over.
Please gather at the Main Hall.
- There it is.
- The results will be announced.
Here are the results.
If winning first place is the goal,
it's only right
to eliminate strong players.
I didn't want to see Xitsuh
get eliminated.
I'll be honest. I'm doomed.
I dug my own grave.
The first elimination candidate
of Bloody Game is...
Kim Young Kwang.
(The elimination candidate is
Kim Young Kwang.)
Anyway, we would pick one player.
There was something Kyung Ran said.
She indirectly hinted that
we should vote for Young Kwang.
That crossed my mind
when I was about to vote.
(30 minutes ago)
Shall I go then?
I'll make it quick.
I really don't know what to do.
This is crazy.
(Young Kwang went to vote.)
But I'm concerned that Young Kwang
might not fully be aware of the rules.
After this, there will be a Deathmatch.
I'm not sure if he gets that concept.
Right.
With this direction, we might be able...
to get rid of Young Kwang, not Xitsuh.
I thought that...
Xitsuh would be more helpful to me
than Young Kwang...
during games.
I think I'll vote for Young Kwang.
I agreed with what Kyung Ran said.
I played politics there.
Ms. Beauty dropped some hints.
"Gosh, I don't think
he understood the rules."
She said something like that.
"Shouldn't we vote for him?"
She nudged people. It was like
she was poking them to vote for him.
As for Young Kwang,
I thought he wouldn't pick a girl.
Even if it meant that he would go home,
he would go head-to-head against a guy...
and get eliminated.
I thought among the two candidates,
there was a higher chance that...
Young Kwang wouldn't pick me
as his opponent in the Deathmatch.
That's when the air in the room changed.
I thought, "Let's not provoke them."
If I play it wrong,
I might come across as rude
or pretending to be kind.
I thought it was risky.
(Xitsuh: 3 votes,
Kim Young Kwang: 4 votes)
The first elimination candidate,
Kim Young Kwang,
can pick a player
who will join him in the Deathmatch.
On Bloody Game, Deathmatches
determine who gets eliminated.
The first Deathmatch...
requires instantaneous judgment skills
and psychological warfare.
The first elimination candidate,
Kim Young Kwang.
Please enter the voting room immediately.
I'll be back.
When someone else's name showed up,
I was shocked at first.
Then at the same time,
I was relieved that it wasn't me.
It would be a lie if I didn't feel that.
Pick one player who will join you
in the Deathmatch.
This is difficult.
We don't know what game it will be.
We all have different skills
we're good at.
I still want Xitsuh to go.
He's smart and works hard,
but it's not like
he has supernatural powers.
I don't think Young Kwang...
would go on a 1-on-1 with me.
"I'll go against a man."
I thought he would have that mindset.
I thought it was a crisis back then.
I thought it would be Acau or me...
because I seem like a weak one
from my qualifications.
I thought about how I would feel.
I wanted to pick someone who I'd feel
less guilty to eliminate.
The decision was made.
The player voted for the Deathmatch
with Kim Young Kwang is...
Goodness.
Lim Hyun Seo.
(Deathmatch player, Lim Hyun Seo)
Okay.
I seem like the weakest.
It looks like I can't use both my arms...
and I'm not fully able.
I think that's why he chose me.
My arms are fine.
I tried to look like a sick person.
"Don't bully a sick and weak person."
That's what I wanted to go for.
But I was selected for the Deathmatch.
What can I do when I look weak?
That's how I look.
What can I do about my looks?
That's an unexpected decision.
I did think Hyun Seo would get selected.
Young Kwang had the least conversation
with him.
He'd feel less sorry.
He seemed like someone who gets attached.
After telling others...
I will eliminate Young Kwang,
I tried to be friendly with Young Kwang.
I think I'll choose him.
(After Young Kwang returned)
I'll go since I look weak.
It would be nice if we had something
like that after the show ends.
We can gather.
Right.
I thought he would select Hyun Seo...
who he didn't bond or talk much with.
Honestly, Hyun Seo stayed the most still.
From the start of the game until the end,
he just went along.
"It wasn't me. How nice."
That's what I felt.
I thought
that would have acted negatively.
Goodness.
Instant decision and mind games.
My job is to play mind games.
I would have a higher chance to win.
Deathmatch.
I don't know who would lose,
- but let's do our best.
- Let's do that.
What is this place?
This is scary.
It'll be a 2-on-2 Deathmatch today.
Two-on-two?
Hold on. Two versus two?
What does that mean?
Your opponents in the Deathmatch
will be presented now.
What?
What is this?
Who are they?
There are other people.
There were two people waiting.
I was flustered. "What is this?"
I didn't imagine anything like this.
When I saw the two people standing there,
I noticed a familiar face.
There are more people going through
the same thing.
I will reveal
the rules of today's Deathmatch.
This is a 2-on-2 Deathmatch.
One person in the team that loses...
from the 2-on-2 Deathmatch will become
the first eliminated player.
The first elimination candidate
from Bloody Paradise...
is Hong Jin Ho, who came in last
in the first come, first served game.
(Hong Jin Ho, the last
in the first come, first served game)
The first elimination candidate
from Bloody Mansion...
is the person who got the most votes
in the elimination vote,
Kim Young Kwang.
(The candidate with the most votes
in the elimination vote, Kim Young Kwang)
Hong Jin Ho, the elimination candidate
from Bloody Paradise,
selected Choi Hye Seon as the assistant
in the Deathmatch.
She's the assistant?
It wasn't a match
between the team members.
The elimination candidates
of each team were going to go on a match.
Kim Young Kwang selected...
Lim Hyun Seo as the assistant
in the Deathmatch.
I felt so reassured.
Hyun Seo would be better than me
in using the brains.
I was reassured.
If I knew that,
I would have brought someone who is good
as my assistant.
The butler said,
"Select two players who you will be
on the Deathmatch with."
In Bloody Game,
Deathmatch decides who will be eliminated.
Kim Young Kwang,
the first elimination candidate,
Hong Jin Ho,
the player in the lowest rank.
You may choose one person
you will be on the Deathmatch with.
You may choose two players you will be
on the Deathmatch with.
Please make a selection.
Keep in mind that all decisions
come with a price.
So it turned out that the two...
weren't people
who would compete against me.
I was to choose two people
who will play in the Deathmatch with me.
I hadn't predicted that.
Even if I lost in that match,
I wasn't going to be eliminated.
"I survived."
"I can go home." That's what I thought.
The fact that I wasn't going
to be eliminated...
was a great thing.
I was happy, but I couldn't show that...
since Young Kwang was there.
We will begin the Deathmatch.
Hong Jin Ho, Choi Hye Seon,
Kim Young Kwang, and Lim Hyun Seo.
These 4 players will be
on the 2-on-2 Deathmatch.
I will reveal today's Deathmatch.
Today's Deathmatch...
is Switch Poker.
Switch Poker is a game where you have to
use your quick judgment and mind games...
to work together with the player
on your team...
to create a combination of cards with
a higher number than the opposing team.
There will be a total of seven rounds.
The first players nominated
for elimination from each team...
will be the main players,
and the ones nominated by the main players
to enter the Deathmatch...
will be the assistant players.
(Assistant players:
Choi Hye Seon, Lim Hyun Seo)
The starting team of the first round...
will be chosen randomly.
In the following rounds,
the teams will take turns to start.
Before the game starts,
each player will be given 20 chips.
Before each round starts,
each player will bet one chip.
In each round, each player will be
randomly dealt two cards...
from a set of cards...
numbered from 1 to 15...
and 1 of the remaining 7 cards...
is opened and revealed to the players.
Each player may take
1 of 4 actions on his or her turn.
First, turn over one of the cards
in the deck...
and change it to an open card.
Second, exchange one card
with a player on the same team.
Third, take one card from the deck...
and discard 1 of the 3 cards in your hand.
At this time, the discarded card must be
placed down so everyone can see it.
Fourth, do nothing.
After all players have had their turn,
each player in turn...
may make an additional bet or give up.
Players who participated in the betting...
will open both cards in their hand.
At this time, the player
with the lowest sum of numbers...
will get the open card
placed in the center...
and add up the total numbers
of the three cards.
The player with the highest sum
of the numbers on his or her cards...
is the winner of that round
and takes all the bet chips.
After seven rounds,
the player with the most chips
among the main players wins.
If a player runs out of chips...
before the end of Round Seven,
the team that player belongs to loses.
Switch Poker...
is a simplified poker game...
with fewer number of cases.
I was determined to win.
I would have to survive no matter what.
Putting the difficulty aside,
the moment I heard Switch Poker,
I shouted, "Great."
And I got the impression...
that they weren't good at such games.
So I thought it was an easy game.
You will have ten minutes
to plan your strategy.
To become the 1st among the 4,
we need the sum to be at least 20.
I think it would be okay
if the sum is above 20.
Luck plays a big part
for the cards we get.
That's right.
If I have only 1 card higher than 10,
Only 1 card higher than 10.
and you also have that.
- Then you could give that to me.
- Right.
- Since I'm the main player.
- That's right.
- You just need to survive.
- Right.
Switch Poker is a game where the player...
with the cards in his hand that
have the highest sum of numbers...
takes all the betting chips.
After the game ends,
the winner is determined...
by the number of chips the player has,
and the number of chips
of the assistant player ...
does not affect the winner.
Therefore,
the assistant players must give...
high-numbered cards to the main players,
and the main players
must take as many chips as possible...
from the opposing team...
as well as the assistant players...
before the end of each round.
However, if a player runs out of chips
before the end of Round Seven,
that team automatically loses,
so players should be mindful
of the number of chips remaining...
as they play.
When it's your turn,
and I need a high-number card,
I'll place my right hand...
on the table like this,
- that means I need a higher number card.
- I got it.
- At least 8.
You should give me at least eight.
The game itself isn't a difficult one.
So we could use sign language...
and place my hand on the table...
when I'm in a situation...
in which I need a high-number card.
Then Hye Seon could give me a card
if she has a card higher than eight.
I think we'd have a better chance...
if we have this.
Let's return together and eat chocolates.
What is counted as a high number?
When you randomly pick a card...
and it's higher than eight,
that's a high number
We have cards numbered 1 to 15.
We get eight cards.
Then the chances of someone getting 15...
is higher than we think.
There is one card covered,
and we have eight cards.
The chances of someone
being in possession of 15...
is higher than the card being in the deck.
That's right.
If you calculate the chances,
if you have 15...
and I also have 12,
the opponent can't win.
Unless they have 13 and 14.
If they have 13 and 14, it's a tie.
If you have 15 and I give you 12,
you can go all in.
There's no chance that you will lose.
I think it's a game about what we'll do...
when we have 13, 14, and 15.
In the end,
we need a signal in which
we can tell each other...
- what cards we have.
- That's right.
If we want to play a perfect game.
If we have 13, 14, or 15,
I'll give you this sign.
If you have one of them,
step on my foot as well.
If we both step on each other,
we'll definitely win.
We'll win in almost all cases.
Then we shouldn't do that
for 13, 14, and 15.
- We should start from 12.
- Yes?
For 14, 15...
Twice?
Twice.
Okay.
- Okay.
We were going to step on the other's foot
once if we had 12 or 13,
and if we had 14 or 15,
we were going to step twice.
We made a protocol in which
we can tell each other...
what cards we have.
That was so that we could control
how we bet.
We will begin Round One of Switch Poker.
I will distribute 20 chips each.
Okay.
(20 betting chips are distributed.)
I can't lose in this game
since my pride is at stake.
I only start fights that I can win.
We will decide the first player.
Here.
Hye Seon will start.
Hyun Seo will go next.
Round One begins.
Please bet one chip each.
I'll distribute the cards.
I had 8 and 4.
They weren't good cards,
so I was a bit concerned.
(Earlier, during their strategy planning)
That means I need a high-number card.
You need a high-number card.
(Stepping)
We were going to step on the other's foot
once if we had 12 or 13.
(Lim Hyun Seo's cards)
I will open one card.
The open card is 15.
Do you wish to switch cards, Hye Seon?
I will open a new card.
I will open one card.
The open card is 12.
- Jin Ho.
- I'll take one card from the deck.
I have 11, 10, and 6.
If I discarded 6, that made 21.
If I had 21,
that was doable.
- Hyun Seo.
- I will exchange with Young Kwang.
We were going to exchange cards...
when I had a high number.
- Young Kwang.
- I'll take one from the deck.
(He gets one card from the deck.)
(Stepping)
If we had 14 or 15,
we were going to step twice.
Young Kwang put down nine.
Please start betting from Hye Seon.
She bet one chip.
- Jin Ho.
- I'll bet too.
In the first round,
we were careful,
trying to read each other.
Hyun Seo.
I'll bet.
You bet a total of four chips.
Hyun Seo bet his chips too.
Young Kwang.
Young Kwang bet a total of six chips.
Young Kwang placed a high bet.
I had very good cards in the first round.
I had 13 and 14.
Will you continue betting, Hye Seon?
For betting more chips,
if I have my hand like this,
add one more chip.
But if I don't do anything,
- you can just call it.
- Just call.
Okay.
Should I go with it?
I'll fold.
Hye Seon gave up her bet.
Jin Ho gave up his bet.
Will you put an additional bet?
You can round up.
- Open.
- The betting ended.
The players who participated
in the bet can open their cards.
The numbers on Young Kwang's cards
have a sum of 27...
and therefore he wins Round One.
(The accumulated chips after Round 3,
Hong Jin Ho: 18, Choi Hye Seon: 18)
(Kim Young Kwang: 30, Lim Hyun Seo: 14)
Let's play safe.
Play safe.
When you look at the structure
of the game,
if you have the upper hand...
and the following rounds
go on without much trouble,
the chances of winning would go up.
Round Two begins.
I will distribute the cards.
(Kim Young Kwang's cards)
(Stepping)
(Hong Jin Ho's cards)
I will open one card.
The open card is one.
Hyun Seo.
I will do nothing.
Young Kwang.
I'll take one card.
Young Kwang took one card from the deck.
He put down three.
- Hye Seon.
- I'll take one card from the deck.
Hye Seon took one card from the deck.
She put down four.
- Jin Ho.
- Yes. I'll take one card from the deck.
Jin Ho took one card from the deck.
I took a card and it was 13.
He put down eight.
I had 24,
and that had low chances of losing.
Please start betting from Hyun Seo.
I don't have many chips.
You can continue that.
Hyun Seo bet one chip.
He bet two chips in total.
You can just call it or raise it.
I'll call...
- and raise it.
- You're rich.
(Kim Young Kwang raised 5 chips.)
What was that?
That was an aggressive bet.
Will you bet, Hye Seon?
I'll fold.
Will you bet, Jin Ho?
The game only had seven rounds.
So it's very important to earn points
in the first rounds.
I was very confused then.
So when it was my turn to bet,
I was in a situation
where I could continue.
But the game would end if I lost then.
(The sum of Hong Jin Ho's cards is 24.)
What number does he have
that he's making such a move?
(Stepping)
If you have 15 and 12, it's safe to say
that you have in the upper hand.
I thought the game was over.
My total was 24.
They were very good cards...
so I should have gone with confidence.
They were the best cards...
that I had to bet on.
I'll...
I'll fold.
Hong Jin Ho gave up his bet.
I had some regrets.
I would have won the game
if I won many chips.
Judging by the cards laid on the table,
there was a high chance...
that Young Kwang had very good cards.
He could hide that...
to gain more chips...
or go big...
so that the other opponents would fold.
Young Kwang was more of the latter.
He couldn't keep a poker face.
I'll fold as well.
The betting ended.
The winner of Round Two
is Kim Young Kwang.
(The accumulated chips after Round 2,
Hong Jin Ho: 17, Choi Hye Seon: 17)
(Kim Young Kwang: 34, Lim Hyun Seo: 12)
In the second round,
even though my cards were good,
it was so obvious
that Young Kwang's cards...
were way better.
So I folded.
It applies to poker and all other games.
You won't be bad at it
because you've never played it.
Your skills and energy are also important.
You need lots of luck too.
I think it's a game with many variables.
We lost points two rounds in a row.
So I thought I might lose.
Round Three begins.
I'll distribute the cards.
It's pretty hard.
(Stepping)
Our pace was good until the third round.
(Kim Young Kwang's cards)
The open card is 11.
Do you wish to switch cards, Hye Seon?
Among two cards, one was good enough,
but the other was pretty low.
I was seriously hoping Jin Ho has...
at least a high-number card.
If I put my hand on the table like this,
- that means I need a higher number card.
- I got it.
I'll switch one with my partner.
(Passing the card)
Do you wish to switch cards, Jin Ho?
I'll have one from the deck.
Hong Jin Ho took one from the deck.
Please put down one of your cards now.
He put down 12.
I thought we lost the round.
"We may lose."
The cards on the table were 11 and 12.
And I was holding 15.
So I guess they were holding 13 or 14.
Please start betting from Hye Seon.
She bet one chip.
I'll add two more.
(Jin Ho bet 3 chips now,
so the total is 4 for them.)
I'll hold.
Hyun Seo gave up another bet.
Me too.
Hye Seon, would you like to bet more?
The sign is the same.
If I put my hand like this,
you add one more.
- Okay.
- You got it?
I'll bet seven more chips.
Then, to keep the balance,
I'll add four more.
Actually, it was a rare chance
to take all the chips.
I can safely take all...
only when the situation and flow are
good enough.
I thought it was the very chance
to take her chips as well.
No more for now.
The betting is over now.
Hong Jin Ho wins the third round
as the sum of his cards is 27.
I got it.
(The accumulated chips after Round 3)
(Hong Jin Ho: 32, Choi Hye Seon: 4,
Kim Young Kwang: 33, Lim Hyun Seo: 11)
Round Four begins.
I'll distribute the cards.
(Choi Hye Seon's cards)
(Lim Hyun Seo's cards)
(Kim Young Kwang's cards)
(Stepping)
I will open one card.
The number is two.
- Hyun Seo?
- I won't do anything.
- Young Kwang?
- I'll switch one of my cards.
(He got a card from the deck.)
He put down three.
- Hye Seon?
- I'll switch one with my partner.
(She passes her card.)
(She received the card
with the same number again.)
Do you wish to switch cards, Jin Ho?
I'll take one card from the deck.
He put down nine.
Please start betting from Hyun Seo.
This is pretty hard.
Round Four.
I'll add some.
Hyun Seo bet two more chips,
so he bet three chips in total.
Young Kwang, would you like to bet?
First, two chips.
If you go too fast, I can't follow.
Three?
- Three. Okay.
- Yes, please consider my situation.
Hye Seon, would you like to bet more?
I'll fold.
Hong Jin Ho, would you like to bet more?
(Hong Jin Ho's cards)
I was holding 13 and 14,
so the total was 27.
That was the highest number.
There was no chance to lose.
It might be a draw at most.
I'll add three more chips.
(Hong Jin Ho bets 8 more chips,
so his total is 9.)
Hong Jin Ho bet nine chips in total.
Why is everybody so rich?
I raise the bet...
to put some pressure on Hyun Seo.
He was trying to trick me.
"Young Kwang, please be careful."
"If you go too fast, I can't follow."
It was certain
he had no intention of following.
All he would do was fold.
Hyun Seo, would you like to bet more?
If I do, I'll go all in.
I tried to give you a chance.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
If you say I die, I die.
I'll fold.
Young Kwang, would you like to bet more?
I'll bet three more.
And six more.
(Kim Young Kwang bet 9 more chips,
so he bet 15 chips in total.)
"What's going on?"
"What number cards make him
do such a bold move?"
"Was I missing something?"
"Did I get something wrong?"
The problem was...
the open card was two.
There was no chance of losing,
but to make things worse,
I have a sum of 27,
but he might have 15 and 11.
If his total is 26,
as the other two have already folded,
Young Kwang takes the card.
That was the only possibility
I might lose.
Other than that, I was sure to win.
The round went well, as I planned.
It was exactly what I wanted.
My cards are pretty good,
but I tried to maintain a poker face.
"His won't be 26."
"If things go bad,
should I be eliminated today?"
That's the destiny already set.
You don't need to struggle
as there's no way out.
Everyone came here to survive.
No one wants to be eliminated.
I'll...
call.
His can be 26?
The betting is over.
Players, who joined the betting,
please open your cards.
If his total is 26, I'm screwed.
Jin Ho's total is 27.
Young Kwang's total is...
also 27.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
"What a relief."
"I didn't lose at least."
I thought
Young Kwang was holding pretty good ones,
so we might win.
But a player with lower-numbered cards
gets...
the open card numbered two and may win.
I guess Jin Ho was also thinking
of that possibility.
As the two players' number sum is
the same as 27,
the chips players bet are on hold
for the next round.
- Then, we bet on those again.
- That's not bad.
(The accumulated chips for betting
are 34.)
Round Five begins.
- Whoever wins this round will win.
- That's right.
There's no reason to hesitate now.
Whoever wins this round will win the game.
This is all about luck.
(The accumulated chips after Round 4)
(Hong Jin Ho: 17, Choi Hye Seon: 3,
Kim Young Kwang: 18, Lim Hyun Seo: 8)
I'll distribute the cards.
I received two cards,
but at that time, I can't be sure...
if I should get a new card from the deck.
If he got good cards,
then I should receive a sign.
But there wasn't.
Mine was bad too.
As soon as we receive cards,
we are all muted.
There was no motion.
This is bad.
The open card is ten.
Hye Seon?
I'll have one card from the deck.
She put down two.
- Jin Ho?
- I'll also have one card from the deck.
He took one card from the deck.
Please put down one of your cards.
I took one from the deck.
It was pretty good.
He put down seven.
Within this rule, I was sure of winning.
I made almost a perfect combination.
"I won this round!"
That's what I thought, but...
Do you wish to switch cards, Hyun Seo?
Please give me some time to think.
I was so anxious for one reason.
The card on the board said ten.
I knew I needed to break that number,
but I failed.
In the worst case...
if Young Kwang managed
to turn his number...
to be higher than 16,
he was going to draw or win.
I thought I'd be in big trouble
if he figured that out.
I thought this game
could be overturned in one go.
So I assumed there would be something.
I wondered what to do alone
for a long time.
I'm going to exchange cards.
We had a high number open.
So I meant for him
to take small numbers at least.
I thought I'd never get to win
with my combined number.
So I was after taking the open card.
Do you wish to switch cards, Young Kwang?
I choose not to do anything.
- You have chosen not to do anything.
- Right.
Please start betting from Hye Seon.
I'll fold.
You have given up on betting.
Jin Ho, will you make a bet?
At that time, there weren't any chances
to turn the tables.
If I were to lose this round,
I was most likely to lose the game.
So I thought Young Kwang would
likely reckon what I had,
make Hyun Seo give up,
and claim the number ten himself...
to raise his number.
I assumed he was aware of it for sure.
The best situation for me was
to have all three do the betting.
Jin Ho, you have betted one chip.
I betted only one chip on purpose...
so that the other two wouldn't notice
this situation.
Hyun Seo, will you make a bet?
(Touching)
Call.
You have betted one chip.
Young Kwang, will you make a bet?
Call.
You have betted one chip too.
It's getting fun.
The betting is over.
The players who betted,
please open your cards.
Mine is 26.
(Hong Jin Ho, 26)
(Lim Hyun Seo, 13)
(Kim Young Kwang, 17)
Jin Ho, you have won the 5th round
with a total number of 26.
- The betting was too little.
- Right.
- It was too small this time.
- I know.
Hyun Seo betted just one in return.
Young Kwang did the same.
Then, I figured they weren't aware.
I thought I was going to win this round.
Did you bet low on purpose just now?
It didn't work no matter what I did.
I had horrible cards.
My cards were horrible anyway,
so I gave him one of mine...
for him to raise his number
at least by a bit.
But even with that move,
it wasn't going to go anywhere.
(The accumulated chips after Round 5)
(Hong Jin Ho: 53, Choi Hye Seon: 3,
Kim Young Kwang: 17, Lim Hyun Seo: 7)
Round Six begins.
I was going to win even if I folded.
That was truly thrilling.
Jin Ho, you have won the sixth round...
with a total number of 25.
How arrogant.
Hye Seon,
you have won the seventh round...
with a total number of 23.
I won at least once.
The game is over.
The main player, Jin Ho's chips are 58,
and the other main player,
Young Kwang's chips are 12.
Thus, Jin Ho is the winner.
- Good game.
- He's professional indeed.
- Don't mention it.
Switch Poker was...
one of my favorite games
which I was strong at.
And I managed to win safely.
I was relieved.
Above all, participating
in a lot of survival shows,
I'd hardly gotten eliminated
on the first day.
I hadn't experienced it until this time.
But despite this scary experience,
I fortunately was over the hump.
I sighed with relief at that moment.
Players shouldn't beat up people.
Let me announce the result
of the 2-on-2 Deathmatch.
The first eliminated player is...
the elimination candidate,
Kim Young Kwang.
Young Kwang, please go outside
and leave this place immediately.
How cruel.
I'm sorry I couldn't do better.
No, you did really well.
- Good work.
- Take care.
- Bye.
I feel a little bad...
because I wanted to play team games.
Still,
I didn't make any cowardly moves.
I played fair and square...
like the manly man I'd been.
I did the best I could,
so I have no regrets.
(Bloody Game)
(The first eliminated player
is Kim Young Kwang.)
The 2-on-2 Deathmatch is now over.
(The 2-on-2 Deathmatch is over.)
The survivors of the 2-on-2 Deathmatch,
Hong Jin Ho,
Choi Hye Seon,
and Lim Hyun Seo,
you cannot return...
to the mansion.
- What?
- Why?
Gosh.
It was unpredictable
what was going to happen here.
I got goosebumps.
I was ready to head back to the mansion,
take a shower,
and enjoy some potato chips.
I was all ready for it,
but then, I heard I couldn't return.
This is a group of dropouts?
- Can't they just...
- I won.
Why wouldn't they send us back up?
I just couldn't understand.
I won, but they wouldn't send me home.
What...
The new survival ground
of the Deathmatch survivors...
is the underground outdoor
survival ground here,
Remaining.
From now on,
you will continue to survive...
here at Remaining as a team.
Go downstairs and move...
to the underground outdoor survival ground
immediately.
I hate this. Darn you!
- How can this be?
- Seriously.
I couldn't stop myself
from swearing at that time.
I won the game,
but I couldn't go back home.
"You need to survive
in the wild Remaining,"
the announcement said.
Goodness.
To think I'd be left here...
As another person,
I thought it was a little weird.
This place was...
Even homeless people
wouldn't sleep at a place like this.
Here...
in the ruins,
I wonder if I can stay sane.
The wild? What the heck.
Goodness.
It seems I'm stuck in this swamp...
where losers can never escape.
I placed last today, at that.
It drains me even more...
both physically and mentally.
I feel a little helpless.
There's a survival ground in the basement?
I wonder how poor...
- its quality will be.
- Gosh.
It must be this way.
Underground? Doesn't it mean it's worse?
Lower than that?
No way. It can't be this basement.
What if ghosts show up?
Oh, my gosh. The lights are off too.
Gosh. I can't even think.
I just want to sleep right away.
We reached a rotten building
which was almost deserted.
I didn't know where we were going.
- It's too...
- Goodness, it's...
They want us to go lower?
I don't think that's right.
(Danger)
(Safety First)
(Basement 1st Floor)
I hear strange sounds.
That must be it.
Do we go down?
It's darn scary.
To where the lights are.
- Gosh.
- "Let there be light."
I don't get what's going on.
(They arrive at the last basement floor.)
What is this place?
Underground water is falling.
- It's too scary.
- Do we go there?
Gosh.
Life has so many ups and downs after all.
To think of that moment,
I get stressed out again.
I doubt I've ever been
to a place like this.
- Wait, I think it's there.
- Where?
Over there.
- What's there?
- There.
It looks like a memorial service.
Do you see it?
- Ghosts might show up for real.
- There.
- Hyun Seo. There you are.
- Yes.
Let's try going there.
They're calling us there.
Don't you hear it?
Did they have to make it this scary?
(Remaining Living Space)
They painted eyes...
- and stuff there. What a fuss.
- I know.
Watch your steps. There are puddles here.
- That thing?
- There's something in the middle.
- You know that box?
- It's annoying.
- What's that?
- The players from last year...
were so eager for it.
- What?
- It's a food supply box.
(A basic supply box for outdoor survival)
(Boiled eggs, raw sweet potatoes,
water bottles filled with water,)
(scratch paper, pencils, railway masks,)
(Paradise player cards,
and Mansion player cards)
What?
See? Darn it.
It only has water.
Thanks. Where did they get these?
- I think these are potatoes.
- When I was in the military...
- Eggs.
- Eggs!
- There are three water bottles?
- Yes.
Gosh, they at least have mercy.
Enjoy.
I was so hungry...
throughout the Deathmatch.
They provided something to intake
carbohydrates, proteins, and fats.
And water.
That came to my mind first.
I've never experienced this before.
I'm lost for words.
It was a little annoying,
but it was better than going home.
What is this?
Is something inside?
These are player cards.
- Let's sit down and take a look.
- Okay.
- Let's sit.
- You shouldn't.
Gosh, it's wet. There's nowhere to sit.
What is this?
It's horrible to live in the wild.
Here... We better do it here.
(The whole floor is wet
due to the falling underground water.)
Hold on. Isn't there anywhere to sit?
It can't be helped.
- Gosh.
- You have bad knees.
I think...
the cards show all the players
in each team.
- Let me see. Let's check together.
- These are...
- for Team Paradise.
- I see.
There are a lot of people.
Dong Min, me,
Pani Bottle, Yurisa,
Heo Seong Beom, Choi Hye Seon.
This is crazy.
(Jang Dong Min, Hong Jin Ho,
Choi Hye Seon, Pani Bottle,)
(Heo Seong Beom, Joo Eon Kyu,
MJ Kim, Si Yoon, Yurisa)
What the? A former martial arts player?
- I guess she's a good fighter.
- Who?
She must be good at fighting.
- She was a martial arts player, and look.
- I should keep a lookout for her.
- She manages prisoners in jail.
- Really?
Level-one brutal criminals, at that.
They were all impressive.
Jin Ho most fascinated me, to be honest.
I was fascinated at Bloody Mansion today,
and it seems a lot of interesting people
are in Bloody Paradise too.
To know that famous people
have gathered for the show...
and to be able...
to play games or have conflicts...
with them,
I'm excited.
These are Mansion player cards.
(Kim Kyung Ran, Kim Young Kwang,
Kim Min A, Chungju-Man, Steve Yea,)
(Xitsuh, Lim Hyun Seo, Lee Gina, Acau)
You went to law school.
I know this guy. No way.
- Chungju-Man...
- Chungju-Man.
- Kim Kyung Ran is here?
- No way!
She is.
Kyung Ran is strong.
- I loved her.
- She is strong.
Kyung Ran is...
really strong.
I remember she was no joke.
I wonder what kinds of moves
she'll make here again.
What? Steve Yea.
- He's a poker player.
- I asked him a few questions...
about poker.
Really? He's good at it.
(Steve Yea, a poker player)
- What? Xitsuh?
- He's here again.
Xitsuh came.
He must have nothing else to do.
He joined again.
(He's glad to know.)
- I should've been on his team.
- I know.
We hit it off quite well.
Xitsuh.
Xitsuh, this punk.
I didn't expect
to have Xitsuh in the show.
It would've been so nice
if we were on the same team.
I felt a little bad.
Other than him, there was Steve Yea,
a skilled player
from the same poker field.
He was memorable.
I thought the other team
had quite the amusing players.
Wait.
Something has come.
The bell sound.
- What's that?
- This hopeful bell sound.
It always means
they provide you with something.
- The bell...
- Where did it ring?
Right, the bell...
(They may receive a notice
or send up a question.)
Here it is.
They're conscientious enough...
to provide the least necessities here.
Here it is. I found it.
What is this?
"Remaining?" We're Remaining?
This place is called Remaining.
(Basic Rules of Remaining)
Earlier, we saw Bloody Paradise,
- Bloody Mansion.
- Bloody Mansion, and...
This is Remaining.
- Remaining?
- Yes.
(Bloody Paradise)
(Bloody Mansion)
(Remaining)
(Bloody Game will unfold
in these 3 survival grounds.)
In any case,
we're aware of the secret information...
that the other players aren't.
It felt a little like privilege,
which I liked.
Now that I have more information,
I get curious about it.
It makes me a little anxious too.
"Basic Rules of Remaining."
"You are Remaining players
of Bloody Game 3."
"Survive in Remaining
and wait for a chance..."
- "to seize Bloody Paradise."
- That's...
That's where we were.
"New Remaining players will be chosen
through the same way as the first day."
- More will come tomorrow.
- We will have more.
We have this rule again.
"On the Day of the Raid,
any kind of violence is allowed..."
"and the rules of Bloody Game
are lifted temporarily."
As for the symbols, one thing stands out.
- The drawing in the middle?
- There's that triangular pyramid.
There was a strange sword.
- There were a lot of swords.
This thing was shaped like a pyramid...
- Like this.
- with an eye in the middle.
- It was made of glass.
- There was one on each floor.
It was in the swimming pool
of Paradise too.
The same glass pyramid.
I figured we were supposed
to break it with that sword.
But the hard sword was
in the main hall, right?
A real sword.
"One of the Remaining players
will infiltrate Paradise as a spy."
Gosh.
- "A spy player..."
- "A spy player may exchange messages..."
"with the other Remaining players
through the SMS Box in the pantry."
We can communicate there.
A spy...
I guess it's plausible.
We can say one of us survived.
Or a whole new face...
But it'll be strange if you join them
suddenly in the middle.
- You know?
- It makes more sense that you go.
If Hyun Seo suddenly joins Team Paradise,
we have to make up a whole story.
They'll notice for sure.
Rather than Hye Seon
beating me and returning,
it's more natural for me
to beat her and join them.
I'll be the spy.
I think that will be natural.
I'll look for what the symbols can be.
Let's communicate through the SMS Box.
- And...
- But the door is transparent.
- Really?
- Yes.
Then, I better move in secret
when there's no one around.
The food pantry's door is transparent.
And the place itself isn't spacious.
The shelves are aligned.
You can easily see what people are doing
if you put your mind to it.
He might get caught once
while putting a letter inside.
If anyone becomes
an elimination candidate,
they can choose someone
as a Deathmatch candidate.
- There will be voting for it, right?
- Right.
At that time, you should...
I should induce them to vote for those...
- who might be of help to us.
- Right. Someone strong, for example.
Who do you want? Someone smart or strong?
The two of you are smart,
so we need someone strong.
Anyway, is our ultimate goal...
- to take over Bloody Paradise?
- Yes.
- We'll go in...
- Our ultimate goal is...
to survive here...
until the Day of the Raid...
when we go to Bloody Paradise,
destroy all the symbols,
and take over Bloody Paradise.
That will mark the beginning.
But if we fail
to take over Bloody Paradise,
we'll be doomed.
The raid.
I want to do it successfully.
Everyone had this thought
when they saw me.
A nerd who only studies.
I have the strongest aggressive nature.
Everyone thinks
my shoulder is half-broken.
But it's actually fine.
I'm stronger than you all. This is a fact.
"You have to sacrifice
one of the remaining players."
"One can't participate in the raid..."
"and be quarantined
as an elimination candidate."
(One of the Remaining players
must sacrifice for the raid.)
One will be decided by a vote.
During the vote...
Three of us are voting?
- We'll have another two here. Okay.
- Okay.
(A vote decides the sacrificial player
and extra votes can be used.)
The sacrificial player will be
the candidate of Deathmatch.
He or she will be the scapegoat.
This is fun.
The sacrificial player seemed
like a passive role.
One will be locked somewhere...
and accept fate.
Will it be possible...
to peacefully choose
the sacrificial player by voting?
I'm worried.
I don't want to be the sacrificial player.
A person with decent strength
should not be chosen as the sacrifice.
Eat something if you're hungry.
What's this? Gimbap?
- A sweet potato or a potato.
- It's long.
The shape looks like
it's a sweet potato or a potato.
- This is too mean.
- I was right.
Is this all they're giving us?
A small sweet potato.
My goodness.
My gosh.
(Eating)
Do we need to wear the same outfit...
until the raid?
For goodness' sake.
I wore the stupidest outfit
I could think of.
For goodness' sake.
This place is... What? It's here again.
(The bell rings again.)
I think it will say
we must choose a spy to send.
This is unbelievable.
Even if I go, I feel like I should find...
more here before leaving.
Let me see.
- My goodness.
- "The spy player should..."
"go to Bloody Paradise immediately."
- Goodbye.
- We met for a short time, but...
- I'll go and try to build a foundation.
- Have fun. Okay.
Don't you think he'll do well?
He's a complex thinker.
I think he'll do well.
I'm worried about one thing.
It's something that Yurisa...
or someone with experience will point out.
There won't be an announcement
that I'm eliminated.
I think some might think that's odd.
I'm not sure
if Jin Ho is prepared for that.
- Stay healthy.
- You can do it.
- Stay healthy?
- Go for the raid.
Stay healthy until the raid.
I'm not good at lying.
I'll mix about 70-percent truth
with 30-percent of lies.
I can hypnotize myself into believing...
what I said is true.
The most important thing is...
my survival.
Everything ends once I die.
Simply put,
I can act as a spy until the end
only if I survive.
The longer I survive,
I'll have more chances to act as a spy.
The player to be eliminated is decided.
Everyone, please come to the Main Hall.
What did you do?
What if he comes in like
a homeless person?
All muddy.
As a result of the Deathmatch,
one player got eliminated.
Congratulations to everyone
who survived the first challenge.
- What?
This is the end of the announcement.
My gosh.
That was unexpected.
Everyone was confused.
I'll announce the player who survived.
"I'll announce the player who survived."
- It was hard.
- What?
- It was difficult.
- Welcome.
(Deathmatch survivor: Hong Jin Ho)
My goodness.
It's really intense from the first day.
What's all this?
I was immediately suspicious
of how he came back.
What did you do?
We had to play poker.
What was the rule?
Let me keep it to myself first.
I think it's important
to know about the games.
Someone who's been through
a Deathmatch is important.
Where did you play?
Somewhere like a complete ruin.
On the second floor.
- For the Deathmatch?
- Yes.
Did Hye Seon go home?
- Hye Seon?
- Yes.
Who's that?
The person who fought against me?
What? This is too...
I think he's a spy. He must be a spy.
He's a spy.
Hong Jin Ho is a spy.
It was the worst situation.
I thought they might find me suspicious,
but it ended up being exactly
that kind of situation.
Si Yoon said...
As an experienced player of Bloody Game,
I think there will be a spy.
In your perspective,
who do you think the spy is?
He asked, "Who do you think the spy is?"
But deep down, he's like,
"I know you're a spy, you jerk."
Whenever I say something,
MJ looked at me with a straight face.
They were very cold.
I'm a spy,
but more than 80 percent of the people
already saw me as a spy.
It was a difficult situation.
(Meanwhile, at Remaining)
Whose water is this?
- I think this is mine.
- Okay.
Let's sit here together.
Okay.
But we can actually sit here.
It's quite wet.
- I'll sit next to you.
- It's fine.
This is hard.
Are my lips pale?
There's some color.
Your upper lip is a bit pale.
I think there's some color.
No, I'm...
not positive at all.
Hye Seon has...
a bright, untroubled appearance.
Will she be the same tomorrow?
She asked if there was a lip tint.
Lip tint...
It's not the time to look for a lip tint.
I'm worried.
I didn't sleep
as much as I thought I would.
It was too hot.
I woke up earlier than I expected.
I need to make sure I get enough sleep.
It's making me crazy.
There's nothing.
- This is unbelievable.
- Why?
This is crazy.
It's insane.
Firstly, I was so tired.
I couldn't think about where I was.
I just fell asleep.
But the weather was too humid.
I was sweaty but I couldn't shower.
It's really painful
that my body feels sticky...
because I can't take a shower.
Is there a valley nearby?
I want to shower in the valley.
My goodness. The fog.
- My goodness.
- It's foggy.
This is absurd.
- Is it hidden?
- This place is a mess.
Windows are broken. What's this?
This is nonsense.
Seriously. This is absurd.
- What can we do here?
- I slept here.
We just slept...
Here.
- My gosh.
- This is absurd.
Seriously.
It's devastating.
This is absurd.
Dramaday.me