(Episode 28, Jealousy is the Sweetest Taste)
Lu Sen.
You boys.
Can't you be serious?
Li Er, come and help me.
Li Er.
We're a team.
Let's defeat Li Zhan together.
I'm my own team.
Li Er, come and help me.
Mr. Xie.
You're here.
You know, don't you?
I'm talking about Lu Sen's condition.
How can I not know?
He has been sick for 15 years.
Back then, the chairman and his wife died in an accident.
He was in a lot of pain.
Ever since then,
he has locked himself in here for 15 years.
He can't be around people.
He has to cook for himself.
He endures it even if he's sick.
Most importantly, no one came to see him.
Why didn't you visit him back then?
We've let him down.
It's not your fault.
It was an accident.
You never know.
It could've been avoided.
What do you mean?
I mean...
there must be a reason...
Lu Sen is avoiding me.
If you feel sorry about that,
then you should say that to his face.
Unfortunately, a simple apology...
can't simply make up for some mistakes.
But I'll tell him that I'm sorry properly.
Thank you, Mr. Xie.
(People who help are the happiest)
Li Zhan.
What are you doing here?
Lu Sen.
Let's talk.
So you're apologizing for Friday?
For Friday...
and for you.
Li Er came to see you?
There's no evidence.
But are you willing to trust me?
This...
is my dad's dashcam from back then.
It's yours now.
But I have one condition.
I hope to be the only one to take the blame...
all the mistakes.
So it's all true.
I can promise you that.
But Li Jing Cheng...
might not agree.
So you knew everything.
Then why are you still keeping us in the company?
Because sometimes,
I don't want to believe it either.
I have my choice.
What about you?
If your dad doesn't come to his senses,
what would you do?
What can I do?
I don't know.
But I'll do my best not to let anything worse happen.
If...
I'm saying if anything bad happens,
I'll stay with my dad.
See?
The choices we make are all the same.
Lu Cheng.
Will you give me another chance?
I...
I know it's wrong for me to embezzle public funds.
But I'll think of a way to make up for it as soon as I can.
You know, we've been friends for so many years.
You can't just sit there and watch me go penniless.
Right, Lu Cheng?
What on earth were you doing?
I only told you to cause a tiny error...
to hold up Lu Cheng's shareholders' meeting, okay?
Why does this scene feel so familiar?
It seems as if it happened a long time ago.
Did you take care of the lab?
I took care of it as you asked.
All the paperwork is being done under Tom's name.
He hid it as you instructed.
But...
He's in a bit of a hurry. He asks when will you see him off.
Tell him to wait.
At a time like this,
make sure he doesn't contact me first.
Yes, Mr. Li.
And...
Mr. Lu sent you an e-mail today.
He wants you to take the initiative to be investigated...
regarding the leak.
Otherwise,
he will reopen the embezzlement case from 15 years ago.
He really is Lu Cheng's good son.
Am I someone...
who can be threatened so easily?
Investigate me?
He has no proof.
Also, in his e-mail,
he attached a few photos from the dashcam footage.
That time when you drove out 15 years ago.
Didn't you say...
Didn't you say you took care of the footage?
How did he get his hands on it?
- Say something! - About the footage,
after we paid the driver,
he just disappeared.
We used every resource at our disposal...
to get the information back.
Every resource? What are you saying?
Keep looking until you find him!
- You hear me? - I'm sorry, Mr. Li.
Mr. Li.
Should we pull some tricks to stop Mr. Lu...
from going to the company?
No.
Not only will I let him to go to the company,
I will also make him take the initiative...
to make me the chairman of the board.
I'll tell them. He needs our help.
We have to do our best, right?
Let's get started.
Uncle.
Be my guest.
Let's talk about Shan Shan.
Do you know why is she so obsessed with inventing?
What do you think?
It's because of her ignorant dad.
You probably don't know.
Shan Shan's first invention...
was an ugly car wash machine.
She said she made it for her uncle.
And an alarm clock that can't be caught.
She said En Bao inspired her.
This kid. Such useless inventions.
Do you really think so?
Whatever it is,
as long as Shan Shan can't live a good life with it,
I will think it's useless.
Both of you don't say it...
but deep down, you care about each other.
This kind of care...
is what gives Shan Shan's inventions...
the charm that warms the heart.
You're the first...
who understands Shan Shan like that.
But I'm not the only one...
who is given warmth by Shan Shan.
If you give me your permission...
to be with Shan Shan,
I must be the happiest person...
in the world.
You're waiting for me here?
Uncle.
As soon as I'm done with things at the company,
I'll tell her how I feel.
You're very quick-witted.
You'll be able to provide for your family in the future.
Man to man.
Don't forget even after drinks.
Actually, what I'm most worried about is...
you and Shan Shan...
are from different worlds.
Yes.
Indeed, back then,
we were from different worlds.
My world is lonely and cold.
But Shan Shan warmed my heart.
She took me...
to her rich and interesting world.
So to me,
she is my world.
Her family is my family.
But her assets are not yours.
Don't even think about the inheritance.
No. All my assets are yours too.
No, you...
Where are your manners?
- Drink up! - Okay.
Hello, Mr. Luo. It's me.
I'm looking at the latest reports.
Something's not right with the cash flow...
of your department.
The outflow of this money...
is said to be still conducting an important project experiment.
What is it?
Even I didn't know.
Mr. Li.
Well, the thing is,
this project...
is managed directly by the board of directors.
It's highly confidential.
Our R&D department only provides resources.
The rest is out of my hands.
So you're saying...
I'm not qualified enough?
I wouldn't dare.
I'm loyal to you and your dad.
He knows about these projects.
So far, only the factory is bought.
You are a busy man.
I didn't want to bother you with such a trivial matter.
I can just approve it.
I remember now.
My dad did mention it to me.
I guess I forgot because I was busy.
Organize the details of this project...
and the location of the factory...
and send them to me.
If I have questions,
- I'll ask my dad directly. - Okay.
Okay.
Friday is already gone.
What would my dad want with a factory?
Mr. Lu, the smoke bomb has been released.
Do you think will Mr. Li do next?
No matter what he does,
he will leave a trace in a short time.
I see. I'll be watching him.
Lu Sen.
Uncle is drunk.
- Be careful. - Why did you drink so much?
If you can't drink, drink less.
It's okay.
It really is. Come on, let's go.
(Small Pot Noodles)
Watch your head.
Lu Sen, are you all right?
- I'm fine. - Okay.
You should go back now.
Okay. We'll go back on our own.
All right. Take care of him.
Don't worry.
I'm off.
- Bye. - Bye.
Be careful.
You made my uncle drink so much.
He's on my side now.
You're stealing my uncle now?
I'm going to steal you from everyone who likes you.
You're not drunk at all, are you?
I'm drunk.
You're drunk?
So what do we do?
I can't walk anymore.
You can't walk anymore?
Since you can't walk,
you can stay here.
I think a lot of people would want to take you in.
Stand still.
What will you do if I get picked up?
Then...
Then I'll take in someone else.
- Don't follow me. - It's not right.
How annoying.
Lu Sen.
Can I borrow Shan Shan for a minute?
You can go up first.
I'll buy you some hangover tea.
Shan Shan.
It's okay.
Don't you want to apologize?
I'm afraid you'll say something to piss me off first,
so I'll forgive you first.
How have the last two days been?
It's okay.
Everyone just doesn't know what to do.
Even so,
it's better than when you first came back.
You used to live in a shabby warehouse...
and had to calculate what to eat.
And you had a bad rap.
You were so rude to me, the delivery person.
You said you were producing the greatest robot in the world.
That bad, huh?
I'm sorry then.
Sorry?
I just think...
you're very cool.
You know why I always followed you?
Because...
I think you're always doing what you want to do.
And you always believe...
that you can make your dream come true.
I...
I want to be like you guys.
It's a pity.
You can make Friday.
I can only pretend to be Friday.
You know why we only order what you deliver?
It's because I'm nice.
Do you think anyone would do it?
Because we wanted Friday to be like you.
Friday is an emotional companion robot.
She was supposed to be based on someone...
who has warmth and is full of life.
Anyway, the longer Friday was with us,
the more boring she would get.
You even want to take advantage of me like that.
That's why, without you...
there is no Friday.
If that's the case,
I must be the kind of person...
who is written in a science book, right?
Even so, it will come after my name.
No, after the Alpha Team.
Fine, they can write about you.
At most, they will have a photo of you.
But I'm on the cover. Friday has my face.
That makes sense.
Everything will be okay.
Aren't you buying me hangover tea?
Where's the tea?
I've said everything I wanted to say.
I'll get going.
Shan Shan.
I'm glad that Friday was modeled after you.
Thank you.
You're sober?
I don't have to buy tea then.
You said you'd buy me some hangover tea.
But in truth, you were chatting for so long with him.
Get up here now.
Then give me 15 seconds.
Ready, go.
How many seconds was that?
Sixty-five.
Sixty-five?
Let's go.
- Carry me. - Okay.
Dr. Ou is on a business trip.
He gave me a device.
He said it can test...
the values.
And then...
Anyway, it's complicated.
You won't understand even if I tell you.
Yes, I don't.
Come here.
I'll check.
You can really see it.
Look.
You have a big heart.
This big?
Pretty much.
I think I should listen to it,
only then will we know.
You're so close. It'll only beat faster.
Really?
It's really faster.
Have you heard enough?
No.
This is where...
I bought your favorite oranges.
Is this not it?
Of course not.
Then...
I went through a lot of trouble to buy them.
Gosh...
Do you want some?
It's sweet, right?
Thank you.
It's okay. Go.
Why are you nicer to the kids...
than to me?
You're jealous of a child?
Jealous?
I don't know what jealousy is.
Would you like to try it then?
So jealousy is actually sweet.
Have another one.
It's really sweet.
It's sweet, right?
How are things going with the company?
Still working on it.
Almost done, I think.
Shan Shan.
We agreed not to get you involved.
I still made you worry in the end.
This isn't just about you anymore.
I promise you.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
Shan Shan.
Shan Shan!
That means...
When Tom was trying to force format Friday,
the AI black box created by Friday...
stopped the formatting.
From this point on,
we will have to take into account of an extreme case like this.
Did Li Jing Cheng make a move?
Shan Shan...
She is in trouble.
Help!
Even if you yell all day long...
and your throat bleeds,
no one can hear you.
It's you.
Why did you bring me here?
Although it's our first time meeting,
shouldn't you greet your elder...
when you see them?
That's so rude.
That's what Lu Sen taught you?
It's none of your business.
Ms. Yang.
Do you really think you know Lu Sen?
Lu Sen, that kid.
I watched him grow up.
On the surface, he looks innocent and naive.
But in fact, everything he does...
is only for his own personal profit.
If it weren't for me,
the company wouldn't be what it is today.
But what about him?
Not even a thank you.
Such a heartless child.
Do you think it's worth it...
for you to suffer for him?
Let's split up.
Search every possible place.
Pai Song.
Get Lu Sen's phone monitored.
Track any calls made from unknown numbers.
Got it.
Li Cha De, give me a hand.
Should I call the police?
I need to find out more about Li Jing Cheng.
If we push him too hard,
Shan Shan may be at a disadvantage.
I'll go with you.
No. Report to the police according to the situation.
And...
please inform Da Tang Zi.
Tell her to call Shan Shan's uncle.
Say...
The truth?
Or...
Lie?
Say...
that Shan Shan will be staying with Da Tang Zi for a few days.
Look at all this effort.
Just tell me what you want.
Tell me everything you know about Lu Sen.
Is it that as long as you're with him,
his condition won't act up?
Where's my money?
Where's the check?
Shouldn't they be ready by now?
Do I look that hard to bribe?
Do you really think I'm playing around?
Listen up.
Lu Sen's family is long gone.
But you still have yours.
Don't you have a younger sister?
She's still in elementary school.
So listen up.
Don't try anything funny.
Of course, you can choose not to say anything for Lu Sen.
You don't have to.
But you'll lose everything.
I want to see...
how long he can hold out...
if Lu Sen loses you.
Ms. Yang.
Li Jing Cheng.
Don't do anything to Lu Sen.
We'll see.
Li Jing Cheng.
Li Jing Cheng!
Let me out!