(Episode 22, The Hardship of Lying and The Possible Happiness)
Don't drink if you can't.
It doesn't suit you.
Are you really giving up on Friday?
I have to, sooner or later.
Before Lu Sen fires us...
hurry up and find a reliable team for the handover.
Then tell me.
Is there a better research team than yours?
None.
That's what I think too.
Fu Yang.
I feel at ease when I'm with you.
I'm willing to take one step closer to you.
But sometimes,
the closer we get, the less sure we are.
I don't know if one day...
you will give up on me like Friday...
just to protect me.
You and Friday are different.
You know it.
That's enough.
I'm afraid I'll sound more desperate than Lu Sen.
If I stay,
I'm confident I can do a better job on Friday.
I will be more helpful to Lu Sen.
Besides staying away from him,
what else can I do?
Give Lu Sen what he really wants.
Actually, maybe he doesn't even know what it is.
Walnut cake.
I peeled the walnuts one by one myself.
Eat it. It's good for your brain.
Da Tang Zi.
Do you have more coffee?
Don't drink too much coffee.
Even if you drink it all, you can't become...
a doctor of medicine in one night.
I have to do something.
There will be a way.
But you still need to eat and sleep.
Now, take a bite of the cake.
Dopamine secreted from eating sweets...
will wash away all the frustrations.
Then you can go to sleep right away.
Okay.
I'll go to bed after this.
I'm not sleepy anyway.
I'll stay here with you.
Let me know how you're doing when you're awake.
I'm worried.
The data is fluctuating.
What happened?
Da Tang Zi.
Da Tang Zi, come here.
It's morning already.
You didn't sleep all night?
Look at this guy. He's not dead.
Based on my level four English knowledge,
the Danish patient...
is not dead.
It's because he later...
found his lover back...
and they lived happily ever after.
Something like that.
Does that mean I can be like him?
And help Lu Sen get better?
Why...
did Dr. Ou tell me that this man is dead?
Is it because he doesn't want me to see Lu Sen again?
Or...
it was Lu Sen's idea?
Shan Shan.
Dr. Ou had no choice.
Everyone is just crossing the bridge when they come to it.
The hardest part is...
Lu Sen's current condition.
He can't touch people.
I...
I can stay away from Lu Sen.
But I just really want him to get better.
All right, Shan Shan.
Just do whatever you want.
Even if the whole world says you're wrong,
I'll scold them for you.
Don't worry.
If you have any requests,
just tell me.
Even if I have to use the ten pounds of meat on my body.
I don't mind exchanging them.
You're such a good friend.
Of course.
We're best friends.
We share happiness and burdens.
Da Tang Zi.
What's wrong?
Teach me how to cook.
You're cooking?
Here. This place.
Remove the prawn vein.
Here, try it.
Are you okay?
Come on.
Shan Shan, don't worry.
I'm here.
I'll take good care of Mr. Lu.
Mr. Xie, how about this?
Take the porridge. Just say you made it.
Okay?
He needs to eat it while it's hot.
It's good for his health. Please.
Mr. Xie.
Are...
Are you okay?
Who let you in?
I just wanted to sneak in...
and leave after dropping this off.
Who gave you the right...
to come in and out of my house?
I just wanted to see you.
See me?
What for?
To make fun of me?
I forgot.
You've always been like this.
You pretended to be a robot...
to make a fool out of me.
You pretended not to know me...
to rip my heart out.
To tell you how much I missed the robot in front of you.
Now...
What more do you want?
Do you want me to die in front of you?
- Come on. - Lu Sen.
Lu Sen.
Ever since I met you,
you're the first thing I see every day.
Every day, I just want to make sure...
if you are happier than yesterday.
We used to be fine.
Now...
Can we start over?
It's all fake.
All lies.
Right now,
I only wish for one thing.
That is...
to have never met you.
Lu Sen.
I'm sorry.
I know I lied to you.
But I can't lie to myself.
You said you couldn't live without me.
But actually,
I'm the one who needs you more.
I'm sorry...
Your 24 hours late-night mode has been set.
Your numbers improved a lot today.
Did you do...
or eat something?
IMU, close the curtains.
Easy.
It's okay.
You can do it.
I've done the inventory.
You're free to hand over Friday.
It's a mistake of our own.
We should be the ones to make up for it.
It's done!
Shan Shan.
I really can't let you in this time.
Don't put me in the spot, okay?
How about this?
You take my stuff inside.
I'm not going in there. Is that okay?
Shan Shan.
Mr. Lu's orders.
Anything from you...
can't go through this door.
Go home.
IMU.
Sleep mode.
Why did you buy so many oranges?
There are orange trees in Lu Sen's residence.
But he prefers sweet oranges.
If I find the sweetest oranges for him,
he's going to love it.
It's sweet. Try it.
Still not enough.
IMU.
Your numbers are good these days.
Were there any changes?
I saw her come by.
I'm hungry.
(Your numbers are good these days. Were there any changes?)
(I'm hungry.)
How did she get in?
Is he getting better...
because of her?
Why are you still working on it?
Look at the time.
Lu Sen has no appetite nowadays.
I need to find a familiar taste.
Maybe he'll eat then.
This is nice.
This orange is green.
It's not ripe, is it?
If even the green one is sweet,
this batch of oranges must be really good.
Not bad.
This is it.
Nice.
It is because of her.
You're here.
It's warm.
In late autumn,
it gets cold at night.
Come closer and you'll feel warmer.
This distance is perfect.
Stop opening the door for her.
Mr. Lu, you've wronged me.
I've never opened the door for her.
Do you think...
our door can stop her?
Mr. Xie.
Have you ever lied to me?
In life,
how can one say they've never lied?
Since you're asking,
then what about you?
You said you'd buy me the tools for the trees.
It has been over a year.
You didn't buy me anything either.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize for the smallest things.
Things that are easily forgotten...
means that they are not important.
They can be replaced.
Things that don't leave the mind...
are what you care about the most.
It's hedgehogs.
They came here last year.
I've seen them.
Great.
They're here again this year.
The hedgehogs have it tough in the winter.
When it's cold,
they will huddle together.
When their bodies come close,
it's inevitable for their spines to stab one another.
Then, they will separate.
Once they separate,
they could freeze to death.
And so,
they snuggle together again.
They probably think that instead of fighting the cold,
the pain of being stabbed by the other...
is easier to deal with.
But compared to animals,
I think humans are more afraid of pain.
People get attached to each other through hugs.
When there is attachment,
it will naturally hurt.
Why don't you go check out that orange tree in the greenhouse?
I wonder what's going on this year.
The leaves are a lot yellower.
What is it that you need?
I'm sorry, Lu Sen.
Lu Sen.
We were wrong.
I'm so sorry we lied to you.
We're going to tell you...
everything about Shan Shan pretending to be Friday.
But I want you to know...
that Shan Shan has nothing to do with this.
I was the one who forced Shan Shan to help me.
Friday.
If anyone lies,
please call them out right away.
That's all.
That's the whole process of our mistakes.
We don't expect you to trust us again...
or forgive us.
If you don't want to see us anymore,
the only thing we can do is to give you Friday.
It's the only thing we can do to make it up to you.
Of course,
if you need us,
we'll always be here.
Lu Sen.
You know I can't eat spicy food.
As long as you forgive us,
I'll eat a facing heaven pepper in front of you.
What's so special about eating facing heaven peppers?
Eat Carolina Reaper if you dare.
Or the Trinidad Moruga Scorpion.
No. That was what we agreed on.
I know you produce less.
Yes, I'm on my way.
You must save it for me.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Should I take you to the hospital?
I got it.
Lu Sen.
You're so gullible.
What are you doing?
I made this myself.
Try it.
And this orange may look green,
but it's actually really sweet.
I've tried it in secret for you.
If you really don't want to eat it,
you can put it around the house.
It's quite aromatic.
I thought it'd cheer you up.
I don't need you to do that.
Then what do you need me to do?
I don't need anything.
You can just leave.
Okay.
Then when you need me,
tell me.
I'll wait for you.
Lu Sen!
Listen.
The orange is really sweet.
You have to try it.
Please.