Craving You [1/2]
Hot, isn’t it?
Ah.
That’s refreshing…
Drink while you work.
Thanks.
Is it really hot?
Ugh, it’s hot!
So damn hot!
Looks like they’re about to roll.
They said we get a twenty-minute break!
And…
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
Yeah…
I can’t quite get into it.
Can you read the lines with me?
You’re fine doing it alone.
It’s not even that hard.
Just help me match the tone.
Please?
How am I supposed to do a melodrama with you?
What, like we haven’t done romantic stuff before?
You’ve always helped me run lines, right?
Ugh, fine!
Forget it, I’ll just do it myself!
I’ll run it alone!
Don’t go.
Why do you keep trying to leave me?
You know you’re all I have.
Aren’t you gonna read the lines?
Put that down.
Just reading lines…
doesn’t feel real.
Let’s stop.
Don’t go.
You’re all I’ve got.
If I disappear…
you’ll finally be happy.
Taeyoon.
Hey…
Jeha, we’re ready!
You should get going.
Yes, you can switch right away.
Okay.
You worked hard today.
- Thank you!
- Thank you
Yes, the sooner, the better.
It’s nothing serious…
Jeha can handle things on his own now.
It’s better if I take a rookie instead.
Yes.
He’s the face of the company, though.
Taeyoon.
Please assign him a good manager.
Not someone too new.
What are you doing?
I’ll call you back.
A “good manager”?
And what’s that about him “handling things alone”?
I can’t just stick with you forever.
Why not?
There are plenty of rookies to look after at the company.
You’re doing fine on your own—
Don’t go!
What if someone sees us?
So what if they do?
Jeha.
Throwing a tantrum won’t change anything. There’s protocol.
You’re the one who said you were leaving.
We’ve been together for seven years since debut.
And now suddenly…
You must have a reason for asking to switch.
There’s no reason.
I just want to work with someone else for a change.
Someone else, huh?
You really expect me to believe that?
Did I do something wrong to you?
No, you didn’t.
It’s just that…
I can’t work with you anymore.
Did I ask you to date me?
Or to kiss me, maybe?
Jeha!
Just—
Just stay by my side.
Is that really so hard?
Jeha.
Let’s stop this.
Guess that gives you a reason to leave now.
Do whatever you want.
Hey, Jeha!
What do you think you’re doing?
You knew, but pretended not to.
You knew I liked you!
I didn’t know!
And I won’t ever know.
Taeyoon…
You’ll have a new manager tomorrow.
Let’s pretend none of this happened.
You can just do that, huh?
Fine.
KISS KISS SXX