Craving You [2/2]
Yes, I’ll take care of Eunji’s schedule myself.
Jaehyung, please head to her house first.
Ah… I’m sorry.
Jeha insisted on filming even though he lost his voice…
How long was she out in the rain?
They kept shooting before she even dried off.
No, it’s my fault.
It’s not your fault either.
We barely managed to fit the ad shoot in.
She was so stubborn about not postponing it, so I called the director.
Just make sure Eunji’s schedule wraps up smoothly.
Still hates bothering others, just like before…
No way…
Jeha.
Shim Jeha!
What are you doing here?
You knew the passcode.
How could you film in that condition?
Did you take your medicine?
You’re not my manager anymore.
Leave.
Go.
Do you know how hard I worked to land that ad?
Listen to me.
Why do you even care?
Then why are you pushing yourself like this?
You think I’m doing this because I want to?
You think the company can’t adjust your schedule for you?
I have to work.
That’s the only way…
I can hold myself together.
Jeha.
Don’t worry about me. Just go.
Jeha!
Shim Jeha!
Do you know how hard it’s been holding myself back?
Why did you hide it from me?
I’m right here.
I’m not going anywhere.
I’ll get your medicine.
I don’t think he can shoot today.
He won’t go to the hospital, but please let the crew know.
Yes, I’ll call once he wakes up.
Okay.
Take your medicine and rest.
You need to bring your fever down.
Water…
Why are you hesitating?
If you’re gonna do it, do it right.
Jeha.
I’m not stupid—I know exactly what you’re thinking.
I’m not gonna ask you to be with me or anything like that.
I’m not good for you.
Did I ever ask you to be?
I’ll handle my feelings myself.
You just…
Stay by my side.
Can you do that for me?
How could I ever win against you?
They said they’re ready, so we can head out.
Yeah, let’s go.
KISS KISS SXX