Wait a sec.
Why?
Are you shy?
It’s not that...
It’s okay.
I can’t do this.
What do you mean, you can’t?
Hey, Song Jio.
What are you doing?
I’m sorry.
Sunwoo!
I’m sorry, Sunwoo.
Can you handle this instead?
Will that be okay?
Song Jio.
Go grab some new chocolate sticks.
Manager.
I apologize for the disruption—our new recruit hasn’t been fully trained yet.
We’ll make sure it doesn’t happen again.
It’s fine. Things happen during work.
Still, Minju, you need to train your rookie properly.
Why don’t you show us how it’s done, Manager Sunwoo?
Song Jio!
Didn’t I tell you to bring the chocolate sticks?
Not a BL [1/2]
Behold, that angelic beauty!
Shining like sunlight in the middle of the night!
Oh treasure as precious as heaven itself, light that appeared out of nowhere!
I cannot close my eyes to such beauty.
I never truly knew what beauty was...
Have I ever even loved before?
Have I ever... loved?
Thank you.
Minju!
Hey, good job out there.
Hi!
Hey, I saw your act earlier—you were pretty good!
Oh, no way.
I’ve still got a long way to go to catch up to you.
Oh, come on.
Call me Minju, not “senior.”
Really?
Yeah.
Minju.
Jio...
Minju!
Jio!
Oh, right—
Wanna take a part-time job?
Seriously?
What kind?
Could use some cash anyway.
Song Jio.
Hey, Jio!
What was that back there?
What do you mean?
You know exactly what I mean.
I just don’t think it’s for me.
You think actors only get to play roles that fit them?
Even if it’s awkward or hard—you make it real. That’s acting.
You call that acting?
You told me this job was acting experience and a paycheck.
But this? This is just...
...pretending to date for tips!
Pretending?
Yeah.
Then what does that make you, if you can’t even pretend?
This café’s a stage too.
If you can’t satisfy even one customer here,
what kind of great actor do you think you’ll become?
No matter how much you hate your role,
to the audience—it has to feel real.
No—
For that moment, it has to be real.
So what, you’re saying you can just touch people casually for the act?
Am I the crazy one here?!
I’m done.
Guess you’re right. I can’t satisfy anyone—not even one person.
What?
Do I disgust you?
Let go!
Didn’t you say you needed the money?
You gonna quit already?
You think I’m here just for money?
I’m here because—
Then...
Do it. One last time.
It’s just the two of us now.
No audience.
Put your whole heart into it. Make your first audience—me—believe it.
Then I’ll let you go.
You mean...
do it for real?
KISS KISS SXX