These things I cooked for you,
this will not immediately rot.
This won’t immediately spoil.
Just like my hopes for you.
Andeng, Ligaya.
Even in the darkest moment,
my hope will always stay,
and it will never falter.
Andeng, Ligaya, apologies.
Don't worry, according to the announcement
the electricity will be restored.
Come on. Let's eat.
There, I want you to taste my adobo.
I cooked it for you.
There.
Come on, go eat.
I want you to taste it first.
So?
How was it? Is it good?
It's a bit bland.
It's bland.
Oh wait, I'll add more soy sauce.
Andeng...
Andeng.
It's you Peter, it's all your fault!
- Andeng
- It's all your fault!
- You animal!
- Wait, calm down.
Hold on Andeng, I'm not Peter.
I'm not Peter.
Who are you?
I am Carlo, don't you remember me?
- Huh?
- I am Carlo.
Who's Carlo?
I don't know you.
Andeng...
- I don't know you...
- Andeng.
- I don't know you!
- Enough, enough.
Shhh... That's enough.
Don't be scared, okay?
It's me Carlo,
I'm the one taking care of you.
Andeng enough, calm down.
Shhh!
It's okay, it's okay.
Let's just pray.
My God,
please heal the heart of Andeng.
I will never give up on you.
Even at times you can’t
remember me.
That's enough, okay?
I can feel your sorrow, Ligaya.
Ma'am.
Even before.
I can feel it.
Biscuits?
Ma'am, biscuit.
Ligaya's such a poor child.
She's so young,
and yet she's all alone.
Do you know who's the
one who deserve our pity?
Who?
It's Helena.
You know, she's in hell,
because she committed suicide.
That's why this house
will be full of bad luck.
So you, Belen, and your son Carlo
should leave this house.
That mother and daughter
are drowning in debt.
Ligaya won't be able to pay you.
I know, I already asked
Carlo to pack his stuff,
we're just waiting for this
wake to be finished, right Carlo?
Here, coffee?
Here.
Ever since Peter,
believe it or not,
I wanted to take you away
from the hands of that demon.
Condolences, Ligaya.
What now, you're all alone.
Do you want me to live with you?
No, I'm okay.
Oh, dear.
There are a lot of evil people nowadays.
- I'm really okay.
- Ma'am, coffee.
In any case, you might no longer be here
by tomorrow, or the day after.
What?
You know that your mother owes me
a huge sum of money.
I can take this house
and apply it to her loan.
But don't worry, I can
think of another way,
in order for you to pay me.
But who am I to do that?
I was there.
But I’m not part of your life.
At that time,
I know that what you needed is silence.
And that’s what I have given you.
Mom, is that you?
That’s all I can do.
Mom?
Why did you leave me?
Mom.
I don't think I can
make it on my own, Mom.
Carlo, my son.
Mother.
Why aren't you dressed yet?
We might not be able to catch the bus.
Mother.
I won't be coming with you, just yet.
Huh?
Why?
I'll stay here for now,
I'll accompany...
Andeng, Ligaya.
You can't!
Ligaya won't be able
to pay you anyway.
She even only paid only a small
part of their debt to me,
and it even came from the wake donations.
Let's go.
Ma, I'll just follow you.
Go ahead.
[sighs]
Here.
Take care of yourself.
Don't neglect yourself.
Yes, Ma. Thank you so much.
There, I'll go ahead.
But follow me after, okay?
Yes, ma. Thank you.
I'll wait for you there, follow me okay?
Yes, ma. I'll follow you.
- Alright, I'll go ahead, take care.
- Yes, Ma. You too, take care.
Yes, Ma. You too, take care.
You take care, okay.
Bye, Ma.
It's good, right?
Until he disappeared
from your life.
But the curse he brought you
did not disappear.
Every night, different men
used your body.
It is as if that’s the only way
to fill your needs.
But who am I to judge you, Ligaya?
You own your body.
And here I am.
A mere house boy.
But despite that,
I will never leave you.
I’ll wait.
I’ll wait for you.
Miss Bebang.
Give us more alcohol.
Our alcohol is almost gone.
I’m just here. When Carding
attempted to abuse you…
Just list it in my tab,
I don't have money yet.
I'll take care of it, Miss Bebang.
I don't have money, bro.
- Can I have this?
- Why don't you just force her?
- What is it?
- She'll all alone in her house.
Don't you think if you go there
she'll just spread her legs?
I'll be able to taste you one day, Ligaya.
That's right.
Cheers.
Hey!
Don’t talk about
Andeng, Ligaya that way.
- Who's this guy?
- You're being rude.
What? Screw you,
who do you think you are?
Mind how you speak.
You're just a house boy, right?
As if you don't masturbate in the image
of that prostitute every night.
What?
You're so nosy.
Just go, I might lose my cool.
- Screw you.
- What's going on? Stop that.
I'll call the cops.
Weakling!
Don't mind them, Miss Bebang.
Stay there!
I'll just take a taste
of your Ma'am Ligaya.
Hey bro, where are you going?
Where else, but to taste Ligaya!
Ligaya?
- Who are you?
- Ligaya.
Ligaya, just one time!
Just this time.
Get out of here, you're drunk.
I'll pay you, Ligaya.
Don't fight it.
I said, I don't want to.
You like this, right?
Damn you, you're just a prostitute,
why are you acting out?
I told you, I don't want to.
Don't fight it.
Hey!
Where are you going?
Stay here.
Stop resisting!
Stop it.
Don't resist!
I've been waiting for this
for so long, Ligaya.
Come here.
- Stop it.
- Shh!
I told you, to shut up, right?
Why won't you listen to me?
Hey, you son of a bitch.
Screw you, who do
you think you are?
Screw you.
Asshole!
Damn you!
Help!
Stand up, asshole!
Son of a bitch!
Enough, I give up. Stop.
Ligaya, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Ligaya.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
Thank you, Sir.
Don't worry about it.
Just call me Andrew.
Thank you, Andrew.
Ligaya, I'm Ligaya.
Do you live alone in this house?
Where are your parents?
They are both gone.
My father.
He died three years ago.
While my mother.
She passed away last month.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, that's life.
That's why you're all alone.
You might need someone
to accompany you in this house?
You know, there are a lot
of evil people nowadays.
I can protect you.
I can do that.
Huh?
Only if you want to,
I can protect you,
night and day.
Are you denying there's
nothing going on between you two?
- You're the one  being malicious.
- What?
Huh?
It's all in your head.
- Don't make it about me.
- Yes, it's you!
You are so malicious!
We're just talking.
Talking?
Why is that her fingers,
her hands,
is inside your pants?
Why?
You're crazy, Ligaya.
Me? Crazy?
Who between us have
a mother who killed herself,
because of insanity?
You bitch!
- What?
- Get out of here.
- You're just like your crazy mother.
- Leave!
Leave! Leave now!
Damn you!
- Why?
- Leave now!
Damn you,
if you ask me to leave,
you'll go back to being
a prostitute? Huh?
It's better than,
being a useless like you!
- What did you say?
- You're just a lazy bum,
despite having huge body.
What did you say?
Huh? What did you say?
Be thankful, I'm kind, Ligaya.
Let it be.
It's our mess.
I'll be the one to fix it.
When Andrew hurt you.
I was there.
But what really is my role,
if in those moments,
I was there,
but I can’t do anything.
There's someone.
There's someone. There!
- There's someone there!
- Andeng, Ligaya.
- No, there's no one there.
- There's someone!
Shh. No one's there.
- There's no one.
- Andrew!
You came back.
Ouch!
It's okay.
Carlo's here.
I can't take it anymore,
I want to die.
I'm tired of all this.
I want to die, I don't want live anymore.
- I'm tired of this.
- It's okay.
But I don't want to
be like my mother.
Her soul is burning in hell.
No.
You're not like your mother.
The gods might have cursed me.
No, no, listen to me.
I did not respect my body,
that's why I deserve all this pain,
for a very long time. Ouch.
Enough.
You're not cursed.
Listen to me, okay?
Listen to Carlo.
You're not cursed, Andeng, Ligaya.
Okay? Listen to Carlo.
You're not cursed.
Enough.
That's enough, okay?
I'm hungry.
Andrew, I'm hungry.
The people are saying, he ate pork
but the pork has,
what was that,
mouth and eyes disease?
That's why he died.
- That's why I don't want to eat meat.
- What are you saying?
Fake news.
Why fake news?
That's what they've been saying.
This is actually what happened,
his daughter, Jeferlyn,
she's the one who placed
rat poison on the adobo he ate.
That's why Mang Lito got poisoned.
Really?
How can it be an accident?
She thought it's salt?
It's because, his daughter
wants to get her inheritance,
you know it's all about the money.
My goodness.
He might buy some chicken.
He's getting chicken.
Maybe, you just don't
have the money to buy the meat?
Bro, are you okay?
Don't believe these two,
they're just spreading fake news.
- Just ignore them.
- Geez...
For now I won't buy pork meat.
- I'll just eat vegetable.
- Right.
Moron.
Just like always, two kilos.
Oh, I got you. Here.
Here bro, I placed extra meat.
The extra meat is
for your Ma'am Ligaya.
Here you go.
- Thank you, Bro.
- By the way,
I've heard that Ma'am Ligaya
is getting worse.
It seems like she has some illness,
what was that, Alzheimer?
It's like an old one acting like a child.
Something like that.
Oh, bro.
I've also heard...
Dude.
She has a lot of money on her.
That's all cash.
The money she earned
when she was a prostitute.
Here's the thing,
why don't we divide it between us?
Seventy-thirty? I'll get the
seventy percent, you get the thirty?
No thanks bro,
I still have much to do.
Hold on, dude. Wait up.
How about this,
let's do sixty-forty?
You'll get sixty percent,
I'll get forty percent,
plus I'll give you a kilo of meat?
Are we good? Is it a maybe?
- No thanks.
- Hold on!
I'll make it two kilos?
What do you think?
Are we good?
How about this,
just so it's fair to you.
Fifty-fifty, let's share it like brothers?
I'll go ahead,
I really still have much to do.
Hold on, stay here for a while.
Maybe, you have a crush on her?
What's up with you?
She's already forgetful.
And she's full of wrinkles,
she's too old, bro!
Let her go, there's a
lot of younger girls here.
They are still fresh.
- Just pick one of them.
- What's wrong with you?
Bro wait, I'm giving you
a really good deal.
Come back here, bro.
Andeng, Ligaya.
Just wait for what I'm cooking.
You know what, I've actually
studied cooking this just for you.
You might like it.
You might think it's good,
and hopefully,
you remember my name.
It smells like ginger,
there's fish sauce.
pepper,
and lemon grass, too.
I won't forget it.
Andeng.
Go on.
Taste it.
Can you remember me now?
Every ingredient,
goes with your every poem.
Joel?
You were that ingredient,
that I was looking for,
which can give color,
in my cruel life.
And now, it’s Joel.
The kindest one.
The one with sweetest words.
Like you,
I thought he’s the one,
I wished...
he’s the one for you, Ligaya.
You're the rose, that blooms.
Start your love,
is the fragrance
that I cannot refuse.
It flows with the wind,
just like a flower in
the morning breeze.
Let's live together,
you can stay here.
We're okay, like this.
You know that there are
a lot of people looking for me, right?
There are a lot of threats.
It's dangerous to
love me for a long time.
I can do it.
Did you like it?
We both know you're good.
Good at what?
With words.
With those luscious words.
It's sweet.
Its so sweet.
My words used to be spicy.
But since we've removed the president,
it turned sweet.
Especially when I met you.
Hey, you whore!
You both are animals!
Damn you.
- You, whore, you are such bitch!
- Ma'am, that's enough!
How dare you, bitch!
Don't you know he's already married?
- Damn you!
- Ma'am!
You whore!
- You have no idea!
- Stop it, ma'am!
Hold on, who are you?
Who am I? I'm his wife!
Damn you, I'm Joel's wife!
You bitch!
That's enough!
Stop hurting Ligaya!
You're ruining my family.
Don't you know we
already have three kids?
Such a whore.
- Stop it!
- Ma'am, stop!
Lisa, stop it.
- Damn bitch!
- Liza, that's enough!
You're a prostitute.
- Let go of me!
- Enough, already!
- You're a whore!
- Liza!
- Ma'am that's enough.
- Stop it.
Ma'am, stop it, you're hurting someone,
don't hurt, Ligaya, Ma'am.
- That's enough.
- Let's settle this at home.
We will not talk at home,
let's settle it here.
You can't do this to me!
You bitch!
Ligaya?
Ligaya.
Are you okay?
How are you?
Why is that despite the large number
of men you chose to be with you,
why can’t I be one of them?
Do I need to be like them
for you to choose me?
Andeng?
Andeng Ligaya?
Carlo.
Andeng.
Here.
Is this from Joel?
But unlike them,
I’d rather choose to stay this way,
to stay with you,
My love,
even in the absence of the sun,
I am longing for the eventual
spring of the beautiful roses.
Thank you for giving
me the letter of Joel.
They left me again.
They always leave me.
Where have you been?
I said, where have you been?
Oh!
You got in to a brawl again?
How many times do I
have to tell you to stop it?
I've been waiting for you, Andrew.
Andrew?
It's Andrew again?
Hold on, where are you going?
Are you going to leave me again,
because you're scared?
Then what? You'll hurt me?
Then you're just going to leave me
behind just like that, Andrew.
Stop it, Andeng.
Can you please,
never call me names
that aren't mine,
Don't ever call me...
a coward!
Don't ever tell me that I'll hurt you.
and that I'll leave you.
Because it's just me.
It's just me who
never treated you that way!
Do you even know
where I have been?
No one can hurt Ligaya!
Remember that!
I defended you,
just like what I always do.
Enough!
You won't remember
anything I did for you,
because not one bit
you see any of those.
Ligaya's such a poor child.
She's so young,
and yet she's all alone.
That's why this house
will be full of bad luck.
You know, she's in hell,
because she committed suicide.
Here's some coffee.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Why is this so sweet?
But what am I really to you, Ligaya?
I didn't have the
courage to defend you
against those abusing your womanhood.
When they are trying
to slowly remove your dignity.
If I can only break every bone
in the hand of that
maniac which slowly
moves around your body.
I'm weak, Ligaya.
I'm sorry, sir!
- But I cannot.
- What the hell?
I'm sorry.
- Step aside.
- I'm weak.
Let them be, Miss Bebang.
Stay there!
I'll just take a taste
of your Ma'am Ligaya.
Hey, where are you going?
Where else, but to taste Ligaya.
Hey, what happened to you?
- Are you okay?
- Ouch.
Sir...
- What is it?
- Sir...
Sir, help me.
What help?
That guy over there.
He's planning to do
something evil against my boss.
I'm sorry I need to be somewhere.
I'm sorry.
Sir, help me please!
Here sir, take my money.
Take this.
That's all yours.
Just help me, sir.
Just help my boss.
Sir please.
Alright.
I'll take care of it.
I got this.
Go ahead, sir.
Even if I'm not the
one who saved you,
and it's not my arms
which helped you,
I'm contented to know that
you're saved from such great danger.
Are you denying there's
nothing going on between you two?
You're the one being malicious.
It's all in your head.
We're just talking!
Talking?
Who between us have
a mother who killed herself,
Even if I wanted to help you, Ligaya,
You're crazy!
- I cannot.
- Damn you!
What?
I'm such a coward.
- Leave!
- I'm weak.
Stupid, and useless.
Damn you, if you ask me to leave,
you'll go back to being a prostitute.
Be thankful, I'm kind, Ligaya.
Joel, Joel, get out here.
- Ma'am?
- Show me your other girl.
- Ma'am, what is it?
- Joel?
- Show me that girl, where are you?
- What is it, ma'am?
I saw my husband, entering here,
is her mistress up stairs?
I saw my husband upstairs!
He's with his other girl!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
I cannot calm down,
my husband is there,
and he has another girl.
I said let me go,
why are you stopping me?
This cannot happen.
- Let me go!
- Calm down, ma'am.
Let me go.
Calm down.
This cannot happen.
This is the reason why
my husband has been neglecting me,
it's because he has another woman.
Ma'am, calm down.
Calm down.
It might just be your paranoia.
I'm crazy too, ma'am.
What is it that's wrong with me?
Is there something wrong with me?
Why does it seem like
he cannot see me?
Why doesn’t he love me?
Stop crying, ma'am.
That's enough.
Go get some rest.
To be honest.
nothing is wrong with you.
So stop crying.
take a rest.
Ma'am, no.
- Don't.
- Why?
If he can cheat on me,
I can also do it.
Ma'am, this is wrong.
What do you mean?
You son of a bitch!
Are you just distracting me?
Ma'am, this is really wrong.
- Joel!
- Ma'am, hold on!
Joel?
- Stop that, ma'am!
- Liza!
You bitch!
You're a prostitute.
- Let go of me!
- Enough, already!
- You're a whore!
- Liza!
- Ma'am, that's enough.
- Stop it.
Ma'am, stop it, you're hurting someone,
don't hurt, Ligaya, Ma'am.
- That's enough.
- Let's settle this at home.
We will not talk at home,
let's settle it here.
Stop it!
You can't do this to me!
You bitch!
Let me go!
Ligaya?
Ligaya.
Are you okay?
How are you?
Are you feeling any pain?
Are you okay?
I'm the only one that...
you don't see.
I'm the only one you can't recognize,
and I'm the only one
you cannot remember.
the times when I left home,
my mother saw me
in front of you house.
And even before I entered your gate,
she wanted me to go home,
she said it's embarrassing.
If you think about it,
even your mother
she wants me to go home,
but I saw you,
I saw you, Ligaya,
you helped your mother,
and since then,
she allowed me to work here.
I will never forget that, Andeng Ligaya.
Because, every moment
I see you,
that's what I remember,
because of that small thing you did,
my life turned for the better.
That's why, if there's
something I can fix for you,
I will fix it, Andeng Ligaya.
My beloved Ligaya,
Each time I see you…
Behind the suffering carried
by the tears in your eyes,
I glimpse the woman
who longs only to smile—
to know, even just once,
the true meaning of her name.
Perhaps not today,
perhaps you cannot see it yet,
but I know,
someday, you will awaken to it.
And when that day comes,
may your heart hold fast.
Not to what I have done,
not to the words I have spoken,
but only to my name,
forever bound with yours…
with Ligaya.
Ouch, ouch!
What's happening?
It hurts!
What's painful?
My love,
even in the absence of the sun,
I am longing for the eventual
spring of the beautiful roses.
With love, Joel.
Carlo?
Andeng!
I was left behind again.
I always get left behind.
I just closed my eyes,
and they're gone.
I'm stupid.
I'm so stupid.
Those who turn blind eyes are more stupid,
than those who really are blinded,
such as when,
you force yourself to look,
even if it hurts you.
You know what?
I received a letter,
from my mother.
She's asking for forgiveness
for what she has done to me.
For abandoning me,
for leaving me.
She said, it's all her fault,
why...
my life's full of misery.
But my mother's wrong,
it's not her fault,
whatever happened to my life,
and I don't blame anyone,
because
this is my body.
It's my decision
to do the things I've done with my body.
No, Andeng.
The world has been cruel to you,
A lot of guys took advantage
of your situation and weaknesses.
I don't blame them,
I don't blame anyone.
At the twilight of my life,
I've realized that they are part
of shaping the person
who I've become.
All of them,
Joel,
Andrew,
Sir Peter,
even Carding,
all of them.
Why?
why those bad people,
are the ones you want  to remember?
Why do you remember them?
How about those people
who truly cared for you?
Those people that even if it's painful
and hard for them,
they chose to stay, just for you.
How about me, Andeng Ligaya?
Can't you remember me?
Even if you're not here,
but you are always here,
in my heart,
Carlo.
Still, I will do everything
for you, Ligaya.
I’d rather be the one to
burn in hell than you.
If only to end your suffering, Ligaya.
Just so you may take
your leave with dignity intact.
Thank you, Carlo.
Thank you, Andeng Ligaya.
Goodbye, Ligaya.
Farewell,
Ligaya.