[Love and Strife]
[Episode 24]
Even if I have to die,
I will drag that bitch's bastard
with me.
You're not like your mother at all.
You are
so...
So vigilant.
Mother never wanted me
to be like her.
Mother.
Mother,
Mother, Mother!
The guilty woman, Consort Shu, has been executed.
Mother!
Let me go!
Mother.
Father Emperor!
Kill him.
Did you see it?
Jiang Yunsheng!
Is the Emperor's health
really failing?
On the day Consort Shu died,
the shock was too great,
causing his blood to surge,
and the poison spread.
Now,
he's just clinging to life.
Why didn't
the imperial physicians prepare an antidote for him?
The only remaining Bi Luo antidote in the palace
was taken by the Crown Princess
some time ago.
Let's go.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
How is it?
All those involved in the rebellion
have been captured.
Especially Consort Shu,
she is sentenced to death,
along with her entire clan.
Why bother?
Her Shu family...
Father Emperor,
the Zhao family
doesn't have many left either.
Additionally,
I have something to report.
Speak.
I
have a dose of the Bi Luo antidote here.
Give it to me at once!
Father Emperor,
this is what I
obtained from the Crown Princess.
The Crown Princess has one question.
She wishes to ask for your enlightenment.
You want to coerce me?
Go ahead.
Your Majesty,
was it you who annihilated
the entire Xu family?
It was me.
Why?
The world says that the northwest frontier
can only prosper under the protection
of the hereditary Duke.
Is that reason enough?
The Xu family...
The Xu family never had any disloyal intentions.
Just because,
of such baseless rumors?
Is that reason not enough?
Father Emperor,
this confession of sins,
you should sign it.
Sheng,
what do you mean by this?
The people need to know the truth.
Whether it's the Zhao family,
or the souls of the Duke's mansion,
they all need to be appeased.
What a joke.
When the subjects are strong and the ruler is weak,
how can the empire last long?
If the deep-rooted illness is not eradicated,
how can I leave this land to you?
With my hands stained in blood,
you can be a wise and virtuous ruler for a lifetime.
According to Father Emperor's words,
your indiscriminate killings
are actually for my good?
Of course.
You are my son,
of course, I have to think for you.
This is also your mother's wish.
But before Mother passed away,
she only told me
not to be like you,
blinded by desire,
losing my true heart,
becoming a monster
only knowing how to manipulate power.
I
dare not forget day or night.
Jiang Yunsheng,
are you going to kill your father?
Father Emperor,
to live on
comes with a price.
[Confession of Sins]
Sheng.
Give me the antidote.
Quick.
Come.
Chuyun.
This antidote was originally yours.
You decide whether to give it to him or not.
Jiang Yunsheng.
I am your father after all.
The father who killed my mother,
and annihilated my maternal clan.
I have already signed the confession of sins.
Xu Chuyun,
quickly give me the antidote.
Give it to me.
Come,
give it to me.
Come.
Give it to me.
Father Emperor,
I believe,
in the court,
tragedies like those of the Zhao family
and the Xu family
must not happen again.
I take my leave.
Xu Chuyun.
Sheng,
bring the antidote back to me.
Bring the antidote back to me.
Sheng!
Give me the antidote.
It has been two months since the late Emperor passed away,
and all the guilty ministers have been executed.
I beg Your Highness to ascend the throne soon.
A country cannot be without a ruler for even a day.
Let the Ministry of Rites start the arrangements.
Your Highness,
should the coronation ceremony for the Empress
also begin preparations?
Approved.
The coronation ceremony for the Empress
shall be arranged according to the highest standards.
As you command.
Chuyun!
Where is the Crown Princess?
She was just here.
I will go find Her Highness immediately.
Master and madam,
are they going back to rebuild the Xu mansion?
Father and mother wrote in their letter
that they are already on their way back.
Speaking of which, after so long,
I somewhat miss
the days at the frontier.
My Lady,
don't you miss home?
Su Zhu,
you may leave first.
Yes.
You see it?
You want to
leave me?
I have thought about leaving you.
Your feelings for me,
I can feel them.
But Father Emperor and Empress Mother,
they were once so deeply in love,
yet later they...
I...
I promised General Xu,
if one day you wish to leave,
I definitely will not stop you.
To leave or to stay,
you decide for yourself.
Empress Mother,
I don't want to let her go.
I...
I can use imperial power,
yes,
I can use imperial power to control her.
I have this right.
But how would that be different
from my Father Emperor?
If I do this,
will I become
like him?
♫Lighting a pair of red candles to shield the cold moonlight♫
♫In the courtyard, intertwined crabapple blossoms stand together against the frost and wind♫
Chuyun?
Your Majesty.
♫But this time, falling for you is not a lie♫
Raise.
You don't need to bow to me.
Don't you want to leave?
♫Yet I'm still in the game, so how could I dare proclaim?♫
Do you want me to leave?
How is that possible?
But that day...
I thought about it these days.
♫Whose mask, whose labyrinth?♫
If I let something
that hasn't happened yet
♫I bury my love and hate, just to share each dawn and dusk with you♫
affect the present,
what is the difference between this
♫I dare not long for you, so I can only hide my feelings♫
and what the late emperor did?
♫Within the shadow of a blade♫
Besides...
♫Whose springtime, whose soaring feather?♫
♫I melt away my frozen walls, promising to be with you♫
This is also
♫Looking back, I see this love was a stratagem♫
the reason I want to stay.
♫Yet you have been by my side all along♫
You're pregnant?
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Empress.
Your Majesty is blessed with double happiness.
♫Through the mist, the light ahead grows ever clearer♫
♫And all along, you have been the truth I've been searching for♫
♫Whose mask, whose labyrinth?♫
Long live Your Majesty!
♫I bury my love and hate, just to share each dawn and dusk with you♫
♫I dare not long for you, so I can only hide my feelings♫
♫Within the shadow of a blade♫
♫Whose springtime, whose soaring feather?♫
♫I melt away my frozen walls, promising to be with you♫
♫Looking back, I see this love was a stratagem♫
♫Yet you have been by my side all along♫