Hawthorn
Red bean
Orange
They were all three cents
Cream
Two-color
Chocolate
They were all five cents
My memory is flawless
That's not right
The two-color popsicle was
three cents a stick
You remember it wrong
I remember it wrong
Impossible
I have a nickname
"Never Forget"
Ms. Liu
You be the judge
I also remember it being five cents
See
I remember it was three cents
Muddlehead
Stubborn mule
Grandpas, stop arguing
It's just a popsicle
I'll buy them for you
One for each of you
Is that okay
It's not about the popsicle
It's about proving my memory is good
Unlike some people
Who are glued to a computer all day
You think I can't use one
You know how to use it
My brain works better than a computer
Why would I use that thing
President Li
Jiajia asked you to reply to her WeChat
No
Where did I leave my phone
And you call that a good memory
Let me ask you then
Yesterday, did you play Mahjong first or
go fishing
Then the 500 yuan you owe me
When are you paying it back
Once I find the phone
Good
When did I ever owe you money
Is the two-color popsicle five cents
President Li
Let me introduce you
This is
Mr. Lv Tienan
He was sent by the company
to visit all you executives
Mr. Li
Hello.
Why are you shouting?
I'm not hard of hearing.
Not hard of hearing, huh.
Little Ma sent you, right?
Yes.
Right.
It's, uh, well...
Mr. Ma sent me.
Mr. Ma mentions you often.
He says you...
...are a great hero of the company.
Really?
Really.
That sounds more like it.
What else did he say?
He also said...
Mr. Ma said that you...
...have worked hard and achieved much.
And have a wealth of experience.
Right.
He said you...
...led our company through its growth.
You must be full of valuable experience.
Isn't that right?
He said you're probably idle...
...and should take these experiences...
Idle?
I'm busy!
I attend to ten thousand matters a day!
That's right.
Mr. Ma's exact words were...
...that amidst your busy schedule...
...you should find time...
...to write down all your valuable experiences.
The educational value for our younger generation...
...would be immense.
That is a very important suggestion.
However, although right now I...
Although...
...I am reluctant to leave...
...but...
...I really cannot...
...disturb your rest any longer.
I'll take my leave now.
Stay busy, old leader.
Who's next?
Elder Sun, Elder Fu.
And Mr. Zheng.
They are all in that VIP building ahead.
Are they all this hard to deal with?
Even harder.
Therefore, I have decided...
...while my memory is still good...
...to immediately start a rescue effort to...
...write my memoirs.
Yusheng, help me type.
You got it.
When the book comes out, the byline will be...
Dictated by Li Jianguo.
Compiled by Ji Yusheng.
You got it, no problem.
Ms. Liu, do you want to write one?
Your memoirs would surely be fascinating.
Me?
No, I'll pass.
I really have nothing to write about.
No, you have to write!
You must write.
I want to write one too.
I can't write one.
Look, when I was young...
...I was either pasting boxes at the neighborhood factory...
...or selling two-eight sauce at the grocery store.
If I write it, no one will read it.
Well, if you put it that way...
If I write a memoir...
...it would definitely be a bestseller.
Why?
There's so much juicy gossip in the arts.
My daughter acts in so many plays...
...and has so many fans.
Then...
Then I'll write one too.
Write.
Let's write.
Professor Fan, what about you?
Writing memoirs is for old people.
For a comrade like me who has just passed middle age...
...writing this is probably premature, isn't it?
Are you throwing up?
I resolutely resigned and plunged into business...
Why aren't you writing?
I'm thinking about this title.
Isn't it a bit too grand?
*Jianguo's Memoirs*.
Me.
Li Jianguo.
My memoirs.
Right.
Nothing wrong with that.
Okay.
Where was I?
Uh...
Going into business.
In the beginning,
Jia Zhixin, President Jia, and I...
just the two of us.
We started by flipping wire rods.
Wait.
What does "wire rod" mean?
Is it a Beijing snack?
Can you stop thinking about food?
Lead wire.
Wire rod.
Rebar.
Those were all...
scarce building materials back then.
Thanks to our joint efforts,
very quickly,
our company began to take shape.
It became...
a major enterprise with six people.
What are you laughing at?
A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step, get it?
So I led President Jia...
We worked our hearts out,
we cut through thorns,
we moved mountains...
Enough with the idioms.
So,
how did this President Jia later...
become the Chairman?
And you became number two?
Me?
Isn't that just because I'm too decent?
But what about Old Jia?
Before he stepped down,
he took his son-in-law...
put him in the top spot,
and kicked me down.
Think about it.
Without me, Li Jianguo,
would the Jia family be where they are today?
Grandpa Li,
come on.
My condolences.
No,
calm down.
How about...
we continue writing another day?
No.
Continue.
In 1997
That was a spring
The dazzling superstar of the Chinese world
Rose from my hands
Diva Bai Jingjing's Biological Father: Past Middle Age
100 Amazing Stories That Must Be Told
This title is great
Then let's start with me and this Bai Fengqin
Start writing from there
Okay
This...
No
Mentioning my ex-wife
I get so furious
I'm out of quick-acting heart pills too
No
Skip this chapter
Okay
Write directly about Bai Jingjing's childhood
Sure
Starting from when Bai Jingjing went to primary school
Her grades were excellent
Wait a moment
How did we jump to primary school?
Shouldn't we start from that...
Write from infancy?
Infancy...
I was quite busy back then
Didn't participate much
I'll make something up later
No, I mean, I'll recall it later
Just start from primary school
Okay
So she...
Which primary school did she attend?
Which primary school...
Is this important?
It is important
It has to be written down
That shows you have exclusive info
This exclusive info about primary school...
I...
I don't exactly have a grip on it
You call and ask
Right
You take it
Okay
Hello
Ms. Bai is filming
Who is this?
Uncle Liang
Hello
Yes, Sister Jingjing is filming
Yes, in Beijing
Not far from your retirement community
Sister Jingjing wants you to come visit the set
Good
She wants you there as soon as possible
Who told you to tell him that?
And "as soon as possible"?
Isn't this causing me trouble?
I thought you...
Are you stupid?
If he comes
What if he runs into my mom?
Then this memoir of Dad's will
temporarily
be put on hold
Just don't write it
You don't even know where I went to elementary school
You're just making things up here
Aren't you just attracting haters for me
Dad is doing this because
I missed out on that part of your growing up
so I want to
make up for it
Enough
Do you have anything else
If not, I'm going to study my lines
No
Look
Dad will just sit here and keep you company for a while
Dad can do anything for you
How about Dad becomes your assistant
That way I can take care of you every day
Do you know how to be an assistant
Well
Being an assistant is too simple
Isn't it just carrying bags, grabbing chairs, holding umbrellas
Serving tea, pouring water, and cooking
Massaging the boss's shoulders when free
Then what am I supposed to do
You may look ugly
but you sure dream big
Bai Fengqin
No
Why is she here
The daughter I raised with so much hardship
Why shouldn't I come
As for you, Liang
Please
stay away
from my daughter
Who is this
You two
Stop filming
Change
"with the assistance of comrades"
to
"all by myself"
"single-handedly"
"All by myself, single-handedly"
Right, good
Still writing
Can't you spare the kid
Then you type for me
Let me take a look first
How's the writing going
Old Li
Listen to this paragraph
It was May Day, 1980
My fiancée and I went on our first date
We watched the movie *Shaolin Temple*
It was truly an unforgettable night
How is it
Jealous, aren't you
Fed you a mouthful of dog food
Pah, you're the dog
Dog brain
*Shaolin Temple*
What year was it released
Wrong
It was '82, okay
Right
Look it up
I checked
*Shaolin Temple* really was released in 1982
See
Listen to this part of yours again
The poem she loved
I wrote in the love letter
The most memorable was Xu Zhimo's *Fragment*
You
stand on the bridge viewing the scenery
Never heard of this poem
Classy, right
Who hasn't heard of it
Check it
Who is the author
The author isn't Xu Zhimo
It's Bian Zhilin
So much for "classy"
Again
Listen to this part again
After the Spring Festival of 1992,
Mr. Jia and I flew to Shenzhen for the first time.
The free Maotai served on the plane...
Mr. Jia got dead drunk.
That's right.
I remember this very clearly.
Maotai.
It was definitely Maotai.
Can't be wrong.
Actually, it is wrong.
Free Maotai on planes...
that part is true.
But in the late 80s,
it was discontinued.
Look it up.
Hey, don't you have anything better to do?
Why are you causing trouble here?
Get out.
Me, get out?
This is my room too.
Where am I supposed to go?
Stop filming.
I said stop filming.
Do I have to turn off the phone?
Look at you.
You're causing so much trouble for Jingjing.
Couldn't you just stay in that nursing home?
Why did you run over here?
You've been scolding me for ages now.
I'm going easy on you in front of our daughter.
Don't go on and on.
How am I going on and on?
Can you two stop arguing?
You fight as soon as you meet.
Isn't it annoying?
Fine.
Old Bai.
Ma'am.
Can we sit down calmly?
You *are* sitting.
And have a talk.
You were just like this back in the day.
Nothing was ever good enough for you.
Pulling a long face all day.
Like everyone on the street owed you money.
Nonsense. Slander.
When was I ever like that?
Actually,
Mom,
you really were a bit like that.
Our daughter said so, I'm right, aren't I?
Actually, back then,
I put up with you for so long.
I really didn't want to divorce you.
Wasn't it just because back then,
you wouldn't let go of that one little thing?
No matter how I apologized or promised, it wasn't enough.
You insisted on divorcing me.
You apologized?
Admitted your mistake?
Was your apology or promise worth anything?
You were possessed back then.
You were completely deluded.
You were dead set
on leaving with that little vixen.
You dumped us, mother and daughter, just like that.
You're making it up, nonsense.
Am I that kind of person?
Actually,
Dad,
you are exactly that kind of person.
See?
Even our daughter knows about it.
Right?
And you still won't admit it.
Go on then.
Go live with that little vixen.
Why come back to find us?
Well, in the end,
I didn't marry her.
Aren't I still single now?
That's because
you left with absolutely nothing.
She despised you and wouldn't be with you.
That's not true.
Can you two stop arguing?
All these years,
how many times have I dreamt
of our family reuniting?
I even fantasized you two might get back together.
But looking at it now,
forget it.
You fight the moment you meet.
You smash things at the drop of a hat.
I remember it all now.
I beg you, don't meet each other anymore.
I really can't handle the embarrassment.
How about...
Old Bai,
we just
shake hands and make peace?
That's good.
Why don't you two just get back together?
It's great for Sister Jing's image.
Trending for at least five days.
That's not completely out of the question
I'm mainly thinking about
My daughter's career
What are you saying?
Your daughter?
That is *my* daughter
Bai Jingjing's surname is Bai
Think about it carefully
Did you care for her growing up?
What did you ever do for her?
Did you take her to the park?
Or attend her parent-teacher meetings?
Or take her to the children's hospital for shots?
Or go with her to tutoring classes?
It was me who endured the hardships
To raise my daughter into an adult
And make her a big star
You...
Now you show up
You just want to reap the benefits, don't you?
Let me tell you, Liang
You get out of here right now
Don't let me see you again
Look at you
You turn on people just like that
You haven't changed a bit in all these years
I...
I remember it all now too
I was right to leave you back then
I'm going
If I ever come looking for you again...
I wasn't looking for you this time anyway
Didn't I say stop filming?
Delete it all
Or we'll take up the weapon of the law
Everyone knows
If you don't believe me, let's ask Ms. Liu
Ms. Liu
There's a modern poem called *Fragment*
Who is the author?
It's Bian Zhilin, right?
See?
Bian Zhilin
I knew that
Right?
The Hong Kong TV star
You're talking about Guan Zhilin
Mr. Li
The first draft of your memoirs
I've typed it out for you
Here, take a look
Hurry, read it out
Read it
I just love listening to stories
Love listening to stories
Alright
I'll read you a section
Pick an exciting part
How about this part
The year 1997
Was a glorious year
At the time, with great foresight
I overcame all dissenting opinions
Financial investment, planning approval
I ran my legs off
I wore out my lips talking
Finally, in the place where I once fought
A Sanjiang Bridge rose from the ground
It was truly a bridge flying north and south
Turning a deep chasm into a thoroughfare
Keep blowing
You're blowing it out of proportion
I'm not blowing, this is real
Mr. Li
When we write an autobiography
We must seek truth from facts
It is not suitable
To exaggerate too much
I didn't exaggerate
Not exaggeration
It's pure fabrication
I...
I have a witness
The Chief Engineer back then, Hu Yuguang
Was my old subordinate
A good partner
He can testify for me
A bear harvesting corn
Pure nonsense
You don't believe me, right?
Tomorrow I'll go find Chief Engineer Hu
And verify
Some of the technical details from back then
Yusheng
Come with me tomorrow
Be my witness
Use facts
To strike back at his
Cynical mockery
Come in.
Xiao Hu.
Long time no see.
Who is this?
Mr. Know-It-All.
President Li.
Don't call me President Li.
I'm retired.
Xiao Hu.
No.
Old Hu.
President Hu.
How have you been lately?
Doing great.
Not working with you anymore,
how could I not be?
Uncle.
How can you say that?
That's just too...
rude, isn't it?
Handsome.
If you knew how we used to
work together back then,
you wouldn't say that.
I do know.
Back in '97,
it was you and President Li
who built the Sanjiang Bridge together.
At the time, President Li
showed great foresight,
overruled all objections,
and fully supported your design and construction.
You two...
weren't you great partners at work?
Is that how you tricked him?
Yeah, that's how I tricked...
No, how is that a trick?
It's the honest truth!
How come you don't remember?
How can I remember something that never happened?
Back then, you were clearly giving blind orders.
An amateur leading the expert.
Why do you think I changed jobs later?
Why did I come to this company?
It's all his fault.
How is it my fault?
That project back then,
we were on the same team.
That part is true.
See? Right?
But... however...
I said right from the start,
the geological conditions there
weren't suitable for building a bridge.
Did I say that or not?
Seems like that happened.
But that project of ours
was to benefit the local people!
Give me a break.
Actually, he...
just wanted to show off
in front of the locals.
Actually, the geological conditions 10km away
were much better for a bridge.
And the people in that county
really needed that bridge too.
So what?
I was a senior executive.
I fully listened to
opinions from all sides
before resolutely making the final call
to build the bridge at the original site.
Great foresight,
overruling objections, right?
It's true you were an executive.
But you can't just
meddle in everything blindly.
Do you know
what we call him in private?
Mr. Know-It-All.
Fine.
Enough.
Stop spreading that around.
Every place has a few backward folks.
Right?
Let's get back to work.
After that project was built,
didn't it benefit the locals?
The company also made a profit.
Half the credit goes to you.
Shouldn't half of it be mine too?
I had no part in a lot of it.
Let me ask you.
That construction team for the bridge contract...
...you decided on them, right?
That foreman, Liu Big Head...
...is an acquaintance of yours, right?
No, his grandfather and I were close.
I introduced him.
But...
...his construction team...
...was seriously underqualified.
Also...
...the project budget...
...you had the final say, right?
Of course.
I'm the head of the company.
My original design...
...was sturdy and durable.
And cost-effective.
But him?
He just had to meddle in it.
Nitpicking everything.
The bridge was nearly half built...
...and he insisted on tearing it down and starting over.
And what happened in the end?
The budget ran out.
We had to cut corners.
Finally...
...it became a tofu-dreg project.
Grandpa Li...
...is this true?
Why is this completely different...
...from what I remember?
Handsome...
...do you still think...
...I'm being rude to him?
How could it be like this?
But regardless...
...from a young novice...
...if not for me...
...if not for this project...
...would you have been fast-tracked to Chief Engineer?
You should at least thank me for that.
Yes.
I'm especially grateful to you.
The year before last...
...it rained for days, and flash floods hit.
That bridge...
...collapsed.
Collapsed.
Luckily, there were no casualties.
Later, when they investigated...
...who designed this bridge?
Well, there it is.
So...
...I changed jobs...
...and came here to do administration.
I'm especially grateful for that bridge.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
For giving me this black mark on my record.
How could it be like this?
Seems memory is quite unreliable.
Mr. Hu...
...I completely understand you now.
I just hope when I start working...
...I don't run into...
...a boss like Grandpa Li.
Why are you like this?
Whose side are you on?
I...
He has a point.
What happened next?
Brother Liang.
You're not writing your memoirs anymore?
Not anymore.
Professor Fan is right about this.
We are still young.
No rush to write memoirs.
Grandpa Li.
Are you getting rid of all these drafts?
Shred them all.
Don't leave a single word.
So *Jianguo's Memoirs* is halted too?
Through this recollection,
I realized many past events
don't match my memory,
or are even the exact opposite.
Many were just things I imagined.
So,
I decided not to write it.
Scrap it and start over.
Seek truth from facts.
Verify carefully.
Even the embarrassing stuff,
I will write it all down.
To warn future generations.
Yes.
Good.
Right?
Professor Fan, what are you strolling around for?
Writing my memoirs.
I need to trace back some details.
I came out to clear my head.
You...
Didn't you say you weren't in a rush to write them?
I thought about it again.
My precious life experiences
should be salvaged and excavated.
Left for the future
generations of students.
I expect it will cause
quite a sensation in the academic world.
This guy is bragging again.
Tell me,
why is he like this?
Probably caught it from you.
Right.
Who?
Everyone,
my memoirs
will start from the resumption of the entrance exams.
That was the turning point of my life.
The fighting year of 1977.
I stepped onto the university campus.
Hold on.
Which year did you say?
1977.
I'm Class of '77.
The first batch.
Wrong.
You students of the Class of '77
passed the exam in '77,
but entered campus in '78.
How is that possible?
Don't mess with my train of thought.
I have to go continue writing.
1978.
Must stick to the facts.
Another Muddlehead.