(PARBDEE TAWESUK)
(Yin Anan) (War Wanarat) (Yoon Phusanu)
(Jane Ramida) (Ohm Pawat) (Milli Danupha)
(Juniors Panachai) (Max Natthapol) (Ploy  Ploypailin)
(Gun Atthaphan) (Proymon Manasaporn) (Oab Oabnithi)
(Off Jumpol) (Kru Ouan Maneenuch)
(Jan Chan Jetsupa) (New Thitipoom)
(Ton Tonhon) (Smile Parada)
(Punpun Sutatta) (Up Poompat)
(Tle  Kittiphak)
Screenwriter Supervisor
(Puchong  Tuntisungwaragul)
Creative
(PARBDEE TAWESUK CO.,LTD.)
Production services
Executive  Producer
(ALISTAIR  DAVID  JOHNSTON)
(Siwaporn  Pengpol)
Producer
(Hlung  Lorjitramnuay)
(Puchong  Tuntisungwaragul)
(Patha  Thongpan)
Producer
(Watthana  Rujirojsakul)
(Thip-Apa  Ukongka)
(Inspired by a radio station’s stories.)
(Club Sapan fine 2 Classify)
Club Sapan Fine is back!
We’re finally here. How are you?
In the past week, how is your life going?
Is it better,
or is it going not fine forever?
Before the talk today, I have one thing
I’m proud to share with you guys.
Right now everyone
can listen to our previous talk online.
Before we answer the phone,
I have something to share with you all.
I’ve been thinking with myself that
I’ve run this show for quite some time
and right now we are in season 2.
Does our show benefit
to the society in any way?
Not at all. How could it be beneficial?
Hahaha.
But, I think the point that
our show can still continue
on is because the audiences,
in my opinion,
think that our show is like a space
where you can share
lessons learned or mistakes
so that we can return you
with insults,
name callings,
and looking down upon, or bullying.
No! We can spread empathy
and understanding to each other. Right?
As the DJ here, I act as a bridge…
Oh, I haven’t made it
to the romantic part,
someone cuts my feeling here.
I have to pick up the call,
by the way. Let’s see.
Hello, there.
Hello, mama! It’s me. Ang.
Which one? Ankalung?
It’s Ang who called to your show
and I shared with you that I am gay,
and I used to have sex with my sibling.
Can’t you remember?
I remember you now! Angsumalin!
A gay man who wanted
to have sex with a guy,
but ended up having sex
with a chick. Correct?
I know you! A scandal!
A scandal!
Yeah, that was me.
This was why I called you that day.
But actually, today, there’s something
I want to share with someone.
Ang, dear! I miss you sooo much.
Oh my gosh, is there a season 2?
How is it? How about Deko?
Could you keep me updated about her?
Tell me now!
It’s been many months
since that day.
My life doesn’t change much,
actually.
But there’s something that changed…
What happened that day
is the turning point for 3 of us.
Deko broke up with Go
and she hanged out with many guys.
But I got her, mama.
Because even though Go
was Deko’s boyfriend,
but he couldn’t fully
perform his role.
I was jealous of Deko a bit.
But there’s one thing
I don’t understand.
Why did Go suffer a lot about this?
He kept quiet
and looked like he changed
to be somebody else completely.
Go, eat something.
You haven’t had anything
since morning.
Here,
eat some.
Om nom nom.
It’s gonna pass you now
if you don’t eat it.
Try some.
Oops, it’s getting dirty now.
Okay. Let’s try one more bite.
I couldn’t believe that Go got his
heart broken so severely from Deko.
But Deko’s gone,
like no chance of returning at all.
Here, try some more.
And for me, I realize that Go
doesn’t have a feeling for me
more than just a friend.
But I couldn’t help
taking care of him.
I can’t leave him this way.
At first, I thought that
I could get over him.
But being with him
and taking care of him
makes me become close to him again.
Go,
I tried to take action, really.
And this time Deko wasn’t here
to block my way.
But I’m afraid I’m gonna
mess everything up like last time.
So, it’s impossible for me
and Go to be together.
Oh, shit!
Why didn’t you sleep
in bed properly?
I’m sorry that I am a burden to you.
What burden is it, Go?
Not at all. We are friends.
Damn, it’s almost 10 o’clock.
I have a morning class today!
I don’t want to go to class.
Can you stay with me?
Okay.
Go, you’re not gonna die
from this heartbreak.
You have never
experienced this, right?
I have!
Who never experienced this?
Everyone has.
Go, but sitting still like this
makes it more stressful.
Go, how about speaking out
what’s on your mind?
Something is better kept inside.
If I say it out,
it might get worse.
No, trust me.
I had this experience before.
I experienced
something super stressful.
I didn’t know what to do.
I couldn’t handle it.
You know what I did?
I called to share with the radio show.
A radio show?
Yeah. It’s the show where you can
call to share your not-fine…
I mean experiences,
or problems in life.
It’s called Club Sapan Fine.
Have you heard of it?
Nope.
Speaking out may not fix the problem,
but it’s better than doing nothing.
I’m telling you now.
But can you promise me
that you’re not gonna be mad at me?
Of course.
Are you gonna tell me about Deko?
When Deko broke up with me,
I was stressed, so stressed.
I was stressed
that I didn’t feel anything at all.
Deko was my girlfriend, right?
I should be sad, but not at all.
I view her Instagram account
every day,
hoping that, seeing her with other guys
could make me feel something.
But I feel nothing.
I’m not sure
whether I’m heartless or not.
Do you get this feeling?
It feels so bad.
But finally,
I realize that, maybe
I didn’t admit it from the beginning
that the person I love is not Deko,
but it is another person.
The one who has always
been by my side,
even before I met Deko.
Ang,
Ang.
I…
I need to go to the toilet.
I’ll be right back!
Ang! Are you stupid or what?
Your dream man
is confessing his love for you
and you pretended you don’t know?
Oh! Get this sound effect from me!
Stupid! Irritated!
Mama, calm down first.
Mama, you really think
that I don’t know?
You really think it doesn’t hurt me?
Oh, please.
Try to put your feet in my shoes,
and you’ll know
how destiny tricks me.
Mama, just think about it.
I even slept with a chick before.
If I express my feelings,
and it’s not what I thought it would be,
it’s gonna mess everything up.
Sorry, I was so into it.
I apologize with respect,
Angsumalin.
Get the jingle sound from me.
Sorry.
Alright, so the reason you call today
is because it’s a mess again, right?
This love is a mess?
Well, after that day,
I avoided seeing Go.
I didn’t go to classes for weeks.
And I thought to myself that
it didn’t work at all to feel this way.
Finally, I realize that
I can’t get over Go, no matter what.
Well, if my heart says yes,
I have to go for it!
I don’t care
if it’s gonna mess up or not.
There you go, girl!
You need to fight! If you love someone,
go get him! Fight for him! Good job!
Then, what’s next?
You’re right. You’re number 1!
I made up my mind that
I’m gonna confess my feelings to Go
so he knows how I feel.
Ouch! Spicy! Spicy!
A round of applause.
You’re right, my girl.
You’re superb!
How did you do that?
Tell me more.
Tell me now.
- Go
- Ang
- Well, I…
- I have something to tell you.
Then you go first.
It’s okay.
I don’t rush. You can go first.
How about
we say it at the same time?
I’m gonna count 1, 2, 3.
And we say it out together.
Okay? 1, 2,
- 3.
- I’m getting married!
Huh?
Wait a minute!
Press the pause button.
Don’t say anything now.
I’m so confused right now.
How come it reaches to this point?
Who is Go getting married to?
Mama, just guess.
Don’t tell me that…
I get my outfit ready
for tomorrow’s event.
Go, I’m so sorry.
Actually,
I don’t want to drag you into this.
But I couldn’t find
a better solution.
I guess this is the only way out
from the problem.
Have you eaten anything?
Did you get some rest?
I can’t eat anything.
I can’t sleep well.
I promise you that I will take care of you
and the baby with my life.
You’re going to be a mother.
No matter what you do,
don’t forget that there’s another life
in your stomach.
The war between us
hasn’t ended yet.
Deko, a bitch!
(Soulmates From Hell Season 2)
(Club Sapan fine 2 Classify)
Go is getting married to Deko!
How is this possible?
She’s pregnant
without the father, right?
Yes, of course.
She’s been with so many guys
and ended up being pregnant
without the father.
She then tricked a good person like
Go to get married to her.
How did you handle this?
You just surrendered to her?
When I slept with her,
I thought that I could be friend with her.
But hell no!
Mama, tomorrow is
the wedding day of Deko and Go.
But I already have a plan.
I can confirm that
the wedding will be a mess!
Hold on here. Ang,
calm down a little bit.
Please calm down.
Think carefully before you destroy
someone’s wedding.
You can go to jail for that.
No, mama. I thought it through.
I love Go.
And I will absolutely never lose
Go to someone like Deko.
I call you because
I just want to talk with someone.
In the end, in case I go to jail,
- then someone can bail me out.
- Aww
Mama, that’s it. Bye!
Hey, are you there?
Oh…he’s gone!
Not even listen to me, Ang!
Dear audiences
who are listening right now, except Ang,
I just want to inform that violence
is not the right solution to the problem.
Let’s pray for Ang,
who is going to destroy the wedding,
to not go too far and end up in jail.
Alright, let’s pick up another call.
Ang spent just a brief time with us.
Wow, someone’s calling.
Hello there!
Hello?, hello?
- Is this the Club Fri…
- Ah Club Sapan Fine,
it is. Club Sapan Fine!
Alright Club Sapan Fine.
Sorry, I remerber it wrong.
Please be careful with the name.
My show only has 2 seasons for now.
Can you introduce yourself, please?
What’s your name?
My name is Go.
Welcome Go to our show.
Go…?
Don’t tell me that…you’re Gobori?
Yes, I’m Gobori.
In the past,
I used to call myself Gobori, too.
Damn it!
What a coincidence!
Excuse me, what did you say?
Nothing. I was just mumbling.
What do you want
to share with us today, Go?
I have something
I’m so worried about.
I can’t find the way out.
I don’t know what to do.
But a friend of mine told me that
speaking out may not fix the problem,
but it’s better than doing nothing.
So here is my story.
I have a crush on my best friend.
It’s strange, right?
My best friend is Ang.
Angsumalin and Gobori.
It’s like we were born for each other.
I’m close to Ang
since the first day of the university.
At that time,
I didn’t know what it is,
but one think I know is
I don’t feel lonely anymore.
After that,
I have a girlfriend. She’s Deko.
3 of us, I, Ang, Deko,
always hang out together.
Eventually, Deko broke up with me.
This is when I realize my feelings.
Actually, I’m not sad
from breaking up with Deko at all.
It’s because I didn’t like Deko.
But I like the person
who has always been by my side.
I like Ang.
My real soulmate is Ang.
But it doesn’t matter
what I think about Ang,
because he doesn’t have
any feelings for me.
It’s nothing more than friends.
Oh, come on!
Ang thinks of you as a friend?
Let’s say buffaloes can deliver eggs,
it’s still more believeable.
You know Ang, too?
No, no. I just guessed.
Well, if you don’t try,
you don’t know.
We’re together,
but I can’t do anything.
I love him, but he doesn’t know.
I just realize how painful
it is to have a one-sided love.
Having a heart broken
is even better.
I built up my confidence
to confess my love to him,
but the result was…
I need to poo.
I’m gonna go to the toilet.
I don’t get any response.
And he avoided me until now.
Finally,
I have to be alone with myself.
Oh, dear,
I think it’s about the right timing.
I think Ang has feelings for you.
He cares for you. He loves you.
He feels the same way as you do.
But he might be afraid of losing
the friendship,
so he does not reveal his feelings.
Why do you know so much?
Like you just had a talk
with Ang previously.
Oh, never!
I don’t know why. Nothing.
I didn’t hear anything at all.
I just evaluate
the situation from your story.
About Ang and me,
it wouldn’t be possible anymore,
because I’m getting married.
Oh, right!
If you like Ang,
why do you get married?
Can you explain?
I’m going to get married to Deko,
my ex-girlfriend.
Because it’s necessary to do so.
Hi, Deko
Hi! How are you? Good?
I’m good. And you?
Well, I’m okay.
Is there anything else?
Go,
I’m pregnant.
Who’s the father?
The point is my father.
My father is very strict.
He cannot accept this for sure.
And if he knows that I’m pregnant
without knowing who the father is,
he will force me to take an abortion.
I just want my child to live, Go.
Deko, calm down.
I think your father will understand.
Try talking to him nicely.
No, Go.
You don’t know my father.
He’s very brutal and conservative.
He never accepts this.
Don’t worry, Deko.
You still have me.
If you want my help with anything,
I’m willing to help you.
Go,
can you lie to my father
that you’re the father of my child?
Can you help me?
But if you don’t feel okay to do it,
I understand.
I just don’t know anyone to turn to.
Or if you have a lover,
or a crush on someone,
you can tell me right away.
- I understand.
- Deal.
I don’t have a lover,
or a crush on someone.
I will pretend
to be the father of your child.
I think your father
will be okay about it.
You made my daughter pregnant?
Yes, I did.
But…
Deko is my only daughter.
She’s like her mother so much.
When her mother dies,
Deko becomes
the most important person in my life.
For Japanese people,
when they make a mistake,
in the past, we would stab ourselves.
But nowadays,
we don’t do that anymore.
In my field, we do this!
It’s time for the wrongdoer
to be responsible for the mistake.
Be responsible for the mistake!
I’ll be responsible
for Deko and the child.
I will marry Deko.
I’m gonna take care of her
until death do us apart.
(Club Sapan fine 2 Classify)
Oh my gosh.
That’s why you have to marry Deko.
That’s right.
That’s why I have to marry her.
At first,
I planned to pretend to be a father
so I can ask her father
to keep the child.
But once
I know her family is a yakuza,
I know now why her name is Deko.
I can’t do anything.
Go, did Ang know about this?
No. Deko told me
to keep it as a secret.
My wedding is a small wedding
with only yaku…
Deko’s family.
I think you should tell Ang
about this as soon as possible.
No, Ang must not know about this.
Sorry, I gotta go now.
Oh, cut the line again.
Did I interrupt you?
Not at all.
I was just on the phone with my family.
It’s a shame
that they can’t attend the wedding.
It’s alright.
But it’s okay,
because from now on,
we are the same family.
Yes.
What a headache here! It was Ang,
and then Go hung up on me.
What a day!
Oh, another call is here.
To be frank, I don’t wanna pick up.
The ongoing problems aren’t solved yet.
Okay. The show must go on.
Hello, there.
Hi, there, Title.
Eh? You sound familiar.
Have we talked before?
Yes, of course.
I’m Deko.
Can you remember me?
What a perfect confidence here!
Hello, are you listening to me?
Yeah, I’m listening.
What about you?
Did you listen to
my show from the beginning?
No, I didn’t.
Now that you mentioned about it,
I’m so stressed.
I’ve been busy
and stressful all day.
I don’t know who to talk
to except calling in your show.
Is this Rachomon?
What is it? Tell me now.
Well, I’m pregnant.
Aren’t you shocked about it?
Not at all, Deko.
If you know what I listened to today,
you being pregnant is a little thing.
Then, can you remember Ang?
The one who used to fight
for the same guy with me?
That guy,
he’s the father of my child.
The father of your child is Ang!
Yes, this is why I call to talk to you.
Since we had sex on that day,
I called Go to break up with him.
Go is a very lovely person, really.
But for a boyfriend part,
he didn’t do it well.
I couldn’t take it.
Well, girls need sex, too.
Luckily, I was born a beautiful lady.
After I broke up with Go,
I met many guys.
But the problem is…
the memory of me having sex with Ang
has haunted me
and I couldn’t have sex with anyone.
At first, I thought that it’s
because I don’t really like the guy.
But it’s not true.
I have the same experiences
with all of my boyfriends.
I’m so stressed.
I got even more stressed
because even when I’m alone,
I still have
the feeling of throwing up.
I feel irritated. I have a headache.
My period does not come.
And I am also addicted to sour food.
You know what it means, right?
Shit!
That’s right! I’m pregnant.
(Pharmacy)
I can’t believe it!
The destiny tricks me.
(Pharmacy)
I never had sex with anyone
after the night with Ang.
Therefore,
the father of my child can’t be anyone
except the guy I slept with, Ang.
Besides, it’s my dad.
He’s a very brutal person.
He couldn’t take this for sure.
I was so lost and hopeless.
I didn’t know anyone to turn to.
Tell Ang then.
No matter what he is,
he’s the father of the child, isn’t he?
Ang can’t be my husband for sure.
And my dad is not okay
for Ang’s girly habits for sure.
If my dad knows
that Ang is the father,
Ang will be murdered
and his body will be thrown into the sea.
Finally, I have to sacrifice my pride
to ask Go to pretend to be the father.
But then my dad forced Go
to get married to me instantly.
The point is,
tomorrow is the wedding day.
What should I do?
Deko?
Hello? Deko?
Oh, what the hell is this?
Just left with no signal?
Oh, shit! Electric shock!
Help me please! Electric shock!
Staff! Electric shock!
Come quick!
(The Wedding Day)
Today, I would like
to thank everyone so much
to witness my daughter’s wedding.
And I welcome
the new family member to…
Who the hell are you?
Who are you?
Ang!
Damn!
(Club Sapan fine 2 Classify)
(1 week later)
You okay?
Please order spicy Cockle salad for me.
(1 week later)
Gorgeous!
Hello! Club Sapan Fine is here.
First of all,
I have to respectfully
apologize to everyone.
Last week, our electric devices...
just went wrong.
It’s electric shock.
All the devices here were exploded.
Just kidding!
It’s a little electric shock.
Today, I’m on duty as usual.
Last week, I couldn’t eat or sleep,
because I have to keep update
about what happen to the 3 of them,
the soulmates from hell.
I have to watch the news
in case there’s a murder
or a dead body somewhere.
Until now, I didn’t hear anything.
So, if anyone knows the 3 of them,
please keep me updated to make sure...
that they are still doing okay, alright?
Oh, the first call is here.
I haven’t even told
what today’s topic is.
Hello there.
Hello, there.
This voice… Angsumalin!
That’s right, mama. It’s me.
Oh, how are you?
Are you alive?
Is this your real voice?
Mama, I’m still alive.
Safe and sound.
How was the day
that you destroyed Deko’s wedding?
Do you know
that her dad is a yakuza?
I know it, of course!
Exciting!
When I got to the wedding,
I knew it right away
without anyone having to tell me.
Seriously, I was afraid at first.
But I can’t absolutely let
someone like Go...
to get married to Deko.
Even though I have to lie
that I’m the father...
of Deko’s child, I’ll do it!
I wanted to see Deko’s reactions
when she knows that...
she has to get married to a gay like me.
(The Wedding Day)
So, the reason that you come here
is to tell me that you are the
father of Deko’s child?
Yes, sir.
But Go said
he’s the father of the child, too.
Err…
it’s not true.
I am the father.
I don’t know
why Deko have to lie like that.
But I really love Deko.
And the child in her stomach...
is my child.
Get out now!
Dad, but I…
I told you to get out!
And...
tell Go to come talk to me here.
Yes, sir.
Why are you here? Huh?
This bitch!
Lower your voice.
If you don’t sleep around with guys...
and get pregnant without the father,
and tricked Go into this,
do you think I wanna come here? Huh?
You knew it, too?
Who wouldn’t?
I know that you and Go never slept together.
What you did is sinful,
you know that?
You only care for yourself.
You never thought of anyone.
You are a selfish bitch!
I’m not selfish.
Stop cursing me.
I think of you as a friend,
Why did you think of me like that?
Stop it now! You’re bullshitting.
Everything I did is just for you.
Oh, stop it!
Stop pretending to cry, too.
Do you know...
who is the father of my child?
If you don’t know,
how could I know...
how many guys you’ve slept with?
Ang...
think carefully.
It’s me?
I went on a date with many guys,
but I’ve never slept with them.
I only slept with you.
I’m the father. I’m the father.
If you don’t believe me.
You can count the months.
No, I don’t have to.
We made a promise...
that if you’re pregnant,
we’re gonna help raising the baby.
See, everything I did here,
I did it for you.
And you mess everything up, Ang.
You see how cruel my dad is.
If my dad knows
that you’re the father,
you will be dead
and become sashimi.
You’re gonna be dead for sure!
Both of you said
that you’re the father of the child.
Deko,
who is it exactly?
Tell me!
Or I won’t let them go home,
Go!
Go home
and forget everything
that happens here.
Go…
well, Go…
Ang,
how are you gonna be
responsible for this?
Let’s begin again.
Today, I would like
to thank everyone so much
for coming
to witness my daughter’s wedding.
And welcome
the new family member to…
Who the hell are you?
What the heck?
Who are you?
Don’t tell me...
you’re gonna marry my daughter too!
No, no. I’m looking
for your daughter, because…
Because of what?
Because…
Just tell me what it is,
or I will force your mouth to do it.
Oh, don’t do that!
I’ll tell you everything.
Please be mercy to me.
I have 2 children.
I still have to pay for my house.
I just got a new car.
I have to go back to my family.
I’m looking for your daughter.
Because I have
an important issue to tell her.
Your daughter...
bought a pregnancy test kit
from my shop.
The products in this lot...
are defected.
The company returned all products.
Because they are all defected.
No matter how you test it,
it only shows that you’re pregnant.
But...
What about the missing period?
It doesn’t mean you’re pregnant.
When you are stressed,
you can miss your period, too.
Will they trample me?
(You idiot!)
(No, you are idiot!)
(You are!)
So, you all got tricked
from the destiny.
Nothing is serious at all, right?
That’s right.
How about your wedding with Deko?
Nope, the wedding was cancelled.
Deko’s father looks happy
that his daughter wasn’t pregnant.
He even said that
if anyone wants to marry his daughter,
that person needs to be
over his dead body.
Whatever it is, Ang.
I think all is good now.
It’s a happy ending for everyone.
Yeah, confusing, right?
By the way,
I listened to previous clips
from your show.
It makes me...
realize how...
Go feels for me.
Woohoo!
My show make people in love.
Here’s a round of applause!
Press all buttons here.
I don’t know, mama.
But I...
miss Go a lot
and I really want to see him.
But he...
avoids seeing me.
He locks himself at home,
not going to classes,
not picking up the phone.
I think he is shocked about
what happened with me and Deko.
But I won’t give up.
I must see him!
Go!
Well,
I have something to tell you.
I knew that...
you...
called Club Sapan Fine.
I listened to the clip already.
And I…
know now...
how you feel about me.
I’m so glad to hear that, Go.
I...
want to tell you that,
I like you, too.
Since the first day we met,
we are like...
Gobori and Angsumalin.
We were born for each other.
So,
let’s be together!
Go!
Ang,
Go,
I wanna tell you that,
I like you.
I like you for a long time.
I like you the most.
I like you more than anything on earth.
I promise that I will not lose you to
some crazy situation like this anymore.
I just knew too that we can listen
to previous clips of Club Sapan Fine.
I listened to
what you shared with the DJ.
I knew why you went away like that,
or why you invaded the wedding.
And about you being the father
of Deko’s child.
Shit!
Go, that night was a mistake.
But I really like you.
- I can swear.
- And also about you
trying to drug my drink.
Shit!
Since we are friends,
I will let you go.
But after this, I don’t want
to see your face anymore.
Go, Go, Go, wait! Go, Go.
Go.
After this,
if you’re still following me,
I’m gonna tell the police.
The previous clips are the evidences.
Go, Go,
Go, I’m sorry.
Shit!
Go.
The reason
I call you today is to tell you
that it’s because of you and your show
that ruined my love life desperately.
Why I’m not fine?
It’s because of you!
Ang, Ang, Ang, Ang,
calm down a bit.
Listen to me first.
Listen carefully.
I’m not calming down!
I’m not listening either!
I’ve been listening to your show,
that’s why my life is like this.
Who told you the idea of having
previous clips available online?
Let’s see
if I am sued,
I will drag you to jail with me.
And then your station will…
Beep…beep!
Oops, no signal.
The call was cut.
Oh, byebye then.
I told you don’t add this function in.
Take it out.
You don’t listen to me.
Alright, I think
I have to end the season now.
Club Sapan Fine Season 2.
Next time, if police don’t drag
the DJ and the crew to jail,
the show will be renamed as
“Club Bang Kwang”
Take good care of yourself.
For anyone who’s in love,
I wish you a happy ending life.
I have to go for now.
Good bye!
Pack all belongings.
Lock the front door,
in case the police come.
Translated by 9 Days team.