- What's this?
- This?
It's kimbap. I made it in the morning.
- Wow, really?
- Yes.
- Let me try one.
- No. It's only good if we eat it at the theme park.
Come on. Let me try just one.
And you made it. It'd be good wherever I eat it.
No, no.
By the way,
why do you want to go to a theme park instead of a pool in summer?
Because...
Oh, the bus is here.
Let's get going first.
Tell me after we get on.
- It's a theme park.
What? Are you sure you didn't plan this beforehand?
How did you come up with the same idea?
I know, huh?
I love it.
You'd want to fall in love with someone when you're at a theme park on a sunny day.
Why don't we do this, then?
"Lovers at the theme park on a hot summer day."
For Winders and Jewelry A's concept keywords...
I chose connectivity, similarity, and diversity.
The keywords for the consumer will be relatability, excitement, and shine.
The reason is the connection between us and jewelry...
and so forth.
I tried coming up with something all demographics can enjoy.
- I love that idea.
- Really?
- Don't you agree?
- Thank you.
We work so well together.
This was our first concept meeting, but we came up with the same concept and ideas.
It's like we've been working together for years.
We worked so hard. Should we take a break over coffee?
Yes, sounds good.
- What would you like?
- I'll have an iced Americano.
One iced Americano.
Same for Hyeon Seong, right? How about Team Leader Han?
- Vanilla latte.
Your blood sugar drops around this time of day. So...
I thought it'd be nice to have something sweet.
Why don't we make it iced, too?
What? It's so specific.
Huh? Do you two already know each other?
Did you know...
I was coming here?
No.
How about you?
Of course, I didn't know.
I never would've thought you'd be at Winders.
H2 didn't join them.
I'm their designer.
I meant it positively.
Thank you.
You did great, too.
Yes.
Well...
Work is still work.
Don't worry so much.
I won't.
I'm not sure how this would sound,
but...
I think it's nice that we get to work together.
We've...
always wanted to do this together.
The situation changed a bit,
but I'm glad that we get to work together...
like this.
Let's make this work.
Let's do that.
You know...
He's waiting.
What?
Your Hubae.
Oh, right.
I'll get going.
Okay.
You worked so hard today.
- You were very good at talking.
- Really?
I was so nervous earlier.
Our project will go well, right?
We need to make sure it does.
Nuna.
Yes?
I'm okay.
So focus on yourself from now on.
I know what you're thinking,
but I can do it.
I'll make sure it doesn't affect work.
I didn't say anything.
Something must be bothering you.
I'm busy. Could you give me some space?
I was blocking your path while you were busy.
Good luck.
Let go of my girlfriend's hand, okay?
No! Gosh.
What do I do?
Gosh, it's not working.
Pig, I'm in trouble.
My laptop died.
You're good with machines.
Please help me. Crying emoji.
I tried not to care if she contacted me,
but I'm getting excited again.
Oh Fatty!
Hey.
Hey, why are you bothering me so much?
Just hire someone at times like this.
They said it'd take days.
I need to fix it today.
Thank you in advance.
Lead the way.
You're the best, Oh Fatty.
Would you like something to drink?
You said it's an emergency.
Let me finish this first.
Okay.
Gosh, whoa!
You're the best, Oh Fatty. You're so cool.
That's it, right?
- I'll get going.
- Hold on.
I should buy you a drink, since you came all the way here to help me.
It's still broad daylight.
You want to start drinking now?
It will get dark by the time I'm done with this.
Well, I guess.
I'll be done in no time.
Just wait a moment.
Okay.
She's pretty.
You don't mind me looking around, right?
Sure.
It's been so long.
♪  What are you up to? Do you want to hang out?  ♪
♪  Play with me  ♪
♪  Are you busy? Today, too?  ♪
♪  I've been waiting all night, I'm curious  ♪
♪  To be honest, I know  ♪
♪  Let's eat something tasty  ♪
♪  And drink tea, too  ♪
♪  Instead of saying anything important  ♪
♪  I just want to sit together with you  ♪
♪  I want to be with you  ♪
Did I interrupt you while working?
Huh?
Yes.
I'll finish the rest.
Go ahead, then.
What was that?
What's with the subtle awkward feeling I'm getting from Min Hyeok?
You're going all the way to Neverland because of the project with Hyeon Seong?
Yes. I think I'd better go there.
What a small world. How did you run into him there?
I know. Did you know he was working for Winders?
No, I haven't hung out with them in a while, too.
I see.
I should've been there.
Are you teasing me? I was wondering if I should leave the project.
Why would you leave? Did Hyeon Seong say he's uncomfortable?
Tell him to leave if that's the case.
No, it's not him. I feel uncomfortable.
And I'm stuck between him and Geon Yeop.
Do you worry about Geon Yeop now?
Why tire yourself out?
Just focus on yourself.
Wouldn't that project help your career?
That's why you want to go all the way to Neverland.
Yes, that's why it's annoying.
Yes, you're right.
It's not easy to forget the one you loved.
You told me to forget before.
What?
Have you been thinking about Im Jun Su since then?
No, I'm not.
I told you to let him go.
Why? Do you miss him again?
It's not that.
I'm just kind of curious about what he's like now.
What he's like? I'm sure he looks older now.
Hey.
What time is it? I need to get going now.
Really?
Bye, then.
Only focus on yourself, okay?
Worry about yourself.
Hey.
The first love is only beautiful if you leave it that way.
It feels like we switched roles.
Bye.
See you.
I heard Team Leader Han of Jewelry A went to Neverland.
She's a proactive designer.
Will she come up with an amazing idea?
Why are you telling me that now?
Because I heard it just now.
What are you doing?
I'll be working offsite today.
I thought you were lying when you suggested we meet again.
But you weren't.
No.
It's been forever since I've been to a movie theater.
Really?
Yes.
- Why?
- I guess...
you meant it when you said you don't do relationships.
Well, I suppose I did.
So this is a bit of a special occasion, then.
Huh?
Yes, I suppose.
- But we're not in a relationship yet?
- What?
Why are you so surprised?
Well, it's not that.
Be quiet and look at the screen. The movie is starting.
What should we do after the movie?
Let's grab a drink nearby...
No, instead...
let's get dinner.
Sounds good.
Are these really that good?
Yes, they're amazing.
Aren't they the same as the ones you get anywhere else?
No, they taste special because you're eating them at a theme park.
Here are your churros.
Oh, okay.
Here they are!
Ta-da.
You look at them more adoringly than you do when you look at me.
You're not as sweet as churros.
- What?
- I'm kidding.
Eat quickly. It's good if you eat it before it gets cold.
Come here.
Geez, it's all over your face.
I'll have one churro.
Got it.
Okay.
Jeong Hyeon Seong.
Hey, Seong Ok.
What are you doing here?
Well...
I wanted to do some research.
I see.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Neverland is known for its churros.
Yes.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
Is it on my face?
Oh, here.
We used to go to theme parks often in the summer.
Do you remember?
Yes, we did.
You always suggested going to theme parks in the summer.
People usually go to the beach or pools in the summer.
It was kind of unusual.
Could you call it special instead of unusual?
Okay, okay.
You didn't even know how to enjoy churros at a theme park, but I taught you.
I'll admit that.
It definitely doesn't taste the same in other places.
Right?
Yes.
I think I've asked why you like going to
theme parks in summer.
You must've forgotten.
No, I remember.
Because it's not crowded.
You said the exact same thing then, too.
You forgot that, too, didn't you?
Did I?
Being together like this feels like...
I'm here to work.
I need to get going now.
Seong Ok,
how about... we walk around together?
What?
Is it kind of weird?
It's not that, but...
it's a big place.
We'll see more if we split up.
Right.
I wasn't thinking clearly.
It's okay.
I'll get going now, then.
Okay.
Good luck.
By the way, why do you want to go to a theme park instead of a pool in summer?
Because...
Oh, the bus is here.
The weather is amazing.
It really is.
So why the theme parks in summer?
Theme parks in the summer feel like a jewelry box.
- Jewelry box?
- Yes.
Didn't you ever think the rides looked like jewelry?
- Jewelry?
- Yes.
The hot balloon rides, merry-go-rounds,
and the Ferris wheels. They're pretty.
And the way roller coasters flip like this looks like a ring.
And the theme park sparkles in the sun in the middle of summer.
That looks like a jewelry box.
That's why I like it.
- Huh?
- I thought it was because it's less crowded.
Come on.
Seriously. That's so Jeong Hyeon Seong.
If we put a miniature rollercoaster
in this couple's ring,
the jewelry box will be completed, right?
Don't try to actually do that, okay?
- Who do you think I am?
- Huh?
I'm Jeong Hyeon Seong.
I know. You're Jeong Hyeon Seong.
Gosh, I want to eat so many things.
Why do they all look so good?
Should you be that serious about picking fried chicken?
This is no good. You pick one.
I'm here to treat you.
What's gotten into you?
- You decided already?
- Yes.
We'll have one order of spicy garlic wings and two 500-cc  (~ 16.9 oz)  glasses of beer.
And we'll have a tteokbokki, too.
Okay.
Oh, we'll have a pineapple soda and a frozen glass, too.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
What?
You said ordering tteokbokki at a fried chicken place is disrespectful to the chicken.
I know you like eating them together.
Here's your soda.
Thank you.
I've been feeling awkward since earlier. Why is that?
Here. Drink it.
Okay.
Why a-aren't you eating?
Didn't you say you don't like wings before?
I tried them, and they weren't too bad.
Right? That's why, right?
Once you fall for wings, there's no going back.
Let's drink.
Okay.
- Cheers.
Gosh, that's too funny.
Did it really?
I'm serious. He fell while walking, and the insole popped out.
And it was this thick.
That's too funny.
Look, I'm crying.
Why is it so fun hanging out with you?
I think someone's calling me.
I'll answer this real quick.
Okay, go ahead.
Yes, Geon Yeop. I came up with an idea for the concept proposal.
Could I present it in addition to what you sent me in the next meeting?
- Did you take those recently?
- Huh?
- Yes.
- They look great.
Right, Winders called and said they wanted to supplement the concept proposal.
Is that so?
What idea was it?
They said they'll tell us in the meeting.
I see.
I'm pretending we're just friends to hang out like we used to.
I'm trying to hide my feelings,
but I can't hide them whenever I'm in front of her.
And I keep having hopes.
What? Are you falling asleep, Oh Fatty?
Hey.
Hey, Oh Min Hyeok.
Yes.
I'll go to the restroom.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, the restroom is...
- She must be drunk...
- Go outside and turn left.
The passcode is 4885*.
Thank you.
4885*. 4885*.
Excuse me.
Wake up. Excuse me?
She can't sleep here.
Gosh, my throat.
What's taking Kim Hyeo Ryeong so long?
Did she fall asleep somewhere again?
- Is the restroom for both men and women?
- Yes.
Hey.
You crazy bastard.
Hold on.
I think you're mistaken. Hold on.
Mistaken, my foot.
Hold on.
Sir, we have a problem outside.
The customers are fighting!
- Hold on, hold on!
- Get in here.
Hold on. Don't do this.
Come on. Seriously!
What's going on? What's wrong?
You're dead.
Min Hyeok!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
What's going on?
Hold still.
He needs to be beaten to death.
Sir, Sir!
Please stop!
What's wrong with you? Why are you stopping me?
I got punched. Why are you stopping me?
Oh Min Hyeok!
I don't know what caused the misunderstanding, but please stop.
Misunderstanding? Misunderstanding?
Do you want to hear what that bastard did to my friend?
He tried to kiss her when she fell asleep in the restroom.
Misunderstanding?
No, I didn't.
I was too drunk that...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Hey, where are you going? Hey!
Where are you going, I asked!
Call the police and take care of it.
Please call them right now.
A bastard like that should get locked up for at least ten years.
Please call right now.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You must've been very scared.
Hye Ryeong...
Why would you be sorry?
I'm sorry.
But why do you keep crying?
I don't know.
How annoying. That pervert.
Are you okay?
Why am I so pathetic?
You're not pathetic at all.
I fell asleep at the bar.
And I'm clumsy, as you've said.
I hate myself.
It's his fault for messing with someone asleep.
There's nothing wrong with falling asleep.
You didn't do anything wrong.
So don't blame yourself.
Geez.
Thinking about it, he didn't even apologize to you.
Gosh, it's pissing me off.
Are you okay?
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
I'm okay. I just need a band-aid.
What in the world? Seriously.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Stop apologizing.
It's not your fault.
It's his fault.
No, it's just that...
We wouldn't have come here if I didn't call you today.
This wouldn't have happened, either.
Because you're my friend, you—
I didn't do that because I'm your friend.
What?
It's because I like you.
Those words came out at the moment I didn't even expect.
The rides that are sparkling in the blazing sun in the summer as jewelry,
and the theme park where those rides are as a jewelry box.
I want the people who see this ad to feel excited, like they're opening a jewelry box.
And that excitement becomes familiar over time
and as time passes, you long for it.
I want to give the consumers fond memories through our collaborative editorial.
Wow, my heart actually fluttered just now.
This is like a film. A film.
This is totally amazing.
How did you come up with an idea like this?
It's all thanks to Team Leader Han.
Oh, really?
Well, I was just—
The idea she suggested...
helped me a lot.
Oh, I see.
Our team has amazing synergy.
Let's take a look at the list of theme parks, then—
I suggested Neverland for the theme park.
Neverland will be good to show the sun in summer.
I suppose it'd be good to show the sparkle.
I've been thinking about that, too.
It might be difficult to shoot at Neverland since it's so big.
So I think we should get a different spot—
No, I think Neverland is perfect to express the feelings of summer.
I agree with that.
We could contact them, right?
Yes, of course. I'll get that going.
Then, let's each prepare our part and meet on the shooting day.
Sounds good.
If you need anything,
feel free to reach out anytime.
Yes, I'll contact you after checking the status.
- Sounds good.
- Let's wrap up today's meeting for now.
Merchandiser Kim, let's chat for a moment.
Oh, okay.
You did great today.
See you next time.
Yes, see you.
Wait, Seong Ok...
Sorry.
I forgot my file.
Oh, the file?
Why am I feeling the excitement I've been longing for only now?
Well, Seong Ok...
At Neverland on the shooting day...
Well...
Nuna, will you take long?
I'll talk to you later.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
The parking pass. I'll meet you downstairs.
Okay.
Well, at Neverland...
Could you wait for me in the central plaza
after the shoot?
I need to tell you something.
Okay?
♫  Why is it so sweet?  ♫
Are you going downstairs?
No.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
♫  I think about it again  ♫
You haven't gone downstairs yet.
No.
♫  We were stars in the night sky  ♫
♫  Every time  ♫
♫  Every day  ♫
♫  Remember when the stars were shining?  ♫
♫  Every time  ♫
♫  Every day  ♫
I want to believe that it's not too late.
♫  You and I are still stars  ♫
♫  We don't shine, but I hope we don't disappear  ♫
♫  We were stars in the night sky  ♫
♫  Every time  ♫
♫  Every day  ♫
Could you wait for me in the central plaza after the shoot?
♫  Every time  ♫
♫  Every day  ♫
Look over here.
Okay.
Yes.
How about something like this?
Yeah. I think it's great.
Hyeong, why didn't you check properly?
We have no choice.
I'll go to the shoot instead.
You'll have to inspect the damaged goods at the office.
- But the shoot—
- It's your responsibility.
Do you want me to do it?
What do you think, Team Leader Han?
Pardon?
Don't you think this project will turn out well?
Yes.
Hello? Yes.
It's No. 3. No. 3.
It's out of battery.
Okay, thank you!
Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Team Leader, I think it'd be a total hit.
Good, good, good.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
You did great, Nuna.
You, too.
Let's go. I'll drop you off on the way.
Oh, okay.
- Thank you.
What?
You need to leave since we're about to close soon.
Okay. Could I wait a bit longer before I leave?
You need to make it quick.
- And return the entrance pass when you leave.
- Oh, okay.
The call is not going through. You'll be connected to the voicemail
and there will be an additional charge after the beep.
What did you expect, Han Seong Ok?
Shit.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
By chance...
is anyone from the film crew still in there?
They all left. Don't you know what time it is? It's late.
Please leave.
Why would you kick the gate?
It's late.
♫  I feel like I'm in love  ♫
♫  I know it looks weird, but walk on the road singing ooh-ooh-ooh  ♫
♫  I fall in love with you  ♫
♫  When you're in my arms, it's better we are singing ooh-ooh-ooh  ♫
♫  From downpour to the rainbow  ♫
♫  Anything looks great  ♫
♫  From the sun to midnight moon  ♫
♫  When I'm with you, when I'm with you  ♫
♫  From downpour to the rainbow  ♫
♫  Anything looks great  ♫
♫  From the sun to midnight moon  ♫
♫  When I'm with you, when I'm with you  ♫
♫  When you're in my arms, it's better we are singing ooh-ooh-ooh  ♫
♫  You asked me another day, "Will you love me forever?"  ♫
♫  And I said, I'm not the type...  ♫
Bo Ram, you like chocolate cookies, too. Why did you give it to her?
Do you want some of my steak?
You like stealing my food.
Because I like Hye Rin.
I'm not asking you to reciprocate.
I'm not asking you to go out with me, either.
We can no longer be friends like we used to, right?
Friends?
Can you be friends with me?
I don't think I can.
Let's stop feeling hurt.
Let's go back to then.
Geez!
- W-What?
- Hey.
I'm Jeong Hyeon Seong, the CEO of H2.
I'll focus more on the jewelry line in addition to the fashion line.
I couldn't envision H2 without you.
Let's become successful for sure.
Let's prove it to those who said we couldn't do it.
We need to do it for ourselves.
We can keep working together that way, no?
I really want you to come.
I'll leave now.
Are you getting in?
♫  I fall in love with you  ♫