Crazy bastard. Why did you drink?
Geez, I'll no longer drink, you losers.
Hey, S-Seong Ok.
Hey.
What made you call?
Well...
Have you been well?
Yes. Of course, I have.
I see.
How about you?
Have you been well?
Well, I...
I've been well, of course.
I see.
Well, I work at a company these days.
Really?
Where?
Well, it's Win...
It's just a design company.
I see.
That's great.
Yes.
It is great.
How about you? Is the work manageable?
Yes.
It's great. I... Well, I like it.
That's good to hear.
Were you sleeping, by chance? I stole too much of your time, didn't I?
No.
- It's ok—
- I'm sorry.
- Go to bed now.
- Huh?
I'll hang up now.
Okay.
All right.
Good night.
I'll hang up for real now.
What was that? You idiot.
Can we meet when you're free, by chance?
I miss you.
When?
Whenever you're free.
I think Saturday would work.
I'll see you then.
You're meeting her?
Really?
- Yes.
- Wow, I'm nervous for some reason.
How did that happen, by the way?
Did you get drunk and call her first, by chance?
- Yes.
- And Seong Ok said yes?
Yes, it just happened so.
Wow, that's daebak.
It was a good thing you drank, then.
That gave you the courage to call, right?
So? When are you meeting her?
- Saturday.
- It's coming up soon.
Gosh, even I'm nervous. Geez.
- Jeong Hyeon Seong.
- Yes?
Good luck.
Let's have a drink with Seong Ok like we used to.
Okay.
Let's do that.
Hey.
What?
Gosh, seriously. What do we do with poor Hyeong Seop?
What's wrong with me?
I have a woman I like, okay?
You've always had a lot of women you liked.
But the women never liked you, you are forever single.
That's not true. I'll finally stop being forever single this time.
How will you do that, exactly?
I signed up for a service. I get ten matches for 30,000 won  (~ $22)  per month.
Wow, are you serious?
That's all a scam.
No, it's not. We chat every day, too.
Wouldn't you say we're flirting?
- Do you actually chat every day?
- We do.
Every single day?
- Let me see.
- Seriously.
You don't believe me. We chat every day.
Let me see. Let me see. Let me see.
"Good morning." "Okay."
"Have a good day." "Okay."
"Have a nice day." "Okay."
"Okay. Okay."
You seriously think you're flirting right now, right?
Yeah. Aren't we?
We can chat longer if I buy an item.
Should I buy it?
Please, Hyeong Seop. Seop, please.
Kim Hyeong Seop, please!
What? What? What? What?
They say you can't spit on a smiling face, right?
That's all a lie.
I could spit on your face right now.
Hey, just leave him. He wants to spend his money. Let him.
Don't be jealous if I get a girlfriend first.
Jealous? Me? Of you?
I'd be jealous of you? Seriously.
You hurt my ego.
Oh, right. Where's Si Hu?
Cheers.
Excuse me.
Sure.
Breaking news. Hyeon Seong and Seong Ok are meeting up on Saturday.
We'd be able to hang out all together like we used to.
To be honest, I ran into her while I was delivering.
An Sibari, talk to me one-on-one.
(Sibari means errand-boy, friendly nickname)
We're drinking with Hyeon Seong right now. Do you want to come?
We should drink together on a day like this.
I'm busy.
Gosh, those losers.
Who was it, anyway?
I'm friends with a couple who broke up after dating a long time.
But they're meeting up, apparently.
Why bother?
I never get back together with someone I broke up with.
- Why not?
- What would be the point of it?
They'll probably break up for the same reason again.
It could be different.
People don't change easily.
Besides, he wouldn't have been so neglectful of me if he cared
and there wouldn't have been a breakup, either.
Once you break up, it's over.
He wouldn't have been neglectful if he cared, huh?
Yes, isn't that obvious?
Why? Do you tend to be negligent with your girlfriends?
What are you like in relationships?
Me?
I don't do relationships.
Oh, r-really?
Why?
Do you not like it?
No, no, well...
I guess it could be like that.
- Should we have the second round at a motel?
- What?
Right now?
Forget it if you don't want to.
No, no. It's not like I don't want to, but...
I got it.
Hold on, let me pay real quick.
I'd like to pay.
She has a boyfriend.
All women are the same.
Yes, I like him.
I really like him, I said.
He's fun to be with, and I want to get to know him more.
I know. I haven't felt this excited in a while.
Hey, don't worry.
I don't think he's a bad person.
Okay, I'll call you again.
W-When did you come back?
Shall we go?
You know, about relationships...
Do you feel that way with everyone, no matter who the woman is?
What?
I was just curious.
I'm not pressuring you. I'm just asking.
What do you like to do usually?
I love taking photos.
Do you mind if I take one of you?
A photo? All of a sudden?
Yes. This is our first date, you know.
I wanted to remember it.
Okay. Shall we take one together, then?
No, no. Just you, Oppa.
I'll take one.
What?
Wow, that's nice.
Are you sure I don't look weird?
No, it turned out well.
It feels like this moment was captured.
It'd feel different when time passes.
I feel like you can truly capture the moment.
But you'd feel differently about this moment after time passes.
Yu Na...
you should go home now.
What?
I just remembered something.
Let's call it a night and hang out again next time.
Next time?
Yes.
Will there really be a next time?
Yes, see you.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
I'll be good to you. I will.
I'll never do what you don't want me to do.
I'm sorry, Si Hu.
Nuna, please.
What's going on?
What brings you all the way here?
I suddenly got curious about something.
No...
It's not sudden.
I've been curious for the last six years.
Why did you do that to me?
Why did you do that?
I was...
young, too.
It took me too long to realize that breakups have to be cordial too.
I was six years older than you,
but...
I was 29 years old then.
I didn't know...
you'd be hurting all this time because of me.
Si Hu.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
I don't know if that was enough of an answer,
but I'll get going now.
Yun Yu Ju.
Did you even love me?
Answer me.
I loved you.
Sincerely.
I loved you a lot,
was very thankful,
and felt very bad.
♫  I think of you every time I take a step  ♫
When you become around my age,
I'd like you to understand how I feel.
♫  With my loose shoelaces  ♫
♫  I stare at the sky that changed me  ♫
♫  Slowly, a little slowly, would you get further away from me?  ♫
♫  So, we could remember our old laughter  ♫
I don't know what true love is yet,
but I could tell she meant it.
I'm sorry, and thank you, Yun Yu Ju.
Ok!
Hey.
- How are you?
- Why are you coming from there?
I walked.
What's going on? Where are we going that you wanted to meet at a bus stop?
Wait and see. Come this way.
- What?
- Be careful. Be careful.
What's going on?
Ta-da!
What? What's this?
Hey, this is so cool.
Are you calling yourself cool right now?
No, not me. I meant you.
You're cool, Han Seong Ok.
- Hey.
- Yes?
You need to talk to me about something.
Like what?
Jeong Hyeon Seong. What happened?
Did you come here to ask that?
What's more important than that?
Huh? Tell me right now.
Aren't you going to tell me?
Tell me. What's going on?
That's the most important thing.
- Tell me.
- Excuse me.
You're Eun Jeong Seonbaenim, right?
- Me?
- Gosh, it is her!
I'm on a soccer team at your high school.
- I see.
- We're big fans.
The school still shows videos of your games.
They tell us to be half as good as you.
Could you let us take a photo with you?
Yes, of course.
I-I'll take it for you.
Okay.
One, two, three.
This is so daebak.
By the way, why do you no longer play soccer?
It's because I've been injured.
I'm a model now.
Wow, daebak.
You're seriously so cool.
Gosh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Take care.
Do you miss it?
Not at all. It's not a good memory or anything.
Hey,
do you want to go to the last stop on the bus like we did in high school?
You suddenly want to go to the last stop?
Let's do it. I want to do it again.
What's the deal? Why, all of a sudden—
The bus is coming.
Gosh.
Won't you get on?
Hey!
What's going on?
Im Jun Su.
I think I saw Im Jun Su.
Spin kicks are about accuracy than speed.
You have to push the ball with the big toe
and the front of your foot to spin it.
The key is to go with the flow rather than kicking with force.
Okay?
Are you listening?
Pardon?
Yes.
Give it a try, then.
Seonbae.
Yes?
I'll train hard and make sure to follow you to the UK.
So wait for me.
You know, too, right?
I trained really hard to go to the UK.
I think that was the problem.
Since I was only focusing on my goal,
I ended up getting injured.
I couldn't go to the UK, either.
I know.
You took it very hard then.
I know I couldn't go because of the injury.
But he told me to wait. How could he date an idol as soon as he left?
Son of a bitch.
I know.
So?
What would you have done if it were really Yun Jun Su?
I don't know.
I guess I wanted to swear at him.
You know...
if I didn't work as hard,
and wasn't as good as others in soccer...
Would it have been...
easier to accept it?
Well...
you discovered a new career since you had to quit soccer.
You're doing a great job as a model.
You're right. I'm doing great.
I'm also...
saying you have to...
let him go completely to meet someone nice.
You can't keep having three-month-long relationships.
What?
How could you be so smart about other people's relationships?
You want to die?
Make sure you don't regret seeing Jeong Hyeon Seong.
Tag along if you're worried.
Really? Can I come?
- I'll sit in the corner without making a noise.
- No, don't.
Aren't you getting off?
This is the last stop.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
The ring.
The ring...
What are you doing?
- Here's coffee.
- Thank you.
These are...
couple's rings for us.
Really?
Yes.
Should I make matching shirts, too, then?
- I'd hate that.
- Right?
Matching shirts are no good, right?
No, that's no good.
What's that?
Why is there a gap here?
- This?
- Yes.
Look at this.
This is where a diamond will be.
I'll connect the ends with a diamond here. Just like us.
Oh, really?
That's so touching.
It might be difficult now,
but let's make sure to connect it when we get married someday.
What?
When we...
get married?
Why? What was that?
- It's nothing.
- What's with your face?
I almost cried thinking about it.
Make the gap bigger, then.
I'll put a diamond as big as your face in it.
How would I wear it? It'd be so heavy.
No, I swear I'll get you one. I'm serious.
I'll get you one.
Be careful. Be careful. Be careful.
Okay.
Do you want to hold it? Do you want to try it?
What are you up to?
It's nothing.
Where do you get stuff like this?
This is just...
Are you preparing already?
- Pardon?
- The thing I mentioned last time.
The jewelry project. The collaboration has been confirmed.
Oh, that's great.
It's called Jewelry A. It's an up-and-coming company.
Check them out and come up with ideas that suit them.
- Okay, I will.
- In my opinion,
I don't know if their designs are that outstanding,
but they do have a certain feel about them.
I think it'd suit the unique theme.
This isn't necessarily about selling products.
It's a concept catalog to show Winders can be versatile, too.
So try everything you want.
Thank you.
What are you looking at so intently?
What?
A theme park?
Yes.
I thought of a concept for the Winders project.
I see.
I can get excited about it, right?
- I'll do my best.
- I'll get ready for the concept meeting, then.
Seong Ok would've liked this.
It'd be better not to drink, right?
This would be good.
Our collaboration with Winders was confirmed.
This is all thanks to Ms. Han.
This was possible thanks to all of your help. Thank you.
You're being modest again.
Everyone here knows how hard Ms. Han worked, right?
- Yes.
Shall we start the concept meeting?
I just printed...
I think I left it on my desk. I'll go get it quickly.
I'll grab it for you. It's on your desk, right?
No, I'll go...
Saturday at three. Let's meet here.
- Shall we take a break?
- Yes.
Oh, right.
Did you know there was an episode at the office?
Here? Why?
Jae Ho's girlfriend came here and caused a scene.
Someone said they saw him leaving a motel with a woman.
Jae Ho did?
Yes. He said he fell asleep after getting drunk, and nothing happened.
But who'd believe that? I wouldn't.
So what happened?
It looked like they let it slide,
but they ended breaking up soon after.
I see.
Why would you tolerate that? She should've dumped him immediately.
She must've liked him that much.
Gosh, just thinking about it makes me feel disgusted.
Don't you agree?
Yes. Well...
I think I'd feel disgusted.
Aren't you dating anyone?
I heard you dated your ex for a long time.
Why did you break up?
Let's stop talking about these things at work.
Mr. Kim, you know you always give Ms. Han special treatment, right?
- Pardon?
- I didn't say anything unreasonable.
But you don't let us ask her anything.
- Ji Eun.
- Okay, okay.
My apologies.
I shouldn't have asked Ms. Han a private question.
I'll go to the restroom real quick.
Okay.
- Nuna.
- Hey.
Are you going home now?
Yes, what is it?
Well, the thing is...
I didn't want you to worry about what Ji Eun said during the meeting.
It's okay.
Did you run out to tell me that?
Well, yes.
What are you doing on Saturday?
Saturday?
Why?
Do you want to see me that day?
I have some musical tickets. I thought you'd like it.
Well, I have a plan that day.
What kind of plan is it?
What?
Can you push it back unless it's important?
Well, I'm sorry. It's important.
How about afterward? Why don't we meet after you're done?
Well...
I'm not sure what time I'd be done.
I'll wait until you're done.
You know, the CEO of...
Yes.
Aren't you going home, Mr. Kim?
I have a few more things to do.
I'll see you then.
See you.
Make sure to call me afterward.
I'm home.
Hello.
Hey. Are you eating?
You're a grown woman, but you can't even cook.
You're eating that because you don't want to cook, right?
- I'm not, okay?
- I don't think so.
It's obvious.
You don't know anything, Mom.
There...
What's this?
It's dinner. I didn't feel like cooking, either.
This is my dinner.
That's not a meal.
Are you sick or something?
No.
I don't feel that hungry tonight.
Hey, just eat.
I got two because I knew you'd be like this.
Okay, let's eat. Looks good.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'll eat it tomorrow morning. I'm not that hungry now.
Do whatever you want.
I don't know what's going on with you.
I'll eat in my room, then.
I'll start the film review.
A man and a woman are in a relationship that went stale.
The two try to erase memories of each other.
But the problem is they fell in love again
after erasing memories of each other.
They ask each other after reuniting.
"We won't be able to stand and get sick of each other again eventually."
"Do you still want to start over again?"
And they answer the question.
"It's okay, no matter what we end up facing."
It won't be possible, right?
Anything is possible.
Did you come up with this design yourself?
How pretty.
No.
It's not my design.
Is it your girlfriend's, then?
Yes.
Those are the days.
Are you proposing to your girlfriend?
Time and women don't wait for you.
What's the use of regretting after they leave?
Make sure it's not too late, okay?
Okay.
Saturday at three. Let's meet here.
Hello?
Mom, did you take my lipstick from my room?
Oh, that...
I think I brought it to the office and left it there.
Why didn't you ask me first?
No, it's okay. Got it.
Is this better?
The blue one?
No, the dress shirt is better.
I'm meeting Seong Ok.
I'm meeting Hyeon Seong.
But I can't sort out my head or heart.
Are the qualities he liked in me still even there?
I feel like I'll finally stop feeling lost.
How should I start the conversation?
Would I even be able to make eye contact?
I'm nervous,
but I can't wait to see her.
I'll try to act natural.
Would I be able to act normal?
♫  I feel like I'm in love  ♫
♫  I know it looks weird, but walk on the road singing ooh ~ ooh ~ooh ~  ♫
♫  I fall in love with you  ♫
♫  When you're in my arms, it's better we are singing ooh ~ ooh ~ooh ~  ♫
♫  You asked me another day, "Will you love me forever?"  ♫
♫  And I said I'm not the type who can leave you, someone like you  ♫
♫  Summer and the winter comes and goes  ♫
♫  Flowers are turning into leaves  ♫
♫  Everything is going by  ♫
Nuna.
Geon Yeop, what are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
I lied to you about something.
♫  From downpour to the rainbow  ♫
♫  Anything looks great  ♫
♫  From the sun to midnight moon  ♫
♫  When I'm with you, when I'm with you  ♫
♫  From downpour to the rainbow  ♫
♫  From the sun to midnight moon  ♫
♫  When I'm with you, when I'm with you  ♫
♫  I called you without realizing and bothered you  ♫
♫  But you let me be by your side  ♫
♫  With a mischievous smile  ♫
Let's meet at three tomorrow.
I'll be dressed in yellow.
Hi, Sally.
Who wants to hang out with me?
I'll leave if you don't come.
Hey...
What's with you?
Why are you going to sleep already?
Are you sure you're not sick?
Get out!
Why did you do that?
You always looked bored
and you didn't even make eye contact.
I wanted us to be more curious and think about each other more.
Was that really that hard?
What broke once is bound to break again.
Discard what's broken and move on to a new one.
The people from Jewelry A are here.
♫  I promise you now  ♫
♫  Stay, stay  ♫
♫  Whenever you're hurting  ♫