Team Leader Seo of Sunwoo Webtoon embezzled company funds.
During the negotiation of the contract with MD Venture Investment,
you apparently signed a backdoor contract with them. Is that right?
Team Leader Seo Hyeon Joo indeed signed this backdoor contract.
But Team Leader Seo doesn't know anything about its contents.
What are you saying?
She only met with the MD Venture Investment representative and signed the contract as per my orders.
The responsibility of this contract all lies with me.
Do you think that makes any sense?
How could she sign the contract without knowing its contents?
I told you I was the one who gave the orders already.
If necessary, I'll accept an investigation, but please do not force an innocent person
to admit to embezzling funds.
Are you perhaps covering for Team Leader Seo?
Me? Why would I do that?
There are rumors that you two are lovers.
Please tell us. Is that not true?
Making a choice for love that could make me lose everything...
That sounds like something that would happen in a novel.
Is that not right?
Since you've admitted to the embezzlement, you'll have to face the legal consequences.
Embezzlement? What is this?!
What is going on? Shouldn't you give us an explanation, CEO Hwang?
I'm sorry to have caused you trouble.
CEO Hwang!
Let's talk about this later.
Why did you do that?
You head off first.
What are you going to do now?
You don't have to go to this extent for me!
I should be responsible for everything related to the webtoon business.
Also, we probably shouldn't meet for the time being.
Mother!
Are you taking revenge on Team Leader Seo and CEO Hwang?
What in the world are you going to get for going this far?
What are you saying right now?
Do you think I fabricated a crime out of the blue to frame them?
Seo Yoon, what reason do I have to do this to CEO Hwang?
It's because of what happened in the past! The person you liked a long time ago...
What do you mean?
I'm begging you. Please stop.
If you go any further, I won't be able to forgive you.
I'll just be wondering whether you're lying to me again. And while I'm doubting you,
I don't have the confidence to see you.
I think we should just stop seeing each other.
There's something I have to tell you today. Let's meet
at the Seongsu neighborhood cafe where we last met in our past life.
Don't wait for me. I'm sorry.
- They've messed it all up.
- We should have stopped them right then.
- How could we have stopped them?... Oh Team Leader, you're here.
- Hello.
They suddenly barged in and told us to go out, so we couldn't stop them.
Is something wrong with the investment contract? I heard it's because of that.
People are saying that CEO Hwang embezzled...
It's not true.
That's right, our CEO Hwang has so much money!
What would he do with such a small amount?
If the CEO were to go to jail, I, Kim Pal Do, will fast!
Someone who eats six meals a day is going to fast? Wouldn't it be better to overeat?
I can do it!
Why don't we clean up the office first?
It's okay. You guys can go back to work.
Yeong Eun, do you have time to talk? There's a favor I want to ask you.
Yeah, I was actually going to contact you, too.
A senior from the Finance Department said that your CEO has been accused of an occupational breach of trust.
And the people at Sunwoo Webtoon are involved, too.
- Did the report perhaps come from Sejong Medical Foundation?
- Yeah.
Was this something planned by that director?
All right, let's talk about it in detail when we meet. How can I help you?
Can you help me find out about MD Venture Investment?
About someone called Team Leader Kim Hyeon Soo.
Okay, thank you.
Yes?
Team Leader, are you okay?
I hope there's something I can do to help. And I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing, PD Han?
If there's something I need your help with, I'll definitely ask.
It seems like she won't let go of Team Leader Seo until the very end.
Did I like you a lot back then, too?
Yes.
What happened to us?
Did we date? Or get married?
I don't know. I don't remember everything. Are you curious?
A little.
If things turned out well for us, I want to give it meaning.
But I don't want that anymore.
No matter what happened to us back then, my feelings for you will still be the same.
How about you?
Is your past life really important to you?
I don't really know.
It seems like the CEO hasn't been able to come out from the past yet.
He has been living like this all this time, so he won't change in the future either.
It'll be hard on you, Noona.
Of course, the present is more important to me.
I don't want to cling onto a past I don't really remember
and have it eat up my emotions.
I'll give you back the documents and photos you gave me last time.
When are you free?
Yes, Mom?
Do Gyeom!
Mom, what's wrong?
Your sister is about to go to jail!
It's even in the news!
What?
You've already made the person you love go miserable three times. Would the fourth time be any different?
That isn't love, but self-pity.
And you've actually hurt Hyeon Joo again.
I have to meet with Director Kim.
If you look here, you can see that until you got to the office after signing the contract,
the envelope containing the contract stayed with Team Leader all along.
Then wouldn't it be that Team Leader Kim Hyeon Soo switched the two contracts after getting it signed?
So it is Team Leader Kim, that jerk.
No wonder I disliked him for no reason.
Me, too.
After we exchanged the investment letters, he gave it to me personally.
So there's a high chance that's what happened.
I think it would be best if we go to MD Ventures in the afternoon to look into the situation.
Will you go there alone?
Yes, hello?
Oh, sure, just a moment.
Team Leader Seo.
They're saying your parents are here at the company's first floor right now.
What?
Why isn't she coming down yet?
Excuse me. Can't we go up there for a bit?
Please wait for a moment.
Mom!
Hyeon Joo! If you need money you should tell us.
My gosh, what's all this about embezzlement?
It's all fake news, right? Why would you steal someone else's money?
It's not like that. That's ridiculous.
Yeong Eun's mom watched the news and told me that you might go to jail.
That's not true.
Noona!
- Oh!
- Do Gyeom, good you're here.
What shall we do with your sister?
She couldn't even get married yet, but she might go to jail.
That will never happen. Don't worry, Mom.
Why would such an article be published then? They said that you and CEO Hwang Ji Woo planned this all along.
I won't ever lay my hand on other's people's money, and the same goes for the CEO.
I'll deal with it and call you, so just go home.
Yes, of course, our daughter would never do such a nasty thing.
How did we raise you, after all?
Words can't describe...
If something happens, don't hesitate to call us. Okay?
- Okay. Do Gyeom, please take care of Mom and Dad.
- Sure.
- We should go, too.
- Yes.
- Mom! Are you okay?
- Dear, are you okay?
Get on my back.
No. Goodness, my son.
Come on, get on my back.
That's not right!
You'll be in trouble.
She's heavier than you think. Your knees will give out.
Try walking.
Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
I'm fine.
I heard you two broke up.
I must have been wrong.
We did break up.
- Then why—
- Why did I falsely take the blame in her place?
Is that what you're wondering?
Falsely took the blame, you said?
Won't that be clear once the police investigation begins?
From my experience, the moment a third person gets involved in a business matter, a clash of opinions occurs.
If the needs of both parties of the transaction were met,
then a third person would not be needed.
Say what you want to say.
From today on,
you and Team Leader Seo cannot meet.
For professional or private reasons, even if there are inevitable consequences,
you absolutely cannot.
But if Team Leader Seo
continues working at Sunwoo Webtoon with you, as she is doing right now,
wouldn't this deal be difficult to achieve?
These are the documents that Team Leader Kim dealt with. Take a look.
Thank you.
He cleaned everything up and ran off. Would he have left the contract behind?
Just a minute.
Yeah, Yeong Eun?
I looked into what you asked.
MD Investment Venture is a start-up company that was built  five years ago.
Recently, they went public on the KOSDAQ, and moved their office from Jongno to the Samseong area.
From Jongno to the Samseong area?
Yeah. And Team Leader Kim Hyeon Soo has been working there for two years, but
it seems like he was in some debt.
Yeong Eun, I'll call you back. I have to check something.
Did you find out anything?
The addresses are different.
I think you should take a look at it, Sir.
Let me check it first!
I think the contracts got switched at our office.
What?
Then, are you saying everything written in here is true?
Probably.
Does Team Leader also remember her past life?
She said she didn't remember everything.
Through meeting the CEO, I think she started remembering bits little by little.
Did you show this to her?
Just the photo.
Since they broke up, I thought it would be hard for her to see this.
Now I understand everything.
About why my mom was so obsessed with the CEO.
It's probably because she felt like her first love was being stolen from her again.
But still, she shouldn't do this.
Going as far as falsely accusing the both of them.
I know it's impolite of me to ask you this favor,
but can you persuade your mother?
I don't want anyone to get hurt.
I'll give it a shot.
Thank you.
Wait.
Let's talk.
If Director Kim ends up pressing charges, I'll undergo the police investigation.
That won't be necessary.
After that time, did you by any chance go meet her?
You don't need to worry about it.
The reason she's doing this is because of you.
Still, this is just too much.
Please tell me.
What on earth happened then, for her to still have such ill feelings towards us?
You told me there are parts of the truth that I still need to hear, right?
Why did you ask me to come and see you at the tearoom where we had last met in our past lives?
That was where we had broken up, wasn't it?
All of that doesn't mean anything anymore, and it doesn't have anything to do with this matter, either.
What about Director Kim?
Are you just going to let her be?
I will handle it. Let's stop talking about it.
It's about time she gets out.
- Oh, she's out!
- Oh! Hyeon Joo!
Yeong Eun.
I came to see you because I was worried. I also brought some good news.
You know how the MD Whatevers wouldn't tell us the Team Leader's address?
Yeong Eun said she can find that out.
- Really?
- One of my seniors in the economic sector has a really wide circle of acquaintances.
I'll be able to find out his address and his family relations information.
That's right. Wouldn't he have at least told his parents before taking off?
Thank you, Yeong Eun!
It's okay. Let's go eat some food.
Hey, but what should I do? Do Gyeom is waiting.
Once this all works out, I'll treat you at a really fancy place.
Make sure you eat your meals.
- Thank you.
- Go on.
- Go safely.
- Bye.
- Want to go eat something yummy?
- Let's go.
I'm worried about Hyeon Joo. I hope it works out well.
I thought she would only have a pleasant dating and professional life ahead, but look at her now.
She's walking on a total spiky and rocky road.
- Would it be that she's caught in three years of misfortune?
- What are you saying?
Yeong Eun, we shouldn't be relaxed and eating food right now.
Then, what should we be doing?
I see you came here because you're worried.
How did you know?
Why are you so shocked by that?
Should I guess something even more shocking?
Someone here cannot eat blood sausage or liver.
- I love it.
- I go crazy for it.
I can't eat it! It's too dry!
- Nope.
- Nope
All right, give me your birthdays.
But before that,
pay 50,000 won.
Oh, right. Actually,
I would like to know my friend's instead.
A woman born in July 1983.
Let's see, let's see, let's see...
Come to me. Speak to me.
Goodness! It's not good!
It's not good. It's crap! Crap!
She has such rotten luck.
She'll lose her job, her health, and her man.
Really?
But it's okay.
There is a strong younger man by her side.
She'll do well with him.
That's not possible. The CEO is older than her.
What about me?
Is there someone for me?
It's quite dark...
Let's go.
I had a bad feeling since the blood sausage and liver.
However, I see a child.
Ma'am.
See, 50 dollars.
Do you not like it? Should I buy you something else?
Tell me if there's something you need.
No, it tastes good.
I'm going to take my time eating it all.
I heard about it from Min Jeong.
What happened this time is not your fault.
You don't have to feel sorry to the CEO, and you don't have to feel any guilt, either.
Whether he clears his name or gets sued, let him figure it out.
♫ I see you again over time  ♫
♫ I recognize you at once ♫
From today on, you and Team Leader Seo cannot meet.
♫ ...the moment you can see it   ♫
♫ no one else can ♫
♫ I’m not waiting, I love you ♫
♫ Even if I feel bad for waiting ♫
Secretary Nam,
arrange an emergency meeting with the board of directors tomorrow.
Please make sure every director is present without fail. Also...
♫ I don’t like it, I hate it ♫
♫ Our breakup ♫
I have something else to ask of you.
♫ ...still seems like a lie ♫
Do you still like CEO Hwang?
It's not because I like him.
Regardless of how the situation goes, it started because of me.
He might be sued in my place
or even be dismissed.
What will you do then?
I received a copy of the CCTV footage.
I'm going to check everyone who entered my office.
Once I get Team Leader Kim Hyeon Soo's address, I'll head there, too.
- I will help you.
- No, you have to work.
Do you think I can even focus on work?
Until everything gets settled, I'll do everything I can to help.
Nothing has to happen to the CEO for you to be at peace.
Why did you prepare dinner?
I have been wanting to make you something delicious for a while, Mom.
Does it taste good?
It's delicious.
The first time I cooked,
do you remember?
Of course. I even took a picture.
I spoke too harshly in the morning.
I'm sorry.
You misunderstood that I wrongfully framed CEO Hwang.
That could happen. It's okay.
Mom, can't we go back to how we used to be?
To before we met the CEO?
Let's eat dinner like today and go shopping.
What?
It seems really hard for you.
You're always nervous and anxious.
- You always—
- Is that...
because of CEO Hwang?
You're convinced that they're the same person.
He and the guy you used to like.
You hate Team Leader Seo because you think she took him from you again.
- Mom–
- What do you know?
How dare you say that so carelessly?
Is this why you made dinner?
Who ordered you to do this? Team Leader Seo?
No, it's not like that.
I just want you to live comfortably—
Then they should live unhappily.
They should, at the very least, suffer as much as I had back then
for me to live at peace.
But...
how did you know about all this?
Don't tell me...
Did you see something?
No.
I heard it from Team Leader Seo.
Stop.
PD Da Eun said she was the last one to leave.
From 5:56 p.m...
- until 6:17 p.m.
All the workers went home.
No one other than our employees came into my office with a document envelope.
- Want me to get you some coffee?
- Yeah. Thank you.
If you're tired, you should rest your eyes for a bit.
I am just going to check one more time.
They were definitely places related to the music box.
I'm from the Haerim Music Box store.
Please give this to Song Min Joo.
Miss Song Min Joo, the music box Kang Jin Ho ordered is now complete.
Please come at 10:00 p.m. for pick-up.
Senior Jin Ho must have ordered it for me.
At 10:00? Oh, I've got to go.
I'm sorry. I'll see you later.
- Hello.
- Hello, welcome.
I'm here for a music box.
I'm not sure what you mean. Nothing came in today.
Maybe there was a mistake.
Soo Jeong!
Have you heard anything about Senior Jin Ho?
I haven't been able to reach him for the past week.
Well, I wouldn't know.
I see.
Kim Soo Jeong ordered that man to give me a fake note. Why?
Why on earth?
You must be tired. You couldn't sleep at all.
I can just go home and lie down for a bit, but how will you cope?
Still, we were able to see every detail because you helped me out.
If anything happens, call me.
Just hearing that makes me stronger. Now go back. I'll call you.
- Okay, bye!
- Bye!
Da Eun.
I checked through the security footage to see if anyone suspicious entered my office, but I couldn't find anything.
Right. The only outside visitors were with the Secretarial Department or the Business Management team.
They only handed over files and left immediately.
Should we all look again?
Maybe if we look with different perspectives, we might notice something.
Madam's friend is correct.
This Kim Pal Do will open his two eyes wide and discover something.
His reliability is the worst in the universe.
- What?
- Nevermind.
We have a problem. There's a directors' meeting right now; an emergency one.
I'd like to start by thanking you all for attending this meeting despite the short notice.
I decided to hold this meeting today
to present my position on the disreputable event that occurred with Sunwoo Webtoon.
Was it already scheduled?
No, the CEO called for it last second.
Is it because of the backend contract with the investors?
I will go and see.
- Let's go together.
- No, don't.
Starting today, I will take responsibility for what happened
and step down from my position as CEO.
What are you saying?
We weren't even sued!
- CEO Hwang.
- No way!
Please find a new CEO as soon as possible.
I will do my best to avoid creating a management vacuum.
Yes?
I called to let you know that CEO Hwang just resigned.
What is that supposed to mean?
He resigned?
Something big happened. CEO Hwang resigned?
- Out of the blue?
- He said he'll take responsibility and step down.
- What?
- Hyeon Joo!
Is CEO Hwang inside?
He just left.
When will he be back?
Since CEO Hwang resigned, he won't be returning.
CEO Hwang!
You resigned?
Even if the CEO changes, no harm will come to Sunwoo Webtoon.
That isn't the problem right now.
I will reveal everything.
Neither you nor I knew about the dual contract,
and Director Kim fabricated all of this. I'll reveal everything.
I already settled everything with my resignation.
I hope you won't cause further problems...
No. This is my responsibility.
It's not because of you, Seo Hyeon Joo.
I am also tired.
Today is the end.
You said this last time.
People fight and hate each other by trying to unravel their string of fate from their past lives,
only to never see each other again.
We became those people.
Please consider today as me repaying my debt.
How?
How can you be so selfish from the very beginning to now?
You never said a word to me. You assessed the situations and made the decisions all on your own.
Did I ever ask you to take all the blame?
If you leave like this, what am I supposed to do?
Haven't you thought about the guilt I would feel alone?
I apologize for finding you and bringing you by my side.
I tried to win your heart, and I did.
Because of me, you found the memories of your past lives you didn't want to remember.
I am sincerely very sorry.
Please forget everything. Don't dwell on them.
Did you show this to Team Leader Seo?
Yes, just the photo.
They broke up, so I thought she'd feel worse if she saw this stuff.
What if... there's some important meaning to all of this...
If anything happens, call me.
Just hearing that makes me stronger. Now go back. I'll call you.
All right, go back to work.
CEO Hwang...
Kim Pal Do, pull yourself together, and get up!
We still need to verify the surveillance footage.
Yes, I must get myself together.
Kim Pal Do can't be like this.
Are you going to fast now?
No. I have to find out who the next CEO will be.
He really doesn't anchor to anyone. Sticking to people like a stick of glue or something.
He sticks to one side, then to another. Super adhesive.
He's not just a stick of glue, more like super glue.
I respect a part of him, though.
What?
At least his wife and children aren't starving.
Why does he look so sad?
I don't know why CEO Hwang suddenly did this.
Don't be too sad. He probably didn't mean what he said to you.
I think he did.
He said he's tired. He really looked that way.
I was the one who asked to break up, but why do I feel hurt?
I guess I thought even if I keep pushing him away, he would still be my side.
Then you should hold on to him.
You really looked happy when you were dating CEO Hwang.
It's Yeong Eun. Wait.
Yes, Yeong Eun?
Really? Okay, I'll tell Hyeon Joo.
Thank you.
It seems she called me because she couldn't get a hold of you.
She said she sent Kim Hyeon Soo's personal information to you.
What are you going to do? CEO Hwang said to just cover it up, didn't he?
CEO Hwang.
I thought we had established a deal. Was I mistaken?
I thought I told you to send Team Leader Seo away.
To be exact, you said we cannot work in the same company.
The deal was to not have me and Seo Hyeon Joo meet.
You'll get what you want.
So you're saying you won't fire Seo Hyeon Joo,
and you'll give up your CEO position instead?
Since you've come a long and difficult way, here is some more good news for you.
Once the new CEO is appointed, I'll go to our company's U.S. branch.
What this means is that you won't have to worry about us meeting in secret.
Take back your resignation immediately and fire Team Leader Seo.
Otherwise, this deal becomes void.
Kim Soo Jeong.
Director, what is it that you want?
You should have set a clear destination
or you'll end up in the wrong place.
Such as the end of a cliff, or in a fiery pit you cannot escape.
You really are Senior Jin Ho.
You guys don't only look alike.
Then, too, you destroyed your life for a worthless girl like that.
You haven't forgotten, right?
What you had to sacrifice for Min Joo.
Are you okay?
Senior!
She left you for a good man, and you ended up dying.
Aren't you experiencing déjà-vu?
Back then, it was Woo Yeong. Now, it's...
Stop it and just go back.
Find out who the next CEO candidate is. We need to take action first.
Yes.
So you're going to protect Seo Hyeon Joo until the end?
I can't let that happen.
Noona.
Do Gyeom, you arrived early.
Investigations are supposed to happen in pairs, you know.
Let's go to the security office first.
Okay!
- Hello!
What is it?
There's something I want to ask you. This person lived here. Do you know him by any chance?
He lives in Building 6, Unit 706.
This person? I do know him.
You know him? This person?
Have some of this and slowly tell us.
I'll enjoy it.
You young people are so friendly.
But I haven't seen that person for three or four days now.
The neighbors should know well. They would come and go to each other's houses.
He asked his younger brother to move his things?
He hasn't moved his things out yet, but he comes by whenever the real estate agent comes to see the house.
Young man, you're so handsome.
By any chance... could you give me his younger brother's contact information?
Sure.
Unit 706's younger brother is over there.
Hey! Excuse me!
Wait! Let's talk...
Noona! Are you okay?
Catch him!
We should've caught him!
Hi, Min Jeong?
Yes? Yes.
Okay, I got it.
It seems like Min Jeong found something in the surveillance footage.
I'll catch that person. You go ahead, Noona.
I'll leave it to you then.
Be careful.
Do Gyeom.
Thank you.
What do you want to eat for dinner?
Let's see...
It seems like it's going to rain. Should we order delivery at your place?
- Shall we do that?
- Yes.
If it rains really hard, you can stay overnight.
Come on.
Wait a moment.
What's up?
Hey, Jin Ah. Are you with Ji Hwan right now?
Why won't you meet me!!
What are you talking about? You agreed on this week's dating schedule.
We agreed on the terms of our divorce, that's what we agreed on.
I won't ever agree on you meeting other guys!
Where are you?
You just wait.
Ji Hwan, sorry but let's have dinner another time.
I'm going to go and show this one once and for all.
I'm sorry.
Okay...
Jin Ah...
He really stuffed his face.
Hey! Get up!
Get up already!
That hurt!
Oh, Jin Ah...
Why do you only hate me?
What about you? Why do you only do things that make me hate you?
I specifically told you I have no intention of breaking up with Ji Hwan, and you agreed!
I did. My mind did,
but this part of me couldn't agree!
Then be with another girl and not me.
Jin Ah, can't you just break up with that punk?
I'll fix everything about myself that you hate.
The way I talk, my personality, my habits, I'll even redo my face.
- What?
- Come on, that punk...
You like him because he's young, has a small face, and is cute.
I already picked out a plastic surgeon. I'll have to sell this place,
but it's okay. I'll get laser whitening, raise my nose bridge, get double eyelids,
and my head's a bit big so I'll have to shave my skull,
but it is completely possible!
How old are you to be saying those things?
I heard kids these days say it. Is it weird?
I can fix my face, but I can't fix my age so I should act young.
That's enough for today. Let's talk again when you're sober.
Jin Ah!
Jin Ah, let's get back together.
I will really, really take care of you.
Kim Eun Beom, did you forget why we divorced?
It was because of your mom.
The woman who married off her son so she could control her daughter-in-law!
Then I'll get cut off my mom! Should I sell my family registration, too?
Jin Ah, let's get back together! Please!
Look at this. This person's butt area seems a bit strange.
It does look like he put something inside.
And...
This is from after they searched your office.
Look.
What if they secretly brought the other contract in and switched them?
I thought the same thing, but it's only speculation.
Did you leave the webcam on this day?
You turned it on the second you arrived for your Vlog.
I did leave it on...
Check if anything was recorded.
Okay.
It's been confirmed that Team Leader Kim Hyeon Soo fled Korea.
I'm sorry.
It's all right. I had expected that they'd take care of him.
What happened with the other favor I asked?
I've taken action.
Also, Team Leader Seo asked about the status on your position.
I said nothing has been confirmed for now.
I didn't think she knew you were moving to the United States.
Please move the head office meeting to the branch in Yeouido.
For my external schedules, let's just go with this.
Yes, Sir.
Who is this person?
We found it.
The person you are trying to call...
Noona, is Hyeon Joo at the office?
She won't answer my calls.
Hyeon Joo went to go meet CEO Hwang.
CEO Hwang?
Yeah, but why wouldn't she answer your calls?
Did something happen?
I'll go and check.
♫ I’ll try to stop myself ♫
♫ I can’t hide all the memories, that’s all ♫
CEO Hwang, I have something to tell you.
It's important. Please make some time for me.
♫ It’s clear again before we know it ♫
♫ you’re still inside me ♫
♫ After a long time ♫
♫ I don’t know why my heart doesn’t flow ♫
♫ A promise not to make you cry ♫
♫ The days that I couldn’t keep are painful ♫
♫ I’ll be with you at any time ♫
The person you are trying to reach....
♫ Across many seasons ♫
♫ Not clumsy anymore ♫
♫ I’ll protect you like that ♫
If you keep your promise to never meet Team Leader Seo again, I will also wrap this up quickly.
So I'll accept that our deal has been finalized.
I'm not done.
If you break that promise, as a shareholder of Sunwoo Pharmaceuticals,
I will go through proper legal procedures to destroy the opposition for professional malpractice.
And the accused person will not be you, but Seo Hyeon Joo.
I understand.
♫ I’ll come to you in the wind ♫
♫ I’ll get you down like this petal ♫
♫ You recognize me ♫
♫ A little bit more than yesterday ♫
♫ I hope I can make you laugh ♫
♫ I hope you can lean on me every day ♫
Kim Soo Jeong had the music box you planned on giving me.
Please don't intervene anymore.
Go to Seo Hyeon Joo's home.
What will you do about the shareholders' meeting?
There is no past that will remain uncovered forever.
You killed them. Kang Jin Ho and Kim Min Joo.
The CEO is moving to the United States branch!
If I had gone to the place we agreed to meet...
If we remember this life in our next lives...
Would we be different?
I would not find you then.
♫ I’ll be right here ♫