[English subtitles are available]
[The Strange Princess]
[Episode 2]
Young General Lu,
according to the merchants nearby,
a few strangers went into
Hu's Rice Store in the afternoon.
I dare not alert them.
I've ordered someone to keep an eye on them.
Tell everyone
to go to Hu's Rice Store.
Dayou.
We're safe now.
I'm not Dayou.
Hu.
Go take a look.
Open the door.
It's me
[Hu's Rice Store]
We're closed.
I'm Ma Dayou.
Be gentle.
Hu.
It's me, Hu.
Hu!
Miss Yang.
We found a spy.
You...
I was right.
I...
It's all your fault.
Give it back to me!
Ma Dayou!
-Give it back to me.
-It's all your fault.
Ma Dayou.
You know this girl?
This girl?
He's not a girl.
I'm the girl.
No.
-I don't know what happened, either.
-It's all your fault.
Give me back my body!
Stop beating me!
Give me back my body! It's all your fault!
Stop arguing.
It's all your fault.
Say it one by one.
I was here to save my brothers.
I didn't expect that after a crash of thunder,
I would become the Princess.
You are the Princess?
I am the Princess.
I...
Listen, everyone inside.
Come out now.
Or we'll force our way in.
Come out!
Young General Lu,
it's the Princess.
It is Qian'er.
You despicable bandits!
I will kill you all!
Come here if you dare.
Let's see if I'll die first
or your Princess?
It's me, Tianxing.
It's me.
Tianxing.
Hongsu.
Hongsu, watch out!
My Lady.
Don't come over.
Put your knives down.
Or I'll kill her.
Put them down.
Arrest them.
Your Highness,
I'm incompetent.
Sorry for startling you, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
are you alright?
What do you think?
I didn't check the almanac before going out today.
I'm so unlucky.
Tianxing.
I'm Qian'er, Tianxing.
Ma Dayou.
You won't escape.
You...
Why does no one believe me?
I'm really Qian'er.
Ma Dayou.
You're a man.
It's just death at worst.
What are you afraid of?
Lu,
can I have a word with you?
Do you know
why I am here?
Didn't those robbers bring you here?
Of course not.
I took His Majesty's…
I took His Majesty's secret order
to make use of this opportunity
to infiltrate Jimao Mountain
and divide them from the inside,
so that the bandits will be eliminated forever.
We'll ask His Majesty to prove it.
It's too late.
You'll make them suspicious.
What do you think we should do?
How about this?
Later,
I'll rush out.
Tell your soldiers to pretend to stop me.
Got it.
Lu Ming.
Come here.
Yes.
Take some men
to escort the Princess
back to the palace.
Yes.
Lu.
You...
Qian'er.
After I finish my task,
I'll play the game of soldiers and thieves with you.
Your Highness.
You're really something.
Put your knives down.
Qian'er.
No!
Stop!
What are you doing?
You are forcing me.
If I die here today,
all of you are to be blamed.
Put down the knives.
Hongsu.
Hurry.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I love you.
You evil thief.
How dare you use my body to collude with the robbers?
I won't go with you.
What are you nagging about?
Hu, take him away.
Let's go, My Lady.
Tianxing, help me!
Tianxing!
Don't come over!
Tianxing.
Let's go.
Go!
Tianxing.
Young General Lu.
What should we do?
Follow them slowly.
Don't let them notice.
Yes, sir!
Nonsense!
I've never given her a secret order.
I'm incompetent.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Although Qian'er is a little mischievous,
she has never done such a ridiculous thing before.
Could there be
more to it?
How are you going to
to deal with it?
I've decided
to disguise myself
and sneak into Jimao Mountain
to save the Princess.
Thank you for saving me, Your Highness.
I, Yang Hongsu,
am very grateful.
Officials and bandits are on different paths.
That's enough to see us off this far.
If you go further on,
I won't be able to protect you.
We're family. Don't be too polite with me.
Your Highness,
you talk wildly.
You behave just like us, the outlaws in the woods.
That's all I can say.
Where are they taking me?
Father and Mother
must be worried for me now.
I have to find a way to escape.
Ma Dayou,
it is nothing to fail once.
You have to pull yourself together.
He was very close to death.
It's only expected to be like that.
I'll talk to him for you.
Look at me.
Don't play dead here.
Get up!
What are you doing?
Haven't you figured it out yet?
Now,
in their eyes,
you are the mighty
patriarch of Jimao Mountain.
If you want to live,
you have to play the patriarch well.
Don't act like a sissy all-day
and disgrace me.
Hongsu,
it's already dawn.
Let's go back to the mountain.
You're going, too?
Yes.
Ma Dayou.
What is going on here?
I...
Just find any excuse.
She is my wife.
What did you say?
He...
He's talking nonsense.
It's true.
What about me?
Who are you?
Second Master.
Second Master!
Bad news!
Why are you panicking?
Ma...
Ma Dayou is back.
What did you say?
I saw it clearly on the wall.
It is Ma Dayou, indeed.
But...
But that was a death trap.
Who would expect
that when the executioner's knife
was about to fall onto his neck,
Yang Hongsu suddenly came out
and saved him.
Who?
[Fortress Qingfeng]
Hongsu.
It's really not what you think.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
After we return,
I’ll ask him to write a divorce agreement.
-It won't affect you.
-Don’t.
Please don't.
Congratulations on your return, Master.
Brothers,
I'm back.
Master, you’re finally back.
I miss you so much.
My Master,
you're so…
Just cry over there.
Don't come over.
Second Master, no need to be so polite.
Please get up.
She is...
my wife.
I...
Then...
She…
Yang…
Why are you looking at me?
Hongsu.
Listen to my explanation, Hongsu.
It's fine.
I've set the table for a banquet
to welcome our Master.
Who am I?
Master.
In that case,
should the whole fortress
listen to my orders?
Yes.
We'll all listen to you, Master.
Good!
I want to take a bath and get changed.
Go boil the water.
Okay.
What's with Master Ma?
Go now!
Okay. Okay.
We'll get it ready now.
I'm going to boil the water!
Don't look anything against propriety.
As long as I don't look…
As long as I don't look at it,
It doesn't exist.
As long as I don't look at it…
As long as I don't look…
How did you get in?
The door was latched, wasn't it?
M-Master.
You know
the latch is broken.
Just leave it there and go away. Hurry.
Hurry up.
Close the door.
Okay.
Close the door!
Is he crazy?
He acted like I was molesting him.
Don't these bandits
take a shower?
They stink.
Who are you?
Where is Ma Dayou?
I am him.