Excuse me?
Me?
Gosh, it is noisy. I can't sleep.
I think something is missing.
What is it?
Drums. We need drums.
You know what song this is, right?
Tommy Emmanuel?
It is my song. The title is "Boomer Warning."
The title. It is good.
What is it?
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Why?
The youth these days, the way they even approach music is different from back in our days.
You do music, I see.
No, I don't.
I thought the person's performance just now was all right.
That is because you don't really know music.
You're right.
I have only worked on coffee.
Does the coffee taste all right?
Well, it is not bad for free coffee.
Goodbye.
Have a good day.
â˜• ð“”ð“¹ð“²ð“¼ð“¸ð“­ð“® 11: Light and Noise
Come again!
Do you want me to come again?
Yes.
I didn't pay, though.
You will probably pay if you come again.
I have money.
I guess the coffee wasn't to your liking.
You're right.
Then don't pay next time either.
I will take the money when the coffee is worthy of it.
Then suit yourself.
This is how you steam. Then if you press it like this, the extractor will operate.
The boiler is down here.
- Oh, it is down there.
- Yes.
Hello!
- Welcome!
- What brings you all the way here?
- Do you know them, Go Bi?
- Yes.
I will watch over here so go and see them.
- Is it okay if I do that?
- Yes.
How could you just leave without even saying goodbye?
I'm sorry.
How does it feel working in a place like this?
It feels like I leveled up.
You made the right decision.
People have to swim in bigger water.
Is the boss doing well?
- His condition these days is—
- He is doing very well.
He's doing well.
Seeing another person standing next to you instead of Ahjussi Seok,
- something feels—
- Much more easy on the eyes.
It's good.
Oh, gosh. We took too much of your time away from work.
Oh... I can't really be away for too long.
These are our signature menus so please enjoy!
Please come by the counter when you leave.
- Okay, thank you!
- You can get going.
Thank you for the coffee.
Isn't he doing a little too well?
His face... it has lightened up. It sure has.
It was always that way.
Even if we were at each other's throats and fought in the past, it was still fun to work together.
Youngsters these days don't even know how to work together,
they don't even want to.
It is sad, right?
I think they all think of it too easily.
It is because they all lack discipline.
Seok Pil, you,
even though you're dressed that way, your spirit is still the same.
What am I going to do with this guy?
What is wrong?
Hyung, let's get it together.
Until when are you going to live like this?
What is wrong with living like this?
The world changed a long time ago, yet you're still going on about drummers.
Won't you do anything?
I'm doing stuff, too. In my own way.
What are you doing?
Why do I even bother?
So? Will you join us or not?
Dressed like that?
What is wrong with this?
Why did you cut your hair?
What about you then?
I don't do it.
You said you do, in your own way.
Hey, let's stop. I'm tired.
What we did in the past... It is just noise.
A past I just want to erase now.
Hey. You can't talk like that.
Forget it, forget it. Let's just get up.
Was the coffee all right?
Yes. Thank you. It was really good.
It wasn't that good for me.
Then excluding the person who didn't enjoy it, it's â‚©6000 for one cup.
I'm sorry, he's normally not like this. I will pay for both cups.
Hey, I will pay for this.
Will you?
What? Go on out. I will be out after I pay.
You don't have to.
I will stop by from time to time if I ever have to pass by this area.
Goodbye.
Put it on the tab, please.
We don't keep tabs.
Can you write down your phone number?
You can take your ID.
Come again.
Did he come often before?
No, recently.
Oh...I was right.
Baek Jong Gil.
Look here.
This person... is that person?
Yes. He was the vocalist slash guitarist for the Black Metal band, Dead Seed.
Metal? Do you listen to stuff like that too?
What? Can't I?
Does he no longer do it?
It isn't that he is not doing it, he can't.
Why not?
The drummer died in a car accident.
After that, he completely disappeared from the indie scene.
He couldn't find a new drummer, I see.
He didn't find one.
They took a step forward into the darkness that they were desperately searching for
so they no longer had a reason to continue anymore.
Would it be okay if I sit for a moment?
I'm doing something right now so please come later.
You're Baek Jong Gil from Dead Seed, right?
Yes, what about it?
Could I ask for your autograph, please?
We didn't even make a lot of copies...
I'm a fan. My name is Kim Joo Hee.
Are you writing poems?
I'm just scribbling.
Thank you!
How was the coffee today?
It was bitter.
Goodbye.
Are you happy?
I am!
So noisy.
This thing actually rings, I see.
Yes?
What?
Okay.
- He's here.
- Oh.
I'm not someone to run away without paying back â‚©6,000.
I'm a businessman, too, you see.
What should I do first?
Cleaning? The dishes?
Can you please see if that boy over there has talent?
Tae Hyun, say hello.
Hello.
Did you write this?
It is Seashells Tied.
This song was that song...
- I was told that if a boy can play this much when he didn't learn from anywhere, it makes him a prodigy.
- Oh...
Right?
Prodigy...
Can you give me your guitar for a moment?
Can you try playing after me?
Don't feel pressured. Be comfortable.
Mom...
Are you crying, my son?
Oh, don't cry. Why are you crying?
- What is wrong with him?
- It is okay.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Hey, wait a moment, Sir.
Yes?
Please take Tae Hyun in as your student.
Mom?
I was looking for a teacher who wouldn't go easy on him.
In return, could you push him as hard as you can?
Whiplash. It is my favorite movie.
What's wrong with her?
Madam, could you listen to what I have to say?
What? I brought him over because of you.
How could you introduce us to a man like that?
You saw how he played, right?
It is Costa Rica Tarrazu coffee.
I no longer owe you anything, right?
Yes.
This coffee was made with green beans that went through honey processing.
There is a subtle fruity acidity and strong sweetness to it. It is a coffee that lingers for a long time.
Enjoy it slowly.
You were pitying me then.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Sir, you want to be a nice person, don't you?
Normally green beans from Central American coffee naturally have weak characteristics,
but that weakness got people interested in more experimental processing methods.
Honey processing is a good reflection of Costa Rica's processing methods from that interest.
Even so, coffee is all the same in the end.
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
You're so twisted like a pretzel!
You're right. It was taken from the South American processing method called Pulped Natural, only the name was changed.
In the end, it is a copy.
For music too. I hate people who just copy other people's work.
But Costa Rican farmers didn't stop at just copying that, instead they subdivided the steps of Honey Processing more.
From white to black. With more diverse flavors and easier names.
This is why the name "Honey Processing" has become a standard of its own now.
You're doing what I did to the boy just now, right?
Trying to make me feel small by showing off your knowledge?
You really don't get it.
How is saying that "we should still try to make something out of it" the same as scaring a child away?
Madam, you have a temper.
I'm not a "Madam," but a regular!
Regardless, from now on, whether our coffee is tasty or not, it is free.
Come by whenever you want.
Should I post a picture on social media and write a sentimental post for you?
That is what you want from me, right?
I have never given you coffee out of pity, not once,
but I think I will have to do that from now.
See? You're finally showing your true colors.
They're all the same.
Isn't it okay to pity someone who has given up on himself?
What do you want?
I don't want anything.
You have a talent.
I don't have anything like that.
You do.
You have low blood pressure, but you have the talent to give others high blood pressure.
That is not the first time I have heard that.
Just do it!
- Do what?
- Music.
I won't.
Can't you make a song for your friend who is no longer here?
Isn't that what true courtesy is?
You even wrote all the lyrics anyway.
No matter how much I look at him... It is a little...
The picture is too awkward.
You're right.
Madam Min!
Mr. Park, you haven't been doing well, have you?
I'm all right. Have you been well?
You know me, because of the one son that I have,
I'm going to die early.
Mom! I'm a grown man too—
For someone who says he's mature—
Oh, you had customers. Excuse us, please.
It is all right, Madam. Please carry on.
Oh, okay.
Whatever Ki Jung, this punk said, our promise is still valid.
You only think about making delicious coffee for a long time.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I will live as a better person.
You have to drink a cup of coffee.
I would love to, but next time.
This punk went around making a mess of so many things so I don't have enough time in the day.
Mom... I just tried to make things better—
Do you think any idiot can run a business?
My apologies.
You think it looks easy because he was in the same spot for twenty years, don't you?
All right. S-Stop. Stop it.
Do you really think the world is your oyster?
All right, then!
- Go back safely.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
Will Go Bi not come back even if he knows about this?
He's someone who left without even knowing it was closing down.
Was he always that ambitious?
It's probably not that simple.
Ahjussi? Should I try contacting Oppa Go Bi?
No, don't do that.
I'm here to pay back the coffee bills.
Mom! I got the car out, what are you doing here?
I don't know, you punk. Just quickly come in.
Wh-Who are you?
♪ Even coffee without sugar ♪
♪ Started tasting good after I kept drinking it ♪
♪ It seemed like a sophisticated person ♪
♪ It's just that the night has gotten longer ♪
♪ The time to be lonely has increased ♪
♪ Turns out I can live in a world without you, too ♪
♪ There are a lot of days I would've been sad not to see ♪
♪ I'm just singing along to the beat of footsteps ♪
♪ On the streets ♪
♪  What do I do  ♪
♪  With no way of putting to sleep  ♪
♪  These many days  ♪
♪  There are only regrets  ♪
♪  That keep piling up  ♪
♪ The morning comes down on my empty coffee cup ♪
♪ Wash your face clean when we meet again ♪
♪  I have many things to say to your bare face  ♪
♪ I have many things to say to that face ♪
- Sir?
- Yes?
- Ahjussi?
It's nothing.
Is it a trend?
Don't smile. You look even sadder.
You keep giving me good opportunities. Thank you, Sir.
I won't take any more of your busy time. Go on down back to work.
What do you think?
It's good.
What is this? Why is it so delicious?
Should we try making an affogato?
What are you doing tomorrow on your day-off?