Oh, you were home!
I'm at my office, not home.
Did I disturb you?
No... you've been coming by often.
Yes, well... I have a lot of gatherings and stuff.
Gosh, I'm tired.
Well, then you should've just stopped by to see me. Why did you buy all this stuff when I don't even cook.
Do you think I was going to have you cook? I bought them so I can cook for you.
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Goodness... Ahn Mi Na!
Why are the side dishes that I made last week still here?
I don't even have time to eat.
Then do you starve?
Sometimes.
Gosh.
I told you to change out this refrigerator, didn't I? How can you call this tiny thing a refrigerator?
I'll be back after I finish what I was working on. The deadline is just around the corner.
All right.
But Mom, didn't you wear that last week too?
Yes, so?
You should change out your clothes first.
â˜• ð“”ð“¹ð“²ð“¼ð“¸ð“­ð“® _ 9: Relative But Also Absolute
You don't have cooked rice.
Where did you put the rice?
I don't have any rice.
You don't have rice?
I eat well. Don't worry.
I didn't even ask you.
But you... Have you gotten thinner?
Maybe it's because I work out so much these days.
I think you're the one who got thinner, Mom.
Are you working out these days?
I have to if I want to live.
Is it a dinner gathering today?
No... tomorrow.
Then why did you come today?
- To see my daughter's face!
- Oh...
Not because you fought with Dad again?
Excuse me, do you not have Panama Geisha coffee beans?
Oh, no... our café doesn't sell those beans.
Then what about El Paraiso Lychee?
We are not a specialty café, so we don't. My apologies.
Oh, those were specialty beans I see...
I'll come back next time.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye!
There's been a significant increase of customers looking for specialty beans these days.
The third wave is flowing over to 2dae Coffee too it seems.
Do you know the third wave, too, Teacher Joo Hee?
I don't know if you know, but my lover makes coffee.
The first wave was instant coffee,
the second wave was franchise cafés with Starbucks as the representative,
and variation menus with espresso.
Then the third wave is none other than the specialty coffees.
Then are you saying that specialty coffee came to be because of the third wave?
Wasn't that it?
Teacher, stop teasing your pupil who needs to learn more and quickly tell him.
The term "specialty" had existed before that already.
The point of the third wave is the mindset.
"Let's break away from the simple and standardized franchise coffees."
"The starting point of that is in the green beans." Is this what you're talking about?
You've studied a bit.
I have no time to go around and taste them, but I can at least read about it.
I guess you can say it's the desire to connect the producers to the consumers even more closely.
It started from the mindset of wanting to share the story of what it took to make a cup of coffee.
There was a reason why it shifted from just categorizing by countries, but people know the cultivating and working environments now.
It does make people look quite cultured, though.
I can feel confidence from them too.
But I don't know if it's that people don't know the original intent or forgot about it...
iI's a little disappointing to see fellows in this field approach it too much like a trend.
They sell because it's expensive and people buy it because they think, "It must be delicious because it's expensive."
It does seem a little pretentious too.
I would think it probably depends on who made it, how, and who drinks it.
Your conclusion is vague again.
What do you think, Go Bi?
I'm curious, but I'm still not quite sure.
This is fine. How much more fashionable do you want me to be?
You always wear those clothes. You also said you have a lot of gatherings these days too.
Did I?
You said you don't have time too! Let's go buy clothes next time!
Gosh... if I knew you would voluntarily spend money I wouldn't have to do this.
Since we're talking about this...
don't you think you should buy and wear some proper clothes too?
Over there... it's my go-to café.
Is that so?
Shall we get a cup of coffee before we go?
You said you wanted to go shopping for clothes, though.
I thought you said you didn't want to. Gosh.
Do you think there is an absolute standard to taste?
- Hello.
- You're here!
We have another debate member.
You came right on time. Hurry and sit down.
- Oh, my M-Mom is here...
- Oh.
Hello.
Shall we sit?
Did you choose?
What should I drink?
Should I recommend you something?
Is it okay if I drink what my daughter recommends?
Mom... you're embarrassing me.
Of course, Mi Na knows better than me.
Then can you give us two lattes? One iced and one hot.
Yes, I'll prepare it for you right away.
Please enjoy.
Mi Na's very awkward... maybe because she came with her mom.
- Is that what you like?
- Yes.
I drink it from time to time.
She was like that too when you first came.
What? Me?
He really is a little oblivious.
I never thought I was someone who made others feel awkward.
It's the situation, not the person.
He's right. No one treats customers as comfortably as you do.
Although sometimes... I think I heard you make your boss feel uncomfortable.
Is it writer's block? I can't seem to pick up my brush...
Let's eat! Come on out!
Mi Na. I said, let's eat.
Let me sleep just a little more. Just a little...
Sleep after you eat lunch. The sun's been up for hours already.
- Oh, my d-deadline!
- What?
- My deadline...
- Wh-Wh-What's wrong?
Mom, get out, quickly.
- Quickly, quickly.
- What?
Go, go, go.
Damn it.
Yes, Sir!
Oh, yes.
I fell asleep while I was writing the concluding line.
I know you gave me a good opportunity... Yes.
Yes... I'm sorry.
Hey, Mi Na?
Yes?
Could you maybe check something out for me?
What is it?
This thing... I don't know how to set my profile picture.
I taught you this last time.
Look here. The picture of the flower is here—
No, no. Not that one. I mean the background picture.
The way to do it is the same.
Which one? Did you decide which one to use?
Decide whichever suits me best in your opinion.
It's your phone, you should decide. Why do you always ask other people—
You said you were busy.
What?
I've been asking you to draw one for me for a while, but you would never.
Well, that's because I don't know what you want, Mom.
I'll think about it.
What's this? You don't have a single selfie... it's all pictures of flowers.
It's pretty.
What is this? Is this your medicine?
What's wrong?
Why are you talking about medicine all of a sudden?
Well, you're the one who took a picture of it.
It's medicine for cold and body aches.
I've been so forgetful these days so I took a picture.
Body aches? Why do you get body aches?
Give it here. I'm not done yet.
I think it'll be better if I choose one and tell you, right?
Well... all right then.
Seriously.
What is it? Did something happen?
Oh, nothing... what is it?
Is there something you want to eat for dinner?
Are you not going to go home today?
I'll go after I make you dinner. I'll stay over if it gets too late.
Mom... can't you help me out a little?
What are you saying?
I need to work.
It'll only take a few seconds for you to tell me what you want to eat.
Food is not important right now.
No matter how busy you are, you still have to eat!
Mom, there's a flow to work.
It keeps getting cut off because of you!
I don't know stuff like that very well.
I'll just figure it out myself.
I'm not asking you to cook for me right now!
Just leave me alone, please!
Then what do I do?
Welcome.
You came alone today.
Yes, because Mi Na's a little busy with work.
Take your time to look and call me when you decide on a menu.
Could you give me a latte, please? Iced.
Yes, I'll prepare it for you right away.
Did you happen to...
Yes?
I was wondering if you chose it because it's something that Mi Na orders often?
You're right.
Then you'll have to change your seat first.
Pardon?
It's a filter coffee made from Ethiopia Sidamo beans.
Thank you.
Is this... the scent of flowers I smell?
It's bright and radiant, but definitely not light.
Just like Mi Na's personality.
Mi Na is like that?
They're also beans that Mi Na actually likes too.
She's quite sensitive, isn't she?
If an artist isn't sensitive, that's much more strange.
That's true too.
She wasn't always like that.
There's a sensitivity that sees familiar things in an unfamiliar way.
Mi Na's that type so I don't think you have to worry too much.
I really don't know my child.
She's a customer who comfortably lets off steam here so I'm always grateful.
You should also comfortably stay a long time and go.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to rest a little.
Oh, yes, yes!
Where are you, Mom?
Did you go home?
I asked where you are!
Mom!
Oh gosh, what's wrong with you.
You scared me!
Why didn't you tell me! I didn't know anything!
I'm so sorry, Mom... I was so wrong.
You sure notice things really well.
It's my fault. It's mine.
I can't live without you, Mom. I really can't, Mom.
You know that, right, Mom?
I'm all right.
It's early so the probability of curing it completely is high.
What do you mean you're "all right" when you're not!
I'm really sorry.
It's all right, it's all right... I'm all right.
Don't cry.
I'm so stupid.
What? How so?
I mean... I didn't even know you were going to the hospital early in the morning.
I just thought you were going hiking again.
Then did you think I ran away over here because I fought with your dad?
That's what I'm saying.
I fooled you well then.
Sit down, Ma'am.
Mom, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Your bibim guksu... I want to eat that.
No, you're tired, right? Should we just order something?
You're probably the only daughter who's so careful to ask her mom to cook for her.
Do you think so?
- Is it okay if it's a little noisy?
- Gosh!
Of course.
Then get working.
I'm not even going to call you this time!
I'm sorry for being sensitive.
You're done.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm used to it now. I'm not hungry yet.
Shall we have a cup of coffee?
Right now?
This is Ethiopia Sidamo, right?
That's right.
This is amazing! How did I never think to drink this iced?
Because there are no customers who ask for filter coffee with ice.
That's true too.
Don't you like the specialty job? Your answer last time seemed unsure.
I'm wondering if there's even a reason for me to be interested in specialties when I can drink coffee like this.
I think, in the end, the roaster's heart and sincerity is what's important.
This is a specialty bean.
Pardon?
Eom Sang Ho, the CEO who came by last time. They're the beans I got from him.
You said it was Ethiopia Sidamo, though...
Yes. Ours is Sidamo G2, CEO Eom's is Sidamo Guji G1.
Why are you putting me to the test again?
No, I just wanted you to try drinking it without any prejudice.
I guess this is what specialty is.
The maker's talent, efforts, and sincerity... all these are very important.
But there's definitely a difference that can't be overcome with just that.
I haven't known you for very long, but I'm confused every time.
A stubborn boomer who has turned his back to the world surprises you at times?
Yes.
I admit that I'm stubborn, too.
But I'm also insanely curious about coffee that other people make.
A boomer with a lot of curiosity?
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'll work harder!
Are you done?
It took some time. Were you waiting for me?
Come sit. I just need to boil the noodles.
I really wanted to eat this.
You finally feel like my child now. Eat a lot.
Let me look at your phone.
Why?
I couldn't change your profile picture.
- Let's see.
- Hey!
Look at it later after we're done eating.
Really? All right, then.
Mom... I'm going to go home.
What?! No! Don't come!
What was that? Why are you so against it?
I didn't want to tell you until the end because I knew you'd be like this.
What if something happened and you didn't tell me?
That's not going to happen. I'm not going to die.
No... even if I die, you should live doing what you want to do and live happily.
That's my wish.
Why aren't you wishing for yourself, but wishing for your child?
Did I?
Then... I'll have to wish instead of you.
What did you say?
Please let my mom be healthy,
until all my unknown 100 volumes of books gets published...
That... isn't something that'll be done quickly right?
Well... let's just say you're going to be immortal.
It's delicious.
Go on a business trip tomorrow.
After only ever seeing a 1.2 kg roasting machine in the store, seeing one this big... Wow!
What brings you here?
It's tempting after seeing it for yourself, right?
I don't know.
How dishonest of you.
Aren't you curious?
How Met Café was?
Eom Sang Ho, that punk... he teased our store for being a hole in the wall right?
I feel re-energized to work even harder after experiencing something new.