[The Lost National Treasure]
[Episode 20]
Wen Wen.
Mu.
Where's your sister-in-law?
Give it to me.
Okay.
Wen Wen,
plug in the electric heater
I just brought.
I don't want it.
Take it away.
Shulan,
the mountain is full of negative energy.
It's not good for your health.
Let's go home.
No matter how heavy
the negative energy is here,
it's not as heavy
as the negative energy surrounding you.
The cold will aggravate your rheumatism.
You can be angry with me,
but don't mistreat your own body.
No amount of suffering
can atone for my sins.
It won't bring my child back.
The sin is mine alone.
If anyone should suffer, it should be me.
Rest assured,
from now on, I'll bear the burden alone.
I won't touch any dirty stuff ever again.
Shusheng won't touch it either.
Alright then.
So stay here,
and copy scriptures
with me to atone for our sins.
Brother, it's not worth it
for such a small matter.
Here's the stuff for you.
When the big river runs dry,
the small river dries up.
Uncle will be the big river
of Qinchuan from now on.
Where did you get so much money?
I saved it up.
Who is Luo Qing?
She's a cultural relic expert
from the provincial institute.
I'll pick up.
Captain Qi,
Ms. Luo Qing,
what's the matter?
That empty tomb has been excavated.
There's another tomb underneath.
That's great!
Why are you so jumpy?
It's nothing. I'll be right there.
You're coming with me to the site.
What about picking up the kid?
Call Mom.
You must go.
Let me tell you,
I'll show you what I do every day.
Director Zhang.
Captain Qi.
Professor Xiang, you're here too.
-Yes, I'm here. Captain Qi.
-You're here.
And who is this?
I'm his wife.
How is it?
I heard there's another tomb underneath.
Come, come, have a seat.
Let's talk about it.
Please, sit down.
Yes, they're still digging below.
Any new discoveries?
Nothing yet.
We're waiting for news.
There's hope.
Good.
You...
Captain Qi.
Ms. Luo Qing, how is it?
It's still an empty tomb.
-Empty?
-What?
There are no burial objects below,
no funerary objects,
coffins, or skeletal remains.
There's nothing at all.
It's the same as the first empty tomb.
The tomb owner must have been crazy.
Why dig two deep empty tombs?
I have a bold guess.
No one would go to such lengths
to design
two such deep empty tombs for no reason.
There's only one possibility.
It's to prevent theft.
So I think the real burial chamber
should be at an even deeper level.
A third layer?
Someone with such intricate planning,
according to the Lv family genealogy,
there can only be one person.
Our ancestor, Lv Dalin.
Director Zhang,
what do you think?
It's hard to say.
It's not impossible.
We still need facts and evidence
to speak for themselves.
Just keep digging.
You'll have evidence once you dig.
Always saying "it's hard to say," come on.
If we dig further,
we'll hit the Liaojiang stone layer.
What's the Liaojiang stone layer?
It's a type of grayish-white rock.
It's extremely hard.
Yes,
when local people dig wells,
if they encounter this kind of stone,
they can't dig any further.
Even if it's hard, we still have to dig.
What's the big deal?
Captain Qi.
We're different from you.
You handle cases,
taking one step forward
with two legs following closely behind.
for us, whether we can take that step
depends on passing three checkpoints.
Don't be in a hurry.
We'll let you know
once we've finished our research.
It's not that I'm impatient,
it's that the case is urgent.
Just dig!
You can pass
six checkpoints for all I care.
Aren't you going to
dig anyway after all that research?
Shut up, will you?
You're so indecisive.
Fine, I'll wait, I'll wait.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing all day long?
Ms. Luo.
There's a major discovery in pit M1.
Your leg
doesn't seem to
be getting any better here.
If you ask me,
we should go back down the mountain.
Your phone is ringing.
Don't worry about it.
Hello?
I understand.
I'll come down right away.
Sir,
how about a fortune telling?
You don't even know
where your next meal is coming from,
yet you're telling fortunes for others?
My next meal is right here with you.
I see that your brows are radiant,
your forehead is full and moist,
surely a sign of
great fortune in your future.
However, there's a slight unfavorable
aura around your eyes,
spreading to your forehead,
which might affect
your children's fortune.
So, do you see
any offspring in my future?
Yes,
within a year.
That's enough.
You're having a hard time too.
You got one thing right though.
Your next meal is indeed with me.
Go eat.
Look at this.
His name was Daya, courtesy name Zhengzhi,
the youngest son of the Lord.
This indicates that
the occupant of tomb M1
is Lv Daya.
The Lord?
It refers to his father, Lv Ying.
There's another passage here.
Look at this part.
Tong had two sons, the eldest named Ying,
who held the position of
Assistant Director of the Palace Library,
and was posthumously awarded
the title of Senior Court Gentleman.
So this tomb's occupant is Lv Ying's son,
and Lv Ying
is also the eldest son of Lv Tong.
Lv Daya's second son
was adopted by one of his cousins.
Can you guess who?
Could it be our founding father, Lv Dalin?
That's right, it's Lv Dalin.
Because Lv Dalin
had no children of his own,
so the child was adopted by him.
There's another interesting point.
Come and look at this.
Here, let me take over.
Take a look at this tomb epitaph cover.
See if you notice
anything different on the back.
There are words on it.
It says "Epitaph of Lord Zhang,
Former Prefect
of Dingzhou
of the Great Tang, Upper Pillar of State."
You're right. This tomb cover
was repurposed.
It originally belonged to
a Tang Dynasty governor surnamed Zhang.
So during the Song Dynasty,
this tomb cover was already an antique.
And in the Lv family,
wasn't Lv Dalin the one
who loved collecting antiques?
Think about it.
Lv Dalin's stepson was Lv Daya's son.
And Lv Dalin loved collecting antiques.
This tomb cover
was likely one of Lv Dalin's collections
that was eventually
used for Lv Daya's funeral.
M2 and M1 are so close to each other.
The more we talk about it,
the more it seems
that M2 is Lv Dalin's tomb.
The excavation of M1
has to some extent helped
confirm the identity of M2's occupant.
Now we believe
that M2 is very likely
to be Lv Dalin's tomb.
This is a newly discovered tomb cover
that has been repurposed.
It has inscriptions on both sides.
The front side is inscribed with "Tomb of
Mr. Lv, Retired Officer of Song Dynasty,"
which refers to the occupant of M1.
The back side reads
"Epitaph of Lord Zhang,
Former Prefect
of Dingzhou
of the Great Tang, Upper Pillar of State."
The exact identity is uncertain.
Chief Wang,
if we dig deeper,
we'll encounter the Liaojiang stone layer.
If we're too gentle,
we can't dig through it.
If we're too forceful, it might collapse.
From what we know now,
both the first and second tomb layers
have a lot of collapsed soil.
If the third layer is a real tomb
and hasn't been looted,
it could easily collapse,
which would cause
irreversible damage.
Your concerns are valid.
The Lv Family Tomb
is now attracting a lot of attention.
If it's really Lv Dalin's tomb,
then millions of eyes will be watching.
I suggest
we proceed with caution
in further excavating M2.
We should first develop
a plan before considering excavation.
We need to base our work on
legal, standardized,
and technological criteria.
We must ensure everything is foolproof.
We will come up with
the safest excavation
plan as soon as possible.
Mr. Mu,
you're impressive.
You have a keen eye.
You've acquired so many
good items in such a short time.
Your ability to take action is remarkable.
Mr. Zhao, you flatter me.
I owe it all to your support.
It's all thanks to your care.
I've just been riding on your coattails.
What coattails of mine are you riding on?
Speaking of it,
recently,
I've indeed heard some things.
They say in Qinchuan city,
there's someone called Uncle
who's been making quite a stir.
Some things have reached my ears.
Mr. Mu,
in life,
one should
keep a low profile.
A tall tree catches the wind.
Is that so?
Right.
You are right.
Mr. Zhao.
They're here.
Oh?
I'll head back first then.
Let's go together.
Alright.
Let's go.
Okay.
Here's the case.
Yuhe.
Please see Mr. Mu out.
Alright.
You go ahead with your business.
Okay, okay.
Welcome back anytime.
This way.
Qin.
I heard there are two decent goods.
That's great.
Let's go inside.
Have a seat inside.
What?
What's the rush?
You must be deaf. Get out of my way.
What?
Sheng.
It's me.
Shuan.
How long has it been since we last met?
You've gained weight.
I have.
Looks like life's been treating you well.
Sheng.
Is this your construction site?
You see, it's really...
Talk about a lucky coincidence.
What a coincidence.
How did you end up here?
I'm stuck in the office all day.
I'm bored to death.
Shuan.
Let me ask you something.
There must be something
underneath here, right?
If there is...
Just dig it up openly.
This is my territory.
I'll cover for you.
Let's be clear about this upfront.
The stuff is under my land.
An organizer
should be me, right?
I quit that business long ago.
You quit?
Yes, I quit.
I'm just a laborer now.
Although it's still digging...
The nature of the work
is completely different.
Working here for a year
doesn't compare to a single day
of what we used to do.
You're not telling me the truth.
Sheng, this is your construction site.
You must know
if there's anything underneath.
Don't you?
There really isn't anything down there?
Sheng.
You must be making a fortune now that
you've switched to building houses.
And building houses is profitable.
The money comes in quickly.
Quick? This is hard-earned money.
What about you?
Why did you change your line of work?
Sheng.
It's not that
I didn't want to do it anymore.
I just couldn't continue.
A group of people
showed up out of nowhere.
They are very powerful.
Any site they set their eyes on...
Any goods they fancied...
They'd just snatch it up.
They don't just rob goods,
they also buy them.
The key is they're pushing
the prices ridiculously low.
No one in all of Qinchuan dares
to offer higher prices than them now.
In the end, there's no choice.
We can only sell to them at a cheap price.
I've only been out
of the game for a few days,
and our industry's atmosphere has
already deteriorated to this point.
Who is it?
So formidable.
So powerful.
I think it's called something like...
Some Uncle...
Li.
Li something Guang.
Uncle?
Close the door.
Have a seat.
What do you want from me?
What is it?
You're always stirring up trouble
out there with an outsider,
making a fortune, aren't you?
You've shoved me off
to that construction company.
What are you getting at?
What do you mean by that?
What do I mean?
Remember this.
One hand can't cover both ears.
Now everyone in the Qinchuan industry
knows about this.
And you're still keeping it from me?
What have I kept from you?
You haven't kept anything from me?
Then how did this
Uncle become Li Yuanguang?
You're hiding it from me.
You two are in cahoots, making big money.
What?
You want to monopolize Qinchuan
and sideline me, don't you?
Sheng,
your mind,
it's really something else.
Getting paid without doing any work,
and you still feel like
you're getting the short end of the stick.
How about this?
If you don't want to do it, step aside.
There are plenty of people
lining up to be a mascot.
I don't need to
keep doing these thankless favors anymore.
As for you,
go back to your old trade.
But since we're family,
let me give you a word of warning.
Qi Dacang has been keeping an eye on you.
If one day they catch you,
don't blame me
for not being capable enough
to bail you out.
Stop trying to scare me.
You're also on Qi Dacang's radar.
Why can you do it and I can't?
Some things
you can't figure out on your own,
and even if others explain it
to you, you still won't understand.
You have wine
but insist on drinking vinegar.
You insist on being a tomb raider
who can't get out of his den.
Then go ahead,
I won't stop you.
So you mean
I can only watch you two eat the meat
while I just drink the soup?
If that's how you want
to see it, I can't help you.
Fine.
Two Circles.
Pung!
Wait a moment.
It's a win.
What?
Look.
Pay up first.
I've been losing all day.
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
You set up this game,
and now you're just quitting?
You want to leave?
Settle your debts before you go.
Lai, pay up.
Bro,
I'm a bit short on cash lately.
I'll bring the money to you later.
Later, later, later...
Cut the crap.
Stop being so shameless here.
Don't be so harsh with your words.
We're all from the same village.
Cut the crap and pay up.
Bro, you
You seem to have forgotten
about that 200-yuan stone.
When have I ever left
you out when I made money?
Is that petty little matter
even worth mentioning?
You have the nerve to bring that up.
I've been playing dumb for so long.
After all that trouble,
we only sold one stone.
Didn't you say ten pieces?
That was because Fang Kun found out.
You've been
following the archaeological team.
What did you actually accomplish?
What results did you get?
Bless your heart.
You're hopeless.
Mr. Lv!
What's up?
Come down for a moment.
Go, go, go, take a look.
What's the matter?
I've drilled all the holes
you laid out for me.
Can you lay out some more for me?
You've finished them all?
You've drilled all
the holes I laid out for you?
That's right.
You're quite impressive, young lady.
You're almost surpassing me, your master.
Master, you're teasing me again.
Why would I flatter you?
At your speed,
you're faster than those who've
been doing this for two or three years.
I wouldn't dare say that, Master.
What's wrong, Master?
Why is there variegated earth here?
Master,
why can't there be variegated earth?
Mr. Guo, Mr. Guo.
Come here with Mr. Fang for a moment.
Mr. Guo.
Mr. Fang.
I've double-checked everything.
We laid out the holes exactly as you said,
using the location where the black pottery
figurine was unearthed as the coordinate.
12 holes in two rows
north to south, that's correct.
16 holes in two rows
east to west, also correct.
The distance between holes is five meters.
Still correct.
Now that we've finished drilling,
God knows we haven't
reached the bottom yet.
What do you think, Lu?
Mr. Guo, Mr. Fang,
I can guarantee
we'll be able to drill so fast.
It can only mean one thing:
This tomb,
is more impressive than we thought.
It seems
the size and structure of this tomb
far exceed our initial expectations.
Let's discuss something.
Can we change our drilling method?
You want to use the plum blossom pattern?
What's the plum blossom pattern?
Look, we're currently
using the grid pattern.
The grid pattern drills two rows
of holes vertically and horizontally,
which means
drilling these
exploratory holes in a cross pattern.
[Grid Style]
Its main purpose is
to determine the stratigraphy
in both vertical and horizontal directions
within the large working area.
The plum blossom pattern,
[Plum Blossom Style]
as the name suggests,
we drill the exploratory holes in a pattern
that resembles plum blossoms.
Like this.
This is mainly
to determine large-scale remains
and the extent of the burial site.
Here's the case.
Let's increase the distance
between these exploratory holes
by doubling it.
Let's reduce the density
of this general survey.
First, let's determine
the range of this tomb,
shall we?
Alright.
Fine.
I think it's good.
Everyone, let's work hard.
I'll go to town later to buy a chicken.
We'll treat everyone tonight.
Okay, okay, no problem.
You've got quite a collection here.
What are you interested in?
Are you just selling,
or do you buy things too?
Are you looking to sell something?
Yes.
What kind of item?
Qin bricks and Han tiles.
Extremely valuable, priceless.
How much do you want for them?
Three thousand.
Three thousand?
Listen.
What?
My shop is small.
Can't handle such high-value items.
Go out,
turn left.
That place
can handle your high-value items.
Are you messing with me?
There's nothing
to the left except a trash can.
Silly.
Even if you throw your garbage
into the trash can, no one would want it.
You're talking nonsense.
Let me tell you the truth.
A whole set of Qin and Han dynasty tiles
is only worth three to five hundred yuan.
Your broken pieces are worth nothing.
You said they're high-value items.
Go away.
Get out of here.
You're wasting my time.
Shulan.
It's me.
Wen Wen made some dumplings for you.
They're vegetarian and still warm.
Shulan.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Don't come here anymore.
Go back.
I'll leave the dumplings at your doorstep.
And the newly bought medicine.
Along with an electric blanket.
Smells delicious.
Mr. Lu, we're counting on you.
Alright.
I've got two bottles of good wine.
Let's celebrate tonight.
Okay.
Guo.
I don't mean to rain on your parade.
It's okay if you're happy about it.
But don't get too excited too soon.
We haven't even confirmed if it's a tomb
or a burial complex yet.
Why have you become so conservative now?
Didn't you say
we should make bold guesses
and seek careful verification?
You make bold guesses,
and I'll seek careful verification.
Right?
Right, right, right.
You verify, I'll guess.
Put the knife down, put it down.
Lu,
I've been thinking,
we should increase the depth now.
Let's find the tomb passage first,
and then we'll measure the depth
and dimensions of the passage.
Let's first
trace the structure of this burial.
What do you think?
No problem.
Is that okay?
It's doable.
Alright, good.
Luo Qing.
You haven't eaten anything
all day.
You should drink
some hot fermented rice soup.
It'll give your body some calories,
so you'll have
more energy to write better.
Thank you, senior.
Don't worry about me.
You all go and rest.
Actually, everyone
is quite worried about you.
You're pushing yourself so hard.
We're afraid you might wear yourself out.
I'm really fine.
You should go rest, quickly.
I'll drink it in a bit, just a moment.
Luo Qing, it's like this.
Actually,
after working with you these days,
I feel
the job of team leader
is indeed quite tough.
I was thinking,
if, I mean if,
you want to step back from the front line,
I can
fully support you.
Who steps back at such a young age?
If you keep talking here,
I'll be even less
able to continue writing.
Alright, I won't bother you then.
remember to drink something.
Every word spoken by an archaeologist,
every judgment made,
could potentially affect
the accuracy of a period
of history and civilization.
Therefore,
we must be extremely cautious,
never make assumptions,
and never jump to conclusions lightly.
Mr. Fang,
someone's going to die.
Mu, don't worry.
I'll go to the mountain tomorrow.
Wen Wen,
thank you on behalf of your sister-in-law.
So many dishes.
You should sit down and eat with us.
We're all family, no need for formalities.
Alright.
Wen Wen.
Sheng, Feng.
Is my brother-in-law here?
Yes, he's eating.
Jianhui.
Look, look, look.
Feng made dumplings today.
She said to bring some over to you.
You're eating dumplings too?
What a coincidence.
Perfect timing.
The filling seems different.
Let's make it a double happiness.
Let's eat together.
I'll go get a cup.
Try the dumplings Feng made.
Sheng.
Feng, enjoy your meal.
Just call me if you need anything.
Come on, sit here and eat with us.
No need, no need.
We brought so much.
You eat.
Sit down and eat with us.
The kid is still quite shy.
Come on, let's eat then.
That day,
after you talked to me,
I went back
and thought about it over and over.
I finally understood.
I realized
who truly cares about me.
You see, I'm short-sighted.
I couldn't see
the grand ambitions in your heart.
The flock needs to follow the lead sheep.
That's right.
You are my lead sheep.
From now on, I'll follow right behind you.
Wherever you go, I'll go.
You really understood?
I did.
That's more like it.
What took you so long?
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Hou.
Fang Kun?
I recognized you from behind.
Why are you here so late at night?
Can't I come late at night?
Just checking on you, paying a visit.
I missed you.
You smooth talker.
Miss me?
You actually miss me?
Who else would I miss?
What's that you're carrying?
It's getting colder, isn't it?
I bought a small heater for Luo Qing.
She's been staying up all night recently.
I'm worried she might catch a cold.
Isn't there already a stove?
That stove isn't enough.
Won't this make it a bit warmer?
Are you sure this thing works?
What do you mean?
Why wouldn't it work?
Nothing.
Hou, is this your first time
doing fieldwork?
It is indeed my first time.
Okay.
First time is good.
What do you mean?
Isn't this written quite well?
You scared me to death.
You didn't even knock when you came in.
Like a ghost.
Oh my god.
When did you get here?
Ms. Luo,
look at your eyes.
You've turned into a panda
in just a few days.
It's just like what Xiaobai said.
Haven't you eaten or slept for days?
He's the one
who tipped you off again, isn't he?
Xiaobai is just
concerned about his teacher.
He's worried you might work yourself sick.
So why did he send you here?
To team up and annoy me?
It's not like that.
At most, we'd team up to knock you out
so you can get some proper sleep.
You should go do whatever you need to do.
Go back to where you came from.
I haven't even warmed my seat yet,
and you're already kicking me out.
We're colleagues after all.
In this freezing weather,
you could at least
offer me a meal or something.
Isn't there any?
Senior made it.
I can't eat. You go ahead.
What the hell did Hou make?
It's so watery.
How can this fill you up?
Luo Qing.
Don't you know how to knock?
You scared Ms. Luo.
I...
Well, Fang Kun.
I made this for Luo Qing.
Why are you eating it?
Luo Qing, I'll make you
another bowl in a bit.
No need, I can't eat.
You have to eat
so that your body can have calories.
Luo Qing, look at this.
Doesn't it feel warm...
Unplug it!
Well.
Senior,
this small heater
can't handle the old house's wiring.
It's definitely going to short circuit.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it would short circuit.
I thought having a small heater
would make you a bit warmer.
How did it short circuit?
How about this?
I'll go find an electrician.
Then have them fix the wiring.
Where are you going to find
an electrician in the middle of the night?
Can you stop making things worse?
Alright, Luo Qing.
Don't blame Hou.
If you want to blame someone,
blame me for not reminding him, okay?
What do you mean?
You knew he was going to use the heater?
Yeah.
And you didn't warn him?
I just wanted the lights to go out.
So you could get some good sleep.
What kind of person are you?
Who are you to me?
Wait, can you guys just...
Stop caring for me in your own way.
Stop being so presumptuous.
I'm really busy with something.
Oh no, now she's really angry.
Jianhui.
Go call Wen Wen out.
Go quickly.
Wen Wen.
Come on, join us.
Let's eat together.
It's been so long
since we've seen each other.
Mu.
Mu drank too much.
It's okay.
It's fine, let him sleep for a while.
Rest a bit.
Sit down, sit here.
I'll help him inside to sleep.
It's alright.
When people drink too much,
we can't move them.
-He might vomit.
-Long time no see.
I've been wanting to thank you.
I can't drink either.
It's okay.
You can't drink.
Sit here and have a chat.
Really, it's good 30-year-old liquor.
That's enough.
-I can't drink.
-It's fine.
It's alright, we're happy today.
That's right.
You've worked hard lately, Wen Wen.
It's my duty.
There's a lot of work to do at home too.
See how busy
my brother-in-law is.
Come on, let's have a drink.
It's all in the wine.
Cheers.
Thank you, Wen Wen.
I'll drink it all.
Drink it all.
It's fine for young folks.
Come on, eat, have a dumpling.
I made them.
Have a dumpling.
I don't want any.
You won't eat?
If you're not eating, then drink. Come on.
Luo Qing.
If you ask me,
your ability to
handle pressure is so poor.
You might as well
not be the team leader anymore.
What do you mean?
From what I know about you,
the plan you've written must be good.
So in my opinion,
you just can't handle pressure well.
You lack confidence in yourself.
The institute has given you
a task beyond your capabilities.
How many eyes are watching?
If anything goes wrong,
not only will you fail to lift the roof,
but you'll also
smash the ancestors' skulls.
So you toss and turn, hesitating,
unable to make a decision.
What are you trying to say?
You know,
we're archaeologists.
It's all about academic work.
Right?
But being a team leader is different.
A team leader has to make decisions.
If you keep hesitating,
your team members will be on edge too.
Whether it's Xiaobai
or Hou,
they're not just your support group,
they're your teammates too.
If one project drains you completely,
then I suggest
you might as well
just go back to
the institute and take an office job.
Wouldn't that be much easier?