[The Lost National Treasure]
[Episode 2]
Didn't you answer
some of their questions last time?
This time,
they've come up with a few tricky questions again.
What kind of questions?
Simply put,
which looting pit did these pottery figurines come from?
But doesn't Winthrop Auction House
usually specify the origin?
You mean Sanmiao Village?
What?
Sanmiao Village?
They labeled it as from Sanmiao Village in the western suburbs.
Western suburbs?
Wulingyuan in the western suburbs?
It's not that far.
So these pottery figurines we've recovered this time,
what are their characteristics?
Are they the same as those of the six pieces?
Well, the degree of blackness
of these pottery figurines varies.
Some are darker,
while others are lighter.
[Sanmiao Village]
Why isn't he answering the phone?
He must be asleep.
Sleeping that deeply, huh?
Captain Qi, we found it.
You found the looting pit?
No,
in the farmland near Sanmiao Village,
I found tools hidden by the tomb raiders.
How did you find them?
Well, that's because Captain Yang is so experienced.
He took me around the village to ask questions.
A villager said
that his farmland had been destroyed.
But it is just a small area.
Captain Yang thought this was a bit strange,
so he brought me over to take a look.
And guess what?
Only this area was flattened.
I quickly dug it up,
and as soon as I did, I found these tomb-raiding tools.
Newly buried.
There are only two possibilities.
Either they haven't started digging yet,
or they're halfway through.
There's no looting pit nearby?
This area is quite large, and it's not easy to search.
But Captain Yang said, since the tools are here,
they haven't succeeded yet.
They should be back soon.
Right.
Quickly restore everything to its original position
at the scene.
Hide nearby.
Don't startle them.
I'm coming right away.
It's right here.
Oh my goodness.
The pit is already dug.
Looks like they're going to loot artifacts today.
Luckily, we came today.
Otherwise, it would have been over.
Slowly, slowly.
Hold on to it.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Hold on to it, hold on to it.
Oh my god!
H-How did he go down?
Are you okay?
Say something.
I'm gonna die from that fall!
Hurry, hurry!
The shovel is coming.
Don't drop me like I dropped him.
Get down quickly, quickly.
Why hasn't Captain Qi arrived yet?
If they succeed in looting artifacts, they'll get away.
There are three of them and only two of us.
Chasing them is a problem.
They won't get away.
Why do you say that?
I have a gun.
What's there to be afraid of?
We're two against one now.
Let's catch him red-handed.
We'll deal with the two below later.
We can do it.
Why bother with all that effort?
Why?
Look at that pit.
There's only one person there.
I'll go over and kick him down with one foot.
We'll catch them all at once.
We can do it.
Police! The police are here!
-Stop!
-Go after him!
Stop right there!
Captain Yang!
Guard the entrance!
Okay.
Be careful.
Stop!
Shots fired!
Don't move!
Still running?
Run if you can!
What took you so long to get here?
Where's Captain Yang?
Inside.
Captain Yang!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
No movement from them, right?
No.
Did you catch
that on-site commander of the tomb robbery?
Yeah.
Guys!
It's stuffy down there!
Come up for some air!
Are you sure there are two of them?
Sure.
Zhou and I saw them clearly.
Has there been no movement at all?
They probably heard the commotion up here.
They don't dare to make a sound.
Bro!
Your accomplice has already confessed.
There's no need for you to hold out down there.
Come up quickly.
How about I give you a hand?
Yongfu.
They don't have a blower.
There's not much oxygen left down there.
Contact the nearby village and police station
to ask for a blower.
I've made the call.
I've made it.
Guys.
You're both professionals.
You know
the oxygen down there won't last much longer.
It's not worth risking your lives
any further.
Right?
Well,
if you come up now,
I'll consider it as turning yourselves in.
We can arrange for leniency. What do you think?
He's asking us to turn ourselves in?
-You can think about it.
-Think of us as fools?
Just say the word.
Let us know.
-You're safe, okay?
-If we're caught red-handed...
Even if we turn ourselves in, we'll still be sentenced.
No response?
I'm going to answer the phone.
Hello.
Go ahead.
Guys,
say something!
Tie.
Tie, don't fall asleep.
If you do, you'll stop breathing.
Captain Qi.
The village and the police station don't have any blowers.
The director said to borrow one from the neighboring village.
That'll be too late.
We can't wait anymore.
What are you doing?
If anyone's going down, it should be me.
That's enough!
How many tomb raiders have you dealt with?
Once someone comes down...
You two, stop talking nonsense.
The oxygen is thin down there.
We're going to hit him.
We'll take down as many of them as come down.
Captain Yang...
If we keep dawdling, they're going to die!
Slow down, slow down, slow down!
-Captain Qi, slow down!
-Loosen a bit.
Hold on to it, hold on to it.
Loosen a bit, loosen a bit, come on.
Loosen a bit, come on.
You two can come if you want,
but why do you have to drag me into this?
When the cat's away, the mice will play.
Mr. Zan will scold us to death after he returns.
You're Fang Kun's pillar of strength.
Once you leave,
he
will lose all his souls completely.
Aren't you afraid that with this pillar of strength around,
he might poke a hole in the sky?
You...
Sir.
May I ask you something?
Is Sanmiao Village somewhere around here?
Yes, it is. Why?
Is there an ancient tomb in this village?
What do you do?
We're an archaeological team here to do research.
Yes, that's right.
Archaeologist team, huh?
A gang of tomb raiders was just caught last night.
I guess there must be an ancient tomb.
Otherwise, why would those tomb raiders
be digging around there?
D-Do you know where it is?
Where is it?
Go straight ahead from here.
It's about 500 meters away.
But now the police have cordoned off the area.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, thank you so much.
What a coincidence.
We've just arrived and already encountered tomb robbery.
Could it be the black pottery figurine gang?
It can't be, right?
The situation is so tense right now.
They wouldn't dare to commit crimes in such circumstances.
Let's make way, come on.
Fang Kun.
-Mr. You.
What are you doing here?
We heard that the black pottery figurines were from here.
So we wanted to take a look.
On the day when those six black pottery figurines were withdrawn from auction,
it was these young archaeologists
who helped answer the questions.
So young.
Truly accomplished at such a young age.
You... You're also here to see the black pottery figurines?
Yes, yes.
Well,
we'll wait for you up ahead. See you in a bit.
Alright, alright.
The one who can solve our puzzle has arrived.
Let's go.
You're awake.
Officer Qi.
How many years have you been a police officer?
Why are you still so eager to take the lead?
You acted like a reckless rookie.
Do you know
you almost lost your life in there?
My head hurts badly. I need some quiet.
Of course it hurts.
Luckily, the oxygen was extremely low in that pit.
The tomb raiders didn't have much strength.
Otherwise,
you'd be gone.
Even Captain Yang couldn't stop you.
Look how capable you think you are.
What are you smiling about?
You just can't be more serious.
You've finally woken up.
You scared us to death.
Chief Zhao, well,
Mr. You brought Director Zhang here.
It's alright.
Okay.
Hey, put it down slowly. Slowly.
Keep an eye on him.
Mr. You.
Chief Zhao.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Captain Yang, Chief Zhao is here.
Mr. You.
Thank you for making such a special trip.
It's no trouble at all.
It's nothing compared to your efforts.
I didn't expect such high efficiency.
Who's down there?
Director Zhang.
He got excited as soon as he arrived.
So he went down by himself.
I don't think these black pottery figurines
have any connection to Sanmiao Village.
Why?
-What evidence?
-What evidence do you have?
What's the main manufacturing technique for black pottery figurines?
Assembly.
Molding.
That's right.
And they have diverse forms.
They're also much smaller than the terracotta figures of the Qin Dynasty,
with proportional body proportions,
full-faced appearances,
and lifelike expressions.
These characteristics
are all consistent with those
of the pottery figurines unearthed from the Western Han Imperial Mausoleums.
So I can basically determine
that they were unearthed from the Western Han Imperial Mausoleums.
But look at this area beneath our feet,
Sanmiao Village.
Although it's relatively close to Wulingyuan,
it's still quite far from the Western Han Imperial Mausoleums.
So I think
the possibility of them being unearthed here
is almost non-existent.
That makes sense, really.
There's really something to you.
Quite professional, aren't you?
Where are you from?
-Who are you?
-Y-You are...
I'm from the Qinchuan City Public Security Bureau.
I'm Captain of the Cultural Relics Inspection Team.
My name is Qi Dacang.
Captain Qi.
W-We are graduate students from Qinbei University.
-We're from the Department of Archeology.
-Department of Archeology.
Fang Kun.
Guo Shilin.
Luo Qing.
Young students.
Who brought you here?
Mr. You.
Zan Maochang is our supervisor.
Have you been to the scene?
No.
But about the black pottery figurines
at the Winthrop Auction House,
we answered the questions.
If you study cultural relics,
you're experts in the field.
We wouldn't dare to say that.
I'm just an outsider anyway.
But why do I say
there's something to what he said?
Look,
have you seen the Terracotta Warriors of Emperor Qin Shi Huang?
Yes.
You see, those Terracotta Warriors,
each one has a different face.
Why?
They're life-sized, and some are even larger than life.
They're all painted.
It shows the nation's strength.
By the Han Dynasty...
-The terracotta figures buried with him...
-He's coming up.
-Slowly.
-Slowly, slowly.
Pull, pull hard.
Come on, come on, pull hard.
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
Quick, quick, quick.
One, two, three, go.
Did you see anything?
What did you eat? You're so heavy.
Turn that off, turn that off.
Come on, come on, slowly.
How is it? What's the situation down there?
It's just
an ordinary Qing Dynasty tomb.
If we rule out this looting pit,
could Sanmiao Village
be the excavation site of the black pottery figurines?
It's hard to say.
From the structure,
I'm also inclined to believe the black pottery figurines
are basically consistent
with the pottery figurines found in the Western Han Imperial Mausoleums.
However,
archaeology needs to speak with evidence.
After all, we haven't found
identical black pottery figurines
in any imperial mausoleums.
What if
this is just our subjective speculation?
We might be missing the forest for the trees.
If we're heading in the wrong direction,
we'll get further and further from the truth.
-Chief Zhao, we're leaving.
-Thank you.
-See you.
Thank you for your efforts.
Thank you.
Drive slowly.
Too many cooks spoil the broth.
Too many hands make light work, but too many heads make for confusion.
So many experts,
yet not one has a solid idea.
It's like they didn't say anything at all.
But they're on the right track, aren't they?
They're experts after all. They need to be rigorous.
Eyes wide open, mouth slow to speak.
You think
they're all as clueless as you?
Like hitting a louse with a hammer.
Big show,
no results.
Stay safe, Chief Zhao.
And he's judging me?
He's really angry.
Dacang.
Is your injury better now?
It doesn't hurt anymore?
It's nothing, really.
When the tomb raider hit me with that shovel, his hand was already weak.
-Good for you.
-I was planning to...
Pretend to be sick for a couple of days
to make my master feel sorry for me.
Instead, I got disciplined
and have to write a self-criticism.
The lead in Sanmiao Village has gone cold again.
Yeah.
Looks like we can only start with King Hua now.
Well,
I'll go back now
and do a surprise inspection.
Alright.
Okay.
I'll go first.
Captain Qi.
-Captain Qi.
What's going on with you guys?
Haven't left yet?
Right.
We have something we'd like to discuss with you.
You see,
it's difficult to find a needle in the sea.
Why don't we focus on the needle itself?
What do you think?
What do you mean?
We want to take a look at the black pottery figurines.
Each of these black pottery figurines...
Has a slightly different shade of black.
Is that all?
Well,
it's been almost half an hour.
I've risked making a mistake,
and this is the conclusion you gave me?
Has a different shade of black?
I suggest we start the investigation from the 11 Western Han Mausoleums.
11 Western Han Mausoleums?
Do you know how big they are?
I only have one month.
Experts,
the museum is closing. The tour is over.
Go back to your studies.
Captain Qi, Captain Qi, wait a moment.
Can I share my opinion?
I've made a visual assessment.
Based on the appearances,
the materials,
and the manufacturing technique of these pottery figurines,
they should be from the mid-Western Han period.
As for why they're black...
I haven't found an answer yet.
You all have X-ray vision in those eye sockets of yours?
Visual assessment?
Visual assessment can indeed have errors,
but with current technology,
thermoluminescence testing
can minimize these errors.
Move along, move along.
Stop looking, stop looking.
Stop looking, stop looking, stop looking.
What's going on? Why are they arresting people everywhere lately?
Well.
This man really doesn't look like a good person.
What's going on?
Who knows?
Why are they suddenly targeting the South Market?
They've caught quite a few people these days.
What kind of people did they catch?
They're all tomb raiders.
How do they end up in the South Market to catch these tomb raiders?
Who knows?
It looks like a big deal.
The waters in the South Market are murky.
Every issue starts with us.
[Busy Shop for Sale]
[Xisong Pavilion]
Mr. Wu.
Mu.
What brings you here?
There's nothing here
for you
to conduct an appraisal.
Why are you planning to sell the shop?
Can't do it anymore.
Are you afraid the police will investigate wrongly
and come to your door?
Don't joke around.
I'm running a legitimate business.
If I'm upright, I don't fear shadows.
You've almost run your business in Shang County.
Let's talk business.
How much are you planning to sell it for?
350 thousand.
Can it be lower?
Well...
You want to buy it?
I can't afford it.
I'm asking on behalf of a relative.
No wonder.
We're neighbors.
And you introduced this.
How about this?
I'll lower the price by 10 thousand.
Thank you, thank you.
Mr. Wu,
everyone calls you the source.
Do you know why the police are targeting the South Market?
If business really can't be done,
I guess my relative won't dare to take over the shop.
I heard
it's about the pit.
The police are looking for someone called, called...
Someone called King Hua.
He's from Guyue, not much related to us.
It'll be clear once the case is solved.
Alright, that's it.
I'll go back tonight and tell my relative.
Alright, alright, alright.
I'm leaving.
Alright, alright.
Take care.
Hu.
Sheng.
Newly unearthed?
This is a bronze square wine vessel with beast face patterns.
These two tripods also have beast face patterns.
This is a jade handle with phoenix bird patterns made of green jade.
These are all from the early Western Zhou period.
Where did Hu dig the pit?
You're not going into the pit.
Why worry about it?
Show us how much these are worth.
Give us an estimate.
This amount.
100 thousand?
Add another zero.
Sheng,
who will you sell these artifacts to?
Is it still King Hua?
Why are you suddenly interested in selling the artifacts?
Do you have any ideas?
No ideas.
Haven't you heard?
Many people have been arrested in the South Market.
When did that happen?
You haven't caught wind of it at all?
Should I have?
I'm busy with my company affairs all day.
I don't have time to worry about such things.
What's it all about anyway?
I heard the police are looking for King Hua.
Hu, do you know about this?
I-I-I only deal with underground matters.
I don't know about what's happening above ground.
Whatever it is,
I think you'd better lie low for a while.
Wait until this bad wind blows over before selling them.
As long as we don't leak anything ourselves,
no ill wind can touch us.
Don't you agree?
Right.
That's right.
Alright, that's it then.
I'll be going now.
Hu,
you've been busy all night too.
Go home and get some sleep.
Yeah.
I'll head back then, Sheng.
What?
What if this backstabber
is really your brother-in-law?
Are you really going to chop off his hand?
Go get me a bowl of oil-splashed noodles.
Hurry up.
I don't believe it.
Six Dots.
-It's a win!
Wow, a winning tile!
And it's a Multi-player Ron.
Come on, come on.
Pay up quickly, pay up quickly, come on.
I'll owe it for now.
We'll settle it in the next round.
Why do you do this again?
You already owe quite a bit.
The rule we set is to settle after each round.
If you do this again,
it won't be fun anymore.
Just one more round on credit.
Just one more round.
Xiaowu,
isn't that your wife and kid?
Look where she's going with the luggage and the kid.
Honey.
Where are you going?
It's none of your business.
You're my wife.
How can it not be my business?
Where's the 5,000 yuan I put in the wardrobe?
Yan Xiaowu,
how much do you think our family has?
You gamble like this every day.
Have you ever thought about me and the kid?
I just wanted to make more money.
I can't live like this anymore.
I want a divorce.
Honey.
Honey. Honey.
I-I'm begging you.
I'm begging you.
For the sake of our kid.
Captain Qi.
What?
You've got panda eyes from staying up.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
Oh, right.
They've basically confessed everything here.
I asked around.
These thieves are quite clever.
They only confessed to recent crimes.
They didn't mention anything from the past.
That's why they're called thieves.
Is there anything useful?
No.
They said they didn't know anything about the black pottery figurines.
They don't even recognize King Hua.
Quickly interrogate those people caught in the black market.
Right.
The tomb raider who hit me with a shovel,
bring him over.
It's not an informal interrogation.
Just a chat.
Alright.
It's mealtime.
But I'm really too busy.
I can only work overtime.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
You dug quite a few pits, didn't you?
I didn't.
Eat.
Captain Qi.
I-I didn't mean to.
W-What do you plan to do with me?
Why would I do with you?
This is my workplace.
I'm just doing business according to official principles.
That little grudge
isn't worth my time.
Eat up.
Just don't try to fool me.
Have you heard?
There's a batch of black pottery figurines
intercepted during an overseas auction.
What black pottery figurines?
You don't know yet?
How much is this candlestick?
Zhang, do you think the arrests in the South Market...
-Should be related to this matter?
-Five hundred.
I don't know.
This candlestick is part of a pair.
The other one is in my car.
Do you want to see it?
Let's take a look.
Okay.
Let's go.
Alright.
Who told you to come looking for me?
You even dare to come to the South Market?
There are too many people and prying eyes here.
If Liu's people see us,
neither of us will make it out alive.
Brother,
it can't be that bad, can it?
I'm a new face.
No one knows me.
Had life not been so unbearable,
I wouldn't have come at all.
What happened?
My wife wants to divorce me.
You've gambled again?
Brother, let's do it one more time.
You couldn't have picked a worse time.
Things are already in chaos.
What's troubling you?
That batch of black pottery figurines is in trouble.
What?
What happened?
I sold that batch of goods
to someone called King Hua.
The police are looking for him.
Have they found him?
If they had found him,
would we still be talking here?
Right.
Look what I asked.
Liu
has started to suspect me.
He just dug up some artifacts in a pit.
I guess he'll still sell them to King Hua.
Once they meet,
if Liu applies some pressure,
King Hua will definitely rat me out.
Wait,
so what if he rats you out?
You're his brother-in-law.
He wouldn't dare to do anything to you, would he?
Brother-in-law?
His uncle once took away a pit from him.
He had someone chop off his uncle's arm.
What?
So brutal.
Brother,
why don't we put some pressure on King Hua first?
Easier said than done.
This guy is very slippery.
He uses each phone number only once.
It's impossible to contact him.
Then we're at a dead end.
Just 10 thousand yuan,
what good did it really do?
Xiaowu,
we've been dealt a bad hand our whole lives.
Isn't the grave robbing just our way of not accepting our fate?
Without seeing the last card,
we can't determine the winner.
Let's split up.
You keep an eye on Liu.
I'll find a way to locate King Hua.
We absolutely can't let them meet.
No problem.
King Hua you mentioned,
his name must have been inspired by Guyue.
How do you know?
Those from Guyue are usually receivers.
Those receivers are all very sneaky.
What's that idiom called?
Something about rabbits and burrows?
A crafty rabbit has three burrows.
Yes, yes, yes. A crafty rabbit has three burrows.
You cultured person is really something else.
I just heard it
from a tomb-raiding organizer.
According to him, those people don't stay in hotels when they come to Qinchuan.
They specifically choose small inns in urban villages.
And they frequently change locations.
That's right.
Those places are a mixed bag.
Hiding in plain sight.
Good for hiding.
You're indeed
smart.
It's not only good for hiding
but also convenient for escaping if anything happens.
If you have his photo,
check a few urban village inns,
and you might just find that person.
Tomb Raider,
you're the smart one.
So young
and so clever.
You must stay on the right path in the future.
If you want to eat roujiamo again, it's on me.
Can you tell me
the name of that organizer
you mentioned earlier?
Captain Qi.
Du!
What's up, Captain Qi?
Find this tomb-raiding organizer
to draw a portrait of King Hua,
then confirm it with the Suizhou police.
Alright, quickly.
[Jililai Hotel]
This person looks familiar.
He stayed here before.
He seemed to have a Guyue accent.
Do you have his registration information?
Yes, yes, yes.
Mu,
that Liu guy has left his home.
He's carrying a bag.
That bag looks big and heavy.
It must contain those artifacts.
Quickly follow him.
I'm on my way.
Keep me updated on his location.
He's heading towards the East Gate now.
Got it.
Brother, he just passed Chrysanthemum Lane, and he's heading towards Xiama Bridge.
Brother,
he's now heading towards Luyuan Street.
Don't follow too closely.
Make sure you're not spotted.
Xiaowu.
I followed him to a place in the alley of Xiama Bridge called...
Liang's Hotel.
So, they're made of bronze?
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Do you know the police are watching you?
I don't.
You're such an idiot.
I don't care who you're doing business with,
but what I hate most
is those who betray their own.
Who gave you those black pottery figurines?
Just give me a name.
Mr. Liu,
you know the rules of the trade.
I can't betray others.
Brother.
Xiaowu.
I'm afraid I won't make it in time.
What?
Well,
let me give you a tip.
Go and find out
who set the rules in Qinchuan.
I am the rules.
I'm not asking for your opinion.
I'm telling you.
If you speak up today,
you can take these goods.
If you don't,
see if you can leave Qinchuan.