[The Lost National Treasure]
[Episode 8]
Why didn't you listen to me?
Guang, you scared me.
I woke up early.
So I thought
I could help you with something.
By the way.
Guang.
Here's the deposit
you left at the front desk.
I spent a bit buying groceries.
You've already checked out of the room.
So where will you stay?
I asked around.
The hostel charges 80 yuan a night.
Too expensive.
I noticed you have
a spare kitchen in your yard.
I've already cleaned it up.
If you don't mind,
I can sleep there.
Guang.
Take this 5,000 yuan for now.
You can either go back to study
or stay in Qinchuan to find a job.
It's up to you.
Guang.
Did I do something wrong?
No.
The work here will get your clothes dirty.
It's not suitable for you.
Besides, it's not proper
for a man and woman to be alone.
If word gets back to our hometown,
it won't be good for you.
I don't care.
And I'm not afraid of getting dirty.
Guang.
I beg you.
If you kick me out,
I'll have nowhere to go.
Stop talking nonsense.
Where there's money, there's a way.
If you run out of money, come back to me.
Guang.
I'll tell you the truth.
I was sold by
Wang Huifang from our village
to a salon at the train station.
I thought I was going to
learn hairdressing,
but it turned out
to be that kind of dirty place.
I did everything I could to run away.
They're definitely
looking for me.
I can't stay in Qinchuan alone.
Don't cry.
So,
hurry back to your hometown.
The days after going back home,
I can see what's ahead.
Work at the shoe factory,
pay for my brother's education
and marry anyone.
That's how people
in the village have lived for generations.
I'm not willing to live like that.
What's there to be unwilling about?
You've already come out, haven't you?
I can do any job.
I can learn what I don't know how to do.
I promise I'll listen to you.
Why do you have to stick with me?
Because you're a good person.
I'm not a good person.
Back in the village, you treated me well.
If you're not a good person,
then who is a good person?
You just said
you'll listen to whatever I say.
Then take this money
and find a job in Qinchuan.
Once you've found one, move there quickly.
The hostel's too expensive.
I'll sleep in the kitchen...
You just said you'd listen to me.
Also,
don't come to this place
when you have nothing to do.
Why?
What?
Because
I
like peace and quiet now.
Since when did you like being alone?
W-Why do you have so many questions?
The food's getting cold.
I'll warm it up for you.
Tang!
Captain Yang's here.
Where's the director?
He didn't sleep last night.
He's exhausted.
He went to take a nap.
As soon as I heard that voice,
I knew it was you.
What's up? Does anything happen?
You're exhausted.
I was just about to ask you something.
There's been nothing
going on recently, right?
I would have told you if there was.
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
It's just that
I'm exhausted.
I'm worn out.
Thank you for your hard work.
Captain Yang.
The motorcycle you applied for me.
It has broken down 3 times in 6 months.
Captain Yang.
Please apply for
another one for our station.
There are 4 of us at the station,
but we only have 1 motorcycle.
That's not enough.
Every time I come to your station,
I get nervous.
First, it was a bicycle,
now it's a motorcycle.
After getting equipment,
you want more staff.
Even if my reputation isn't worth much,
I can't keep begging
the leaders every day.
But it's all for public business,
isn't it?
So you know it's for public business.
Then why did you run away
when Yan Shoucun called you over?
What? He complained about me.
Of course.
Listen to me.
He rushed us over there,
saying the dog barked
and there were tomb raiders.
When we got there,
he knew nothing about it.
So you didn't check around?
That's a false report.
I can't indulge him.
He is stubborn.
I think
he should quit being
a cultural relic protection volunteer.
You think being a cultural relic
protection volunteer is good?
The yearly allowance is
only a few hundred.
Why should he
be guarding it day and night?
Ever since Professor Zan
had that incident,
Yan Shoucun has been living in the fields,
just him and his dog, for all these years.
Captain Yang,
I know that he's righteous.
But I have my own difficulties.
We're already short-staffed.
Yin Village is far from
the cultural protection area.
I have to patrol a huge area
just for him.
You see, you can't solve
the staffing issue.
For cultural relic protection volunteers,
can you help us recruit a few more?
Got it.
Okay.
Captain Qi. Shilin.
Why are you carrying luggage to a wedding?
Work's done for now.
I want to take a break.
Ms. Luo, let me help you.
It's fine. Hello.
Why haven't you left?
I haven't. I was waiting for you.
Waiting for me?
I need to talk to you.
Then say it.
I can't.
It's a private matter.
I can only tell you.
It's fine, you two talk.
Talk later.
We're going to the wedding.
You should go back now.
But...
Captain Qi.
How's Yin Village?
I heard there were
a few more groups of tomb raiders.
Yes.
Some were caught,
but some are still at large.
What's under Yin Village?
We've discussed it.
Director Zhang thought
we should check the area
around Yin Village,
to see if there are any relics.
And asked me to take some time
for a field survey.
But, I'm so busy
every day.
I don't even have time
to visit Yin Village.
Yes, I know you're really busy.
I heard that in your institute,
a worker's family follows her husband
around every day to get pregnant.
Wherever her husband goes, she goes.
Who is it?
Who knows?
Wait, wait.
Captain Qi.
You still have a lot to do at the station,
but you keep gossiping and teasing me.
I'm too busy.
Why hasn't she gotten pregnant yet?
You...
Never mind.
I'll handle the Yin Village matter
for you.
I'm on vacation anyway.
Uncle.
It's so lively.
It's really lively.
Dacang, you're here.
Eat peanuts.
Thank you, thank you.
Uncle Youliang.
A grandson
has made him really proud.
Look at this big 100-day banquet.
It must cost a lot.
It's not easy
to change people's minds around here.
Exactly.
It's even grander than your wedding.
That's for sure.
Hello.
Good, this is fine.
Who's playing this?
It sounds awful.
Probably my brother-in-law.
It's terrible.
Dacang, you're back.
Aunt.
So much food.
It's all food.
Uncle.
Dacang's here.
You take care of him.
Grandpa. Aunt.
I was wondering
who was playing that horrible sound.
You're still alive?
Fang Kun.
You idiot, why didn't
you tell me you were back?
Are you trying to do magic?
Ms. Luo.
Long time no see.
Why so formal?
We've worked together for so long,
don't we get a hug?
Since when did you pick up this habit?
I can't eat anymore.
You've changed.
How have I changed?
You've gotten thinner
and tanner.
Seems like you've gotten a little older.
You're the one getting older.
Don't you dare to say that again.
Captain Qi.
Do these two look like fighting chickens?
They start pecking each other
as soon as they meet.
Grandpa.
Do you remember me?
Of course.
Even though I may have
poor eyesight and hearing,
my mind is still sharp.
Since our village discovered
the black pottery figurine,
you three have been staying here.
Always either
looking for old photos
or searching for looting pits.
If Zan knew you three
had become successful,
he'd be very proud.
Alright.
How many people have arrived?
Chief Qi, everyone
from the village is here.
Alright, alright.
See the baby.
So cute.
Sit down. The banquet will start soon.
The banquet is about to start.
Here.
Take a look at my grandson.
Is everyone here?
Yes, everyone's here.
Let's get ready to start the banquet...
How can you start without me?
You think I won't start the banquet
without you?
You're still bringing the dog?
Hurry up, find a seat.
Come on, hurry up.
Kun, why're you back?
Just got here.
Move your dog away.
Don't let it hurt my baby.
I'll sit here, I'll sit here.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, everyone, for coming
to my grandson's 100-day banquet.
I've prepared eight cold
and eight hot dishes.
Let's begin the banquet.
Come on, come on, Uncle Shoucun.
Come on, come on.
Eat more, eat more.
Aunt, enjoy your meal.
You eat, Uncle, you eat.
Delicious, it's very delicious.
You are so thin.
And you haven't cut your hair.
Look at your lips.
Eat more meat and get some nutrition.
I heard that
Xiaoxue has given birth.
Is it okay for you to come back now?
Bai and the others
are taking care of her over there.
It's fine.
What do you want to eat?
Heizui's grown so big.
It's been years since I've seen him.
I remember Captain Luo
used to be afraid of dogs.
Now you are crazy about them.
People change.
Now the dogs are afraid of her.
Captain Luo is decisive and authoritative
at the construction site.
Right, Heizui.
In my memory,
Captain Luo wasn't exactly gentle.
But now, she is forceful in her actions
and sharp with her words.
I wasn't gentle?
That's how you felt it.
Because I only treated you like that.
Alright.
Come, come.
Dacang.
Don't rush off.
These past few nights,
Heizui's been barking a lot.
The tomb raiders have been showing up
on the site every other day.
Even more often than the people from
Cultural Relics Management Office.
Are you going to do
something about it or not?
Of course I will.
It's the peak season for tomb raiding.
I know.
Well, Uncle.
Keep an eye out for me.
Let me know immediately
if anything happens.
One more thing.
We need more
cultural relic protection volunteers.
Uncle Shoucun can't handle it all
on his own.
Uncle Youliang.
By the way,
I need to keep doing field survey
in Yin Village for a few more days.
Can I stay at your place a bit longer?
Would that be okay?
Same as before.
I'll pay for food and lodging.
What are you surveying for?
Uncle.
You know how our village
keeps attracting tomb raiders.
Our director
wanted us to go over the whole village
to see what exactly is there.
I've got something else going on.
So Luo Qing will do the visits for me.
What will you do after the survey is done?
If there's a high preservation value
or serious damage,
I can apply for
more relics protection funding.
Alright, I support that.
What are you doing?
Be careful not to fall.
Last year during spring irrigation,
a few families found
their land wasn't absorbing water.
Turned out the place
was riddled with looting pits.
Those fools have ruined our land
by digging up graves.
Here's the thing.
There are two empty rooms at home.
I'll have your aunt clean them up.
You can stay there.
Great, thanks. Uncle.
Then I won't see you off.
You can head back.
Yeah, go back.
Bye, Uncle.
Take care.
We're leaving, Uncle.
We're leaving.
Congratulations, congratulations.
Dacang, you'll handle it.
I'll take care of it.
Hello?
What happened?
On my way.
Look, there's another looting pit.
You're totally drunk.
Professor Guo, come with me.
No problem.
The situation is urgent.
I can't take care of you two.
Alright.
Right. Kun, see Luo Qing off.
Give me my suitcase.
Okay.
Alright.
Be careful.
He drank too much.
Slow down.
You just hanging out here?
Where are you going?
None of your business.
Where are you staying?
Not telling you.
If you don't tell me,
how can I take you home?
So don't bother.
Got someone at home
you don't want me to see?
What's wrong with you?
I heard Hou Yuelai still hasn't
given up on you all these years.
You two…
Didn't spark anything?
You must've been in the desert too long.
You've become so gossiping.
Just caring about an old friend.
You stayed in Qinchuan back then,
because of Hou Yuelai, didn't you?
It was for you.
What, scared?
You serious?
What do you think? Nutcase.
If it really was for me,
I might have to go cry it out.
Cry?
Go ahead, cry for me right now.
Alright, so where
are you actually staying?
At the Ms. Zan's house.
Okay. Then tell her
I'll drop by sometime
to visit her and Mr. Zan.
[Fengjiapo Village]
What happened?
You're here.
Captain Yang.
During a routine patrol,
the cultural relic conservator
discovered a large empty area.
It was very strange.
So they took a closer look.
The surface was covered
with a layer of fresh dirt.
When he dug down,
it turned out to be a looting pit.
I'll go down and take a look.
It's clearly new.
Alright.
Careful.
– Pull.
– Slow down.
Come up.
Easy, easy.
Okay.
How is it?
It appears to be a tomb
from the Sui and Tang dynasties.
Already completely emptied.
I'll report it to the bureau right away.
See if we can do a salvage excavation.
Thanks.
Go quick.
Look here.
This dirt looks freshly dug.
Yeah.
You can tell it's all new.
Captain Qi.
This spot is really close to the village.
Someone might have heard the explosion.
I think we should gather the villagers
and ask around in a meeting.
What do you think?
Yeah, good idea.
Everyone.
Please come to the village square.
Everyone, come to
the village square for a meeting.
Be quiet, folks.
Listen to the folks from
the Cultural Heritage Bureau.
Everyone,
has anyone heard
any strange noises recently?
Like an explosion.
Similar to the sound of gunfire.
Whose home is closest to the south side?
Uncle.
Isn't your place nearby?
Yeah.
Bro.
His place is pretty close.
Did you hear anything?
Didn't hear anything.
Exactly.
Bro.
Nothing at all.
What time do you usually
sleep and wake up?
I go to bed around eight or nine at night.
Get up around five or six in the morning.
Seen any strangers?
No.
You didn't even think about it.
Let me ask you.
Within the past two weeks...
Nope.
Haven't seen anyone.
You're all so quick to answer now.
I haven't even finished asking.
You have an answer
without even thinking about it.
I really haven't seen any strangers.
Hello?
Anyone home?
Why are you all here?
Can we come in for some water?
Of course, come on in.
Come in, have a seat.
Come inside, come in.
Sister-in-law.
What a coincidence.
Why are you just standing there?
Pour some water.
Let me do it.
Have a seat.
Your courtyard here
is quite far from
other villagers, isn't it?
This is an old house.
I never moved.
Here, have some water.
Don't be polite.
No, thanks, I'm good.
No, really. Thanks.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Honestly.
You know.
They said your place
is kind of close to that looting pit.
I didn't think it'd be this close.
And only your family is here.
No one else could've heard anything.
Forget explosions,
even if tomb raiders were whispering,
you'd probably hear it clear.
Right?
I can't even think of an excuse for you.
You don't even know how to lie.
With the location of  your house,
how could you not hear it?
What? Are you one of the tomb raiders?
No, no, no, no way.
I'm an honest person.
Never done anything illegal.
That's true.
Sister-in-law, listen.
Don't be nervous.
Just tell the truth.
We've already figured it out.
We know everything.
If you ask me,
it's not that serious.
But look at your husband's attitude.
If you knew something
and didn't report it,
then it'll become very serious.
I'll tell you.
Did you hear anything?
Yeah, sounded like a gunshot.
Sleep, sleep, sleep, whatever.
Who's that?
I'll go check it out.
But who's gonna refuse it?
I know it's dirty money.
We don't dare to spend it.
You don't dare to spend it,
but you dare to take it?
Ding Yan.
Check with the Chief
and ask if there are any nearby cameras.
Alright.
When did this happen?
A few nights ago.
Did you see the person clearly?
I went outside.
But they were already gone.
If anything else happens,
call me.
Call me right away.
Officer.
Do you think
they'll come back for revenge?
What's there to be afraid of?
I'm from the Cultural Heritage Bureau.
This is from the Public Security Bureau.
We're here to protect you.
Don't talk to outsiders about
everything that happened today.
If it affects the investigation,
you'll be legally responsible.
I won't say anything.
If anything happens, call right away.
Don't be scared.
Okay.
Take care.
[Qinchuan Relics Inspection Team]
[Qinchuan Municipal
Cultural Heritage Bureau]
We asked the traffic police
to help us check.
The nearest camera to the village
is on the provincial road.
It's a high-traffic area.
Most of them are vans
without license plates.
So there's really no way to trace it.
At the time,
if someone had reported it,
we would've caught them red-handed.
But,
honestly.
The problem is
our inspection frequency is too low.
And the villagers' awareness
of heritage protection is weak.
Captain Qi.
Are you saying
we didn't do our job properly?
I'm not the type
to say sweet things.
That's exactly what I mean.
We're not even doing the basics enough.
Not doing enough?
We've been working all year
without taking any time off.
Ask everyone here.
Who's had a day off on a Sunday?
I didn't even go back
when my wife gave birth last year.
Daytime's for fieldwork.
Nighttime's for patrols.
How many of us
have gotten a full night's sleep?
Here's the thing, Captain Qi.
It's just a few of us
in this Inspection Team.
There are hundreds of
heritage protection units.
If we didn't eat or drink all year,
we still couldn't finish it all.
Are you done complaining?
What's there to complain about?
Now that the tomb was looted.
What does that mean?
It shows that we haven't
done our job properly.
Heritage protection
is all about prevention.
How do we prevent it?
Mobilize the masses.
Mobilizing the masses
to protect is the only way
to stop the tomb raiders.
I've been applying to
the higher-ups for years
to strengthen
the cultural relic conservator program
and to increase
the intensity and scope of publicity.
I know it's not something
that happens overnight.
But,
that's not an excuse
for not doing your job properly.
Captain Qi.
I have a request.
You know we're
an administrative law enforcement agency.
We can't really deter tomb raiders.
Next time,
could we take a joint law enforcement?
That's a great idea.
I've been thinking about it too.
Our two departments
have always worked together.
But this requires an official application.
Alright.
One more thing,
I need your help with
some publicity work
to promote the cultural relic
protection volunteer program.
Our first stop will be in Yin Village.
Protect cultural relics.
Guard our beautiful home.
It starts with me.
Start from childhood.
Fellow villagers.
Protect cultural relics.
Guard our beautiful home.
Thousand-year-old cultural relics
are profound and extensive.
Loved by future generations.
Passed down through generations.
Knock.
What?
Scared?
We're already here.
Oh, it's you two.
Ms. Zan.
Why didn't you call us in advance?
We didn't want to disturb you.
It's early.
Am I Acalanatha?
Come on in.
You're here.
Don't bother changing shoes.
No need to change.
You brought so much.
Give it to me.
Come in.
Fang Kun.
What are your plans
now that you're back?
Take a break.
So, you're
going back?
You got to
let the past be past.
All these years,
you shut yourself up in Yusai,
refusing to come back.
I understand
you.
If I hadn't gone back
to the village to
call people that night...
If I had caught
the tomb raiders with Mr. Zan...
This isn't your fault.
Let it go.
It's time to let it go.
Ms. Zan.
I've got something I need your help with.
Mr. Zan did some exploration
on the plain before.
I'd like to borrow his work notes.
Alright.
I'll get them for you.
Why do you need his notes?
I'm planning to do a field survey
on the plain.
It hasn't changed at all, has it?
What changes could there be?
The people haven't changed.
How haven't they changed?
Some people just walk faster now.
Wait.
Fang Kun's back.
Let's talk it over first.
Who's leading the field survey this time?
Me.
Why you?
Some people have no sense of
organization or discipline.
He might just mess things up
and leave me to clean up.
So from now on,
all instructions will come from me.
Why are you still seeing people
with the same old perspective?
I've been gone for a few years,
and you think I haven't changed at all?
Who was it then?
Ran off, leaving the whole team behind.
Went deep into the desert.
What do you mean?
You're asking Bai about me?
You can't forget me, huh?
You really haven't changed at all.
Stop arguing, stop arguing.
-Listen to me.
-Ms. Luo.
-This field survey.
We will follow Luo Qing’s instructions.
Ms. Luo.
Hello, hello.
Bai, what are you doing here?
Mr. Jiang told me you're here.
So I came over.
Can I join you?
W-we're not here for fun or vacation.
We're here to work.
I know,
I've done my homework on
Yin Village, Dou Mausoleum,
South Mausoleum and Zi Mausoleum.
I've read the county records and maps.
Look.
Bai, your internship is over.
This is my personal route now.
I understand.
But I really want to be with you.
I've loved Chinese culture
since I was little,
interning with you
just made me more certain to do this.
Please, can you
give me a chance to learn?
Sure, no problem.
Really? Thanks, bro!
No need to thank me.
Just call me Bai.
I'm Fang Kun.
Alright, Kun.
Fang.
-Uncle.
Why are you here too?
Hello.
Why are there more people?
We'll need to rearrange
the accommodations.
Charge whatever is needed.
Well...
Come, come, come.
Come in, come in.
What's going on?
You're usually so sharp.
Why can't you
figure this out?
What?
You really think Bai's here
for an internship?
So?
Well.
Y-You're paving the way for him.
Chief.
-What's wrong?
-Chief.
Hurry, go check
the foundation of the wellhouse.
They've dug something up.
What is it?
I don't know either.
You go take a look.
What kind of foundation is it?
There are a lot of cherry trees
being planted in the village now.
They drilled a well
for irrigation.
What is in the foundation?
I can't really say.
I just dug a bit but couldn't go further.
It felt like I hit something hard.
Hard?
What did you dig up?
Take a look.
What is this?
Just a few hard things.
It's nothing, it's nothing.
Keep digging.
Okay, everyone, keep digging.
Wait, wait a second.
What's up?
This looks like river pebbles.
How could there be river pebbles here?
What river pebbles?
It's fine, it's fine.
Keep going, keep going.
Wait, wait. Come here.
Guo.
Take a picture
and show it to Director Zhang.
Be careful.
What are you doing?
I'm checking the coordinates.
Give me that locator. Did you bring it?
Yes, yes, I brought it.
Here's the notebook.
Bai.
Didn't you do
a lot of work on this already?
Let me ask you.
Which river is closest to Yin Village?
The Zishui River.
It's about five kilometers away.
Are there river pebbles
in the Zishui River?
It doesn't seem to be
mentioned in the literature.
Okay, let me tell you.
Literature
is just a reference, not the whole truth.
We're in the downstream
of the Zishui River.
Downstream areas usually
have river pebbles.
It's common knowledge.
Got it?
Okay.
Chief.
Will we dig up some treasure?
Uncle.
Let's study this for a couple of days.
Can you stop the work for now?
We can't stop.
We've already invested
a lot of money into this.
We can't delay the work.
Those river pebbles don't matter.
There are all kinds of
strange things out here.
You're saying anything
that's dug up is a cultural relic?
Impossible.
Uncle, we wouldn't dare.
If you dig up some ruins down there,
and it gets destroyed.
The consequences could be huge.
Alright, alright, let's stop for two days,
But you have to figure this out quickly.
Okay, okay.
We can't delay the schedule.
Alright, alright,
Get this figured out fast.
[Beijing]
At a typical auction,
this is how
they display porcelain.
Small cabinets
with lights shining on them.
It looks beautiful.
It doesn't work
in our place.
In our small town,
we just stretch some wire,
put some clips on it,
and hang the paintings.
Different places, different methods.
This is the capital.
You really have to
come often to auctions.
Auctions all around the world
are pretty much the same.
That's right, they're all like this.
Look, it's just like this.
Let's sit over there, it's empty.
Sit.
Mr. Zhao.
You're here.
It's been so long
since we last saw each other.
Alright, alright.
This is...
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good morning.
Zhao Youlin.
This is our first item
for today's auction.
No. 7201.
A Famille Rose "Hundred Flowers" Cup
from the Qianlong Emperor period
of the Qing Dynasty.
The starting price is
30,000 yuan.
Anyone for 30,000?
30,000.
I see No.872 wants it.
35,000.
No.868 makes it 35,000.
Anyone for 40,000?
Bid from the proxy bidder, 40,000.
45,900. Let's back in the hall.
Now No.900 mkaes it 45,000.
50,000.
No.892 makes it 50,000.
55,000, anyone?
There, No. 878.
Our proxy bidder raised it to 55,000.
60,000.
60,000, anyone?
I see No.868.
Thank you, 60,000.
60,000.
65,000.
70,000.
Any bids for 70,000?
Proxy bidder, 70,000.
70,000.
75,000.
80,000.
Anyone for 80,000?
There, No. 871.
No.896.
85,000.
[Beijing Zhongjia's Four
Seasons 5th Auction]
90,000, right?
90,000.
The proxy bidder raised it to 90,000.
100,000.
No868, 100,000.
Anyone for 110,000?
There, No. 900, 110,000.
Anyone for 120,000?
Let me flatter him.
120,000.
Any more bids?
Mr. Zhao.
Aren't you going to place a bid?
First time.
120,000.
Don't even bother with cheap items.
Second time.
120,000.
Last call.
Sold!
Congratulations to No. 877!
Alright.
The second item is
Blue-and-White
"Seawater Dragon and Nine Dragons" Vase
from the Jiaqing Emperor period
of the Qing Dynasty.
The starting price is
1 million yuan.
Any bids?