70 dollars for a full body massage,
and 50 dollars for only the feet.
I'm Korean.
(Humans is unfair,
but the deities are just.)
Don't move.
Whenever I came home, there was
always something on the floor.
So I got suspicious.
It's a box cutter.
I didn't want to use a weapon
like a gentleman though.
Have you heard of this expression?
"A blind man is reckless."
I'm that blind man.
How did you know the laptop was
the only valuable thing here?
No!
No! Not the laptop!
Blood.
Sir, could you just take my eyes
instead of the laptop?
I'm just a blind man.
I can't buy a laptop to my family,
but at least I shouldn't
let it be stolen, sir!
Hi-Fi.
Yes, did you call me?
Can you...
No!
Make a call to Jeong Gal...
"Jeong Gal" is not found
in your contact list.
It's not "Jeong Gal".
It's "Jeong Gal Hee"!
I'm afraid I have a hearing problem.
Could you say it more clearly?
No...
Call the police!
I will dial the number.
Be careful...
Police emergencies. Hello?
Hello? Please say something.
Hello? Are you okay?
We've got your address.
We'll be right there.
Hey!
I must have lost my mind.
What's wrong with me?
I'll tell him everything
when I go to work tomorrow morning.
Please give me one day.
Where should I start...
and how should I tell him?
Why is there a police car here?
What is going on here?
Sir.
What is this?
There's cash right here...
and he just left without taking it.
He didn't touch anything
in the rooms.
Then he was trying to steal...
just this laptop?
I remember you. From TnT Mobile.
Do you live here?
Yes. What's the matter?
There was a thief.
A thief?
Where is my brother, Jung Hee?
He was taken to the hospital
by ambulance.
He said he was trying to
protect his sister's laptop.
Jung Hee!
There you are.
Would you like a glass of juice?
- Jung Hee?
- Can I have some crackers?
Okay.
You idiot.
Why did you have to hurt yourself
for this dumb laptop?
Did you just hear that?
Human always comes first.
That's humanism.
I saved your laptop's life.
Do you have any idea
how much a VIP room costs?
This laptop doesn't even turn on.
Do you have any idea how much
the hospital bills will be?
Darn capitalism.
Is there a room with six beds?
I'm sorry. This is the only room
we have left.
Is he hurt badly?
He said he bled a lot,
but it turned out he mistook
grape juice for blood.
I got flustered at the moment.
His little toe is slightly cracked,
so we got it splinted.
But his doctor said
he didn't need to wear a cast...
and he could leave tomorrow.
The painting is crooked.
Or is it not?
Hey. Come gather around.
Didn't Gal Hee say,
"Min Ik"...
that day?
- Did you hear that too?
- Yes.
I thought I misheard it
because we were busy.
Come to think of it,
it's really strange.
I have never seen her
wear such an outfit to the office.
Even when we went to a club,
she put on that fuzzy red cardigan.
It's Gal Hee!
Gal Hee, hi.
Myung Jung.
Did you feed the fish?
Yes.
Are you working on
the scrap papers again?
- Yes.
- Hey, Gal Hee.
Yes?
If you ever came to the office
with a vivid red lipstick on,
what would be the reason?
That will never happen.
Then...
What about if you took your
glasses off and wore contacts?
That will never happen either.
Then what about if you
ever call your boss, "Min Ik"?
That will never happen.
Are you asking this...
because you saw
something yesterday...
in the office?
- No!
- Hey.
- Come on!
- We weren't even in the office.
- Don't be ridiculous.
We weren't here, right?
Yes, sir. I'm on my way!
How am I going to face him?
(Director, Do Min Ik)
Don't get nervous.
Let's just act normal.
I'm the same Secretary Jeong
as I was yesterday.
Hello, Director Do.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Something happened at my house.
You didn't eat breakfast, did you?
Here's a blueberry yogurt
and a flat white.
And I bought some sushi takeout...
from Kingdom Hotel,
so you can have it for lunch...
You must really not want
to look at me...
judging by how you
turned your head like that.
No, it's just that I feel like
I'm coming down with a cold.
Your pebbles are over there.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Why?
Are you hoping that there'd be
something wrong?
No, I mean...
If you're okay, then that's fine.
Something happened.
I broke up...
with Veronica Park.
- What about you?
- Pardon?
That date you had...
at the dry sauna
who kept sleeping all day.
I also broke up with him.
Like you said,
he wasn't that great of a guy.
Good job.
- By any chance, Director Do.
- Yes?
If you feel a little down...
and need a buddy
to eat or drink with,
you can always ask me.
I'll go running to you
regardless of...
where I am or what I'm doing.
Why are you suddenly being so nice?
It's making me feel nervous.
Because once I tell Director Gi
about what happened,
this might be the end for us.
I don't need an eating
or drinking buddy,
so go and do your work.
Okay.
I'll hurry up
and get my laptop fixed first.
Why did you suddenly want
to meet me at the office?
I found out that there was
a misunderstanding.
- Director Gi?
- I thought you were behind...
Veronica Park's 100,000 shares,
but I guess it was someone else.
This.
You know what this is right?
(Sangmo Hospital,
Department of Neurology)
"Department of Neurology"?
Is Min Ik ill?
My gosh, I almost fell for that.
Your acting is good enough to win an
award at the Cannes Film Festival.
You and Min Ik know everything
about each other.
How can you not know this?
But then again, it doesn't matter
whether you're acting or not.
Just find out
the name of Min Ik's illness.
If I can use that
to get rid of that punk,
I'll integrate the Media Department
and let you have it all.
My gosh.
(Director Gi Dae Ju)
Hello? Director Gi?
He told me that I can't tell anyone
about his illness.
Just find out
the name of Min Ik's illness.
If I tell him the truth, that will
put Director Do in danger.
Secretary Jeong.
Yes?
By any chance, did Min Ik fail
to recognize me that day...
because he's sick?
No.
He was drunk.
What do you mean?
He never drinks more than
a glass of champagne.
Yes, I know.
You're right. But...
What do I need to say
to make him believe me?
What should I say?
- I like Director Do.
- What?
To be honest,
I met up with him that day
to confess my feelings for him.
You saw my outfit, right?
It was different from usual.
But when I actually met him,
I couldn't bring myself
to say anything.
That's why he got drunk?
Yes, we both kept
pouring drinks for each other...
and ended up
drinking two bottles of soju.
So he eventually got drunk...
and couldn't remember
a single thing about that night.
He couldn't remember
my confession...
and the fact that we went
to the theater to sober up.
Can you please keep it a secret?
He actually likes someone.
So I felt relieved...
when I heard that he couldn't
remember anything.
If he finds out that I confessed
my feelings for him,
he'll obviously feel uncomfortable
working with me.
But I still want to remain
by his side.
Do you like Min Ik that much?
I want to protect him.
If I can't do that as his woman,
I want to do that as his secretary.
Secretary Jeong.
Yes, Director Gi.
If Min Ik ever happens...
to become ill,
you must tell me no matter what.
You and I are the only people...
that can help him
in this entire company.
Okay, sir.
By the way,
can I also ask you a question?
What's your relationship...
with President Park of Cinepark?
I met up with her for work.
President Sim introduced me to her
so we could talk about...
our company's exclusive rights
to Cinepark's contents.
Was that all?
Yes.
Gosh, I hope I did the right thing.
But why did they watch
a late-night movie together...
if they met up for work?
Gosh, I can't get a grasp
of what's going on.
Director Do, where are you going?
Cancel all my schedule for today.
Everything? Why all of a sudden?
Just cancel them all.
You should also go home.
What if he fails to recognize people
while he walks around alone?
Should I go after him?
Hey.
This place is...
Gosh, it's so delicious.
It's not delicious at all.
What?
He pretended to be fine.
It's been hours.
He hasn't had anything
since morning.
Gosh, what if he passes out?
(Chocolate pie)
Who are you?
No, thanks. You can eat it.
I'm okay.
Is she mute?
Okay, ma'am.
Thank you for the food.
What a weird lady.
Is it okay to eat something
from a stranger?
Why would she even watch me eat?
Eat it.
He ate it.
What's with her?
Come to think of it,
all I've had since morning
was a cup of coffee.
My gosh, what?
Hello, Director Do.
Hey, where are you?
Well... I'm home.
That's good. This morning,
you said you'd be my...
drinking and eating buddy
whenever I want.
Is it still valid?
Sure.
I happen to be in your neighborhood.
Can you cook for me?
What?
You know...
you cooked white rice for me
at the hotel before.
I want to eat it.
I don't think you can, right?
Actually, I can cook it for you.
Then...
come to my place as late as you can.
Make sure to come
as late as possible.
Okay.
Why today of all days?
He's here already.
Flowers?
This is my first time
to get flowers from someone.
Don't get me wrong.
It's just wrong to visit
someone's place empty-handed.
And the flower shop was the only...
store that was open
in the neighborhood.
The supermarket is closed already?
Can I come in?
Yes. But...
the house is a little messy.
It's very messy.
Is this how you live?
Actually, a thief
broke in yesterday.
- What?
- Nothing's stolen though.
I mean, there's nothing to steal.
Still, the kitchen is fine.
Let's go to the kitchen. This way.
Okay.
This way.
It's delicious.
I got you your favorite foods.
Why did you want to eat this?
No reason.
I just thought of that day.
The white rice you cooked for me
before the stockholders' meeting.
Try this.
I made it myself.
I guess you've lived here
for a long time.
Yes.
My older brother is blind.
It's not easy for him
to get used to a new place.
Fortunately, we met a good landlord
and have lived here for 10 years...
raising the rents regularly.
How is he a good landlord
when he raises the rents regularly?
I can say he's a good landlord.
Many others asked us to move out
saying the house price would fall...
because he's disabled.
You have a lot of people...
to take care of.
Do you have more rice?
Yes. Sure.
It's good, isn't it?
Did you make this too?
Of course. I made them all.
I'm a pretty good cook.
You're so mean.
Fine.
One more time?
Okay.
You're here.
I went to your office
and heard you were here.
This time,
I found this in my bag.
Gosh, it was in your bag?
I had no idea.
Is he one of the guys
who caught your eye?
One of the actors who caught my eye.
And you have to be in bed
when you talk to actors?
Awesome.
Are you...
being jealous?
I'm asking a question.
He gets happy when I
tell him his pay.
But what should I do
to make you happy?
The bathroom set
came out pretty well.
And the office looks good too.
Which one do you...
prefer?
Have I done something
to deserve to get shot?
Hands in the air.
You're the one who said
you were a bad person...
and turned yourself in.
You're not going to date me anyway.
Does it matter if I'm a bad guy?
Of course it does.
Bad guys are so attractive.
When it comes to being naughty,
I deserve this too.
Who knows?
If you're just as bad as me,
I might take you, Gi Dae Ju,
seriously.
I have a wife,
but I got swayed by another person.
That's infidelity.
I'm going to quit.
I turned a blind eye to
an obvious danger. That's aiding.
Does it answer your question?
Well, that makes you...
deserve a handcuff too.
You can't unlock it?
Oh, my! What should we do?
Secretary Kim! Secretary Kim!
The key!
Did you do this on purpose too?
It was a mistake.
As soon as I see the prop team,
I will fire all of them.
Who told them to make
such well-crafted handcuffs?
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
I'm hungry too.
I want to go to the restroom too.
Ma'am.
Why don't you eat this at least?
The prop team is on their way now
from Namyangju,
but the traffic doesn't seem good.
Yes. Where are you?
No, that's not where I meant.
You said you were hungry.
I'm the president of Cinepark,
Veronica Park.
The Korean movie industry is
in the palm of my hands.
I can't eat such food in a jail!
Then I will eat some.
Here you go.
It's delicious.
I want that too.
The stuffed cucumbers.
Why are you smiling?
I'm sorry if I offended you.
Sometimes, you're like a baby.
A baby?
Baby, as in, baby?
Yes.
It looks like the National Institute
of Korean Language...
has changed the definition
of the word, "baby".
A demon, the ultimate evil,
the weirdo, or crazy witch.
Those are the words people use
when they call me.
Babies are evil.
But...
they cry not because they're bad.
They cry
because they don't feel well.
They don't put on a fake smile.
They smile when they're happy.
So I find babies lovely.
If you really need to go to
the restroom, I can come with you.
- What?
- I'll be standing at the door.
You just need to stretch
your arm a bit...
while you take care of the business.
- It's not totally impossible...
- Hey!
I...
I'm the president of Cinepark,
Veronica Park!
Hey.
It would be nice...
if you could at least
close your ears.
As you probably know, I can't...
close my ears...
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
I can't close my ears
when my arms are stretched.
And I can't stretch my arm
when I'm closing my ears.
So this is
what they call humiliation.
Fine.
Even if I, Veronica Park,
end up wetting myself,
I will try to hold it in
until I can't.
Until the East Sea's water runs dry
What are you doing?
I will sing as loud as possible
so I can't hear anything.
Now, I want you to focus
on your business in there.
I'll focus on
my patriotism out here.
Until the East Sea's water runs dry
And until Mt. Baekdu is worn away
May the deities protect
And preserve our country
So...
Are you...
sleeping alone tonight?
Yes, I guess.
Aren't you scared?
You have to sleep alone
in a house where a thief broke in.
I have been through
even more scary things.
Do you...
want me to stay with you?
What?
No, thanks.
You didn't get much sleep last
night, so you should go home.
Right.
I'm your boss, so I guess it's
a bit weird if I sleepover.
You'll probably feel uncomfortable.
Thank you for the food.
I'll get going.
He's really leaving.
I wish he'd ask one more time.
Are you sure you don't need me?
Don't you come here.
I will kill you.
I have never been treated so well
in my whole life.
Well, it's just that
I'm a bit scared...
to sleep alone. So...
Hey, your sister is a woman...
too.
I have to go.
Sir! Oh, my gosh.
I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
It's been more than two hours
since you left.
By any chance, were you trying
to protect me like a guard dog...
because you got worried
that I might get scared alone?
"Like a dog"? You called me a dog?
No, that's not what I meant.
Yes, it's been a while since I came
to a small town like this.
The air was fresh, and
the night sky was filled with stars.
So I was just taking my dog-walk.
You human being, can go back home.
And don't mind me, the dog!
Well...
Then are you going to continue
to stay here?
Would...
Would you like to go inside?
I'm not sure if you'll be able
to sleep here.
Wouldn't you be better off
sleeping in my brother's room?
In order to guard the house
like a guard dog,
I should sleep in the living room.
I can't sleep inside.
Don't mind me.
You should go inside and sleep.
- Hey, Director Do.
- Yes?
Can I ask you something?
What?
Director Gi is...
your best friend, isn't he?
But why are you hiding your illness
from him?
I'm not hiding it.
Even you, my secretary,
keeps wanting to quit
because it's so hard to work for me.
He's the only friend I have.
How bothered would he be
if he finds out that I'm ill?
Dae Ju is so foolishly nice.
Ever since we were seven,
he'd carry me to the hospital...
even in the middle of a test
if he heard that I'm sick.
If I tell a guy like him
about my illness,
it'll only end up burdening him.
It's not that I want to hide it.
What?
It's nothing.
Anyway, I don't think you should
tell anyone about your illness...
until the final election
of the next company president.
You can't afford to make
any mistakes,
so always take me with you
wherever you go.
Does that mean...
you're not going to quit?
Sleep tight.
Don't go.
Secretary Jeong.
What should I do?
Right now...
Ever since a while ago...
No.
Throughout the entire day,
I kept wanting to call that woman.
Are you not over her yet?
I want to call her right now...
and tell her...
that I miss her,
that I want to meet her,
and that I want to hug her.
But I already promised her...
that I'll forget about her...
after today.
So...
can you please hold my hand...
so that I can pass the night...
without doing anything stupid?
Can you hold my hand as well?
Why do you need me to do that?
Because I also felt the same way.
I wondered all day...
if he'd eaten...
and whether I might've
hurt him or not.
I was worried about him all day.
I wanted to be next to him.
But...
I decided to forget about him,
so I should.
Let's both try to forget.
Hold on tight.
Don't even think about
calling that guy...
who did nothing but sleep all day.
By the way,
aren't you going to help me
fall asleep as well?
What?
You didn't have a problem
singing a lullaby for that guy.
Are you serious?
I just...
want to fall asleep...
without thinking about anything.
Please put me to bed.
Then lie down over here.
This is what my mom
used to sing to me.
I'm not sure if I'll be able
to remember it very well.
Goodnight, my baby
My cute baby
Beautiful roses
Have bloomed around you
Goodnight, my baby
Rest throughout the night
And when the morning comes
- Secretary Jeong?
- Director Do?
It's 9am!
- Let go of my hand.
- Hand? Gosh!
Gosh, let's be calm.
- Secretary Jeong.
- I'm sorry,
but can you please come to my house?
My goodness.
- My pants! Where are my pants?
- I don't know!
- Director Do!
- Where are they?
My pants.
Oh, okay. Where are my socks?
- Your socks?
- Gosh, my socks!
Your socks are over here.
Secretary Jeong,
where are the towels?
They're in the cabinet.
Why does she have this?
Director Do, can you come outside?
Oh, okay.
Secretary Jeong.
What?
Look at this.
Should I drive you to the office?
No, let's go to Yeongdeungpo
Police Station.
The police station?
- You brought it, right?
- Yes.
Will this be okay?
- Sir.
- Hey.
I looked into it, and it's not
an ordinary box cutter.
Then what is it?
It's an auto escape tool.
- An auto escape tool?
- Yes. Look at this.
This part right here is used
to cut the seat belt.
And this on the other side
is used as a hammer.
It's used to shatter the car window
during emergency situations.
Is this the box cutter you saw
on the day of your accident?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Ordinary people normally wouldn't
carry this around.
Drivers and repairmen might
carry these around,
but others would rarely find this
useful enough to carry around.
Come to think of it, I also saw
that somewhere else.
The new driver had it with him.
Back then, I thought it was just
an ordinary box cutter.
No way.
Why? Do you think he's the culprit?
You said you remember
the culprit's face.
Let's think. The suspect revealed
his face to the victim.
And he's back as your driver?
How cheeky is he?
I want to hire him.
We will figure it out once we
have the fingerprints identified.
- Here.
- Okay.
Are there any important documents
in your laptop?
Like customers' personal information
or company confidential.
I don't have such things.
All I have is Director Do's schedule
and work materials.
Oh, right. There was
one strange file though.
- What is it?
- It was...
On the day of the incident,
you picked up a USB stick
from Director Gi Dae Ju's office.
Gi Dae Ju? There you go.
Oh boy. I thought he was
as slippery as an eel.
- And this is it.
- I told you he was strange.
What about Dae Ju?
All his alibis on that day
were incongruous,
so he came to receive
investigation again.
What's the file
you're talking about?
I have a copy of it.
I'll find it and get it to you.
It's not here.
- It's not there?
- This is strange.
I'm sure I put it in here.
Didn't you say
something was written in the file?
"Humans is unfair,
but the deities are just."
"Humans is unfair..."
(Humans is unfair...)
(Humans are unfair,
but the deities are just.)
"Humans are unfair,
but the deities are just."
"It's Henry Wadsworth Longfellow's
famous quote..."
"that means justice will
prevail in the end."
"We should never forget..."
"that those who do injustice
will eventually..."
"be brought to justice"?
What do you think it means?
I should've taken my laptop
to repair immediately.
(It's Henry Wadsworth Longfellow's
famous quote...)
File? What file?
"Humans are unfair,
but the deities are just."
Hey, the deities are
not just at all.
I've got my good looks
and high intelligence all together.
Why are you staring
at me so sharply?
I've never seen
or created such a file.
Then why was that USB
in your office?
I don't know.
Is the file important?
I can't see his face,
but I have to believe him.
If I don't,
no one in this world
would believe him.
Stop drinking.
You might make
a drunk mistake again.
When did I make a drunk mistake?
By the way,
about the woman you like.
Are you still seeing her?
I don't think...
it will end in the past perfect.
We can't do this then.
I guess I should set
Secretary Jeong with someone.
- No.
- Why not?
No. I just don't like it.
Why can't she date anyone
when you're seeing someone?
She has a crush on someone...
and she can't even sleep at night.
And who do you think he is?
Use your brain.
There's a guy. He's a scumbag.
By the way,
did you decide not to quit...
because of me?
I'm preparing a gift for you.
Once it's ready, I'll
make a beautiful exit.
All you need to do
is get a handkerchief.
Director Park?
I just took my only suit
to the cleaners.
You go first. I'll pick up
my suit and be there.
What do you...
think of my face?
My mother told me I should
try to be honest all the time.
Okay. Be honest.
Your eyes are filled with desire.
Your cheeks are full of greed.
And your lips look so wicked...
that I want to slap you on the...
I'm sorry.
I'm supposed to
be in good terms with you,
so I tried putting it
somewhat nicely.
I agree.
But the thing is...
Even so, he called me...
a baby.
There's a guy who says
I'm like a baby.
Can I trust him?
Try to believe in a cult instead.
Did you call me
just to ask a question like that?
Baby's phone ringing.
Is it phone number one?
It's phone number 10.
Director Park Hyun Chul
lost his mother?
Wait.
Director Park?
It means all the employees
of the company will come.
And it also means
my baby is coming too.
I should go to
the department store first.
Why?
To buy...
the world's sexiest mourning dress.
Why? Do you think he's the culprit?
Director Do, what about your suit?
Secretary Jeong will bring it.
- 100 dollars.
- 200 dollars.
300 dollars.
Well done today.
- Well done.
That's a lot.
It's a lie that
the company has no money.
I know.
Even the condolence money
from directors is that huge.
By the way, how come there's
no notice these days?
It's been a while since
we got together last time.
I've been busy.
There will be a notice soon.
Wait a little more, guys.
- Shall we go now?
- Wait, Ms. Lee.
Gal Hee will be there too.
Aren't you going to tell her?
Right.
She should know
what we're up to now.
Chief Director Sim, I'm here.
You're not here yet? Where are you?
You're here already?
I'm coming in now.
Stay calm.
Secretary Jeong will be here soon.
Director Do.
It's me, Secretary Jeong.
Change your clothes first.
What? Something's wrong?
Something's stuck inside.
Why is it you again?
What?
What's wrong with my blood pressure?
I can see.
When I'm with Secretary Jeong,
I can see faces again.
Sir, are you having
the blood pressure problem again?
Dr. Gu said my blood pressure
would rapidly go up...
when I'm nervous or excited.
That's why when I exercise hard
or drink alcohol,
or...
Or what?
When he saw a woman he loved,
he could clearly see her face.
Or...
But when I was with her,
I couldn't, even if I wanted to.
Why does my blood pressure go up
only when I'm with you?
At the door.
It's President Sim Hae Yong.
What's up?
My poor uncle.
Look at your dark circles,
your rough skin,
and all those rashes
next to your nose.
Did you not go to the restroom?
You're good.
- Yes, Ha Ni.
- Jung Su.
I think you should be
hiding for now.
What?
It's here.
Secretary Jeong,
could you wait here for a second?
Sir, where are you...
Hey.
Mr. Do Min Ik?
Who are you?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Veronica Park.
(The Secret Life of My Secretary)
It was definitely him.
I think I should disappear
from the company.
- You...
- I just met a woman.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Veronica Park.
Does your boss have problem
seeing people's faces?
The girl you like is Veronica Park?
I want to be with you.
From now on, you're going to be
the real Veronica.