Episode 17
Will Tae Hee Hyung be okay?
He may feel hurt after unnecessarily going to the airport.
We should stay close by him and take care of him.
Oh, I think he's here. Wait.
Oh, Hyung.
I was waiting to fix dinner.
I'll get it ready, Oppa.
No, no. Let's not do that and go out.
Why don't the three of us have a delicious meal
and a light drink, Hyung?
I want to be alone. You guys leave.
Oh! What in the world. What in the world!
Sara was Geum Ran?
I knew it. Every time I saw pretty women, I didn't like
them. But that wasn't the case with Sara.
It was because she was Geum Ran. She was Geum Ran.
This Geum Ran betrayed me.
How could she fool me like that?!
But isn't it great that she is alive, Mother?!
Kyeong Joo, I can't get in touch
with Geum Ran right now.
She must be traumatized since
her marriage plans were broken.
I heard Han Tae Hee is the Winner Group heir.
Do you think marrying him would be easy?
Han Tae Hee is that great of a person?
Whether he's the Winner Group's heir or not, there was
a huge fuss in the media and on the Internet.
That's when I found out, too.
Yes, Mother.
Your daughter left for overseas today.
Alone?
I think it was because I'm lacking in many ways.
I am sorry.
It's not that I want to hear an apology.
Why did Geum Ran suddenly make that kind of decision?
Geum Ran, don't crumble, no matter what.
Never.
If you are having hard time, I am also here.
Who is it?
Mom. I'm Geum Ran.
Geum Ran.
Oh, my daughter.
You're alive.
Thank you.
Hey! Sa Geum Ran.
Kyeong Joo.
How are you?
While I was pretending to go abroad,
I was just going to go back to our hometown,
so that I can hide in a place that nobody knows.
As I was about to, I heard your voice message.
You don't have to explain anything.
I won't ask you anything.
That's right. Get some rest, Geum Ran.
You've suffered so much, all this time.
I like the fact that I am your friend.
If we go around together, I think I'll walk around
with strength in my shoulders (proudly).
Mom. I am thinking about going back
to our hometown tomorrow.
I'll go with you.
Let's stay together, Geum Ran.
If I wake up from my sleep, Ajumma will be here.
This must be a dream. Right, Ajumma?
It was just yesterday that you announced your divorce. So, do
you think it's okay to have such a cheerful expression?
It's been a long time since I decided to divorce.
I wandered in darkness.
So, shall I say that I finally feel like I can see the light, now?
Staying here is only temporary, so don't worry.
You don't even have anywhere else to go.
I'm going to sell the building and look for a house.
Have you guys talked about it?
If you don't have Brother-in-law's consent,
you can't do what you want to with it.
I made an offer that Kang Joon can't refuse.
That ugly Chae Yeon hired someone and
pulled out all of her belongings.
Hey, make sure to take good care of the building.
Chae Yeon won't be up to any tricks, will she?
Even if she tries, the building is mine.
Who is it? Chae Yeon?
Is there still something left to talk about?
Let's talk face to face.
I'll go to your office.
Come in.
How is Sara? Did she arrive well?
I spoke to the employee who was
supposed to pick up Sara at the airport,
but he says that Sara wasn't on the plane.
Why? What happened?
I don't know for sure, either. Her
cell phone remains turned off.
Has the bus come?
I'll go look outside and be back. Stay here.
Missed Calls (16), Messages (4),
from Doctor
Ajumma, I'm at the airport. Even if you're going to leave
when it's time, see my face before you go.
Please turn on your phone.
Ajumma, at least listen to my voice before you go.
I'm still at the airport. Call me if you haven't left yet.
Ajumma, please. Please call me.
Han Min Hyeok
Yes, General Manager.
Sara, you've finally turned on your phone.
One of my employees, who is at Logan Airport
in Boston, says that you didn't get on the airplane.
I worried about you.
Truthfully, I had no intention of getting on
the plane from the start.
Please make it as if I'm overseas to everyone else.
I thought I had to do that, in order for no one to look for me.
I understand.
Call me as soon as you decide where you'll live.
The bus came. Let's go.
♫  What's wrong with my age, is there an age for love,  ♫
Doctor, it's the clam soup that you like,
and doenjang Jigae (beanpaste soup) for a broken heart.
And, I even put in my special sauce that you like.
The first stage of accepting separation.
Denial of reality.
I can't acknowledge that she left me.
How long has it been, Yeo Ok?
It's been about ten years, right?
I've been wondering why you don't visit.
I'm so glad to see you, so glad!
Can I ask you a favor?
I'm looking for a place to stay because
we came here suddenly.
Of course. Hey, there's plenty of space
in this restaurant.
Just think of this as your house, and
stay comfortably.
But, who is this young lady?
She's my daughter's friend.
Ajummoni,
"Kitchen Ajumma urgently wanted."
Can I do this?
Aigoo, a young lady who's this pretty
wants to be a kitchen worker. Aigoo.
I am really good at cleaning and cooking!
Please use me once, Ajummoni.
Oh Mom, there's water there.
You're going to slip!
- Aiyoo, it's okay
- Aigoo, give it to me!
Mom, you just rest like a princess.
Princess?
No, no, Mom. I'll do it.
Rest, Mom.
Broadcast Board of Directors Meeting . . . Notice to Appear?
CEO, they say that the Board of Directors'
disciplinary meeting will be tomorrow.
I think you're going to have to transfer
the Canvas building to me.
It's compensation for my ruined life,
which was destroyed by you and Sa Geum Ran.
You were the one who seduced me, a married man.
Who was the person who complained
about his loveless marriage?
I don't want to talk for too long.
Give me the building quietly
or this will be revealed.
It's the black box's memory card.
That night...
The scene where you murdered
Sa Geum Ran is recorded here.
Tomorrow is the Board of Director's Disciplinary meeting, right?
What would happen if I revealed this to the public?
It starts at ten o'clock, right?
Send me the building transfer papers by 9 am,
or I will participate in the board meeting.
Miss Sara?
Oh, yes. I'll come to the office now.
What is the name of the cooking school that Miss
Sara has gone to overseas? Where is she staying?
I, too, don't know up to that point.
Does it make sense for the PD in charge to not know the
whereabouts of the poster girl participant of the program?
It's something that happened at the headquarters of Winner Group,
so I'm not in a position to ask in detail. I'm sorry.
The headquarters of Winner Group?
Did you tell General Manager Han Min Hyeok about
the agenda of the Broadcast Board of Directors Meeting?
I wasn't able to tell him. He went down to a province.
Province? Why didn't Secretary Jung go with him?
He said he'll be going there by himself.
Miss Sara.
I'll find a suitable place for you to stay.
It's comfortable here.
I know the owner, and
there are not a lot of people
who recognize my face.
Even if they recognize you,
they'll doubt it.
Why would a person who appeared yesterday,
on TV, suddenly work at a restaurant?
Now, I think I know you a little more, Miss Sara.
I want to work with you, Miss Sara, but
you are not moved by money or fame.
Still, I need you, Miss Sara.
So let's look for another way.
Are you sleeping, Geum Ran?
It must be hard.
Alright.
If your body is tired, time will go by more quickly,
and you will eventually forget.
♫  I was the only one who didn't know, I thought that it will be forever  ♫
♫  I was the only one who didn't know, I thought that I will be happy  ♫
♫  I love you, the words that I can't say to you now.  ♫
What kind of card is this?
Oh!
Ajumma, you can't open it yet.
My wishes are written down on it.
If I write down my wishes, hang them on the tree,
and turn on the lights,
it is said that all my wishes will be fulfilled.
If I do this, then all my wishes will be granted.
♫  It is a very hard thing  ♫
♫  Living well without you  ♫
♫ Reluctantly I just survive.  ♫
Ajumma, you have to be happy.
♫ I live in regret. ♫
♫  Even if I know it's not so,  ♫
♫ Perhaps you will come back.  ♫
♫  I was the only one who didn't know,
I thought that it would be forever,  ♫
I thought that we'd be happy,  ♫
♫  I love you, the words that I cannot say to you now, ♫
The second stage of separation
that comes to find you, after denying reality; anger.
I'm going to hate you, Ajumma.
I'm going to curse you until I die and
I will never forgive you.
Italy? You will never be able to be there comfortably.
You're going to regret it forever.
Oh, Ajumma.
♫  I believe that you will come. You told me to only look at you.  ♫
♫  I trust what you said, you can't live without me  ♫
Tomorrow is CEO Lee Kang Joon's disciplinary hearing.
Your participation is needed.
Team Leader Choi, you participate for me, instead.
There should be enough files.
You already said that you would attend
so that you can reprimand him personally.
You do as you see fit. Also, don't
come looking for me for a while.
President!
- How is it?
- It's delicious. Isn't it, Unni?
What in the world did you put in this?
The way that I cook it results in something
that tastes completely different from yours.
It's natural seasoning.
I ground fermented beans and shiitake mushroom.
Then, I roasted it for ten hours, after adding dried pollock.
It brings the ingredients to life.
Oh, really?
Do you think it would be okay to put this
in the restaurant's food from now on?
Of course, Ajummoni.
From now on, put it in everything
on the menu.
There will be a ton of customers.
I know, right?
Oh, this is so fascinating!
So delicious!
Ajumma!
Can we have two bowls of hangover soup!
- Where are you going?
- I told you
to prepare the documents by 9 am, today.
There was no reply. So, I think
I'll participate in the board meeting.
I will transfer the building to your name, so go back.
Are you sure?
I will fill out the paperwork for you!
Then, have it ready by five o'clock.
HBS Emergency Board of Directors Meeting
The agenda for today's Broadcast Board of Directors Meeting is
regarding the one who handled the broadcast of
false information about Madame Park Man Deok.
The agenda is for the discipline of
HBS CEO/Director Lee Kang Joon.
I heard that the one who submitted him
for discipline, Han Tae Hee, cannot attend today.
Do we have to delay the meeting?
There's no need to delay it.
Position of HBS News With Respect to Park Man Doek's
Embezzlement and Breach of Fiduciary Duties in Broadcast
These are signed documents.
The report was fair.
Han Tae Hee was recently hurt in an accident.
Since we've confirmed that he has no intention of
participating in this Board Meeting, dismiss the matter.
These are additional documents concluding that he worked
diligently to damage Madam Park Man Deok's honor.
This is a magazine reporting on his marriage and divorce.
He has violated the regulations of the company.
All of these are materials that were personally
prepared by Han Tae Hee.
Announcer Gyo Chae Yeon announces her divorce.
I will announce the result of the meeting.
The unanimous decision by the Board of Directors,
from Lee Kang Joon's disciplinary hearing, is
that CEO Lee Kang Joon
is to be suspended for three months.
Tae Hee has let go of the Winner Food work?
Yes, Grandmother.
If Oppa wants to receive the recommendation
of the Board of Directors as the leader,
they say he has to have a track record.
There isn't much time, so I'm worried.
Is it because of Sara?
Aghhh, I pointlessly broke this.
No matter what I do, I can't get rid of my anger!
Ajumma. Ajumma.
- Why?
- I called you about a Winner Food matter.
The labor unions keep calling.
I'm sorry. I can't do anything right now.
Ajumma. There's no one who would come at this time.
Ajumma. Ajumma.
I heard that you let go of the Winner Food work?
You are the person who will take charge of Winner Food.
With the General Stockholders Meeting ahead,
at this most important time,
it's not right for you do this over a woman issue.
Tae Hee, only you are having a hard time.
Sara, that child, isn't like that.
What are you talking about?
Sara said first that she wanted to break up.
And, in the end, didn't she go to study abroad for herself?
Sara doesn't feel as you do.
You must accept that truth and find your place.
Why must you know where Sara is?
I have a bit of a personal situation.
I heard that you received a three-month suspension
by the Board of Directors.
You're becoming more and more
unfavorable in my eyes.
The fact that I received a suspension
is because of the coverage of Madam Park Man Deok.
I heard that Han Tae Hee even raised
the issue of your personal life.
So, why did you give them such an excuse?
Why did you handle your personal life in that manner?
And also, why should you, who has so many
unsavory rumors surrounding you, look for Sara?
It's a matter related to Birth of a Chef.
Sara's past life isn't important.
I'm thinking to directly decide on matters
related to Sara's future.
I'm even going to become Sara's guardian.
I'd like for you to have no further dealings
with Sara, in the future.
Leave.
Ajumma, you didn't feel like I did?
Is that right, Ajumma?
Was I the only one who loved you like a crazy person?
I was the only one who loved you
and the only one who is hurting.
What happened at the cooking competition?
Are you curious?
Of course I am.
If you're curious, look at the rebroadcast.
This beef soup . . .
With which the broth was made with mussels,
I'd like to praise the idea greatly.
The ingredients, seasoning, and taste have all married nicely.
The striking and sumptuous royal table
that Oh Kyung Hee has prepared,
no matter what family receives it,
I think they will be 100% satisfied.
Then, shall we look at Sara's cooking?
It's Doenjang Jigae (bean paste soup) and tuna.
The taste is amazingly harmonious.
But, why is it tuna?
I recently promised to marry the person I love.
Since it's a table to be prepared for one's family,
I thought of that person.
That person is a bit unwell right now,
so I prepared a table only for him, with
ingredients good for the heart.
I made a broth with the tuna bones
which can lower cholesterol,
so I used tuna as an ingredient.
The mixed rice, fried walnut anchovy, onion salad . . .
And, I tried making a Duck Bulgogi (sweet soy sauce marinated).
There are traditional flavors in the four side dishes.
I added some natural seasoning that
I created using a traditional method.
I think that the tasters will have to try it for themselves.
How Sara's natural seasoning was made,
I can only say that it's the best.
♫  My each and every single day without you,  ♫
♫  I couldn't think that it would be this hard,  ♫
Today at the cooking competition, for ingredients, seven points.
For creativity, four points, for health evaluation, five points,
and from the taste evaluation, the ten points previously . . .
It's Sara. You are the winner of the third round.
Thank you. Thank you.
♫ The way you speak, everything. Perhaps, ♫
♫ If you feel the same way that I do ♫
♫ If like me, perhaps, you're hurting very much ♫
♫ I will run ♫
That gaze can't be a lie. Definitely (not).
♫ I will be embraced in your arms ♫
♫ Without you, I am nothing. Because I love you. ♫
Team Leader Choi, where is Han Min Hyeok right now?
I've been hearing from here and there that Han Tae Hee
has been looking for me. Now, you show up in person.
What happened?
Tell me where you sent Sara.
Do you think I could hide Sara by my own will?
Sara left by her own will.
What happened to the Han Tae Hee
who was so proud that he had nothing to lose?
Did you approach Sara on purpose so that
you could show off to me?
The reason isn't important.
What's important is the outcome.
Han Tae Hee, in the end, you could not
protect your woman,
just like your father who passed away twenty years ago.
Han Min Hyeok.
Your car is ready.
Han Tae Hee gave up Winner Food completely?
He cares for Sara that much?
He's completely lost all reasoning.
Things have become easier.
If Han Tae Hee can't save Winner Foods,
I will be the only candidate for the Board of Directors.
I believe it will be easy to get a ruling for me.
All of Winner Group and Sara...
I will have it all.
Then, have it prepared by five o'clock.
In this kind of situation, how is it you are acting like this?
- I have been suspended from the Director position also.
- Is that right?
Let's compromise on the building.
Let's each have half.
In one hour, call your house.
What do you mean by that?
I'm Chae Yeon.
Why are you calling me?
Since you made Kang Joon into a bad person,
we can't even leave the house.
Right now, it's just the start,
so it's worrisome if you're already worn out.
Have you checked your email?
What?
What is it?
Chae Yeon told me to open my email.
This is the video from the black box of Kang Joon's car.
It shows him killing Sa Geum Ran.
What?
What is this?
Isn't that the car Geum Ran was driving
at the time of the accident?
Is he following Geum Ran?
Oh my, Kang Joon!
Oh my, oh my!
What? Then, K-Kang Joon killed her?!
It's true that he killed her?
Looking at the video, it's certain.
On the road that our Pig Sister-in-law died,
Oppa was driving at a really scary speed.
The date and the time matches.
Kang Joon?
There must be something to it, in order for
somebody to report him for murder
and for him to be arrested!
What should we do?
I'm getting goosebumps.
Oh my word.
What are you guys doing to all be gathered, like this?
Why are you like that?
Did you guys commit a sin?
No. How could we sin?
What happened?!!
Nothing happened, Honey.
I'm here.
Kang Joon, you brat!
Why did you do that?
What are you going to do?
If that's revealed, you'll really be ruined.
Your life will be completely over!
What are we going to do about this?
No, never.
Who would believe that?
Even if we say that it wasn't you,
imagine if people in the world see it!
You're completely finished.
What should we do about this?
Chae Yeon, filled with spite, manipulated the video.
Don't say anything to Father.
Tell Noona and Min Yeong to erase the email.
Our house is over.
Our household is totally over.
What should we do?
How is it? Did you change your mind?
- Where are you?
- Just listen first.
If you don't want to hand over the building,
there is no need for us to meet or know where I am.
You must not be ready yet.
Fine, then.
I am currently organizing the list of directors
in charge of the broadcasting company.
I'm thinking to send the black box video
to the personal emails of the directors.
Can't you stop?
Then are you ready?
To hand over the building.
Have you brought the transfer of ownership document?
Change of Ownership Application
Lee Kang Joon
There is nothing to feel unfairly wronged about.
Think of this as a punishment for
abandoning women too easily.
Why can't you look directly in my eyes
if it's not a big deal?
That's right.
My eyes are growing dim nowadays.
Of what are you guilty?!
Guilty? What do you mean?
Kang Joon and you, what are you guys
doing about the building?
It's been a while since we decided to give it back
to the in-law! Why aren't you saying anything?
Give me the files! I will take care of it.
Okay. I got it.
Kang Joon, Kang Joon!
I think your father found out!
He told me to bring the files for the building.
What did Chae Yeon say?
Calm down! Father is going to hear us at this rate.
I can't calm down!
What is going to happen, Kang Joon?
Is the building going to be taken away from us?
I'm not going to give up on the building.
Didn't you hand over the files?
How can you not give it up when
Chae Yeon is threatening you!
There is still one more method.
What method?
The more you try to endure,
the more dangerous it will be for Han Tae Hee.
You know me well,
what I did to Sa Geum Ran . . .
You need to give me time to think or prepare myself!
How can you say it so quickly, without a reason?
This isn't right, Ajumma.
The person you are trying to reach is not picking up
the phone. You will be directed to voicemail.
After the beep, you will be charged additionally.
Kyeong Joo, I was wondering
if Han Tae Hee called you.
If you are able to call him or meet him,
tell me if he's okay.
He was very sick recently.
And if he's eating.
What do you mean Sara's mother isn't here?
Where did she go?
She went down to the province because
she had something to do.
She isn't picking up my phone calls.
Her battery must have run out.
I need to know where Sara is.
I don't know!
I have to leave soon, so can you go?
Geum Ran
Geum Ran.
You know about Sara, right?
What is this number?
Isn't Sara overseas?
She's in this country?
A person that is very close to Mother has a restaurant.
Geum Ran is over there with her mother.
Ajumma...
CEO said that he is going to the province.
He is going alone today also.
It's Han Min Hyeok. I'm going to you right now.
I have something to talk to you about, about work.
Yes.
Can I have some more radish kimchi?
Yes, it's coming!
Eat well!
Thank you.
Who wanted more radish kimchi?
Here!
You must have been hungry.
Eat a lot!
Ajumma...
Eat well!
Han Tae Hee?
I was wondering if Sara is doing well.
She is doing well.
I'm not happy to see you.
I asked a favor of you
to not hurt Geum Ran again.
I am very resentful.
Is Sara really okay?
She's settled down a lot now.
I heard that you are the son of Winner Group.
Geum Ran is barely living with someone else's identity.
You two don't suit each other and look precarious.
Since you guys broke up, you should start anew.
I've decided to be the bad guy,
and I hope that you don't come back again.
How can the noodles be so chewy?
Can you tell me your secret? Huh?
The secret is the strength of determination.
That hand determination which can crush an apple in one try.
Anyway, you are so interesting.
If you go on TV, you will be successful.
You should go on one of those cooking competitions.
Cooking competition.
Even if it's just for me, go on the show.
And, if you are going, winning decisively
would be even better.
Kyeong Joo, did Han Tae Hee contact you?
Yes, he came.
I had no choice but to tell him where you were.
I think he was going to where you are.
♫ How can I forget you? How can I erase you? ♫
♫ I can't stand a single moment without you. ♫
Doctor.
♫ My heart hurts so much, I can't let you go like this.♫
♫ I'll wait for you until always. Even if it hurts, it's ok. ♫
Sara.
Sa Geum Ran, I see that you were hiding here.
Winner Food is going to declare bankruptcy?
Since you left, Tae Hee hasn't been
taking care of his company.
And, this isn't the only thing.
I think there will be more unpleasant things
happening to Tae Hee.
The labor union's reaction is not looking good.
Now, she has settled many things.
I don't think Sara feels the same way as you do.
Tae Hee, you are the only one who is suffering.
Recently, I promised to marry someone who I love.
You have been hurt badly.
I didn't think I was going to see you again.
If there is more news regarding Winner Food,
please let me know.
I understand.
But Sara, are you really going to be okay staying here?
I'm doing fine here, so don't worry.
I'll see you next time.
Ajumma.
You look good, Ajumma.
It's tolerable.
Are you doing okay, Doctor?
Are you eating regularly?
You said you were going to study abroad,
but why are you here?
I wanted live here quietly here, and plan things
and settle things around me.
I hear that Winner Food is in a dire situation.
It's an important time, so how can you neglect the work?
Because of you, Ajumma,
I became an idiot who can't do anything.
Because we broke up, you can't do anything?
That's just an excuse.
When married couples are separating everyday, what is
the big deal about a man and a woman breaking up?
I'm doing well. So you, too, go back to what you were doing,
and don't come to see me anymore.
To you Ajumma,
is that possible?
Wasn't it difficult for you?
You said that I was a woman with no emotions.
I am like that. If one only does housework,
one becomes realistic.
I just work, worry about what to eat, and mingle
comfortably with others.
You feel differently than I do.
I saw you laugh.
When I saw how well you were doing, I honestly hated you.
Yes, I should just let her be.
Let's just pretend that I didn't see her.
I thought that and was going back to Seoul.
But then, I turned my car around.
Why?
The reason is...
because I wanted to see you.
That's not the case for me.
If we ended, then it's the end.
Now, I don't want to see you anymore.
I like being alone.
I don't want to be attached to anyone anymore.
You like being alone, but you're in contact
with Han Min Yeok?
Why, of all people, does it have to be Han Min Hyeok?
We ended our relationship.
So, do I need to explain anything?
You are going way overboard, Ajumma.
It's too much.
So, don't have any lingering feelings.
Don't be concerned about me.
With that energy . . . Put that energy into your work.
♫ Because it's a fearless love. ♫
♫ Because love comes out before pain. ♫
♫  Even if contemplating is all I can do, ♫
♫  I can't throw you away. ♫
♫ Yesterday, and today. ♫
♫  You destroyed half of me and made me crazy  ♫
♫ The longing which can't be erased even though I tried very hard.  ♫
Geum, I am going to go the ajumma's house.
♫ Even if you don't love me ♫
I am going to get a blanket.
Geum Ran.
Mom, I'm going to go shopping for food.
♫  I am without fear.  ♫
All the food in storage for the restaurant has run out.
♫ I'll throw everything into this love. ♫
♫ Even if the ending isn't happy, ♫
♫ I will follow where my heart goes. ♫
♫  You're the reason that I live.  ♫
The last stage of separation.
Acceptance.
♫  Even if all I can do is think about you..  ♫
♫  It's a love that I can't let go of.  ♫
♫  Love is not something you can put in you hands. ♫
Get out.
This is a restaurant. I came here to eat too.
What do you want?
Chae Yeon threatened me and took my building.
Chae Yeon has the black-box recording
from the day of the car accident.
It recorded me, who pushed you over the cliff.
You need to save me.
It will be solved if you reveal that
you are Sa Geum Ran, not Sara.
The building belongs to you, so you should
reveal your identity and get it back.
And, you need to say that I didn't murder you.
Why would I do that?
If you don't do that,
I will come visit you everyday.
I did not become the CEO,
got divorced, and even had the building taken away.
What else do I have left?
All I can do is to hold onto you.
They say that fights between a couple
are like trying to slice water.
Why are you here?
How did you find out?
Are you okay?
Get out! Get out before I call the police.
Get out right now.
Now you must have found out her identity.
Honey, you are a good daughter.
You need to keep this happiness.
Go! Get away from my Geum Ran!
Think about my words carefully.
Out!
That disgusting rascal!
How can he even follow you here?
Let's move somewhere else.
Do you think that he won't find us, if we do that?
No matter whether you love or hate me, we're in the same boat,
so you should help me from now on.
When I become the head of Winner Group,
you will benefit as well.
This is the opportunity, since Han Tae Hee is weak.
I'm going to report Han Tae Hee to the police,
after fabricating the files.
I will take care of this.
My grandmother's trial...
Make sure that her sentence is finalized.
I'm trying to make it so that she spends
the rest of her live in jail.
This is something that you have to do.
Immediate Loan Application
What is this?
To slow down the bankruptcy of the company,
it is an application for a loan from the loan sharks.
He wanted to save the company,
but the method he used was wrong.
He gathered illegal bonds.
He made it seem like the Labor Union agreed with him.
If this is known to the officials,
it is a minimum of five years in jail.
Since the labor union agreed with him,
they committed the same sin.
Where is CEO Han Tae Hee?
After doing this, would he still be at the company?
It's been a while since he took
his hands off Winner Foods.
What? CEO made corporate bonds?
That's nonsense.
He said he would save the company.
Is deceiving people with corporate bonds
as a way to save the company?
We're not going to stay still on this.
CEO! CEO!
Something major has happened!
You can't be like this!
Please answer your phone!
Han Tae Hee is going to be prosecuted?
We can't contact him. At this rate,
something major will happen!
The labor union is going to sue Han Tae Hee.
The situation is going in our favor.
This was not meant to just prosecute him.
Sara is the objective.
General Manager Han Min Hyeok, it's Sara.
May I see you?
I'll head down.
Yes.
I heard that the labor union is
going to prosecute Han Tae Hee.
But Tae Hee isn't moving at all.
The reason why Han Tae Hee is like that
is because of me.
Just help him overcome this.
If he finishes cleaning up his feelings,
he will solve everything. He's that kind of person.
Help him. I beg you, General Manager.
Then, how about if we help each other with one thing?
I told you. I'm a businessman.
This seems like good timing.
I will put all my effort into saving Tae Hee. However,
you have to accept my offer.
The labor union is going to report me?
Yes, CEO. I fear that it's too late to stop anything.
Where are the representatives for the labor union?
They are having a meeting at the company.
Yes.
- You came?
- Are you ready?
I'm ready for the debate as well.
The spotlight for today is on you.
Since CEO Jung, from Han San Group,
wants you to present him,
it means he is thinks of you as the
future head of Winner Group.
Is that right?
- Let's go.
- Also, are you okay if I have one more person join us?
I know that you worked hard for this.
Of course you may.
Your car is here.
Sara.
♫ How can I forget you? How can I erase you? ♫
♫  I can't stand a single moment without you.  ♫
♫ My heart aches so much, I can't let you go like this. ♫