I've become quite strange
these days.
I mean...
Not strange...
Something like that...
What I mean is...
It bothers me when you are
close to other women.
And it bothers me when you ask me
to set you up on a blind date.
That's how I feel.
Now, I don't want you to
lean on me anymore.
Now...
I...
I want to...
I can't express my love to you with words
Even if you add all of
the world, it's not enough
Until my tears dry,
until my heart wears out
The love that I want and long for is you
My...
My blood vessels...
My blood vessels feel hot
like pipes inside a boiler.
I am in love with you...
Inside my heart, it feels like
someone's beating on the drums.
Even if my tears dry,
even if my heart wears out
I am in love with you
Then, what about me?
How do you think I feel?
I feel the same way.
I...
I don't understand.
I don't know what I should
do for you.
You don't need to do anything.
My hands are cold.
I guess it is cold out.
You should be careful
not to catch a cold.
I will be careful,
but my hands are still cold.
I will buy you a pair of gloves tomorrow.
You always clasp the hand
so tightly.
Yes.
Did you hold a lot of different
girls' hands?
Are you a player?
No.
When guardians take autistic patients around,
this is how they hold their hand.
In case of impulsive acts,
they need to have a tight grip.
I see.
The director used to hold me like this
when I was young.
Now, I'm not the one holding you.
You're the one holding me.
I see.
- Dr. Cha.
- Yes?
By any chance...
Do you think you'll regret this
tomorrow morning?
Regret what?
I often regret things I do and say
in the evening.
I regret them exactly at 6:30 AM.
Hey!
It's not like I was drunk.
Why would I regret anything?
Then...
can you promise me one thing?
If you do regret it, come to work
tomorrow with your hair tied up.
What's that?
I don't think I can bear to hear
it if you are regretful.
Please do that, so I can tell
just by looking at you.
Fine.
Then, I'll be going back
to the hospital.
When you miss a person,
no matter how much you insist
It's like trying to stop a young child
Everything that fills my eyes is you
I only look at you, who doesn't
know my heart, though it hurts
Wind blows in my heart,
stepping on the countless scars
Though I know love is painful
My heart beats once again,
I want to believe that our love
Isn't momentary, but is like destiny
My heart beats once again...
I won't... regret it, right?
6:30 AM.
6:30...
Good morning.
You're here?
What?
It's nothing.
Try going outside.
What?
Do you know how windy
it is outside?
Walking here with all my hair down,
I looked like a crazy woman.
Bad wind...
I'll be going to the ward then.
Why did you want to see me?
I want to ask you two things.
Go ahead.
Do you think you'll be able to stick
around in this unfavorable environment?
I think your definition of an environment
is very different from mine.
No matter which department, the
most important environment is the doctor.
The external environment
is only secondary.
Let me ask you the second question.
Giving a future to the children...
Giving them happiness...
You don't think doctors in other nations
want those same things?
I'm sure they do.
But the difference is that they only guarantee
a future and happiness to the chosen few.
The future we guarantee to the children
doesn't include the words 'chosen few.'
Cha Yoon Seo!
Yes, Eun Jung.
Why didn't you answer my text
last night?
Something came up.
I heard you were set up with
a prosecutor.
My mom called you again?
It's nothing new that she's asking me
about your personal life.
Let's just end our friendship.
That's what I want to say.
She drives me crazy with her questions.
Why...
Now that I'm dying,
you're happy?
I'm sure you are...
I'm not happy.
This kid...
You're such a good liar.
Just like your mother.
Honey.
I'm not lying.
Shut up, you retard!
Shi Duk...
My son, Shi Duk.
How good it would be
if our Shi Duk was around.
- He would have taken such good care of me.
- Why are you bringing up Shi Duk?
Shi Duk...
My damn life...
I hate my life...
You...
This is your last chance.
Get rid of everyone who will
get in our way.
I heard from the chairwoman
that you are helping her a lot.
I created the problem.
I should at least pretend to
take care of the problem.
Yes.
You should continue to do that.
For the chairwoman.
The chairwoman never wanted
anything from you.
She only thought about what would
be good for you.
I won't tell you to understand the chairwoman,
or become friendly with her.
But...
Don't avoid her.
If you stay around her,
there will be an opportunity to reconcile.
But if you avoid her,
you won't even get that opportunity.
Okay?
Okay.
I requested for a conference
regarding this matter.
I'll have a debate with Chief Kim.
Then, have you found the reasons
why we must operate on In Hye?
Just about.
- What is it?
- First, the blood vessel anastomosis.
And the small intestine fistula.
True, we have more experience
with small intestine fistulas.
We'll come to a decision tomorrow.
Before then, don't say anything.
Yes, sir.
- Are you eating well?
- Yes.
- Please check Dong Jin's temperature frequently.
- Yes, sir.
What are you writing down?
All the happy moments in my life.
Thinking about it now,
there were a lot of times.
I'm sure there are a lot of times
that you can't remember as well.
I hope I'll remember enough memories
to fill up this entire diary.
That way...
If something happens to me,
my sister will look at this and not be so sad.
In Hye, why do you keep on
saying that?
I know everything.
The small intestine transplant...
It's a very difficult
and dangerous surgery.
Even so, I wish the doctors at the
pediatrics surgery department could do it.
I think I'll be more at ease, then.
That girl...
Why does she keep saying such
hurtful things?
She must have been traumatized
when she collapsed the last time.
She wasn't like this before.
I'm sorry.
If we perform the surgery like In Hye
says, she won't be as scared.
I'm sure you feel scared, too,
with the surgery date approaching.
Yes.
A little.
More than being painful...
I think it will feel very cold.
The doctors' hands are warmer
than you think.
Please believe that.
There's more resistance from the hospital
than we anticipated.
We just need to get rid of
the difficult ones.
If we get rid of them, we need
to bring in others to replace them.
But they won't be as great as
the current doctors we have.
- How different can doctors be?
- That's not true.
They may not differ much in skills.
But there are differences
that are not noticeable to our eyes.
What is it you are trying to say?
The acquisition of
Sung Won University Hospital...
How about just switching it back
to getting funded by public investors?
What?
Rather than trying to put on tires
that don't fit...
It may be better to fill up the air
on tires that fit well.
Hey.
Kang Hyun Tae.
You want to take the easy way?
That's not it.
Listen carefully.
Kids are our hope.
Hope that's just a bit different.
Look.
What's this?
An app for anniversary dates.
It's a bit embarrassing to say this,
but I really wanted to do this.
Look here.
It's been one day
since we started dating.
You're not going to download it too?
I don't need that.
Since I've met you,
it's been...
Stop.
I'm still going to use this.
In any case,
it's our first official day together...
Is there anywhere you want to go?
- Zoo...
- Besides a zoo or a PC room.
There.
The man is always surrounded by
animal spirits.
That's why they always protect you
and keep you from getting tainted.
No matter how much someone
tries to taint you.
I think that's true.
What about me?
There are two.
One is the spirit of alcohol.
Oh my God.
She's right on.
- What about the other?
- Spirit of fire.
Is that because I have
a hot temper?
No, the nature of fire is not to burn.
It's to give warmth.
Giving warmth to people, land, and air.
Right?
Then...
What about us together?
It's great.
There's nothing in the way.
But...
There's only one bridge.
Bridge?
Yes, a bridge that connects
the two of you.
The couples who break up and
get back together often have a lot of bridges.
But between the two of you,
there's only one.
If that bridge disappears...
you'll never get back together.
Why is she saying such nonsense?
We shouldn't believe in something like that.
You're the one who said she's good,
and took me there.
Maybe she's lost her touch.
What's that?
This is real.
If you can match up this cube in two minutes,
we'll give you one of these prizes.
This!
I really need this egg cooker.
- Can I do it in ten seconds?
- Excuse me?
You should ask for more time.
Ten seconds is not enough.
No.
And it won't be fun if I do it
with my eyes open.
What?
Count to ten.
Start.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Awesome!
This.
Please give me that.
It's done.
Thank you.
I really needed this.
If you need anything else,
tell me anytime.
I guess you used your talent
of saving children's lives for this.
Sometimes, I use it for other purposes, too.
I used this skill in a maze contest once
at an amusement park.
I won a box of
spicy noodles then.
I'm so proud of you.
That's nothing.
Being arrogant again...
You know...
Should we just openly date?
And tell everyone?
Why?
You think I'll get teased?
Nobody will tease me.
Don't worry.
Still...
I don't know.
It'll be fine.
Then, let's take time.
I want to tell them later.
Later when?
You'll do great, right?
Please make it possible for us to
operate on our In Hye.
Please shut Chief Kim's mouth.
I'm not going there to fight.
I'm going to have a medical discussion.
We understand.
Don't worry, and work hard.
Let me ask one thing.
How do you plan on carrying out
the enteroenterostomy?
We will connect the small and large intestine
by end-to-end anastomosis...
If you connect the small and large intestines,
you can't make an intestinal fistula.
How will you observe the small intestines
after the surgery?
Another thing...
There is something more important
than enteroenterostomy.
It's blood vessel anastomosis.
Fortunately in this case, there are
uninfected aorta and caval veins remaining...
During the transplant,
if you connect two fixed blood vessels...
The connection can bend,
so the failure rate is high.
If I may add to that...
Taking the microvessles to conduct
the anastomosis...
That will increase the success rate.
You are here to ridicule us again?
If you are here to push us to
make the repayment, there's no need.
We are well aware of the due date.
Why weren't you interested in
protecting the hospital?
What?
You are the one who
brought this upon yourself.
Look here.
What are you saying?
You are not only losing the hospital
and foundation.
But you and the director are
losing your values.
Get out.
Who are you trying to lecture?
From now on,
listen carefully to what I say.
It's almost time for him to come.
Professor Kim.
You did your best.
You worked hard.
Not bad, right?
In Hye's surgery...
We'll be performing it.
Way to go, Professor!
Why were you putting on a show?
See? This type of acting suits me
much better than Captain Hook.
You're not a hole anymore.
Your acting is full of soul.
Not bad, right?
If you make fun of my acting again,
I'll crush you.
Do you have time today?
I was hoping to have a team dinner.
Will it be hard?
It's okay with me.
It works for everyone, right?
- Yes.
I want some marbled rib eye steak.
Go and buy it yourself, then!
Hello.
You are that doctor from before.
Yes.
How are you feeling?
What are you asking me for?
As you can see,
I'm half-dead already.
But...
What brings you here?
It's because of Shi On.
What has he done?
Father.
You should stop treating him like a child,
and treat him as an adult.
Shi On is a doctor here now.
You'll have to treat him like an adult if you
want Shi On to be a responsible son to you.
If you are going to say that
kind of nonsense, get out!
Please.
Who cares if you are a doctor?
Why are you getting involved in our
family matters?
If Shi On's brother were alive,
he would have told you the same thing.
You know...
Should we just date openly?
And tell everyone?
Why?
You think I'll get teased?
- For the pediatrics surgery department!
- Cheers!
Order whatever you want to eat,
except you, Park Shi On.
You all work so hard, but
I've never brought you out before.
It's okay.
We came out on our own.
I'm sorry for not being a good
manager to all of you.
No.
We are sorry for not taking
better care of you.
It's okay...
Chief, looking at you closely,
you look like actor Lee Byung Hun.
That kid...
Saying useless things again.
'Tell me.
Were you really going to kill me?'
Maybe we are alike...
But like a dried-up Lee Byung Hun.
What did you say?
Park Shi On.
How dare you talk to the manager
like that?
I'm sorry.
Seriously...
Attention, please!
I...
I'm dating someone.
That's good news!
Then, you're no longer single?
Congratulations.
Who is he?
It's Park Shi On.
Stop kidding around.
Who is it?
It really is Park Shi On.
Seriously...
You shouldn't have said anything, then.
It's true.
It really is Park Shi On.
Really?
Another round of applause.
Are you mad because I announced it
without your permission?
You're worried, then?
It's something we need to
overcome once.
We can't do this because of other people.
We don't need to do this.
I know what you are saying.
You are happy, too, right?
It feels good?
Yes. It does feel really really good.
You should go back to the hospital.
Yes.
Go.
Okay.
When you feel that it's far,
know that you're not alone
I pray your time
I pray your faith
Whatever it is, nothing can replace you...
Why are you so sad?
It's nothing.
Wow, Park Shi On.
How did you get Dr. Cha
to like you?
You're really something else.
- Shi On.
- Yes?
You have that license now.
So, don't lose it.
I won't lose it.
Never.
Good.
Good attitude!
I like that!
How cute.
Dr. Cha and Dr. Park.
But, you look worried.
How can I not worry?
Who are you worried about?
Both of them.
You should congratulate them.
To them, you are their biggest support.
Right...
I had something important to tell you.
- What is it?
- The vice president...
It's something good,
but it feels a bit strange.
We can accept it because we're their family,
but it's going to start a rumor.
Why worry about that?
If the two of them are happy, that's all.
That's true, but...
I don't think it will go over well.
You think they are fools?
You don't think they thought about that?
This is big...
I knew it when they were
always going around together.
I really don't understand.
He's cute, but how can you
have feelings for him?
I know...
You're gossiping again.
I told you not to gossip here.
Who?
Park Shi On and Cha Yoon Seo?
Yes, the rumor is all over the place.
Cha Yoon Seo...
She was always so arrogant,
and she dates someone like that?
I guess she likes unique people.
You better walk around with
more energy.
Why are you so down?
I'm sorry.
- I won't be like this in front of patients...
- Not patients.
How can such a weak guy
take care of a girl?
You'd better get three times as strong.
Stop being a kid.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Why aren't you saying anything?
About what?
About me and Park Shi On.
What can I say about that?
Still...
You're more clever than anyone
else I know.
I'm sure you thought well before
making the decision.
Thank you.
Let's go prepare for the performance.
Yes, please put on your
best performance.
Everyone, what day is today?
The day we watch Peter Pan!
From now on, this is no longer
the pediatrics ward, this is Never Land!
Should we call out Peter Pan?
One.
Two.
Three.
Peter Pan!
Again.
Hello.
I'm Peter Pan from Never Land.
I'm Wendy.
I'm John.
I'm Michael.
It's so nice to meet all of you.
Peter Pan.
Today is the day I get rid of you.
Do as you wish.
Peter Pan, go and teach that
bad Captain Hook a lesson!
Okay.
Don't worry.
Tinkerbell, please sprinkle the
magic powder!
Why are you walking instead of flying?
I had pork feet for lunch,
so I'm too heavy to fly.
You're not Tinkerbell.
You're Chubbybell.
What are you saying?
You want a piece of me?
You better be prepared,
Chubbybell.
Get up here.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Who are you, looking so ugly?
I'm the Little Mermaid.
What kind of sea creature are you?
I'm a blonde.
Why are you here?
I came to look for a witch who makes
the potion to turn me into a human.
You are mistaken.
You have to take the shuttle bus,
and travel 72,000 stops.
I'm sorry.
We're home, Wendy.
No, I want to go back to
Never Land with you.
You can't.
Take her with you.
Don't part with her.
You're still growing.
You can't stay with me.
I'm going to stay with you,
and live as a child forever.
No.
You have to live happily
with everyone here.
Peter Pan.
I have to go now.
Good bye, Wendy.
Peter Pan.
One, two, three.
There's a call from the ER.
A five year old girl fell from a slide.
She has heavy bleeding.
What are you waiting for?
Vitals?
It's unstable. The wound is deep,
the rectum may have been damaged.
Park Shi On, get the sonogram ready.
What are you smiling about?
I may not have many around me willing to help,
but I've been blessed with such good students.
I brought the sonogram.
It's all thanks to your dedication.
No.
Look over there.
Before they think about healing the patient,
they truly care about the patient.
I only treated my patients out of
a sense of duty.
The doctors in the pediatrics surgery
department are indeed different.
Even more so than you.
If you were me,
wouldn't you have been scared?
Of course.
I have nothing to say.
You are really done with
that life style?
Of course.
I can't even remember the
last time I used my fist.
But, how did you get clean?
I heard it's not easy to get out
of that life style.
I had a nephew.
My brother and his wife
died in a car accident.
I raised him.
But, he was very sick.
He had a malignant lymph tumor.
He was more dear to me
than my own child.
But I couldn't even take care of him
because I was going around fighting.
All I did was pay for the hospital bills.
And one day...
he left.
In a letter he left for me
he said...
'Thank you for being with me.'
'I love you.'
Although I didn't even do
anything for him.
I couldn't even protect him.
That's when I had a change of heart,
and I came here.
If there are kids like my nephew,
I want to take care of them.
I thought I would only be able to
forgive myself then.
What's wrong with me?
How embarrassing.
I'm so tired.
Performance...
Surgery...
You should get some rest.
I need to wash my face.
Just sleep.
I can't. If I do,
my skin will look horrible tomorrow.
You will still be pretty.
Let's see if you still say that
tomorrow morning.
But, I really don't think I can get up.
I'm so tired.
I'm just going to sleep.
Then, go to sleep.
I'll go back to the hospital...
Go after I fall asleep.
Yoon Seo!
Hey!
Let's talk.
In this big hospital,
the rumor is everywhere.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Yoon Seo.
- You're not an impulsive person.
- No, I'm not.
I thought hard about it.
I know you are kind-hearted
and sympathetic...
It's not sympathy
or an act of kindness...
I really like him.
What if your mom finds out?
You think you can convince
her to understand?
In the process of trying to convince her,
one of you will get hurt.
Just end it after dating a bit,
or end it now.
You may be upset, but I'm
sure this is the right thing to do.
Fortunately, it's not a big cut.
I don't want you to get a scar
on your pretty hand.
Is everything about me pretty to you?
Everything?
This is not good...
You're completely blinded
by something.
There's nothing there.
Dr. Cha, are you really okay?
Of course.
I'm not only okay,
I feel really good.
If something upsetting happens
because of me...
Even if that happens, it's fine.
As long as the two of us are okay.
Tomorrow is finally the day
of In Hye's surgery.
We've been checking thoroughly until now.
But her body, whether it be liver, kidney,
or blood vessels, may reject immunization.
Even if something goes wrong,
we have to remain calm and take care of it.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
Should we administer the
immunosuppressant tonight?
Yes.
- Administer it quickly.
- Okay.
I need to go over to their ward now.
Don't be scared.
It'll be okay.
Unni.
Why are you crying again?
You're crying, too.
In Hye.
This surgery...
It won't make me lead
a miserable life.
It's dividing up happiness into two.
When happiness is divided into two,
you know it gets bigger, right?
So, don't ever feel bad for me.
Okay.
I won't do that.
I love you,
my one and only sister.
I love you, too,
In Young.
Yes.
I'm just going to be a fool.
I don't want to be a dumb fool...
But I don't mind being this
kind of a fool.
Please bear through the uneasiness
you feel because of me.
I'll make sure that it's all
worth it in the end.
In Hye.
If you wait just a bit longer,
you'll get to eat all kinds of good food.
I'll make you really good spaghetti.
That's not something you can eat.
It tastes really bad...
You two look great.
You're embarrassing me.
Thank you, In Hye.
This is all thanks to you.
The two of you need to be happy.
You sound like a wedding officiant.
Smile now, don't be lonely
When you think that you're alone,
hold my hand tightly
The you that is in my heart is not weak
You can cry all you want
Because holding it in
doesn't mean you're strong
Always love, love yourself
Don't worry about anything.
Okay?
Okay.
Dr. Han.
Sadness and pain are just keys to happiness
It feels warm.
Not because it's a doctor's hand...
But because it's yours.
Let's start, then.
Scalpel.
We should open up In Hye and wait.
Let the donor room know,
so we can start when they are ready.
You have to stay by my side.
No matter what.
Okay, In Hye.
In Hye.
Sleep for a few hours.
Have a good dream.
Anesthesia will begin.
The blood flow looks good.
Let's start.
Mosquito.
Tie.
Cut.
It's finished.
Let the recipient know.
Vascular forceps.
One more.
In Hye, it's almost finished now.
Hang in there.
Just a bit more.
It's done.
- Finish up, and move her to the aseptic room.
- Good job.
Good job.
She should be waking up from
the anesthesia, why isn't she up, yet?
Let's wait a bit more.
Yes.
What happened?
Her breathing hasn't returned,
and her BP is low.
In Hye.
D.I.C...
D.I.C?
Then, there's bleeding inside the stomach...
- Then we can't stop the bleeding.
If the bleeding doesn't stop,
she may never wake up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Some day, that day will come,
days of love will come
If I hope and hope
Do you know how it feels
To love someone so much
that you hate them?