Subtitles by DramaFever
Episode 18
Scalpel.
Professor Kim.
Are you okay?
Professor Kim!
Professor Kim,
get a hold of yourself!
Professor Kim!
I'm fine.
The wound must have gotten infected.
Right?
Bring him out immediately.
I'm fine.
Not in this condition.
Hold me up.
- Professor Kim.
- Now!
- Dr. Cha, you perform the surgery.
- Excuse me?
And, Dr. Han...
- You will be the first assistant.
- Pardon?
I will stay in the operating room.
You all will become my hands
and my eyes.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Dr. Cha, start the laparotomy,
and locate the gallbladder.
You must approach the adhesion carefully.
Yes, sir.
Scalpel.
Army navy.
One more.
Forceps.
Get me the right angle.
The intestinal adhesion is more serious
than we thought.
It won't be easy to approach it.
Park Shi On, estimate the area
of the adhesion.
Okay.
We should start with this area.
Be careful not to damage the
small and large intestines.
Yes, sir.
- I've located the gallbladder.
- I'll set the catheter.
- Make it longer.
- Isn't this long enough?
We can't operate on the child with a
new catheter each time he grows.
- Put in enough from the start.
- Dr. Cha is right.
Put in a long one.
Cut.
I will insert the catheter.
If the bile leaks,
it will be problematic.
What should we do to prevent that,
Park Shi On?
Two purse string sutures,
and also tunneling.
That's right.
Do just that.
The catheter is inserted.
Good.
- Finish, and close him up.
- Yes, sir.
Dr. Cha, good job.
You did much better than myself.
- No.
- Everyone, good job.
Good job!
Whether the result was
successful or not...
- that wasn't a perfect surgery.
- If you only look on the outside...
You're right.
But, I was sure.
That we would succeed.
Joon Young gave me this.
This was the ball he used
for his first hit.
I had it in my pocket during the surgery.
I kept thinking about this.
And because of this...
I couldn't leave the operating room.
Our team...
We enter that operating room
thinking about the children's future.
Unless we give up on the
children's future...
there's no reason for us to
give up on the surgery.
Hold still.
Aren't you embarrassed as the
top surgeon in our hospital?
Letting your wound get infected...
What's this?
Don't say anything.
Just treat it.
Getting stabbed for the sake
of a patient...
Getting the wound infected...
And the surgery on top of that...
Do you think you're Iron Man?
Even Iron Man thinks about
his own health.
You talk so much.
Unless you want to get hospitalized,
you should go home and rest.
There's no need.
You should take my advice!
Do you want to collapse again?
You'll only be a nuisance.
Nuisance.
Hold still.
His condition is worsening.
Soon, it will be hard for him
to move around.
You should visit him often.
You don't have much time.
Shi On.
I think I should take your father,
and go down to Tae Back.
What do you mean?
There's nothing else
that the hospital can do for him.
What good would it do
to stay here?
To you and to the director...
We are being a burden.
You can't do that.
You can't go.
If you are alone with him,
he may hit you again.
He won't do that anymore.
Soon, he won't even be able
to move around.
No.
Still, you can't do that.
Good job.
It'll be better for him to stay here
to lessen the pain.
You were thinking about
your mother, too.
I feel bad for both of them.
I feel bad for dad who lived alone
after mom left.
And I feel bad for mom who fled
from getting beaten by dad.
But, I'm getting mad thinking about
how I feel bad for them.
I'm very very angry.
Why?
If they abandoned me and lived alone
for 20 years, they should be happy.
If they lived without a stupid child
like me...
they should have led a comfortable life.
- Shi On.
- They are the ones who are stupid.
Mom and dad, both.
I feel better that you are angry.
I feel like I can count on you.
It seems like you now have the strength
to take care of your parents.
They can count on you now.
Please, Chairman...
All of the financial institutions
are turning us down.
When everything returns to normal,
we'll repay you.
Please.
I'm sorry, Chairwoman Lee.
I don't have any money I can spare.
I should pay you back for everything
that the late chairman did for me...
but right now, I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
He can't spare any money?
He's got a corporation that makes
over 100 billion won in LCD sales alone.
Forget it.
It doesn't make any sense.
Who helped him from going bankrupt
20 years ago?
Who can we blame?
It's all my fault.
Chae Kyung.
Thank you.
For staying by my side.
It's the video file for the pyriform sinus fistula
surgery that you asked for.
I see.
I heard your surgery was
very impressive.
Oh...
I know your fellowship years are hard.
But those times...
are crucial for a surgeon.
I'm doing fine.
But, Dr. Cha...
- Were you always this pretty?
- Excuse me?
Since what age were you this pretty?
Three years old?
Ten?
Since birth?
If I do say so myself...
- It was since birth.
- I knew it!
I knew you were a natural born beauty.
Have a good day.
Yes...
It's back to normal now.
From now on, make sure you don't
skip any medication.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Why are you staring at me like that?
It's nothing.
Dr. Park.
I...
When I grow up, do you
think I'll be pretty like In Young?
You are already pretty.
- Then who's prettier, Dr. Cha or me?
- Dr. Cha.
That was so fast.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to respond so quickly.
What's wrong?
What's bothering you about
In Hye's condition?
I can't pinpoint what it is.
It feels like I left the house with the gas on.
Like I left the PC store without logging off.
And like I ate triangular rolls
without checking the expiration date.
- How can I understand if you say that?
- We can't have the surgery yet.
We should thoroughly examine her
before having the surgery.
There wasn't anything wrong
when we ran the tests two weeks ago.
And it's not enough to go
just on a hunch.
The HPB department can operate on In Young.
But, can we operate on In Hye?
I want to do that, too.
Dr. Cha.
I have a request.
What is it?
Tell me you will okay it.
Dr. Park here is in charge of In Hye.
He has something to tell you.
What is it?
Compared to other patients,
In Hye's always been more prone to infections.
That means that her immune system
is not great.
If she happens to have the idiosyncratic form,
she may get infected during the transplant.
And considering that it's a pediatric transplant,
we need to prepare...
These guys...
Did you hear or not?
Who are you to say anything
when your leader is quiet?
No...
- We just wanted you to consider...
- Cha Yoon Seo.
Worry about yourself.
You should worry about
not causing another table death.
How can you say that?
I don't want to hear
that kind of an insulting comment.
- You should apologize to Dr. Cha...
- What?
Dr. Park.
We'll be going.
I'm sorry.
Listen to him talk...
Hey!
Where are you going?
I'm going to make him apologize.
Why are you so easy to anger
these days?
It's okay if he says something
bad about me.
But I can't stand to see him
talk badly about you!
Here.
Don't look so mad.
I feel nauseous.
Why do you want to put me in the
chairman position for the Sung Won Foundation?
There's nobody else who knows about
the hospital and the foundation as much as you.
You devoted your whole life
to the foundation.
Chairwoman Lee and General Manager Yoo
are the ones who betrayed you.
I don't doubt that you'll
do a good job.
Please reconsider.
He's not fit for a chairman position.
It's only temporary.
I'll kick him out once we are done
with personnel restructuring.
Didn't you guarantee succession
for existing employees?
Situations always change.
If anything goes wrong,
call me right away.
Seriously...
I told you to go home!
I'm going to check this,
and then leave.
Why do I get so many complaints that
the sheets don't get changed in time?
We're short staffed because all
the rooms are full.
Again?
Another excuse?
- If I get another claim...
- Boss!
Hyung Mi.
Do you know how much
I've been looking for you?
How did you find me?
- Oh my...
- You still haven't lost your touch.
You're still great!
Who are these people, Senior?
Why are you talking to our
boss like that?
How dare you?
Hey!
She's just calling me Senior.
Follow me.
Consider me dead.
- Don't come here anymore.
- Boss.
I'm not going to use my fists anymore.
I want to live here happily
with the children.
If you come here again,
I'll crush all of you.
Hyung Mi.
You should stop your ways,
and live like a human being.
Like a human being.
Boss.
Oh my God...
They were my neighborhood friends
from my childhood.
Who knew they would come visit?
Nurse Nam.
I'm busy.
I have to go.
Joon Young...
The surgery went well.
But, there's something I didn't tell you.
What is it?
It'll be hard for you to continue
playing baseball.
You can't move around too vigorously.
I knew that.
How?
Joon Young.
I know that you are sad because
you can't fulfill your dreams.
But, you know what's great
about dreams?
The fact that you can have
other dreams.
Just as you dream when you're sleeping...
you can have other dreams.
You are not abandoning your dreams,
just dreaming again.
Look.
This is the first ball
that you hit.
You can make another 'first'.
I don't know what that is yet.
But you have to give me that
as a gift later on.
Okay?
That's why I decided to
dream a different dream.
I'm going to study hard,
and become a baseball reporter.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I thought you would be worried
if you knew.
That's why I didn't tell you.
It's okay.
Joon Young, you are so cool.
Hello.
My name is Park Shi On,
and I'll be in charge of Seung Hyun.
I see.
Please take good care of him.
If you need anything let me know.
Okay.
But, you talk sort of funny.
Yes.
Did Seung Hyun urinate?
No.
Then, he must urinate quickly.
It's not good to keep it in for too long.
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of surgeries.
It's hard for me to make time.
Yes, it's hard to check
my text messages, too.
Yes.
Okay.
Good bye.
Why didn't you make any sound?
Were you talking to
Prosecutor Voldemort?
Oh...
Yeah, he wanted to see me again.
I see.
Are you going to meet him again?
No!
Why would I?
Then, why didn't you tell him that
when you were on the phone?
You should make it clear that
you don't like him.
That's true.
I'll do that next time he calls.
But, why were you eavesdropping?
I wasn't eavesdropping.
I heard it even outside the door.
Then, you should have
blocked your ears.
Did Professor Kim go home?
Yes.
Oh, right!
Did you hear what
Professor Kim said to Joon Young?
About dreams?
It's abalone porridge.
You should eat.
You are taking strong medicine,
so you need to eat.
Why aren't you on call at the hospital?
Who gave you permission to come out?
I didn't think you would eat
if you were alone.
I know well because I live alone.
I don't eat sometimes because
it's bothersome.
You're too relaxed.
I must have been too lenient on you.
No, I'm not too relaxed.
I'll go to the hospital right after.
Oh, right!
I heard about what you said to
Joon Young.
About dreams...
It was so very touching.
- You are such a great doc...
- Don't you dare put it up!
Oh...
I'm sorry.
You should go in.
Okay.
But, you are like a big brother to me.
Since the day you saved me
from those thugs.
My brother did the same for me.
I'm always thankful.
I'll be quickly leaving then.
Your fever's all down,
so you'll be getting the surgery soon.
You still don't want to
get the surgery?
No.
Then, are you still in a bad mood?
Dr. Han.
I...
All of a sudden,
I'm afraid of dying.
Why would you think that?
When I fainted at
Dr. Cha's house.
It was for a second, but I felt it.
I felt fear.
I felt like everything in this world
was disappearing.
In Hye.
Don't worry about that.
Dr. Han.
Do you think I'll ever be happy?
In Young and I?
Of course.
Excuse me.
In Hye must be feeling
weak-hearted.
The children get anxious
when their surgery dates approach.
If it's normal, that's fine.
But, I see such a sudden change in her.
I'll try to coax her.
Don't worry so much.
Dr. Han.
Yes?
Are you sleeping well?
Yes.
I'm sleeping well.
I see.
Then...
Then why didn't you tell him that you're not
going to see him when you were on the phone?
You should make it clear
that you don't like him.
That kid...
Yelling at me for nothing...
You...
You're really not upset?
Are you sure?
I haven't been around, right?
In Hye, you should stay in bed.
I should get some exercise now.
- Okay.
- It's hard for you to bear it now, right?
It's written on your forehead.
'I'm having such a hard time. '
No.
It's okay.
One-sided love is truly a hard thing.
That's true.
It's hard.
It's very hard.
Of course, I was wrong to do that.
But, I wanted to keep you around.
I thought you would make a
great surgeon.
You came to sleep?
No, I came to get my book.
You are lying to me now?
No, it's true.
Stop lying, and go to sleep.
Instead of nodding off in the morning.
- Producer Kim, did you decide on the piece?
- Yes.
Peter Pan.
Why?
If we do that,
we'll have to get dressed up funny.
It's still better than
last year's Cinderella.
Remember when Dr. Cha sprained her ankle
wearing that glass slipper?
I heard you were so embarrassed that you
got acupuncture instead of getting treated here.
Who said that?
Professor Kim.
He's got such a big mouth.
Dr. Park, you have to participate, too.
I can do a good job.
At the orphanage Christmas shows,
I was always the main character.
Dr. Park, you must be some actor...
First, I'll put the casting on the
bulletin board.
Hey!
Do it right, so there are no fights.
Okay.
Professor Kim won't participate
again this year?
Should we push him?
I won't do it!
Don't even think about it.
He's so sharp.
He'll do it.
- Pumpkin.
- Pirate!
Tell him to do something like that.
Dr. Park.
Joon Young, I have a request.
What is it?
Whoever comes to acquire the hospital, we
should side with them if will improve the hospital.
A for-profit hospital is an improvement?
Before it becomes for-profit, if we introduce
the charge-per-diagnosis system
the situation will worsen.
When the quality of service falls,
and private insurances gain power...
the hospital will naturally
become for-profit.
I agree with Chief Kim.
Without having to go the round-about way,
it may be better to take this route.
It'll provide a better environment.
How many times do I have to tell you
that the environment is not everything?
We are talking about forming a
for-profit children's hospital.
Does it make sense to discriminate
patients based on their income level?
Are you a doctor,
or a consumer representative?
Now, now...
We are getting off the topic of the
agenda for today.
The agenda for today is regarding the action
we will take as a collective group of doctors.
We need to communicate our decision
to the investors, and protest...
This is not something we can solve
by protesting.
But we should be adamant about our stand.
How can we do that when we
can't agree on anything?
Professor Kim!
Is there anything I can help you with?
I would have helped you out in there
if I knew something...
I'm afraid the only way I can help you
is to add to your head count.
It'll be helpful if you can
side with my position.
Of course, I'll do that.
The one leading the pack is always the one
going through the most trouble...
But, not everyone can
lead the pack...
If the wrong person becomes the leader,
it becomes a mess.
Thank you.
Look at that...
I knew it...
That damn kid...
Hello.
Dr. Park.
Yes?
Do you still think that I'm a bad guy?
Just like a half fried-half spiced chicken,
I feel that way about you.
I guess the bad half is because
of the work I do...
What's the good half about?
For believing in Professor Kim
and our team.
I'm most grateful to people
who believe in me.
If you believe in me,
I feel strengthened and full.
Full?
Yes, having faith is like the pump
used to put air in a bicycle tire.
If you fill up the tire with air,
you can speed along with force.
About In Hye's surgery...
Can you talk to Chief Kim again?
Do you remember that mess we went through
with Chief Kim regarding Dong Soo?
Of course. You even had to go to
the disciplinary committee.
Then, are you afraid that
there may be a problem again?
No.
I'm waiting until we have a just cause.
Excuse me?
There was a rumor back then.
Regarding the preemie with
necrotizing enteritis...
People say that you returned him because
you lacked the confidence to operate on him.
And...
they are saying that you didn't want to get
blamed if anything went wrong with the surgery.
That helped me to make
a firm decision to have the surgery.
Not because my pride was hurt,
but because I had a just cause.
A just cause to be responsible
for that patient.
You were planning to do it all along.
But a just cause must be backed up by
a strong basis and an alternative plan.
We had definite medical basis.
And Park Shi On had suggested
a good alternative.
That's why...
I'm working on finding a
just cause to operate on In Hye.
It won't take long.
Professor Kim, you are the best!
You better not put that up.
Why are you all acting so childish?
You heartless kid...
- You don't even show your face?
- You told me not to come over to your house.
You still should have visited!
Do you know how much your sister
grilled me?
- That's not my concern...
- What?
I'm giving you one last chance.
Get rid of everyone that's in our way.
Why...
- Why should I do that?
- Just do it!
If things work out, you won't
just become the director of a branch...
you may become the director
of this hospital.
So, do it right.
Don't make any mistakes!
I don't have any other wishes.
You don't need to apologize to me.
Just don't hit mom.
If you do that,
I'll be grateful to you.
Did you eat lunch?
Shi On.
I didn't eat yet.
I was going to eat after I was done.
I didn't eat, either.
Really?
Then, let's sit.
No.
Let's go out,
and eat together.
Why did you bring me out to eat?
Today...
Today is my payday.
You worked so hard to earn that money.
You shouldn't spend it like this.
Hurry, and eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
You don't need to make me
the potato soup.
Anytime you want to eat something good,
let me know.
There's one thing I want to ask you.
After you left home,
why didn't you come back to get me?
I want to know the real reason.
I wanted to go back
to find you.
But I heard a rumor that
your brother was looking for me.
If I came before you and the director,
I thought something bad might happen.
I'm shameful...
But I had no choice but to believe that
the director would take good care of you.
I'm sorry, Shi On.
From the beginning, I knew there was
something wrong with the way he talked.
How can you put someone like that
in charge of my child?
Dr. Park Shi On is a great resident.
You don't need to worry.
Would you put your child in
the hands of a handicapped doctor?
How can you say that?
Dr. Park Shi On is in charge
of my child, too.
Mine, too.
Dr. Park has no problems.
He's so good to the children,
and does a great job treating them.
Mind your own business.
I don't want him.
We'll change the doctor for you.
You can change your child's doctor
if you wish.
Dr. Cha, please do as she wishes.
Are you okay?
I'm really okay.
The ones who know me well
trust me.
But it's possible for people
who don't know me to react that way.
I can totally understand.
It doesn't hurt me anymore that
I'm different from other people.
If I do a good job,
people come to trust me, too.
That's what I'm saying.
But, there's one thing
that hurts me.
About being different...
Never mind.
It's nothing.
I think he's fine.
But, I'm a bit worried that
he might have gotten hurt.
I think he'll be fine.
Park Shi On is free from his
handicap now.
He's got a good sense of
who he is.
More importantly...
Park Shi On's genius ability...
It's not the absolute anymore.
What do you mean?
I trained him to develop that ability.
That was the only way
for him to survive.
But, I don't think
that's true anymore.
Before, all he had was his
genius ability.
But now, he's got much more than that.
So even if he loses that ability,
he'll still be a great doctor.
Even if he lacks a little bit.
Like what you said before...
I guess this is the second option
you mentioned.
Second option?
First option, a superior doctor
with no common sense.
Second option...
An average doctor
who can reason well.
The second option here.
That was a good sleep.
I...
I'm really not here to sleep.
Fine.
I'm craving something spicy...
- Hey!
- Yes?
Go home, and bring back some
spicy beef stew.
Right now?
Yes.
That was pretty good.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Let's sleep some more.
It doesn't hurt me anymore that
I'm different from other people.
But, there's just one thing
that hurts me.
About being different...
Before...
I didn't get to tell you.
I'm sorry.
The one thing that hurts me
about being different from others.
It's because of you.
I'm really okay now
being different from others.
It doesn't hurt me anymore.
But...
Whenever I see you,
it hurts me.
If I was a really cool guy,
I would be able to make you happier.
I would be able to do
more things for you.
I would sing you a lot of
great songs.
While we are on the topic...
It's a bit embarrassing,
but let me sing you a song.
I'm not good.
But, it's a song that
I really want to sing for you.
If I were the sky...
I would want to
remain on your face...
Like the reddening sky
of the sunset...
I would want to
paint your cheeks...
Whatever it may be...
I want to become for you.
If we are together like this,
it's the greatest happiness to me.
My love...
Do you know?
About my feelings for you?
Let's go!
It'll be so good.
- I just have an average role.
- Why am I #2 again?
- Pirate #2?
- Hey, don't complain.
The producer has every right to
cast as she wants.
Park Shi On!
I'll do a good job.
I'll put my soul into it.
But, who's going to play the part
of Captain Hook?
Just wait.
Right, Dr. Park?
Who is it?
Who?
Our hidden card.
Joon Young...
It's my wish.
I want to see you in the skit.
I think that would make me
really happy.
I think I'll be able to heal sooner.
Can I do something else for you?
Forget it.
I won't watch the skit.
I'll just take the medicine, and sleep.
Peter Pan!
The pirate is coming!
He must have a big crew.
What do we do?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of him
once and for all!
Captain!
This is Peter Pan!
I see.
Peter Pan, this kid.
Pull out the sword.
Professor Kim!
Why are you reading the parenthesis?
Don't you know anything?
I know.
I was just trying to make it perfect
for our practice.
I hate to say this,
but you are a bit like a hole.
A hole at least two meters wide.
Were you all good from the start?
Even if it's for kids...
You call this a script?
There's nothing wrong with the script.
It's fine.
Never mind.
Let's start from the beginning.
Fine, get on the boat.
Again!
Let's try again.
Cue!
Help!
Captain Hook's coming!
He must have a big crew.
What do we do?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of him
once and for all!
Captain!
This is Peter Pan!
I see.
Peter Pan, this kid.
Michael, take care of the rest.
What's wrong with me?
In Hye,
why are you out here?
My back hurts from
laying down too much.
Then stay here for a while,
and go back in.
Dr. Cha!
Come and have a seat.
What is it?
Dr. Park is hurting a lot.
More than the kids who are sick here.
I'm better now.
But, I'm still not good with
expressing my emotions.
But these days,
I think that it's a good thing.
Dr. Cha won't see.
But sometimes...
I wish I could show her my heart.
But when I get the chance,
I can't do that.
You see...
I wish there was a neon sign
on my chest.
He said he wishes you could see it
loud and clear.
What a fool.
You didn't go home, yet?
I'm going now.
It's getting late.
You should hurry home.
It's late.
You don't want to walk me?
I'll walk you out to the door.
No, walk me all the way home.
What?
Okay.
Is something wrong?
Yes.
May I ask what it is?
Some foolish kid
is making me feel so frustrated.
Who dares to make you
feel that way?
I know...
There's just this kid.
That's not good.
I want you to feel good at all times.
But, I don't feel good.
What?
Shi On.
Why do you always pretend to be okay,
when I know you are hurting?
Am I the one who is making you
feel frustrated?
Who else is next to me?
I told you before...
I was trying not to make you
feel uncomfortable.
Stop thinking about putting a neon sign
on your chest.
Just tell me honestly.
Then, you will...
What?
You're afraid I won't see you then?
No.
I'll continue to see you.
As much as you...
Because I want to see you, too.
You don't know who makes me
both smile and cry these days, right?
You don't know who makes my heart
ache these days, right?
Of course, not.
I think it's because of me.
Since the beginning,
I was lacking in a lot of things.
But, you took good care of me
like a little brother.
I think I made you worry about me
too much.
It's not because I think of you
as a younger brother.
Then, what is it?
These days...
I've become quite strange.
Well, not strange...
Something like that...
I mean...
It bothers me when you are
close to other women.
And it bothers me when you ask me
to set you up on a blind date.
That's how I feel.
Now, I don't want you to
lean on me anymore.
Now...
I...
I want to...
Subtitles by DramaFever