[English subtitles are available]
[Love you seven times]
[Episode 24]
Do you think you can escape
with such petty tricks?
Who are you?
Why did you lock Zihui up here?
It's none of your business.
He is our friend.
We must take him away today no matter what.
I was going to spare your lives
for old times' sake.
But since you are so ungrateful,
none of you will be able to leave today.
Here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
From now on,
you are mine.
Understand?
[Find Zihui]
Zihui.
I'm already very content
to have met you in this life.
[Tomb of my beloved wife, Xie Yingshi]
Your beloved lover
had long been killed by me.
My motive from the beginning
is to take your Stone Heart.
It's you.
You remember now?
Yes.
I remember everything.
I remember who I am
and who you are.
You assumed Yingshi's appearance and approached me back then.
Everything you did
was just for taking my heart.
It's not like that.
I have my reasons.
I was forced to do all this.
You have already taken my heart.
And now you're locking me up here.
Were you forced to do this too?
Your Stone Heart
can resurrect our clan's empress Cang Hai.
Until Cang Hai is resurrected,
you and your Stone Heart will never be at peace.
I've found out that
the Demon Realm might have a way
to resurrect Cang Hai.
Your Stone Heart won't be needed then.
You're still trying to lie to me now?
What do you take me for?
I may have lied to you before,
but I've never let you down.
Zihui.
Trust me one more time.
Fine!
Give me back my heart now.
Then, I'll trust you.
Why are you so silent?
Because you think this heart is useful to you now,
and that I'm naive and foolish.
You think I don't deserve to possess this heart
or even to possess memories.
You think I don't even have the right to hate you.
So, what about everything that happened between us?
When you stood here,
while assuming Yingshi's appearance,
and made those promises to me. What were they all for?
Or was everything just a lie?
Your heart is just like your face.
They're all fake.
You've never loved me.
If you think it's all fake,
then I have nothing to say.
Why don't you dig out your heart and have a look,
to see if it's real or not?
Fine.
Dig it out for me.
Why won't you do it?
Because you are Zihui.
You know
what happened between us are not fake.
Stop lying to me.
I can't return the Stone Heart to you.
Because I harbor a guilty conscience,
and erased your memories.
It's my fault.
You're right.
You have the right to hate me.
But remember,
you're Zihui.
You are kind,
but not foolish.
The Sparrow Head Ginseng can help you restore your demonic power.
Take good care of yourself.
We'll meet again.
What secret is Jin Luo hiding?
Who's trying so hard to take my heart?
I will definitely find out everything
and get my heart back.
Why don't you come with us?
Although we don't know
how long we will stay in the State of Qi,
I'm worried about you being alone.
Miss.
Sect Leader.
I will never forget
your kindness.
But I have my own plans.
If our fate hasn't ended,
we will definitely meet again.
Where are you going?
It wasn't easy for us to get you out.
What if you get caught again?
Don't worry, Miss.
I'm no longer that
ignorant man I used to be.
We should respect his decision.
Take it.
This...
Just take it.
Always be careful.
Don't be impulsive.
See you again.
I'll take my leave.
If we win this battle,
can we really gather the two jade pendants together?
Could Li
have left a clue in the Scale Nine Peaks?
Maybe,
or maybe not.
The State of Wei is coming at us aggressively,
and the Empress Dowager and the Emperor are suspicious of each other.
The people are innocent.
The State of Qi is in danger.
We can't just stand by and do nothing.
I know.
Since we're here in the mortal world for a tribulation,
we have to shoulder this responsibility.
Your Holiness.
Were you
looking for me?
I just received news
that Immortal Li
met a Great Demon during his tribulation in the mortal world...
and has died.
H-he is dead?
He didn't win the fight against the Great Demon?
Wasn't he practicing some great move?
He did use a great move.
But he perished together
with that Great Demon.
Well, that makes sense.
Immortal Li
was a civil official.
His martial arts skills were very shallow.
He must have tried his best.
Yes.
Even you think Immortal Li's magic
was weak,
let alone others.
For his reputation,
you must say
you saw it with your own eyes.
Yes.
[General's Mansion]
Here.
It seems that every time before we part,
we drink and admire the moon.
Yes.
You liked to do this when you were Lu Changkong.
Why are you laughing?
I remember someone once said
he's not Lu Changkong.
But I know
Lu Changkong is a part of you.
Have you already
fallen in love with me since then?
Actually, I always knew who I am
and what are parts of me.
But...
But was your pride too strong
or was it too awkward
for you to admit it?
Listen carefully.
When you return to court after winning the battle,
remember to come and drink the Crabapple Flower Wine
I made!
Do you hear me?
Yes, I heard you.
You're so noisy.
[Loyalty, Righteousness, Benevolence, and Bravery]
If you have something to say, just say it.
Don't keep it to yourself.
In the front line this time,
Wei's troops are several times that of Qi's troops.
You must be very careful.
I know.
By the way,
Grand General of Zhenyuan
works for the Empress Dowager.
He will be on his guard against you.
You should be careful about that too.
I know.
Now the enemy is in front of us.
Although Grand General of Zhenyuan is estranged from the Emperor,
he's still a general of the State of Qi.
Protecting our country and people is the most important responsibility.
As for Xinran,
I've already sent someone to keep an eye on her.
Don't worry too much.
[Loyalty, Righteousness, Benevolence, and Bravery]
General.
It's time to depart.
I'll get going.
Don't see me off.
Keep this
with you at all times.
[Loyalty, Righteousness, Benevolence, and Bravery]
I know it's just a tribulation.
Even if you die on the battlefield...
Chu Kong!
you'll just return to the Immortal Realm.
But why
am I still unable to bear for you to leave?
I'll wait for you to come back.
Your Majesty. Your Highness.
I've got news from the front line
that General Chu Kong won the first battle.
Our army's morale was greatly boosted.
But...
But what?
It's just that
after the State of Wei's defeat,
they immediately reinforced with 100,000 troops.
The front line
is hard-pressed.
If the State of Wei is defeated,
Xinran and her backers
will definitely make a move.
Then, you can make good use of the opportunity
to get them all in one go.
Chu Kong is brave and skillful in battle
and resourceful.
He will definitely return safely.
The Qi soldiers are risking their lives fighting against the enemy in the front line.
There's not much I can do to help.
Tomorrow, go to Daguo Temple with me
to pray for the soldiers.
Mother, you can't do that.
Why not?
Are you still hiding something from me?
Mother.
Do you still remember Xinran?
[Daguo Temple]
It's you?
Ridiculous.
She caused you to have a miscarriage
and is a spy from the State of Wei.
How could you have let her go?
Mother, calm down.
We did it for the big picture.
If she didn't bring the fake information back to the State of Wei,
we wouldn't have
gotten our first victory this easily.
Then where is Xinran now?
Chu Kong has already sent someone to keep an eye on her.
Unfortunately, she found out
and went into hiding.
Now the enemy is in the dark, while we're in the open.
Mother, you must not leave the palace.
It's too dangerous.
In that case,
all the more should I get out into public.
You've finally shown up.
I wanted to spare you for a few more days.
But since you're asking for your death,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
You should just surrender.
You can't escape.
What I hate the most
is your arrogant attitude.
How dare you speak to me like that?
Do you think that just because you're the princess of Qi,
that everyone has to listen to you
and obey you?
Even my Chu Kong has changed.
It's all because of you.
I was so good to Chu Kong.
But in the end, he repaid my kindness with ingratitude.
He pretended to let me go
and even got me to send back fake information,
causing me to make a big mistake.
Today,
I will kill you and the Empress Dowager
to redeem myself.
Your conspiracy will never succeed.
Really?
Mother.
Do you know the situation that Chu Kong's currently in?
If you want to save Chu Kong,
help me kill the Empress Dowager.
Then, I'll find a way to save Chu Kong's life.
Although our army was tricked by you,
and suffered great losses,
the State of Wei still has countless elite soldiers.
No matter how powerful and strong
Chu Kong is,
how can he defeat the State of Wei's
hundreds of thousands of soldiers?
You went to such great lengths
to get my mother killed,
in order to shake the foundation of the State of Qi
and cause civil unrest in the State of Qi.
In this way, you can win without a fight,
while the State of Qi
will be devastated
and its people will be in misery.
These
are everything Chu Kong doesn't want to see.
Even if you capture Chu Kong,
he wouldn't let me
sacrifice
the lives of Qi's people for his life.
Don't waste your energy.
Fine.
Since I'll die anyway,
I will kill the Empress Dowager today
and let everyone in the State of Qi
die with me!
Brother.
Mother.
Sorry I'm late in my rescue.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Mother.
I told Brother to come.
Zhi!
Brother!
What did you
call me just now?
Guards!
Escort His Majesty back to the palace.
Yes.
Hurry.
You will never...
see Chu Kong ever again.
Chu Kong promised me.
He won't break his promise.
A military letter from the border.
General Chu Kong
used 3,000 elites as bait
to enact the stratagem of luring the tiger out of the mountain
and lured Wei's elite soldiers into the forest.
The remaining troops
made use of this chance when Wei's headquarters were unguarded
and advanced straight to the enemy's capital,
[Qi]
and captured the Emperor of Wei who came to supervise the battle.
Now,
the State of Wei has signed a Letter of Surrender.
They've promised that for a hundred years,
they'd never invade the borders of the State of Qi.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty. Your Highness.
This year's harvest is bountiful.
There are great grain harvests everywhere.
Five million dan of grains from eight prefectures
have all been expropriated.
But the transportation of grains by water is not smooth.
I'm afraid it'll be hard to reach the capital.
You can make the decisions.
Grains are the foundation of our country.
The transportation of grains by water cannot be obstructed.
Minister Li.
You will supervise the Ministry of Works
in checking the finances
and clearing the rivers as soon as possible
to facilitate the transportation of grains by water.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You may leave.
Son.
I'm not as capable as I used to be.
The world
will depend on you from now on.
I
won't let you down.
Brother.
Can I have a look?
Nursery rhyme?
Thank you, Brother.
Mother.
Let me play another round with you.
Come on.
You can't go easy on me this time.
Yes.
Chu Kong.
Now, the Empress Dowager and Emperor are united in heart and mind,
and the State of Qi is prosperous and the people are in peace.
It's only until today
that I truly understand
the righteousness you seek.
Yun.
The front line has said that
although Chu Kong is seriously injured,
he's safe.
The State of Qi still has some military conflicts that need to be dealt with.
Chu Kong prioritized the country over his family.
He's a good man of the State of Qi with an indomitable spirit.
I know you love him deeply.
But as a country's princess,
you should know how to prioritize the overall situation.
Just wait in peace.
When the war has completely subsided,
Chu Kong will return.
At first, as a mortal,
I thought there were too many things
that were beyond the control
of one's will.
But after this experience,
I realized the responsibility on one's shoulders.
Even a country's general in the mortal world is like this,
let alone the God of War of the six realms.
Chu Kong.
For tens of thousands of years,
in order to protect the peace of the six realms,
you must have made a lot of painstaking effort that no one knows about.
Cang Hai is about to be resurrected.
All the more can't I let you worry about me
and hurt your primordial spirit.
[Mother]
Mother.
Brother.
I hope this letter finds you well.
I was fortunate to have received the love and kindness
from two elders like you in this lifetime.
Now that you two have reconciled your previous disagreements,
I have no other wishes.
Although I can't bear to say goodbye to my old friends,
I have something more important to do.
If we're destined in the future,
we'll definitely reunite again.
Chu Kong.
Let's consider that the Crabapple Flower Wine I owe you
has been made up for.
When you return to court after winning the battle,
remember to come and drink the Crabapple Flower Wine
I made!
I'll wait for you to come back.
Chu Kong.
I have to leave first this time.
You must live on well.
Xiangyun.
This is all I can do for you.
You can only rely on yourself for the rest of the time.
This time,
you must live on well.
[Qi]
♫Brighter than the moon was your face♫
♫When you said goodbye♫
♫And turned around to leave♫
♫Missing you in the cool wind♫
♫I know I can never see you again♫
♫Tears stream down my face♫
♫We were the perfect match♫
♫But the unpredictable fate pulled us apart♫
♫Stumbling on the way to you♫
Why are you back so soon?
Is your primordial spirit okay?
♫I found myself trapped by love♫
I'm fine.
♫I don't regret meeting you♫
What about you?
I think I'm fine too.
♫I'll wait for you my whole life♫
That's great.
♫Our love is already water under the bridge for you♫
♫Can you hear my wistful sighs?♫
♫Do you wish we could start all over?♫
♫Does the one giving more have to end up with a broken heart?♫
♫You left at sunset♫
♫My heart grew cold because I knew our story ended♫
♫Your face faded in the wind♫
I have something to ask you.
Didn't you promise me
you would come back alive?
Why did you follow me back here
from the tribulation?
I should
be the one asking you this.
Didn’t you say you would wait for me to come back
and drink your Crabapple Flower Wine?
Then if I
came back here earlier than you on purpose,
what would you do?
Then of course...
I'll tear down your Marriage Pavilion.
That Li.
Seriously.
It's all his fault for writing such a ridiculous script in the Fate Book.
He wrote me out so hastily.
If I find him,
I will...
I don't even know
where he is now.
Don't worry.
We will know the whereabouts of Immortal Li soon.
Your Divinity.
Have you found any clues?
Li worked hard to write his Fate Book.
It's impossible that
it's just to let us
go down there for a stroll.
Judging from the State of Qi's situation alone,
there seems to be no problem.
It's still in his
indescribable style.
Yes.
A general and a princess.
It's obviously Li's style.
And
the Scale Nine Peaks.
The Scale Nine Peaks?
It's a nursery rhyme.
A nursery rhyme!
What nursery rhyme?
The clue Li left us is a nursery rhyme.
Mr. Grievance
herds the cows.
He walks the cows at 9 p.m. every day.
The cow headbutted the grain warehouse and the maize is roasted.
His parents want him to switch to fishing.
Mr. Grievance went into the water to gather the fishing net
and fished out a wooden man.
In other words,
the nursery rhyme contains
the clues he left for us?
After combining the Tiger Tally,
the words "nursery rhyme" sparkled.
I think
Li is a lazy person.
He wouldn't write beyond what's necessary.
Why would he
write such a
seemingly mysterious
and irrelevant plot for no reason?
He has never written such things
in the Fate Book.
What does Li want to tell us?
He walks the cows at 9 p.m. every day.
Who would do that at night?
Stop frowning.
We will definitely find Immortal Li soon.
Sir.
I’m back.
Sir?
Sir.
I'm back!
[Marriage Pavilion]
I heard
you're looking for me.
Leave.
Lord Protector.
You are no match for him.
Retreat!
Yes.
What is the relationship
between you and Jin Luo?
So
Jin Luo didn't tell you.
It seems like
she still hates me, her brother, the most.
Brother?
You are Jin Luo's brother?
Why are you two
trying so hard
to get my Stone Heart?
Qianren!
What are you talking about?
Open the door, Mou.
You saved my life.
I'll repay it for you now.
Mou!
Mou, listen to me.
Mou, open the door!
Mou, come back!
Come back now!
I didn't ask you to repay me, Mou!
Qianren...
is already dead.
In the Shengling Sect,
we went through thick and thin together
and shared weal and woe.
Why?
Why did you take my Stone Heart?
Why did it have to be you?
Even if I used to be Qianren,
so what?
Everyone has their own inescapable mission.
The 20 years at Shengling Sect
is just an accident
that I had to go through.
How can it...
affect me?
In your eyes, was everything that Qianren and Qian Mou
went through
just a mere accident?
No matter how beautiful the time at Shengling Sect was,
you and I should understand that
it was just a dream in the mortal world.
You're not Qian Mou,
and I'm not Qianren.
I'm the Protector of the Moluo Divine Clan,
Jin Lian.
I shoulder the mission of the deep blood feud of the Moluo Divine Clan.
My life is dedicated to
seeking revenge
and reviving the Moluo Divine Clan.
What about me?
What am I in the eyes
of you and your sister?
You're just
a Nuwa Stone that can help me revitalize my cause.
Good.
Well said.
It was all my wishful thinking.
In the eyes of you two,
I'm nothing but...
a tool to help you complete your mission.
Give me back my Stone Heart.
Give me back my Stone Heart!
If you want the Stone Heart,
you'll have to lure Jin Luo out!
Do all the immortals
know about this?
Yes.
Immortal Li was lively
and quite popular in the Heaven Realm.
His death couldn't be concealed.
I'm afraid the news
has already spread to the Marriage Pavilion.
Your Divinity.
You came just in time.
Xiangzi...
Did she find out
about Immortal Li?
That girl has always been very close to Immortal Li.
Who knew...