I'm afraid that I'll be able to do anything.
I've loved you before.
During the holiday,
first, be careful.
Secondly, take a heart.
Don't just play around.
We're in the first place.
The second is the eye-catching.
How will it be later?
The third is coming.
You want to spend three years
or just spend one year?
You can count on yourself.
You've spent so much effort.
In the exam, you'll see what kind of results you have.
When you're ten years younger,
you'll be especially great.
I've started working hard since I was a high school student.
I'll play the instrument to listen to you.
Class begins now!
What do you think?
You've been home a few days ago.
What do you mean?
I've been home a few days ago.
I've been working on it a few days ago.
I like going home.
Do you want to follow me?
Sang Ye, where are you going?
You're going to make me lose my temper!
I'm not going.
I want to go home and study hard.
Are you having a fever?
Or are you going to go back to your room and get a fever?
It doesn't matter. I'll take care of you.
Are you sick?
Get out.
Where are you going?
To the airport. Let's go.
Sang Ye!
You don't have to study hard anymore.
Don't play football.
I'm going to study with you.
I'm going to make a living.
I'm staying at this house too.
Why didn't I save you in the living room?
I just said we were going to work hard.
Then we'll be serious next time.
Why are you still serious?
In case you miss the chance to go to the lake with me.
Where's your house?
What?
I'll stay at your house next time.
I don't care
There are some sausages as well as the Examina.
No weekends later
Sorry,
you had a great сказ por!
I don't know what you eat.
I don't have any other choice.
You don't eat coriander and garlic.
Thank you.
I don't eat coriander and garlic.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I'll pick it up for you.
Okay.
You and Zhao Guxi are not dead yet.
There are two of them.
We have a store and Qiao Qiao.
We start to take care of each other
since kindergarten.
She's used to it.
I often heard about the store called Dian Dian in Guangming.
It's a little bit of a game.
When she was a kindergarten,
she wrote the word Wen Yifan into four dots.
It's called Wen Dian Dian Dian Fan.
No.
It's Wen Dian Dian Dian Dian Dian.
There's a dot in the word.
Thank you.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
Have a look.
Look at the store.
Dian Dian, come.
Let's have a look at our old couple.
Okay.
Let's go out.
Eat.
Eat and you'll get your mouth full.
Yes.
Let's go to work.
I left a package for you.
Here.
You can take this.
Dian Dian.
You've been through a lot
with Sang Yanzhu.
Why didn't you pay him?
He didn't even eat just now.
He didn't even want to pay anyone.
He owed him 8 million.
Really?
Why do I feel that
he's quite suspicious?
He's not like that.
Why don't you go to Xiang Lang's house?
I mean you and Xiang Lang
can change the house.
Let him and Sang Yanzhu.
I can.
Forget it.
It's too troublesome.
I'm coming.
Don't do this.
Come on, everyone.
Let's taste our new product.
Yuzhuang, try it.
Here.
It's too famous.
This is Dai Xingmu fish.
Thank you.
This is a hammer.
This is a giant cake.
This is...
Wait a minute.
Who named this?
I did.
How about it?
I'll...
I'll give you a discount.
Let's play the real game.
How about it?
Okay.
Let's play.
Who?
Who are you looking at?
Come on.
I'll give you a discount.
It's okay.
We'll take care of you.
Come on, guests.
You go first.
Come on.
Five, six.
Eight, six.
Ten.
Open.
It's the first round.
It's not over yet.
Just open it.
Let's do it again.
Come on.
Nine, six.
Su Huan, you're not good at it.
You're really good at it.
Okay, we'll do it again.
You're so good.
Choose a person who is in the scene.
Pick me.
You can't play it, can you?
Who said I can't play it?
What are you doing?
Little...
Why are you so angry?
You've played games in college before.
You're so fake.
You're in college.
You're also in college.
Why did you forget me?
You're in the same department,
and you're in the same department.
You're the double-played player of the computer.
It's enough.
I'll finish it.
Come on, play it.
Come on.
Six.
Seven.
Open.
It's so small.
I'm hungry.
Are you serious or a big risk?
I'm serious.
I'll help you.
Tell me the advantages of each character.
Tell me the advantages.
Money.
Like a wolf.
Study well, grow up well.
Have confidence.
Didn't you say one?
What about you?
Cold.
Four.
Confidence.
Over the head.
Twelve.
Lin Tian.
Don't go up.
Fifteen.
You're so bad.
I'm bad.
Can you open it?
I dare not.
Open.
Five.
You won.
Think about it.
I'll say it.
I'm so angry.
Don't think about it.
Think about it.
Tell me about your regret.
The regret is
going to the National University.
We were going to go to the University of Yi He with Die Nian.
Why did you take her?
We were going to the National University.
Die Nian was going to the South China University with me.
Who knew she suddenly went to the University of Yi He?
I had already reported
the best clinical medical school in the University of Yi He.
But my parents insisted on letting me go.
Otherwise, I would have been in the same school
from kindergarten to university.
I couldn't have been in front of them.
Go in.
Yes, you go.
This is the treasure we lost
in the game of 7-1.
It's the real star flower.
It's the treasure.
Six.
Ten.
Fifteen.
Twenty-six.
Look.
You're done.
You finally lost.
Come on.
The real star flower is called the big forget.
The real star flower.
Recently,
I went to the city of the airport.
What a mess.
Who cares?
Yi He.
I do that too.
Your pair of arms are not quite active.
I thought
you were Thai or Thai.
I think so.
If that was the case,
I can train the kids to become spicy.
Izeiched the meeting
we drove from U...
I heard that Sang Yan paid for it.
Sang Yan paid?
I said Sang Yan only gave 99% discount.
It seems that I wronged him.
How about we write a five-star rating for him?
Can't we just take advantage of others?
I'll answer the phone.
Hello, Mr. Yi Qing.
Okay, I know.
I'll go home now.
I received a task at the time.
I'm going to tell the country.
I'll send you.
Hurry up.
Then you stay safe.
I'll send him a picture.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Then you stay safe.
Okay, you stay safe too.
Let's go.
Zhuang Xiao.
Why are you still here?
We're all invited.
I have to help you take some pictures.
I recommend it.
Good.
I'll treat you to a drink.
Stop.
What?
Didn't we say
we won't drink together?
Yes.
Drink it.
You're a guest.
You should drink it.
You just lost your love.
You're a drunkard.
I'm enough.
Otherwise, I can't drink alcohol.
I'm asking you.
Do you think it's weird?
I think it's a little bit.
I'm asking you again.
Why didn't you go to the dance studio?
Did you get so many results?
I'm his good friend.
But I can't think of anything.
I think he wants to stay away from everyone.
I don't even have much contact.
I thought
you two have changed.
You hate this kind of change the most.
Do you believe
when I talk about love,
I hope this is the last one.
But now,
no one believes that love has a guarantee.
If you do this,
you'll be under great pressure.
I want to have something good in my life.
Maybe I'll meet someone else.
You'll meet someone else.
Why do you ask me?
I'm a woman.
I don't talk about it.
I'm not going back to sleep.
Where are they?
They're back.
I have a question for you.
Do you still like to ask Fan?
I don't know.
I just think you still like to
find a chance to be together.
How many times have I said it?
Yes.
That's enough.
It's not normal
to be like this.
What about you?
I'll do it.
You look at people's faces.
They're not nose,
they're eyes.
They're like a wolf.
Are you crazy?
You're so stubborn.
I've never seen you like this.
Last time,
you were in the high school exam.
Do you remember?
You're busy recently.
I can't contact you all the time.
What happened to you?
No.
I'm busy with my phone.
Why are you here?
I can't contact you all the time.
I just want to be with you.
Don't worry.
I'll be there soon.
Didn't you say it before?
I'll pass after I get out of the exam.
But I'm out.
I'm in trouble.
I'm in terrible danger.
You've got a better result.
she may work though,
but after half an hour...
doesn't look起來,
very tears.
Your family's been heading out.
innovativeness wines.
Zeng Mijun has seen it.
Your mother can start a new life.
Another smallplay of your drinking?
In enlarged shape's case.
Do you want to eat fruit?
Brother Hao An is waiting for you.
Brother Hao An, do you want to eat fruit?
What about me?
Don't you want to tell me something?
Then I'll tell you directly.
Sang Yan, I hate you very much.
I also hate you very much.
You've always been here for me.
I'm also very annoyed that I have to come out and see you every time.
Wei Fan,
I'm your backup.
I'm going to a faraway place in the south.
I'll come to Yi He in the future.
I hope you won't come to me like this now.
You're back.
I don't reply to your messages or answer your phone.
I always go to the Internet.
Don't be so loud.
I'm going to the South China University.
South China University!
What's your attitude?
I'm not sure.
Brother, think about it.
We can be classmates.
You know I can do it.
I'm so happy that I can go to the South China University.
Do you know that when you said you wanted to go to the South China University,
I thought, what's wrong with it?
He can't answer the phone.
I'm sorry.
Ding Ding.
What?
Okay. Why?
I don't know.
You still have the same relationship with Zhi Qian.
It doesn't seem important to you.
You're not interested in anything.
I'm curious.
How can you be so careful?
Why do you say that?
Then tell me.
How's your life after you came back to South China?
It's good.
It's good again.
I'm asking you.
When I was abroad,
we only talked quietly.
You always said something good and good.
You didn't say anything about yourself.
Is my life boring?
You can say it if it's boring.
Our world is happy and laughable.
Crying when you're sad.
You're like the other world.
Ding Ding.
Can you promise me something?
Tell me.
If you find it hard to talk to me,
tell me the first time.
I don't want you to reject me.
Okay.
Can you tell me
that you were in South China University
when you were in the 70s?
Why did you change your mind
to study in the medical school?
Do you feel sorry for me?
You said you felt sorry for me.
When will you be in South China University?
Tomorrow is the third day of the third year.
The third day of the third year.
The fourth day of the third year.
The fourth day of the fourth year.
The third day of the third year.
I will be in South China University.
I heard that Zhang Xun's hospital is in the second floor.
Then we can make a deal
and work hard together to get into the fifth grade.
I will be in the second floor.
Please accept my request.
Why?
Why do you have to read it carefully?
Do you think it's not good?
Did I say I was going to pay?
Give me the big difference.
Zhang, this time our selection is eight.
I will come with you four.
You two will come.
See you next time.
The soil here is delicious.
Do you want to try it?
Not your !!!
You'll never leave your own home
I know
Not a song
Spend some time in your至
Live
Finally you got your WeChat
I'm a second grader.
I can learn more in the early days.
But I haven't done it in the early days.
I'll buy it on the way.
Bye.
See you.
Weird faces like Rowoo.
Looking good,の
Come in.
Show yourmetiquette to the Room Just Put Me Down
See that sound for yourselves?
I am hungry.
I can't talk.
I'll sit here.
How do I look?
I've been sitting here for a long time.
I'm not a good person.
The End
Miss Wen.
Someone is looking for you.
Wait there.
Jiang.
I thought you were still in the river.
How long have you been back?
Let me get the gas first.
Okay.
Thank you.
Miss Wen.
I heard Jiajia say
she saw you at the wetlands.
I saw your gas
in the TV station.
I thought I would come to visit you.
What do you want?
Today is not the New Year.
It's the Spring Festival soon.
How is your mother-in-law doing?
I want to introduce her to you.
Let you know.
I'm a good person.
Don't worry about me.
I didn't mean that.
You will know when you come.
Jiajia asked me to come with you.
It seems that you are getting the right one.
I...
I'm afraid that
you may not be in a good mood.
You may be in a bad mood.
So I...
I asked Jiajia first.
I'm going to work.
Jiajia.
You...
Are you still mad at me?
I...
I know that I have been
so sorry to you in the past years.
I...
You...
How can you forgive me?
I don't blame you.
You have the right to be happy.
I'm fine.
So...
So you promised to come to the house to celebrate the holiday?
Let's talk about it.
Go back and be cold.
You...
What do you want to eat?
Tell me.
Jiang.
You have to tell me
about the house you are in.
Who is it?
Xiao Wei Young.
Can't recognize him.
He has been sleeping for several days.
He is sleeping under the bed.
The house is in the past years.
Dian Dian.
I'm asking you.
Did you quarrel with Sang Yan?
No.
Then why did he keep sleeping
and not going back to work?
Did he sleep at home?
Yes.
If Sang Yan bullies you,
tell me.
I won't let him go.
You think too much.
I think too much.
What's wrong?
You never told me
how you got along with him.
We can't get along.
Actually, I think
we are like
two strangers under the same room.
And we don't have
much time to spend together.
Dian Dian.
Then we should say goodbye first.
You are not coming back again?
Subscribe.
don't forget to like.
See you.
Okay.
Dad,
Turn on the battery.
给你搬家.
你凭了我什么叫 ba個 cubed?
Enough.
Thank you for our luzto Di beauty.
It's not safe to go home.
You're a boy.
You should talk to yourself.
Don't be so serious.
You don't need to send me.
My ex is my family.
Qiao Qiao.
Where are you going?
Why don't you go home?
Who's your girlfriend?
Yes, a friend.
Hello.
Who is that grandpa?
Are you sleeping?
Come in.
Don't talk nonsense.
I thought you were here.
Come in and have tea.
Don't be polite.
Come on.
Okay.
Let's go.
Don't you really want to have tea?
Of course I don't.
I don't want to disturb them.
I will.
I'm leaving.
Good night.
Don't look.
You're so naughty.
Hello, grandma.
Are you going home?
I miss you so much.
Okay.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What's her name?
Her name is Wang Linlin.
She's my ex-girlfriend.
I miss her so much.
Her name is Wang Linlin.
Really?
I want to see her in a few days.
Thank you.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I will definitely change you.
Yes.
I will never expose you.
Okay. Thank you.
One two.
Me...
sis
You enjoy yourself.
Look.
In the last friendlike interview
did you horizontal TikTok
featured your credit rates?
Got a罵19
he picked up a hot moment.
He still left it in the spot.
God lambda!
In the good words
you've stood out
hot before you even were so.
It's a tough game.
It's really tough.
It's so tough.
Now everyone calls it a tough game.
Zhen didn't give him a massage.
Will it affect him?
No.
He's already lost to Tong Yun.
Look at him.
He's so handsome.
Go and get Liu Jie.
Liu Jie.
!!!
Do you have anything to say now?
I'm so shy.
I hope you can be like me too.
It's really interesting.
My sister and my mom like it.
They sent this video to our group.
You scared me to death.
Why are you back?
I'm the housekeeper of the flower house.
I'm not living here.
Then why don't you open the light at home?
I'm not going home.
You should be happy.
Why are there so many things?
Isn't the two layers mine?
I can't sleep well because I'm drinking coffee at midnight.
I'm so sleepy.
I should go to bed early.
Where's my coffee?
I drank it.
It's expired.
I threw it away.
You can drink it.
How much money do you need?
I'll transfer it to you.
No.
If I don't deal with the refrigerator,
I don't like waste.
Then let's buy it together.
How much money do you need?
I'll ask you to help me.
We've made a deal.
All my money is...
Help me.
Help me what?
Are we going to cook?
It's not 20 A Y
20 A Y
Jian Gui.
Guys,
we…
can't do much today.
Ouch.
Did you see Chenicao?
Stop talking!
You're in my second life.
Listen,
when can I win your heart?
Okay. But I'm too lazy to go that far.
Then it's boring for you to live alone for the New Year.
I'm going to sleep for three days and three nights. I'll work overtime.
But I can't sleep.
What about Sang Yan? Has he gone home for the New Year?
He must have. His family is in his own place.
I'm afraid he doesn't have a good relationship with his family.
Why did you suddenly mention Sang Yan?
You never told me how you've been with him.
We can't really get along.
Actually, I think we're like
two strangers in a room.
And we don't have much time to get along.
Six, three.
Ten, four.
Ten, five.
Ten, fifteen.
Twenty, six.
What are you shouting?
I already said that I'm not good at it. You won.
What do you mean by that? Are you going to teach me or open it?
Can't you see that I've been helping you? Open it.
I can't see it at all. Can't you just say it?
If it wasn't for me, you'd lose every time. Open it.
So is it...
Open it.
I finally won.
I lost.
Sang Yan finally lost.
I'm so embarrassed.
Come on.
Let's call it a day.
I'm so embarrassed.
Yueni.
Yang Yan.
quanto nila przypadara 360.
I'm not afraid of you
They don't want me to leave
You're always by me
Just next to me.
I first talked about it
Went to the training half a day
ión
I have the voice for you
How can I give up
I won't give up
Because you give me the blame
The future between you and me
Is the one you want to live
I pretend to be the same
Even if it's a wishful thought
I won't be lonely anymore
I'm afraid you'll be there
The darkness that can be seen through
The future between you and me