The most beautiful view.
Only you today?
Do you want to have a bowl of noodles?
I want to have a bowl of noodles today.
The bowl of noodles?
It's okay, let's have a bowl of noodles together.
Here.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Hello.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
You?
You're not. How can I lose to you?
I'm in the noodle restaurant now.
Don't make a deal.
I'll definitely...
discuss with you about my plan.
You...
You are properly respected,
But I especially couldn't oppose you.
I'm not afraid.
Here!
Thank you.
Do you like noodles?
Son of a bitch!
Don't have any sort of thing.
So comfortable.
I heard that your family is coming.
So?
So I'm going to pick you up
and become your next roommate.
Next...
...person.
I'm afraid that you'll get used to living here.
Don't you want to leave?
I haven't promised you that you can move in.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely become a better roommate.
I won't cause you any trouble.
I won't give you any trouble.
I can just turn around.
The kitchen is so big.
There's a whole kitchen and a washing machine.
Clean and clean.
Don't worry about washing dishes anymore.
A toilet machine.
Let me feed you.
Senior Sun, you should have a flat nose.
But it's very stressful for someone like you.
I'll have a bigger flat nose.
And he's usually very close to you.
Let me take a look at my future room.
I refuse.
Xiao Mu, you're making me feel so uncomfortable today.
And you're looking for Senior Sun.
You didn't...
You didn't say hello to Senior Sun.
I don't think that's good.
Yifan, you said that those things were all not a problem.
Now that you're a good roommate, you're much more difficult to find than a good house.
In the future, you can't find a good house.
You can't find a good house.
You can't find a good roommate.
In the future, you can become a roommate and add me to your family.
We can work together, work together, and cook together.
Isn't it good to take care of each other?
Xiao Mu, you should go back first.
If anything happens, wait until this room is really empty.
And I don't like to be in a relationship with men.
Then what about Senior Sun?
He... He's a special guest.
Don't do this again.
Bye-bye.
I never said that I would come to see you.
I don't know how he suddenly came here.
Maybe it was before that Tian Jie mentioned that I was looking for a roommate.
He heard it.
So...
So you just like my roommate?
Of course not.
But...
But your house is almost renovated.
I'm afraid if you suddenly move out,
I'll have to take over the house alone.
The house is already yours.
The rent is already yours.
So...
How long will you live?
How about you?
I hope I can live longer.
Or...
I'll wait for you to find a girlfriend.
It's not convenient to say that.
I'll go back to my room first.
Okay.
He will move out one day.
Why do you care?
Don't worry.
There is no one in the world that can be saved.
These are the two results.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be there for you.
You have to be mentally prepared.
Don't you know how to do it?
You have to save him.
You've tried your best.
I don't know what to do.
I don't want you to be saved.
Be careful.
The other person may be like his father.
The patient will be fine.
He will be in a state of no good.
He is 44 years old.
He will never leave me.
On March 11th,
at 14.04 pm,
Wu Xiao was released from the hospital.
Please keep your hands off.
Aqiang, hurry up.
I'll be waiting for you.
Be careful.
It's okay.
He may be like his mother.
He can have a better life for himself.
He chose to abandon me.
I hate people who are always separated.
They say goodbye.
Why don't we not get used to it?
We can't get used to it.
We shouldn't get used to it.
Don't be afraid.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see you.
A Sun's wife.
Sun's wife?
Yes.
Lingling.
Lingling!
Zhong Xiao.
Hello?
Zhong Xiao, I say the end.
I'm not free. You can find someone else.
Grandpa is at my house now.
He said he wanted to find Wang Linlin.
I forgot which time I was drunk.
I told him that we were married and we were meant to be.
We were meant to live together.
Please come to my house now.
I'm not free now.
What?
Please.
Please, this time.
Good night.
Grandpa, Linlin went to her house to celebrate her birthday.
She won't be back today.
I just want to wait for Linlin to come back.
By the way, let me ask you.
Why didn't you go to your parents' house to see your brother?
I'll find more time.
I'll go to my parents' house.
Really?
Yes.
I've heard from the management of my house.
In the past two years, there was no one else except me and your grandma.
Let me ask you.
Do you really dislike them?
I'm busy with work.
I'm really busy. You'll know when you come next time.
How busy you are!
Look, Linlin, you should finish your work.
You'll be late for the day.
Linlin, I don't want you.
Why are you coming back now?
Grandpa, I'm back.
Where did you go?
I only used the toilet paper at home.
I'm going to buy some today.
Didn't you go to your parents' house to celebrate her birthday?
Yes, I opened the supermarket at my friend's house.
She's celebrating her birthday today.
Xiao Han, go and buy some.
We'll have the best breakfast.
It's your birthday. I'll take you to your house.
Grandpa, you've bought a whole night.
You forgot?
It's been so long.
Grandpa, I'm not hungry.
Yes, he's not hungry.
What do you mean?
You can buy this bag for Linlin.
You can buy this bag for grandpa.
Go.
Go?
I'm so worried.
Linlin, I want to ask you a few questions.
Are you used to sleeping on the left or on the right?
On the right.
That's weird.
Xiao Han is a kid.
He sleeps on the right.
Yes, I know.
But I've been sleeping on the right since I was a kid.
So he let me sleep on the right.
What about your clothes?
Grandpa said it's not good looking.
He bought me new clothes.
So I'll take his clothes off for now.
It's loose and comfortable.
And it's sweet.
Are you hiding something from me?
Xiao Han, you're lying to me.
You're not living together, are you?
You're getting married soon.
What's your problem?
After you get married,
you can't sleep at night
when you sleep on the right.
You can't sleep at home
when you get off work.
You can't do housework.
Wang Xiaorou's bitter-skinned windmill
is a long-awaited story.
The house is so messy.
Grandpa, you're quite ahead of your thinking.
Grandpa is young.
Love is a nightmare.
Xiao Han has been doing things
since he was a kid.
He's been working hard
to hide his feelings.
Don't worry.
I know how to do it, Grandpa.
How did it change?
Don't worry.
I don't mind.
fiveís
Since when did you tie it up sotight?
I've cooked too much porridge. Help me eat some.
I'll just eat the pulse.
I'm going.
I can't get used to everything.
I was the best when I came back to the beginning.
I'm used to having his world.
Maybe one day, he'll disappear.
I'm used to being with him.
He'll disappear one day.
Good morning, Yifan.
Morning.
This is the breakfast I prepared for you.
I'll share it with you.
I've eaten it this morning. You can eat it yourself.
Just help me.
I can't finish it all.
Morning.
Morning, sister.
Where's the breakfast?
Have a taste.
He's done a lot.
Let me help you.
Okay. I haven't eaten it yet.
I'll have it.
Thank you, sister.
Yifan.
I'm sorry to say this.
Did you get into a fight with Sang Yan yesterday?
Yes.
But I just don't understand.
He's not warm at all.
Yifan, why do you have to be so serious?
Yifan, why do you have to feel wronged
to live with him?
You deserve better things.
I don't feel wronged.
Maybe I'm used to it.
Yifan, the God of Finance has come to you.
Morning.
Chengyu, did you have breakfast?
Did you buy two servings together?
Yifan, I hope you know how to treat yourself.
You need to look at yourself.
Who really treats you well?
Don't always think that others are bullying you.
This is bad habit. You have to change it.
Okay. Thank you, aunt.
And,
I think I should be able to distinguish
what is bad habit.
Director Shen,
I sent you a big interview last night
for the big company.
I've arranged the interview
for your team.
Is there any problem with my interview?
I heard about you
in the Daily Daily.
Although this is your personal matter,
the big company is using this reason to reject you.
You can go back now.
Go away.
You're Wen Yifan, right?
Human being has all the six senses.
I won't judge you
if you're here.
Take a look at this two of them.
I'll show you where they go first.
Get out of my sight or I'll beat you to death.
F ilei, what happened?
Why is the face so pale?
Fulei.
How are you?
Let's go.
The person over there is Zhang Yifan.
Cut it out.
Let's go and help him.
Hello?
I am the last one to come to your place.
You guys...
I don't want to see you anymore.
What do you want?
Ji Yao.
Did you see the message I sent you?
Your aunt is back in Beiyu.
I am not going to see her again.
Did your mom forget to tell you...
How did you come in?
I won't let her come in again.
I am your mom.
Can you not feel my mom?
Jiang.
I talked to your aunt for a while.
I didn't know anything about the past.
So I didn't stand by your side.
I was sorry to you.
But I thought they took good care of you.
I was very worried.
I wanted to take you back.
I am sorry.
But if you are afraid that the house will affect your reputation,
I am not worried.
I am wrong.
I am not a good person.
I just want to wait for a while.
When you come back to Nan Wu University,
I will take good care of you.
I have to go.
You told me to drive you home.
She is waiting outside.
I will call you back.
You are so rude.
I didn't expect that...
you will report to a place so far away.
Will you live with me in Nan Wu University?
Jiang.
I will make up for you.
Okay?
Don't...
Don't be angry with me.
What else do you want to say?
I have to work.
I got you something you like.
You are too thin.
No need. Thank you.
Jiang.
I am so tired.
Okay.
You can goЯ
What are you going to do?
I·ve cut it again.
Nan...
Will you protect your mother line?
Jia.
Where am I?
Never mind.
No need to wait for her anymore.
Li' tomato
Let's just go to the بن ,
I'm tired.
As you expect,
I'll take a look.
You're so good.
But you didn't even want to come to my side to support me.
You know that I'm the one who's been working in this company for a long time.
If you don't believe me, I'll tell them the same thing.
Wang Gao, don't think about me.
How should I explain this?
This matter...
Sorry, I've already explained everything about what happened in the first and second day of the press conference.
I don't understand why such a ridiculous rumor can continue to spread in our press conference.
Finally, I have to take responsibility for these false accusations.
False accusations?
If we, as reporters, don't seek the truth and don't seek the truth,
what's the difference between gossip and small news?
Where are the persistence of these reporters?
Okay, you're right.
Yifan, you've been working in this company for a year.
We must be brave enough to do our job as a journalist.
We must not find out the truth and never give up.
We must not be afraid of the truth.
But some people forget the basic truth of this company for a long time.
Am I right, Mr. Wang?
No, I'm like this.
If someone thinks I'm running away from this position because of my relationship,
I'll try my best to prove my ability by using practical actions and using my grades to block their mouths.
Do you understand what I mean?
Thank you, Director Kang.
I'll get back to work.
I'll see you out.
Okay.
Yifan, you've changed your habit.
Your habit is to like to make yourself suffer.
But you said that word just now.
You're so generous.
You're so cool.
You're so nice to the one who bullied you.
Do you want to drink?
No, I don't want to.
This wine is not that easy to drink.
What's wrong?
I forgot the rules.
If you don't come back at 10 o'clock, tell me.
Okay.
I'll go get some water.
I forgot.
Sorry.
How do I feel that you've been a little...
a little bit...
I'm just sleepy.
I want to sleep.
Then you can sleep.
I'm sorry.
So you're...
in a bad mood and drunk.
You're back to your dream.
What's wrong with you today?
I'm sorry.
Are you going out?
What are you looking at?
Why are you like a pervert?
Where are you going?
You're not the one who's going to the wrong place.
This is not your room.
Your room is over there.
Over there.
Go.
What's wrong?
Your room is over there.
Go.
You're so mean.
You're not looking for me?
I think you're okay.
I can't see you're always so upset.
I'm sorry.
I'm used to sleeping and preparing to go to bed.
I'm still a strawberry.
You're so talented.
Really?
I used to think that reporters are all so mean.
I hope you can be a good singer.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
You too.
Yifan, you've succeeded.
There are many kinds of reporters.
They don't like me.
No.
I think they're quite comfortable.
We're not service workers.
We're not just comfortable to let the victims go.
The truth is the most important.
Of course, it's better to be humble.
You're a trainee.
You're not a good singer.
You're also a trainee.
You should be the best in the world.
You can do it.
You've worked hard today.
Yifan,
are you free after work tomorrow?
Are you sure?
Okay.
It's okay. I'll take it.
It's like Xiaoyu.
Yifan,
I have a friend who knows me.
She just gave birth to a girl.
So I want to buy a gift for her.
But I don't understand it.
So I want to ask if you can pick one with me.
A girl?
Yes.
You can ask Zhenyu.
She has a daughter.
I don't know it.
Zhenyu.
I'm not familiar with her.
It's okay. I'll tell her.
Let's go.
Yifan, wait a minute.
I think you have something dirty on your neck.
I want to help you.
I'm sorry.
I was so careless.
I didn't hurt you.
It's okay.
I just didn't expect you to react so much.
I don't like being exposed by others.
I'm sorry.
Yifan.
Zhizhi.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see my brother.
He seems to be not back yet.
Come in first.
Okay.
Sit down.
I'm here to see my brother.
Have you been out of the library recently?
Did you get a good grade?
Yes.
Which university did you like?
The University of the United Nations.
The University of the United Nations is far away.
Have you thought about it?
I've thought about it.
I've thought about it for a long time.
It's like the South.
The major I want to report will be better.
And I don't want to stay in the South.
I want to go to other cities.
It's good.
But I don't seem to be happy.
Why?
Actually, I didn't tell him
about my parents' relationship.
So he thought
I was a man.
He started to talk to me
after I knew it was a big deal.
Brother.
Take off your clothes.
Okay.
Let me help you.
I've got a question.
Do you know who was the leader
of the legendary team at the time?
I'm not sure.
Why did you ask me that?
Because I think
he looked like
the one who was angry
when he was playing with Zhixian.
He was alone for days.
He was not polite.
I think he was a good guy.
I don't think my brother
liked his relationship with the early age.
At that time,
my brother was not doing well.
He suddenly
got back on his feet
when he was a kid.
He didn't do anything
except learning.
My parents were very happy at that time.
They thought he finally understood.
I think
someone must have encouraged him.
I guess he was the girl
who was in the early age.
What did you talk about?
Our girl knows
how to thank you.
Brother,
I didn't tell you
that I was wrong this time.
But I did a good job
choosing
my favorite university and major.
Isn't that a good thing?
I just don't like Yi He.
I didn't hear that
Yi He was doing something bad.
Are you done?
You should eat quickly
if you are not done.
You have to eat here
before you wake up.
You can go back by car later.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to sleep.
Yifan.
What's wrong?
Maybe I'm not used to
sleeping well.
Did I get a headache?
It's hard to get used to
sleeping like this.
Yifan.
Do you need my help?
No, thanks.
Go back.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I'll see you next time.
Take care.
I'm so embarrassed
to eat.
I can't digest it.
I'm going to buy something.
I can't make it in time.
It turns out that the problem is fake.
Don't talk to me.
I'm angry.
Yifan.
Don't you want to go to the hospital?
His attitude is like
I was so bad at the beginning.
And then I secretly kept it
and kept it from everyone.
I want to be cured.
At the same time,
I can't see Cuuuu's face.
I've never seen it before.
It's too dark.
entonces,
I kept telling her
I can't see Cuuuu in this space.
I examined everyone
and器w able to reduce it.
Then,
she suddenly
was drunk.
Not that long ago,
she Nousi
already recognized
thanks to Lu Suren.
He was so happy when the result was out.
He said that he would visit him whenever he needed.
He was so excited to go out.
He was so happy to see him tonight.
I think someone would encourage him.
I'm the director's wife.
I'm sorry.
You're so flattered.
I'll rest that thing!
solving
Just today,
it's your second try!
Good serious job.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm afraid of you.