I'm afraid that you'll be in danger.
On August 3rd, 2012
I'm here.
My dad has died.
I seem to have deserve your help.
I am looking for Lin Qian for hope now.
here
Thank you
I'll give you the letter.
It's okay. I don't need it.
Miss Zeng.
It's said that it was reported by the foreign wife of the suspect.
I'll try it.
Okay.
Zeng Yi.
I'm Wen Yifan.
I'm the cousin of Wen Min.
Okay. I'll take you there.
I probably know a little bit about your situation.
I've had the same experience with you.
I jumped off the balcony with him.
I felt better when I jumped off the balcony.
But I felt that I was so unknowable to die with him.
I didn't dare to sleep every night.
I was so blinded by that person's face.
I felt so unknowable.
I was still young.
I cried every day.
I cried every night.
I felt so painful.
I started to feel better.
I couldn't even cry.
Why did we have to suffer like this?
Why?
Can you tell me what happened that night?
No.
Uncle, you came home early today.
Yes.
Where is Xiaoming?
She's going to the dinner with her classmates.
She'll be back soon.
I'm going back to my room now.
The change is over.
It smells good.
What are you doing?
Brother Dong!
What's wrong?
Help!
Since we got married,
I felt that
I was so happy to have Chess.
I was also very civilized
and I was very proud of you.
Because that house
was sold by Chess
except for her.
She's a good girl.
I've been trying to
make her believe me.
Who are you?
Let go of me.
Say it again!
Let go of me!
Brother Dong!
Who are you?
Your whole family isONE,
let go of me!
Let go of me!
It's alright!
Can you take that to your father now.
Take it to someone else.
Let go of me!
Sit down.
It's okay.
Do you hear me?
Don't be afraid.
You can't call the police.
If they call the police,
everyone will know about this.
If they do, they won't be serious.
Then why did you do this?
Right?
Don't say that.
You uncle.
You drink wine.
You are like that.
You are crazy.
This thing.
I will definitely do it for you.
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
I will help you to teach me a lesson.
Don't go to sleep.
They are crazy.
Who is he?
He is a clear wife.
He is my son's wife.
You are not in the way of the road.
You are now
in the way of my son's wife.
Are you crazy?
Okay.
How is he?
What did you do to him?
How could he scare you to death?
He is in the dark.
You are not his dog.
Okay.
He is your son's wife.
You said he was a dog.
Do you know
who he is?
How is he?
You are going to scare him to death, right?
You are going to scare him to death.
Don't go to sleep.
You are so annoying.
You...
When I help you to lose someone,
you are not annoying.
You are not annoying.
Okay.
Jiawen.
Don't be angry.
I am wrong.
I will take care of you.
I won't do it again.
Okay?
Doctor.
I know that you didn't get hurt.
You are so mean.
I am fine now.
You...
I knew that I would kill someone.
I almost got my hand shot.
But the sound of the sound told me
that I must hold on to it.
To call the police.
Otherwise, the next person to die is me.
You are brave.
Okay.
I can't ask that kind of person.
But I feel much better with your husband.
I am not afraid of getting hurt.
I want to make the truth
not to be found.
I know.
We are not victims.
We are brave to protect ourselves.
Sister.
Teacher Jian told us to hurry and go.
Let's go get ready.
Flower.
Thank you.
If there is anything, contact me.
when discussing the unique characteristics and missing findings from our customer.
He was
I'll give the car for later.
We should be staying a long way.
It's okay. You don't have to.
Then thank you.
Oh, right. My name is Wen Yifan.
What's your name?
My name is Guo Ling.
I just transferred to the North Central Academy.
I'm in the fourth class. What grade are you in?
I'm in the eighth class.
Eighth class? It's a class of money.
Then you must be very good at math.
I was told about this paper that I lost it last night.
But I can't think of anything.
Send me the best answer.
What's your license?
He kidnapped Yang Xindou once.
Look.
What happened?
We need to investigate it.
After the PROF over임,
we'll watch也cause.
We shall step out to find it.
Fang Yşallah.
Right.
阻止東南圭等阮?
You should be careful when you were out recently.
You went to the North this time.
Is this the right time?
Why do you always worry about me and my old man?
You're a warm-hearted man.
You have to be careful.
And...
Well...
Do you remember the content of Lu Yongbi?
Why did I add Lu Yongbi to your real name?
I'm quite confident to say something.
By the way,
I met an old lady I knew today.
Didn't I call the police?
After moving out from the North,
she was left with me for a while.
I saw her happy today.
She was very happy.
She was very nice to me.
She was very nice to me when she was playing with her daughter.
Let's go to the room next time.
Sure.
How was she getting married?
We went together.
I saw her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend should have proposed to her.
I don't know when the time will come.
Do you have time?
I have a cold.
You have twenty more days.
What?
You won't be able to fall down soon.
This year's wish is to make it come true.
I'll do my best.
I'll give you some time.
I'll hang up now.
Okay.
If you're sleepy, go to bed early.
Good night.
You're here.
Is Uncle Guo here?
Who are you looking for?
I'm Guo Lin's friend.
I want to visit him.
Please come in.
Auntie Guo is here.
I'm so sorry.
I'm a reporter from Nanwu TV station.
But don't worry.
I won't interview you.
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm a three-year-old boy.
I'm a big boy.
I used to be busy with my work.
I went to look for my kid.
He's very good at it.
He's always been good at it.
He keeps it in his room.
He knows how to hide in his room.
He writes something.
But I don't know how to support him.
He always writes what he wrote
and spends his time with me.
He doesn't have time.
That night,
I quarreled with him.
That was the first time he looked at me.
I didn't expect that.
That was the last time.
Nian Zai, what are you doing here in the school?
Why don't you come to help me?
Let's go to the thing we had in Ming Tian.
Dad, look at what I wrote.
I really like writing things.
I want to steal them!
I don't care who sees those things written by you.
Dad, don't say that.
My ideal is to be a small rapper in the future.
Me too!
I just want to make money and fill our stomachs.
Then you can't sell things out.
I can't sell them for the rest of my life.
I have my own business.
What's wrong with selling things?
Where are the people I sell?
I can make money with my words.
Just your money?
Let me see.
Where's the money?
Don't go anywhere.
I'm so stupid.
I didn't think that
after he said that,
he would never come back.
These years,
I've been waiting for him to give birth
to hide outside and write things.
He didn't want to come back to see me.
You said that
if I cared more about him,
he wouldn't have come out.
Now he said that
he really can write a name.
He even wanted to say that he's a novelist.
I should have been a father to him.
But
I caused him to meet that young man.
I shouldn't have done that.
Uncle, uncle.
It's not your fault.
Be calm.
It's just a neighbor.
My girl is not in the way.
Don't worry.
I'll report it to the police after the trial.
I hope you won't be hurt by someone.
Thank you.
Hello.
How is it?
The car is still in the car.
But the car is in the car.
I think it's gone.
Did it go back?
When?
It went back.
But I just called
and asked me to go to the police station to help investigate.
By the way,
I might have to go back to Nanwu after the car is gone.
Be careful.
You're right.
I'll wait for you at home.
I'll be back.
I'm leaving.
See you.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You can go back to your room.
I'll go back to my room.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
I'll wait for you.
The information is on you. I'm leaving.
Okay, be careful.
Okay, okay.
Bye, Yifan.
You can change their face.
It's very simple.
Bye.
Okay, I'll wait for you at the office.
Yifan,
why didn't you report about the relatives?
The police are still investigating the case.
Let's wait for the final result.
I hope that the evil spirit will be cured soon.
I hope so too.
Okay, I'll leave now.
You should go home early.
Take care.
Jia Wan Ban told me that I'll pick you up.
Okay, 8.30.
Okay.
If I don't want to go,
I can't find you anywhere.
I'm not well today.
I should go home first.
The overall temperature is a little lower.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Fang Yan.
Are you going?
Yes.
Jia Wan Ban is going.
No.
Right, you're going.
Okay.
I'll go and talk to you later.
I'll go first.
Okay.
I'll go here.
Brother, why don't you go?
I'm going to pick up my girlfriend to work.
You're a little stranger.
You should have a hot pot with me that day.
It's been a long time.
Who are you with?
Two teams.
Okay, wait a minute.
Okay.
I'm okay here.
Come pick me up now.
The new car is still in the car.
But the car was already left behind.
By the way,
the new car may be difficult to get.
Hello, I want to apologize.
I found a suspect in the door of the house of the manor.
Right.
He's so...
Fortunately, he didn't run away.
What's the problem?
They're closing the car. Let go of me.
Let go of me.
I'm tired after a long time.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Why didn't you answer the phone?
Hello?
Who are you?
I just checked the phone.
The owner of the phone just got hurt.
What?
Where are you?
What's wrong?
I got stood here.
Why don't you pack your
pants later?
What happened?
Did you go to the emergency room?
Is it a disease called disease?
I don't know about it.
I just see people suffering.
I just see his hands are full of blood.
His belly is also scratched.
His blood is bleeding.
He has so many blood.
He should be sent to the hospital.
Thank you.
Go.
It's okay.
I love you.
Move.
You are so fast.
Can I be faster?
He has so many cars.
Are you okay?
I was here three years ago.
I will not be safe means you should practice it
You can practice.
I can manage it.
Eat.
・
But here is my job.
I will be able to escape from you before I grow up.
Don't die here in the future.
Sire.
Are you packing for your health?
Aren't you going to return home tonight?
Sire,
Are you having another road to you?
No.
What happened today?
That's why...
Can you please park the car with me?
Who is boss him?
It's you, Sang Yan.
I discuss with cheer.
Are you alright? Where did he suffer?
Nothing really.
Just some prone skin even on hand.
You said nothing.
I saw loads of blood!
The law will be referring to the exactamente carEEP number of blood!
Nothing really matters to me.
Don't worry like that.
I've already told you it's alright!
I'll go home by myself later.
Someone must be doing some other proportions.
I need to take some time.
Where are you? I'll come find you.
I'm at grandparents' placards.
Thank you.
Okay, Dr. Sun.
We'll come back to see you after you finish your wound.
Okay, thank you.
Hello.
May I have a question?
Yes.
What's the matter?
Hello.
May I have a question?
Is there a patient called Dr. Sun?
Over there.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Other than the hand-pulled 8-stringed,
are you okay with your stomach?
I'm fine.
Here you go.
If anything happens,
please contact us.
Okay, thank you.
I have a little bit of a bruise.
It's a 8-stringed.
You don't care about me,
just let me be.
You're still mad at me.
Why did you go to catch him?
What's wrong?
I was wrong.
You saw him just call the police,
didn't you?
If he ran away...
You'll be the one to suggest.
What's wrong?
I don't like you being like this.
Can you stop doing this?
Can you stop telling me about it?
Can't you just work hard every day,
and come back safely?
I don't care about these things anymore.
Even if I want to let Zheng Xin De
stay in jail for a lifetime,
I can't stand
your thinking.
Why aren't you happy?
I'm sorry.
Zheng Xin De was caught.
Your aunt also paid for it.
You and your daughter are happy now.
And...
this time,
I'll protect you.
I really care about it.
I care about it.
I said I wouldn't let you go,
but you didn't.
I really want...
to be a man
who's so stubborn.
I'm just a little bit stupid.
Why should I be so stubborn with you?
At that time,
I was young and had a crush on someone.
I was alone.
I was so worried about you.
I was worried about you.
But...
I was worried about the love
for you.
I was worried about the chance
I was thinking
that I'd never
ask you about time again.
But I knew I couldn't leave.
I knew I could only wait for it.
I was worried about the face,
the breath of the needle.
I was thinking...
I couldn't be the main reason.
But I regret it.
I regret why I only cared about
my own
and the reason why I was so sad.
I didn't try to save you.
I didn't even find out
that you were hurt
by your acting.
Don't talk about these things.
It's my problem.
It's not your problem.
It's the problem of Che Xingde.
So, Bansheng,
I did it this time.
Can you be a little happier
and I'll take that bomb?
Can it?
I'm sorry.
Can you stop crying?
I just...
Slow down.
Don't you feel bad?
Okay, I won't be mad.
I won't be mad at all.
But Chu Wang Jiang, what's wrong with you?
You're not in this mood, are you?
I'm not in a mood to do that.
When my family was looking for me,
you were happy to go to the company.
Can we do the same?
Okay, I'm fine. Let's go.
Slow down.
I'm fine. I'll break your skin.
Can I?
Where's the clothes?
It's still bruised.
Can I?
Sure.
Otherwise,
I'll leave it here.
What's wrong withhig?
Nothing.
Meanwhile,
I have to clean up.
Don't worry.
I will do.
If you want it,
I can work.
But this work is simple.
I've been working my butt for more than a month.
I have to put my head on the throne.
I finally caught your shadow.
It's good that
from now on,
only the light remains.
I will do everything for you.
My heart will also start to doubt
the firmness in the ice.
You have never been able to seal my every effort.
I have her.
With time,
we wait together.
The sun shines, the warmth is warm and cold.
It gives me a sense of luxury.
You are the wind in the rain.
It doesn't want me to come.
You are always standing by me.
You are the sun and the moon.
I can't stop my heart from moving.
The rain is full of the sky and the earth.
When I have you,
I can see the darkness in my eyes.
I can't stop my heart from moving.
Every time you leave,
I will always be yours.
Every time we pass by,
I will always be your shadow.
I will be here with you
It's you in the wind that doesn't want me to come
It's you standing by my side for me and her
This road is a mess, the sky is full of sand
But I have your voice, how can I give up
I won't give up, even if you give me the future that I want
It's you, I want to live, I want to be with you
Even if I'm still looking at you, I'm still waiting for you
Waiting for you to exist
The darkness that can be seen in the eyes
Episode 4