[English subtitles are available]
[Love on a Shoestring]
[Episode 18]
What did you break this time?
The plates.
Okay, stop washing.
I will wash them.
There are only a few dishes left. I'll finish washing them.
When you're done,
the dishes will all be broken.
What should we use for dinner tomorrow?
Alright, come on.
Sit down.
Let me ask you.
Is something bothering you?
You're usually so agile.
What happened today?
Yuanchong
said he wanted to invest in my shop
with his money.
That's great.
Don't you need money to open a shop?
In this way,
you don't need to worry about money.
But I don't know
whether he really values my ability
or just because he likes me.
What should I do if I make him
lose money?
Besides,
this is his savings for a long time.
I can't accept it.
Jiali.
Do you
like Yuanchong?
No.
No?
Then why do you worry so much?
You think so much for him.
There must be
a little bit
of affection, right?
Think about it.
I'm going to wash the dishes.
Did I really fall in love with Yuanchong?
I love him.
I can't leave him.
Uncle, I beg you.
I beg you.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Let me tell you.
Yingjun
is the successor
of our W Group.
You are an ordinary office worker without any background
or family connections.
Who are you to be with him?
Zeng Yingjun's father is really snobbish.
What's so great about being rich?
Rich people can be willful.
Later,
he'll give money to that woman.
I won't mistreat you.
This money is enough for you to live.
See?
I can be a screenwriter now.
It's an old cliché.
It's because these old clichés
happen in real life
that such stories keep being made.
Young people nowadays are free in love.
Whose parents would intervene
and even pay money to send someone away?
No!
You just haven't seen enough.
Me?
Things like loving someone without family approval,
being forced to leave,
and being unable to stay together,
really do happen in life.
That feeling
is like being abandoned by the world.
It's really hurtful,
painful,
and sad.
People who haven't experienced it won't understand.
You're weird.
I...
I'm just too immersed in the role.
Weird how?
Is that so?
Yeah.
Is it that Haikuo's father also...
How do you know?
Gave you money and asked you to leave?
What did you say to him?
I...
Of course, I didn't cry like her,
so weak.
I just...
You want me to leave Haikuo?
That's right.
Could it be that you just want to give me a sum of money
to make me leave him?
Listen.
Even if you gave me billions,
I wouldn't leave him.
Then I want to see
just how determined you are.
This is the contract I prepared
to sign with your company.
You want me to leave Haikuo
and also want to sign a contract with our company.
What exactly are you trying to do?
As long as you can convince Haikuo
to come to me personally to discuss this business,
not only will it bring a billion-NTD order
to your company,
but I will also agree
to you dating Haikuo.
A billion-NTD order?
Just the commission alone
could pay the down payment on a house.
Keke.
You wouldn't just watch this money slip away, would you?
You're Haikuo's father.
It should be easy
for you to see him.
But Haikuo considers you dead.
It means your relationship isn't good.
What exactly is your purpose?
That's right.
There are indeed
significant issues between my son and me.
So, I sought you out,
hoping you could
help mend our relationship.
After all,
you are the only one
who can speak to him
on my behalf now.
So now I have to find a way
to help them reconcile.
Earlier, Elly noticed
that he rarely mentions his family.
I asked Haikuo before.
He told me
his
whole family was dead.
Oh my.
Why did he talk so grimly?
What kind of feud
could lead to this?
Did his father tell you?
But Haikuo did tell me before
that during his mother’s final moments,
he was the only one by her side.
His father doesn't care at all.
He didn't even pay a visit.
So heartless?
Such a man
deserves to die.
Really.
Honey, don't worry.
When you're dying,
I’ll be right by your side,
never leaving you.
Although you mean no harm,
it feels like
a curse.
No, you misunderstood.
I’m just afraid you’ll be lonely
with no one to take care of you.
You better mean it.
I think this isn’t simple.
What are you planning to do?
I don't know.
I’m still figuring it out.
They say
even a fair judge can hardly resolve family disputes.
Why are you here?
I came to ask
if you’re toying with Yuanchong’s feelings.
I'm not.
Why would you say that?
Because I saw
you both go out
after work that day.
Your expression was different.
You were smiling so happily.
And it was genuine.
You never smiled at him like that before.
Really?
Did I?
I was just starting to admire you.
Don't disappoint me.
Don’t turn into the kind
of scheming woman I despise the most.
I just don't want to become that kind of person.
So I've been hesitating
about whether to accept his investment.
He wants to invest in you?
Reject him.
Didn't you just tell me
that as long as things are kept clear
and separate, it would be fine?
Now you're asking me to reject him?
Yuanchong has already changed so much for you.
First, he learned baking for you.
After you rejected him,
he didn't give up
and said he would look for some dream.
Now, even without finding that dream,
he wants to invest in you?
Do you think
I would hurt him?
Yuanchong is falling deeper and deeper for you.
Your attitude is the key.
You two are so ambiguous now.
I feel like I need to step in to protect him.
Do you
like Yuanchong?
You think so much for him.
There must be
a little bit
of affection, right?
Don’t accept Yuanchong's investment just because
it benefits you
and turns him into a tool.
I'm not treating him as a tool.
I think
I'm starting to change my feelings toward Yuanchong.
What kind of change?
I think
I might care about Yuanchong a bit.
You like Chen Shi?
Keep your voice down.
So that's why we wanted you to invite Chen Shi
to the guesthouse with us.
Don't tell him
I like him.
Chen Shi is indeed
a little bit inferior to me
among men.
But he's still a pretty good guy.
You've got good taste.
Yes.
So
will you join us on the trip to the guesthouse?
For Chen Shi's happiness,
sure.
Cheers.
How are things going with Mr. Fang?
Mr. Fang...
Mr. Fang has put forth some conditions.
If we can satisfy him,
the benefits of this contract will be considerable.
If we can secure Mr. Fang's contract,
I’ll almost have enough for the down payment on a house.
Otherwise, with housing prices constantly rising,
the salaries never keep pace.
Don't you want your own house
and home?
I think
home is like eating.
What's important is the people,
not what food
or house it is.
As long as I can be with the one I love,
anywhere is home.
I really like the atmosphere in your family.
Even though
you may speak loudly, argue, and bicker,
you
genuinely care for each other.
Actually,
your dad's love for you
is really admirable.
Haikuo.
Do you also want
to have your own family?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't worry.
I have you now,
as well as Uncle Jian and Auntie Jian.
You are all my family.
Don't worry.
By the way,
I recently met a new friend.
He's very interested in our company's products.
I thought I’d introduce him to you
to see if you can secure an order from him.
Sure, no problem.
You set it up,
and I’ll coordinate on my end.
I've finished my work here.
What about you?
-Done.
The girls in our Accounting Department
are indeed efficient.
For the sake of going out to have fun,
our work is twice as effective.
Of course.
Since the work is done,
it's...
Shopping time.
I must take this opportunity
to make Michael Zhao face his true feelings
and confess to me.
This dress is too sexy.
Michael Zhao won't be able
to take his eyes off you.
I'm going to have a nosebleed.
Elly.
You shop online so often.
Do you use cashback?
What is that?
Let me tell you.
Look.
This app.
The clothing website you’re browsing right now
has a partnership with it.
You can get cashback.
Here.
This is it.
Download this cashback app.
See? Click through here.
Whether you're booking a hotel, arranging travel,
ordering food delivery, or shopping online,
you can get high cashback.
Come on, use this
referral code.
After joining it,
you and I will both get a 100 yuan cashback.
I know this app.
Michael Zhao introduced it to me last time.
I'll download it right away.
Speaking of Michael Zhao,
your eyes are all pink and bubbly.
Then I’ll download it too.
-That gives us another chance.
-I’m telling you.
This way.
You both owe me your 100 yuan cashback.
Okay.
-Here.
-This one.
Yes.
You were supposed to give me 300,
but you only gave me 200.
If I hadn't caught it today,
you would've taken that 100.
I'm sorry.
I will conduct more employee training.
My apologies.
Qianqian.
Since you started working here,
you've never made a mistake.
What happened today?
You seem a bit off.
Manager, I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful.
Cheer up.
Here, this is for you.
Hello.
I brought some desserts for you all.
These desserts aren't cheap.
Money is no longer an issue for me.
I'm going to be rich soon.
What do you mean?
Did you win the lottery?
No.
I picked
a very promising investment target
and I'm going to be rich soon.
Investment target?
Stocks, bonds,
funds, or ETFs?
None of those.
Just eat.
I'll tell you when I make the money.
Jiali, are you off work?
I'll give you a ride home.
Okay.
Yuanchong.
Well...
After work today,
I want to buy some computer parts.
Come with me.
Is it urgent?
-Can we do it another day...
-No!
It has to be today.
But I've already arranged
to go with Jiali...
Jiali.
It's always Jiali.
Is Jiali's matter that important?
My matters are just casual
and can be postponed to another day.
It's not that. It's just...
Qianqian.
Why are you acting so differently today?
You usually don't blame Yuanchong like this.
Maybe she's really in a hurry
to buy that computer part, so...
I don't need you to speak for me.
Why are you talking so aggressively?
This...
This was originally
a matter between the two of us.
It has nothing to do with her.
Even so,
you shouldn't speak so aggressively.
Jiali is even speaking up for you.
Enough.
You're scolding me!
Li Yuanchong.
I... I know you like her.
But you can't scold me because of her.
You...
You're putting romance before friendship!
Is she crying?
Yuanchong, you made a girl cry.
She...
What's wrong with her?
Go check on her quickly.
Wait for me.
Why are you crying?
I just said a few words.
Do you need to be so emotional?
Yuanchong.
I've still lost you.
But...
You never had me.
You're right.
Kind of makes sense.
All along,
you've only seen me as a junior.
I was the one who held onto hope.
Calling you senior
while hoping
one day it could be more than that.
I like
Jiali.
Looking at me like that
won't change my feelings.
You...
Please stay calm.
Don't act impulsively.
Even if you force me,
I won't change my mind.
I just wanted to tell you
that Jiali said
she has started to have some feelings for you.
Manager, where's Jiali?
When you went to the break room to find Qianqian,
Jiali went home.
Didn't I tell her to wait for me?
She probably guessed
that I would tell you
she had some feelings for you,
so she went home.
Why did you run away?
Well.
He confessed to me before.
I rejected him.
And I told him
I thought of him as my brother.
Now that I've started liking him.
It feels so embarrassing.
I don't know what I'm doing.
When it comes to love,
if you know what you're doing,
it's not called love.
It's the uncertainty that makes it fun.
Then,
do you think I should accept his investment?
Of course not.
When it comes to money,
whether it's family affection, love, or friendship,
no matter how good the relationship is,
it gets too complicated
once money is involved.
The way you put it...
What's going on between you and Haikuo again?
It's like
a soap opera:
family and money drama.
Family?
I thought he had no family.
I thought so too,
but suddenly his dad showed up.
They don't get along,
and his dad tried to
bribe me
to reconcile them.
Your problem is trickier than mine.
Indeed.
I didn't want to get involved,
but Haikuo
seems to want family,
so I thought
I'd help.
I really hope
Haikuo can have a good relationship with his family.
Thank you.
Try this. It's delicious.
Chen Shi.
I heard Yu Fen loves meat.
Give her a piece.
Yu Fen, this is for you.
Katy.
The chicken wings are ready.
Do you want some?
Yes, thank you.
Wait.
Chen Shi.
I heard Yu Fen also likes chicken wings.
Let her
have it first.
Sure, give it to her.
Here.
I'm stuffed.
I'm starving.
Eat this.
Where is Elly?
Why didn't she come to the BBQ?
Elly's legs
are stunning.
Michael Zhao can't
take his eyes off them.
As long as Elly shows her legs,
Michael Zhao will fall for her.
Your meat
is about to burn.
You...
Why are you staring at me?
Your legs are slim
but need more muscle,
and they're a bit O-shaped.
I recommend
watching this video
to fix them.
I do it every day. Look.
Look at this.
There's a pool over there.
Yeah, let's play in the water.
Yes, let's go.
Let's play in the water.
Is it nice?
Yes.
Join us.
Elly,
you are so beautiful.
Elly, why are you laughing?
Go play in the water.
It's cool.
Right, go play in the water.
Michael Zhao.
Do you want to
join me for some water fun?
Sure.
Is it fun?
Play water splashing with me.
Yes.
I'm the best at it.
No one can beat me at water splashing.
Let me show you how it's done.
Back in the day, I was known
as the Freshwater Prince.
By the river,
I could splash
without even blinking.
Impressive, right?
Freshwater Prince, huh?
I'm the Freshwater Prince's mother.
Come here!
Freshwater Prince, huh?
Mom, I don't dare!
I'm your mom!
Mom, I won't do it again!
You won't?
I love you, Mom.
This is not how I imagined it.
Elly is so powerful and aggressive.
Michael Zhao.
I love you.
This is not how I imagined it.
Did you
have fun today?
You had fun.
But I didn't.
You didn't treat me like a woman.
When we were playing in the water,
you kept attacking me so hard.
I played with you for over an hour.
You should
see me
as a considerate woman.
I have a question for you.
Answer me honestly.
Since you saved me,
I feel
there's something different
growing
between us.
So,
am I
your type?
You like tempura, right?
Here, have some.
How did you know?
I noticed you ate a lot tempura,
so I thought you liked it.
So you've been observing me?
No, I just...
What are you two doing?
What are you doing?
Why aren't Michael Zhao and Elly
coming over for the BBQ?
Yeah,
what are they doing?
Why are they staring at each other?
Did their conversation fail?
Fail at what?
Relationship.
Their relationship.
Relationship?
It's burning.
Let's check on them.
Bring them some food.
Guys,
Chen Shi is quite good at BBQ.
Have some.
Yeah,
even if the talk didn't go well,
we're still colleagues.
Don't let it get awkward.
Right, Michael Zhao.
You're a man.
Be more accommodating.
Michael Zhao, you...
What's wrong?
He...
He's snoring.
He's asleep?
Elly.
She's asleep too.
How can they sleep like this?
Turns out Michael Zhao sleeps with his eyes open too.
They're a perfect match.
Drink more.
This mung bean soup will cool you down.
-Thank you, Grandma.
-Drink more.
Yuanchong?
You're finally back.
Yuanchong has been waiting for you.
I'll go
put away what I bought.
No need, I'll do it.
You...
You two chat.
-You…
-You...
You go first.
It's okay.
You came to see me.
You go first.
Alright.
These are some stores I found online.
You can choose the ones you like,
and then we can see them offline.
You found so much information?
You could have just
sent it to Jiali on her phone.
Why did you print it out?
You came here
specifically to see Jiali,
didn't you?
Grandma!
Aren't you putting away things for me?
Why are you eavesdropping on our conversation?
You two were too slow.
It was driving me crazy!
I just wanted to speed things up for you.
Take this back
first.
I'll find a store on my own.
Why?
Are you refusing my investment
because you know I like you?
Jiali,
didn't I tell you
to think about
your feelings for him?
Haven't you thought about it?
I have.
But you still refused him?
Look at him. Yuanchong is so pitiful.
Grandma.
Keke said
it's best for couples
not to mix money
with their relationship.
You want to date him?
You two want to be a couple?
That's great!
Keke is right.
Couples should
avoid financial entanglements.
That's right.
But...
But I want to invest in Jiali's store.
Don't you get it?
Jiali said
couples shouldn't
mix money with their relationship.
So you don't want to be her boyfriend?
No.
I do.
I really do.
Jiali.
I promise I'll make you happy.
Keke,
do you really want to help reconcile them?
I think
it's a thankless task.
I agree.
What if it affects your relationship
with Haikuo?
It won't.
Haikuo and I have a great relationship.
He has a good temper
and doesn't get angry easily.
He might be surprised to see his dad,
but if things get tense,
I'll
smooth things over.
It shouldn't be too awkward.
Just remember,
being a mediator often means pleasing no one.
Got it.
But I want to give it a try.
Okay.
Here.
Mr. Jian. Mrs. Jian.
Are you here to pick up Keke?
Yes.
Okay.
We're leaving.
-Okay.
-Okay. Go.
Bye-bye.
Haikuo.
Here.
Let me tell you.
No matter what happens,
be more tolerant of Keke.
Mr. Jian, don't worry.
I will treat Keke with kindness
and make her happy.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
How could I fall asleep?
You
must be too tired from playing in the water.
Don't be too upset.
There will be more opportunities.
Creating chances isn't helping.
He fell asleep too.
He didn't hear what I said.
In my opinion,
he's just a fancy piece of wood.
No matter how gentlemanly,
he is just a stiff piece of wood.
I heard someone
talking about stiff wood outside.
Want to see a sacred tree?
Feeling better after a nap?
Much better.
That's great.
Now
drive me home.
I just came to ask
what you want for dinner.
I'm not eating.
I want to leave now.
Take me home.
Elly!
Are you giving up in anger?
No.
I will
hold onto him tightly
and make him understand my feelings.
Hold tightly.
Good luck.
Don't be nervous.
Just
leave it to me.
This is your client.
I will try my best
to secure this order for you.
Sorry, I'm late.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you in the wrong room?
No.
I am the client
Keke wants to introduce to you.
You only met him once.
You shouldn't trust strangers so easily.
Haikuo.
I already know he's your father.
I arranged this meeting
so you two can talk.
He's not my father.
I've warned you
not to get close to Jian Keke,
yet you still used her?
She's my son's girlfriend.
I should meet her.
How could you say I'm using her?
We are just strangers.
You have my blood.
Blood ties can't be broken.
No matter how hard you resist,
the fact remains.
We're family after all.
Family?
Do you think you have the right
to talk about family with me? Do you?
Haikuo,
your dad truly wants to reconcile.
He is...
You don't know
what kind of person he is.
Don't speak for him.
Haikuo.
Haikuo!
Calm down.
Whatever happened before,
listen to what your dad has to say.
Getting angry won't solve anything.
-Your dad...
-I said,
he's not my dad.
Jian Keke.
My family matters don't need your interference.
Do you have something to say to me?
You haven't given me your home address.
Just drive towards your place.
My place?
Why?
Because starting today,
I'm moving in with you.
I want to live with you.
[Preview]
He just left.
If he breaks up with me tomorrow,
I wouldn't be surprised.
Why are you avoiding me?
I confessed my feelings to you.
What's your answer?
President Wang.
If you genuinely want to
mend your relationship
stop interfering with the people around him.
Are you threatening me?
You care if Elly is sincere to you.
That means
you actually like her too.
This is a goodnight kiss.