[English subtitles are available]
[Love on a Shoestring]
[Episode 23]
Actually, when we broke up,
I was...
very sad.
I felt I was betrayed.
But you came to me today.
I know you still...
Yes.
I still like you very much.
I like you very much.
So, love
can't be forgotten easily.
But we really can't be together.
Why?
Since we love each other,
why can't we be together?
Can you forgive your dad?
If I forgive my dad,
what about my mom?
She was so miserable and lonely
in her last days.
What about her?
That's why I'm not forcing you.
You said you're not forcing me.
But if I don't make up with my dad,
you will break up with me.
I don't know what this has to do with it.
The love I want
is like my parents' love.
Although they quarrel
for trivial things
every day,
their love won't fade away.
Because they have the same values.
But we are really different.
I think money is very important.
So I'm frugal.
But because of your dad,
you hate money.
If you can't resolve your inner conflict,
there will always be friction between us.
Do you think this kind of relationship can last long?
Here's your change.
Thank you.
Please come again.
Welcome.
Why are you here?
It's all Manager's fault.
On the opening day,
he insisted on scheduling a shift for me.
So I couldn't come to celebrate with you.
That's why I came as soon as I'm free.
They made me lose
two employees in one go.
I'm short-handed.
Manager, Qianqian.
-Jiali.
Congratulations. You really have opened a store.
Thank you.
I smelt the bread's fragrance from afar.
They must be made by Jiali,
Yuanchong's girlfriend.
What do you want to eat today?
My treat.
Really?
Let me do it.
No need for that.
They all smell so good.
Don't you think they're weird?
They don't have any of the intimacy
you'd expect from a couple.
It's not good
to act intimately during work.
Now they're behaving
more distantly than us.
So?
Based on my experience,
they are
on the outs.
When my wife and I
-have a disagreement,
-Really?
we'd give each other the silent treatment.
We'd pretend not to see each other.
I can see.
You heard it?
Invisible man.
It's my lunch break now.
I can't have lunch with you.
It's okay.
Our plan is
to eat with you
after you get off work.
It's not convenient.
Why?
I need to clean this place after work.
It'll be very tiring.
I just want to go home to rest.
I'll be back in about an hour.
Then you can go out
to have lunch with Jiali.
Is this for me?
It's not for you.
We're here to exchange money with you.
Aunt,
I know you need 500,000 NT dollars.
So, I would like to ask you
to give the 300,000 NT dollars you borrowed from Jiali
back to her
and tell her
you don't need the money anymore.
You mean...
you'll lend me money?
Yes.
Because Jiali
needs her money to run the store.
I don't want her
to be easily held back from achieving her dream.
You also know Jiali needs money to run her store,
but you still borrowed money from her.
How dare you!
Mom,
-I...
-Stop talking.
Return the money to Jiali as soon as possible.
Tell your husband to find a job as soon as possible
so that you can pay back the money borrowed from Yuan.
It's okay even if you
don't pay back the money.
W-What?
It's not okay.
But...
I hope
you can promise me one thing.
What is it?
I hope you
can contact Jiali frequently.
It's okay even if it's just a simple greeting.
How are you?
How have you been?
How is your work going?
It's also okay if you just ask her if she's full.
I want Jiali
to feel more cared-for.
Look.
Even Yuan knows he should treat Jiali well.
As her mother,
you haven't even given her a greeting.
She's your daughter too!
Grandma, don't be angry.
Of course I can do that.
In the past,
my youngest daughter was still little.
I really couldn't spare time,
so I ignored Jiali.
But I can do it now.
Jiali is my daughter.
Of course I would care about her.
Thank you.
I thought
you asked me to ask Jiali's mother to come out
because you wanted her to pay back the money.
Instead, you gave her money
and asked her to return it to Jiali.
Why are you so silly?
Grandma,
I'm not silly.
I just chose
the current best solution
for Jiali.
I think
I'm very smart.
Don't be mad at Jiali.
Since you left that day,
she's been very upset after she came back
from work every day.
She has barely eaten.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
Actually, I know
Jiali cares about you very much.
I know.
So I'm not mad at her.
She said she lacks love.
As her boyfriend,
I should give her lots of love.
Yes.
Great.
When you left that day,
I saw your facial expression.
You looked very hurt.
I was so worried.
I was worried you suffered a blow
and wouldn't dare to love her anymore.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Even if I feel hurt,
I'll become stronger
and love Jiali forever.
Yes.
Great!
I love you too.
Thank you, Grandma.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Somehow, my shoes
are chafing my feet today.
Really?
What are you doing?
No, put me down.
L-Look.
Someone...
is watching us.
So what?
I'd rather let them watch us
than let your feet
feel any discomfort.
Let's go.
I'm going to order something.
Excuse me?
Min.
Oscar?
Long time no see.
Just now, why...
My shoes are chafing my feet.
Still exaggerated.
Yes.
No.
Elly.
Your friend?
He was my classmate in Singapore.
Hello.
I'm Michael.
I'm Oscar.
Hello.
I'm her boyfriend.
Okay.
Why don't we...
friend each other?
-Okay.
-It'll be easier to contact each other in the future.
Just contact me.
If you want to get in touch with Elly,
just contact me.
Okay.
Baby, do your feet feel uncomfortable?
No.
Let me carry you.
No need for that.
Right,
send me the contact information
of my former classmate.
It'll be weird if we contact each other through you.
I'm your boyfriend.
I think it's fine.
It won't be weird.
But he's my former classmate.
My former classmate...
is your former classmate.
Your former classmate is my former classmate.
We are on intimate terms, right?
But...
It's great to meet you here.
The shop offers a 50% discount on the second cup of coffee.
You... don't want coffee, right?
Elly, do you want a cup?
If it's your treat,
I don't mind having another cup.
I want one too.
You don't drink excitant drinks, right?
It's okay to drink a cup occasionally, right?
But if both of you want a cup,
you can already get a 50% discount on the second cup.
Well...
It's okay.
My treat.
I'll buy four cups and give you two cups.
You can give the other cup to anyone.
Don't waste money.
Forget it. I don't want it.
Is she angry?
Can't you see?
Is she angry because I want a cup of coffee?
No.
Elly.
You actually don't understand.
[Closed]
I'm off work.
Bye bye.
This can't continue.
Sun Jiali,
Yuanchong didn't do anything wrong.
You should take the initiative to apologize.
It's not sincere to apologize via a text.
I should apologize to Yuanchong
face to face tomorrow.
You scared me.
[Sorry]
Jiali,
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me
for not talking to you these days
and giving you the silent treatment.
I've reflected on myself.
No matter how different our opinions are,
I shouldn't have given you the silent treatment.
I always said I love you
and I want to treat you well,
but what I did goes against
what I said completely.
Please forgive me
and give me one more chance.
If you are
still angry,
you can hit me,
scold me,
and kick me.
You can do anything to me.
Instead of hitting me,
you're hugging me.
Does this...
Does this mean you'll forgive me?
I want to apologize to you too.
Yuanchong,
can you forgive me?
You didn't do anything wrong.
You have your own opinions
and ideas.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have forced you or compelled you.
From now on,
I will do my best to stand in your shoes.
I know you did it for my own good.
You were helping me protect my dream.
I was too stubborn.
I even said I wanted to break up with you.
Stop talking.
If you continue to talk,
aren't you worried that I'll run away?
Will you run away?
Of course I won't.
What are you watching?
A new movie. It's funny.
Don't watch this.
What are you doing?
Watch this health show.
I don't want to watch it. I want to watch that movie.
It's about the importance of sleeping early
and getting up early to our memory.
Your memory has been getting worse, right?
Watch.
-Watch.
-Who said my memory has been getting worse?
I want to watch...
Watch.
Yes.
It says the veteran driver often takes the wrong routes.
Really.
Baby, are you reading a book?
Don't read this.
Here.
I found two books recently.
I recommend them to you.
They are about regimens.
You said you have
cold hands and feet these days.
Listen.
It can adjust your sleep, nutrition, emotions, and physical activities.
I noticed that your emotions haven't been stable recently.
I think you can
drink this.
Baby.
What are you doing?
Wait.
Baby.
Why... Why are you packing your things?
I plan to move back tomorrow.
Move back?
No.
Don't touch them!
Why do you want to move back?
Because I think
I can't breathe here.
You can't breathe?
I'm going to open the window.
That's not what I mean!
I think
we should
keep a proper distance.
We're so inseparable
that we don't even have
any private space.
Baby, we...
we are in a relationship, right?
What's wrong with being inseparable?
You still don't understand.
I'm accusing you of being too controlling.
You're too macho.
Now I can't even make friends.
Macho?
I... I'm not macho.
I...
I'm just...
just...
Just...
Just what?
I'm just a little afraid.
Afraid of losing you.
But this is what a macho man is like.
When you're in a relationship,
you keep a close eye on your girlfriend.
You don't allow me to do
what I want to do.
I don't like this kind of relationship that makes me feel fettered.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
I really like you a lot.
But I think it's better
that we keep a distance for the time being.
In this way, we can continue
our relationship.
I'm going to sleep in the living room.
Baby, no.
You sleep in the bedroom.
Wait.
Baby, you're not angry?
Good night.
Go to bed early.
President Wang.
Can I talk to you?
Jian Keke reminded me
not to use Mr. Fang to control you again,
because you're Haikuo's best friend.
Why did you take the initiative to come to see me?
Actually, I'm not the one who wants to see you.
Someone asked me for help
in order to talk to you face to face.
Who?
-It's us!
You're Jian Keke's parents?
Yes.
So,
today, you're here to condemn me?
No.
We're here to
resolve the grudges between you
and Haikuo as father and son.
Your daughter and my son have already broken up.
What does the relationship between my son and me
have to do with you guys?
Because our daughter Keke and Haikuo
love each other.
But
because of you,
they had no choice but to break up.
We hope that
Haikuo and Keke can be together.
Whether Haikuo and Keke will be together
is his own decision.
I'm sorry, but there's nothing I can do on this matter.
So there's nothing to talk about.
See you.
-No.
-President.
-Let me tell you.
-Wait.
I did talk to Haikuo.
I can feel that
he really respects you.
What's more,
he admires you very much.
Since childhood, we've been educated that
no parents in the world make mistakes.
But I always think that
there's something wrong with this saying.
There are no human beings
who never make mistakes.
Just take myself as an example.
I once lent all our family's savings
to one of my best friends
because of my momentary softheartedness.
As a result, even until now,
I haven't got any money back.
Because of that, my daughter and my wife
have been suffering with me.
Dear, it's all in the past.
So what?
A father also makes mistakes sometimes.
Right?
He's not a god.
-Right.
-Right?
Right.
What's more, we often educate our children and say that
if you do something wrong,
you have to admit your mistake and apologize.
Right?
Then let me ask you.
As a parent,
if you do something wrong,
don't you need to admit your mistake and apologize to your child?
Also,
a child usually puts his parents
in the most important position in his heart.
If you really love him,
don't give him a hard time.
Why did you ask him to make a choice
between you two?
That was quite cruel.
Right?
-Right.
-Right!
I still have an important meeting to attend.
You guys can leave now.
We've talked so much to persuade you, but you...
-Don't stop me.
-Alright.
-I really...
He's just like a stone.
What do you want to tell him?
Okay. I won't talk to him.
-How stubborn he is.
-How about we knock him with an iron hammer?
No need.
As the president, he's a bigshot.
"President" means that he's always dismissed.
I just don't want to come.
-How stubborn.
-Bye.
Yes, how stubborn.
I wonder if President Wang's attitude
will soften.
Oh God.
God.
Dear gods,
please bless us so that President Wang will go learn about Haikuo
and let Haikuo be with Keke.
Otherwise,
the Accounting Department will become a cruel hell soon.
What?
You want to move out of Michael Zhao's home?
He's keeping an eye on me too closely.
I'm afraid one day,
I won't even have a male friend.
I didn't expect that Michael Zhao
would be such a male chauvinist.
Right. I didn't sense that.
He usually looks like this
and like this.
But let me tell you.
This kind of man is actually very dangerous.
The stronger his desire for controlling his girlfriend is,
the more easily he'll fail to control himself.
By that time, you may become
a horror lover.
I didn't expect that he would be like this.
Right. How is that possible?
He doesn't look like that.
He just doesn't look like that.
Elly.
If you really care about Michael Zhao,
just have a talk with me.
Go ahead.
But I only have ten minutes.
I have a meeting to attend later.
Do you remember Michael Zhao once said that
all this time, he didn't believe that you liked him?
Yes, I remember.
But later, he believed it,
so we became boyfriend and girlfriend.
No.
I don't think he has ever believed it all this time.
That's why he feels insecure.
What nonsense are you talking about?
In the past, boys always chased me initiatively.
Now I've taken the initiative to chase him.
How could he feel insecure?
That's the point.
In the past, boys always chased you initiatively.
What's more, those were all rich men.
So, you've never believed that
I genuinely like you,
because my past targets
were all rich men?
The woman I love
should love me only.
Because
I will also love her only
wholeheartedly.
Then I'm more eager to live with you.
Only in this way
can you sense my sincerity.
He really doesn't believe it?
Michael Zhao really likes you.
He likes you very much.
That's why he feels so insecure.
He did that because he was afraid that
you would be taken away by a man who is better than him.
But it is obvious that I really like him.
Why doesn't he believe in me?
Elly,
don’t forget that
before you dated each other,
you and Michael Zhao
had been colleagues for many years.
Your affections for him
appeared
so suddenly.
I don't care what reason you have.
Return the money now.
Do you have a conscience?
Jiali's 300,000 NT dollars,
and Yuan's 500,000 NT dollars
were all pocketed by you privately.
How... How dare you!
-Stop talking about it!
-Grandma.
Why did you come back suddenly?
To whom did you say that Yuanchong had given 500,000 NT dollars?
Did he give the money to my mom?
No.
You... You heard it wrong.
Grandma.
Don't lie to me.
Why did Yuanchong give her money?
Because...
She thought that I didn't give her enough money,
so she borrowed money again from Yuanchong?
No.
Your mother didn't borrow money from him.
Yuan just took the initiative to give her money.
He hoped that
your mother would return the money to you.
I was wondering
why there had been no news
after so many days,
so I called to urge her.
So, you mean that
she not only took my money,
but also took away Yuanchong's 500,000 NT dollars?
Yes.
Your mom told me that she was in short of money
and asked me not to tell you two about it.
Jiali.
Don't blame Yuan.
He was worried that without the operating funds,
your shop would go bankrupt.
Jiali!
Jiali, where are you going?
You have to know that
sharing food is the same as sharing love.
Yes.
Excuse me. I need to answer the phone.
Okay.
Hello, Grandma.
What's the matter?
What?
Okay. I got it.
I'll go there right now.
I don't want to hear any reason from you.
Go bring Yuanchong's 500,000 NT dollars
for me now.
Otherwise, I'll call the police
and tell them that you swindled him.
I didn't swindle him.
He gave me the money himself.
Do you have a conscience?
Yuan gave the money to you
and told you to return the money to Jiali.
I didn't say that I wouldn't return the money.
I'll just return all the money
together later.
-You...
-No way!
It's fine if you don't return my money to me.
Go withdraw Yuanchong's
500,000 NT dollars from the bank right now.
Let's go get the money.
-No!
-Let's go get the money.
-Let's go. Stop nagging.
Let's go get the money.
Jiali!
Sun Jiali!
How could you treat me like this?
Then how did you treat me?
Have you ever regarded me as your daughter?
Have you ever cared about me?
You only care about
whether I'm useful or not.
I was just like a fool
and had been longing for family love that I couldn't get.
In the end, I neglected those who really cared about me.
From now on,
I, Sun Jiali,
won't long for such a feeling of
being needed.
My efforts
will only be left to those who truly care about me
and show concern for me.
Well said!
Jiali,
I fully support you.
As for you,
speaking of you...
How did you fulfill your responsibilities as a mother?
You've gone too far.
I'm telling you that you should know your place.
Give her the money now.
That's right.
You're Jiali's mother.
If you do this,
you'll put Jiali in an awkward position.
Let's go.
Go withdraw the money from the bank.
-Come with me.
-Mom.
Let's go withdraw the money from the bank.
Stop nagging. Let's go.
She has gone too far.
Li Yuanchong.
I promise you that
from now on,
I will love myself more.
If you want it,
you can also love me more.
In the end, it's the same as the beginning.
I'm back to my single life.
Elly.
I'm sorry.
Are you trying to break up with me?
I like you so much.
How could I break up with you?
I'm apologizing to you
because I forgot to tell you
the reason why I fell in love with you.
All this time,
the condition I've set for myself for choosing a spouse
is that I should select a man with three high standards.
But
these are all based on the rules of the outside world.
Actually, what I really want is
ordinary happiness.
Ordinary happiness?
You're dating me
just because I'm ordinary?
Yes.
Because I'm quite ordinary, too.
So,
from now on,
I don't need to sleep with an eyeshade anymore.
Nor do I need to care about my appearance
and dressing style so much.
Because I know that
you won't stop loving me
because I'm ordinary.
So,
I won't stop loving you
because you're ordinary.
Even if I'm not rich,
and even if I'm ordinary,
will you still love me?
We can
earn money together.
I forgot to tell you that
I've put all my designer handbags
on a second-hand website and sold them at auction.
I've even earned a sum of money.
We can put
this sum of money
in our fund for purchasing a house.
Also,
I've deleted
the contact numbers of all irrelevant men
from my mobile phone.
I only kept my dad's,
my relatives'
and all our company's...
You don't have to tell me these things.
It'll be fine that you just like me.
Mi.
Mi, don't cry.
Don't cry.
Mi.
All this time,
I've always wanted to say that
I don't dare to be with you,
because I'm not confident in myself.
But today, after hearing you say that,
I feel very happy.
Mi, don't cry.
Please don't leave me.
Silly boy, I won't leave you.
I really like you so much.
I like you very much.
I also like you very much.
I want to talk with you.
I want to apologize to you.
Can you give me this chance?
Stop looking.
There's nothing that is worth looking at.
You haven't got a child yet.
You won't understand
how much a father would miss his child.
What you want to tell me is not about missing your child,
but something else, right?
For a father,
the most painful thing
is that his own child
returned the money for upbringing
to him so resolutely.
He didn't want a single penny.
He just wanted to cut off the relationship in this way.
But can you measure the family affection
between father and son with money?
If you have nothing important to say,
please leave first.
There's nothing about the past that's worth talking about between us.
This is my most precious photo album.
What is recorded inside
is about your birthday every year.
Every year on your birthday,
the three of us in our family would take a photo together,
because you were our baby.
Your birth brought us joy.
But since the day when your mother passed away,
I've not only lost my beloved wife,
but also lost my most precious son.
Since then,
every year on your birthday,
I've faied to stay by your side.
Because you rejected me.
Because I refused to apologize.
That's why we've wasted time for many years.
As for the good wishes I wanted to give you,
I could only ask someone to secretly take
a photo of you on your birthday,
and then I would hold the photo alone
to sing the song of Happy Birthday privately.
Haikuo,
you're a year older now again.
I hope your wish will come true.
Happy birthday to you.
I can only care about my son secretly.
But even though I missed you so much,
I still refused to apologize.
Because I always thought that
one day, you would understand
why I had taken such great pains as a father.
Son,
it was my fault.
I'm sorry.
[Preview]
You proposed to Elly?
Am I quite sincere?
But you're going back to Singapore
with Elly next week to meet her parents
for the first time, aren't you?
You'll give them a wedding invitation letter when you meet them for the first time.
Does buying a ring
has the same meaning as what I know?
I want to get engaged with you
so that I can be your future wife.
Yu Fen.
I like you.
Will you be my girlfriend?
You should go sign the contract personally.
I'll ask Chen Shi, the manager of Division One, to go with you.
General Manager, TV Group's representative is here.
Haikuo?