[English subtitles are available]
[Love on a Shoestring]
[Episode 3]
This dried turnip is delicious.
My mom made this.
Your mom made it?
Yes.
Mr. Zhang, listen.
Nowadays, we can
buy any kind of food outside.
But only the food made by our mothers
is irreplaceable.
Also, we'll miss it after eating it.
So I believe your fermented bean curd
should be what everyone misses.
Otherwise, it wouldn't have been so popular
during Mr. Wang's market research.
The flavor we miss?
Dried turnip?
Fermented bean curd?
Maybe they can create a new flavor.
Maybe.
Mr. Zhang, please
develop a new flavor.
I'm giving the dried turnip made by my mom
to you.
Okay.
Why are Haikuo and Keke here?
Who are they here for?
Elly.
Can I take a look at your hand?
Your life line and career line
are complete.
But something is missing.
What?
Me.
Today,
I have a small gift for you.
What gift?
Open it.
It's Zhang Zhanpeng.
You know him?
Many people want to do business with them.
I heard that your company
just messed up a collaboration.
So it's Mr. Zhang.
Looks like their relationship has already eased.
Mr. Wang,
I admire you.
I'll leave my fermented bean curd to you.
Okay.
Mr. Zhang, thank you so much
for being willing to forgive me.
Next,
I'll fulfill my promise made today.
Then give me the contract as soon as possible.
No problem.
We are good friends now.
Don't forget
you promised to give me a jar of dried turnip.
No problem.
Leave it to me.
I'm leaving.
Allow me.
Mr. Zhang, your wine.
Thank you.
-Bye.
Bye.
W-What's wrong?
Thank you.
You're welcome. It's my duty.
Jiali and I held you up this time.
I remember that very clearly.
So you remember it clearly?
Everything?
Yes.
What I mean is not what happened recently.
What you mean is...
What I mean is...
the first time we met.
Hello, Jiali.
Emergency room?
Which hospital?
Okay.
Bye.
Remember
not to spill the beans later.
I know.
You don't want Grandma to be worried.
That's why you asked me to pick you up.
Sun Jiali,
you knew you felt uncomfortable.
Why did you still go to work?
The person on duty today asked for a leave.
Manager couldn't find a replacement,
so I wanted to relieve his burden.
You fainted while at work.
Is this how you relieve his burden?
Can you please
learn to be selfish?
Don't always think for others.
Think for yourself first, okay?
Okay, I know.
Let me ask you.
Does Zhigang know you passed out?
I told him.
What did he say?
He happens to have a job interview today.
Work is important.
You'd better pray
that he really went to work.
Otherwise, I don't know when he can
pay back the money.
He said
he needs me.
I need you too.
I need you
to take good care of yourself.
Don't make us worried anymore, okay?
Okay.
Do I look pale?
What are you looking at?
Is there an announcement recently released in this area
that reminds you to pay attention to weird people?
No.
Nothing.
Go in and rest.
[Trendee
Business Department]
It's been three months.
I finally got my first order.
And it's a big order.
I'm so happy.
You look so happy.
Mr. Wang,
you're my God
and my lucky star.
Because of you,
I think I'm going to turn the tide.
Finally, I won't be at the bottom.
You also helped
make Mr. Zhang cool off this time.
Not really.
I just delivered the wine.
You had to face him head-on.
If it weren't for your professionalism,
Mr. Zhang wouldn't have cooled off so easily.
But... Keke
played the most important role this time.
Mr. Wang,
will you be angry
that I told Keke about your schedule.
Scold me if you want.
You really...
did a great job.
If it weren't for Jian Keke,
Mr. Zhang wouldn't have agreed to sign the contract that day.
Really?
She really is
a surprising girl.
Are you sure
it's Jian Keke we're talking about?
There's no time.
I have to hurry.
Mr. Wang,
what do you want to do?
No way.
Is what you're thinking...
the same...
as what I'm thinking?
No, Mr. Wang.
No, Mr. Wang!
No.
I want...
No!
-Mr. Wang.
-I want to go to the toilet.
That's good.
I'm so full.
You've finished eating, right?
I'm going to clear the table then.
Grandma, let me do it.
You offered me a free meal.
Just
leave it to me.
You're a guest.
Let me do it.
What guest?
I'm yours.
I'm a member of your family.
Don't regard me as an outsider in this.
Yes.
Keke is right.
[Linchen Yueyun, Jiali's grandma
Thrifty and hardworking]
You're family.
Right?
Keke, go wash the dishes.
I'm going to prepare some fruits.
Jiali, wipe the table.
If you don't rest well,
I'll tell Grandma that you fainted.
Keke.
I should thank you.
Jiali's parents haven't been with her
since she was little.
You've always accompanied her.
I really want to thank you.
Grandma, don't mention it.
I should thank Jiali
for letting me have a grandma who's a good cook.
I'm so lucky.
You're so sweet.
Here.
Let me feed you one.
You're biased.
I want one too.
Take it yourself if you want it.
You're so good at acting cute.
Give it to me.
-It's sweet.
-Is it?
Yes? Here.
It's sweet.
I'm so full.
[Xingfuli Lane 68]
The hood, the clothes, and the shoes
are all the same.
It must be the same person.
A man is waiting outside your house.
Prepare your weapons and follow my instructions.
Grandma, Jiali.
-Hurry.
-Who are you?
-Let go of me!
-I'm coming.
I got him!
You brat!
Let go of me!
Stop!
-Stop!
-I'm going to beat you to death.
-What are you doing?
-What do you want?
-Grandma! Beat him!
You want to bully girls.
It's me!
It's me, Jiali.
-It's me.
-Yuanchong.
It's me.
I'm going to beat you to death.
Darn it!
I don't care who you are.
You... you know each other?
You...
He's my colleague in the convenience store.
What are you doing here?
You fainted today,
so I came to see you.
You... You fainted?
No. No.
Grandma.
Grandma, Jiali just had an IV drip
in the emergency room.
She didn't faint.
Having an IV drip in the emergency room?
No.
You...
You two...
It's important.
Why... Why didn't you tell me?
No.
I'm old. I'm useless.
You don't have to tell me anything, right?
I'm so angry.
Grandma.
I'm useless.
You go back and rest.
I'll explain to Grandma.
Grandma.
Sorry.
It's okay.
How do you know
Jiali's home address?
I took Jiali to the hospital today.
I memorized it
when I helped her register the information.
Excuse me, someone fainted.
Put her on the bed first.
Sir, please wait outside.
Your girlfriend is too tired
and has a cold.
That's why she fainted.
Let her get some sleep.
She'll feel better after the IV drip.
Don't worry too much.
She's not my...
girlfriend.
Hello, Li Yuanchong.
Where are you?
There is no one in the store now.
The owner next door told me
there's no employee in the store now.
I'll go back immediately.
Thank you for taking Jiali to the hospital.
Did your manager punish you after that?
After he knew what happened to Jiali,
he was also worried.
So he didn't say anything.
That's good.
Jiali became like that
because she waited for her boyfriend on the street at night.
She waited 56 minutes and 8 seconds.
It's safer to call a taxi.
A few days ago, the borough warden told me
a girl was followed.
So it's better to be careful.
It's okay.
My boyfriend will come to pick me up.
Your boyfriend hasn't come yet?
Not yet. I'm waiting for him to pick me up.
Let me take you home.
Don't bother.
Your boyfriend is here. I'm leaving.
He's not my...
boyfriend.
What took you so long?
When her boyfriend showed up,
he blamed her for getting off work so late
because she took someone else's shift.
In the end,
she kept apologizing to her boyfriend.
Sun Jiali really gives me a headache.
You stayed to wait for her.
Why did you hide
instead of accompanying her openly?
We are not familiar.
I was worried...
she would feel uncomfortable.
You're so thoughtful.
Could it be that you like Jiali?
No way.
I was just saying.
This is for Jiali.
Please help me give it to her.
Thank you.
O-Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Sun Jiali.
According to the content of this contract,
you focus on the distribution of both parties' interests.
I can see that you've put effort into it.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
I want
-Isn't that Mr. Zhang?
-to do my best to achieve a win-win situation
and shorten the time spent on the contract.
Haikuo offended him before, right?
When did their relationship
become so harmonious?
I'm very satisfied with this cooperation.
I'll introduce some of my good friends
to you.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Zhang,
we will give it to the legal department to stamp a seal.
Then we'll give it to your company to stamp a seal to complete the contract signing.
Mr. Zhang.
By the way,
please give this gift to Keke.
The food in this bottle contains my secret recipe.
-He's giving him a gift.
-It's
my family's heirloom.
-Mr. Zhang is giving a gift to Haikuo.
-Thank you.
Not at all.
-What's going on?
-On behalf of Keke,
I thank you, Mr. Zhang.
But
I'm very curious.
You're in the Business Department.
Keke is in the Accounting Department.
Last time, you stood me up
because of her.
Then
you came with her to apologize to me.
You're in a good relationship, right?
We're just friends for now.
But I like her.
I'm pursuing her.
You have a crush on her?
I will make her fall in love with me.
Very good.
That's what a man should do.
Don't
hide your love.
If you like someone, just say it bravely.
Right?
-Right?
-Yes.
Also,
I should put it into practice
and be perseverant.
You really don't know
how scary Jian Keke is.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Let me walk you out to your car.
No.
I insist.
Haikuo is really amazing.
He offended Mr. Zhang
and messed up the collaboration not long ago.
It's only been a few days.
I didn't expect their relationship to be so harmonious.
He even gave a gift.
That's right.
Could it be
that it was actually a rumor
that he offended Mr. Zhang?
Or are they relatives?
Otherwise, why did he give a gift?
Whatever.
That's not the point.
The point is
whether Haikuo will know we're gossiping about him like this,
considering what happened last time.
Anyway,
we're not the only ones gossiping about him.
It should be okay, right?
You're right.
Tonight,
the Business Department will have a celebratory get-together.
I'd like to invite everyone in the Accounting Department
to join us.
The Business Department's get-together?
Why do you want to invite us from the Accounting Department?
We managed to secure
the contract this time
because Jian Keke helped us a lot.
I get paid.
It was my duty.
Then... Jian Keke will confirm the number.
After I book a restaurant,
I'll text you guys the time and the address.
Who wants to go?
I want to go.
Me, too.
Elly, aren't you going?
No, I'm not going.
Okay.
Do you know what kind of help Keke offered?
No, I don't.
That's strange.
There was a chance to get to know a rich guy,
but she didn't seize the chance.
That's strange.
It's a bit strange indeed.
Judging from her personality,
I don't think
she would give up the chance so easily.
Right?
Has her appetite changed?
Or does she have a bigger appetite now?
Does she think that he's not rich enough?
There's something fishy about it.
I don't think the case is simple.
Eat it now.
The lunch break will be over soon.
Is your grandma angry?
Actually, she's not really angry.
I think that she's just
worried about me.
Of course.
You're her dear granddaughter.
Of course she's worried about you.
By the way,
your colleague asked me to give it to you.
My colleague?
A tall guy.
What's his name?
Yuanchong.
No wonder he specially came to see me.
He probably wanted to give this to me.
Have you been working with him for a long time?
He has just joined our company.
Actually, I don't know him well.
He doesn't talk much
and is silent.
You two don't know each other well, but he cares about you.
Good.
I think this is okay.
What is okay?
It's okay that he can be your new boyfriend.
Miss Jian Keke.
Why not?
I think he's good.
He's tall and cute.
I think he's upright and considerate.
He's 100 times better
-than your useless boyfriend.
-Hurry up and eat.
I really think that he's good.
If you go on talking about it,
-I'll introduce him to you.
-Then I'll…
No need.
You seem to like him a lot.
No need. I'm short of money, but I'm not short of a boyfriend.
He's really good.
You're so early.
I think, as a salesman,
it's a basic rule to arrive ahead of time.
Please give me a cup of iced Americano.
Thank you.
I got your message today.
I thought you sent it to the wrong person.
I know that we barely associate with each other
in the company at ordinary times.
So I asked you out today
to tell you something good.
I believe you know that
Wang Haikuo, the newcomer in our company,
has recently persuaded Mr. Zhang to cooperate with him.
I still remember that Mr. Zhang
once severely criticized the proposal
put forward by you.
Don't look so angry.
Otherwise,
how can I continue to talk about
Jian Keke?
Jian Keke.
That's interesting.
I think you know that
Jian Keke is obsessed with money.
But for an unknown reason,
recently, she has taken the initiative to spend 30 bucks
buying the milk which Haikuo gave her.
Jian Keke took the initiative to spend money?
So,
I want to cooperate with you.
For what?
Do you still
have feelings for Jian Keke?
It's my treat today.
So everyone,
please order as much as you want.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
[Price of Food]
This is too expensive.
Why don't you just treat us to some stir-fried food?
What are you treating us to barbeque?
Then the bonus will be used up.
I want three portions of Wagyu beef, please.
Three portions of Wagyu beef.
Three portions of Wagyu beef cost 7,500 NT dollars.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Girls will gain weight easily if they eat too much meat at night.
But I'm not trying to lose weight.
Eating meat will make you fat.
Then let's order some seafood.
Two portions of lobsters.
-Two portions of lobsters. Okay.
-Alright.
-I want three portions of lobsters, please.
Three portions of lobsters.
With their way of ordering the food like this,
I think I'll have to spend two months' salary on this meal.
It's okay.
When I booked a table, I also ordered some food.
Later, if the food isn't enough,
we can order again.
You're so considerate.
You're so generous.
It's burnt.
Congratulations to you on getting a big order, Mr. Wang.
Congratulations, Mr. Wang.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Mr. Wang.
So many people are drinking a toast to you, so you should drink it up.
Of course.
Mr. Wang can really drink a lot.
Awesome!
It's all thanks to you guys this time.
So,
eat as much as you want and drink as much beer as you want.
-Okay.
-Right. Let's eat as much as we want.
Mr. Wang, that piece of beef is very delicious.
Eat more.
Mr. Wang,
this shrimp is very chewy.
Come on. Taste it, too.
Thank you.
Keke, you're too thin.
Eat more.
Thank you.
You should eat more, too.
Don't drink too much.
Drinking alcohol is bad for your health.
You're right.
Health is important.
Mr. Wang.
I don't mean that
you shouldn't drink at all.
I mean, when others drink a toast to you, you just need to
drink a little to show courtesy.
There's no need to drink it up.
That makes sense.
Health and manners are both important.
Mr... Mr. Wang.
How obedient.
No woman can resist a man who is so loyal like a dog.
I got this first.
It's obvious that I got it first.
Just eat something else.
You're so petty.
No wonder your performance ranks last.
Get closer to each other.
Those who stand at the back, don't be blocked.
Come on. Smile happily.
Three, two, one.
It's done.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
-Mr. Wang.
-Thank you, Mr. Wang.
Then we'll go to the KTV to get a room first.
See you later. Bye.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
Bye.
-Let's go.
-Bye.
Keke.
What?
Will you also go to the KTV later?
No.
I have to go back to put the desserts in the refrigerator.
Then let me give you a ride.
No need. It's too troublesome.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
What is it? Just tell me now.
I have to tell you here?
How about
telling me about it when you come to work tomorrow?
I'll go back first.
Don't force anything.
This shows that God gives you more time to think about it.
Mr. Wang.
It's not too late to repent now.
You're right.
I'm too impatient.
I should take it step by step.
No.
That's not what I mean.
I...
-I mean...
-Make her have a crush on me first.
In that case, the chance of success for my confession of love
is 1,000 percent.
Mr. Wang, no.
Mr. Wang.
It's so good that I can
see you again.
[The amount of this transfer transaction: 100,000 NT dollars]
[Note: Education fees. Remittance failed.]
Why did I have such a nightmare?
Is this a warning?
[Trendee]
It's such a large bouquet.
It's so beautiful.
These are real flowers.
So romantic.
Seeing Elly smile like that,
I think there must be something wrong.
Why are you all standing around my desk?
Keke.
You're finally here.
I've just checked it online.
The Taurus will have luck for love today.
Cupid is ready to shoot his arrow.
Go and see who gave you the flowers.
Who gave you the flowers?
Keke.
I think you must have been a carbonated beverage in your previous life.
Otherwise, why am I so happy with love bubbles
whenever I see you?
Michael Zhao!
Is everything okay with Mr. Zhang's project?
Yes.
Keep an eye on it closely.
Don't make them feel slighted.
Then help me make an appointment with Mr. Sun.
Mr. Sun
seems to have decided on his cooperation partner.
I know he has decided on it.
But just help me make an appointment.
Okay. Got it.
Mr. Zhao.
-You're back from your vacation?
-Mr. Zhao.
[Michael Zhao, Manger of Division Three of the Business Department, a very confident man who is handsome in a non-mainstream way]
I'm sorry.
I'm used to it.
Hello.
I'm Wang Haikuo from Division One.
The skin of your hands is so rough.
Does Keke like this type?
The skin of my hands
is just too tender and too soft.
You look stern with an angular face.
You have dark and deep eyes,
thick eyebrows,
a high nose,
and a perfect lip shape.
You're really the same as people said.
You're as good as me.
Mr. Zhao, what can I do for you?
Call me Michael Zhao.
Michael Zhao.
What can I do for you, please?
Nothing.
I went on a vacation previously.
I haven't had a chance to say hello to you.
We finally met each other.
Hello.
I'm thinking
in the future, we'll
have many chances to communicate with each other.
That's strange.
Mr. Zhao's business objects
are usually some chairwomen
or rich married women.
Why do I feel that
he's targeting you now?
Really?
I think
it's just a competition between men.
A competition?
Really?
Michael Zhao.
Why did Michael Zhao suddenly appear?
Keke.
Why are you looking at me in that way?
Nothing. I'm thinking about something.
What's wrong?
This is the reimbursement form of the Design Department.
It was among the Business Department's receipts
which you gave me just now.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Jian Keke.
What should I do?
What's wrong with Keke?
This shows that
she's scared.
I'm afraid
she's under a lot of pressure now.
Jian Keke, what are you doing?
There seems to be something wrong with this account.
Check it for me.
I'm sorry.
This one.
Check it for me.
Okay. I...
I'll check it again later and then give it to you.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for your hard work.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Keke, is there something urgent?
How come you have that kind of smell?
It's so disgusting.
What smell do I have?
I think that's the smell.
It's Michael Zhao's smell.
Michael Zhao's smell?
Yes.
You probably don't know that
Keke is very scared of Michael Zhao.
Because Michael Zhao
once pursued Keke crazily.
Very crazily.
I'll go wash my hands first and then attend the meeting.
Ten bucks.
Jian Keke.
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
Seeing your expression, I know that
you haven't forgotten me.
[Preview]
I'm not the one who Michael Zhao likes.
I didn't force him to chase you, either.
Please don't waste everyone's time.
We still have work to do. Get lost!
You're not saying what you really think.
Why do you like to take away someone else's boyfriend so much?
Why are we wearing the same bracelets?
There are many swindlers now.
Some cheat others for money, and some cheat others for sex.
Who are you calling a swindler?
So you want to chase Jian Keke again?
I like Jian Keke, too.
Let's compete with each other fairly.
Later, when I throw the bridal bouquet,
you must catch it.
I like you.
Will you be my girlfriend?