♪Regardless of the length of my journey♪
♪Or how intertwined our fate is♪
♪As I climb countless mountains♪
♪Will I find my answer?♪
♪I gaze upon the dark night♪
♪My sword to the sky, the moon shines♪
♪Blood has tarnished the sand dunes♪
♪I try to brush it off♪
♪Feud and vendetta,
they go as quickly as they come♪
♪Life or death is decided within seconds
so why care about the outcome?♪
♪Life is like a tide
and we, the current♪
♪Who can come out unscathed?♪
♪Right or wrong♪
♪There's no turning back♪
♪To him I go♪
♪I will not head back♪
♪A thousand pots of wine♪
♪A million aftertastes♪
♪Let's chug it♪
♪To what we have been through!♪
♪Oh, this burning ambition♪
♪But the end of my journey
is still far away♪
♪Yet it never dies away♪
♪I will chase after my dream♪
♪The towering waves♪
♪Try to stop me♪
♪But I have my faith♪
♪Adamancy is my name♪
=Heroes=
=Episode 3=
(The dragon summons the rain,
The Red-Sleeved wields his sword)
(Pobanmen)
(Di Feijing, Six Half Hall)
Elder, the box...
Say less.
It is meaningless to say any more.
The most important thing right now
is to kill Su Mengzhen.
Tell Lei Hen to take care of him.
Yes.
Wonderful.
Great.
The Red Sleeve Blade
cuts at the speed of light.
If I had known
the target was Su Mengzhen,
(Madam Dou, Six Half Hall)
I would've taken this job for free.
(Lei Hen, Six Half Hall)
Amitabha.
All beings are equal.
I charge for
the assassination of Su Mengzhen,
(Monk Huayi, Six Half Hall)
just as I would for any other lives.
It is unbecoming of a monk
to be greedy.
It is unnatural for an old lady to kill
as well.
Charging money
for doing work for the Hall?
I can't believe both of you.
Amitabha.
Fighters.
We must win
this battle.
Failure is not an option.
See to it that Su Mengzhen
meets his demise.
Yes!
Are you the messenger from Baixu Garden?
I am.
Please come up.
If you seek the holder
of the Red Sleeve Blade,
you have found him.
I am Su Mengzhen.
He didn't look surprised
by the mention of your name at all.
My master, Recluse Tianyi,
asked me to deliver this to you.
Thank you for making the trip.
You're an interesting young man.
Many in the martial arts world
would be flabbergasted
at the mention of the name Su Mengzhen.
But you didn't seem
to be taken aback at all.
My name is Wang Xiaoshi.
Does that surprise you?
The successor
of Baixu Garden is interesting indeed.
Indeed.
Thank you, young man.
We shall bid farewell for now.
If you ever find yourself
in the Capital,
you can tell them
that you are a friend of Su Mengzhen.
It is good to make friends
in the martial arts world.
From now on,
you are my friends as well.
All right.
Farewell.
Let's go.
(Yang)
W... Why are you making promises again?
You just met each other.
What... Why...
How did he become your friend?
Sometimes,
there are people in this world
that you just know
you are meant to befriend.
My lady,
(Mo, Six Half Hall)
we didn't manage to get the box.
What are we going to tell them?
Father said as long as we got the box,
the Six Half Hall
and the House of Sunset Drizzle
would be able
to discuss things in a civil manner,
without the need to draw swords.
But since he went back on his words,
there's no need
for me to get the box.
I'm afraid you'll be punished
by the Hall for doing so, my lady.
So what?
I would endure anything
for that person.
(Yang)
Do you reckon
those are our  enemies or friends?
You're the advisor. You make a guess.
Is your archer here?
No. He went elsewhere.
What a bad timing.
It's Gu Dong.
(Yang)
Mr. Su. Mr. Yang.
Gu Dong.
Why are you here?
As per House Master's orders,
I have come
to escort you to the Capital.
On the House Master's orders?
I shall trouble you then.
Tension is high in the Capital.
I'm sure you must've received the news
on your way here.
What do you plan to do next, Mr. Su?
Pay a visit to the House Master
and eliminate the disloyal.
Very well.
I have come
to assist you in disposing
of all disloyal members
of the House, Mr. Su.
You think there are traitors
among us as well?
Yes.
I have already been
investigating the matter in secret.
I have the list of traitors right here.
Should we help them?
Not for now.
He is Su Mengzhen, after all.
Pity.
I am one of them as well.
I cannot betray my men.
So I'm afraid your life
will have to end here, Mr. Su.
The Six Half Hall has twelve Elders.
Wuxie, how many are here?
The monk to the east
is the Eighth Elder, Monk Huayi.
The old lady to the west
is the Seventh Elder,
Madam Dou of Mount Qilian.
This formation
appears to be the doing
of the Fourth Elder, Lei Hen.
I wonder if he is here as well.
The Four Elders.
All of them are tough fighters.
Gu Dong,
what is your identity then?
The Ninth Elder
of the Six Half Hall, Gu Dong.
I've been meaning to have a duel
with you, Su Mengzhen,
the greatest red-sleeved swordsman.
All right.
I'll grant you this opportunity.
The House of Sunset Drizzle
shall purge our sect of all traitorous.
Let's not waste time.
Come at me all at once.
Get them!
Watch out!
Mother!
Are you all right, Mother?
The dart was poisoned!
It's time for us to help.
No.
He can handle it.
Mother...
Mother!
You'll pay for this, Su Mengzhen!
There is no way out
for both of you.
I'll take care
of the archers on the right.
Can you hold off the left?
Yes.
But I'll die.
It's time for us to curb the violent
and protect the weak.
Protect the weak?
Don't let him hear that.
Thank you for helping us.
Thankfully, both of you came back.
Not at all.
Are you all right,
Mengzhen?
He suffered some minor injuries.
Nothing he can't handle.
Mr. Su!
Your cough must be
the effect of a long-term illness.
I suffer from
about four terminal illnesses
and around six
that don't even have names.
When all of them
act up at the same time,
they help to keep me awake instead.
As long as I'm still awake,
I won't die.
Lei Hen's setup was good.
Ambush, assassins,
and archers.
Wuxie,
you should thank them.
If it weren't for them,
you would've been dead by now.
I believe you were their target.
No one can kill me,
but I can't say the same for you.
Now you've really surprised me.
The two of you
have been kind to lend us a hand.
But why did you help me?
To protect the...
One should help
when seeing injustice in one's way.
No need to mention it, Mengzhen.
I've met Wang Xiaoshi.
But who are you?
I am Bai Choufei.
Bai Choufei
and Wang Xiaoshi.
Since both of you decided to help me,
you should come with me.
I want both of you
to come with me to Pobanmen.
Are you still going to their branch?
Gu Dong is dead.
Hua Wucuo has yet to make a move.
There is no better time than now.
The Six Half Hall would go as far
as killing me to help Hua Wucuo.
I must have a proper talk with them.
Otherwise, are we supposed
to charge into the Capital
with just the four of us?
But we're not members
of the House of Sunset Drizzle.
You weren't,
but you are now.
You're right.
We are now.
What do you mean?
Because our intervention
ruined the Six Half Hall's plan.
The only one who dares to challenge them
is the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Enough.
Give me the word.
Are you coming along or not?
Of course, I will.
I will too.
But Mengzhen,
your martial sister, Wen Rou...
(Yiji Inn)
You've come at last.
This way, please, Miss.
I've been waiting all day for you.
The dishes are all ready.
If you had come any later,
they would've gone cold.
Who told you to prepare these?
A man with the surname Wang
told us to prepare these.
Please enjoy your meal.
Call me if you need anything.
I guess he still has a heart.
The food looks delicious.
Wang Xiaoshi knows his stuff.
Who are you?
How do you know Wang Xiaoshi?
It's to be expected
that you don't know me.
I've heard your name countless times,
Young Lady of the Wen Family.
My name is Yang Wuxie.
Your martial brother
sent me here to protect you.
Mengzhen is here too?
He and your two friends
went to hit the Six Half Hall's branch.
My friends?
Impossible.
Who do you think my martial brother is?
As if he would bring
those incompetent men to do that.
Tell me.
Who are you?
What are you after?
"After"?
I told you the truth.
Your martial brother sent me here.
In that case,
tell me about the three of them.
Your martial brother is Su Mengzhen.
They call him
the greatest red-sleeved swordsman.
Isn't that right?
Everyone in the Capital knows that.
I was talking about the other two.
One of them is Wang Xiaoshi.
He wields the Retainment.
He is handsome and earnest.
He is forthright.
He carries the air of a hero.
The other guy's name is Bai Choufei.
He is dressed in white
and good with daggers.
He is direct and blunt.
I suppose you could call him
good-looking as well.
Who are you fooling?
One is a wild monkey from the mountains,
and the other is a cunning fox
with a sharp tongue.
They don't sound
like anything you described.
Do you think this is my first day
roaming the martial arts world?
You definitely
don't look like a good guy.
I don't look like a good guy?
Do you know what they call me?
"The Sincere and Honest."
The Yang family
only has one son in each generation.
We only produce good people.
The bad is not allowed
to enter the ancestral shrine.
Why won't you believe me?
"Sincere and honest"?
Mengzhen, why are you here?
Liar!
Greetings, Mr. Su.
(Shi Wukui, House of Sunset Drizzle)
Wukui, who are you to me?
I am your most loyal servant.
I would die for you if you command it.
I trust you.
But if a person truly cares for another,
they won't wish
to see them die for their sake.
But I am willing to die for you.
I would have no regrets.
I want you to be my trusted aide,
not a subject who will die for me.
Remember that.
Yes, sir.
(Pobanmen)
Sir, Lei Mei is here.
I'll leave her to you.
Three people from the Six Half Hall
remain a mystery to everyone.
First, you have Lei Sun.
No one knows him.
Then, you have Di Feijing.
He knows everyone, but no one knows him.
Lastly, Lei Mei.
(Lei Mei, Six Half Hall)
She appears as if she is easy to read.
But you'll come to realize
that you will only know
the things she wants you to know.
I would like to meet all of them today.
It's not a good thing
when all three of them gather together.
It makes things more fun, at least.
Don't worry.
The game has just started.
Di Feijing is waiting for us
at the top of the city wall.
If you have no friends,
go to Di Feijing.
He will be your friend.
If you have no bosom friend,
turn to Di Feijing.
He will become
your greatest friend for life.
Sounds like a pretty righteous guy.
Don't underestimate him.
The characters of the martial arts world
aren't always who they appear to be.
I need someone
to stay here to be the lookout.
You guys decide who it will be.
Of the two,
it is more dangerous to stay.
I'll stay then.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
I have matters
to discuss with First Elder Di.
I would prefer not to be disturbed.
First Elder Di.
Mr. Su.
Please come up.
If I have you stay here,
would you mind?
Of course.
If you do, that's all the more reason
for you to stay.
Do you know why?
The Young Master of Sunset Drizzle
is going to see someone
from the Six Half Hall.
If I went in with you,
I would serve as your foil.
From the first moment I saw you,
I knew that you would rather die
than allow yourself to act as so.
So my advice for you
to stay is for your sake.
I'm not usually this considerate.
I shall humbly heed your advice then.
Men from the Ministry of Justice.
They've been waiting
to watch a show ensue from our meeting
for a while now.
All of us have eyes and mouths.
Who says they are the only ones
that can enjoy a show?
Perhaps we are the spectators.
Mr. Su. Please.
You came with your sword.
Have you come to kill or to talk?
If I came with the intent to kill,
you would not get a chance to speak.
You are here to talk then.
In that case,
let us have some tea first.
It looks like Lei Hen couldn't stop
the Red Sleeve Blade, after all.
The greatest red-sleeved swordsman,
Su Mengzhen.
(Fu Zongshu, Minister of Justice)
To try to defeat him with numbers
is a joke itself.
Why haven't you raised your head?
I injured my neck.
Physician Su from our House
used to be an imperial physician.
Let him take a look at your injury.
It's an old injury. It can't be treated.
Your physician failed
to cure your cough.
It doesn't seem
like he is that good either.
It was my choice.
Between death and cough,
I chose the latter.
It's my fate to hang my head as well.
There is always a time
when one must lower their head.
If I have to choose
between this and a cough,
I would rather endure this.
I was only away for half a year,
and so many things
have happened in the Capital.
Di Feijing,
how much was the Six Half Hall
involved in all of this?
I, Di Feijing, do not deal underhand.
To be frank with you,
to prevent you
from returning to the Capital,
we mobilized 11 branches.
At the Kushuipu,
our Four Elders
combined forces to stop you,
but alas,
they were still no match for you.
It is our disgrace.
Then, given your forces,
if the Six Half Hall
truly wishes to defeat me,
it will be up to you and Lei Sun
to work together to stop me.
Why not make that battle happen today?
If you don't summon him here now,
I will end your life right here and now.
Your life is in my hands.
Would you agree?
You are upfront indeed, Mr. Su.
I have the upper hand.
I will state my conditions then.
I'll decide after hearing them.
Before I meet the House Master,
the Six Half Hall will abstain from all
internal affairs concerning the House.
That can be arranged.
Good. When I return to the Capital,
I will have a plaque made
with the words written by myself
to praise your virtue
and have it delivered to your Hall.
But Mr. Su...
Do you know in whose hands
your life is?
(Lei Sun, Six Half Hall)
This area is close to the Capital.
It is unwise to let them cause a ruckus.
(Ren Lao and Ren Yuan,
Ministry of Justice)
They are fighting down there.
Should we stop them?
Don't.
Look at how exciting this is.
They're all dogs in the streets.
Having these dogs fight one another
saves us a lot of troubles.
But at the building across ours
stand some
of the greatest heroes of the era.
Heroes?
Who are you calling heroes?
No matter how powerful
those martial artists are,
they are nothing but ants
in the face of the government.
(Pobanmen)
Good.
I share the sentiment.
Much cry and little wool.
I woke up early for nothing.
Let us return.
Oh, right.
When we get back,
run a background check
on the two men following Su Mengzhen.
- Yes, sir.
Strange.
Wash your hands and eyes.
You use your hands to kill
and your eyes to read.
You need to take good care of both.
Third Elder,
why did you stop?
Our higher-ups refused to fight.
It's pointless for us to continue.
Goodbye.
Sir.
The deal is done.
Hurry back to the Capital
and hold down Hua Wucuo.
Rest assured, sir.
Strange.
How is he still alive?
Every fiber of his being
is practically plagued by ailments.
He is suffering
from at least three or four illnesses.
There are three possible reasons
why he is still alive.
Number one. He is simply too powerful.
He is able to prevent the illnesses
from clashing and devastating him.
No matter how skilled he is,
it's impossible to stop his condition
from worsening altogether.
So what's the second possibility?
Number two.
The diseases inside his body
are restraining one another.
And the last possibility?
The final possibility...
A miracle.
He knew I was here,
and he still came up here alone.
The greatest red-sleeved swordsman
is a phoenix
among the younger generation, after all.
A miracle is keeping him alive.
To kill him
would require a miracle as well.
It's a pity that the sword wasn't here.
It left a crack for him to slip through.
He wouldn't have been able
to walk out of here alive otherwise.
If I team up with the Chief Elder,
we could take him down.
And if you include those down there?
It would be our win as well.
The martial arts world
is also a world of business.
It's good if you can win,
but remaining undefeated
is where the true challenge lies.
Even if we can kill him
by working together,
it would still incur a hefty price.
We would leave ourselves vulnerable
for others to take advantage of.
It's not worth it.
From here on out,
the Capital
shall find itself without peace.
It has never been peaceful.
(Pobanmen)
What happened? Did you get into a fight?
Not exactly.
Who was he?
I couldn't get a good look.
His face was covered.
He kept his weapon hidden as well.
Chief Elder Lei certainly went all out
to prevent me from entering the Capital.
But thanks to that, I met you two.
This might be the luckiest thing
that has ever happened to me.
(Pobanmen)
♪With whom do I visit this restaurant?♪
♪The moonlit hall
stands within the clouds♪
♪With whom do I ride my horse?♪
♪The snow has blanched our attire♪
♪In whom can I confide?♪
♪It's hard enough to find a true friend♪
♪With whom do I drink?♪
♪And who will tell me chug more?♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible, that sentiments
go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
is like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We weathered through the storms♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible,
that time will always move on♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
is just a wishful thinking♪
♪I will find it, I will pierce through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪
♪One blade, one sword♪
♪For my life, I have been wondering♪
♪One lance, one arrow♪
♪A solitude and regretful life♪
♪I discard my attire, I cut off my past♪
♪Will happiness bloom?♪
♪Perhaps I should get rid
of mortal desires♪
♪They are the source of woes♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible, that sentiments
don't go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
isn't like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We will weather through the storms♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible,
that time can move slower♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
isn't just a wishful thinking♪
♪I found it, I pierced through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪