♪Regardless of the length of my journey♪
♪Or how intertwined our fate is♪
♪As I climb countless mountains♪
♪Will I find my answer?♪
♪I gaze upon the dark night♪
♪My sword to the sky, the moon shines♪
♪Blood has tarnished the sand dunes♪
♪I try to brush it off♪
♪Feud and vendetta,
they go as quickly as they come♪
♪Life or death is decided within seconds
so why care about the outcome?♪
♪Life is like a tide
and we, the current♪
♪Who can come out unscathed?♪
♪Right or wrong♪
♪There's no turning back♪
♪To him I go♪
♪I will not head back♪
♪A thousand pots of wine♪
♪A million aftertastes♪
♪Let's chug it♪
♪To what we have been through!♪
♪Oh, this burning ambition♪
♪But the end of my journey
is still far away♪
♪Yet it never dies away♪
♪I will chase after my dream♪
♪The towering waves♪
♪Try to stop me♪
♪But I have my faith♪
♪Adamancy is my name♪
=Heroes=
=Episode 15=
(A Duel and Contention. Part 1)
Madam.
Wen Rou insists on coming back with me
to help you pack.
Madam,
I feel sad that you're leaving.
what's wrong?
Madam.
Where's Mr. Wo?
He won't be able to let it go
if he doesn't kill Guan Qi.
I let him go.
Little Rock!
Watch Madam!
Madam,
it'll be all right.
Mr. Wo.
Don't cry.
When someone holds a sword
to go on a killing spree,
someone will bathe in blood
for stepping in.
Take good care of Cha Hua.
Mr. Wo.
Mr. Wo!
Little Rock.
Madam.
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect Mr. Wo.
You're back?
As long as you're back.
As long as you're home.
Place him in the main hall
with his head to the door.
Put a light at his feet.
Little Rock,
go to the roof
and remove the tiles.
So he can see the sky
with his body not touching the ground.
One sickly man
and one useless old man.
Let's see how long you two can last.
Chief Elder Lei's martial arts skills
are equal to mine.
As long as there's tea,
he should be able to live
for a long time.
I have food and water.
I'll compete with you to the end.
Sir!
Sir.
Why are you panicking?
Guan Qi has caused Second Madam...
Did he kill her?
She lost her mind.
But many other died.
Let them die.
It has nothing to do with me.
There was a dead old man too.
Wang Xiaoshi carried him away.
Sir.
Guan Qi is going on a killing spree
and causing an uproar in the Capital.
Yes, he can't find you
if you hide here.
But if this goes on,
it'll alert the imperial court.
I'm afraid no one can afford
to take the responsibility.
Sir,
Guan Qi is behaving recklessly
without restraints.
If we let him continue
with the killings,
the Six Half Hall
and the House of Sunset Drizzle
won't be able to save all the citizens,
no matter how powerful we are.
This matter is serious.
We mustn't waste our time anymore.
You'll have to guarantee my safety.
We will make sure you're safe.
It's your favorite braised meat.
I braised it while
waiting for your return last night.
So you could eat before you leave.
Fu Zongshu has agreed to be the bait
to lure Guan Qi out.
Where do you plan to surround him?
House of Sanhe.
What House Master meant
was Guan Qi is highly skilled.
It's useless sending
many average martial artists.
So the House of Sanhe
will evacuate most people.
I'll play the qin with five customers.
The three of us,
Di Feijing, and Lei Sun
can definitely subdue Guan Qi.
Are we going to subdue him only?
He killed so many people.
If we kill him,
we might kill a bad person
or a good person.
I don't see why not.
But Guan Qi knows the secret
of Youqiao Group.
We must keep him alive in our hands.
If we think so,
Lei Sun would think the same too.
After we subdue Guan Qi,
the next fight will start right away.
If we want things
to go smoothly tonight,
everyone must work together
with one heart.
(Romance and Pleasure, House of Sanhe)
Xiaoyao,
Mr. Su, Chief Elder Lei,
and the rest are here.
Have you completed
the task I assigned to you?
Please rest assured.
It's all arranged.
(Jifang Garden)
You're skilled in playing qin
and excellent at shooting.
Miss Xiaoyao is indeed unparalleled.
Zhu Xiaoyao's identity
is a secret to our House.
Unexpectedly,
your informers are everywhere.
A spy is highly valued
before exposing himself.
Once he makes a move,
he's no longer a spy.
The greatest value
of an informer is staying alive.
Once he's dead,
it's useless
even if he knows many secrets.
(Jifang Garden)
I can forget
about you punching me before.
But you must not tell anyone about it.
Why are you glaring at me?
I'm not Guan Qi.
I suggest you be cautious.
We can't afford any mistakes now.
You made a huge fuss about this.
Anyone with good sense
knows this is a trap.
Guan Qi is not a fool.
Are you certain he'll come?
He wasn't afraid
of breaking into your residence.
He'll come anyway
as long as he can kill you
despite knowing it's a trap.
Now
you should open a window.
Your noodles are here.
I heard Minister Fu's concubines
either died or lost their minds.
But look at him.
He went to the House of Sanhe
the moment he had time.
I can't believe he dares to come out.
I thought someone wanted to kill him.
But he's the imperial court's minister.
No one would dare to kill him.
I do.
I'm the one who wants
to kill Minister Fu.
(House of Sanhe)
Is he coming or not?
We're waiting for a killer.
It'll be fortunate if he doesn't come.
I'll leave things to you now!
Get ready now.
Sir.
Sir, we're over here.
Over here, Sir.
Be careful.
Watch your step, Sir.
Sir, let me help you.
Hurry.
Quickly now.
Get in.
Close the door. Let's go.
(Splendid Beauty, Jifang Garden)
Red Sleeve Blade?
You're Su Mengzhen?
If I'm not Su Mengzhen,
how can I hold you down in one move?
You should've finished your move
in one go just now.
I never resort to sneaky attacks.
How rare.
In this world,
anyone who fights you face to face
is considered a man of noble character.
Most people
prefer attacking behind the back.
Some don't even need
to do it themselves.
Am I right,
brother-in-law?
It would be even better to subdue you
without any fighting.
You've already killed me once.
But I let you live once too.
If you're willing
to go back into the well,
I can let you live again.
He won't.
He'll kill you for sure.
After spending eight years in the well,
there are many talented people
in the martial arts world.
Brother-in-law,
you're old now.
I'm afraid you have no say now.
It doesn't matter if I don't have a say.
Your fate has been decided today.
Wang Xiaoshi, did you hear that?
I'll kill anyone
I can.
I'm not the only one
who follows this principle.
I don't talk nonsense
in a fight.
Zhu Xiaoyao is one of yours, right?
What's the meaning of this?
What's your intention?
You saved Guan Qi again and again.
Are you waiting for him to turn around
and kill every one of us?
Listen.
There are no heroes
who die a tragic death
or unfortunate good men in this world.
Dispatch the men!
Search Guan Qi and Zhu Xiaoyao
all over the Capital.
Did you instruct
Zhu Xiaoyao to take Guan Qi away?
(Splendid Beauty)
(The House of Sunset Drizzle)
(Apothecary)
Zhu Xiaoyao went missing with Guan Qi?
Our hard work
was for nothing.
They say a person lives
for 30,000 days.
There are some nights
you don't wish to go through.
Zhu Xiaoyao has worked for you
for many years.
Haven't you found out her identity?
I know she was a member
of the Mitian Sect.
But I had no idea
she's still loyal to Guan Qi
after all these years.
When someone works for you for so long,
it doesn't matter
what kind of past she had.
If she had bad intentions
all these years,
Red Sleeve Blade wouldn't exist
in the martial arts world.
At first,
I thought she could stop
Lei Sun from killing Guan Qi.
Yet, Guan Qi escaped because of this.
It was my fault.
Try this one.
They're freshly picked.
Not bad.
Xiaoyao.
Did you buy the medicinal herbs?
Yes.
I bought cogon grass
and cypress leaves separately.
I also bought medicinal powder
to stop bleeding.
Is he still unconscious?
I'm not worried
about his external injuries.
But Guan Qi would have died
from Di Feijing's palm strike
if he wasn't highly skilled
in martial arts.
Xiaoyao, you must be tired
from watching him all night.
Why don't you get some rest?
I'll take care of him.
All right.
If you were not mad
or a killer,
would my life
be different?
Shuang,
you've been with me
about seven to eight years, right?
That wasn't long.
I planned to stay with you all my life.
When a boy grows up,
he can't grow up among women.
The martial arts world is vast.
The House of Sanhe isn't a place
for you to settle down.
Now that your father has returned.
I want to send both of you far away.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have lived until today.
If I leave at this moment,
I'll never hold my head high.
I didn't have a home in the first place.
If it weren't for that man in the room,
I wouldn't have lived until today too.
You filthy little thing,
I've experienced this too.
When the customers see you cry,
they'll feel sorry for you.
My dear,
come to me.
Leave if you want to live.
(For a long time,)
(I feel like a nobody.)
(That day)
(was the only time)
(someone gave me the hope.)
(So even if violent killings
and dangerous situations)
(followed wherever he went,)
(I was willing to stay by his side.)
Why did you stop?
My feet are cold and painful.
You must never betray me
if you stay with me.
Understand?
I'll never betray you.
I saved him
and raised you
because of this past.
But I'm not only indebted
to your father.
I'm also indebted to Mr. Su.
I kept thinking
if I had to repay them one day,
I could only give them my life.
That's why I always say
that life is short and bitter.
It's more important
to find leisure in life.
None of the men we dispatched last night
found Zhu Xiaoyao's trail.
As far as I know about Zhu Xiaoyao,
she may be hiding
in these several locations.
Zhu Xiaoyao is a spy and meticulous.
Would she hide in the places
you could think of?
She doesn't know
what I know.
I have all the information
about the House's spies.
I'll hand over Lawless to you.
(Lawless)
We must take his life
while he's injured.
If we wait until Guan Qi has recovered,
no one can subdue him anymore.
So we must find him as soon as possible.
But the Capital is huge.
I'm afraid it'll take forever.
But we still need to find them.
We'll try to alert them.
We'll search these places
and let her know on purpose.
If we do this,
she'll rush to send Guan Qi
out of the Capital.
It's inconvenient for Guan Qi
to move around with his injuries.
They might leave the Capital
in a carriage.
(Maxing Street)
The gate is what we must guard.
(Yiji Inn)
(Clouds of Visitors)
Is Madam all right?
She's in her room.
I lit a calming incense for her.
I hope she can sleep well.
Yellow, you want to avenge
Mr. Wo's death too, right?
I'm useless.
I don't even know
where the person who killed Mr. Wo is.
I have an idea.
What is it?
Yellow, let's go.
(House of Sanhe)
Yellow, hurry!
Yellow.
Yellow?
Come here.
Can we really find Guan Qi
with this method?
Bai is leading the men
to search for them.
I suddenly thought of this method.
So I wanted to give it a try.
If we can find Guan Qi,
I'll end this matter myself.
Yellow, let's go.
I know I can't stop you from going.
But I'm really scared.
All of you can't even defeat Guan Qi.
If you meet him alone...
I was the one who released Guan Qi.
He killed Mr. Wo
and so many people.
If I don't seek revenge,
it'll be hard for me
to live after this.
I understand.
But you must promise me
that you'll come back.
I promise.
I'll come back.
(I will.)
♪With whom do I visit this restaurant?♪
♪The moonlit hall
stands within the clouds♪
♪With whom do I ride my horse?♪
♪The snow has blanched our attire♪
♪In whom can I confide?♪
♪It's hard enough to find a true friend♪
♪With whom do I drink?♪
♪And who will tell me chug more?♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible, that sentiments
go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
is like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We weathered through the storms♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible,
that time will always move on♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
is just a wishful thinking♪
♪I will find it, I will pierce through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪
♪One blade, one sword♪
♪For my life, I have been wondering♪
♪One lance, one arrow♪
♪A solitude and regretful life♪
♪I discard my attire, I cut off my past♪
♪Will happiness bloom?♪
♪Perhaps I should get rid
of mortal desires♪
♪They are the source of woes♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible, that sentiments
don't go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
isn't like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We will weather through the storms♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible,
that time can move slower♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
isn't just a wishful thinking♪
♪I found it, I pierced through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪