♪Regardless of the length of my journey♪
♪Or how intertwined our fate is♪
♪As I climb countless mountains♪
♪Will I find my answer?♪
♪I gaze upon the dark night♪
♪My sword to the sky, the moon shines♪
♪Blood has tarnished the sand dunes♪
♪I try to brush it off♪
♪Feud and vendetta,
they go as quickly as they come♪
♪Life or death is decided within seconds
so why care about the outcome?♪
♪Life is like a tide
and we, the current♪
♪Who can come out unscathed?♪
♪Right or wrong♪
♪There's no turning back♪
♪To him I go♪
♪I will not head back♪
♪A thousand pots of wine♪
♪A million aftertastes♪
♪Let's chug it♪
♪To what we have been through!♪
♪Oh, this burning ambition♪
♪But the end of my journey
is still far away♪
♪Yet it never dies away♪
♪I will chase after my dream♪
♪The towering waves♪
♪Try to stop me♪
♪But I have my faith♪
♪Adamancy is my name♪
=Heroes=
=Episode 9=
(Hardship weathered.
Aspirations renewed. Part 3)
Someone! Help!
Someone! Put out the fire!
Get some water! Hurry!
Hurry!
Someone!
Help us out!
You'll catch a cold
if you don't wear anything thick.
We cannot afford
to see a physician right now.
Bai,
don't you think
it's too tough for us
to live in the Capital?
It's difficult to pay the rent
and see a physician.
But earning money is the hardest.
I just wanted to make some money
so that I could buy a brush for you.
Even that wasn't easy.
You can stop
worrying about me.
You shouldn't mind
the fire too.
The weather was dry.
I think the manager can pull it through.
No.
The manager was implicated
because of me.
I thought something was off today.
I had the feeling that someone
was eyeing the apothecary.
Back then, I didn't take it to heart
as I thought it was my imagination.
Now that I think about it,
I'm sure no one would try
to sabotage the manager
since he's a simple person.
If so, that means he was aiming for me.
It must be someone
from the Six Half Hall.
The Six Half Hall again?
Don't worry about being lonely
on the road ahead.
Everyone in the world
recognizes you as a friend.
He's still not willing to let us off,
even though we're already
in such a plight.
What?
Did they make things
difficult for you too?
They aren't from the Six Half Hall.
It's the heavens.
Yellow.
Even a dog is despising us.
♪Stubborn and proud♪
♪Lamenting the
martial arts world to be too lonely♪
♪What are good and evil?
Who can be on the same path?♪
♪Countless great achievements♪
♪The past is gone.
It's time for another long journey♪
♪When I stand on the top,
I can see the faraway skies♪
♪Even if there are troubles,
wickedness, vanity, and adversity♪
♪Let me be the hero♪
♪Even if the road ahead is harsh♪
♪The journey won't be a waste♪
♪Yelling to the sky!
I want to soar to greater heights♪
♪Being a laughing stock for ages because
my road ahead is always full of hurdles♪
♪Yelling to the sky!
I want the results to be decided♪
♪Drink a bottle of wine.
To the ends of the earth♪
♪The tales of heroes I shall speak.♪
Mister, it's you?
Do you still remember me?
Of course.
We once met in Xiliu.
I travel the world
to gather tales and anecdotes.
I realized something
only when I came to the Capital.
All the top martial artists
are actually here.
Speaking of which,
have your two friends
made a name for themselves?
Not yet.
Now, they're going through
a huge ordeal.
The place they worked in
was burned down.
And no one bought their
calligraphy and paintings.
I think they have to starve every day.
Although it's tough for now,
it will pan out well in the end.
That's what I believe in too.
I believe that my friends
will be included
in your list of heroes one day.
Young Lady is over there! After her!
Mister,
I shall make a move first.
Hurry!
♪Dressed in gray♪
♪The Sincere and Honest♪
♪Brandishes his sword♪
My lady, have you heard about this?
The two men you met on the boat
actually didn't make it
into the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Right now, one of them is selling
calligraphy and paintings on the streets
while the other is
working in an apothecary.
They're pretty pitiful.
Looks like you're pretty
concerned about them.
Of course, my lady.
They're your acquaintances.
Since they didn't make it
into the House of Sunset Drizzle,
my lady, why don't you ask
Chief Elder for his permission
and let them join the Six Half Hall?
They will never join the Six Half Hall.
And,
I've made a promise to my father.
I will step out
of the martial arts world.
If so, I don't think
they can stay here for long.
It's hard to say.
Both of them don't look like
they'll give up easily.
Come and take a look at my painting!
I just acquired a painting
of an old man grazing his calf
while overlooking the river!
Miss,
I knew
you could recognize
quality paintings at first glance.
This is the painting I just acquired.
Look.
Look at the strokes and imagery
depicted in the paintings.
I'm sure it came from
someone extraordinary.
I do know something about paintings.
The strokes look new and fresh.
It doesn't seem like the work
of a famous painter.
That's right.
Miss, you're exactly right.
I just made his acquaintances
not long ago.
He has no particular strength.
He came to the Capital
with an easel on his back.
However, he's very ambitious.
Look at this painting.
Don't you think it's amazing?
If so, why didn't you
give it a better name?
Old man grazing his calf?
I'm sure no one would buy that.
Young lady,
you see,
the name of the painting
can be altered accordingly.
Mainly, it depends on
whether your Young Lady likes it.
Throughout the stages of life,
when you look back
at your life at old age,
you'll feel sentimental.
The majestic landscape in the background
is still and calm.
It depicts the vastness
of Heaven and Earth.
Now that I think about it,
the people you meet in life
are just passengers.
You might be able to sell it out
if you change its name
to "Floating Dreams".
Aren't you buying it?
No.
Didn't you say
that the strokes are new and fresh?
Does that mean it can
achieve success in the Capital?
I guess there's nothing else I can do.
Please take care.
(Second Year of Song-Yuan,
drawn by Bai Youjin)
What is he doing?
Ladies and gentlemen,
gather around!
Don't miss out on this opportunity!
Today, I hope you guys
will enjoy my show!
I will
stand inside this circle.
You can get one stone
for one copper coin.
If you guys hit me with your stones,
you can take back your money.
If not,
the money will be mine.
It's that simple.
It's that simple?
Just try it and you'll know.
- Anyone wants to give it a try?
- Me!
Mister.
Come on.
He's amazing!
That was so close.
Again!
Aim better.
- Aim better.
- That's right.
Aim better.
Thank you.
I quit.
Go now.
So, Tenth Elder,
regarding the things I said just now...
It's just a stall vendor you
killed, right?
The Six Half Hall will deal with it
for you.
Thank you, Tenth Elder.
I will accomplish the task
you gave me immediately.
Let's go.
Thank you, everyone.
Please come again next time.
See you, young man.
Take care.
Thank you.
Get out of the way.
Look at the amount of money.
He's so generous.
That's right.
You're right.
Mister, you're pretty generous, huh?
I have plenty of money in the world.
I wish to try something fun.
Do you dare to take up my challenge?
You can't do that.
He'll be injured.
He'll die from this.
That's too risky.
Sure.
If I don't hit you in three shots,
you can have all of it.
All right.
Young man, that's too risky!
Don't agree to his request!
Be careful!
Just forget it!
Amazing!
You're pretty good.
I was just lucky.
You have two more shots.
He's very skillful.
That's right.
That's so scary.
Boss!
Bai?
Who are you?
Mind your own business!
Scram.
Let's go.
I...
Bai!
Bai, wait for me!
Can you wait for me?
They're falling to the floor.
Just wait for me!
My coins are falling.
Was this the idea you mentioned?
Didn't you say we need to retaliate
when people bully us?
So, can people bully and humiliate you
when they give you money?
I'm selling my craft for a living.
You're not selling your craft.
You're selling your dignity!
It depends on one's capability
to make a living as a martial artist.
This can be counted
as experience, right?
I don't think
I'm degrading myself by doing this.
I know life is tough right now.
But I'm sure
there are more solutions than problems.
We have to think of a way somehow.
If we wish to stay in the Capital,
we have to...
If I have to resort to this
to stay in the Capital,
I would rather leave!
Bai!
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
(So, not everyone)
(can find their place in the Capital.)
(People who have the power)
(can close every door.)
I'm sure the things it sees
will be different from what we see.
That's great.
It's flying
freely.
I'm sure it has been to more places
than us.
I'm going to stay here.
I wish to join
the House of Sunset Drizzle
as soon as possible.
(I can choose
not to stay in the Capital.)
(But it's different for Bai.)
(He has been waiting for too long.)
(The fame he desires)
(can only be attained in the Capital.)
I'm poor and unknown to the world.
I wonder who's following me?
Judging from what you said,
it seems like
you've taken advantage of me.
You're indeed poor and unknown.
I'm not here to be your follower.
I'm here to chase you away.
So, the Third Elder of the Six Half Hall
is here to see me personally?
Seems like you're bent on
forcing me to a dead end.
Come on then.
Tell all of your men to come out.
There's no one else.
I'm the only one here.
Although I'm here to chase you away,
that doesn't mean we need to fight.
If you're not afraid
of a young woman like me,
you can follow me.
I'll treat you to a drink.
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
(You're not selling your craft.)
(You're selling your dignity!)
(If I have to resort to this
to stay in the Capital,)
(I would rather leave!)
If I knock on the door right now,
Bai will never forgive me.
Tenth Elder,
Chief Elder said
we should leave him alone
if he didn't knock on the door.
So, do we still need to follow him?
I saw him knocking on the door just now.
Didn't you see it?
I understand.
Many people came to the Capital
to embrace their dreams
and establish a foothold here.
But why must some people bully the weak
and chase them away?
You fooled me again.
Fine.
Since you're not leaving,
you should stay here forever then.
Since you've offended the Six Half Hall,
according to our rules,
you have to pay with your life.
You want to take my life?
I'm afraid you're not strong enough.
Attack!
Six Half Hall may have their rules,
but I have my own rules as well.
Do not attack those
who are holding onto their last straw.
You killed Hua Wucuo
when he was holding onto his last straw.
That was just the first punch.
Do not attack those
who cannot defend themselves.
But you burned down
the manager's apothecary.
That was the second punch.
As for the third punch,
I just felt like punching you.
(Maple Bridge)
Third Elder.
Nan, bring me a coat.
Sure.
Have you ever heard of this saying?
In the Capital's martial arts world,
the liquor you drink
determines
your status.
Of course.
This place is the top shop
in the Capital.
(Liquor)
The liquor here is excellent and pricey.
An ordinary person might not be able
to afford to get drunk here
with their annual wage.
The name tags on the liquor pots
are largely unknown
as they're just nicknames.
(Liquor)
It might be Chief Elder Lei,
(Mugehei)
Mr. Su,
(Liquor)
Qi Shaoshang,
or even Marquis Shentong.
So, did you bring me all the way here
to humiliate me?
Don't you think
you should be humiliated?
I know you're skillful in martial arts.
However, it's useless
to be skilled in martial arts alone.
Moreover, you've offended
the group you shouldn't have,
the Six Half Hall.
The Capital's martial arts world
is small in the first place.
It was already difficult enough
for you to enter the door.
Moreover, this door
has been closed in front of you.
Now, it's a wall.
It's an iron wall.
You can't open it that easily.
You were only released from prison
after a prominent figure
like Mr. Su knelt
and pleaded for your sake.
If you wish to stay in the Capital,
your buddy has to
perform in the streets.
You're so prideful.
However, the people beside you
have cast away
their pride long ago for your sake.
So,
do you think you still have the face
to stay in the Capital?
Have a drink.
This is the only place
in the Capital
where you can get such excellent liquor.
♪At first, I intended
to conquer the world♪
♪But I had no choice
but to hide under the dirt♪
♪I dreamt of ruling the world, but I
had no choice but to wait for a chance♪
(Second Year of Song-Yuan,
drawn by Bai Youjin)
♪Reaching the peak is difficult,
a path filled with thorns♪
Mister,
are you buying paintings
at this late hour?
♪I wanted to quit
the martial arts world♪
Is that painting still unsold?
♪But I cannot come to terms
with the time I had wasted♪
I'm just a part-timer.
I'm not clear about that.
However, according
to the rules of the trade,
the paintings hanging on that wall
all belong to new painters
who are not famous.
Basically, no one buys them.
♪Trying to win fame and fortune♪
There are rules in this trade too?
Mister, you must be joking.
Everywhere in the Capital
has its own rules.
♪Wielding absolute power
and standing out in the world♪
The most pitiful thing
is that many people come to the Capital
in search of fame and fortune
every year.
However, literally none of them
have made it big.
♪Drifting about and sparring
with living beings don't matter to me♪
Mister, have you taken
a liking to this painting?
♪When I swing my sword,
nations will fall and tides will rise♪
♪I'm a reckless person
who only wants to reach the sky♪
♪The chaotic world
cannot do anything to me♪
♪Even when my lips are bleeding,
I put on a contemptuous smile♪
♪I'll never be satisfied
with struggling in a human body♪
♪I would rather drink
and fight with all I have♪
♪Have my name known throughout the world,
admired by all beings before I die♪
♪My lofty aspirations
are too huge for me to sigh♪
♪Ignoring worldly affairs
and focusing on success♪
♪But I cannot escape my destiny,
plagued by loneliness♪
♪If I wanted to be a hero♪
♪Fearlessly, I spar with living beings♪
♪How many can conquer the world without
being scorched by the summit smoke?♪
(Little Rock,)
(I'm leaving.)
(Please tell Mr. Wo and Madam)
(about my departure.)
♪If only I could be a hawk
and soar through the sky♪
(Please thank them
for taking care of me.)
♪But I forgot about the storms up there♪
(You said)
(everyone should be free.)
♪My greed has become a cage,
and there's no going back♪
(However, when
you're in this plight with me,)
(you became restricted.)
(As a friend,
I shouldn't drag you down.)
(Although the days we spent
in the Capital were tough,)
(they were fun and memorable.)
(No matter where I go,)
(we'll always be brothers.)
(Please do not forget me.)
My lady,
you've been kneeling the entire night.
Why don't you get up and stretch?
Is there no news of Mr. Su yet?
No.
Mr. Su went on a long trip
to the northwest.
He's only late by one day.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
And,
with his skills,
I'm sure he can protect himself.
Mengzhen always keeps his promises.
In the past, whenever he made trips,
he never returned late.
When you fall for someone,
and if he's in the same situation
as Mengzhen right now,
you will understand how I feel.
Amitabha.
Miss Lei,
Mr. Su has returned to the Capital.
My lady, be careful.
(Fu's Residence)
Who's there?
I'm Su Mengzhen
of the House of Sunset Drizzle.
(Fu's Residence)
Mr. Su, please wait a moment.
Mr. Su,
our minister will see you.
Sir,
I've retrieved the item you asked for.
Mr. Su, I'm sure
it was an arduous trip. Good job.
Is the item with you?
Show it to me.
It's his head indeed.
Su Mengzhen, you do
live up to your name.
There's nothing you cannot achieve.
I think I've gotten worse at it.
I've been practicing Cuju lately.
When I saw something that's shaped
like a ball, I feel like kicking it.
Mr. Su,
please pick it up for me.
Someone!
Yes, sir!
Su Mengzhen assassinated Liu Anshi,
a court official!
Take him down!
Yes, sir!
Sir,
how can you prove that
I assassinated Official Liu?
This head is all the proof I need.
Sir, did you see clearly
whose head this was?
Sir, it's fake.
How dare you, Su Mengzhen!
I gave you a task,
yet you try to deceive me!
I'm ignorant.
Sir, what exactly
did you want me to do for you?
You!
Su Mengzhen,
the House of Sunset Drizzle
is under my governance.
Now that you've offended me,
life will be difficult for you.
Sir!
Sir,
don't tell me this head
belonged to your friend?
By the way,
what did you say you'd do to me again?
Leave.
All of you, leave!
Have you ever thought about
the consequences of your actions?
I have.
Do you think I don't dare to arrest you
just because you're famous?
I can even kill you if I want to.
Sir, I know you're bold enough
to do anything in the world.
However,
if I was sent to the dungeon
in the Ministry of Justice
or died in some other place,
sir,
you will never know about
the things I had witnessed.
(Bianliang)
What are you trying to do?
Are you trying to leave by yourself?
Are you going to abandon your friend?
I'll break your legs for it.
I'm not abandoning my friend.
We've been living
in the Capital for some days.
It's fine that I couldn't
make a name for myself.
But you had to perform
in the streets for my sake.
Mr. Su was humiliated because of me.
I feel more humiliated
when my friends
have to suffer because of me.
That's why I'm going
to leave the Capital.
Are you done?
Since you said we're friends,
those minor sufferings didn't matter.
We came to the Capital together.
Since you're leaving,
let's leave together.
Wait.
Little Rock,
you still have your dreams to pursue.
You...
Why are you so wishy-washy today?
Didn't I tell you before?
Just listen to me.
Let's travel around for a few years
and return here.
If the Six Half Hall
dares to oppress us again,
we'll retaliate against them!
Okay.
Let's travel together then.
After that, we can return here together.
Let's go.
(Bianliang)
It must've been an arduous journey.
You're finally back.
I've prepared hot tea
and a warm environment for you.
Treat this as your welcoming feast.
It'll get rid of the cold.
The journey was not too bad.
But I was almost arrested
in the minister's residence.
You brought a human head into the
residence of the Minister of Justice.
And, you actually came out alive.
Whose head did you bring
to keep you alive after all of that?
I got hold
of an intel from Official Liu.
Fu Zongshu and the Six Half Hall
have been operating a shady business
in the north.
And, it's related to the Liao people.
Following Official Liu's clue,
I went to the border area
and found the contact
of their shady business.
Are you the contact
of their business in the north?
Mr. Su, I'm sure you know that well
when you came all the way here
to track me down.
How did you guys go about
with your business
and do your handovers?
Tell me everything you know.
Mr. Su,
although the things we do
are harming other people,
we had no choice but to do it.
The families
of the people in charge here
are under the surveillance
of the Six Half Hall.
Does that include your family too?
I have a pitiful brother
living in the Capital.
His life
is under their control too.
If you escort me to the Capital
and save my brother,
I'll tell you everything
I know.
All right, I promise you.
Thank you, Mr. Su.
Save...
Save my brother.
Initially, I wanted him to tell me
about the so-called "business"
in the north.
It's a pity that he was killed
before he could tell me anything.
However, the contact
was vital to their business
in the north.
Official Fu backed off
when he saw his head.
This move
is risky indeed.
If you're 60 percent
confident about it, you should do it.
Regarding the contact's brother
who is under surveillance,
tell Messenger Pigeon Group
to locate him.
I will do so.
Hurry.
Drink your tea
and expel the cold in your body.
After drinking the warm tea
and getting your body warmed up,
you should hurry and leave the city.
Why?
The two people you told me to monitor,
Wang and Bai,
I think they can't stand it anymore.
If you wish to keep them here,
I'm afraid
you have to leave the city
and intercept them.
Prepare my horse.
It's already prepared.
Stop right there!
Wen Rou?
You're not gentle at all.
First, you flirted with other girls.
After that, you left me
in the House all by myself.
You didn't look for me even though
you were in the Capital for a long time.
And now, you're leaving
without bidding farewell.
You want me to be gentle?
You, and you!
Did you two even take me as a friend?
I'm sorry.
I know the ordeals you guys faced
for the past few days.
However, are you sure
you want to leave just like that?
I came to the Capital
to join the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Since I have no chance to join it,
there's no meaning for me to stay here.
Actually, it's not that big of a deal.
Although the Capital is huge,
it's only a tiny part of the world.
Even if we can't make a name
for ourselves here,
I'm sure we can do it elsewhere.
What if you still have a chance?
Come on.
Someone wants to see you two.
Let's go.
Come on.
Where are you bringing us?
You'll know when we get there.
Mengzhen, I've brought them here.
You guys can enjoy your chat.
I'll make a move first.
Wen Rou.
Mengzhen?
Mr. Su, why are you here?
I was waiting
for two important people to show up.
Judging by your looks,
I assume you two
are leaving the Capital.
The Six Half Hall
oppressed us all the time.
The Ministry of Justice has forbidden us
from joining
the House of Sunset Drizzle too.
We have no choice
but to leave the Capital.
I've already told
you guys this long ago.
You two are already members
of the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Forget about the Ministry of Justice
and the Six Half Hall.
You guys are joining
the House of Sunset Drizzle.
It has nothing to do with them.
But Mengzhen,
when you knelt in front of Fu Zongshu
and pleaded for us,
I...
I knelt in front of Fu Zongshu?
Fu Zongshu
is only good with his words.
I didn't expect you two
to be duped by him.
You want me to kneel
in front of a person?
I guess I can do it
if it's for the sake of my brothers.
What did you say?
Did you say we were brothers?
Your ear is perfectly fine.
We're sworn brothers.
But we only met each other once.
But we did experience
life-or-death situations together.
Do you even know who we are?
I don't care who you are.
You want us to become
your sworn brothers
without knowing who we are?
Who said that one must inquire
about the other party's
family history and background
before becoming sworn brothers with him?
If so, why are you trying
to make us your sworn brothers?
I don't need a reason to do so.
Do you expect me to say something
like we will be in weal and woe
and stay together forever?
If so, how many
sworn brothers do you have?
Two.
You
and him.
You're trying to recruit us to
join the House of Sunset Drizzle, right?
If you two are not willing to do so,
you may leave right now.
Even if we don't see each other again,
you two will forever be my brothers.
Big Brother!
You're the big brother here?
You don't say?
Big Brother!
Big Brother, Second Brother!
Third Brother!
Second Brother,
- Big Brother!
I finally found myself a big brother
in the Capital!
Great!
Big Brother!
Second Brother!
Third Brother!
(Yang)
I, Su Mengzhen.
Bai Choufei.
Wang Xiaoshi.
We hereby become sworn brothers.
We will go through
thick and thin together.
We will entrust our lives to each other
and never let each other down.
If we go against this vow,
may the heavens punish us!
♪With whom do I visit this restaurant?♪
♪The moonlit hall
stands within the clouds♪
♪With whom do I ride my horse?♪
♪The snow has blanched our attire♪
♪In whom can I confide?♪
♪It's hard enough to find a true friend♪
♪With whom do I drink?♪
♪And who will tell me chug more?♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible, that sentiments
go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
is like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We weathered through the storms♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible,
that time will always move on♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
is just a wishful thinking♪
♪I will find it, I will pierce through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪
♪One blade, one sword♪
♪For my life, I have been wondering♪
♪One lance, one arrow♪
♪A solitude and regretful life♪
♪I discard my attire, I cut off my past♪
♪Will happiness bloom?♪
♪Perhaps I should get rid
of mortal desires♪
♪They are the source of woes♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible, that sentiments
don't go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
isn't like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We will weather through the storms♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible,
that time can move slower♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
isn't just a wishful thinking♪
♪I found it, I pierced through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪