♪Regardless of the length of my journey♪
♪Or how intertwined our fate is♪
♪As I climb countless mountains♪
♪Will I find my answer?♪
♪I gaze upon the dark night♪
♪My sword to the sky, the moon shines♪
♪Blood has tarnished the sand dunes♪
♪I try to brush it off♪
♪Feud and vendetta,
they go as quickly as they come♪
♪Life or death is decided within seconds
so why care about the outcome?♪
♪Life is like a tide
and we, the current♪
♪Who can come out unscathed?♪
♪Right or wrong♪
♪There's no turning back♪
♪To him I go♪
♪I will not head back♪
♪A thousand pots of wine♪
♪A million aftertastes♪
♪Let's chug it♪
♪To what we have been through!♪
♪Oh, this burning ambition♪
♪But the end of my journey
is still far away♪
♪Yet it never dies away♪
♪I will chase after my dream♪
♪The towering waves♪
♪Try to stop me♪
♪But I have my faith♪
♪Adamancy is my name♪
=Heroes=
=Episode 5=
(Countless efforts in vain.
Red Sleeve Blade dictates fate. Part 2)
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
I haven't asked you this yet.
Why did you come to the Capital?
I came to the Capital
to establish a foothold for myself.
Seems like
you're not afraid of anything.
You're just afraid that
you can't make a name for yourself.
To martial artists,
drinking represents one's status.
Did you come to the Capital
to have the best liquor?
Of course.
If I have to drink,
I'll drink the best liquor.
All right. I'll remember that.
I'll prepare them for you
once the deed is done.
It's a promise then.
There's one more thing.
My father is bedridden.
I don't want to see him
when I'm bathed in blood.
Don't worry.
By then, you can enter
the room immediately.
Just leave the rest to me.
I'll buy some time for you,
no matter how many people
they send after you.
My archer will help you out too.
That's even better.
It's one quarter before 9 a.m.
The sky is clear!
It'll be 9 a.m. soon.
Seems like Hua Wucuo and the rest
will be reaching
the House of Sages soon.
(Seasonable Weathers)
It's one quarter before 9 a.m.
The sky is clear!
It's not the time yet.
Why are they here already?
The person on the right is Mo Beichen.
The person on the left is Li Niantang.
I think they're waiting for Hua Wucuo.
Is everyone here?
Where's Delegate?
(The House of Sages)
Delegate is still on his way.
He'll arrive soon.
If so, let's wait here.
There's not much time left.
Let's get ready.
(The House of Sages)
I'll head inside and meet him first.
Greetings, Delegate!
Where's Long Xiaoqing?
He was anxious.
He said he wanted
to meet Su Mengzhen in advance.
If so, we can head there later.
He can enjoy his meeting with him.
Where's Shi Wukui?
He's not here.
That's good too.
I'll deal with him later.
Those who are here should think twice
before they pick their sides.
Both Delegate and Mr. Su
come from the same family.
Both belong to
the House of Sunset Drizzle.
As their subordinates,
no matter who we side with,
we're siding with
the House of Sunset Drizzle, right?
Who's there?
I'm Long Xiaoqing, a Keeper
of the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Mr. Su, since you were back to
the Capital, I came to visit you.
So, what's so important that you can't
discuss it in the House?
I will explain everything
when everyone is here.
Delegate and the other Keepers
are already waiting at the door.
Mr. Su, could it be that you're acting
as the house master
even though you haven't
succeeded House Master yet?
Don't tell me you want us to
welcome you by kowtowing to you?
Mr. Su, you summoned us here,
yet you're not revealing yourself to us.
You're playing tricks on us
behind the curtain.
Don't you think
this is inappropriate of you?
Why don't we speak face to face?
You!
If you dare to touch me,
even the House of Sunset Drizzle
won't be able to protect you.
Mr. Su, I didn't expect you
to get yourself a woman
after you went to the border area.
You!
My master is the Red Sleeve Nun.
Su Mengzhen is my martial brother.
Touch me if you dare.
My father is Wen Wan, Lord of Luoyang.
I'm the Young Lady of the Wen family.
Touch me if you dare.
So, it's the Young Lady
of the Wen family?
Xiaoqing, how dare you make
things difficult for her?
We're just mere martial artists.
She's from a dignified family.
Stop arguing.
Sit down.
This young Keeper is trying
to cause trouble
because he's upset.
I'm younger than him.
Even so, I know
how to respect my elders.
I'm Wen Rou, the daughter of Wen Wan,
Lord of Luoyang.
I will serve you all tea.
She does come from a dignified family.
I'm not worthy.
It's 9 a.m.
There are dark clouds in the sky!
(Once it's 9 a.m,)
(Wang Xiaoshi and I will burn
the joss stick at the same time.)
(Wang Xiaoshi and Wen Rou)
(need to stall Hua Wucuo and the rest
until the joss sticks run out.)
(And we must)
(meet House Master.)
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
I only kill traitors.
If no one moves,
I'll treat it as if this encounter
never takes place.
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
(Honor of Dezhao)
If you wish to kill him,
you have to go through me!
Do you think these men
can fend me off?
This is the House of Sunset Drizzle's
family matter.
Buddy, can you
bear the consequences
if two of the major sects
in the Capital
get into a fight because of you?
Is there anyone else
who can be in charge here?
So, it's Lei Mei, the Third Elder.
Miss Lei Mei,
has the Six Half Hall
prepared themselves
for the showdown against
the House of Sunset Drizzle?
Who said we were going to fight
in broad daylight?
It's just that the Sunset Drizzle
made things difficult
for a friend of Chief Elder's.
I just wanted to help him out.
Mr. Su was the one who made
things difficult for him.
Even if you're there,
do you think
you can do anything about it?
Besides, Mr. Su is already
engaging Hua Wucuo
while we're talking.
We've sent our greetings
and drank the tea too.
Mr. Su, why haven't
you shown yourself yet?
Mr. Su is our junior.
We came here because he told us to.
We're his guests.
Mengzhen has his own reasons
for not showing himself.
What do you mean?
House Master is terminally ill.
And Mengzhen just came back
from the northern battlefield.
Everyone knew that
he had reached Kushuipu.
However, no Keeper came to welcome him.
Even one person is enough
for the sake of courtesy.
However, the sinister Gu Dong
was the one who came to receive him.
Although Mengzhen
was lucky to be alive,
he was poisoned and wounded.
He cannot afford to catch a cold.
What?
Did Gu Dong betray us?
Did he do so under
someone else's instruction?
Mengzhen, hurry
and explain it to the Keepers.
My fellow peers,
I'm seriously wounded.
I hope you guys
can pardon me for the rudeness.
You're seriously wounded indeed.
Even your voice was affected.
Of course.
Mengzhen is a skilled martial artist.
Back then, that scoundrel
slashed his throat.
You don't need to act it out
when you speak.
Mr. Su,
you may continue.
Mengzhen, you can continue.
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
You can leave first.
Leave this to me.
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
I've summoned you guys here
to explain the whole story.
A few days ago,
a good friend of my father's
suddenly gave me a white jade box.
Inside the box
was something extremely important.
I wasn't assaulted at Kushuipu
because they wanted to kill me.
They were aiming for the box.
Those who tried to assassinate Mr. Su
were from the Six Half Hall.
Everyone knows
that the Elders of the Six Half Hall
do kill for money too.
Mr. Su, could it be
that you forgot who
you had offended?
You better think twice
before you speak next time.
Niantang,
let Mr. Su finish his words.
Many assassins were aiming for the box.
I'm sure it's something extraordinary.
Mr. Su,
where is the box right now?
The box is still with me.
Initially, I wanted to hand it
to my father personally.
However, I'm seriously wounded.
I don't have the confidence
to hand it to my father personally.
So, since Delegate
and the Keepers are here today,
why don't we open the box
and show its content
to the public?
Since this item is so important,
we should hand it to House Master.
I don't think
we should open it here.
(Virtuous and Kind)
You're finally back.
Good job.
Is he doing fine?
Follow me.
I'm not dead yet.
Greetings, Father.
Is the Capital cold?
The North is colder.
You sicko.
I brought you a pot of Shiniangchun liquor
from the city's gate.
People say that the treasures
of the world aren't durable.
Bright clouds scatter easily
while glaze is fragile.
However, their liquor remained the same
after so many years.
This is something rare.
Lianxin,
get us two cups.
I will drink together with my son.
Have you obtained it?
It never left my side.
Open it.
Indeed.
Hua Wucuo does belong
to the Six Half Hall.
Delegate, if you don't allow it,
I still have another idea.
Pickled kidney with liquor and vinegar.
Mengzhen feels sick.
Let me take a look at him.
What's going on?
Yesterday's menu?
Continue.
Regarding the other idea I have,
I need someone
to escort me to Sunset Drizzle.
However, since there are
traitors among us,
I don't trust anyone here right now.
Keepers, I hope you guys
can escort me personally.
You don't need
to go through all that trouble.
Since you're unable to move freely,
why don't you hand the box to me?
I'll hand it to House Master for you.
Everyone,
how long do we have to keep up the act?
The person inside
isn't Su Mengzhen at all.
I was wondering why he sounded strange.
So, it is an impostor!
The Red Sleeve Blade?
Now that I've returned to the Capital,
I wanted to have a drink with you guys
and speak out freely.
All of you are my elders
and martial brothers.
I don't wish to fight you guys.
Good.
I'm sure you'll be a better
house master than me.
I have two pieces of advice for you.
First,
you must be benevolent and righteous.
Only then, you'll be able
to gather popularity.
Second,
you must understand how power works.
Life-or-death situations in the martial
arts world are determined by swords.
However, when you're in this position,
power decides whether you live or die.
You can hate power,
but you must understand how it works.
All right.
It's time for us to have a drink.
House Master,
your body is...
A person only has a limited number
of meals and drinks
to enjoy in life.
With the last drink of my life,
I will celebrate my son's ascension.
Su Mengzhen,
listen closely.
You need to keep
the martial arts world in order.
House Master!
This is bad! Something
happened to the House!
I knew it was a trick!
I knew you were a fake.
I'll leave this brat to you guys.
I'll return to the House!
Xiaoqing,
she's the daughter
of Wen Wan, Lord of Luoyang.
You can't afford to offend her.
The joss stick has already run out.
Mr. Su already has
the situation under control.
You have no chance now.
The Red Sleeve Blade?
This is pretty interesting.
Their act
was pretty good.
Chun,
at first, you hoped that
Su Mengzhen could win,
right?
That's because you and father
went against your promise
and attacked Mengzhen.
So,
don't blame me for helping him.
Hua Wucuo,
do you know your fault now?
(Memorial Tablet of Su Zhemu)
He's useless indeed.
He died before I had the chance
to kill him.
You and House Master
were
sworn brothers.
I'm still keeping you alive
because
you didn't attack your own brother.
However, you're a traitor.
That's a fact.
So what?
It's been so many years.
I've done a lot for the House.
You did do a lot for the House.
However, if people find out
that our next house master
is actually someone
from the Six Half Hall,
the House of Sunset Drizzle will cease
to exist in the martial arts world.
As long as I'm still alive,
you
won't get your way.
Hua Wucuo,
do you know your fault?
The box is in your hands.
If news of this gets out,
I will lose my foothold
in the martial arts world.
(Memorial Tablet of Su Zhemu)
You're the hero of all heroes.
It's my gain
for dying in your hands.
Come.
Give me a quick death.
I'm not killing you
because the House of Sunset Drizzle
emphasizes benevolence.
However, you don't act like
one of us at all.
That's nonsense.
I had plenty of chances
to kill your father.
I had the blade with me.
Why didn't I do it then?
Who gives you the right to say that
I'm not one of you?
All these years, we've witnessed
what he had done for the House
ourselves.
If we ask him which side
he belongs to right now,
I'm afraid he'll be confused as well.
As humans, we need to be
benevolent and righteous.
If not,
we're no different than livestock.
I kept him alive
because he's at least a decent human.
He's your subordinate.
How do you plan to deal with him?
Bring him here.
We can ask him if he admits defeat
and his mistake
in front of us.
Okay.
If he admits his mistake,
I'll keep him alive.
(Memorial Tablet of Su Zhemu)
After you said that,
there's no reason for me to kill you.
As for the name list,
it's not important to me at all.
Father told me to ask you this
right before he died.
Hua Wucuo,
(Memorial Tablet of Su Zhemu)
do you admit defeat?
Do you admit your mistake?
I've been defeated.
I admit my mistake.
(Memorial Tablet of Su Zhemu)
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
The old House Master has passed away.
Gu Dong was a spy
from the Six Half Hall.
I've already executed him at Kushuipu.
The Delegate, Hua Wucuo,
has shown his disloyalty
by attempting to usurp
the house master's position.
According to our rules,
he shall be expelled
from the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Delegate.
I'm fine.
Come.
One,
two,
three.
Keepers,
each of us used to serve our own masters.
Let's wipe the slate clean.
In the future, we're still brothers.
Everyone knows what
the House of Sunset Drizzle has done
but not what it's capable of.
In the future,
the House of Sunset Drizzle is me.
I am the House of Sunset Drizzle.
Gale as fierce as gold,
the drizzle exists forever!
The long breeze graces us
with its presence,
conquering all mountains!
Gale as fierce as gold,
the drizzle exists forever!
The long breeze graces us
with its presence,
(House of Sunset Drizzle)
conquering all mountains!
(Good Health and Long Life)
Greetings, Chief Elder.
You're here?
It must've been tough for you out there.
You should return to the Hall.
I've kept the position
of the Tenth Elder for you.
Thank you, Chief Elder.
I heard Hua Wucuo
thought of himself
as a member of
the House of Sunset Drizzle in the end.
He was expelled
according to the rules
of the House of Sunset Drizzle, right?
Yes.
He's too muddle-headed.
Since that's the case,
Hua Wucuo
is the traitor of Six Half Hall.
I'm sure you know how to deal
with the traitors of the Hall.
Yes,
Chief Elder.
(You established
Sunset Drizzle yourself.)
(Father, do you have)
(a centurial plan for the House?)
As the saying goes,
if you raise your son to 100 years old,
you'll be worried for him for 99 years.
However, the House of Sunset Drizzle
isn't my son.
You are.
You are the centurial plan
I've left behind for the House.
You are the House of Sunset Drizzle.
So, I'm not much happier
now that you're dead.
The martial arts world won't be as fun
without you around, Su Zhemu.
Both of you are considered
old acquaintances.
Come.
You should drink with him too.
Now that he's dead,
you won't be able to seek your revenge.
The elders in the martial arts world are
getting fewer and fewer by the day.
There are no grudges between us.
To the elders of the martial arts world.
Chief Elder.
Father?
My daughter, you're back?
Your father isn't dead yet.
Why are you wearing this?
Take it off.
I'm wearing it for Uncle Su's sake.
I know Su Zhemu is dead,
but the engagement
between you and Su Mengzhen
was called off five years ago, right?
There's no need for you
to do this for the Su family.
So, once the wedding
has been called off,
you've forgotten all about benevolence
and righteousness too, right?
That's why you tried
to kill Su Mengzhen, didn't you?
Su Mengzhen?
He should've been dead long ago.
I could've saved myself a lot of trouble
if I had killed him earlier.
And you two
wouldn't end up like this today.
Father.
My daughter,
Su Mengzhen is the house master
of the House of Sunset Drizzle now.
The martial arts world
is no longer peaceful.
You should forget about him.
And,
you should return the token of
the Six Half Hall to me.
My daughter,
the martial arts world
is no longer peaceful.
You shouldn't get yourself involved.
Come, be a good girl.
Regarding the martial arts world
you want to conquer,
I'm not interested in it at all.
This token means nothing to me.
You can take it if you want.
Now that Uncle Su passed away,
I'm sure Mengzhen
is in a bad mood.
And, he has plenty of other things
to deal with.
I'll take care of you guys
for a few more days.
I didn't expect you to be this sensible.
Can you only tell by now?
You'll know how nice I am
after I bring you guys
around the Capital.
You can take care of him then.
I don't need you to take care of me.
Why must you go against me all the time?
I'm not going against you. I'm serious.
I wish to join Sunset Drizzle
as soon as possible.
Little Rock,
do you remember
what I've told you before?
I said I have to go
to the brightest place
in order to make a name for myself.
But, look at the Capital.
Mr. Su, Hua Wucuo,
Di Feijing,
all of them are here.
That's why I have to stay here.
I want to be the brightest flame
in the martial arts world.
I was suddenly reminded
of my martial brother
after hearing that from you.
So,
do you also wish to become
someone like him?
Of course.
I do envy him a lot.
However, I'm only envious
of him right now.
Maybe it'll be different in the future.
Will that change too?
Mr. Su is the most glorious man
I've ever seen.
I envy him a lot.
But I don't want
to keep being envious of him.
I want to make
other people envious of me.
I want to be the top martial artist too.
One day,
I, Bai Choufei,
will dictate the rules
of the martial arts world.
Cabbage,
are you trying to reach the sky?
That's precisely what I'm going to do!
Come.
What about you, Wen Rou?
Me?
You can forget about me.
There's nothing in particular
that I would like to achieve.
That's right.
You're the Young Lady of the Wen family.
You're well-fed and well-clothed.
You don't lack anything.
You don't even need a dream.
I don't want it.
Forget it if you don't want to tell us.
Precisely.
Come on.
Come.
That's not it.
The only thing I want to do in life
is "I don't want it".
I don't want other people
to dictate my life for me.
Since young, I've had to wait
for my betrothal.
I had to learn music and needlework.
I don't want that.
I want to learn martial arts.
When I'm grown up, I had no choice
but to go for an arranged marriage.
I have to see guys I don't know
and attend blind dates.
I don't want that.
I want to roam the martial arts world.
This world always
views women with contempt.
Women from dignified families
aren't supposed to show themselves.
I don't want that.
I want to be a heroine
who helps the weak.
I didn't expect your life
to be this tough.
That's right.
As a woman,
there are many ordeals
we need to go through.
However,
why must they reinforce
such ordeals onto the ladies?
My dream
is to tell the people
who always dictated my life
that
I'll decide my own life.
Great!
Great words!
Good!
Little Rock,
you haven't told us
about your dreams yet.
What do you want to
become in the future?
I've made up my mind.
I want to become a hero.
Don't misunderstand me.
I don't want to become the kind of hero
listed on the list of heroes.
I just wish to be myself.
Aren't being yourself and being a hero
two different things?
- That's right.
- It's the same thing.
To be a hero, you must be
the best version of yourself.
I wish to become a first-class hero.
I will bring justice to the world
and beat up the guys
that deserve a beating.
I just hope that I can be an influence
on other martial artists around me,
so that they can help out the weak too.
That's the reason
I want to become a hero.
Not bad at all, Little Rock.
Come, let's drink.
Let's hope that our dreams
can be realized.
- Cheers!
- To our dreams!
♪With whom do I visit this restaurant?♪
♪The moonlit hall
stands within the clouds♪
♪With whom do I ride my horse?♪
♪The snow has blanched our attire♪
♪In whom can I confide?♪
♪It's hard enough to find a true friend♪
♪With whom do I drink?♪
♪And who will tell me chug more?♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible, that sentiments
go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
is like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We weathered through the storms♪
♪Don't tell me♪
♪It's impossible,
that time will always move on♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
is just a wishful thinking♪
♪I will find it, I will pierce through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪
♪One blade, one sword♪
♪For my life, I have been wondering♪
♪One lance, one arrow♪
♪A solitude and regretful life♪
♪I discard my attire, I cut off my past♪
♪Will happiness bloom?♪
♪Perhaps I should get rid
of mortal desires♪
♪They are the source of woes♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible, that sentiments
don't go in a blink of an eye♪
♪That to stay out of it
isn't like an unreachable dream♪
♪I'm glad to have you accompany me
on my journey♪
♪Begone, the thick evening mist♪
♪We will weather through the storms♪
♪If♪
♪It's possible,
that time can move slower♪
♪That the wish to leave behind a legacy
isn't just a wishful thinking♪
♪I found it, I pierced through
the layers of fog♪
♪I will not allow my life to be wasted♪