[English subtitles are available]
The following content is intended for viewers aged 18 and older.
It may include content featuring inappropriate images, sounds, violence, sexuality, or language.
Viewer discretion is advised. Viewers under 18 should watch with parental guidance.
[Characters, actions, locations, organizations, professions, and incidents are fictitious and intended for entertainment purposes only]
[No intention to endorse any behavior depicted in this series. Viewer discretion is advised]
[Unforgotten Night]
[Previously]
As you can see,
I already have a boyfriend.
It's fine.
I understand.
Are you interested in me?
I am.
Can you help me forget the embrace of someone I know?
I'll make you forget that embrace.
Why did I let him do that? When he's so violent towards me.
[Why do I feel more aroused when my partner uses violence when we're in bed?]
I don't think so.
I told you to gather information on Kim. How did it go?
Here, sir.
Kim Kunanon
The only son in his family.
His parents have retired.
He's living at a condo located in Silom, the same condo where Day lives in.
He's currently running an auditing firm.
He and Day were classmates.
[Moscow, Russia]
[Evan, 45 years old, Moscow, Russia, Casino owner]
[Evan]
Hello?
Don't trust Danai.
Danai is interfering with my connections in the ministry.
I've heard of that.
I have a backup plan.
Good.
What about Danai?
Did you find any information?
Here, sir.
[Mr. Danai tells the news reporters]
[That he is ready for a casino auction legalized by the government committee]
Keep a close eye on him.
Check what he's been doing
and who he's been in contact with.
Yes, sir.
Jin.
Kim won't be here today. You can send him e-mails if anything comes up.
Roger that.
Hey, what's going on?
Oh my goodness.
We're here to meet Mr. Kunanon.
He didn't come to work today.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for the sudden visit.
I forgot.
I left a lot of marks on his body last night. Of course he wouldn't dare to come to work today.
Kim, are you all right?
What's wrong? I'm fine.
Someone came to our office looking for you just now.
He came with a lot of bodyguards, like a boss of the mafia.
They went to the office?
Yeah, he said he's looking for Mr. Kunanon.
And I said, you didn't come to work today.
Then he made a spooky grin on his face and left.
It's nothing. He might be one of our clients.
Really?
But Jin doesn't think so.
He has a mafia boss vibe, totally.
Jin, did you watch too many movies?
I think he's just a client.
I mean it, Kim. You didn't see him in person.
Since Kim said he's one of our clients. Then I can be relieved.
Don't worry.
You guys should go back to work.
If anything comes up, just e-mail me.
Understood, sir.
Someone went to my office to look for me?
And he looked like a mafia?
Where's my food delivery?
That's fast.
Who is this?
Should I be upset?
You don't remember me?
I don't know you.
May I come in first, Kim?
Please get your hand off the door, I really don't know you. I'm sorry.
I don't have anything to say to you.
Pardon me for being rude.
So this is your room?
Do you live here alone?
Who allowed you to get in?
Get out of here, right now!
Otherwise, I'll call the police.
You...
Let me keep this for you for a while
so that we can have a nice talk.
How did you know my address?
You finally admit
that you still remember me.
I don't know you.
You said you were sober.
You said you could remember everything.
You just asked me to hug you last night.
And now you're kicking me away?
I didn't do any of that.
Are you saying you already forgot what happened between us last night?
Kim.
Get out! Don't come in!
Kim!
Let's talk properly, Kim.
Why are you avoiding me?
Just stay right there if you want to talk.
What's your name again?
I'm Kamol.
How did you know my address?
What do you want from me?
Here's my answer for the first question.
It wasn't that hard for people like me to get someone's address.
As for the second question,
I'd like you to come live with me.
Why do I have to live with a stranger?
Plus, about last night, what's done is done.
It's just a one-night stand. Why are you being so stubborn?
You can think of it that way.
But for me,
you're the one that I want to spend my life with.
Take your time to think about it.
I'll come by every day.
So we'll get to know each other more until you agree to live with me.
Isn't that just a one-night stand?
Can't you just move on?
Besides, I will never go live with you.
It might have been just one night,
but that single night
made me very impressed and satisfied.
Can't a one-night stand turn into something more?
Get lost.
I'm done talking to you. Just get out of here.
Why?
I just want to be responsible to you.
Ouch!
[Unforgotten Night]
Can't you just give me a chance?
You know
how compatible we were last night.
Or did you think it wasn't good?
Is it too much to ask you
not to shut me out?
[NEXT BREAK]
Who sent you here?
♫Please let me love you once, let me see with my heart♫
[Unforgotten Night]
You know...
[This series was filmed under pandemic restrictions]
how compatible we were last night.
Or did you think it wasn't good?
Is it too much to ask you
not to shut me out?
I'm sorry to disturb you, sir.
What is it?
Our warehouse in Chachoengsao is on fire. We're currently trying to put out the fire.
I don't have time to continue our conversation today.
Just think about what I said.
What was that about?
He really acts like a mafia.
Kom.
Send someone to keep an eye on Kim.
Don't let him out of your sight.
Understood, sir.
About the warehouse.
What happened exactly?
Explain it to me.
It happened when the guards were changing shifts.
Someone sneaked in to set fire.
We were able to capture one of them,
but the rest have escaped.
I already told Krit to take that person to the office.
Did anyone get injured? Did anything get destroyed?
Fortunately, our latest products have been exported already.
There were only a few bulletproof vests left in the warehouse during the fire.
As for our subordinates, they are all safe.
Did you tell the police not to interfere with this?
Yes, I did, sir.
Good.
I'll deal with it myself.
Who sent you here?
Hey!
My boss just asked you a question.
Answer him.
If you're not going to answer,
well, then...
Clean this mess up.
And go find out who sent this scumbag.
Wait! Don't hurt me! I'll tell you!
It's too late.
They're all dead?
Didn't you say only one of them was captured?
Maybe the one who got captured confessed everything.
But at least we managed to burn down his warehouse.
I know! But that also means he's aware that I'm behind all of this.
He killed all my subordinates to threaten me. Nice try, Kamol!
He stuck his nose into my business first, and now he has killed my subordinates!
I'd like to see who will have the last laugh in the end.
Hey!
Tell everyone that we'll have an urgent meeting.
Yes, sir!
Kamol!
Danai.
My father told me to give this to your father. Congratulations on getting a cabinet seat.
Thanks. Have a seat.
Hey.
Thank you on behalf of my dad.
My dad is not here today. He went out to play golf with his friends.
Please send my regards to your father too.
Sure thing.
By the way, Danai, don't you want to get into politics like your father?
I want to have a brother who is a politician.
I know we're just cousins, but I've always seen you as a real brother.
Aww.
That's so sweet.
No wonder my dad adores you so much.
All right. Maybe I'll try in the next election.
Danai, what are you doing right now? Am I disturbing you?
I saw your subordinate leaving the room just now.
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Have you eaten anything yet?
Do you want to have lunch with me?
Of course. I'd love to!
Okay.
I'll tell them to set the table.
Pick up the call, Kamol. This is urgent!
Hello, Ms. Cherry.
Why didn't Kamol pick up the call? I have an urgent matter to talk to him.
My boss is in a meeting.
You can tell me instead.
Fine.
I accidentally overheard something...
The government will make a public announcement soon.
[Seoul, South Korea]
But before that,
I'll go to Korea by myself.
Only you this time? Is Mr. Evan coming with you?
Mr. Evan has specifically assigned me to take care of this case.
I'll report and keep Mr. Evan updated on this case.
All right. See you then.
Get me tickets to Seoul.
Just you and me on this trip.
Make sure we arrive there by the afternoon. Once the business is done, we'll return right away.
Yes, sir.
What do you want to say? Just say it.
And about Kim. How is he?
He hasn't left the apartment since we left, except for a couple of times to go downstairs for takeout.
Lop tried to do it for him, but Kim wouldn't let him do that. He insisted on coming down by himself.
You are...
serious about this guy, right?
You know me well.
If I wasn't serious,
would I waste time looking for him in person?
No, sir.
I've never seen you interested in anyone as much as Mr. Kim.
By the way, I already told our subordinates to deal with the people who caused the fire at the warehouse.
There's one more thing.
If it's about Cherry, I already know that.
I just didn't want to pick up the call.
But this time, I think you should listen.
Ms. Cherry has sent us some information about the mastermind behind the arson case.
[Unforgotten Night]
Who?
Since she provided the information, I think it should be Danai, right?
Yes.
It matches the information we got from those arsonists we took care of.
As for his motive,
I think he must know that we've sent people to spy on him.
I was just collecting information.
I haven't done anything to him yet.
Danai was just asking for trouble.
If you keep watering them like this, these plants are gonna die.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I just got lost in my train of thought.
What are you thinking about?
You seemed to be distracted after you came back from the reunion.
I don't want to be unreasonable, but sometimes I think you and Kim...
I only have you, Itt. You just need to remember this.
Stop overthinking, okay?
What's wrong?
If you want to keep an eye on me, just do it.
I won't yell at you.
I have something to report.
What is it? I have to go to work soon.
It won't take long.
Ruj and Kit said that Kom told them that...
Mr. Kamol has a message for you.
Wait, you're telling me that Mr. Kamol has something to say to me, right?
Yes.
Mr. Kim, I haven't told you his message yet.
Shoot it.
Mr. Kamol said he'll take you out to dinner in two days.
Okay, got it.
Excuse me, could you get your foot out of the doorway?
My boss really likes you. Why are you so mean to him?
[Ruby Rose Clinic]
What's the queue now?
Ms. May, please wait a moment. The doctor is currently preparing.
Okay, sure.
Please wait a few minutes.
This is my seat.
Is there a name tag somewhere?
I came here first. I've been waiting for a while now.
The doctor made an appointment with me first.
My appointment with the doctor is right now.
No way! I came here first. Besides, I've been waiting for a long time.
The doctor made an appointment with me first, right?
No! I came first, right?
Ms. May, your room is ready, this way.
Hello, Jin.
I'm at Ruby Rose Clinic. I'm here to pamper my facial skin.
That's right. I'm at the clinic now.
Kim won't let you visit him? Why?
No!
If you're not ready yet, I'll go first.
Jin, I just got cut in line because of you. I'll deal with you later!
Let's call it a day now. It's going to be tough tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Water, sir.
Mr. Kamol, well, I...
What's wrong?
Is it about your nephew?
Yes, sir.
Where is he?
He's in the kitchen. I'll bring him to you now.
Have you met her nephew before?
I haven't, sir.
Hello, sir.
What's your name?
Baiboon, sir.
What grade are you in?
If you want to stay here, the only thing you have to do is take good care of your grandmother.
As for your study,
I'll take care of it.
Mr. Kamol...
That's the deal.
Don't think too much about it. You don't owe me any favor.
Let's just do what I said.
Yes, sir. Thank you very much.
Kom.
Yes, sir.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay, sir.
Baiboon.
Say thank you to Mr. Kamol.
Thank you, sir.
Alright. I'll go get some rest then.
Baimoon, say thank you to Kom too.
Thank you, Kom.
Auntie Ne, if there's nothing else, please excuse me.
All right.
See? I told you Mr. Kamol is very kind.
You're right.
Hello?
You shut the door in my subordinate's face today?
Mr. Kamol.
So you remember my voice.
Where did you get my number?
I don't know. You number just pops up on my phone.
Liar. You're being rude.
Why didn't you ask me for my number politely?
It's my privacy.
You got my number without my consent...
Okay, okay. It's my bad.
Well,
will you give me
your Line number now?
No, I won't.
Please don't call me again. Or else I will change my phone number.
I just wanted to tell you that I have to go abroad for work.
So I won't be able to see you for the next few days.
When I return, I'll pick you up at your place.
Where are you taking me? I'm not going to live with you.
So you have thought about it, haven't you?
I just want to take you to dinner.
I won't go anywhere with you. I won't go to dinner with you too.
Also, I won't go anywhere with someone like you.
I'm hanging up. I'm going to bed now.
Who would go with someone like you? It's never gonna happen.
What are you laughing at?
You look funny in the photo that Toy just posted.
How so?
Furrowed brows and a long face.
Why were you so stressed?
Anyway, it matches with the caption.
The thug couple?
What about you? Do you think you have a thug vibe?
I was very brutal back then.
What about now?
I'm not talking to you anymore.
It's good that you're no longer brutal.
Don't become a bully.
Why?
Because I don't want to be tough on you.
Kim looks good in every picture.
That's an exaggerated compliment.
[He's single]
He is good-looking. Take a look.
I'm not worried about Kim anymore,
because you said you only have eyes for me.
[Unforgotten Night]
That's good.
Do you promise you'll only have eyes for me?
Yes, I promise.
[Viewer discretion is advised]
When will I forget about him?
We'll arrive in an hour.
Take it easy.
Yes, sir.
[Seoul, South Korea]
This could be called a mega project in our country.
The specific details of the bidding process
will be officially announced later this afternoon.
It seems very promising to invest in this project.
Mr. Dong-wook wants to know the cost estimation of this project.
No problem.
[Location]
Kim, are you feeling better?
Yes. That's why I'm here to work.
I'm worried that you guys will be lonely.
Come on, Kim. We were just teasing you being so mean.
You wouldn't even let us pay you a visit.
That's because I don't want you guys to catch my cold.
But, was it really a cold,
or perhaps
just a hangover?
You know me so well.
You tell me.
Right, is there any unfinished work?
Just send it to me.
I'm ready to take my punishment.
Hooray. Be prepared to receive your punishment. I mean, work.
Kim, please wait a moment.
Let's go! It's time for Omakase.
Kim, you're the best.
He hasn't said he'll treat us to Omakase yet.
Omakase, please!
Anything is fine for me because I'm so hungry.
Kim.
Hello.
How are you doing? I came here yesterday, but May said you were on sick leave.
I was actually planning to pay you a visit.
I told him that you didn't want anyone to disturb you.
I'm much better now. Please take a seat, Mr. Karan.
If only I knew your address, I would definitely pay you a visit.
Here. I've brought this fruit basket for you. At first, I was going to ask May to give it to you.
Thank you.
But please don't bring gifts next time.
Kim,
you're on a lunch break now, right?
Well...
do you want to have lunch with me?
Please?
Actually, I...
Mr. Kamol.
Kim.
[NEXT EPISODE]
When are you going to keep quiet? Stop bothering someone who belongs to me.
Please leave.
Isn't this the hotel where we first met?
What are you trying to do?
What do you think?
You've changed.
You weren't like this before.
You used to be very kind.
I'm not a kind person.