=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 31=
Yunchang,
are you really getting married?
Who are you?
How dare you trespass in Shen Manor!
The Gate Bureau is here
catching a thief.
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
Insolence!
(Harmonious and Gentle)
How dare you resist official officers?
Who are you trying to arrest?
Her.
She is my daughter-in-law.
What if I don't allow it?
Then, I'll take you down,
too.
Young lady,
you're young, but you talk big.
Do you know that in all of Xichuan,
(Happiness. Bright Moon and Clear Winds)
no one dares to disrespect me?
No matter how great the Shen family is,
do you dare to be
an enemy of the Gate Bureau?
Young lady,
if you dare to be an enemy
of all the Xichuan outlaws,
then bring it on.
I'll be waiting.
Fine.
I will take everyone in this manor
into custody.
I'm afraid you don't have the ability.
No one move!
(Token)
I have the royal command token of the Prince of Shu.
By order of the Prince of Shu.
Here's the Prince of Shu's oral decree.
Shen Gongquan once saved my life.
No one is allowed
to act presumptuously in his manor.
(Token)
The order concluded.
Young lady,
do you still want to fight?
I never thought
the current Prince of Shu
would act as your guarantor.
In my younger days,
I traveled the martial world.
By chance, I saved the Prince's life.
The Prince was grateful,
ensuring no one in Xichuan
would dare to touch the Shen family.
The Prince of Shu
is the current Emperor's uncle.
Let's drop it for today.
Fine.
Since the Prince of Shu
has given orders,
the Gate Bureau will comply.
Chu Yunchang,
you'd better hide in Xichuan
for the rest of your life.
Otherwise,
once you leave
the protection of the Shen family,
I will make sure you
have no place to be buried!
Withdraw!
(Shen Manor)
Sooner or later,
I'll have Grandfather wipe this place out.
Yu,
where is Chief Mao?
Deputy Luo,
what are you doing now?
Chief Mao is inside.
I'm going to find him.
Deputy Luo,
you've just arrived in Chengdu
and almost caused a major incident.
Fortunately, no violent
conflict broke out today,
otherwise, how would
I explain it to the Prince of Shu?
And now you want to go back?
If you really push
Shen Gongquan too far,
I'm afraid neither of us
will be able to handle the consequences.
But Yu is still inside.
Deputy Luo,
calm down.
He'll be fine.
Are you really going to marry him?
Yes.
I just want to ask you one thing.
Are you being forced,
or is it of your own free will?
Of my own free will.
♪Can't bear to keep acting anymore♪
♪Pitted against each other,
neither of us gives in♪
♪One is cold as ice,
the other is burning like fire♪
Fine.
Today is my wedding day.
Chief Mao,
please
leave.
Did you hear that?
My wife told you to leave.
♪Despite countless ordeals♪
♪I can't untie the knot in your heart♪
Leave now!
Wait, man, who are you?
Right, leave now!
Go!
Leave quickly! Go!
Fine.
Hurry, let's go.
I'm leaving.
- Go back.
- Go.
Go back.
- Hurry and leave.
- Just go.
I'm leaving.
Get going.
♪Worlds apart, I wait for our reunion♪
♪But I'll spend my life
keeping you safe♪
♪Lies and vows,
let them stay in the past♪
Chu Yunchang.
From now on,
we are finished.
♪Worlds apart, I wait for our reunion♪
♪But I'll spend my life
keeping you safe♪
♪Lies and vows,
let them stay in the past♪
♪Let's return to when we first met♪
(Happiness)
I am terribly sorry.
My deepest apologies.
The mood was briefly dampened just now,
but everything is back to normal.
The couple may
continue with the ceremony.
Wait!
Feng?
Feng,
what are you doing here?
(Shen Liefeng, Young Master of the Shen family)
Liefeng, why did you come out?
I...
What do you want to say?
I... I don't...
Could it be that you want to perform
the wedding bows yourself?
No, I don't want to marry her.
What nonsense is that?
Feng,
I am doing this for your own good.
It's all for the sake of the Shen family.
No, I...
Did she say something to you?
What could I possibly have said to him?
Lord Shen,
it seems you don't understand
Young Master Shen's feelings at all.
His feelings?
Father,
all these years,
could it be you didn't know
that my heart
already belongs to someone else?
I do not love Sect Leader Chu.
Your heart belongs to someone?
Who is it?
She is
Biyao, who has always taken care of me.
Hurry, let's go.
Young Master,
(Biyao, Shen family maid)
let me help you.
I've been tormented by illness
in my whole life.
Only when I am with Biyao
do I forget
all the troubles of this world.
I cannot live my life without her.
Therefore,
I will never take
Chu Yunchang as my wife.
Biyao, come.
Come.
You... You two...
Biyao, tell the truth.
Are you and my brother in love?
Lord Shen,
I deserve to die,
but I
truly love the Young Master.
Ridiculous!
You lowly servant, how dare you
have feelings for your master?
Do you know what you've done?
Father,
I also truly love Biyao.
Silence!
How... How dare you two do such a thing?
Why wouldn't they?
Biyao has always
taken care of Young Master Shen
with such devotion and care.
Spending every day together,
feelings were bound to grow.
Why try to stop them?
They are not of equal social standing.
This is improper!
Lord Shen,
that's where you're wrong.
We in the martial world
have never cared for such trifles.
Your son and Biyao
are in love with each other.
So why are you so furious?
Indeed, Lord Shen.
Do you have the heart to watch your son
marry a woman he doesn't love
and be miserable
for the rest of his life?
Father, I felt that I was
a burden to the Shen family
and brought shame to you.
So I never dared
to leave the back courtyard,
let alone defy your wishes.
But now,
since it concerns
Biyao's and my happiness,
I'm emboldened
to ask for your blessing, Father.
Their love is unbreakable.
I withdraw voluntarily.
Father, Liefeng has suffered
his whole life.
This is his only wish.
Please just grant it to him.
You...
You have made me
lose face completely
before the heroes of Xichuan!
Father,
please just give
Biyao and me your blessing.
As long as I'm alive,
don't even think about it!
Then, I will wander
the world with Biyao!
I'm leaving too!
Don't you dare!
Lord Shen,
why are you being so stubborn?
My family affairs
are none of your business.
Well, this happened at my wedding.
I know you're angry right now,
but think about it carefully.
Isn't children's happiness
what parents value most?
Because of Mr. Shen's illness,
you
want to carry on the family line.
But Biyao
can also carry on the Shen family line.
Besides,
don't you still have Die?
Though Die is a woman,
she is ten times better than any man.
I'm a woman too,
but I'm also the Sect Leader
of the Sacred Hand Sect,
a Grandmaster of the martial world.
Why insist on a male successor?
Die is also your successor.
Father,
please bless Liefeng and Biyao.
As for revitalizing the Shen family,
I will take full responsibility.
- Young Master.
- Liefeng.
I have no other wish in this life.
Please, Father, grant it.
Fellow heroes,
I am very sorry.
Today's wedding is temporarily canceled.
I shall choose another auspicious day
for my son, Liefeng,
to marry Biyao.
Good!
Young Master...
Congratulations!
- Congratulations, Young Lord!
- Congratulations!
That's wonderful.
Yes, indeed.
I also have another announcement today.
From now on, my family estate
will be inherited by my daughter, Yidie.
Father.
My daughter, Yidie,
has assisted me since childhood.
She has mastered all my skills.
In the future,
all matters of the Shen family
will be decided by my daughter, Yidie.
Good!
Father,
you've finally recognized me.
Congratulations.
Die,
all these years,
I've treated you unfairly.
Congratulations, Lord Shen.
Congratulations, Miss Shen.
- Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Great news!
- Good!
- Excellent!
What a double celebration!
A great joy!
Congratulations!
Si,
you rest for a bit.
Yes.
Wushuang.
Yu, are you okay?
You scared me to death.
Master, you're finally awake.
You really worried us.
Look, I've even got
dark circles under my eyes.
Where are we going?
We're going back to the Gate Bureau.
The Gate Bureau.
What about Yunchang?
She...
She's already married to Shen Liefeng.
She has the Prince of Shu's protection.
We can only wait for her
to leave before capturing her.
Did she really marry Shen Liefeng?
Yu,
don't be heartbroken.
It should be in that direction.
I didn't expect Shen Gongquan
to actually be a man of his word.
He really gave us
Dongfang Bai's hiding place.
If he hadn't spoken up,
who would have thought that Dongfang Bai
was hiding right here
on Skyscraper Cliff?
You know,
on the wedding day,
I was really worried for you.
Tell me,
did you already know Shen Liefeng
was in love with Biyao?
Was that why you agreed to the wedding?
To provoke him on purpose?
The first time
I saw Shen Liefeng and Biyao,
I realized they were in love.
Shen Liefeng
was held back by his illness,
and Biyao by her status,
so neither of them spoke out.
I deliberately agreed to the marriage,
believing Shen Liefeng
would call it off for Biyao's sake.
So you had it all calculated.
You really had us worried sick.
I'm sure you noticed it long ago, Uncle.
Seeing how confident you looked,
you must have had a counter-strategy.
It's just that...
Mao Buyu...
Don't bring up sensitive subjects.
I only care about the truth now.
As for everything else,
we'll talk about it later.
Enough talk. Let's get moving.
Alright, let's go.
Slow down, Yu.
Master, how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Yu.
Shun.
Are you okay?
(Skyscraper Cliff Thatched Hut)
Is anyone here?
How can these scarecrows be alive?
Darn it.
These scarecrows
aren't afraid of weapons at all.
How can these scarecrows have life?
Someone must
be controlling them in secret.
These scarecrows
are controlled by golden threads.
Cut them!
Pull!
That fall nearly killed me.
He's the one
manipulating the scarecrows.
Who on earth are you?
(Powder-Faced Buddha, Dongfang Bai)
I am their master.
And who are you?
So you are Dongfang Bai?
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪