=The Autumn Ballad=
♪Winter clouds fill up the sky as the
geese leave behind a trail of sorrow♪
♪I lean in front of the window,
gazing from afar♪
♪I heard your singing♪
♪By the west riverbank♪
♪As our eyes meet each other,
our longing is still there♪
♪Mountains and seas apart,
waiting for the full moon♪
♪All for our sweet encounter♪
♪Smiling with you
as I stare at the bead curtains♪
♪I will not disappoint
our mutual affection in this lifetime♪
♪We fly wing to wing
beside the sea of mountains♪
♪Even if all creations go silent♪
♪I will not disappoint
our mutual affection in this lifetime♪
♪We fly wing to wing
beside the sea of mountains♪
♪Even if all creations go silent♪
=The Autumn Ballad=
=Episode 5=
Liang Yi?
What are you doing here?
I just finished talking with your dad.
So I stopped by to see you.
Why would you want to see me?
I'm just a rich idler.
I'm no match to Marquis Weiyuan.
You've been doing great business.
What's wrong?
Are you angry at me
because of He family?
How would I dare?
Let me ask you.
Did you send someone to the jail
to take care of Zhao Mingli?
How did you know that?
In the capital city,
nothing could be hidden
from Firewood Office.
Let alone you.
I have some advice for you.
Zhao Mingli and that girl are
at Firewood Office now.
Stop sending money
to Fengjing Prefecture.
You're being taken advantage of
by those guys in Fengjing Prefecture.
Both of them are at Firewood Office?
You protect them two?
I knew it.
You're not a cold-hearted man.
Who told you that?
Don't talk nonsense
if you don't know anything.
Look at you.
I'll write Qiu Yan a letter about this.
So that she could rest assured.
Stop there.
They would die if you told her this.
Fine, I'll listen to you.
I won't tell her.
Why is this fan here?
Madam has invited Qiu's daughters over
to play cards this morning.
One of the ladies must've left it.
I think it belongs to Qiu Min.
I saw her used it when we were eating.
Qiu Min?
She is Qiu Yan's younger sister,
Qiu Min.
She is my cousin too.
Give it to me, I'll return it to her.
I found it, I'll return it to her.
Let's try another day.
Why must it be another day?
We're in our uniform today.
This would scare her.
Please pass the message.
That Third Young Lady of Qiu Family
left something at my place.
She wanted to look for it.
Are you looking for a folding fan?
Yes.
I found it
at Duke Ying Residence's garden.
I never thought it was yours.
Thank you.
May I know your name?
So that I could send you
a gift to thank you.
(Evil-Purger)
What's your name?
I haven't known your name yet.
It's a trivial matter.
Don't mind it.
Let's go.
Fate brings people together
no matter how far apart they may be.
I didn't expect Third Young Lady
of Qiu Family
was the young lady
you rescued back then.
However,
why does she seem to have
no impression of you?
Seeing her being well-educated,
she's different compared
to that stubborn girl back then.
I guess she must be doing well.
It's good to forget
those bad memories about the past.
As you made a scene
in front of the matchmaker,
I'm afraid no one would dare
to propose to you in the future.
I'm worried about you.
That's great. I'll be less troublesome.
But you can't just stay at home
for your entire life.
Even if Seond Madam agrees with it,
Old Madam and the others
wouldn't accept it.
I can't take care of all things now.
I thought everything would be fine
after we returned from He Residence.
If I knew it'd become this way,
I'd rather stay in the temple,
it'd be clean and quiet.
The temple has its own difficulties.
Life is nothing more than forging ahead
or you'll fall behind.
Men are free,
they'll naturally have ways.
But we're women.
There's nothing we can do
to forge ahead.
How nice would it be
if we were this wisp of smoke?
So that we can go
anywhere we like with the wind.
Qingdai,
will there be a day
which women can read
and study freely like the men?
That we can take the liberty
to choose our mate for life.
And we don't have to be despised
and controlled by our families.
Miss, don't you want to open the gift
from Young Master Qin?
Qin Xuan gave them jade pendants.
He casually asked Min'er
to bring one to me.
It's just a courtesy.
Miss,
it's not a jade pendant,
it's a wooden hairpin.
Let me have a look.
First Young Lady and Fourth Young Lady
got jade pendants.
But he gave us a broken piece of wood.
When we were at He Residence,
seeing Young Master Qin helping you
that way,
I thought he was a nice guy.
I didn't expect he was a snob, too.
(Lonely smoke straight in the desert,)
long river setting a round sunset.
Even if it's a wisp of smoke,
one day, it'll go straight
to the blue sky.
There are always options
as long as we don't give up.
I'll throw it away for you now.
Don't.
It's a wooden hairpin,
but it means something.
Could a wood be better than a jade?
He knew that I was trapped here.
He wanted to use
this wooden hairpin
to advise me not to sulk.
But
there's no lettering
on it.
Put it on me, I want to try it.
Yes.
Sir, Madam said she'll send
the matchmaker to Qiu Residence
to propose after you look
over these betrothal gifts.
You go tell Madam
to postpone the proposal
for several days.
If she wants to know why,
just tell her that I have my reasons.
Yes.
Sir, why do you want to postpone it?
If the matchmaker went to propose,
of course Qiu Family
wouldn't reject it.
Just that I don't know
how Qiu Min feels about me.
Why would you care about her feelings?
Since ancient times, a lady's marriage
has been decided by the parents
and arranged by the matchmaker.
I saw her as an ordinary lady.
I'd just marry her.
But I never thought
that she was the little girl
I rescued back then.
As I rescued her back then,
why would I make her marry
a man she doesn't like?
Sir, you should just tell her the truth.
That you're her benefactor.
I'm sure she'll agree with it.
Threatening a lady with a small favor,
what would it make me then?
What's your plan?
Tomorrow,
you stop by Marquis Yongming Residence.
(Invitation card)
(First Madam Qiu, Jiang, Marquis Yongming
Residence will hold Chuiwan)
(in the late spring, Qiu's young ladies
are invited to the party)
Traditionally, only the children
of the third-rank officials
or the officials
with a higher ranking can attend
Chuiwan Party
in Marquis Yongming Residence.
Second Brother is
a fourth-rank official.
Why did they send the invitation card
to our residence?
Marquis Yongming Residence
has been officials for generations
and it's supported by the palace.
The officials and their wives
in the capital city will attend
Chuiwan Party every year.
Ostensibly,
it's a party.
In fact, it provides chances
for the royal princes
to meet young ladies.
(Madam Kou, Qiu Hong's concubine)
I'm afraid someone has already had
their eyes on our daughters.
Those who can attend Chuiwan Party
have higher status than our family.
That's our daughters' karma.
You don't have to show your happiness
on your face.
People will look down on you.
Old Madam has agreed to it.
We, Qiu family, will send
three young ladies over.
Three?
Old Madam didn't allow Yan to go.
Didn't she say she's weak
and hard to recover that day?
Just let her stay at home to recuperate.
I knew that Old Madam
wouldn't let you off the hook easily.
Obviously, she's trying
to embarrass you.
It's expected.
There's nothing to be mad about.
Didn't you want to thank
Young Master Qin in person?
I thought that you could meet him
at Chuiwan Party.
It's impossible now.
I must thank Qin Xuan
for sending me this gift.
You go tell Second Madam
that I have to go out
tomorrow afternoon.
I'll be back in one hour.
(Liang Residence)
Sir, Sir, Sir,
it's the letter
from Marquis Yongming Residence.
It said all three young ladies
from Qiu family would attend it.
Including Qiu Min.
Young Master,
Second Young Lady of Qiu Residence sends
us an invitation card.
Miss Qiu Yan?
How is it possible?
I think it's Third Young Lady
of Qiu family. You've misheard it.
Sir Jin, I didn't hear it wrong.
It's Second Young Lady of Qiu family.
She asked to meet me at Guiyun Building.
She is Qiu Min's sister.
I must show her some respect.
Greeting to Lord Liang.
This is from our Young Lady.
What does Miss Qiu Yan mean by this?
My Young Lady said
Lord Liang will understand it
by seeing it.
Qiu Yan.
You've put a lot of effort into it.
I think Lord Liang
must've understood what I wanted.
You wanted to use this stone
to remind me
that I was the one
who switched your gift
for Noble Consort to a stone.
I owed you this.
You want to attend Chuiwan Party.
Unfortunately, your engagement
with He family is broken off.
You've dishonoured your family.
So they want you to keep a low profile.
You want me to help you.
I like to talk with you, Lord Liang.
As it's easy.
If I didn't misremember it,
you said that
you hate me.
Why would I help
a person who hates me?
I couldn't help it if you insisted
not doing me this favour.
But I bet that you're unwilling
to owe anyone any favours.
You're arrogant.
Sir,
Miss Qiu Yan doesn't seem
like a sociable person.
Why would she take
Chuiwan Party so seriously?
Everyone knows that there'll be
many royal princes at Chuiwan Party.
I guess she has decided
to be a social climber.
I've never seen
a lady as shameless as she is before.
These four Chuiwan Rods
are made of the finest scented Rosewood
which is picked during autumn and winter
and they're made
during spring and autumn.
The rubber is mutually adhered,
it's a suitable time to make them.
I'm sure
the Young Ladies can take the top slot
by using them to compete.
Thank you, Madam.
Just that
Qiu family replied that only
three young ladies would attend it.
There's an extra one.
The extra one
is for Second Young Lady, Miss Qiu Yan.
Please have a seat.
(Walking under the moonlight)
Miss, you didn't see it.
First Madam looked awful.
And she became surly
and said that you're so capable.
I never thought
Lord Liang would be willing to help you.
Just that
I don't understand
why you didn't ask
Young Master Qin to help you
with this matter.
The reason I attend it is
to thank Qin Xuan.
How could I ask him a favor?
As for Liang Yi,
he went to any lengths to use me,
then I should just use him for this.
It's a two-way street.
Let's go.
Yan'er,
be honest with me.
How did you know
the wife of Marquis Yongming?
Is it because of Qin Xuan?
You've told me
that Qin Xuan had helped you a lot
when you were at He Residence.
He sounds like a righteous kid.
Is it because of him?
Nothing gets by you, Mother.
When we had dinner
at Duke Ying Residence,
Qin Xuan asked Min'er
to bring this hairpin to me.
He has indeed
put a lot of effort into it.
As I'm at Qiu Residence,
everyone despises me,
except you, Mother, you're nice to me.
After I came back from He Residence,
it became more serious.
This hairpin is like the skyglow
in the dark clouds
to me.
I can't help but grab it.
I want to get close to it.
I never thought
that Qin Xuan would be so attentive.
But Duke Ying Residence
has been officials for generations.
It's out of our league.
But if I don't take a leap of faith,
I could only marry
to that strange bones.
I remember you've told me
that it's tough to be a woman.
We have to bear kids and educate them.
There are many hardships
we have to go through
in our lives.
But I'm not afraid to suffer.
I want to entrust my life
to a man who's genuinely nice to me.
I don't want to entrust
my life to another in a haze.
I understand.
But I'm worried
this will get you into great trouble
if you do this.
I don't understand
why women should be controlled.
Why can't we have our own ambitions?
We can't speak it out even if we have.
I always remember
the poem you used to read me,
Spring Excursion.
If I could just be married to him,
my destiny would be forever set.
He might at last forsake me,
I'd have nothing to regret.
No matter how it ends,
I want to fight for it.
So that I won't regret.
Okay.
Since you've made up your mind,
just go at ease tomorrow.
Since ancient times, young men will
always pursue a fair lady.
Who sets the rule
that a lady couldn't take
the initiative?
Yes.
I'll be the one.
You'll be the one.
Hurry up, let's go there.
It's so lively.
Let's go, go there, let's go.
Come here.
Marquis Yongming is very generous.
- Madam is coming.
- Madam is here.
- Madam.
Madam is here.
Madam, you're here.
How are the young ladies doing?
They're ready.
Sorry for the inadequate care.
Don't mention it.
Min'er.
I'll take a look over there.
Sure.
You've done a great job
on the thing I requested.
I never owed anyone any favours.
From now on, we're even.
That's all I wanted.
However,
why do you come to Chuiwan Party?
What about you?
Why did you go to such lengths
to come here?
Qiu Yan,
what's wrong with you?
Are you upset?
Look at that man.
I saw him.
What's the matter?
That man is the inspector
from Firewood Office,
Liang Yi, Marquis Weiyuan.
He's mad for power.
He's hateful.
Qin Xuan is here.
Qin Xuan.
- Qin Xuan.
- It's been days since we met.
- Qin...
Even if you're restless now,
he won't speak to you either.
But...
What should I do, then?
Enough, you can just look at him.
Did you forget to buy
the sandalwood ink
that I asked you last time?
How would I dare to forget
the things Miss Xue asked of me?
Here you go, Sir.
Qin Xuan, you're great.
Thank you, Qin Xuan.
Qin Xuan, what's in your box?
It's fruit cake.
It's made with mint and basil.
It can soothe emotions
and improve eyesight.
It's efficient for strengthening
the stomach and spleen.
I've lost appetite lately.
I've been thinking
about Qin Xuan's fruit cake.
Qin Xuan, how could you be so stingy?
Yes, we want to eat it too.
No, just take as much as you like.
Thank you, Qin Xuan.
Beixue, serve everyone for me.
Yes, sir.
Qin Xuan.
Ladies, ladies,
the fruit cakes are here.
Greeting to Aunt and Sisters.
Qiu Yan, you're here too.
Good boy.
Are your mother here?
Aunt, my mother couldn't come
as she's handling
some family affairs.
All right.
Greet her for me.
Mei'er, come.
You and your cousin
should talk more.
This is the game for you youngsters.
I'll just leave you to it.
I didn't learn Chuiwan for long.
I heard that Qin Xuan had won
the first place
on the previous Chuiwan Party.
Can you teach me about it?
Qiu Mei,
everyone in the family knows
that I'm the weakest player.
Qin Xuan should teach me first.
Qin Xuan, look,
I embroider it myself,
does it look nice?
It's nice.
Qiu Ying is indeed a handyman.
Qin Xuan,
can you teach us
the rule of playing Chuiwan?
Meng Yu.
Qiu Ying, Qiu Mei,
Young Master Meng is good
at playing Chuiwan.
You may directly ask him
if you have any questions.
Qiu Yan, did you receive the hairpin
that I asked Qiu Min to bring to you?
Did you?
I received it.
Thank you.
I didn't see you wearing it.
Do you not like it?
There are many people
in Chuiwan Competition.
I'm afraid I'd lose it
or break it if I put it on.
It'd treat your favours not amiss.
I see, it's fine as long as you like it.
To be honest with you,
I made that hairpin myself.
I'm not good at making it.
I was afraid
that you'd think it's coarse
and dislike it.
Thanks for your kindness,
I'll see you at the game.
Qin Xuan, why are you standing here?
Follow me.
There are few rich ladies
that would like to meet you.
Let's go.
Miss,
I thought Young Master Qin
only treated you nice.
Who knew he'd spread his gifts around.
No wonder you treated him that way.
I don't have the prettiest face
and innate talents.
Why would he
only treat me nice?
I'm not the female character
in the skit.
It'll be harder to get
what you want now.
Why don't you teach them?
No, no.
Young Master Meng is tired,
just let Qin Xuan teach us.
All right, let's go over there.
All right, let's go.
If he has eyes only for me,
of course it'd be a precious fate.
If I haven't got the luck,
it'd be my strength
if I could make him fall for me.
Sir, I've asked around.
Miss Qiu Min is practising
Chuiwan alone over there.
Why do I get
the sense that she comes here
for Qin Xuan?
Fellow participants,
please provide prizes
in accordance with your capacity
as the reward for the winner
of this Chuiwan competition.
How could she offer a wooden hairpin?
It's embarrassing.
Fourth Young Lady is right.
This hairpin is given
by Young Master Qin.
Miss, you should keep it.
So this is the hairpin
that Qin Xuan mentioned just now.
It's just a cheap thing.
How is it a cheap thing?
A treasure box is not
as worthy as the ebony.
This hairpin
is made of Golden Silk Nan Ebony,
it's rare.
Only you will treat it
as an ordinary wood
as you grew up in the landfill.
Qiu Yan,
since this hairpin is a valuable item,
why don't you give it out as a prize?
It's Young Master Qin's gift
for Young Lady.
You've donated it,
there's no turning back.
Are you going to take it back?
A nobleman wouldn't take
what others are fond of.
Why would you two force her?
Greeting to Lord Liang.
It's just a joke between us sisters.
Moreover,
as I ask Qiu Yan
to donate her favorite item,
it's for the sake of our Qiu family.
Yes.
Indeed,
I don't have
other valuable items to donate.
I'll help Miss Qiu Yan
to donate the prize.
Miss Qiu, you should cherish the gift
from others
even if you don't like it.
Miss, you were trying
to use the wooden hairpin
to test Young Master Qin's feelings.
So that he could see First Young Lady's
and Fourth Young Lady's true colors.
But who knows
Lord Liang would meddle in it.
Liang Yi is ill-intentioned
and he hates me.
He must've done this
for some purpose.
Sir, as you helped the she-devil
and gave the ring out,
those unwitting people
would think that you have
your eyes on her.
This woman is cunning.
I must keep an eye on her.
Instead of waiting
for her to make a move
to start a relationship with Qin Xuan,
let's just pretend to be nice to her.
As Qin Xuan sees it,
he certainly won't compete with me.
This could make him
give up on his thought.
This is the preliminary round.
Participants, ready.
Participants, take your positions.
The match begins now.
Madam.
She's good.
I didn't expect that.
It's all right, leave it to me.
Qiu Mei!
Qiu Mei, are you all right?
Qiu Ying,
you can't hit Qiu Mei's face on purpose
even if you're jealous of her skills.
You've gone too far. Let me take a look.
Qiu Mei's face is swollen.
Someone help Qiu Mei
and take her to rest.
And ask Seond Madam
to send a physician over.
How could I face people like this?
Yes.
Easy.
Qiu Mei, have a good rest.
Qiu Mei,
Qiu Mei, I didn't do it on purpose.
Sure.
You were trying to hit me, weren't you?
Fortunately, I guarded against you
and stood behind Qiu Mei.
I see.
You framed me.
Don't blame me, you're bad at it.
Qiu Yan!
Do it in accordance
with the competition system.
- Qiu Yan, are you all right?
- Qiu Yan!
Qiu Yan.
Qiu Ying, what have you done?
I didn't do it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
here's a message from Madam.
As Qiu Ying, Fourth Young Lady
of Qiu Family, loses her manners
at the game,
based on the system,
she's disqualified from the game.
Host, Qin Xuan, she framed me.
Qiu Ying, the rod is in your hand.
Why would you hit Qiu Mei and me
if you didn't have evil intentions
towards us?
Miss.
Just wait and see.
What a good series of taunts.
She uses every means
to get rid
of all the eyesores to her.
Sir,
why don't I just call Mr. Qin back?
You're a cabbage...
Head?
Qiu Yan,
are you all right?
I'm fine.
In the next match,
please show me what you got.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be fair.
This won't do.
You're a lady.
Since this is a match,
all people are equal at the game.
Please show respect to your opponents.
I'll take you up on that.
Miss Qiu Yan,
I saw you had quite a fall.
Don't walk too fast.
Lord Liang, thanks for your concern.
I'm fine.
You're a delicate lady.
You can't get used to being hit,
unlike men.
You'll regret it all your life
if you hurt your body.
Let me carry you down.
Qiu Yan...
Liang Yi.
The more you move,
the more suspicious you look.
Liang Yi, what are you trying to do?
What do you think?
I can't bear to see you having contact
with the other man on the field,
can't I do that?
Since you knew that it was a dive,
why didn't you expose me?
Why would I expose you?
I don't want you to get mad at me.
Qiu Yan, how's your leg?
It's fine.
As usual, I'll let you have
one handicap point.
It's unnecessary.
I want to compete fairly with you.
Do you mean Chuiwan
or Qiu Yan?
It's the rematch,
participants, get ready.
Take your positions.
The match begins now.
Qin Xuan, you can do this.
Qin Xuan,
do you really fall for that girl?
Yes.
I'm telling you this for your own good.
Stay away from her.
Liang, I might listen to you
if it's about the other matters.
Anything else
except this.
Go on.
Nice shot, Qin Xuan.
Good job, Qin Xuan!
Great!
Qin Xuan, young master
of Duke Ying Residence, wins.
Young Master Qin, congratulations
on winning the match.
These prizes are all yours.
Young Master Liang, congratulations.
Keep it up.
Liang,
I didn't beat you
for these
useless gold and jade items.
You can have it all.
As I can beat you in Chuiwan,
I can also win Qiu Yan over.
You...
Ladies,
Young Master Qin won the match.
He asked my master
to distribute today's prizes
to all the participants.
Young Master Qin said
sharing is caring.
These gold and jade items are useless
to him.
He'd rather use it
to make everyone happy.
Come on.
Let me see it.
Let me see this.
Look, this is nice.
I like this.
Let me see yours.
Miss Qiu Yan,
why don't you pick a favorite item?
This is a token
of Young Master's Qin regard.
Song Jin.
As Lord Liang helped me preserve
the Ebony hairpin,
I should give this back to you.
I don't want to owe anyone
any favors like you.
Isn't that Qin Xuan?
Qin Xuan.
Qin...
I thought you forgot about us
after winning the competition.
How could it be?
Qin Xuan is not that kind of person.
This item you give me looks very nice.
Thank you, Qin Xuan.
This looks very nice, yes.
I'm serious.
Yes, this is particularly good.
It's suitable for me.
Is that so?
You did great on today's match.
Yes.
Young Master Qin grew up
in an environment that's full of women.
He is nice to everyone.
I won't approach him
like the other ladies do.
So that he could remember me.
Later, you go forward and make an excuse
to draw Qin Xuan here.
Remember to avoid Liang Yi.
The others can play Chuiwan well
except me, why am I so stupid?
You're too nervous.
That's why you can't play it well.
Let me help you.
Are you afraid of me?
You were graceful
when I last saw you.
But you're jumpy today.
Why is that?
That guy is the inspector
from Firewood Office,
Liang Yi, Marquis Weiyuan.
He's mad for power.
He's very hateful.
It's nothing.
I understand.
There's a discipline in Firewood Office.
Seeing is not believing.
What you hear may be false.
Let me teach you.
Okay.
As soon as I'm not around,
Qin Xuan
is going to be distracted
by that cunning vixen again.
Song Jin.
Come here.
Teach Miss Qiu Min Chuiwan for me.
Miss Qiu Min and I be alone together?
I don't think it's appropriate.
Look.
Qiu Yan, I've been looking
for you just now.
But I couldn't find you.
Fortunately, I met Qingdai.
Can you sit by and watch your buddy
go down in flames?
I can't bear to see it, just go.
Liang, Liang,
I need you to help me out.
What has Qin Xuan got that I haven't?
Meng, I have something on.
Everything happens for a reason.
On the ancestry, we're the descendants
of the important ministers.
We're evenly matched in education.
Besides, I'm good at playing Chuiwan.
Why do the ladies only like him?
This is poria cake.
It can moisturize the skin
and tone the stomach.
I don't want it.
Why?
I specially made this for you.
If you treat everyone equally nice,
I'd rather not to accept it.
Maybe it's because of my appearance.
As I'm handsome,
the ladies can only dream
of winning me over.
- Right?
- Song Jin.
Help me counsel Young Master Meng.
Come.
Liang, Liang!
Young Master Meng.
Min'er.
Qiu Yan.
Where did you go just now?
Lord Liang from Firewood Office
taught me Chuiwan just now.
Liang Yi?
When did you get acquaintance with him?
I never got acquaintance with him.
Just that he was patient enough
to teach me Chuiwan as he saw
I was terrible with it.
Besides, I've met him once before
at Duke Ying Residence.
Miss, have some water.
Okay, thank you.
Last round.
Ladies, please put an earring on it
as a keepsake.
Gentlemen,
please put a marked folding fan on it
as a keepsake.
Madam will pair you up.
Men and women will be paired up.
The final winners
will get the reward from Noble Consort.
I think you're coming after me today.
You're right.
I'm coming after you today.
Qiu Yan is very cunning,
you can't get involved with her.
I think you've stayed in Firewood Office
for too long.
You think everyone is a criminal.
Her engagement
with He family is broken off.
She is distressed
as she thinks her future is ruined
so she wants to use some tricks
to seduce a stately house.
She has her eyes
on the lineage of yours,
Duke Ying Residence.
Liang Yi,
I think you have a deep bias
against Miss Qiu Yan.
Let's make a bet
on the last round.
If I win,
I hope that Liang will stop
meddling in the affair
between Qiu Yan and me.
Why are you so stubborn?
You just won't believe me.
Which earring belongs to Miss Qiu Min?
Madam, this is the one.
♪A sliver of moonlight
passes through the roof♪
♪Your sweet smile had warmed my heart♪
♪If the hazy night is a garment♪
♪Your appearance will be the pigment♪
♪Looking at your direction♪
♪All the scenes appear in my mind♪
♪As I draw your eyebrows♪
♪I'm willing to wait for you
for an entire lifetime♪
♪A sliver of moonlight
passes through the roof♪
♪Your sweet smile had warmed my heart♪
♪If the hazy night is a garment♪
♪Your appearance will be the pigment♪
♪As people part from one another♪
♪I hope the story goes your way♪
♪I was reminded of your vow♪
♪I'm willing to wait for you
for an entire lifetime♪