=The Autumn Ballad=
♪Winter clouds fill up the sky
as the geese leave behind a trail of sorrow♪
♪I lean in front of the window,
gazing from afar♪
♪I heard your singing♪
♪By the west riverbank♪
♪As our eyes meet each other,
our longing is still there♪
♪Mountains and seas apart,
waiting for the full moon♪
♪All for our sweet encounter♪
♪Smiling with you
as I stare at the bead curtains♪
♪I will not disappoint
our mutual affection in this lifetime♪
♪We fly wing to wing
beside the sea of mountains♪
♪Even if all creations go silent♪
♪I will not disappoint
our mutual affection in this lifetime♪
♪We fly wing to wing
beside the sea of mountains♪
♪Even if all creations go silent♪
=The Autumn Ballad=
=Episode 14=
Fourth Uncle!
What was the treatment
you mentioned earlier?
It's just a slip of the tongue.
Fourth Uncle.
Her life is important.
Please, I beg of you.
Get up.
Look at you...
Fine.
If you want to know,
I'll tell you.
Your mother is afflicted
with an infectious disease.
Do you know where you can get
infected easily?
Brothel and southern wharf.
I have a mist...
A friend.
She was infected two years ago.
Thanks to a hand-down regimen
from a traveling physician,
she survived.
I'm not talking out of my hat.
When the Renshen River Disease ran amok,
he saved half a boat of people.
Fourth Uncle, where is he now?
He is
a traveling physician.
God knows where he is now.
However,
I still have his prescription with me.
Master, we visited all apothecaries.
All shopkeepers
said the tokay gecko and
the euphorbia decaryi
on the prescriptions
must be something exotic.
They have never seen them.
They can't find them on the market.
It doesn't mean it's impossible.
I'll go find them myself.
Where's Qiu Yan?
Miss left to purchase medicine for you.
She's not home.
Thank you so much for these few days.
I'm feeling okay now.
You can rest now.
No need to stay with me.
If Song Jin has any news,
he'll come back immediately.
Patience.
Sir!
Anything?
I have news.
Tokay gecko and euphorbia decaryi
are rare
but with the right price,
you can find them on the black market.
However, the apothecary that supplies
for the black market
was seized last month.
By whom?
By
Main Administrative Office.
(Main Administrative Office)
Sir, please have mercy
and save my mother's life.
If you can do us this favor, Mr. Yuan,
the Firewood Office
will definitely repay it.
Unfortunately, Lord Liang,
this apothecary
is no ordinary apothecary.
They didn't just smuggle medicine.
Everything that has been seized
has to be recorded
and confiscated.
If one thing goes missing,
troubles will arise.
If you can save my mother, sir,
I am willing to shoulder any punishment.
Corporal or other punishment,
anything you want, sir.
Miss Qiu Yan.
We have rules.
Your filial piety is admirable
but the Main Administrative Office
has its own rules.
I'm sure
Lord Liang knows it very well.
Don't do that.
We're colleagues.
I can't accept this genuflection
from you, Lord Liang.
I understand your constraint, Mr. Yuan.
However, this is about someone's life.
Exception should be made.
Please accept my kowtow.
I hope you can make this exception.
Real men do not bow down.
You even knelt on one knee.
I can only say yes now.
However,
there are many lips in the office.
It's hard to seal all of them.
That said, I do have a solution.
Lord Liang, we can both put up a show.
Just let me whip you.
I'll summon all my underlings
and say you are willing
to serve this punishment
in exchange for the medicine.
No one can fault you for anything.
Yuan Lang, you made a fool of yourself
when you last
came to the Firewood Office.
And now, you're taking revenge.
I am the one asking for the medicine.
Mr. Yuan, if you want to take revenge,
take it out on me.
Lord Liang, you're not willing to do it?
Too bad.
Wait.
No!
Saving your mother is important.
Jiang Yun, bring everyone here.
Yes, sir.
Song Jin, send Miss Qiu out.
- Liang Yi.
- Miss Qiu.
Liang Yi.
I'll be fine.
How should we do this...
Lord Liang confessed to a crime.
We're all witnesses here.
I don't dare
to whip you.
Song Jin,
you should do it.
Song Jin.
Sir.
Listen to him.
Sir, just kill me.
Whip me.
Whip me!
Harder.
You should consult a physician.
(Main Administrative Office)
Just some scratches.
I'm used to it.
Come, Song Jin.
Take the medicine.
Your mother needs it.
Go now.
I owe you this one.
I'll repay you.
Okay. Go.
Father, I found the medicine.
Mother can be treated now. Father!
(Hall of Sanguinity)
Second Young Lady.
Madam is not here anymore.
She's inside.
I'll look for her.
Miss.
Second Young Lady.
Madam is not here anymore.
Let go of me.
She was infected. They had taken
her body out of the city already.
She really isn't here anymore.
Miss!
(That day,)
(when your biological mother
gave you to me)
(to save your brother,)
I know
you must have been through hell.
(Collection of Odd Occurrences)
(But I don't want you to be a bitter kid.)
(Your life doesn't come by easily.)
(Don't shut yourself in)
(because of fear,)
(because of trust issues.)
(You'll only suffer more.)
(From now on,)
(live well.)
(I'm worried about you.)
From now on,
I'll leave the second chamber to you.
Physician Li,
did my mother
pass away peacefully?
Second Madam left the world
in her dream.
It was painless.
Min'er.
Qiu Yan, did you find the medicine?
It's okay if you can't.
I'm begging our ancestors
to grant mother a speedy recovery.
I just have to burn one short
and two long incenses,
they will then grant my wish.
I also have to finish copying
this last chapter.
Mother has left.
No.
Our ancestors will not lie to us.
Mother has left us.
We even cremated her coffin.
No way.
Our ancestors promised me.
Look.
Mother will come back.
What ancestors?
What promise?
All lies!
If they actually see it,
if they have that
little bit of conscience,
they won't let mother
leave this world alone.
It's all fake.
- Stop!
- It's all fake!
Qiu Yan,
why tell me mother has left?
I'm sure she's with us.
I'm sure.
Qiu Yan, can I have a hug?
Hug me like mother does.
This can't be it.
Mother is here.
Mother definitely is here.
Mother is gone.
Wake up now.
From now on,
no one will pamper you anymore.
If you're still this vulnerable
and delusional,
you will spend the rest
of your days weeping.
Qiu Min.
Qiu Min! Someone! Help!
Qiu Min!
Help!
Qiu Min, don't you scare me.
Stop.
Help!
Qiu Min.
Qiu Min, are you okay?
Wake up.
Help!
Qiu Min, are you okay?
You're scaring me. Help!
Mother...
You're dismissed for now.
Yes, sir.
You did your best.
She won't blame you.
This spot is for her.
For me too.
Mother,
I shouldn't have said those things.
I know you're in grief.
We all are.
Blood. So much blood.
Min'er.
So much blood.
What? Did you have a nightmare?
So much blood. Mother must be in pain.
I asked physician Li.
- So much blood.
- Mother passed away in her sleep.
It was painless.
No,
I saw mother
vomiting blood.
What?
That day, I missed her so much
so I snuck into her yard.
Hurry up and wash it.
Then go back inside.
Don't let anyone see this.
Okay.
I was horrified
so I went to the ancestral hall
and prayed for mother's health.
You mean you saw
physician Li and the nurse
enter mother's room
without any protective garment?
(Lunar Steps)
Second Young Lady,
no one was infected in the temple.
There are two villages by the foot
of the mountain.
34 households in total.
I visited all of them.
None of them
contacted the infectious disease.
All right. You're dismissed.
Noted.
If my mother had an infectious disease,
why did no one from Mount Taiying
or from our family
contact it too?
Don't you think something's off, father?
Physician Li discovered
the infection early
and isolated her from us.
That's how
we could escape from the same fate.
Physician Li wouldn't even let anyone
come close to my mother's yard.
But Min'er saw
that he and the nurse went in
to treat my mother
without any protective garment.
If the infectious disease
is that lethal,
why is he as healthy as a horse now?
There's no way this infectious disease
can only infect my mother.
Perhaps he misdiagnosed,
prescribed the wrong medicine,
and that's why my mother
could never recover.
Yan'er.
I know you're a good daughter.
You're saddened by your mother's death.
I am too.
But we
can't accuse someone of wrongdoing
just because we lost someone dear to us.
I am not.
But my mother left this world
out of a sudden.
Father, shouldn't we get to the bottom of it?
Enough.
Your mother was afflicted
with an infectious disease
and died to it.
That's the truth.
It can't get any clearer than that.
Father, Min'er will not lie.
The physician lied that my mother
passed away peacefully.
There must be a reason.
Even if physician Li said that
to console me,
but there are no other cases from
Mount Taiying and here.
Where did my mother get infected?
And what was she infected with?
And what happened
before she passed away?
Enough!
Everyone is busy
organizing the funeral now.
As her daughter,
you did not perform a wake or pray.
All you think about
is conspiracy theories.
Do you have to
sow more chaos into this family
until you're satisfied?
Father.
If you won't believe me,
I'll investigate myself.
I will find out
how my mother passed away.
You...
Someone!
See Second Young Lady to her room.
Watch over her
until she apologizes.
Second Young Lady...
(Lunar Steps)
Back then,
you groveled to this
and coddled to that.
When the moment comes,
only I came to take care of you.
Come eat with me.
I'm not hungry.
Honestly,
why crossed your father?
Your father
has a lot on his plate already.
Yet, you bothered him with something
he doesn't wish to hear.
Come eat
and stop brooding.
You know,
anything can change within seconds.
At first, I thought
I could never be the legal wife.
And I might have to be
a concubine forever.
Things change so quickly.
Oh, we should coddle your father now.
One day, your father might make me
his legal wife because of your brother.
And then,
you'll be the legitimate daughter.
So you cried so much just now
and hugged Qiu Min,
saying you would love her
and protect her.
All that was for show?
How can you say that?
Among the second chamber,
Old Madam loves Min the most.
If I don't
bring her to my side now,
someone else will.
I'm not dumb.
Go away!
You...
What are you doing?
I'm your mother!
No, you're not.
Fine.
Fine!
You want to be the pious daughter.
Go ahead.
The day when your father
makes me his legal wife,
I'm sure you'll come to me
and call me mother.
Careful.
Condolences, Uncle Qiu.
Condolences, Official Qiu.
Thank you.
Both of you
brought me so many medicines
to fight against infections.
Allow me to thank you
on behalf of the Qiu family.
It's all Lord Liang's doing.
He searched all apothecaries in the Capital
and amassed so many medicines.
You're most welcome, Official Qiu.
Lord Liang.
My wife passed away suddenly
and it only delayed the marriage.
I was supposed to meet you
to discuss it.
Uncle Qiu.
The marriage can wait.
The funeral for your late wife
is more important.
Thank you.
Uncle Qiu.
Where are Qiu Yan and Qiu Min?
They are both deeply affected
by their mother's death.
Min'er is now bedridden
and Yan'er
remains too stubborn
to admit
that her mother has passed away
because of the illness.
Remember your favorite poem,
Far-off Journey?
You always say
you're envious of how the men
in the poem
can travel around.
Even though your wish
won't come true now,
but making a miniature world
in this square ceramic plate
should help to realize your dream
in a way.
I shall then ride this noble steed,
travel with my mother,
and visit all of Jiangnan
and everything beyond.
You're not holding a noble steed.
You're holding the mythical giant,
Kuafu.
Yan'er.
As women,
we might be confined to the house
for the rest of our life.
But if you have an adventurous spirit,
the world
will exist in your heart.
Done.
It looks beautiful.
(Lunar Steps)
Miss, Young Master Qin
wishes to visit you.
Tell him to go back.
I'm too tired.
Qiu Yan.
My wet nurse told me
that when someone passed away,
his or her soul would linger around
the ones they loved.
If Aunt Qiu sees you
suffering like this,
she'll be worried about you.
(Solemnity)
Lord Liang is here.
I'll summon Third Young Lady then.
No need.
The loss of a dear one
cannot be alleviated with
words of consolation.
Please take good care of Miss Qiu Min.
May she recover soon.
As for the void she feels inside,
only time
can heal that.
Give this to her.
See you.
I'm not hungry.
Just one bite.
You have to move on.
I can't.
My hunch is never wrong.
My mother passed away
under peculiar circumstances.
If I can't find out the truth,
I can't move on.
Qiu Yan, sorrow has blinded you.
Infectious disease is dangerous.
If the royal family contacts it,
they still stand a slim chance
of surviving.
You won't believe me?
It's not that I don't.
But the coffin
has been turned into ashes.
The devil is in the details.
I'm sure I can find something.
I'll investigate
whatever is suspicious.
Thanks, sir.
Have a safe trip, sir.
See you.
Go.
Miss Qiu Yan, it must be stuffy inside.
Where's Lord Liang?
Over there.
Lord Liang, let's go.
Perhaps we can intercept the physician.
Song Jin, go to the Firewood Office
and send people to block all exits
from the city.
Okay.
Follow me, all of you.
(Jingqi Apothecary)
(Outbound for an undetermined
amount of time)
He took his saving with him too.
I don't think he's coming back at all.
Something's up then.
It's still warm. He's not far away.
(Staging post)
This is the only staging post outside
of the city within a hundred li.
The watcher by the city gate
reported that Li Zhengyuan
and his daughter left on foot.
Without a horse carriage,
the furthest he can reach is here.
Sir, come in, please.
Firewood Office.
Did a middle-aged traveling physician
and a young woman come here?
Not at all.
Stop right there.
You mother
couldn't stop coughing
but her pulse was normal
and vigorous.
My benefactor asked me
to say that she had
an infectious disease.
Her pulse was normal?
What's the cause of my mother's death?
She...
She vomited blood before she died.
After she passed away, red spots
appeared on her skin.
It looked...
It looked like red safflower poison.
You're saying
someone poisoned my mother?
I don't know about anything else.
My benefactor
just told me to leave now
so that I wouldn't be involved.
I did this to repay the favor I owed.
Who is
this benefactor of yours?
You stayed in my house
for more than a decade.
(Memorial Tablet Beloved Mother
in the Qiu Family, Han Ruogu)
I treated you like my own daughter
and felt sorry for you all this time.
I had
to do what I did.
Don't blame me.
Second Young Lady,
let me inform her first.
Move aside.
Second Young Lady.
Why?
Why did you do that to my mother?
My mother treated you with respect.
What did she do that you had
to burn her corpse too?
Nonsense!
Nonsense?
My dear grandmother
bribed a physician
to poison my mother.
Is there anything else
crazier than this?
Old Madam.
You did this, didn't you?
Utter gibberish.
Old Madam Qiu,
we're talking about one life here.
Please explain yourself.
Ridiculous.
A daughter who lost her mother
started spouting nonsense.
No explanation is needed.
Physician Li Zhengyuan
is now imprisoned
in the Firewood Office.
If you won't admit it,
I will just interrogate him
and invite you to the Firewood Office
some other day.
Lord Liang.
This is my family business.
I shouldn't burden you with it,
Lord Liang.
Yan'er, come here.
Father, I found Li Zhengyuan.
My mother didn't have any
infectious disease.
She was poisoned by red safflower.
Old Madam asked him
to rule it as an infectious disease.
All right.
Old Madam poisoned my mother.
Yan'er, go back to your room.
My mother continued your bloodline.
She was killed
and you don't want to find her killer?
Physician Li said
your mother was poisoned.
Where is his proof?
Without proof,
it's just an accusation.
Old Madam rushed to cremate my mother
to erase the evidence of her crime.
Enough.
Bring her away.
Uncle Qiu.
Qiu Yan was right to question it.
That physician was behaving oddly.
Lord Liang.
We're both government officials.
Just two days ago, you called me
father-in-law.
And now, you accused
my mother of a crime.
Is this
how you're supposed to treat your future
father-in-law,
Lord Liang?
If the Second Madam of Qiu family
was poisoned,
then it's a criminal case.
The Qiu family cannot hide it forever.
Lord Liang, sounding the drum
to have your case heard, that's a case.
Going to the court to complain about
injustice, that's also a case.
My wife died of an illness
and my family is struck with sorrow.
That's just a family business.
Please don't meddle in this, Lord Liang.
Your Lordship,
I, Qiu Yan, a commoner,
would like to see the death
of my mother, Han, be investigated.
Qiu Yan.
Get up now.
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
I can't compromise, I can't be soft.
I can't learn everything
my mother taught me.
You...
If fighting
is what it takes
to make an appeal for my mother,
then I'm prepared to die for it.
You...
Lord Liang.
The Lin of the Qiu family
poisoned my mother, Han.
May justice be served!
Qiu Yan, you're...
The insolence!
Official Qiu.
If Old Madam Qiu is innocent
and Madam Han truly died
from an infectious disease,
she has nothing to fear.
Yan'er.
Your mother passed away.
Do you think
you're the only one suffering?
She was my wife for many years.
My heart
is bleeding right now too.
And now,
you accuse
my mother of killing my wife.
Yan'er,
do you know you're just
adding insult to injury?
Father,
you can be the pious son
and take your mother's side.
But I will also be the pious daughter
and find out the truth
of my mother's death.
I just want the truth.
And the truth is
your mother died
of an infectious disease.
Tell yourself that lie then.
Yan'er.
Are you my daughter or not?
If being your daughter means
I have to accept
my mother died mysteriously,
then no.
You...
Uncle Qiu, calm down, please.
♪A sliver of moonlight
passes through the roof♪
♪Your sweet smile had warmed my heart♪
♪If the hazy night is a garment♪
♪Your appearance will be the pigment♪
♪Looking at your direction♪
♪All the scenes appear in my mind♪
♪As I draw your eyebrows♪
♪I'm willing to wait for you
for an entire lifetime♪
♪A sliver of moonlight
passes through the roof♪
♪Your sweet smile had warmed my heart♪
♪If the hazy night is a garment♪
♪Your appearance will be the pigment♪
♪As people part from one another♪
♪I hope the story goes your way♪
♪I was reminded of your vow♪
♪I'm willing to wait for you
for an entire lifetime♪