[Won Do Hyun]
♫ Like the lyrics of a typical love song, ♫
[Kim Jun Hyung]
♫ I don't want to live like that. You're the only one ♫
[Bae Si Jun]
♫ Like the lilac scent, you touched my heart ♫
[Han Da Sol]
♫ You're beautiful, smiling at me ♫
[Jung Ho Gyun]
♫ I'm singing the story of you and me ♫
[All the Liquors]
[Barbecue Chicken Hoolala, 1997]
Oh, that hurts!
Having fried chicken and beer by yourself...
Couldn't you catch me?
Why do I have to?
Never mind.
By the way, why did you come here?
I wanted to eat fried chicken.
But why did you sit here?
- Shall I go?
- No, no.
Have a seat.
I was also bored.
Please, eat some.
Now that I think about it, did you see me coming in here?
It's not important.
Aren't I a really good foodie?
I live to eat either that is food or liquor.
I just think it's good to be happy.
Eating delicious food,
chatting and laughing while drunk together...
That's when I feel all the hardships wash away.
I think that's happiness.
Let's sign the contract.
Sorry?
♫ Like the lyrics of a typical love song, ♫
♫ I don't want to live like that. You're the only one ♫
♫ Like the lilac scent, you touched my heart ♫
♫ You're beautiful, smiling at me ♫
♫ I'm singing the story of you and me ♫
[CONFERENCE]
Hello, I'm Deputy Kim Yeon Ah.
Hello, I'm Park Ki Hoon.
I heard a lot about you. Thank you for deciding to work with us.
I look forward to working with you.
What's this? He's insanely handsome.
He is indeed good-looking.
Please, have a seat.
Okay.
- Why don't you show that to him?
- Yes.
Here's the contract.
And this is the kitchen area.
The facility is pretty good.
Yes, we sometimes cook food for us here, too.
It might be a bit unfamiliar since it's different from your kitchen.
But you won't have much trouble using it.
And this is the bowl of cleaned clams that you asked for.
Thank you so much.
Then, I'll get going.
Where are you going?
Excuse me? I should get back to work.
Then am I making the menu on my own here?
Yes.
Oh, excuse me.
Yes, Deputy Kim.
I need Mr. Han Ji Yoo.
Sorry?
What do you mean by that?
It's not easy to develop a menu alone.
I would like to work together to develop the menu with Han Ji Yoo, who's in charge of this project.
If that's the case, I'll get you someone who's more professional on that matter.
I don't think Han Ji Yoo is a proper person to develop a menu.
He's the most appropriate person.
From what I've seen, he has a deeper knowledge of food. And...
Right. Ji Yoo knows a lot about delicious food.
Really?
If so...
Deputy Kim, how's Ji Yoo's schedule right now?
I think it'll be okay for him to support developing a menu.
Is that so?
- Then, let's do it.
- Thank you.
Please take good care of our Han Ji Yoo.
Team Leader, I'm not a child!
It may not be enough, but I'll use it well.
I'm telling you ahead, but he won't be enough.
"Use it?"
Am I a tool?
No, I didn't mean it that way.
It's fine. Let's get to work.
I thought of a menu using the clams.
Shall we start from there?
Okay.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm okay, but your clothes!
I'm sorry. I'm always so clumsy.
As long as you didn't get hurt, it's okay.
Clothes can just dry.
But I don't think I'm the only one who got wet.
Yes, you're right...
It's like a scene from a TV drama, isn't it?
Let's clean up now.
Yes.
♫ I think I'm still in a dream ♫
♫ After I met you ♫
♫ I pull my cheeks hard sometimes ♫
♫ A careless smile ♫
♫ Sometimes it leaks out ♫
♫ Oh oh yeah (You will be the same) ♫
♫ Even the stars embroidered in the night sky ♫
♫ look at us ♫
♫ Like a dream ♫
♫ Even meaningless things makes me excited ♫
♫ So precious ♫
♫ At the end of my day in your arms ♫
♫ I want to fall asleep oh oh ♫
♫ With you oh oh ♫
♫ When you're tired ♫
♫ You can lean on it and rest ♫
♫ I will hug you tight ♫
♫ The most beautiful in the world, your wake-up call ♫
♫ I want to hear more, pretend not to know ♫
♫ I'm ready, but I can't take my feet out of regret ♫
♫ oh oh yeah (You will be the same) ♫
♫ The time with you filled with the scent of flowers ♫
♫ My heart is pounding, oh my babe ♫
♫ Is it like a dream? ♫
♫ Even waking up makes me excited ♫
♫ So perfect for me ♫
♫ I have a pleasant imagination ♫
By the way...
Don't you think knowing the liquor's taste will help develop the menu?
No, I'm not saying you should drink it now.
You're right.
I'll drink it when I'm ready.
Okay.
Let's take our time.
Let's do it tonight.
Chef!
You're here.
What? This place is amazing!
This is the best spot to have a night snack!
Everything's ready here.
Oh, yes.
Can I sit next to you?
Yes.
Is it okay?
It's been such a long time.
Just have a taste.
You have to know the taste of this liquor to develop the menu.
Right.
Is it your first time...?
No, it's not my first time.
How is it?
It's good.
That's a relief.
Chef? How can you pass out after one shot?
Chef!
Chef?
You shouldn't fall asleep here. Chef!
What should I do with him?
Now that I think about it, did you see me coming in here?
It's not important.
Do you want to have some ramen?
Ramen?
♫ Maybe I'm already in your little univers ♫
♫ Falling down ♫
♫ From the time we first met, you know that ♫
Here. Try it.
♫ Like this, holding your hand ♫
♫ Dive in love, dive in love, dive in love ♫
♫ Will never ever say goodbye ♫
♫ Will never ever change my mind ♫
It's delicious.
♫ Of all the people in the world ♫
♫ I'm am nothing, but only you ♫
♫ Will never ever be alone ♫
♫ Will never even leave you ♫
Can I call you "Hyung?"
♫ I'll always be in your world ♫
♫ Always want to tell you love ♫
Do you want to have some ramen at my place?
No, I don't need it.
♫ Maybe I'm already deep in your eyes ♫
Your face got blushed.
How is Ki Hoon these days?
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
They said they need you to cook on a stage.
♫ Holding you in my arms like this ♫
♫ Dive in love, dive in love, dive in love ♫
♫ Will never ever say goodbye ♫
♫ Will never ever change my mind ♫
♫ Of all the people in the world ♫
[All the Liquors]
♫ I'm am nothing, but only you ♫