[Won Do Hyun]
♫ Like the lyrics of a typical love song, ♫
[Kim Jun Hyung]
♫ I don't want to live like that. You're the only one ♫
[Bae Si Jun]
♫ Like the lilac scent, you touched my heart ♫
[Han Da Sol]
♫ You're beautiful, smiling at me ♫
[Jung Ho Gyun]
♫ I'm singing the story of you and me ♫
[All the Liquors]
What is it?
It's nothing.
You know, last night...
Last night?
You drank the liquor.
Yes.
Why, I mean... How did it feel?
It felt nostalgic.
Okay.
It reminded me of the food my mother or grandmother made.
Traditional liquor and local food...
Hometown food.
Then...
Can I see the report that analyzed the foods that got the most responses among those we tested?
Did you think of something?
I think something's coming up.
Hello?
Are you still in bed?
Yes.
Hurry up and get ready. We don't have much time.
Sorry?
Today's a day off.
There's a place we need to go together.
Where?
♫ I can feel your eyes looking at me, little by little ♫
♫ Maybe I'm already in your little universe ♫
♫ Falling down ♫
♫ From the time we first met, you know that ♫
♫ We already know ♫
♫ Like this, holding your hand ♫
♫ Dive in love, dive in love, dive in love ♫
Shall we eat first?
Yes, sounds great!
It's early, but a lot of customers are here already.
I heard this place is a local favorite in Gunsan.
Where many tourists go must be tasty, but it won't have the real local flavor.
So this is a home-cooked-meal-style restaurant?
Yes. I'll say it's a home-cooked-style restaurant with seasonal food.
I'm so excited about the seasonal food, even just hearing the words.
It looks delicious.
Let me get you chopsticks.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's done. Please, dig in.
Okay. Thank you for the food.
Auntie, one bottle of soju, please!
And we only need one glass.
Thank you.
Don't drink too much.
Can I have another glass?
Shall we sit here for a bit?
Okay.
By the way, do you also have social media?
No.
Oh, really?
I just asked because it was the first time seeing you taking photos.
I took food photos to study and to remember easily.
Chef, you're awesome!
How was the food today?
The food was all delicious.
I could tell without hearing that.
How do you know that?
It's because you asked for soju immediately after the first bite.
That's because you ordered it, so I just had to drink it.
That's what I'm saying.
If I didn't stop you, you would've still been drinking.
No, I wouldn't.
Do you like drinks that much?
No!
It's not like that.
Hello, I called you earlier.
- Right, you were looking for this.
- Yes, that's right.
If you look over here, the small one is 5,000 won, and the big box is 45,000.
Can you show it to me over there?
Oh? Stir-fried squid.
Would you like this one?
Yes, I'll take that one.
Which size do you want?
I'll take one box of this.
Okay.
It's 45,000 won.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you. Bye.
Isn't it all the same?
You don't know anything yet.
What? No!
Let's go!
[Seafood Market]
[Live fish, Dried fish, Line fish: Seafood Market]
I got some inspiration by visiting the marketplace.
I know!
Let's go!
Why didn't you wake me up?
I was organizing my thoughts.
Why?
Are you still uncomfortable with our project?
No.
Now I can finally forget about everything and start anew.
I'm going to change from now on.
Sounds good.
This place is so nice.
It feels so refreshing. Isn't it great?
I wish the time would stop now.
Why do you want the time to stop? Our time is waiting for us in the future.
What did you say?
Nothing. Let's go now.
Go inside safely.
I will. Thank you for the ride.
Thank you for your hard work today.
I didn't do anything! You did everything.
Also, it was fun today.
For me, too.
I'll let you go inside now.
Okay.
Drive safely.
I will.
Chef, why are you still here?
I'll get going now.
Chef.
Do you want to have some ramen at my place?
(Is also a Korean pickup line, like "Netflix and chill")
No, I'm good!
I told you not to drink too much.
I didn't get that drunk.
It's because we drank early during the day...
So I got a bit tipsy faster.
I don't think that's the case.
I'm really not drunk! I'm really not.
♫ So every night, I fall asleep holding my head ♫
Okay.
♫ I think I heard it from somewhere ♫
I'm really not drunk.
♫ The obvious melody ♫
♫ I erase everything, yeah ♫
♫ A one-way ticket to you ♫
♫ I don't miss it. Always ♫
♫ I still remember, even if my eyes are closed ♫
[All the Liquors]
♫ Like the lyrics of a typical love song, ♫