♫  With no specter to cut off the waves  ♫
♫  With no halo bestowed by heaven  ♫
♫  I should admit I was born ordinary  ♫
♫  But I'm not resigned to the silence on stage  ♫
♫  Break it down, I'm taking over now  ♫
♫  Tough it out, that's what I'm all about  ♫
♫  We are destined to break through a mental wall  ♫
♫  To unlock a ray of light  ♫
♫  We know there will be infinite waves  ♫
♫  Getting in my way  ♫
♫  They will build up into roads that enable me to climb high and see far  ♫
♫  To test me, inspire me, make me, and give me courage  ♫
♫  I'm ultimately the master  ♫
♫  Of my own destiny  ♫
[Psychologist]
[This TV series is produced with a special fund for guiding and supporting TV series in 2020 from the National Radio and Television Administration and is a key TV series project supported by the Hainan Free Trade Port.]
[Episode 33]
Mr. Qian.
Brother Qian.
You all know?
You went to Director Pan's office in such a hurry, so we knew something must have happened.
But I still have to tell one thing to you.
Brother Qian.
- We've heard of it by accident...
- It doesn't matter, Brother Qian
I'm confident about our program.
That's right. Who cares?
Maybe it's an incentive for us.
Right.
But I still have to tell you my thought.
This time I'm indeed selfish.
You've known from the news that He Dun is being attacked by those rumors.
I can't help her with others,
but at this critical moment, I can't let her be abandoned by our station.
But if you don't want to join, I can understand.
If I lose then, you won't suffer with me.
What are you talking about?
We're a team.
No one can give up in the face of difficulties. Got it?
He's right, Brother Qian.
Although you said you did this for Miss He,
we understand and we know if it were one of us,
you would definitely protect us.
It's them who have gone too far.
They transferred Miao and now want to replace Miss He with another psychologist.
Brother Qian, I got your back.
But our program is understaffed.
Shall we employ a few interns to share the workload?
In fact, I've found some candidates whose major matches our business.
Since our program rose to No. 1, your workload has doubled.
I know that.
[58.com Job Listing Candidates]
Look.
58.com?
Then I'll schedule on-site interviews for them.
We don't have so much time. Do the video interview.
All right.
In fact, I'm prepared for it.
Rumors are just like blisters.
The fastest way to heal blisters are to poke them.
Then cut them open to show them.
Yeah. Brother Qian, tell Miss He to keep her head up high.
We all got her back.
Thanks. I got your back.
- Fighting!
Are you still watching news?
I'm trying to find any new clue.
Do you have an appointment today?
No.
There is a man outside walking around.
Xiao Mo.
Xiao Mo, you look different from before.
I've taken off the fake glasses.
You passed here just now. Then why didn't you come in and have a seat?
To be frank, I've stood at the door for a while.
I'm afraid you don't want to see me because of what I did to you.
It doesn't matter. Let bygones be bygones.
I'm also glad to see you in good spirits.
Wait a moment.
Would you like a bottle of lemon tea to quench your thirst?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
What do you want from me today?
I saw the news about you on the Internet.
You've helped me so much.
I don't believe you're such a person.
Thanks.
In my heart, you're a conscientious counsellor.
Unfortunately, I misunderstood you before.
I'm really sorry.
In fact, I've been so curious about your misunderstanding of me.
I hurt you by accident.
Then I went to the doctor. He said I took the wrong medicine
so that I lost control of my emotions and hurt others.
Anyone who experienced this will feel afraid.
But I think there must be something that led to the visitor's change.
Miss Wen, do you think there is a third party or something
that interfered in the counselling?
Was the medicine prescribed by your doctor?
No, one of my friends gave it to me.
But I only know his name.
I'm afraid he has forgotten me.
Do you have a history of taking psychotropic drugs?
No.
If my memory serves me correctly, it was during our third counseling
that I started to take the medicine.
- I see.
- The police have contacted me for investigation.
I've explained it to them.
Miss He, don't worry.
I've given up the medicine,
and I've been using the method you taught me to detect myself.
That's good.
How's your life going? Is it good?
Yes.
I went to another company.
My work goes well now.
I was even promoted to group leader recently.
Really?
Miss He,
in fact,
after meeting the doctor, I should have come to apologize to you face to face.
But such a thing happened.
I'm so ashamed to face you.
Today, I want to say sorry to you in person.
I hope you can forgive me.
I accept your apology.
In fact, I didn't blame you long ago.
The fact that you can embrace your life
and live so happily is also a kind of support for my work.
I'm happy to see it, instead.
I have something to handle.
Then get back to your work. I'm leaving now.
All right.
Bye.
He Dun,
I saw today's news.
Are you all right?
Rest assured. She's fine, devoid of any impact.
I'm sorry, He Dun.
If it weren't for me...
If it weren't for Wang Zhuo,
if it weren't for your position as the host of the Night Talk to Your Heart,
you wouldn't have been thrust to the forefront.
Are you talking in tongue twisters?
There is no assumption.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
If I were in trouble, I wouldn't have come to you for that theme.
Right, Qian Kaiyi, enough already.
If you continue to be so sad, both of us need to comfort you.
No way.
If so, I'll be a troublemaker.
Let's get down to business.
I have something to discuss with you.
Guess who just came here.
Who was it?
- Xiao Mo.
- Xiao Mo?
Why did he come?
To apologize to me.
Isn't it already too late?
Isn't that so insincere?
There's a reason why he didn't come earlier.
But that doesn't matter.
What matters is that he said he attacked me because of the influence of medicine.
What? He attacked you?
That man attacked you?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'll explain it to you later.
Wait. Medicine?
Psychological counselors can't prescribe medicine for patients, can they?
It wasn't me.
You mean he got the medicine from another person?
Yes.
He said it was one of his friends.
But he isn't familiar with him.
What's the most important, he took the medicine right during my counseling with him.
So I guess someone interfered in my work.
Then does he have anything to do with Yao Kexin's matter?
I don't know.
But for now, all the news is against me.
So the person behind Yao Kexin might target more than Professor Ji.
Xiao Mo and Professor Ji have connections with you in your life.
Who else gets involved among your acquaintances?
You mean my senior is in a relationship with her visitor?
A veteran psychologist like her can't make such a mistake.
At the hearing, she admitted all the charges against her.
It's my fault.
I'm willing to bear all the consequences.
My senior, Li Yun.
She fell for one of her visitors.
In order to protect him, she didn't mention the thing between them.
In the end, her license was withdrawn.
Do you have a good relationship with her?
Yes.
And I have a lot of respect for her.
She's also one of my teacher's best students.
Some of them are close to you, and some to Professor Ji.
But the mastermind who targets you is perhaps one of your acquaintances, right?
Yes.
But I don't know who it is yet.
What's wrong with you, Professor?
- Where is your medicine?
What's up?
I thought of one person.
But I don't know whether to say it.
Who's it in your mind?
But I don't have any hard evidence.
Qian, we can't let go of any clues.
By the way, we can find the evidence together.
Ye Jiahui.
At Yao Kexin's hearing,
I saw him.
Jiahui. Jiahui!
Ye Jiahui.
Ye Jiahui, come out.
We need to talk to you.
Forget it. I don't think he's home. Let's go.
Let's talk to him when he returns.
Wait.
Where are you going?
I've got an idea.
Don't…
Welcome.
Qian Kaiyi, it's the first time I've thought you're so handsome since I knew you long ago.
He isn't here.
Wait.
The back of this cabinet is empty.
What did you hear, He?
The sound of the ventilation system.
Ventilation systems are installed at the back of enclosed spaces, especially in basements.
Then why didn't you hear it when you came here before?
Then, I didn't notice it.
It can be heard only in a quiet place.
It's indeed empty.
How shall we open the door?
Could there be a cog?
Wait.
What's up?
Dust.
Ye Jiahui is a clean freak.
There is no dust in the whole shelf.
Only a few areas are dotted with little dust.
It's very thin, but I can still feel it.
What if there is dust?
Static electricity.
A certain amount of dust will gather together in static electricity.
There is definitely a cog nearby.
It opened.
Let's go.
Could Ye Jiahui be down there?
Yeah.
He Dun.
Let's go.
Wait.
What's wrong again?
Turn on a torch.
To be honest, I'm a bit tempted to break up.
I'm with you.
Hurry up!
Why is it so dark here?
What is this?
Is it graffiti?
Watch the stairs!
Will he come back after a while?
He's outnumbered.
Why are you afraid?
Qian Kaiyi, why are you trembling?
Let me give you a sense of security.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just a doll. Don't be scared.
Qian Kaiyi.
Why are you hiding here?
Well, let's go upstairs for now, He Dun.
I'm sweating.
Go upstairs?
You... Are you a man?
Come here!
Let go of my arm.
In there.
If I'd been a bit late, you could have been killed.
We're being bugged.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
I'm fine.
Come over here.
The patient drank heavily after being sedated, which led to respiration disorders.
- He is now in shock.
- I'm Ye Jiahui.
What a coincidence. I never thought we'd be neighbors.
Have you ever met such a case?
No. My mentor knows something about it.
My senior is in a relationship with her visitor?
This person is very high-functioning.
I'll introduce my teacher to you one day.
My senior thought this file was in my hands.
[F's client file 99-00]
I'm now handing over this file to you.
Keep it well.
Keep the information about visitors strictly confidential.
Jiahui knew everything about me through all my visitors and friends.
He even disturbed my life and work.
I've been wondering why a gifted and self-restricted
psychological counselor fell for her visitor.
Now I finally know who that visitor is.
It's Ye Jiahui.
He made such a careful plan for one purpose.
[Interview with renowned professor of psychology]
You rat!
What are you doing? Stop!
Can't you have a good talk?
Stop!
Are you all right? Get up.
Stop! Stop!
Are you all right?
Ye Jiahui, let me ask you. Why did you do this to me?
Why did you do this to Professor Ji?
You approach and get close to me on purpose, right?
You never treated us as your friends, right?
Ye Jiahui. If you're a man, just admit what you have done.
Say something! Are you mute?
Your behavior is illegally sneaking into others' houses.
According to Article 40 of the Regulations
of the People's Republic of China on Punishments in Public Order and Security Administration,
you shall be detained for not less than 10 days but not more than 15 days
and be fined not less than 500 yuan but not more than 1,000 yuan.
Sir, it was me who burst the door open.
It has nothing to do with them.
You're the judge?
They're accomplices, and you're the main culprit.
Fortunately, your friend doesn't press charges.
Otherwise, all of you will be detained with him.
Mr. Qian, don't be impulsive.
Intentionally hitting others can constitute the crime of intentional injury or provoking troubles.
Sir, he won't do it again.
This lady,
why do I see you everywhere?
Are you trying to meet me by every means?
Sir, if I say it's a coincidence, will you believe me?
Sir… Sir, may I ask
how long he will be detained?
It depends on the severity of the consequences of wiretapping.
We'll search the scene later for evidence.
If it's minor, and you're willing to mediate, it won't be too long.
But you have to go back with us to give a statement.
All right.
Okay.
Let's go.
You're spineless.
Mr. Ye, your conduct doesn't constitute a criminal offence.
But according to the Regulations of the People's Republic of China on Punishments
in Public Order and Security Administration,
peeping, filming, eavesdropping and disseminating others' privacy are serious.
You shall be detained for not less than 5 days but not more than 10 days.
Mr. Ye, did you hear me?
Whatever.
This is my house.
Are you hungry?
Yes, a little.
Let me defrost some dumplings and then cook them for you.
- Make yourself at home.
- Okay.
So this is yours…
This is your water.
It's cute.
Wait a moment.
What are you doing?
These are your parents?
They're a perfect match.
The elders in the Wenchang Street said the same thing.
Have a seat.
They must love each other so much.
They were a model couple in the Wenchang Street.
I remember when I was a child, my mom cooked dinner every night and waited for my dad.
No matter how late he returned and how tired he was,
he would have a bowl of soup cooked by my mom,
as if he couldn't sleep without it.
It seems your mother is a good cook.
My mom's cooking skill…
But my dad thought it was good.
So sometimes, I thought if his taste buds had changed after he married my mom.
That's because he loves your mom.
Idiot!
So...
Are you feeling better?
Today, I asked Ye Jiahui why he framed Professor Ji and me.
He didn't answer it.
We were strangers before.
I really don't know why he did that.
But the result is that he hurt you.
That's unforgivable.
In fact, I've always known little about him.
He isn't talkative, looking quite incomprehensible.
But when he was in the Wenchang Street, he talked with the elders…
I major in medicine.
Are you a doctor?
He cooked and played chess with them,
and played games with children.
I could tell his smile was sincere.
He was really happy.
Sometimes, I think a person's characteristics
can determine if he's good or evil and whom he likes.
I really want to have a chance to talk with him.
What's wrong?
All right, but I have to be present.
Okay, Mr. Aloha shirt.
Forget it.
Anyway, Ye Jiahui's matter has been handled.
- Then I'll tell you about the next thing.
- What is it?
But you have to promise me not to get angry.
I must hear what it is before deciding whether to get angry or not.
I want to do an episode about psychological counseling.
If we get more listeners than they do, they won't be allowed to snatch our men.
What if you lose?
Then I'll have many things to do.
For example, I can sell coffee in the garden house.
I can also serve as your assistant in your counseling office.
You can also open a shop for aloha shirts.
- I can't believe you have that idea.
- What's up?
But I support your idea.
In fact, I'm not afraid of others' comments on me.
In my heart, sadness is overtaken by worries that the public will misunderstand the profession
as psychological counselors because of Professor Ji and me.
If we can really do an episode to tell them what this profession is all about,
let them know about me and clear up some of their misconceptions about the profession,
I think it's a good thing. Don't you think so?
My sweetheart always cares about the public no matter when it is.
♫ Listen to the melody of the wind ♫
♫ Slowly blowing off leaves from the trees ♫
♫ Look at the clear sunshine ♫
♫ Hurriedly brushing past your figure ♫
You always bring me food.
I don't know what I should give you.
So I chose
a brand-name lipstick. Look.
Then I'll take it.
I saw you always bought on vip.com, so I also bought it there.
Thanks.
Why did you give me a ride home?
I saw Qian Kaiyi took He Dun home.
So I was worried about you returning alone.
I did it deliberately to create an opportunity for them.
I've been down this road many times. You know that.
But thank you anyway.
You're a girl. You'd better be more cautious if you're alone.
Isn't Ye Jiahui your friend?
Yes, you're right.
In fact, many people who go astray aren't absolutely bad guys.
Take the old man we met as an example.
He went to others' houses at midnight.
He didn't steal anything valuable, but some plastic bottles
and abandoned cardboard boxes to sell them.
He did this just to buy food for his starving grandchildren.
So many things need to be balanced by law.
- What I can do…
- …is just to uphold social justice.
In fact, I think you and Dun He are quite similar.
The difference is that you deal with the people
whose behaviors go wrong,
and she deals with those whose mind goes wrong.
Yes, I'm increasingly aware that many people who make mistakes
have an unhealthy mind.
So your work is very important.
Sir, before leaving, can you teach me a few self-defense skills?
I just thought what you said was reasonable.
Girls should learn some skills
to protect themselves.
Take it as a thank-you for the food I brought you.
For the sake of your just-so-so food,
I'll teach you some.
All right, thanks then!
Look.
When you're in danger,
you need to guard.
Use the hand for fending off the blow to grasp your enemy's hand.
Grasp, dig, and elbow.
- Elbow.
- Yes.
Grasp, dig, and elbow.
Hit me.
Are you sure?
Yes, have a try.
You're a quick learner.
Sir, may I ask you a question?
Don't turn around.
Say it.
Can you be my boyfriend?
Can I be your girlfriend?
It's fine,
good night.
How about helping me finish it?
How do you feel about me?
Well…
You…
You're here. I'm leaving now.
Good night.
You haven't answered me yet.
What do you think of Professor Ji's reaction when he saw the letter at the hearing?
It wasn't anger, but panic.
He has never been so panicked.
- Because that letter can't be read out.
- Have you forgotten it?
He wanted to stop this farce not for himself.
Yes.
It's for the owner of that letter.
He wanted to protect that person.
So who is that person?
His love.
Otherwise, he couldn't have hurt your mentor.
If Ye Jiahui's target is Professor Ji, why has he lurked around me for so long?
Because you have what he wants.
This F is my senior's visitor?
He Dun,
keep this file for me.
[F's client file 99-00]
No, he's my visitor.
- I'm already in love with him.
- F.
He's always been mine.
Have you seen our mentor's File on F?
File on F?
Li Yun's F is Ye Jiahui.
So the F who Ye Jiahui is looking for is the real owner of this letter.
- Hello.
- Senior.
How are you doing overseas? Is everything all right?
Yes.
He Dun, thanks for caring about me.
How about you?
Senior, I need your help.
Something happened to me recently.
Our mentor is sick.
One of my friends may be detained for a few days.
You also know him.
Ye Jiahui.
What happened to him?
He… Where is he?
He should be home in a couple of days.
You don't need to worry about him.
Senior, only you can help us now.
Sorry, I can't.
Senior, how much do you know about Ye Jiahui?
And what has he been looking for?
I'm really at my wit's end.
I need your help.
His matter isn't that simple.
There must be a great scheme hidden behind it.
You must pay attention to your safety. Got it?
A long time ago, our mentor gave me an address and asked me to help.
But I was so busy that I didn't pay attention to it.
But in retrospect, I think there might be the answer you're looking for.
Auntie, may I ask what soup can restore energy?
Cinnamon, red dates and American ginseng
are all good for girls.
I didn't say it was for a girl.
Who else do you have except for He Dun?
By the way, I have a secret recipe for nourishing during pregnancy. I'll tell it to you.
Auntie, you're thinking too much.
Don't you want to restore energy?
I'm afraid that He Dun will lack energy because of talking too much.
That secret recipe can also restore energy.
All right, I'll write them down.
Thanks, Auntie.
Why did you get up so early?
You also up?
It was because of you that I had trouble sleeping yesterday.
I saw you slept well last night.
- Have a taste.
- Did you make it?
It's a little hot.
What do you think?
Then I'll get a bowl for you.
Thank you, Qian Kaiyi.
Don't be foolish!
I'm going to meet a person later.
Who is it?
F.
This way.
Ran fast?
Sit down.
Keep an eye on him.
Hello.
I came just at the right time. They've all gone to lunch.
Why are you here again? You're addicted to bringing me food?
You don't like it?
Then I'll bring another dish tomorrow.
What's it?
You're looking forward to it.
Don't behave like this all the time. This is my workplace. It's improper.
What's wrong with it?
You can order takeaway food in the workplace.
Food deliverers can come, so can I.
So, you got a part-time job as a food deliverer.
Policemen should be healthy when serving the people.
I'm making contribution to the people.
You're really good at flattering yourself.
What do you mean?
Be decent.
Don't cause trouble for me.
I didn't.
Did I kill or cheat others or set fire?
If you talk nonsense again, I'll have you arrested!
Go ahead. I can be here every day and watch you.
Sis, I'm wrong.
Can you save my face?
Can we have a serious talk?
Here's a truce for a minute.
Well, are you still in touch with Ye Jiahui?
Why did you suddenly ask that?
It's my duty to care about the follow-up of the case.
Fine.
I'm fine. Rest assured.
But I have to warn you.
You, who lives with other girls, still need to pay attention to the security of your house.
Tomorrow, I'll have someone check out my house, including every room and every corner.
Is that fine?
You have a good sense of precaution.
It's because you're a good teacher.
Anyway, thanks for your food.
I have to work now.
Got it. I'm leaving now.
- Bye.
Wait a minute.
It's been washed.
Don't buy new lunchboxes anymore.
Yes, Sir.
I'm off then.
Bye.
Brother, you look so happy.
You're sensible.
Brother Qian, I saw a few interns on 58.com and talked with them.
They're all excellent.
In particular, this one, Cheng Weizi.
She's outstanding in all aspects.
All right. Then arrange a video interview.
I'll definitely get the job done.
- Have you read the program outline?
- Yes.
What do you think?
Do you have any confidence in tomorrow's program?
Yes.
Definitely.
Come here.
What's up?
Just now, Sister Qiao asked me for the program outline.
I gave it to her.
I have to warn you.
She didn't look happy.
All right.
I know what to do.
Wow.
- Good morning, Sister Qiao.
Kaiyi, go in and have a word with me.
Okay.
Don't worry, Brother. We're all confident.
Focus on writing your articles.
Come in.
My Gosh!
Sister, you need to control your expressions.
You're prone to wrinkles.
I'm not as relaxed as you are.
Do you know what you're doing?
I know you care about me.
But what's done is done.
Then let's do it.
Let's do the best we can tomorrow.
Do you know what's this behavior?
Competing.
Why do you have to compete with Wang Zhuo?
Did Director Pan say there would definitely be a personnel change?
Even if it's true, Director Fei and I will help you.
Sister, in your eyes, am I really that useless?
I didn't mean that.
Then don't worry.
I'm telling you, I have figured out a perfect plan.
Fine, you're the smartest.
But you must know, if you lose, your team will be demoralized.
Are you ready for it?
In this case, we had a meeting.
And we all agreed.
It's imperative for us to get the program done.
Tell me the truth.
Do you do this to protect He Dun?
Yes.
But if it were Dong, Qing, Li or you,
I would make the same decision.
The psychological counseling cases in this TV series are artistically stylized for visual presentation purposes. Please seek help from professional psychological counseling institutions if you encounter similar cases or have other psychological distress.
♫  Each dawn blooms with a word of flowers  ♫
♫  Here is an aroma of coffee and you  ♫
♫  Whether the haze turns into rain or the weather suddenly clears up  ♫
♫  I wish to be with you  ♫
♫  A shower of rain gently floats far out of the sky  ♫
♫  Taking with it my blue and cloudy memories  ♫
♫  I bloom like a scenery as clear as a song  ♫
♫  I see your eyes as bright as a star  ♫
♫  They warm my smile and listen to my true voice  ♫
♫  Giving me the gentlest response  ♫
♫  I see the sudden arrival  ♫
♫  of a beautiful love  ♫
♫  Holding your hand, I can feel your heart  ♫