Excuse me, Madam.
Madam.
Would you like something to drink?
Oh, yes.
- Are you OK?
- Yes. Excuse me.
We have coffee, tea, Japanese tea,
and orange juice.
Then, coffee...
Coffee, please!
Certainly, Madam.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Why are you speaking English when you don't speak it?
Oh dear, I didn't know you were awake.
We're going to Okinawa,
you don't need to speak English.
Because this is my first time flying.
When it comes to flights, it's:
"Attention, please! Coffee or tea?"
Ugh. You're getting carried away.
Of course, I am. It's our honeymoon!
Yes, we're on our honeymoon...
to Okinawa!
And sitting here next to me
is the person that I've loved for a long time: Irie-kun!
What?
We really got married!
It's really starting to dawn on me now.
How many times do you have to
look at those pictures?
I'm gonna take a nap.
Are you sleeping?
It's our honeymoon.
My mom's set up our wedding and
this honeymoon without asking me.
I'm tired.
Are you on your honeymoon?
The girl who laughed at me earlier.
Yes.
So are we! Right?
Hi.
Oh, did your husband fall asleep?
Poor you, it's your
long-awaited honeymoon.
I'd never fall asleep and leave
Mari-chan alone.
You have such a sweet husband.
'Cause Takumi-kun is madly in love with me.
Madly in love...
The day Mari-chan joined our company,
I felt, "She the one!"
It was just a boring office romance.
What do you mean boring?
And you?
I'm Kotoko. Iri...
I'm Kotoko Irie.
Your husband proposed to you?
N-No! Never! No way!
What?
For us, I'd say...
I was the one who tried and
pushed him like crazy.
Tonan High School
Entrance Ceremony
All the way back at the High School Entrance Ceremony
it was love at first sight.
I love you.
I don't want it.
I'm sorry for what happend to you.
I'm the eldest son, Naoki.
Nice to meet you.
Will you keep you're distance from me?
I hate stupid girls.
Kotoko.
What?
You may not know me, but I know you.
I was attracted to your intelligence and good looks
at the Entrance Ceremony.
I'll...
I'll stop loving you.
I'll see if you can do that.
Serves you right.
Yuki-kun! Yuki-kun! Hold on!
Papa! Are you all right!?
I'll protect my dad's company.
This is Mr. Oizumi,
the chairman of Hokueisha.
How about having
a marriage interview?
I'll snatch Kotoko away from you.
I'll make you forget that bastard.
No! Stop! Irie-kun!
You love me!
You can never love anyone but me.
How could you be so confident!?
Yeah, you're right, you're right! I can't help it!
But you don't even love me!
You don't even...
I love you so much.
Serves you right.
And so...
My 6 year-long one-sided love
finally ended with our marriage
and here we are.
You were quite patient, Kotoko-san.
Oh my, what am I...
You came from behind to win at destiny.
Yeah, maybe.
So you pushed and pushed and
pushed him down into the bed? Right on!
No way! We have yet to go
that far...that far...
Last night, he said he was tired and so just fell asleep.
Wait, so you mean...
You're kidding!
You haven't has sex with him yet?
It's really rare nowadays.
But, aren't you nervous?
What?
I would be shocked if my partner
didn't want me as a woman.
I might wonder if I'm not attractive.
Well...
Are you guys OK? Please don't
end up being a Narita airport divorced.
Oops, it's not Narita.
It's Haneda.
My bad.
Narita... divorce...!?
I feel I'm a bit tired.
Takumi-kun, give me a shoulder massage.
Yes, gladly.
Na... Narita divorce...!?
How dare she say that to me
on the first day of our honeymoon!
Mischievous Kiss 2
Love in OKINAWA
What's up?
My sunglasses.
Sunglasses? I thought you were
night-blind.
Night-blind people
feel brightness, too.
Let's see...
Wait till we get to the hotel.
I wanna wear them right now.
It doesn't open..
Yeah, right.
What, maybe the lock is broken?
You don't wanna break that.
It's open, Irie-kun!
You wear that?
No! I never wear
this kind of swimsuit!
I wonder who would wear
this kind of showy stuff.
Hey! That's mine!
Is that... mine?
I'm so glad that we're staying
at the same hotel!
Why in the world do we have to stay
at the same hotel with this woman!?
Hey after this why don't we have
a meal together?
Irie-kun! Let's hurry and go to our room!
Excuse us, please.
So finally, it's just the two of us.
Kotoko!
I'm sorry! Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Go... Minam?
Minam ...
Are you Go Minam of the A. N. JELL?
Kang Shin-woo... Jeremy...?!
Yup, we are.
(Chinese) I'm Go Minam.
Kang Shin-woo.
Jeremy.
Oh my gosh! It's A. N. JELL!
The popular band from Taiwan!
From Taiwan?
I love these guys!
Sorry for the trouble.
We're OK thanks to you.
Please ask them why
they're in Okinawa.
You do it.
But, I don't speak their language.
Come on.
Why are you guys in Okinawa?
To shoot a music video.
Okinawa is awesome!
What? What did they say?
They're here to shoot a music video.
Really? That's so cool!
Have a nice trip.
Bye-bye.
Best wishes.
Wow, thank you!
Bye-bye!
- Let's go.
- Ok!
Fantastic! How fantastic!
It's the ocean! Amazing. And blue sky!
Okinawa! We're in Okinawa, Irie-kun!
Calm down a bit.
It's like a princess bed.
I can roll over and over!
Hey, look, Irie-kun!
Wait. Tonight in this bed...
with Irie-kun...
I will truly become one
with Irie-kun.
Irie-kun...
Yeah?
Um...
I'll do my best to become
a good wife, so...
So, please don't give up on me.
You were caught up with
A. N. JELL a few minutes ago.
What?
Nothing.
I don't expect too much.
Just stay as you are.
Stay as you are.
Hello?
Hello? Naoki-san? It's me! Mari!
Naoki-san, Naoki-san! Kotoko-san!
Over here!
We saved seats for you!
How dare she repeat
his name like they're dating!
Naoki-san! Right here!
We saved seats for you guys!
Hi.
They said you can have drinks at the poolside.
Naoki-san, let's go order together!
- Ok, then let me...
- Sure.
Let's go.
Please excuse her,
I guess she likes Naoki-san.
Hey, Takumi-san! ...is it right?
What kind of discipline
are you giving your wife!?
If you know what's going on,
stop her! Aren't you her husband?
Yeah, but my love was one-sided
for a long time,
It's like I finally got her to marry me.
Why are you talking
You guys are married aren't you? Your status is equal!
It's 50/50!
Stupid Kotoko.
How can you say something like that?
I think I just heard
Yuki-kun's voice.
It looks like those two are getting along.
So we should hang out too!
Hey! She's being all clingy to Irie-kun!
Oh, no.
- It's so cold!
- Are you all right?
I will bring you a towel immediately.
What the heck!?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, what are you doing?
Good work! Ms. Blonde!
Mari-chan, are you OK?
Are you OK, Mari-chan?
This is terrible.
Sorry very much.
It was my mistake.
Hey, Mom, come on.
Let's go to the beach.
Sandy, wait.
Sorry.
Wait a minute, those people
are foreigners.
Wow, so you're a future doctor?
No, I'm just aspiring
to be a doctor.
Even just aspiring to that is fantastic.
Irie-kun, will, without problem
get into medical school!
Because he has an IQ of 200!
You two got married after Kotoko pushed violently, right?
Violent?
Because. You're from a completely different world than me.
You two are married, and
you still call him "Irie-kun."
It's funny!
So you're not close enough to call him by name?
Mari-chan!
It's just a habit after many years.
Oh, after only that little alcohol.
Kotoko, we're back in our room.
Hey, Kotoko.
Wife, we're back in our room.
Irie-kun...
I love you.
Day 2
It's Shisa! So cute!
Let's have a picture taken with him.
No way.
Let's ask somebody
to take a picture!
Let's see...
Excuse me, could you take
a picture of us?
Of course. That's okay.
Thank you! I appreciate it.
Here we go! Irie-kun!
Get more closer to each other!
Yes, yes. Pretty.
(speaking broken English)
Oh, no, boy. Look, look.
Look at me and smile, smile.
Viva!
Say, Chinsuko!
Yes!
Thank you very much!
Is it okay?
Yes, this is great! Thank you!
Okay.
Come on!
Oh, Bob. Sorry.
Oh, sorry.
I've seen those guys somewhere.
We were at the pool together!
They're the people that were at the pool yesterday!
We came to the same place. What a coincidence!
Not surprising. This is a recommend spot!
That was so much fun! I'm starving.
Let's eat!
Oh, what a coincidence!
Can we have lunch with you?
Excuse me!
- What have you been doing today?
- We just saw the Eisa show.
Eisa show?
Cool! We're going to see it after this!
We're so excited, aren't we, Takumi-kun?
Did you enjoy it, Naoki?
Yes, we did!
Say, Cheese!
Day 3
What is this? How colorful these fish are!
Irie-kun, a coconut crab!
Do you think this tastes good?
Excuse me! Can I have this?
Yes.
Let me show you to the second floor.
Let's go.
Naoki-san! This way!
Hurry, we got seats for you!
Hurry, Naoki-san!
Day 4
Naoki-san!
Hurry, Naoki-san! Over here!
Can you see me? Hurry up!
I'm waiting for you!
Naoki-san!
Why the heck does
she get in the way every day?!
Day 5
Voila! This is the main-temple.
They say this was a Ryukyuan castle long ago.
1, 2, 3... 3 dragons!
I wonder why it's not Shisa!
A bright red castle!
Naoki-san, what's your favorite color?
Day 6
You're kidding, right?
All of a sudden, all of a sudden...
it's our last day in Okinawa!
Tonight is the end.
We're heading back
to Tokyo tomorrow.
But we haven't made any progress
in our relationship.
It's all because that couple
bothers us every day.
Every night they invite us for drinks.
Cool. I wonder if it's the same as mine.
Oh look we have the same marriage line.
You have two lines of fate!
Another round!
I know it's partially my fault that I drink
even when I have a low tolerance.
Thanks to all that, we're still
far away from anything romance.
Please don't end up being
a Narita divorced.
What if we continued on with nothing happening?
My dear Kotoko-chan! I expect a lot from you!
For my mom's sake, and for my sake!
I'll never go back to Tokyo
like this!
Tonight!
We will definitely have
a true bridal night!
Wow, it's a whale shark! So huge!
Tonight, I will definitely...
Look, Irie-kun!
What a beautiful chapel!
Good smile both of you!
OK, are you ready?
Say, Cheese!
OK, let's take another one.
Looks good! Say, Cheese!
And another one. Say, Cheese!
Now, sir, please put your hand
gently on your wife's shoulder.
Looks great! Good smile, Madam!
Sir, give me a smile! Smile please!
Say, Cheese!
Lucky us, we could have
our photo without reservation.
It reminds me of
our wedding ceremony!
Ugh. I'm never gonna do this again.
Thank you so much.
No problem. We were expecting another newlywed
couple for a photoshoot so it was perfect.
Newlywed couple...?
I guess they're here, the newlyweds.
This way, please.
Oh! You two were here?
We met again.
You know each other?
Yes. Kind of.
Naoki-san, you look so handsome.
I bet it's because you're tall!
Look our height is perfect for each other.
Oh! While we're at it, maybe I'll take photos
with Naoki-san too!
Nah, I think not.
Kotoko-san, I'd lend you Takumi-kun.
What do you think, Naoki-san?
Sorry, but we need to go now.
We're going to buy souvenirs, right?
Y... yes.
Let's go, Kotoko.
Yes.
Wait for me, Irie-kun!
What happened?
Mari... Mari...
It hurts.
Early, she said her stomach
suddenly started hurting.
Why don't you take her
to the hospital?
It's the weekend, and
it's probably too late.
Then call an ambulance!
She doesn't want to make this serious.
It'll get better if I keep
lying down. Oh, it hurts!
Mari-chan! Are you OK? Are you OK?
Naoki-san! You said you wanna be
a doctor, right?
Can you do anything?
No way! Though he aspires to
be a doctor, he is still...
Okay. I'll take a look.
Does she have nausea?
No.
Fever?
Not particularly.
Let me check your pulse.
Naoki-san, is Mari going to be OK?
Where does it hurt?
Let me see your stomach.
No, Irie-kun! Don't touch her!
Hey, I think we should call
an ambulance.
It depends on her condition.
Then what about our dinner?
This is not the time for that!
It hurts...
No! Don't touch her, Irie-kun!
Don't touch another girl!
That's enough!
You married a guy who wants to be a doctor.
Be a bit more self-conscious.
Irie-kun.
Are you always going to be that way
when I see patients?
I don't want to deal something so pathetic.
If you don't understand,
I can't be with you.
Naoki, you're going too far...
Kotoko-san!
You don't have to
go after your wife?
Your wife's alright. I assume
she's got mild food poisoning.
The pharmacy is still open, give her
some stomach medicine and that should do it.
Thank you so much.
Takumi-kun, go buy it for me.
Yeah, sure. I'll be back soon.
You should go find your wife.
Takumi-kun, hurry up!
Yes, then...
So, I'm off here.
Naoki-san, you're so cold.
I guess it can't be helped as Kotoko-san as your partner.
Maybe you don't really love her.
I thought you had a stomach ache.
I made it up.
You made it up?
Because I wanted to be alone with you.
I heard you guys haven't had
anything sexual yet.
Well, it's understandable.
You don't even really want to touch Kotoko-san, right?
I fell in love with you
at first sight.
I wish I had met you before she did.
Then both of us wouldn't have
had to make mistakes in our marriages.
It's not too late.
Shut up.
What?
If I met a woman like you 100 times,
I would ignore you 100 times!
What...
Do not compare yourself with Kotoko.
Sorry, sorry, I forgot my wallet.
What happend, Mari-chan?
Naoki-san seemed angry.
I'm not gonna forgive him.
He made a fool of me.
Mari-chan?
I'll definitely break them up!
He didn't have to be that mean!
What are you doing?
That's my line!
Why do I have to get hit? I gave you a marriage!
We're finished! We're splitting up!
You're right!
We started off with
my one-sided love!
But now we're married, we're
at the same level.
You're my wife! Don't look
at other guys!
Do you understand?
Yes.
I'm so stupid.
I'm so embarrassed that
I want to die.
I thought I understood Irie-kun's
ambition to become a doctor.
Where am I?
I'm totally lost, aren't I.
I don't remember how and
where I came from.
I left my wallet at the hotel.
Feels like I came to a sketchy part of town.
Hey, excuse me.
Can I help you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm going to be kidnapped!
What if I get kidnapped and
never see Irie-kun again!
Irie-kun, help me!
Irie-kun!
Irie-kun, I love you!
I didn't want a Narita divorce!
- Don't worry. It's ok.
-No!
- Hey, I will take you there.
- Help me ...!
What is she doing?
Don't worry.
I'll help you out.
Hey, what's the matter with my wife?
Your wife?
- Irie-kun!
-Kotoko.
I thought I would never
see you again!
I thought you will
never find me.
Everything is okay.
He thought you were a lost elementary
school student and tried to help you.
An elementary school student?
So, he is not a bad guy?
Anyway, apologize.
I'm sorry.
Okay, okay, okay.
Don't worry, don't worry.
It's okay, thank you.
You guys are nice.
Good luck.
I wish you guys can enjoy your
fantastic and good, amazing honeymoon.
Thank you.
Have a nice day, thank you.
Thanks for coming.
Your screams were real loud.
Because...
Narita divorce... how classic.
If you're gonna say that it would be a Haneda divorce, right?
Really ...
I'm sorry.
I was jealous.
I was being selfish,
I was being so stupid.
You fool,
I really worried about you.
Splendid!
I was right to buy
this fantastic camera.
That chaotic irritated, "don't know
what to do" feeling inside me
was turning into something
warm and sweet like candy.
It took a long time to get here.
Yeah, but it's OK.
I was happy just being
by your side.
I'm not okay.
If there was a way to
measure my happiness...
I wouldn't have been the happiest person in the world.
I'll never forget
what happened today.
Never.
Time flies in the blink of an eye.
I'm so sad. I already miss Okinawa.
It was our honeymoon and we didn't
spend that much time together.
It, it, it tastes good!
You're silly.
Mari-chan, your turn.
What is up with those two?
They're the reason for all this jealousy!
It's good for them.
Well, you're right. But...
What?
Nothing.
Our stay was short, but
Okinawa gave us sweet memories.
Sorry for making you wait, Okasan.
(okasan: mother)
Irie-kun and I finally
met your expectations.
Excuse me.
- It's sweet.
- Tastes good.
That was fun!
Let's go again someday.
Yeah, someday.
Next time, we'll be all alone and…
Naoki-san!
Kanamori-san…
Welcome home, Naoki-san.
And Misus.
Misus...
What are you doing here?
I came to meet you.
Meet us?
What is it? Did something happen
at the company while my father was away?
Your father was away?
It's not for me to say.
Aren't we heading home?
Where are we headed, Kanamori-san?
We'll be there shortly.
Shortly?
[Preview- Ep.02 My Marriage Still On Hold?!]
You're not officially married?!
I'm not ready to register our marriage.
I don't understand Irie-kun at all.
It's fine.
There must be some reason.
Tennis warrior Koto-rin!
What a useless bride.
Don't play with her heart!
What are you men thinking?
I don't want to see him.
This isn't a marriage!
Then leave.