Irie-kun...
That's right. He left.
Irie-kun, are you doing well?
Have you adapted to your life there yet?
Irie-kun, congratulations!
Irie-kun passed the National Examination for
Medical Practitioners, which had been his dream.
It's not a bad thing, so think about it.
I think I'll work at a hospital in Kobe.
You stay here. I'll go there by myself.
You should stay here and study.
I... will definitely become a nurse in a year.
And then I will go to Kobe.
I will definitely go. So...
please wait.
All the best, Irie-kun!
So it has been 2 months since he left for Kobe.
All the best...Kotoko.
All the best...to the both of us.
I... I...
might not be able to
stand it any longer.
Mischievous Kiss 2
Love in Tokyo
Nursing Practice Room
#12 - And Love in Kobe
Jeez, recently, she's been absent-minded.
Or rather,her absent-mindedness by nature got worse recently.
Are you getting along with Irie?
Of course we are!...Isn't that a given...
No... why are you crying, Kotoko?
This is pretty bad...
Don't stress yourself out. Just go see him.
That's right. I don't want you to make any more mistakes.
We are okay! Our relationship as a couple is really deep and ...
Men feel like being bachelors
when their wives are not around.
And they go on the loose.
Right. He is a man, you know.
If he were approached by pretty nurses and patients,
he would actually feel fairly pleased.
If Kotoko doesn't go...
-I could go to Kobe and approach him.
-Marina don't say that...
I'M FINE!!
Oh my.
So mean! Everyone is so mean!
Even though I really want to see Irie-kun,
and I've been suppressing this feeling.
They just keep talking about what I don't wanna think about.
Of course,
meeting Irie-kun, kissing him and hugging tightly ...
I wouldn't ask too much like that.
Even from far away, I just want to catch
a glimpse of Irie-kun.
From far away...a glimpse...
That's right!
I did it...such a reckless act.
But if I'm just seeing him from afar...
As long as I don't actually meet him...
I'm not breaking the promise, right?
After all...
After all, I feel...
out of energy~!
Here, this street, is where Irie-kun is.
We're breathing the same air.
Doctor Irie!
Doctor Numaguchi has something to discuss with you.
He's at the examination room for outpatients.
- Okay.
-Excuse me, then.
I found him! It's Irie-kun!
My energy level is going up now.
I can go back to Tokyo now...
It's Doctor Irie!
He is so handsome.
He is definitely the best among all the interns.
I wonder if he is married.
Here, I am his wife.
I heard he doesn't even have a girlfriend.
No way! He is definitely ... popular.
See? That's why he doesn't have to look for a girlfriend.
- Oh, my goodness ...
- Then, should I approach him?
There's no way you can get him. It's too competitive.
I know at least 10 people are already making a pass at him.
Hey, I might become the 11th.
It's okay.
Things like this used to happen all the time in Tokyo, too.
While I am still full of energy,
I should go back home now...
Ouch.
What a hindrance.
You were just standing around here. That's why!
What's this? She is like the Kansai-version
(southern-central region of Japan's main island) of Yuuki...
I'll have to talk to this kind of kid strictly!
Hey, you should say "I'm sorry" when you bump into a person.
Please, say it.
Idiot!
This kid...
Mom, I'm scared. She is like Slit Mouth Woman.
Hey!
I'm sorry. My daughter is foul-mouthed.
- Wow, such a pretty and young mother.
- Apologize to her.
Go ahead.
Sorry. You are not the Slit Mouth Woman.
You're so cute, it's okay.
Auntie, you look like Kuidaore Taro.
(the famous drum-playing doll in Osaka)
My goodness, Nami ...
She is just like it. Just like it!
Wait, don't run.
Nami-chan, you shouldn't run around in a hospital.
I saw an auntie who looks exactly like Kuidaore Taro.
Auntie who looks like Kuidaore Taro?
If only I'd seen her.
I wonder where she went...
Hello, Doctor.
Hello, you came.
What's with them? Do they know Irie-kun?
What are you doing, Nami?
I am sorry, Doctor. This kid...
Mom spends a lot of time wearing make-up when she meets Irie-sensei. Right?
What are you talking about?
That's true. Mom loves Irie-sensei.
Come on! Cut it out.
I'm sorry.
Irie-sensei ... do you have time today?
Yes,of course.
Oh, good.
Then, I'll see you at Central Park at 5 o'clock.
Okay.
What?
What? You're going on a date with Mom?
Yeah, kind of.
I..I...Irie-kun
The sun's starting to go down.
I'm so...
Why do I have to be here
and do such an embarrassing thing?
Is the doctor not coming yet?
But I have to confirm for myself what his relationship is with the married woman.
I can't go back even if I wanted to!
He's here!
- Doctor.
- It's Doctor Irie!
Sorry, I'm late.
No, thank you for coming, as always.
Irie-kun...
Dr. Irie, let's go to the slide!
Over there! Let's go!
Nami, go buy some juice with this.
OK, fine. I guess I'm intruding, right?
Can't be helped! I'll be thoughtful (and leave you alone).
No way!
Don't be thoughtful...don't!
What is with this mood?
What? What is...
Something must be wrong, right?
Irie-kun...
Found you!
Doctor Irie!
-Come here, quick!
-Wait, hang on!
- Please!
-Ahhhh!
Be quiet!
You're going to blow my cover!
Kotoko.
What are you doing?
The mother and daughter, their name is Shiina-san.
The daughter Nami-chan is under my care.
But there's another surgeon in charge of their care.
She seems so healthy.
Yup, she seems healthy right now, but
she's had heart problems since she was born.
Up till now, she's had several seizures.
Her heart...
She had an operation once when she was 5 years old but
heart procedures aren't so easy.
She was told that when she got older
there's a need for her to have another surgery.
The surgeon and I both
feel that the best time is now.
However, I heard Nami-chan's father passed away two years ago.
Nami-chan is thinking that during this next surgery
she might also die as well.
She's scared.
Her mom is also very worried.
So I was supporting them and offering them advice.
Oh, so that's what it was. I am so (bad).
Speaking of which, Irie-kun you're going to work
at the Pediatrics Department?
Yeah I am. You didn't know?
I had no idea.
I had assumed you were going to be a surgeon.
If I can, I'd like to become a pediatric surgeon.
That hospital is famous in that field.
I was contemplating going into the field of surgery, but
I was thinking over what I really wanted to do
and what I aim to do by becoming a doctor.
When I thought about that, the answer came to me quite easily.
What got you interested in becoming a doctor?
It's not a big deal.
What is it? What is it?
I'm not telling you. I'm going to bed.
Awww...I want to hear! Tell me!
Good night
Irie-kun in Pediatrics.
Might be good!
I'll be going now.
I feel bad but I can't see you off.
It's ok. I've fully recharged (my energy).
Plus I'm sure Mother and the others are worried.
Irie-kun, work hard ok?
Hey, it's the "all-you-can-eat" big sister.
You're with Dr. Irie again!
Were you with him since yesterday?
Nami-chan...
-What's your relationship with Dr Irie?
- Nami!
I'm sure it's impossible but I'll ask anyway.
Are you perhaps his girlfriend?
If you say a girlfriend...
You're being rude to her.
No.
I knew that. I thought it could never be that.
Even if you thought that, you shouldn't say it!
I am so sorry.
She is my wife.
What?
I said that she is my wife.
No way.
It is true.
That's a lie. I don't believe it.
Nami-chan.
But...
you have to marry my mom!
My mom is much prettier,
and her cooking is super good and...
Nami-chan,
I can't do that.
You're an idiot!
Nami-chan, don't run!
Nami.
Nami!
That girl, on top of her father passing away,
she's probably nervous and sad because of her illness.
So she figured that, Doctor Irie, if you were her father...
She wanted to choose the person she looked up to the most.
But everything's okay.
I'm sure I'll be able to convince her before her surgery in three days.
I'll do everything I can on my side, too.
I will, too. Please leave it to me!
I will for sure convince Nami-chan to have the surgery.
What are you talking about?
You're heading home now, aren't you?
I can't leave like this!
You're better off going home!
Why? This is partly my fault, too!
Plus, you're attitude just earlier
is too blunt and direct for a child.
You should consider a child's feelings first and foremost.
It's okay, mother!
Even if I don't look like it, I am a nurse!
I've decided last night that I'm going to become a pediatric nurse in the future.
There is no way you can do that.
Then...I'll leave it to you.
Okay!
We might have to use drastic measures for her.
Yeeees, I am "drastic measures."
You didn't understand the meaning of it, did you?
I will convince Nami-chan with everything I have within 3 days!
And I'll ensure that she gets better as soon as possible.
And have her give up on Irie-kun.
Hey, I came to visit you!
Nami-chan?
Nope.
What did you come here for?
Nami-chan!
Hey, I thought I'd bring you flowers!
Well, I kinda made a mistake...
-You like flowers, right?
I don't want it!
-Well, since I got them for you...
-I don't want them.
I really like roses but...
Woof woof! Woof woof!
You're here again?
I'm here again!
By the way, that's more like a fox.
Isn't it a dog?
It's not a dog.
A dog is like this!
Like that?
You do this and say "woof woof."
And so this is how I ended up staying in Kobe without producing any results.
Two days passed like that.
Hello~
What? It's you again.
I bought taiyaki. Want to eat together?
(taiyaki: a Japanese fish-shaped cake)
Have you made up your mind
to have the surgery and get healthy?
How about you? Do you feel like breaking up with Doctor Irie?
That's the only thing I can't do, right?
What's with your Kansai-ben?
(a dialect used in Kansai region)
How did someone like you manage to marry Dr Irie?
That alone would be worth praising for.
Even Irie-kun...
couldn't resist my charm.
I said you are worth to be praised,
but I'll take my words back.
It was just a joke.
There were lots of difficulties leading up to
my marriage with Irie-kun, you know?
I can imagine.
I fell in love at first sight with him in the first year of high school.
And confessed in the third year.
Then one thing led to another, and I ended up
living in Irie-kun's house.
Eh? Sounds like everything went smoothly
for you and him. No fair!
Or...could it be fate?
Yes. Fate!
After that, we have slowly but surely nurtured our love.
Didn't you have competitions?
I'm sure he was pretty popular.
Well, there were some tough competitors, but
I chased them away with my Love Beam towards Irie-kun.
No one couldn't win against my passion.
You probably freaked everyone out.
But I'm confident that I won't lose to anyone
for my love towards Irie-kun.
You, too, grow up and one day
you'll fall in love with someone nice.
But until then, you have to save your strength
to chase that person.
If you do that, you can get a boyfriend like I did with Irie-kun!
Nami-chan,
what you said about your mom was just an excuse, and
you like Irie-kun for yourself, right?
W-what are you talking about?
It was for my mom.
It's okay, you can tell me.
Irie-kun is like Superman.
He comes to rescue people in need.
He might be only an intern,
but he is very capable as you know.
He would definitely help you when you need him.
I know you trust him, don't you, Nami-chan?
Yup.
But... even if I become healthy after the surgery,
he is still your husband, so...
I know you won't give up on him.
I wonder if there is a person like Irie-sensei somewhere.
If there is, I can bear anything.
Nami-chan... this is only a suggestion...
Shiina Nami-sama
Chirata Hiroyuki-sama
Osanai Mitsuki-sama
Are you sure you want to go through surgery?
- Yes. I'll do it.
- Really?
That's great!
Good girl, Nami. Thank you.
Okay, leave everything to me, Nami-chan.
Irie-sensei and I will do our best.
Right, Irie-sensei?
Yes.
You made a good decision. What happened?
I promised with Onee-chan that after the surgery...
Right?
Yes..
What are you plotting?
No... nothing at all.
It is a secret between us.
Yes.
So, thank you very much!
We will get started after preparations.
I don't know what you did, but hands down to you.
Irie-sensei.
What's the matter? Are you scared?
You'll be fine. It'll be over while you are asleep.
No, I'm not scared at all.
Because I trust you, Irie-sensei.
Thank you.
Why did you decide to become a doctor?
When I didn't know what I should do in the future...
and I was suffering, I remembered someone telling me,
"It'd be nice if you became a doctor."
And I thought it wasn't a bad idea.
Was that person Onee-chan?
She probably doesn't remember saying that anyway.
How's Nami?
She's fine.
Thank you very much!
That's a relief.
I'm sorry I broke our promise.
But don't you think I was pretty good being a pediatric nurse?
Oh, right.
Nami-chan gave me this to give to you.
Nami-chan! How is she doing?
She is doing well. It's remarkable
to see how kids recover quickly.
I see.
I wonder what she wrote.
"Dear Nee-chan (Kotoko),
I'm recovering quite nicely.
I'll go to Tokyo soon!
If you break our promise, I'll kill you."
She's scary. What did you promise her?
Well...um...
What was it?
Actually...
Yuuki to be married with Nami-chan!?
Well... because she said
she would like someone just like Irie-kun...
but I can't let her have you.
Also she agreed to have the surgery, so I was really excited.
So, I couldn't take it back anymore ...
So...
So you promised that?
You are an idiot! Such a liar!
How can you make a promise you can't keep?
How are you going to explain this to Nami-chan?
That's why... I was counting on genius Irie-kun to solve this...
There is no way to solve this.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
I thought you were supporting her.
That's why... I feel terrible about that.
But I thought she'll forget soon enough.
This is so awkward, but we must say goodbye now.
Bye.
Thanks for seeing me off.
Why am I always...
...being this way.
You must definitely pass the National Nursing Exam in one try.
Irie-kun!
I..
I'll do my best!
Wait for me, Irie-kun.
I'll become the best nurse in Japan, who is right for you.
108 days until the National Nursing Exam
Seasons have passed after that;
summer came and went,
and fall has passed...
[ Until National Nursing Exam... 1 day! ]
( Wait for me, Irie-kun )
I'm not sure if I can endure this long winter safely.
Okay!
[After two weeks]
Results of National Nursing Exam
National Nursing Exam
Result announcement (bulletin)
Alright. It's 2 o'clock.
Hey, Kotoko. Hurry.
No! I can't look!
- Wait!
- Kotoko-chan, it's okay!
Didn't you study hard?
But Mother, my examination number
is 794!
I'll cry!
Pun: 7 "NA" 9 "KU" 4 "YO" = I'll cry! (Like a bad omen)
Is that so? Oh my...
Okay, okay. So you're number is 00794?
I look for it for you.
I passed!
My number's here, too!
-Mine, too!
Moto-chan, Marina, Keita and even Tomoko-chan...
I see.
Everyone passed.
I passed!
- Woohoo!
- Congratulations!
That's awesome! Whether it was a miracle
or by chance, passing is passing!
You passing in one try really is a miracle.
You actually had Irie sit your exam, didn't you!
How mean!
I think it would be good for you to study for five years.
For the patients' sake.
Hmm. That's right.
Jinx!
Not you, too, Fathers!
But still,
with this, everyone are nurses!
I'm so glad!
Let's celebrate!
Yeah!
The long winter ended
and my long awaited spring is here.
But...
The number you have dialed is unavailable,
please leave a message after the tone...
No matter how many times I call,
it won't go through.
Oh why?!
Is he working a night-shift!?
Even though I passed!
I don't want to say this kind of thing through voicemail!
Alright.
I'll go to Kobe,
then meet Irie-kun and announce it in person!
Kotoko-chan, are you sure you're okay? Do you remember how to get there?
I'm alright.
Irie-kun, my first appearance as a nurse!
Wait for me!
So cold.
Why did it turn out like this?
I came on the last train but he's not here...
Jeez...
I have no idea...
I don't have a map so I don't know which direction...
I don't have my phone so I can't call either...
And it's cold, too.
Can such a horrible day even exist?
There's nothing I can do about it.
Tonight, I'll just do what that drunk guy is doing.
Excuse me, Mister?
I'm not really used to this, but
I'm not really sure how to act around you so I might come across as rude.
But would you let me stay here for the night?
I'm sorry if I'm noisy.
It's my first time sleeping outside.
Please don't mind what I'm wearing.
It's not cosplay or anything.
There's a lot going on so...
There's really so much...
Will you hear me out?
Ah, it's okay if you fall asleep. I'll just talk by myself.
My husband is a very excellent doctor and
he's working in the hospital here.
So, I worked and worked my butt off in Tokyo to become a nurse and finally today...
no, yesterday...
I passed the National Nursing Examination!
And then, Irie--- ah...
I wanted to tell my husband the most,
I took the bullet train in a hurry.
I thought I'd surprise him when we met, so I am wearing this.
But I met a person who suddenly became ill on the train,
and I entrusted the person to the parademics at Shin-Osaka
and the train had left!
What is more, I left my coat on the train,
AND my phone and map was left inside!
I pulled myself together and took the next train
but it didn't stop at Shin-Kobe...
It was really like a nightmare!
Hey! Don't laugh! After all I'm...
That was a big ordeal, wasn't it.
Hey.
- Iri--
- What the heck do you mean by 'please sleep'?
You're voice was too loud.
These past three days, I haven't slept because of surgeries.
Even though I thought I'd be the one to surprise you...
I was surprised alright, with what you're wearing.
W-w-why...
are you in this kind of place?
Mom contacted the hospital.
She said you were coming here but you'd definitely get lost on the streets,
so she told me to meet you at the train station.
But who knew, instead of on the streets, you got lost on the train...
Why do you always come without informing me?
Because, Irie-kun...
I couldn't talk to you on the phone or leave a message.
Not only that, I wanted to tell you
as soon as possible.
I'll finally be able to work with you.
You worked hard for one whole year.
Umm...
Irie-kun!
You look pretty good in that.
♫ The world is brighter because you are in it. ♫
- I got off the train at Shin-Osaka.
- You alaready told me.
I left my coat and cellphone in the train.
You told me that too.
That was me talking to the old man.
You know, in Okayama...
You were explaining better before than now.
I know, right?
I asked about the train to Shin-kobe,
but they said the last train already left.
You already told me.
I didn't even know where the platform for Shin-Kobe...
♫ Just to hear you say 'Good morning' ♫
♫ feel like we'll stay happy together forever. ♫
♫ I never knew this could be happening to me,
but thank you, my love.  ♫
♫ I kissed you with an indifferent expression ♫
♫ But i'm the only one feeling it ♫
♫ I love you with my all, ♫
♫ no matter what you're like. ♫
♫ The love that understands all ♫
♫ we'll make that happen together.
So that we don't get separated ♫
♫ embrace me please ♫
~Next on Mischeievous Kiss 2~
Hospital in Kobe...
has no opening, so I can't go?
Irie-kun!
I'll teach you all about injections.
- Right.
- You might be a nuisance to Irie-sensei.
If it's Kotoko, you can overcome flowers and storms!
You are right. I have to hang in there.
Finally, we can work together here.
I'll be right there. I need to suture the blood vessel here.
- I can't, Irie-kun!
- Kotoko!
Change into scrubs now.
[ This drama is based on a fictional story ]
Mischievous Kiss 2: Love in Tokyo