THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
About yesterday.
Yesterday?
- Yeah, when we kissed.
- What?
I was so excited to see you again
that I couldn't even sleep at night.
Did you sleep well?
Is he serious?
Did you kiss him?
Yeah, I did.
But why should I have to admit it
in public like this?
Are you going to stand there?
We'd like to have a private conversation.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
EPISODE 5
What's the important thing
he wants to say? Is it...
I know we took a while,
but we found each other again.
- And we even kissed.
- I'm not the type
- to change my mind
- He sounds
- like he's about to ask me out.
- but will you work with me?
What should I say?
Should we start dating first,
then get to know each other?
Ui-yeong?
So, do you want to work with me?
Oh, do what together?
Eun-ho brought me this
along with my stuff yesterday.
DAD AND UNCLE
Oh, yeah, Sua is great at sketching.
What about it, though?
Well, she doodled
where she shouldn't have.
WOOD AND SPIRITS NIGHT
WHISKEY BRAND POP-UP PROPOSAL
The hotel's losing out on a lot
from this deal.
You guys offered whatever budget we needed
to follow the proposal.
And we loved the new idea
about making special suites
using our furniture from the pop-up.
This would smoothly introduce
our furniture to the guests.
Furniture makers are always thirsty
for a chance to prove
how sturdy their products are,
instead of just how pretty they are.
I'm sorry
for getting angry at you
instead of giving you a chance to explain.
Don't feel bad.
I'm so glad you've changed your mind.
I look forward to working with you.
- Me too.
- I'll contact the brand
to confirm the design
and schedule a kick-off meeting.
How's your schedule?
We'd like a meeting as soon as possible.
Let me check my schedule.
Sounds good. Let's see...
We're free on Monday at the earliest.
See you.
By the way
the ki...
The ki...
"Ki"?
Key ring! No, cream!
You have cream on your face.
Oh, here?
It must be the latte.
What I mean is...
You know...
The ki...
Oh, there's my key.
Ta-da!
Oh, sure.
See you around, then.
Bye.
Why do I have cream on my face
when I had a latte?
So
that's all he has to say about our kiss?
What was I even saying?
They kissed?
Wood is finicky.
It contracts or expands,
depending on temperature and humidity.
Sometimes, that causes faults
in furniture.
- What?
- Sorry?
What was that?
Oh, my point is
we offer free repairs for a year.
Yes.
I WANT TO GO TO YOUR HOUSE AFTER WORK
You have nothing to worry about.
Take your time
and look through the catalog.
I didn't know you were such a brave guy.
Everyone in heaven must be talking!
How could you kiss her inside a church?
I didn't think it through.
With the kiss and when I brought it up.
I did both because I wasn't thinking!
Good job.
Nothing seals the deal better than a kiss.
Now that you've sealed the deal
don't even think about running away.
- Be responsible...
- Uncle! Dad!
What? Were you listening?
My headphones don't have noise-canceling.
Sua
you know
Uncle kissed someone.
You know, like how we kiss.
You kissed her? So, you're dating now?
- Basically.
- That was a trick question.
You realize things are different now,
right?
A kiss doesn't mean you're committed.
Did you hurt her? Or break anything?
I think I'm broken.
No, you're not. You're just soft now.
That's what happens when you like someone.
Oh, good point.
I'd forgotten how it felt.
Congrats, Uncle. Falling for someone is
something to celebrate.
So, what's your plan now?
I'll work hard
and ask her out on a proper date.
Good luck!
Tell me if things go well.
And tell me if things don't go well.
You know we're always on your side, right?
You got it!
Sua, how do you know this so well?
Have you had a boyfriend?
I know you can hear me.
Promise me you'll ask me for permission
before dating anyone, okay?
Not that I'll ever let you date!
You don't have a boyfriend, right?
He's our Executive Director.
And they're HOME representatives.
I'm Song Tae-seop.
I'm Lee Eun-ho.
Everything's ready.
Here.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
It's been a minute, Mr. Kang.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I heard there was an incident
in the bidding process.
Thank you for giving us a second chance.
We understand.
I hope the two companies can now focus
on the project.
We don't hold grudges.
This is the theme for the pop-up.
Our motif is a local bar
showcasing Deerfiddich's heritage
and its perfect first sip
that hasn't changed in 100 years.
But we'll put a clean, modern twist
in the photo zone and the mini bar
which will lead to an exhibition
of the brand history.
Our goal is to provide an experience
to enjoy the whiskey with all senses.
In the second exhibition
we'll display whiskey
at different aging levels
and explain the charm at each level.
We look forward to working with you.
Try to support HOME
with everything they need.
- Yes, sir.
- Pleased to be working with you.
I asked my team
to make sure the food was extra good.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I'm so glad. Please enjoy it.
Mr. Song, why did you change your mind?
You didn't want to work with us.
It's all thanks to Ms. Lee.
Mr. Song always leaves out key details
and gives the wrong message.
He means that Ms. Lee's passion
changed our minds.
I've never seen anyone make towel animals
as well as she does!
Ms. Lee has a humorous way of working,
doesn't she?
For sure.
So, we'd like to keep her
as our main point of contact.
- Oh, well...
- Sure, if that's what you want.
I'll be in touch with Deerfiddich.
That'll be fine, as long as she keeps me
in the loop.
Okay.
Please let me know anytime
if you need anything.
Okay.
- Eat up.
- Yes, sir.
You'll need to set up the pop-up booth
and the guest suites simultaneously.
I'm worried about the tight schedule.
I know.
Since we're going to be too busy for now
do you want to go on a date
once the project's over?
A date?
Sorry, it's just that we're at work.
Right.
I don't think anyone heard me, thankfully.
So, is that a yes?
Yes.
"Cherry up!" "Get a grape on yourself."
"What are you even celery-brating?"
"Don't get so melon-cholic."
Sorry?
Look at the signs. They're so funny.
WHAT ARE YOU EVEN CELERY-BRATING?
GET A GRAPE ON YOURSELF
GOING BANANAS FOR ME YET?
Why don't we grab some coffee
before heading back?
Sounds good.
You know the chicken feet we had?
I keep thinking about them.
At first
I didn't even understand
how I was supposed to eat them.
People don't eat them outside Korea,
do they?
But there's no way out
once you get addicted to the spice.
Please invite me
to the Eat Eat Club again.
Will do.
We'd better head back.
I need to get some coffee for my team.
You can go first.
- Thanks for today.
- It's nothing.
- Hey, Ui-yeong.
- Hey, Hyun-min, I'm getting coffee
for you and Sae-byeok. What do you want?
Two iced Americanos, please.
Oh, and a sandwich, too.
Huh? Have you not had lunch yet?
I have, but not Sae-byeok.
She feels too guilty to have lunch.
Oh, really? Okay, I got it.
Did you just come to work?
Yeah, I work from 6 p.m. until closing
from Monday to Wednesday
and from 1 p.m. to 6 p.m.
on Thursdays and Fridays.
So
you're working
with the blind date guy now?
I didn't know it,
but his company participated in our bid.
What a coincidence, right?
Yeah, that's cool.
So, are you two dating now?
No, we're not there yet.
That's the spirit!
What are you, 20?
One kiss, and you're all his? No way.
I've had my fair share of kisses
maybe even 500 of them,
including those in plays.
Once you start overthinking it,
it leads to unnecessary feelings.
I could even kiss you right now.
What the hell are you doing?
And I know a kiss isn't everything
but it doesn't mean it's nothing.
What kind of a life have you lived
to think that?
I lived a pretty normal life.
How does it feel to ride a motorcycle?
It feels like you're cutting the world
with scissors.
"Cutting the world"?
You want a ride to see it for yourself?
Yeah, I'd love that! Next time.
BREAK ROOM
Your internship's over soon, right?
I just happened to see your contract.
Yeah, it's over in a month.
Let's be honest.
Working at a hotel feels fancy,
but the pay is so low.
Your starting salary is everything.
I have a close friend who's a banker.
He could give you some advice.
Why don't I introduce you to him?
I'll take care of it myself.
Okay.
Where are you, my lazy intern?
Come to the Conference Room.
I have to go. Ui-yeong is looking for me.
- Please excuse me.
- Okay.
You've been on a diet lately, haven't you?
What? No, I'm not.
Or is working here so hard
that you've lost your appetite?
It's okay. Work gets hard sometimes.
You learned a big lesson this time.
You must be so disappointed in me.
I can't be disappointed
from just one mistake.
It's time for you
to learn how much energy food gives you
even when you force it down.
Thank you.
Eat this, cheer up, and help me.
- Sorry?
- I want you
to back me up
on all tasks related to the pop-up.
Me?
But HOME wouldn't want to work with me.
If I were them, I would've liked you less
if you ran away after one mistake.
And I'd give another chance to someone
who tries to make up for it.
Ui-yeong!
You'll stay strong, right?
Yeah, I can do it!
Alright, who wants to go first?
Let me keep it short.
How many people do you think use cabinets
for their stuff at a hotel?
- Think of something more practical.
- Okay.
And you two need to check
the layout again first.
There's no space for big pieces.
I stayed up for multiple nights,
looking at the layout
and the suite is too small
with so many items already.
Mr. Song, this layout is like a canvas
that's already full.
I know it's not easy.
Let's wrap it up for today.
You can go home early and rest.
- Okay.
Man this is so heavy!
You can get the best prices
on the Internet!
Look up what you need,
list the items by price, order
and they'll arrive the next morning.
But I feel better
when I check the products myself.
I can check the expiration dates
and check on my good old friend
while I'm at it.
And make your friend a pack mule?
Thank you, friend.
So, how's working with your date?
Huh? Oh, the project?
All we do is work.
I want to message him first and all
but I know he's super busy, so I can't.
How nice would it be
for him to message me first?
- We even kissed...
- What did you say?
You kissed him? When?
Huh? Well...
It was just in the heat of the moment.
One thing led to another.
Are you going to lecture me?
No, who am I to do that?
You know the girl I sold my comics to?
What?
Never mind. It's nothing.
You want to work out?
I just worked out! And I'm exhausted.
This is my pay for the day.
- Bye.
- Get home safely. Thank you!
Bye.
- Huh?
- Ui-yeong
can we meet tomorrow?
What? He really messaged me.
Yeah, little pecks are great.
Pecks lead to kisses
and kisses...
It's rare to hit it off so well
on the first try.
Hmm?
I had to leave first because of work.
I've never had a man tidy my home
after a night together like that.
What did she just say?
I don't know.
- Hello.
- Yeah?
Do you have a minute?
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
It's your last personal training session.
Did you feel yourself get stronger
after the sessions?
I lost a pound or two.
But I can lose that much
just by going to the bathroom.
Losing a pound or two
with more muscle mass and less fat is
a huge achievement.
Now that you've built a good habit...
But I could really notice
the money leaving my account.
Gosh, my husband nags me about it
all the time!
Bring your husband next time, then.
I'll make sure he doesn't nag...
No, don't cause trouble in my family.
- You're getting a lot of messages.
- Sorry.
Goodbye!
Wait!
Hey...
What are you doing?
I'm sure you thought of me at least once.
You want to meet tonight?
No way.
Did she notice it?
I should've told her honestly!
That would've been less embarrassing.
BIG DISCOUNTS
I'm busy tonight.
What happened that night was a mistake.
Please don't get mad.
SOONMU PAY
SEND MONEY
SEND MONEY TO BIG DISCOUNTS
15,000 won.
SEND 15,000 WON TO BIG DISCOUNTS
Is that too much?
How about 10,000 won?
PLEASE ENTER YOUR PASSWORD
Could you check this equipment?
Coming!
YOU RECEIVED 10,000 WON
Did he just send me money? Is he crazy?
This son of a...
Is his brain made of mush or what?
This moron!
You're dead!
Hello, Deukgeun Deukgeun Gym.
Sorry?
Isn't this Mr. Lim Seung-jun's number?
Yeah, that's me. Who is this?
We're calling from Soonmu Market.
Did you recently sell comic books?
The buyer just filed a report against you.
Did you make inappropriate comments
and scam the buyer?
Sorry?
WHY THE HELL DID YOU SEND ME MONEY?
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
AM I A JOKE TO YOU?
JUST BECAUSE I SLEPT WITH YOU?
ANSWER ME, YOU JERK! WHAT ARE YOU, SCARED?
Oh, gosh.
YOU WANT ME TO BREAK YOUR NECK?
What's all this?
- Ui-yeong!
- Yeah?
This is the list of sample whiskies
and recipes for the pop-up.
Okay.
Sae-byeok, have you found a bartender?
Yes, I have.
I'll e-mail his profile to you.
- Alright.
- Perfect.
Ms. Big Discounts,
I didn't mean to offend you.
I'd like to apologize to you.
Do you have time today?
So, he wants to fight in person?
- The comic book seller?
- Yeah.
Turns out, he's the biggest scumbag!
Absolute garbage.
- The comic books?
- No, the seller.
It's like he slept
through sex ed, literature
and when his mom taught him manners.
I'll teach you a lesson today.
SONG TAE-SEOP
Hi, Mr. Song.
Right now?
Oh, you'll come to the office?
Is this the only cafe around here?
Here are your drinks.
- Thank you.
Do you have a girlfriend?
It's a secret.
- Tell us!
- Come on.
She brought us both here today.
Come three more times. I'll do that.
- Man!
- That's so mean.
- Three more times?
- Hello...
You're here. Again.
Yeah.
I didn't know the barista had favorites
among customers here.
What do you know? I'm only human.
I'm less glad to see some than others.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Four iced Americanos to go, please.
Sorry about my white lie last time.
You know I'm not her cousin, right?
Yeah, but I don't care.
Choose chocolate.
Ui-yeong likes chocolate.
I'll get the carrot cake instead, then.
This is for a big group.
The chocolate cake is on the house.
The cake is just for the two of us.
But I won't say no to extra cake.
Hello.
- Mr. Song!
- Hello.
Hello!
You even brought us cake!
- Thank you.
Why don't we head right up?
Oh, sure.
I'll be back.
Okay. Bye!
Is something wrong?
I'm in a bit of a pickle.
I think talking to you might help.
Oh, sure. What is it?
There's not much space for your pieces.
No, we're trying to come up
with different ideas
but nothing's perfect for the suite.
What can we do?
Let's run a simulation, then.
Okay, I've checked in, and I'm walking in.
I'm looking around the room,
and taking a photo first.
Maybe a selfie. Then
I'll go...
- right to the bed!
- What?
I'll roll around this way
and that way.
I'll become one with the bed.
I'll even watch TV from here.
Oh, you're that type.
Then, I only get up
when I'm hungry.
Tae-seop, how about we incorporate the bed
into the design?
- Incorporate the bed?
- Yeah.
Maybe a tray?
You can use that in bed.
Oh.
Oh!
- How about a tray table?
- A tray table?
I used to have this set up on my bed
and ate food on it and even drew pictures.
I see.
That sounds like a great idea.
It won't take up too much space
and it'll go well with whiskey.
- Yeah.
We should choose a dark shade
for the comforter
so that stains don't show
if anyone spills anything.
I'll work with the tray table idea
and design something.
- Here.
- Yes!
Eui-yeong.
Is she not here?
I thought she was showing him the suite.
Where is she?
Eui-yeong?
Is she in a different suite?
Gosh.
You're off soon, right?
Yeah.
I'll drive you home.
SEASONS OF US
"Seasons of Us" must be back in theaters!
"Seasons of Us"? Is it good?
You haven't watched it?
It got 10 million views!
I watched it three times
because I love that actress.
I see.
I should check it out for sure.
- Tae-seop.
- Yeah?
We got our idea today
so we're done with all the big tasks,
aside from setting up the pop-up.
Yeah?
You want to watch a movie that night
maybe after we set it up?
That movie's really good.
It'd be a shame to miss it again.
Sure, let's get a nice dinner
before that, too.
What's your favorite food?
- I like...
- Yeah?
pretty much everything.
I'm not picky at all.
It's going to be so much fun.
Did you just get off work?
- You must've had a long day...
- Whatever.
This is your last chance.
Think before you speak.
I'm sorry for not understanding you.
I'm just very inexperienced in this field.
Is this enough?
You bastard.
I told you it was your last chance,
didn't I?
Didn't I tell you?
- Did I not?
- Wait! Let's talk it out!
- You jerk!
- Use your words!
- It's not that expensive!
- What?
Who are you to decide how much I am?
Hold up.
Decide how much what is?
I didn't know that was for the torn book.
I had no idea.
What do you take me for?
I'm a personal trainer.
I don't eat fried food.
This body took a lot of work.
Sure, you need to protect your gains.
I'm Jung Hyun-min, 30,
and I work at an office.
Just a question,
why did you clean the house that night?
Wait.
It's even weirder
if only the books are put away.
I thought it'd look weirder
if only the books were put away.
So, I just cleaned it all...
You can eat this, right?
I'm good at stripping, you know?
Do you become uninterested in someone
after you have sex with them?
No!
Gosh.
I'm glad.
I really like you.
What do you think about me?
Are you really asking that
after what's happened?
Yeah, we now know
it was a misunderstanding
and we'll be warmed up soon.
And we can eat fried chicken
without fighting over the legs.
How can it get better than this?
Give me a chance, okay?
Mr. Song, you're coming
to set up the pop-up, right?
MR. SONG, YOU'RE COMING
TO SET UP THE POP-UP, RIGHT?
Yeah, see you soon.
Hey, watch out.
Hey!
- Stop destroying everything.
- Okay.
Why are you wearing a white shirt
on the set-up day?
- No, this is good!
- What?
You know the prof from Hannam-dong
who requested a kids' desk?
He asked if we could move the meeting
to tonight.
But I have to take Sua to the doctor,
so you have to take over.
What? No, I have to be at the hotel.
He's our regular. Make time for him.
It's because of his kid's tutoring.
Delay your dinner plans
until after the meeting.
Tell him to come
as soon as possible, then.
Jin-su!
- Yeah?
- I'll go after the meeting.
Please tell the hotel.
And send me photo updates.
- Photos?
- Yeah.
That intern is like Ui-yeong.
She's a wolf in sheep's clothing.
She looks kind,
but inside, she's real picky.
You're rich with a new car
and an expensive taste for drinks now.
How come your taste in women
hasn't changed?
You think so?
Stop wasting time on someone
who won't give you a chance.
I have ladies lined up to meet you.
You sure you don't want to return
to the law firm?
Okay, let's go! One, two, three.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Did Mr. Song come with you?
Oh, he couldn't make it.
He had a client meeting.
Did he not tell you?
Oh, maybe.
- No, he didn't.
- He must've forgotten.
He forgets all the time.
I see.
Which floor should we take these to?
All of this is for the lobby.
This way, please.
Be careful.
Take your time.
- There? Okay.
- Yeah.
You can just help with the lighter stuff.
I guess I was a little too ambitious.
- Let me help.
- Okay.
- This is heavier than I thought.
- Yeah.
This way.
So, she has no issues
receiving help from anyone else.
- See you tomorrow at 6 p.m.
- Okay!
- Hello.
- Ready to order?
- Yeah.
I'll take 10 iced Americano, hot.
I'll also take another 10, cold.
And one hot chocolate.
And I'll take all the desserts.
- All the desserts?
- Yeah.
Ji-su!
- Come again.
- Goodnight.
Sir
are you going somewhere close?
Yeah, The Hills Hotel.
My crush is working late today.
Oh, the hotel?
You can just put them here.
Oh, sure.
Alright, then.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh? Why are you here?
- Just making a delivery.
- You deliver?
Just for the day. You? Working late?
Oh, it's for the event
I mentioned last time.
Everyone, have some coffee!
- Do-hyun?
- Have some coffee.
Sae-byeok! Over here.
Mr. Kang?
What are you doing here?
I got coffee for everyone
because you were working late.
But I got you hot chocolate
because it's nighttime.
Wait. Let me see which one it is.
- Just a sec!
- I'm fine...
Why didn't the barista label them?
Did I ever ask you
to do this for me?
No, right?
I'll be right back.
Do-hyun.
Talk to her tomorrow.
Our partnering company is here, too.
Can't I at least get you coffee?
If she feels uncomfortable about it
you need to give her space.
You're responsible for this, too.
- What?
- Don't you owe me an apology?
For what?
Sae-byeok would've taken me seriously
if it weren't for you.
Why...
Why did you suddenly decide
that you liked me and get in my way?
Oh, I...
This is...
Bye.
I'll take these back.
Wait!
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
- It burns!
- I'll take you to the hospital.
Bring something to wipe it with.
Gosh, what do we do?
Mr. Kang.
You seem to be badly mistaken
but this isn't about Ui-yeong.
People like you
who think their feelings are
the only ones that matter
make me feel so uncomfortable.
You make me uncomfortable.
No, I can't stand you.
Not even as a friend or a coworker.
So, please
stop trying to win me over.
Put that back up, too!
Jin-su
- call Mr. Song.
- Okay.
Sorry, I'm late. Something came up,
but I'm on my way now.
THERE'S BEEN A BIG ACCIDENT
There's been a big accident.
We need you to come here.
What happened?
Thankfully, it's not a big burn.
Okay, thank you.
- Here's the receipt.
- Okay.
Don't you know you have to make sure
not even water touches them?
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Your employees did nothing but work hard.
No, it's not your fault.
There was a bit of an accident.
Let's use a dark oil
to finish the surface again.
For all the pieces?
Yeah, to match the colors.
Hurry. Let's get it done tonight.
- Yes, sir.
Roll it on like this.
Oh, I...
I'll have to return to the hotel.
With that hand? You sure?
I think I left my phone at the hotel
and everyone must be busy
fixing the furniture.
I need to check on them.
Call them and ask first.
Oh, okay.
Is this dark enough?
Go over this area again.
Mr. Song is here to take care of it.
Oh, he came.
Yeah, it's almost done
so don't come to the hotel.
Go home and rest.
It must've really hurt. I'm so sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
I'll just go home, then. See you tomorrow.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Let's go home.
But there's a place we have to go
before that.
Oh, I was too shocked to ask earlier
but why do you have two helmets?
One for you, and one for me.
You said you wanted a ride one day.
This is so refreshing.
What?
It's so refreshing!
I feel so refreshed now!
Ms. Lee tried to stop him
and he started blaming her for everything
in front of everyone.
What does this mean?
A love triangle.
There's no way.
Think about it. Mr. Kang likes Ms. Sim
and Ms. Lee is in his way.
That means they either dated
or had a fling.
You know nothing. You've never even dated.
Even so, I can tell
they don't look good together.
Over there. That's the lawyer.
Just a sec.
Are you Mr. Song Tae-seop?
Mr. Kang?
Do you have a minute to talk?
What do you want to say?
If it's about the furniture,
it was something out of my control...
Yeah, I'm mad about that,
but that's being taken care of.
And if things go wrong,
I can ask the hotel for compensation
since it's very clear who's at fault.
You wrote the contract,
so you must know what's in it.
Are you blackmailing me?
That's a violation of Article 283...
Not sure if this is blackmailing
but I like Ui-yeong.
- What?
- She's important to me
so please watch your mouth.
So, this is about Ui-yeong?
Watch your words, actions, and thoughts.
All of them.
SORRY, I'M LATE. SOMETHING CAME UP,
BUT I'M ON MY WAY NOW.
SONG TAE-SEOP
Huh?
SONG TAE-SEOP, EUI-YEONG
Man, what is this?
Isn't it just ordinary ramyeon?
Why is it so good?
Because the view is extraordinary.
Doesn't it just soothe your soul?
I'm so full now.
Did you like that lawyer guy, too?
Do you fall that easily?
It's not like that. He was just...
a quick crush.
You have a horrible taste in men.
Don't trust the guy you kissed, either.
Where is he
when your hand is all bandaged?
He's the CEO. He must be busy.
You must be tired, too.
You worked all day, right?
Is working at the cafe okay?
I'm sure you can make more money
in movies or dramas.
I don't want to chase money with acting.
I do it out of love.
Yeah. You can do what you love
and earn money.
And wouldn't it be nice to get famous?
But there will be consequences.
I'd have to give up moments like this.
I see.
This view soothes me...
more than any fame or money.
I see.
Thank you.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Thanks for working until so late.
It was nothing.
Thanks so much for your help.
Oh, this...
What was that?
It's nothing.
Your arms and shoulders will be sore.
Give yourself a good massage.
Okay, thanks for all your help.
- Good work.
- Thanks.
They say tears take away sadness.
Does the wind take away anger?
All my anger's gone with the wind.
Call me when you want to cruise.
And you know,
I make cocktails at the cafe at night.
Visit me. I'll give you freebies.
Here. Give me your number.
Huh?
What brings you here?
You left your phone at the hotel.
Oh, I was going to get it tomorrow.
Thanks.
Can we talk? Just for a sec.
Oh...
I'll talk to him and head in.
You can go first.
- Thanks for today.
- Sure.
What happened to your arm?
Did you see a doctor about it?
I got a burn from the coffee spill,
but it's nothing bad.
Sae-byeok told me
you sorted things out at the hotel.
Thank you.
This wouldn't have happened
if I'd just come sooner.
But you couldn't.
You know
I was waiting for you.
Sorry.
I won't be late
or make you wait again.
Do you have any photos of the pop-up?
- You want to see some?
- Yeah.
- Here.
- Wow!
That's even better than what I imagined.
It's nice, right?
I got home safely.
Rest well.
- Hyun-min, is everything ready?
- What?
Yeah, I think so.
- Ui-yeong!
- Hey.
The bartender we hired just called
and he can't come. His family is unwell.
- What?
- On the day of the event?
Yeah...
But we have to have a bartender!
What should we do?
Oh, wait. I can fix this.
The pieces you made are perfect
for our hotel.
This octagon tray table is my favorite.
Thanks.
I heard you came up
with the tray table idea with Ms. Song.
You two have great teamwork.
Thank you.
And the suites will be opened
to the brand reps and VIP guests
as a tester first
fixed as needed,
then be open to all guests.
And we'll collect all orders
from the pop-up on a list
and have Ui-yeong send it to you.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thanks.
And here.
This is a small gift
for all of your team's hard work.
- My gosh.
- Wow!
They're going to be so happy.
Yeah.
This room is for you, Mr. Song.
You can rest up until I call you
in time for the pop-up event.
- Okay, thank you.
- See you.
I couldn't find anything else,
so I just got our uniform and a tie.
Yeah? It's okay, there's nothing else.
- We did our best.
- Yeah.
How do I look?
Are the sleeves too short?
We've hired a bartender
to make the drinks for tonight.
That's amazing.
If you buy one or two bottles...
As you can see...
DEERFIDDICH
Here you go.
Hey!
My wrists are dying.
I said I'd make cocktails for you.
When did I say I'd make some for everyone?
I promise to repay you for it.
Did that Tae-seop guy
really build all this?
Yeah, impressive, right?
Oh? Tae-seop!
Hey, Ui-yeong.
You want a drink?
No, I'm fine.
Have you looked around?
Yeah, it looks incredible.
And the brand reps seem very satisfied.
I'm so glad.
- If you have time...
- Mr. Song!
Could you say hi to those guests?
Oh, sure.
- Just a sec.
- Okay.
Look, it's Son Jeong-a!
What's she doing here?
The brand is the main sponsor
for the Geumsang Arts Awards.
This is unbelievable. She's stunning!
She's my favorite actress.
How's she an actress?
She doesn't even act anymore.
She's just an influencer now.
Did you see that? She winked at me!
You saw her winking at me, right?
Hi!
- Here you are.
- Yeah.
You seem busy,
introducing yourself to everyone.
I know.
But I think I'm good for now.
Yeah, everything went well,
all thanks to you.
- Ui-yeong.
- Yeah?
About what we couldn't do last time.
Are you free today...
- Ms. Lee!
- Yes!
Some people don't seem to know
about the afterparty today.
You sure you announced it?
- Oh, right.
- Come on.
What about you?
Oh, I don't drink, so...
We're going to the cafe by the hotel.
Please join us with your team.
I don't drink,
but I always attend afterparties.
That's a proper way to finish a project,
after all.
- Join us, then.
- Okay, see you later.
You promised!
That was great.
- Great work.
- You, too.
- Hello.
- Good work.
- You, too.
- This way!
- Hi!
- Have a seat.
- Great work!
- Welcome!
- Good job.
- Have a seat.
- Come.
Okay.
How are you everywhere?
I'm where I'm supposed to be.
Have you maybe considered
that you're the one intruding?
I work for these afterparties.
You can sit there.
Mr. Song!
- This way.
- No...
I already saved a seat for you.
Have a drink.
- No, I...
- Join me first.
- Sit with them later.
- Great work today.
You, too.
- Come on.
- Where's Mr. Lee?
He couldn't make it.
He had to watch his daughter.
- Thank you.
Alright.
- So, you want a glass?
- No, I don't drink.
Okay, just fill it
for the sake of raising it.
Here comes your drink
- Chug!
- Thank you
Ji-su, join us.
- Can you?
- Come here.
Alright.
A glass for you, Na-ri.
We need to drink on a day like this.
Let's see...
- I'll pour for you.
- Okay.
- Good work.
- You, too.
Everyone, fill your glasses!
Take good care of yourselves,
and see you again in a new project!
- Cheers!
- Good work!
- Great job.
- You, too.
- Good work.
Oh, no, the drink tastes sweet.
I'm screwed.
I'm starving.
- What does the bunny say?
- Bunny!
- Carrot!
Hold up, where's Mr. Kang?
I doubt that he's coming.
How would you know that?
Just have a drink.
Let's all raise our glasses without her!
- Sounds good!
- Let's go!
- Cheers!
So, Ji-su, what are you? A bartender?
Oh! He's actually an actor.
- Really?
- No way!
I worked a lot of part-time jobs
while acting on stage, and here I am.
Really?
No wonder you have that aura.
Do you have a fandom?
If not, I'll be the leader.
- My gosh!
- Really?
No, just be my audience.
I'll invite everyone here to my show.
Promise me you'll come.
- Sounds good!
- I'd love that!
Promise me!
- Okay!
- Cheers!
- You have to keep your word.
- Of course.
Oh, not yet.
We have to go!
- Let's go!
- Come on.
Everyone has to come!
- Keep drinking!
- Chug!
Do you drive on the Gangbyeonbuk-ro
if you live in that area?
Do you usually...
Mr. Kang... Where's Mr. Kang?
You can't drink
more than two bottles of soju.
How many fingers am I holding up?
How did you end up with six fingers?
Wait.
I need some fresh air.
Be careful.
I'll be right back.
I...
Tae-seop.
Tae-seop?
Are you okay?
No, I'm not.
I feel...
- like I'm going crazy.
- Oh, no.
Let me get you a hangover drink.
Just wait here, okay?
No, don't leave me.
- What?
- You're so close to me
yet I can't reach you.
That drives me crazy.
You can't go.
I didn't know you were so cute
when you got drunk.
Tae-seop.
I'm not going anywhere.
You don't have to hold my hand so tight.
Okay.
But Ui-yeong
do you still want to go on a date with me?
Yeah.
I do.
Then...
you want to go...
for another drink, just the two of us?
Right now?
Sure.
Let me just grab my purse.
Stay right here, okay?
Don't go anywhere. Stay right here, okay?
I'll be right back!
Tae-seop!
Oh?
You can't sleep here!
Wake up, Tae-seop.
It's not safe to sleep out here!
You said we'd go for another drink!
What's this?
Where am I?
Hold up. What's going on?
Why is the duvet black?
No.
No way. Did I sleep with him?
Did we do it?
What are you doing?
What? What are you doing there?
- Oh, gosh!
- Oh!
What is...
going on?
Oh, I...
I don't really know, either
but it looks like we're screwed.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
YOU WANT TO GO ON A DATE WITH ME?
THAT WAS TOO STRONG
DOES THE WIND TAKE AWAY ANGER?
NO, DON'T LEAVE ME
According to the witnesses
there wasn't just one man
but two!
I must've been out of my mind.
I'm not the type to be
all up in anyone's business
but I can't stop being nosy around you.
You're always so weirdly close.
What do you think about the rumor?
Is it... Ji-su?
So, he knows Jeong-a?
There's a 46% chance of rain.
I've never seen a guy prepare so much
for a date.
You look like a virgin.
Do you even know how to get a chance?
A virgin?
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim