THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
Blind dates usually take place
on weekend afternoons
and last about 2.5 hours on average.
The appropriate distance
between first dates is 45cm.
It feels like too much
if you're any closer
but doesn't feel heart-fluttering
if you're any farther.
And it doesn't take 1 or 5 minutes
to fall in love.
It only takes five seconds.
An expert says everything's decided
within five seconds.
I ticked all of the above on this date
and things were going smoothly.
Until he asked me this.
Ui-yeong
how do you feel about dating me
with marriage in mind?
Did you just say "marriage"?
Yeah, I want to date to get married.
We're not young.
I'd like to have a serious relationship...
- Oh, gosh!
- Oh, no.
- What do I do? Oh, no!
- Are you okay?
- Here.
- Thank you.
Oh, no...
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Darn it.
Who said wearing bright colors
on a blind date was a good idea?
"Marriage"?
I've known him for only 30 minutes.
How can I be thinking about marriage?
I scrubbed it as hard as I could,
but the stain won't come out.
You'll ruin the fabric
if you scrub it too hard.
That might lead to a permanent stain.
Really?
This is one of my favorite dresses...
Man.
You should go home
and throw it in the washing machine
after a salt soak and a sugar soak.
Soy sauce is water-soluble,
so it should come out.
I see.
We should probably call it a night.
I guess.
Sorry about today.
You barely ate, did you?
We can eat next time.
"Next time"?
I parked my car nearby.
I can drive you home.
We can talk more...
No, I can go home by myself.
I don't want to cause you more trouble.
Okay, then. Get home safely.
How's the blind date going?
You're heading for drinks now, right?
Why does he have to know it all?
I'm heading home.
You can't leave me on read!
Focus on your date,
and if you like the guy
send the Sun emoji.
Hmm? That's Tae-seop.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
EPISODE 2
Your date brought an imported car
on his first date?
- How about this one?
- Huh?
I don't think that's the one.
How should I describe it?
It was, like, a white dolphin?
- A dolphin?
- Yeah.
No way.
How about this?
It's about 100 million won for a new one.
100 million?
Yeah, it kind of looked like it.
But maybe not.
What could it be?
And you're sure it's not an SUV?
Yeah.
Aren't SUVs big? With four wheels?
You dumb? All cars have four wheels.
Yeah?
Just take a photo of his car
next time you see him.
Why didn't I do that this time?
You might as well tell him to bring
his income tax records.
I wonder if your date is also judging you
by the purse you wore that day
in his fancy car.
You're my mom.
You're not supposed to roast me like that.
I'm not judging him. I'm just curious.
I'm just saying
you need to be ready to be judged
if you're signing yourself up
on blind dates now.
But wouldn't you prefer her dating
a guy with a fancy car?
A fancy car can't be bad.
- And a guy with a fancy car can't be bad.
- Exactly!
His whole family could be rich
or he could be
a self-made young and rich man.
Or he could be car poor.
Car poor?
No, he wasn't the type to flaunt his car.
You were so judgmental about me
not dating anyone.
Why are you so eager to stop me now?
Did I judge you? No, you judged yourself.
And he asked you about getting married
on the first date.
He just sounds plain dumb.
Introduce each other to your families
and send out wedding invitations now.
That'll surely make a year fly by.
Your dates would be so much fun.
Come on! She had a good date.
- Stop it.
- Stop it!
Whatever.
So, when are you seeing him next?
No idea. He hasn't called yet.
He still hasn't asked you out
on a second date?
No.
I see.
He hasn't called or texted you yet.
Don't call or text him first.
It'll show how desperate you are.
Why are you still here? It's late.
Stop with those snacks.
Gosh.
Why did we even look up his car?
There's no time limit
on asking someone out again.
AVERAGE TIME IT TAKES TO BE ASKED OUT
ON A SECOND DATE
Second date...
I HAD A BLIND DATE,
AND HE HASN'T CALLED ME YET
HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE
FOR A GUY TO ASK YOU OUT ON A SECOND DATE?
WITHIN TWO DAYS?
IF HE REALLY LIKES YOU,
HE'LL ASK YOU OUT AT THE END OF THE DATE
DON'T THEY USUALLY ASK YOU OUT
BEFORE THE DATE IS OVER?
BY THE NEXT DAY, AT THE LATEST
BEFORE GOING HOME AFTER THE FIRST DATE!
I'D ALSO SAY ON THE DAY OF
Excuse me.
I was wondering who it was.
Did you get a new car?
No, it's the company car.
I just drive it all the time.
When did you get here?
Don't tell me you were here all night
on a Saturday.
No, I came after sunrise.
I heard the lumber came in.
Yeah, we got the shipment.
But it's not on display yet.
Did you come early just to make me work?
I'll help you.
The lines are beautiful.
Can I use this?
Of course. That's your pay.
Mark whatever you want.
- Okay!
- Are you joining us for lunch?
No, I have to go somewhere.
Can I use the shower here?
BATHROOM, SHOWER, BREAK ROOM
Hey.
- Man!
- What now?
Sua is making her debut
as a flower girl today.
She absolutely hates the outfit I picked
that took me hours of research
on little girls' wedding outfits...
The more you try to make it look like
you didn't pick my outfit
the tackier it looks, alright?
I was in charge of your outfits,
even when your mom was around!
She never had a better taste than I did!
Hey.
Sua, don't be so mean to your dad.
And you look great in that dress.
Well, I'm just a good model.
I can rock anything.
But is that the best you can do?
- Hmm?
- Button it up all the way
and fix your hair.
Come closer.
- Hey!
- All done.
Let's go.
You look stunning.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Please look here.
One, two, three!
- Congratulations!
- See you later.
- Come here. Hurry!
- No.
- Why not?
- You're busy.
We'll just wait outside.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you!
Can't believe they're getting married
- after dating for 14 years.
- I know, right?
You know, they probably broke up
like a dozen times.
Hey, our graduation photo!
Hyun-ju is in it, too.
Her eyes look so naive and pure here.
Who would've known
she'd leave you so heartlessly
just six years later?
Do you see her?
You don't want to see the photo?
- Catch the bouquet for me.
- See you.
You're looking at her, alright.
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't she say Hyun-ju was coming?
She might as well make us sit
at the same table as her.
Hello, I'm a friend of the groom
- and today's host.
- What a seating arrangement.
I guess you're still friends from college,
even after the breakup.
Hyun-ju, I heard you're getting married
this year.
Are you catching the bouquet today?
Yeah, I agreed to catch it.
The plan is to get married this year.
I'm happy for you.
Did you hear about his chair being sold
at an art fair for 13 million won?
- Really?
The first two years
after starting the company were rough.
He had no clients and no money.
All he had were his people to rely on
and someone was heartless enough
to leave him.
Eun-ho.
No time is lonelier than others.
Don't you make your wife lonely at times,
Eun-ho?
Hey, watch your mouth.
You started it. Cut it out.
Please welcome our flower girl, Sua.
Did I?
Come in, Sua!
Look here!
Sua! Good girl!
You look beautiful! Right on!
Look this way! You look stunning!
My gosh! Who's this pretty girl?
Tae-seop.
Why didn't you say anything at all?
One, two, three!
- It's been a minute.
- Exactly.
When your girlfriend of years leaves you
you're supposed to beg her to reconsider
or wish her best or worst in life.
You were supposed to say something.
Anything.
I wasn't mature enough
for a mature breakup with someone I loved.
I just shut up and focused on work,
despite wanting to stay in denial
and years just flew by.
So
how are you now?
One, two, three!
I'm great.
I thought you'd go bankrupt
and have your father
hand his business to you.
I wanted to see you one day.
Congratulations on your wedding.
And you? Are you seeing anyone?
I haven't heard any updates.
You're frustrating to date.
You can only focus on one thing at a time.
I...
went on a blind date.
- What?
- Let's go!
- Go!
- Isn't that Hyun-ju's bouquet?
- Tae-seop! Eun-ho!
- We congratulated her enough!
Run! Let's go!
68 HOURS SINCE THE FIRST DATE
Yu-been and Woo-hyuk,
make sure you get good shots
- of our work for the Design Awards.
- Got it.
You're going to Jeju
for the presentation, right?
The roastery owner is
really looking forward to it.
Yeah, I have some technical things
to explain.
I'm leaving tomorrow evening.
Okay, go with Jin-su.
I'll book the flights and the hotel.
- Next, the boutiques!
- Yes.
- The design was in on Monday.
- And confirmed on Thursday.
Okay, dismissed!
- Come here.
- What?
When are you going to tell me
about your date?
So, is she pretty?
That's adorable!
It's a pup.
- They look alike.
- You love this one!
So, is she pretty?
- Come on.
- Is it a secret?
I guess so.
I can't believe
I'm watching you start dating again!
Tell me you paid for the dinner
and drove her home.
Oh, well...
What now? You're scaring me.
Did you ask her out again?
Oh, I'm too busy this week.
Maybe I'll text her next week.
You can see her next week,
but you still have to ask her out soon.
Give me your phone.
- I'll do it for you.
- No, I'll do it after work.
You can go home now, then. Go.
Leave already! Why are you still here?
I'm home.
You need to take better care of yourself
since you live alone.
Oh, man...
Why can't I move?
My phone...
90 HOURS SINCE THE FIRST DATE
MEETING FOR NEW SUMMER BINGSU
Darn it.
He still hasn't texted me.
Why is Ui-yeong zoning out all day?
Maybe her blind date didn't go well.
She went on a blind date?
I thought she wasn't interested
in dating at all!
Did I say "blind date"? No!
Can we check the schedule first?
Na-ri!
I hear the hotel's pride
- depends on the summer bingsu items.
- Yes.
We're aiming for a fine-dining quality.
We'll only use the best-quality melons.
With that said,
we've prepared a blind test.
It's too sweet.
It's nice.
MELON PROFILE ANALYSIS
It's tasty, and the smell...
Isn't it good?
- This is even sweeter.
- Yeah!
For sure.
But this smells better.
HONEYDEW
CANTALOUPE, WHITE DREAM
HONEY ONE, NOEUL, MUSK
Musk smells nice and is tasty,
but it's not special.
Noeul isn't as fragrant
but it tastes like pumpkin
and has a deep, sweet taste.
Honey One has great characteristics,
but it's not in season.
White Dream is sweet enough
but not crisp enough.
Cantaloupes have the best balance.
- Purchasing, please look for suppliers.
- Okay.
Let's test the recipes
when the cantaloupes arrive.
- Okay.
- Yes, Chef.
I can't wait.
Me neither.
He hasn't picked up his phone all day.
Is he out for lunch?
Bo-yoon and Joon-hyung
- Yes?
- Where's Tae-seop?
He didn't have lunch with us.
We haven't seen him all day, have we?
Is he spontaneously skipping work?
Tae-seop?
He never missed a day of school
until college.
He only gets sick during breaks.
Tae-seop! You in there?
Eun-ho! Hey!
Hey, are you inside?
Hey! Open the door!
I can't. Open it yourself.
I'll give you my password.
It's 2-6-2-1.
2-1?
- It's 2-6-2-1!
- What?
Is it 2-6 or 1-6?
2-6-2-1, you idiot.
Tae-seop!
- Tae-seop!
- Yeah.
- Don't shake me.
Hey!
Why would you throw water at me?
I answered you.
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't shake me!
- What's wrong?
- Help me up.
- Let's get you to a doctor!
- Help me up slowly.
Is it really bad?
Well...
- It's a pinched muscle.
- What?
A pinched muscle?
But he can't even move.
He was on the floor like that
the whole day!
In oriental medicine
we say 9 out of 10 illnesses come
from a badly-pinched muscle.
Take it seriously.
Get some acupuncture before you go.
You definitely live alone.
Yeah, I do.
Even adults need guardians.
Save your friend's number
as the emergency contact on your phone
and share your doorlock password with him.
Live alone, die alone.
You look so drained.
You sure you can go to Jeju?
We can just send Jin-su.
I have to go.
I feel a bit better after the acupuncture.
Live alone, die alone.
Whoops.
Excuse me!
It's so nice to have a girls-only night!
Come on. Spill it.
Any issues you're having?
Right, you!
I hear Mr. Kang from Legal asked you out.
Looks like you won't learn much
other than love here.
What? I have no interest in dating.
Why not? Give him a chance.
Don't waste all your years
rejecting everyone
and end up like her.
Huh? What?
You've been looking at your phone all day.
I heard you went on a blind date.
You're waiting for a second date!
If he still hasn't texted you,
it means he's not into you.
You know, I met my husband
on a blind date, too.
Does that apply to all men?
Yeah, every single one.
You want me to set you up
with a really great guy?
He graduated from a top university
and did his Master's
right after graduation.
Then, he got his PhD in the US.
He works for S Electronics now
where he was offered a job
for a few hundred million won.
A few hundred million?
That was three years ago.
I bet he makes even more now!
He's not interested in partying
or seeing a lot of women.
He's a rare gem.
If he's that great
why is he still single?
You know nerds, right?
He spent all his years studying,
so he just lacks social skills.
And he's not that handsome.
So, he's ugly.
- Don't tell me looks matter to you.
- They do.
I'm not really picky about a guy's face
but I notice it first in strangers.
You'll get used to his face soon enough!
Let's be real. You're not on his level.
You can't meet a guy like that!
We may look good on the outside,
but don't have much else going for us.
Just give him a chance.
I'll give you his number.
Wait.
Let me wait a bit longer and let you know.
Sure, go ahead.
Let me know, then.
And didn't we call the server?
I love this place,
but the servers are so lazy.
Excuse me!
Thank you.
Ui-yeong.
Am I too desperate for him to text me?
I feel like I can even see him now.
What are you doing here?
Did you drink? You're all red.
I had a staff dinner tonight.
I guess you're going somewhere.
Oh, I have a work trip.
I'm heading to the airport.
I see.
Once I come back...
Tae-seop
did you go on another blind date?
What?
No, nobody has set me up since.
I see.
Someone has offered to set me up.
Should I say no to that?
That's...
not for me to decide.
You can say yes if you want.
Right.
I shouldn't have asked you.
You can go, then.
Wait.
I'll text you after I get back.
"Text me"?
The stain is really gone!
Perfect.
SONG TAE-SEOP
I washed the dress as you told me to
and the stain is completely gone.
I'm not just thanking him.
I'm also fishing for a second date.
It felt like we were meant to be
when I ran into him last night.
I WASHED THE DRESS AS YOU TOLD ME TO,
AND THE STAIN IS COMPLETELY GONE
He'll read it, right?
111 HOURS SINCE THE FIRST DATE
SONG TAE-SEOP
I WASHED THE DRESS AS YOU TOLD ME TO,
AND THE STAIN IS COMPLETELY GONE
Was he just being nice?
And I just fell for it?
- That's stunning!
- It looks so fancy.
This is my thank-you
for getting the great cantaloupes.
Can we eat it, then?
- Of course.
- Let's dig in.
Here.
It's so pretty!
Alright.
It's so sweet and juicy!
The cantaloupes were so good.
Marketing is itching to start selling it
- so order more cantaloupes for us.
- Okay.
It's out of this world.
- Right?
- Yeah, it's incredible.
Do you think it'll sell?
I haven't seen bingsu cost 130,000 won,
not even at a hotel.
If you think about what goes in here
the price isn't that ridiculous.
And people like splurging on dates,
anyway.
Let's trust the chef and go for it.
- Okay.
Hi, I'm Lee Jeong-u.
I got your number from Na-ri.
Are you free this Saturday?
I'd love to meet.
I said I'd let her know
if Tae-seop didn't ask me out.
But even she can already tell
it's over between us by now.
CHATS
I WASHED THE DRESS AS YOU TOLD ME TO,
AND THE STAIN IS COMPLETELY GONE
But it's a bit rude
that he hasn't even read my message.
HI, I'M LEE JEONG-U
Saturday sounds fine by me.
Where should we meet?
I'm not interested, either, alright?
DATE WITH LEE JEONG-U AT 6 P.M.
APRIL 2025
MELON PROFILE ANALYSIS
Looks and personality matter.
LOOKS
Personality...
And...
I'd prefer someone who won't be lazy
about going on dates on holidays.
Does that mean he needs good energy?
Or, he has to be fit.
FITNESS, LOOKS, PERSONALITY
And money.
We need to have similar spending patterns.
FITNESS, LOOKS, PERSONALITY, WEALTH
I hope he doesn't mind splurging on dates.
Good humor!
Can't forget about that.
I can't date a thinker type.
He has to be a feeler, no matter what!
FITNESS, LOOKS, PERSONALITY, WEALTH,
EMPATHY, HUMOR
I'll do really well this time.
Second time's the charm.
SATURDAY AFTERNOON
That's expensive.
- Take something else.
- My gosh.
You said my dates would judge me
based on what purse I was wearing.
You're fine with men scoffing at me?
I don't want men to think
you're richer than you are.
Oh, come on.
190 HOURS SINCE THE FIRST DATE
THE DAY OF THE SECOND BLIND DATE
Alright, then.
I'm glad. The dress looked good on you.
Are you free this evening?
What took him so long to reply?
I'm on my way to another date, okay?
Sorry for my late reply.
The work trip was packed, and I was so...
I'm meeting someone tonight.
I'll text you another time.
Okay, then.
He wants to meet at a cafe?
That means
he'll just have coffee and leave
if he doesn't like me.
A practical man who doesn't waste
his time or money.
I guess that's what it takes
to earn hundreds of millions.
You know nerds, right?
He spent all his years studying,
so he just lacks social skills.
And he's not that handsome.
At least text me
if you're going to be late.
He should value my time
as much as he values his.
Sorry, I'm late.
Did I tell you too late?
Are you Mr. Lee Jeong-u?
Yeah, that's me.
And you're Ms. Lee Ui-yeong?
Yes.
No way. I thought Na-ri said
he wasn't handsome.
Ui-yeong, stop smiling. Get serious!
PERFECT SCORE ON LOOKS
You look like an actor.
Nobody's told me that before.
Really? Are you into movies?
Who isn't?
Yeah, good point.
What genres are you into?
I love comedy and rom-coms.
Anything except those two.
What the heck?
It's like he's pushing me away
because I seem to like him.
MID HUMOR AND EMPATHY
We're the opposite.
Na-ri said you worked at S Electronics.
Don't they pay you good incentives?
I heard they also give
good bonuses and perks.
Must be motivating.
It's just like any other salaried job.
But I'm not really curious
about my date's financial situation
on the first date.
He just threw shade at me, didn't he?
TERRIBLE PERSONALITY
Get through the whole date this time,
okay?
What's that neck tattoo for?
I thought S Electronics was very strict.
You seem very free-spirited.
Are you one of the board members' son?
You wish that I were, don't you?
- Sorry?
- Why else would I be here?
You talked
about my job and money the whole time.
I get that my job is a big appeal
but I don't like
how obvious you're making it.
I spend as much as I earn.
So, even if we were to end up together
don't expect me to spoil you.
What a jerk.
Was he forced to go on this date or what?
I get that you're making yourself clear
but I have no plans
on looking for a man just to spoil me.
I'll get this. Let's just leave.
Okay, then. Excuse me!
I'll get a macaron, a tiramisu cake
and an iced mocha
with extra, extra whipped cream.
You want anything else?
That'll be all, then.
The world is full of crazy people.
I really love sweets.
You're finished, right?
What is Tae-seop doing here?
What's wrong?
I get dizzy when I get up too suddenly.
Who is he?
Your ex?
Your ex-ex-boyfriend?
- Ex-ex-ex-boyfriend?
- Shut up!
Why would you say...
You're not even interested in me.
I'm leaving first.
Let's say goodbye outside.
You're going to crawl to the exit?
Wait. Stop...
Stop there for a sec. Stop...
Don't touch me!
- Darn it.
- Ui-yeong?
Hi, Tae-seop.
Are you okay? Do you know the guy?
Of course.
She's my older sister.
"Older sister"?
I'm really sorry.
Sorry about stealing from your coin stash.
I didn't know you had it
since first grade.
Didn't you say you were an only child?
She is.
I'm just her cousin.
But who are you to talk
like you know everything about my cousin?
It's not what you think it is, Tae-seop.
I see.
I was just worried when you screamed.
Sorry.
Sorry for causing trouble.
I'll get going, then.
I'll text you later.
Okay.
My cousin?
Tae-seop wouldn't believe that!
Just to make it clear
I was pulling your dress down
because it was riding up.
Only if he didn't stall
with the cakes and the coffee!
Anyway, sorry for touching your dress.
I panicked.
- Are you listening?
- Yeah.
It's fine.
It didn't help,
but thanks for acting, too.
Goodbye, then.
So, the date is over?
Yeah, it's over.
- Bye.
- You ended it first, okay?
Because you don't like me.
- Right?
- Yes.
So, goodbye.
Hey.
If you're free today
you want to grab a drink with me?
This isn't a date, okay?
- Two draft beer, please!
- Coming!
Let's set things straight first.
I paid at the cafe,
so you can pay for the drinks.
Sure.
I assumed we'd have dinner on this date
meaning I'd starved the whole day.
What are you, a hamster?
Eat slowly.
Aren't you having any?
I don't have an appetite
after all that sugar.
What?
Why do you drink beer like that?
You got a problem with that?
By the way, I'm older than you are.
Can I drop the honorifics?
You're already doing it.
I'm doing the same, alright?
It must've been a blind date.
Should I have told her not to say yes?
DINNER PLANS ON A SATURDAY WITH A COUSIN?
Sir, we're closing in ten minutes.
I'll get going, then. Sorry.
My goal is simple.
I want to find someone compatible
before it's too late
and live happily ever after.
I really don't understand you.
Why did you even agree to this date?
I'm the same.
I want to find a good person.
Huh? "A good pencil"?
No!
I want to find a good person...
We almost crashed.
That's why everyone goes on blind dates.
So, why am I not the one, then?
What?
I'm not complaining. I'm just curious.
I may not make as much money as you do
but I have a stable job.
My mom also still works, and my dad...
He doesn't live with us,
but he works in the public sector.
And people say I'm too kind
for my own good.
Nobody's ever told me I was mean.
I'd say I check a lot of boxes.
Aren't I a pretty sweet deal?
You're great.
You do pretend to be nicer than you are
but it's better than being mean.
Oh, am I just not your type, look-wise?
I'd say...
you're pretty.
No, come on. You don't get it.
You need to tell me honestly
so I do better on my next first date.
Drink that, and I'll tell you.
I was going to drink it, anyway.
I'll drink this, forget it all
and find my perfect guy.
Just wait and see.
Do you have anyone you can set me up with?
Any friends who look
as handsome as you do?
Hey! How can you ask such a question
to your date?
And I don't have any friends.
Ask someone else.
What a bore.
Gosh, it's late.
You ate so much.
Thanks for the dinner.
If you mean that, let's walk for a bit.
Gosh, I'm full.
TQ MOTEL, BADA FISH MARKET
Hey, come with me.
Huh?
Come on!
What?
I got scared for nothing.
Come here!
You know what this is?
Of course. It's the spinny thing.
I was the queen bee of the playground
back in the day.
No, what's the real name for it?
Does it have another name?
Yeah.
"The spinning stage."
"The spinning stage"?
Alright.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
This is nice.
Hold on tight.
Hey, can you stop it for a sec?
I feel like throwing up! Stop it!
Are you okay?
Hey...
Hey!
Do you need to throw up?
Want me to tap your back?
I'm spinning.
You okay?
I'm still spinning.
Look! The earth is spinning!
You're so funny.
You know that?
And so are you.
This is bad.
My heart is pounding.
I can't help but keep imagining
what it'd be like
to leave my life in his hands.
It'd probably be
even better than I imagine.
But...
I don't want to sleep with you.
Why not?
Are you
not enjoying it now?
No.
It's a problem that I'm enjoying it.
Ui-yeong!
But as long as this woman set us up
there's no way I can just follow my heart.
What if she finds out about everything?
That'd be such a nightmare.
Why are you so late?
I'm dying to hear about it!
How was it?
Come with me.
Why? Did anything happen?
SUPPLY ROOM
You have an update for me, don't you?
So, what happened?
We had a good time.
Jeong-u is my type.
Really? Even his face?
Yeah, he seemed nervous at first
but I liked seeing him ease up over time.
We even got drinks after.
We had four bottles of soju.
Oh, my! And what?
That's all.
- That's all?
- Yeah.
Nothing more?
So, you had four bottles of soju
on your first date.
Did you dress up and style your hair?
It would've been nice to show some effort.
That was the end of my second blind date.
He didn't ask me if I got home okay
or if the hangover was bad.
SLEEPLESS NIGHT, DIVING, RED LOVE
Ji-su, how was the date?
No, you ruined it, right?
You didn't find me attractive at the cafe
when we were sober earlier.
And you kept beating around the bush
at the pub, too.
And you're asking me
if I'm enjoying it now?
- I...
- Do you really like me?
I doubt it.
You're just in love with this moment.
You know what they call this?
"Lust."
Hey, that's...
Let's go!
Blind dates are supposed to be cute.
Man, I drank too much tonight.
I hope you find someone you really like.
Someone worth giving your all.
I hope you find her.
Jeong-u, I'm sorry
but can I have Ui-yeong's number?
I met the one who set us up in some group
and she kept asking what my type was.
I didn't want to come out as gay.
Thanks for going in my place.
Here's your payment.
- This looks so good.
- I'm not sure.
- I can't wait.
- It'll be amazing.
Is the melon bingsu a hit?
MIMI gave a shout-out to our bingsu
on her socials.
Is MIMI popular?
Mr. Oh!
You don't know MIMI from OH MY GIRL?
She's in a K-pop group
and on so many TV shows!
She's super cute and famous.
I know! OH MY... GOSH.
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
Can we order more melons?
Yes, we can. I checked with the supplier
before the meeting.
The media is talking about it, too.
We're going to offer a bundle
with the bingsu and a room.
Please order as many melons
- as you can find.
- Okay.
Celebrities are really powerful, huh?
If the bingsu weren't so great,
she wouldn't have raved about it.
We worked hard to create the recipe
and secure good melons.
Give credit to those who deserve it.
Yeah, that's exactly what I mean.
- Good work, Ui-yeong.
- Congratulations!
And thank you, Chef!
- You're the best!
- Thanks!
- Good job!
- Good job.
Good work, everyone.
- Have a good one.
- Good work.
- Please check it.
- Yes, Chef.
Chef, are you free after work tonight?
Yeah, I am.
She should be here any minute.
There she is!
You can sit here.
- Glad you found the spot.
- What would you like?
- Beer, please.
- Okay.
Welcome.
Mr. Eun with three from Purchasing?
What an odd combo.
We have a little study group at work.
- It's called "Eat Eat Club."
- "Eat Eat Club"?
Yes, "Eat Eat Club."
We go around, trying foods we haven't had.
They supposedly started it
to be better at their jobs
but I doubt it.
It's basically a stress-eating club.
We've gathered today
to celebrate the bingsu's huge success.
It's on me today!
- Watch out, it's hot.
- Thank you!
- That looks amazing.
You look great today.
- Do I?
- Yeah.
First, get your glove on.
It looks amazing.
Are you new to chicken feet?
Yeah.
She studied abroad, remember?
There's nothing better than chicken feet
for relieving your stress.
Try one today.
- Should I?
- Yeah.
- Here I go.
- Welcome to Korea.
- Let's go.
- High-five!
- Cheers!
It's more like a high-four.
What do you think?
- It's good.
- Right?
- Is it hot?
- It must be.
Drink this if it's too hot.
I see why it helps you de-stress.
Right?
Do you guys also get stressed easily?
Everyone in Purchasing looks happy.
Of course.
My needs are never met, 365 days a year.
I still don't know
if I'll get a permanent contract here.
And I flunked my blind date.
- Feel better.
- Thanks.
I'm fine.
I'm just happy to be enjoying good food
with all of you.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Why are you home so late?
I was going to fast from 7 p.m.
Sorry, I got stuck in traffic.
But fasting can always wait
until tomorrow, right?
Sua!
Uncle had to go to a doctor.
- Really?
- Yeah, so don't nag him today.
No nagging.
Why did you see a doctor?
Are you badly hurt?
Yeah, I am.
I'm in so much pain.
I'm dying here.
Don't die.
I can't die, but I already have.
Can you just take her for a month?
It was so good!
You're adorable.
Chef
do you think
I'll find my perfect melon one day?
You're talking about men, right?
Yeah.
You've only gone on two blind dates.
What are you looking for?
I just happened to find out
that my blind date had an expensive car
and that made my heart pound.
But...
But I doubt I'll recognize it
if it were to drive right past me now.
I can't even tell
a sedan apart from an SUV.
I have my license, but I never even drive.
It doesn't matter if he drives a fancy car
or makes
hundreds of millions of won a year.
Here's your wine.
Could you tell us more about it?
SHIN JI-SU
Of course.
It's an easy drinking red wine
from Orsogna.
- It tastes like ripe fruit with a tang.
- Looks don't really matter, either.
Just because a guy is handsome or rich
doesn't mean we'll hit it off.
What's important is
that you two are on the same page.
Love doesn't begin
when one person falls for the other.
So, blind dates are fun.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Try it on. It'll look good on you.
Sure, then.
You look stunning!
You could pull off a cute dress, too.
How about this?
Do you have something in a darker color?
Something that won't show any stains.
Just a sec.
How about this?
Let's see.
My journey's begun already, anyway.
I might as well go all out.
- I'll try it on.
- Okay.
So, if you know a good, single guy
set me up with him.
TEXT NOTIFICATION
I found the cutest dress!
Isn't it adorable?
Yeah, I'll try it on.
YOU HAVE RECEIVED A MESSAGE
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Looking forward to meeting you.
- Ui-yeong?
- I'm Ho-gwang.
I'm Yuk Jun-seo.
- Hello.
- Are you free this Friday?
- Is this Ms. Lee?
- Hey.
- The weather's great.
- Hi.
Would you like to grab a coffee with me?
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
- Hello.
- Ms. Ui-yeong?
Are you free?
- A friend...
- Looking for a date?
I'm Yuk Jun-seo.
Are they all asking me out
on a blind date?
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE TO FALL IN LOVE?
FIVE SECONDS
IT'S A GO SIGN!
LOOKS
WHAT IF I LEAVE MY LIFE IN HIS HANDS...
It may have been a drunken wish
Hello, nice to meet you.
You know me, right?
People go on blind dates before work?
Yeah, I'm one of them.
I'll know for sure
if I just see her one more time.
Run into her one more time.
Ui-yeong!
Why would I shake her hand?
Why are you doing this to me?
- Stop it.
- Hey!
I don't want everything about me
to be a lie to you.
The problem is
- that none of the men were my type.
- Tae-seop.
Are you here to see me?
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim