[A Prime Minister's Disguise]
[Episode 5]
I have a feeling that Huo Jingheng's drunken words
were a bit strange,
as if he deliberately said them for me to hear.
Could he already know something?
When did he find out?
Was Ling'er being summoned to the palace
just a coincidence?
Yue.
Go check if the pastries from the kitchen
are ready.
Alright.
Yes, Your Highness.
Ling'er.
Chi.
Come.
Be careful.
Was your journey smooth?
It went very smoothly.
Someone came to escort me here
as soon as I got off the carriage.
But Chi,
why did you suddenly call for me?
Is there something urgent?
I just want to ask you,
do you still want to be the Empress?
If you have feelings for someone else
and you don't want to enter the palace,
just tell me as soon as possible.
I'll make other plans for you.
Who could I possibly have feelings for?
During these days
at the Prime Minister's Mansion,
don't you have any feelings
for Du Tianzhao?
Feelings?
Of course not.
Are you telling the truth?
Of course.
Then what do you think of Huo Jingheng?
His Majesty?
His Majesty
is a rare and brilliant ruler.
He's accomplished in both civil
and military matters,
wise, brilliant,
kind-hearted, benevolent,
naturally pure and good,
and very trustworthy.
Chi, what do you...
think of His Majesty?
Hmm...
You...
You think...
so highly of him?
Then it's settled.
Since you have feelings for him anyway...
Yes.
You won't mind switching back with me.
Switching back?
Starting today,
you'll be the one to get along with Huo Jingheng.
So soon?
Are you planning to leave the palace?
Are you willing or not?
I am.
But I think now is not a good time
to switch back.
It's better to act sooner than later.
I've done all I can.
The rest can only be done by you personally.
Everything you need is here.
Just memorize it thoroughly.
Records of Dog Huo's Daily Life?
This log
records all the details
since I first entered the palace
[Day 1: Huo Jingheng practiced martial arts at 5 a.m. to stay fit—fairly self-disciplined. At 9 a.m., he met with the court officials, attending to everything from national affairs to trivial matters.]
and served Huo Jingheng at night.
You have to memorize it well
so you won't slip up.
Trouble comes from the mouth.
I shot myself in the foot.
If Chi really leaves,
what should I do?
His comprehension isn't bad either.
Given time,
he could achieve great things.
However,
benevolence and righteousness to him
[Day 2: He still practiced
martial arts at 5 a.m.]
are like water to a boat.
[At 9 a.m., he met with court officials,
keeping the people's well-being in mind.]
They can either make him
or break him.
But his benevolence and righteousness are misplaced.
He's actually pretty cunning
when dealing with others.
You know him well?
Not really.
Don't you remember, Chi?
I met him
when we were kids.
I'm just
guessing from the words
in this log.
Stop guessing.
Memorize it well
and get ready to serve him tonight.
Serve him tonight?
Consort Yue.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Well then,
Dear, keep me company again tonight
while I go over the memorials.
The person who had been with him
for so many days
was suddenly replaced,
yet he didn't notice anything unusual
at all.
Something's not right.
What should we do?
Dear, look at this advice.
It really speaks to me.
Let's not make a move now.
[Records of Dog Huo's Daily Life]
My brother has fully prepared
and is determined to succeed.
What should we do now?
Give it to me.
I want to see it.
No matter how they try to fake it,
the familiarity in those little details
can't be forged.
The two of them have probably been
in contact in private for quite some time.
To avoid any complications,
I'll leave tomorrow.
[Yongqian Palace]
[Records of Dog Huo's Daily Life]
[Day 1: Huo Jingheng practiced martial arts at 5 a.m. to stay fit—fairly self-disciplined. At 9 a.m., he met with the court officials, attending to everything from national affairs to trivial matters.]
Dog Huo has injuries on his back.
It hurts faintly when exposed to wind,
so make sure to keep him warm.
He prefers light food,
dislikes anything too strongly flavored.
Steamed or boiled dishes
with minimal oil and salt
suit him best.
He is a man of benevolence
and righteousness.
Perhaps I could marry my sister to him.
In this world,
there's no shortage of talented people
who can be generals and ministers,
nor ambitious schemers.
But it's rare to find someone who truly
values benevolence and righteousness.
Chi,
you're leaving already?
I've memorized the log,
but there's still this whole pile
of memorials.
How can I handle them on my own?
Come on,
Chi.
I know
you've always been the kindest to me.
Please help me.
Our Ling'er is capable of anything.
You don't need any help.
But...
Ling'er,
isn't there something...
you want to tell me?
No.
By His Majesty's oral decree,
Consort Yue
-is summoned to the Imperial Garden!
-Chi,
did you hear that?
Here we go again.
Every time I hear that, I get nervous.
If I go out like this
and slip up,
it could lead to the execution of our entire Yue family.
Don't be afraid.
Just go.
If something really happens,
I'll be long gone.
Given his temperament,
he won't make things difficult for you.
Go on.
Greetings, Your Highness.
You think I'm Consort Yue?
His Majesty said you are,
so you are.
Huo Jingheng really does know
how to use people.
I hope he can win over my brother.
Alright.
You must be tired
from following me around.
Just take a rest here.
Yes, Your Highness.
My brother is really leaving.
You'd better think of a solution fast.
I've thought it through carefully.
He cares about you,
so he'll continue reviewing the memorials.
As for whose hands they're
submitted through,
it doesn't matter to me.
After all, "Consort Yue"
is still in the palace, right?
Listen to your own words.
You're being unreasonable.
Trying to burn bridges after crossing?
Consort Yue, watch your words.
She didn't go home all night.
She must be mad at me.
They already switched?
Can this really work?
Those two siblings are
obviously different.
Is my nephew blind?
Don't panic.
They've probably just met.
Your Majesty,
you may not care,
but I don't want to waste
my precious youth
stuck in the harem.
Aren't you a man of benevolence
and righteousness?
Then help me out.
Think about it.
Having him by your side would be so great.
Talking to him all night would be
convenient and enjoyable.
Sure, keeping him here might be
a bit troublesome,
but once it succeeds,
you won't lose out either.
Keeping him isn't easy.
Let me think about it.
So,
you've agreed?
But there's one more thing
you must promise me.
Don't come to my place again tonight.
I'm not like you rough guys.
I can't stay up late.
Last night was my first time serving you.
It really wore me out.
Serving at night?
She was kept up most of the night?
Imperial Uncle,
you're finally back.
Where have you been?
The Empress Dowager summoned you
to meet her at 3 p.m.
It's already past that time.
Why do you look so lost?
Hurry up.
[Zhou Xiran,
daughter of the Grand Guard]
[Xie Yingran,
daughter of the Minister of Works]
Now Heng has someone
he cares about by his side.
As his uncle, you should settle down too.
Among so many beauties,
is there anyone you fancy?
Sister,
it's easy for you to say.
Is it that easy to find
someone you care about?
Besides,
even if I find her,
does that mean she'll be mine?
If heaven has feelings, it too grows old.
From today, I, Du Tianzhao,
will have no heart and no feelings.
I'll be alone for the rest of my life!
It's nobody else's business!
What nonsense are you talking about?
I think you need to be taught a lesson.
[Auspice and Blessing]
Wake up, you fool!
Who said it's easy to find your soulmate?
Heng
was single for many years
before he found Consort Yue.
[Auspice and Blessing]
One day,
you'll find that special someone too.
My special someone was stolen by him,
my dear sister.
Chi,
you're leaving right after dinner?
In such a hurry?
Huo Jingheng might come by again tonight.
I'll give you two some space.
No need.
We have plenty of time.
But you need careful planning
before leaving the palace.
Why don't you take it slow?
I've already planned it out.
What's your plan?
In the previous dynasty, a
favored consort loved fresh water.
The emperor secretly ordered
a hidden canal
to be built beneath the Imperial Lake,
connecting the waterways in
the capital to the palace.
I can swim through the Imperial Lake
to get directly outside the palace.
I see.
Let me verify
if it's really what I think.
So many flowers.
Yes.
Marigolds.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
are these flowers...
all to be placed in the Imperial Lake?
Consort Yue, you love flowers.
I want to fill the lake and plant flowers.
That's not necessary.
It's too much trouble.
I think this lake is fine as it is.
Hmm.
Then I'll listen to you
and won't plant them.
Dear, you're dressed quite uniquely today.
You can't leave anyway.
Why don't you just stay?
There is no hidden canal here at all.
So it really is Ling'er who's been
tipping off Huo Jingheng.
You may leave now.
-Yes.
Your Majesty, are you planning
to live in Fengluan Palace?
We love each other deeply
and can't bear to be apart
even for a moment.
Huo Jingheng keeps setting traps
and pressing forward step by step.
What exactly does he want?
I just remembered
you still have some memorials to review.
Tonight,
I don't want to review any memorials.
Never mind then.
Your Majesty, are there any
difficult matters at court lately?
The night is long.
Why don't we talk about them?
Dear, weren't you the one who least
wanted to interfere in politics before?
Tonight you seem quite open to it.
In ancient times, there was a ruler
who deceived his vassals
just to win a beauty's smile.
Now I'm getting involved
in politics for you.
What is there to fear?
Very well.
Oh my.
[Memorial]
These are
all the difficult cases
I encountered at court,
and I've made notes on all of them.
Dear, why don't you discuss them with me?
This is the first one.
Dear, what are your thoughts?
Your Majesty,
it's time for the morning court session.
Your Majesty?
Please rise.
Shouldn't you be attending court now?
The morning air is chilly.
I came back
to give you an extra layer,
but I didn't expect
to find you leaving in such a hurry.
Where are you going?
I woke up and didn't see you.
Unable to bear the longing,
I caught up to take a look.
If I could catch one more
glimpse of your back,
that would be enough.
Even so,
it's a bit reckless.
If you had walked too fast
and gotten hurt,
wouldn't I have lost my helper?
Your Majesty, you're right.
This helper is going back to work now.
Do you still have many
difficult cases left to review?
While I'm away,
you must protect Consort Yue well.
-Yes!
Go.
Chi.
You seem so happy.
You don't want to enter the palace
and marry Huo Jingheng,
do you?
Chi,
actually, I didn't think it through.
At first,
I agreed in the heat of the moment.
But after spending time with His Majesty,
I realized I have no romantic
feelings for him.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to marry him anymore.
I'm very disappointed.
Ling'er, if you have any concerns,
why can't you just tell me directly?
To me,
your feelings matter most.
If there's even a trace of reluctance,
you shouldn't marry him.
No matter who he is,
we don't care.
Chi.
She's my own sister—
how could I not spoil her?
Since that's the case,
we'll change the plan.
I'll arrange for you to leave
the palace first.
Once you're safe,
I'll find another chance to escape.
Then won't Huo Jingheng be able to keep him?
What now?
How about this?
Let's discuss it a bit more.
The longer you stay,
the more trouble you'll face.
Hurry and pack your things.
Leave immediately.
So many people?
Yes.
Every time we're out, there are
so many imperial guards following.
How can we possibly leave?
It's good that the imperial guards are here.
Chi can't run away now.
Everything has its match.
Only that person in the entire palace
can keep Huo Jingheng in check.
Looks like we can only use this way to get away.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I am of humble appearance,
without talent or virtue.
Since entering the palace,
I've been blessed with the care
of His Majesty and Your Grace,
for which I am deeply grateful.
I dare not monopolize His Majesty's favor.
I plan to use three months' salary
to invite Yanshuang Opera Troupe
in the capital to the palace,
and invite all sisters in the palace
to present their talents as well.
Your Grace,
I humbly ask for your approval.
She's really pushing her luck.
Qu,
Consort Yue asked the Empress Dowager
for rewards for the whole palace,
giving us a chance
to show ourselves before His Majesty.
Isn't that a good thing?
What do you know?
She's playing a strategic retreat.
Now that she's in favor
and already a consort anyway.
Now that she has pulled this stunt,
all the consorts in the palace are saying
she's kind, dignified, and understands propriety.
If His Majesty whimsically
makes her the Empress,
Then I...
So what do you plan to do?
Why her, of all people?
I suppose Consort Yue is quite special.
Bah!
I'll make her realize
that no flower blooms forever.
Hey!
You were once a princess.
Tell me,
what's so good
about staying in this palace?
As a consort,
no matter how rich
or how favored,
you're still just a bird in a cage,
a fish in a pond.
It can't compare to the freedom of being by my side.
I won't force her to do anything.
Why does she have to enter the palace?
Who are you talking about?
Whoever she is!
Is it Ling'er?
Yes.
What's your relationship with her?
What's it to you?
You like her?
Let go of me!
I'm warning you,
stay away from her.
Don't get involved with her.
Ling'er and Yue Chi
shouldn't get too close to anyone
from your new imperial family.
What?
It's dangerous.
Dangerous?
For whom?
Only by leaving the capital
will they be completely safe.
You crazy woman!
The commander has ordered
that you can't leave!
Put down your swords!
She's got a sword to my neck.
Come protect me.
Hurry, hurry.
Let her go.
Where's Dugu Xing?
He's carrying out a secret mission under the commander's order.
Secret mission?
Something big has happened!
[Notice] [Wanted]
Look, look!
The palace just posted a new notice.
They're offering a bounty for rare flowers,
with a generous reward.
Look!
Wow!
[Notice]
Looks like the palace is having
a flower appreciation event.
Yes.
Yue.
Have you prepared everything I asked for?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Everything is well-prepared.
Be careful, Your Highness.
Watch out for your dress.
Walk slowly.
It would be better if I didn't step on it.
I'd like to see if they'd still dare
to stare at me if my skirt fell.
[Elegant Dwelling with Spring Grace]
Consort Yue is here!
Consort Yue.
Why are you leaving so soon after arriving?
[Elegant Dwelling with Spring Grace]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Grace.
I...
feel ashamed facing all my
beautiful sisters.
Wouldn't it be a waste of all that effort
you put into dressing up if you leave now?
Yue not only is tall,
but her way of walking
also has a masculine charm to it.
That's true.
She's so strong,
and with this vibrant outfit,
it really enhances her presence.
Alright.
Stop discussing her appearance.
Is it a tradition
in every dynasty for the consorts
to insult each other indirectly
before the banquet?
From now on,
you should just throw hammers.
Consort Yue,
your outfit today...
-is quite...
-is extraordinary
and truly stunning.
I've never seen
my son shy before.
Looks like I might
finally get a grandson now.
Alright, Mother.
Stop saying that. Let's begin.
Later,
all the consorts will show their talents.
There will be quite a show.
Watch how I escape later.
I'd like to see what tricks you're up to.
[Tianwei Gate]
General Dugu,
did my brother say
where we'll go once we leave the palace?
He didn't.
Didn't you ask?
There's no need to ask
when following military orders.
I think...
there's some misunderstanding
between my brother and His Majesty.
He
actually doesn't want to leave.
Why don't we call it off?
My Lady,
if you keep talking like this,
I'll have someone send you back.
Bestow a peach blossom on her.
Lady Lan, please take the flower.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I can also perform sword dancing.
May I offer you another dance, Your Majesty?
Bestow her another flower.
Another flower!
Consort Hui will present
the Swift Battle Breakthrough Tune.
Bestow her a flower.
What...
what flower?
But I haven't played yet,
Your Majesty.
Bestow a white peony on her.
A white peony.
-Peony?
"Only the peony truly represents
national beauty."
Could it be that His Majesty
has already made a decision?
Your Grace,
I have a unique skill as well.
You must be interested.
Consort Yue,
you want to show your talent too?
What are you going to show?
Uprooting willows by the roots
or breaking a big stone with your chest?
Neither.
Please wait a moment.
This is our Yue family's secret technique,
called "Returning to the Source."
Returning to the Source?
What does it mean?
May I borrow your hairpin?
Thank you.
Returning to origin
and tracing the source.
This is the origin of this hairpin.
That's right.
This hairpin is made from
an entire piece of coral.
It's very precious.
I present it to you, Your Grace.
I wish you longevity
and blessings that last forever.
Your Grace, look.
What a wonderful item.
This is the handkerchief I carry with me.
Returning to origin and tracing the source.
Your Highness?
Yue?
How can it be Yue?
She conjured up a person out of thin air.
Your Highness, I was just making pastries for you.
Why did I suddenly come here?
That's right.
This handkerchief was made by Yue.
How amazing!
Marvelous, truly marvelous.
Consort Yue,
may I try
your secret technique?
Of course.
However,
today His Majesty is bestowing flowers.
I'm thinking…
why not let His Majesty try it first?
Well said.
Let him have a try.
Dear, is this secret technique
for real?
It is.
Can it trace the source
of anything?
Yes.
Very well.
Your Majesty, you are the supreme ruler.
Your wishes carry more weight
than ordinary people's.
I fear that my single prayer
may not be granted by the gods.
Therefore,
I need everyone here to close their eyes
and chant
"Returning to the origin
and tracing the source" with me.
You may stop only when I say so.
By then,
your wish will manifest itself.
Don't disappoint me.
Returning to the origin
and tracing the source.
Returning to origin and tracing the source.
Play with me?
Goodbye.
Huo Jingheng.
Sorry.
Yunqing?
Ling'er?
What are you doing here?
How do you know we are here?
Did you betray us?
What are you talking about?
That's not true.
Ling'er, how did you get out?
Didn't you enter the palace and become Consort Yue?
Who told you that?
I thought...
you truly wanted to marry my nephew.
I was upset about it all night.
That's not important.
I have something more important to do now.
You should go first.
I almost forgot.
I have something more important
to tell you.
Jiang Yunqing ran away.
What?
Oh no.
With Yunqing's temper,
she might storm back in.
General Dugu, what should we do?
The commander ordered us to wait here to assist him in leaving.
Let's stay calm and wait for his orders.
We must not disrupt his plan.
What?
Yue Chi is leaving?
That's not okay, is it?
What on earth is Consort Yue up to?
Once I kill Huo Jingheng,
I'll take you out of the palace with me.
Hurry up and go back.
The Empress Dowager is here today.
Even if Huo Jingheng steps in,
he won't be able to protect you.
I want to leave,
but I want to take you with me more.
Don't be foolish.
Consort Yue?
Where did you go, Consort Yue?
Your Grace!
Your Grace,
bed news!
His Majesty was ambushed
by an assassin in the Imperial Garden!
What?
Eunuch Wang.
Yes.
Hurry
and summon the imperial guards!
Yes!
This way!
Hurry, this way!
Surround the Imperial Garden!
-Yes!
Mother,
why are you here?
What do you think?
Hurry up and go after them!
Never mind, Mother.
The banquet is meant to be a joyful occasion.
Let's not let the assassin ruin our mood.
Let's put this matter behind us.
Put it behind us?
I think you're intentionally letting them go.
Over the years,
you've always been lenient with
the assassins who've infiltrated the palace.
The palace has become a fighting arena.
Have they shown any appreciation for your kindness?
Have they hesitated when swinging their swords at you?
I must take care of
this matter today.
Pass on my decree!
Lock down the palace gates!
Anyone who resists
will be killed without mercy!
Yes.
Those who harbor, protect,
or have connections with the assassin
will be punished equally!
Yes!