[A Prime Minister's Disguise]
[Episode 21]
You're awake.
Your Highness.
Are you surprised?
Why didn't you kill me?
If you died,
our two countries would surely be at war.
I didn't do it for you,
but for the people.
I won't be grateful to you guys.
You were just injured yesterday.
Eat something.
Don't worry. It's not poisonous.
You...
Forget it.
Let him be.
How's your leg?
Does it still hurt?
The wound is festering.
Later,
apply the herbs I just picked to it.
I think it'll get better then.
His wound won't heal.
Apply that small piece of
black ointment in my bag
to his wound.
What is it?
It's very precious.
With it, necrotic flesh can regenerate
and broken bones can be mended.
This way, I won't owe you
anything anymore.
When we meet again next time,
let's fight against
each other to the death.
Come and eat something.
Otherwise, your body can't endure it.
I've drunk too much decoction.
My digestive system has long been damaged.
Even if you now bring me
some nectar,
I wouldn't want to drink it.
You were just
bitten by a snake
and then attacked
by my palm.
I've also readjusted your internal energy.
You've even taken the herbs
Prime Minister Yue picked for you.
Why is your pulse
still so chaotic?
Your Majesty's physique is quite strong,
while my body
is as weak as
a deep well that's about to dry up.
What's the use of irrigating it again?
It will only nourish those
vines clinging to the well walls
so that they can gradually swallow me.
If you're the ultimate winner,
there won't be
any benefits for Li State.
You must be curious
why a dying man like me
has caused
the Li State's bloodline to wither.
You have no descendants.
Li State will surely
fall into chaos when you die.
I may be vengeful,
but I'm not a narrow-minded person.
There's no harm in telling you two now.
My nephew, Yi Xin,
is still alive.
He will inherit the throne.
Yi Xin?
Why haven't I
heard of this prince before?
Because the former Crown Prince
hated this son the most.
He's the most unlike his
cruel and ignorant father.
Then why didn't you directly
support him to ascend the throne?
And why did you still
come to provoke Ning?
Being a monarch is difficult.
I think you understand it
deeply as the King of Ning.
I have a bad reputation,
and I'm dying soon.
If I support Yi Xin to ascend the throne,
it will surely cause controversy
and affect the foundation of our country.
It's better to arrange everything well.
Then I can die in peace.
The 10 cities in Ning State
are my final gifts for
Yi Xin's coronation.
Wars are cruel.
The civilians have to suffer a lot.
You said our Ning State
had taken 10 cities from you.
But with the disputes between
our two countries over these years,
Li State has also taken
cities from our country, hasn't it?
If just like you, every generation
of rulers had been
solely focused on reclaiming something,
would the wars ever end?
There's no need to
explain these principles to me.
The King of Ning and
Prime Minister Yue are kind-hearted.
Why don't you just
return the 10 cities to Li State?
Then I'll order the troops to
withdraw immediately.
I think it would be more convenient
if we strangle you, the Crown Prince.
At this point,
whether to withdraw the troops or not,
I'm afraid
it's not up to
the Crown Prince.
As for the plan with Jiang Yunqing,
I've misjudged it indeed.
You've been using her
all this time, haven't you?
When did it start?
You said you would help her
restore the Former Ning.
I would restore the Former Ning?
Did you really believe in
what she said?
She agreed to help me
only because
I had poisoned her with poisonous insects.
If she doesn't want to endure
that excruciating pain,
she can only yield to me
and obey my every command.
You...
It looks like love can indeed
blind people.
Even you, Yue Chi, have been misled
in your judgment of others.
You couldn't even sense that
she was an impostor.
Not long after I returned to Li State,
I heard that the former Empress's
daughter had been found.
What did you say?
The newly appointed
Princess Changping of the Ning Dynasty
is the daughter of the former Empress?
It's absolutely true.
How is that possible?
Back then, my father
ordered a night raid on Cheng'en Temple.
He intended to capture the Princess
and the Empress alive,
but they only found
their corpses in the end.
Now her corpse is still there,
but she's alive?
What's the reason for that?
What a good chance to manipulate her!
My poisonous worms
could finally be useful, too.
Come on. Cheers, everyone.
Princess Changping.
What's the matter?
Don't be so aloof.
I specially came here for you,
the fake princess of the Ning Dynasty.
I suppose
the fake princess
needs some real things to
maintain her identity.
For example,
my worm poison.
So you mean
Jiang Yunqing...
No.
She's Xue Jingguan.
Prime Minister Yue, there's no need
to be angry with me
about this matter.
I've already done so much,
but I still haven't
gained control over her.
Xue Jingguan
has never been a simple person.
Otherwise, how could she just
stand by and watch me,
who has been controlling
her life, get abducted?
She's even willing to risk
her own life.
It's evident that this woman
is unscrupulous.
It's possible that
when the Cheng'en Temple Incident
happened back then,
she took the chance to make it worse
and seized the opportunity to steal
the Jiang family's heirloom
to risk her life
for a lifetime of wealth and honor.
As a mere farmer's daughter,
she infiltrated the capital
and became a princess.
If the Former Ning had not fallen,
with her ability to manipulate situations,
her prospect might not
have been like this.
This woman's capabilities
are rare in the world.
To be honest,
I even admire her to some extent.
Yue Chi, oh, Yue Chi.
If you had not
broken off the marriage with her,
you might
have ended up
with a different fate.
What you said
is not impartial.
I don't think
you've ever seen
her true self.
The person you've described
bears no resemblance to her.
In my mind, she's a woman
who values loyalty and is courageous.
She remains aloof from
the world and is resilient,
being able to bear
all hardships alone.
Back then, the princess stayed
in the Changmen Forest.
But it was you who died.
Are you going to
atone for this for the rest of your life?
That's also why
I want to protect her
for the rest of my life.
What I care about and admire
has never been
her identity or bloodline as the princess.
Your Majesty, if everything is settled,
I'll set off two bundles of fireworks.
Your Highness, when we leave here later,
I'll ask someone to
escort you back to Li State.
Before that,
there's one more thing
I want you to help me with.
She doesn't even want
her own life anymore.
I also don't plan to continue using
poisonous insects to control her.
I'll do you one more favor
as a gesture of goodwill.
After I leave here safely,
I'll certainly give her the antidote.
It looks like
I must ensure that
you can leave here safely.
Giddy-up!
Your Majesty.
We arrived late.
The rebels have all been
captured or dispersed.
But the Princess and the Crown Prince
from the previous dynasty have escaped.
Please punish us, Your Majesty.
The incident happened suddenly.
You've already done quite well.
Get up.
Your Highness.
I said
I would make sure that
you could leave safely.
Wei Zhang.
Prime Minister Yue.
-Giddy-up!
Commander, are you alright?
I'm fine.
It's no big deal.
The Qilin Army has appeared.
I'm afraid the capital will soon
receive the news.
It looks like
a bloody war is inevitable.
What are you thinking, Your Highness?
What the King of Ning and Yue Chi said
is not entirely wrong.
[With the monarch's serenity,
the country will be at peace.]
That day in the cave,
he could have easily
killed me.
Then Li State would have been in chaos,
and Ning State could have
launched a full-scale attack.
He could have even
taken advantage of occupying Li State
to conquer the Huaye State at one stroke,
target the east coast of Qin Sea directly
and expand their territory to the maximum.
But he didn't do that.
What he cherishes
is the current Ning State's
long-awaited stability.
But...
But reclaiming the 10 cities
is still an urgent task.
Your Highness.
The geographical locations of
the 10 cities in Qiongzhou are special.
In Li State, they are the areas
with the least natural disasters
and pest infestations.
Now,
as long as the Yuming Worms
are not eliminated,
and the 10 cities are still
occupied by our enemy,
it means that
Li State won't be able
to harvest even a single
plump grain of food.
I wonder how much food is
left in Li State.
Huo Jingheng talked about
so many grand principles.
But can he solve
Li State's practical problems?
Xue Jingguan.
You're being too presumptuous.
Do you remember who has been
controlling your life?
I haven't gotten even with you
for what happened on the Xidu Bridge.
The three top generals of
the Kingdom Restoration League?
Your Highness, I advise you
not to act rashly.
Otherwise,
if the Crown Prince of a kingdom
silently
dies here,
wouldn't it be such a pity?
Have you guys forgotten who
brought you back from the battlefield?
Without me,
the Kingdom Restoration League
wouldn't have existed.
It's really ridiculous.
These are the people of our Ning State.
They want to restore Ning State's
legitimate sovereignty.
Do you think
they'll obey the orders
from the Crown Prince of Li State?
Your Highness,
I guess you also don't want
the Former Ning to unite
with the current Ning State
and attack Li State, huh?
Xue Jingguan.
I've really underestimated you.
Once I return to Li State,
I will gather a large army
and start the war immediately.
Good.
I will bring people
to join you in 10 days.
The people of Li will also
be grateful to you
for choosing
the right path.
Xue Jingguan.
Before Yue Chi left,
he asked me for your antidote.
To me,
a man's pity
is the most useless thing.
Your Highness, please also remember that
from now on,
there's only an alliance between us.
We are no longer master and servant.
[Fengyuan Hall]
Your Majesty.
There's a military rebellion in Li State.
The rebel army has already gone through
the Yumen Pass.
Right now,
the eastern and southern
vassal kings all want to rebel, too.
Dispatching troops
is a matter of the utmost urgency now,
Your Majesty.
Here's a request from the Ministry of War.
Your Majesty, please issue
a decree immediately
to dispatch 20,000
elite soldiers northward
and also recruit another
5,000 soldiers from across the country
to suppress the vassal kings.
If we recruit soldiers now,
I'm afraid we'll be short-handed.
Your Majesty.
In the Battle of Xidu Bridge,
the Qilin Army once
saved Your Majesty, didn't it?
Right now,
it's just the time to use them.
No way.
Since Yue Chi has maintained
his own army privately,
it can be considered as treason.
How can we use the Qilin Army again?
These people must be punished.
Your Majesty.
I agree. I agree with that.
These 1,000 or so men under my command
quit being soldiers a long time ago
and were scattered around the city.
They can hardly be called
soldiers anymore.
The title of Qilin Army
has long become history
of the previous dynasty.
Indeed.
In the households of ministers,
who doesn't have a few personal guards?
The Yue family has been in
high-ranking positions for generations.
The soldiers who once
worked for the Yue family
are naturally countless.
How can this be considered
as evidence of treason?
Your Majesty.
Everyone knows that
the Qilin Army is proficient in warfare.
During times of great chaos,
they even once fought against
Your Majesty's troops.
You're telling me that those are
ordinary guards?
Your Majesty, the military
situation is urgent.
Please issue a decree  immediately
to dispatch troops northward
and resist the enemy.
Your Majesty.
In my opinion,
Yue Chi
has secretly kept elite troops
and a large quantity of armaments.
He should be punished.
And with the Yue family's
crimes from the previous dynasty,
the Qilin Army
should be completely exterminated.
Yes.
We should also confiscate
all the Yue family's
private property
for our state
to buy military provisions.
Guards.
Dismiss
Yue Chi from his post as Prime Minister.
Put him in the imperial prison.
Your Majesty is wise!
Bad news.
[Prince Anle's Mansion]
Just now, I overheard
two officials saying that
the ministers requested
His Majesty to execute Master Yue
and capture the Qilin Army immediately.
His Majesty
seemed to be wavering.
The Commander has risked
his own life for him
and racked his brains.
What an ungrateful villain.
He intended to kill
officials of the imperial court.
Yue Chi is truly rebelling.
Now Lord Wang and Lord Qian
are both injured and bedridden.
The physical evidence is here.
Your Majesty, please convict him at once.
Your Majesty, please convict Yue Chi
to quell the public's anger.
Your Majesty.
The Qilin Army raided the prison.
What are you doing?
The Emperor wants to kill you.
Come with me now!
Who told you that?
There's no time to explain.
Come with me now!
His Majesty is here!
Yue Chi!
You're using your personal
guards to break out of prison.
What punishment do you deserve?
I've been
behaving well in prison.
They must have believed in
the slanderous remarks of evil people,
which led to such rash actions.
Your Majesty, please
investigate thoroughly.
Your Majesty, now the
evidence is irrefutable.
The facts are right in front of your eyes.
How can you still believe in
Yue Chi's deceiving words?
Don't force me.
Your Majesty, please
eliminate the rebels.
Your Majesty, please eliminate the rebels.
Yue Chi!
Back then, in the imperial court,
you kept saying that
you would never use the Qilin Army again.
Are you trying to rebel now?
The Qilin Army
absolutely has no intention of rebellion.
This matter started because of me alone,
and I'll bear the responsibility myself
in exchange for sparing
the lives of the Qilin Army.
All the Qilin soldiers here
should be killed!
Huo Jingheng.
I believe that you've
always been loyal to me.
But now that I am
the Emperor of Ning State,
I have no choice but to eliminate
my Right Prime Minister.
Kill them!
Commander.
This stupid Emperor is clearly
an ungrateful villain.
He doesn't deserve your trust at all.
There are still so many buddies outside
who need you.
Commander, leave first!
Take the Commander away!
Go! Come on!
Kill them!
Dugu Xing!
Just go!
[Notice]
You didn't leave.
I've been waiting for you.
Yue Chi.
If I hadn't arrived in time,
that farmer and his family
would have tied you up to get the reward.
[Yongqian Palace]
How is my brother?
Is His Majesty injured?
His Majesty
got severely injured while he was trying
to resist the rebel, Yue Chi.
He hasn't regained consciousness yet.
Your Highness.
Your anxiety won't help.
Please go back first.
My brother is not a rebel.
Eunuch Gui.
Please let me go inside and take a look.
Only after I see His Majesty
will I stop worrying.
Your Highness.
I don't dare to let you in
without permission.
When His Majesty sees you,
if he's sad
or angry,
then...
then I can't bear the consequences.
Please...
don't put me in a difficult position.
[Yongqian Palace]
Let me help you.
No need.
Don't move.
The imperial physician
who came with us told me
you could sit up now.
I'm here to check on you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I told you long ago
that you would eventually
part ways with Huo Jingheng.
I should've taken Your Highness's advice.
Your Highness saved my life.
I have no way to repay you.
How can you have no way to repay me?
Yue Chi.
You are a rare elite.
Now that Huo Jingheng has
treated you like that,
don't you want to get even with him?
But Ling'er is still in the palace.
Since I had a way
to send Wen Rou into the palace,
I can surely find a way
to get your sister out.
But I'm still a citizen of Ning after all.
Ning?
The Ning State you've been
so loyal to
has taken everything from you now.
Your family's reputation,
your buddies' lives
and your sister's freedom.
It's all because of Huo Jingheng.
Yue Chi.
I promise you that
after I reclaim the 10 cities
in Qiongzhou,
I will withdraw my troops.
I won't kill the innocent civilians.
Really?
With my identity as
the Crown Prince of Li State,
I guarantee it.
But I have one more request.
After you and I
capture Huo Jingheng,
let me deal with him personally.
I'm going to take revenge for
my buddies from the Qilin Army by myself.
Alright.
Yue Chi, you're good at
both civil and military affairs.
You're not only a top talent of Ning,
but the people of our Li State
will also respect and support you.
When you recover from your injuries,
I will appoint you as the prince regent.
Our Li State
will be the arena for you
to fully exert your talents.
Greetings, Your Excellency.
Send a troop to go through the canyon
and occupy the high ground.
When the Ning Army advances
and reaches this low-lying area,
we can ambush them.
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
We can also arrange for a troop to advance
and occupy this military position.
The Kingdom Restoration League
can provide support at any time.
What do you think?
Alright.
My Lady, please slow down.
Be careful not to fall.
Consort Yue.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I'm going to beg the Empress Dowager.
Why are you going to
beg the Empress Dowager?
It's about my brother's incident. I...
You can just leave me here.
Get back to work.
I've just come out of
the Empress Dowager's palace.
The news from the Empress Dowager is that
your brother escaped from the capital
and went north.
Now he has defected to Li State.
And he's about to attack Ning
with Yi Qingyun.
You're talking nonsense!
My brother would never do such a thing.
Your brother wouldn't do it indeed.
But now we've all
fallen into someone else's trap.
Trap?
What trap?
It's such a pity that
the Qilin Army's identity
has been exposed.
The Qilin Army rashly attempted to
get him out of prison.
That was instigated by someone.
Those were all traps.
The purpose was to force your brother
into a desperate situation.
Was it Yi Qingyun?
Yes.
But not really, either,
At a time like this,
just don't keep me guessing.
Tell me who it was.
It was Jiang Yunqing, who is
the fake princess
and your brother's fiancée.
How is that possible?
The Qilin Army's rebellion was suspicious.
After the Empress Dowager
learned about this matter,
she immediately sent people
to investigate it.
Only then did we discover that Yunqing
was actually an impostor.
Moreover,
the news that Yue Chi would be executed
was also deliberately spread by her.
She wouldn't do that.
My brother and Yunqing
love each other so deeply.
She wouldn't put my brother
in mortal danger.
I think she must have
her own reason.
What's more, last time,
when she abducted me,
she didn't hurt me at all.
She's not that kind of person.
No matter what reason she has,
she shouldn't have done
such a rebellious thing
to betray her country and family.
The Empress Dowager has sent people
to search for this woman.
Once they find her,
she will be killed.
I don't believe she would do such a thing.
I need to find her
and figure out the truth.
Based on just your few words,
you can just sentence her to death?
Don't be impulsive.
Her martial arts skills are very good.
What if you get hurt?
She won't hurt me.
But without
the permission from His Majesty
and the Empress Dowager
you can't leave the palace.
I can beg the Empress Dowager
to allow me to go to
Cheng'en Temple alone
to pray for my husband
and repent for my brother.
If you insist on going,
as it's difficult to travel
to the northwest area,
I'll go with you.
Jiang Yunqing always appears
and disappears mysteriously.
Where can we find her?
I know a place.
I guess she might be hiding there.
Alright. I'll do as you say.
It's fine if you can't ride a horse.
But you even have motion sickness from it.
I'm fine.
Finding Yunqing is more important.
Giddy-up!
Uncle Liu?
Why is he here?
What's wrong, Ling'er?
Yunqing.
Ling'er.
The Empress Dowager has issued a decree.
They're searching for you everywhere.
So I thought
you might be here.
Then I came to take a look.
You shouldn't have come.
At that time, the Qilin Army
was incited by others
and thought my brother
would be executed soon.
They...
They all said it was you
who spread this news.
It was me indeed.
You know what?
Yue Chi was arrested for treason.
Yue Chi?
That Yue Chi?
He was arrested?
He was finally arrested.
Yue Chi deserved to be arrested.
Yunqing.
Why?
Did my brother let you down,
or did someone force you to do that?
It's okay, Yunqing.
If you have any difficulties
that you can't speak of,
you can tell me.
I'm Consort Yue now.
I have the power to help you.
Ling'er.
My relationship with Yue Chi is over.
How can you just give up on
your many years of
relationship with my brother?
I can even give up on myself,
let alone him.
As a citizen of Ning,
I have to help our country
arrest people like you,
who have strayed from the right path
and betrayed your country and family.
But now,
for Ling'er's sake,
I'll let you off this time.
But in the future,
if you dare to do anything
to hurt Yue Chi and Ling'er,
I won't let you off.
It's Jiang Yunqing. Shoot arrows!
Don't!
I'm the Imperial Uncle.
Consort Yue and I are both here.
I'd like to see who dares to do it.
Put down the arrows.
Yunqing.
Just leave.
Let's go, Ling'er.
Let's go back to the palace.
I'm not going back to the palace.
Then where are you going?
Are you going to look for her?
Yes.
Now that's the only clue
to find my brother.
Then why didn't you chase her just now?
If I had chased her just now,
would she let me do so?
I was wondering why you
let her go just now.
I really couldn't
bear to see Yunqing
die right in front of me.
However,
since Yue Chi is working with Yi Qingyun,
she's very likely to appear at
the border between Li and Ning.
Do you know
if we want to go to
the border, we'll have to
climb very hight mountains
and cross very deep sea?
Can you and I do that alone?
No matter what,
I must find my brother.
Wait!
I'll go get the horses right away.
Is that okay?
You don't know anything,
and you still want to go alone?
Guys, you can go back first.
I will
report this matter to
His Majesty and the Empress Dowager.
Yes.
Look. Haven't we caught up with her?
At least, we caught up with her
before we might get killed.
Why don't we also take a break?
I really can't endure it anymore.
Yunqing stood up.
Is she about to leave?
This is not okay.
I need to drink some water.
Just a sip of water.
There's no time for drinking water.
Don't drink. There's no time for it.
Let's keep up with her.
Giddy-up!
This witch...
Du Tianzhao!
Idiots.
Yunqing has gone far.
Hurry up. Let's catch up with her.
Alright.