[A Prime Minister's Disguise]
[Episode 17]
I'm so happy that I don't even know
what to say.
Hahaha!
Loser pays
for treats today, alright?
Alright.
I'll definitely have you guys
losing round after round.
You're talking
as if you could actually beat me.
Exactly.
You bet I can!
Bring it on.
I'm going to
win all your savings
from you today.
Thank you all for keeping me
company today.
You're welcome.
That's what sisters are for.
You're really hard to beat.
Next time,
I'll definitely win it all back.
Of course.
You want to win my savings?
Dream on.
Hahaha.
It's getting late.
We should go back now.
Get some rest early.
Okay.
We're off then.
Hurry up.
Go back quickly. No need to see us off.
Your Highness,
are you waiting for His Majesty?
Your Majesty.
Aren't you going to see Consort Yue?
I will.
I'll go after I finish this stroke.
Your Majesty.
Jiang Yunqing has been captured.
When did this happen?
It's reported that the day
before yesterday,
when the Empress Dowager learned
that Consort Yue had been taken hostage,
she was furious
and sent out the imperial guards
to search the entire city.
This morning,
she was caught at the ferry dock.
Where is she now?
In prison.
Can we release her?
You go there yourself.
It'll still be difficult.
The Empress Dowager has assigned
soldiers to watch her there.
Go.
Summon Yue Chi secretly to the palace.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Someone new has been imprisoned
in the imperial jail?
Yes.
It's Jiang Yunqing.
We can't release her.
There are guards watching.
I beg Your Majesty to sentence me to death
to appease the people.
Yue Chi,
don't let me hear
you say that again.
Your Majesty.
You may leave.
Go.
Follow Yue Chi,
and keep an eye on him.
♪ Bones were decaying in the sandstorm ♪
♪ The Dayan Pass witnessed numerous wars ♪
♪ General Yue guarded the pass alone
with a blade alone ♪
♪ To conquer this pass ♪
-♪ 100,000 soldiers dared not fight with him ♪
-This place is quite nice.
♪ But top talents tend to fight
with each other ♪
They say the Princess Changping
isn't dead.
Isn't "Changping"
the title of a princess
from the previous dynasty?
Not only is she alive,
but she has been living
in Prince Anle's mansion all along.
Isn't that the current
Right Prime Minister's residence?
How could she be living there?
Yue Chi is engaged to
the former dynasty's princess.
He is a prince consort.
He must have
harbored treasonous intentions long ago.
Indeed.
Such a perfect chance—
I should take it and get rid of
Yue Chi for good.
How was it?
Very smooth.
Though this tea is not fancy,
it does quench thirst.
Right.
I've known that for a long time.
Well said.
Officials!
We once
advised His Majesty
that Yue Chi harbors treasonous intentions
and cannot be trusted,
yet His Majesty simply wouldn't listen.
I've sent people to investigate secretly
in the streets
and found that someone has already
reported to the government office
that Jiang Yunqing
did, in fact, stay at
Prince Anle's mansion.
Surely now, His Majesty
will believe our earnest advice.
Your foresight is truly remarkable,
my lord.
Yue Chi flatters His Majesty
of the new dynasty
while secretly colluding with
the remnants of the former court.
He's utterly shameless.
When dealing with
such a treacherous villain,
if we don't completely eliminate him,
even a sliver of opportunity could
allow him to rise again.
This time,
even if we have to sacrifice our lives,
we must eliminate
this treacherous scoundrel
for His Majesty and for Ning!
-That's right.
-Yes.
Lord Ouyang's righteousness is admirable.
Eunuch Gui is here.
Lord Ouyang,
is there something wrong?
Where is His Majesty?
We have matters to report.
His Majesty
is feeling unwell today
and won't be attending the morning court.
Please go back for now.
Is His Majesty truly ill,
or is he unwilling to punish Yue Chi?
Your Majesty!
Yue Chi has secretly harbored
the princess from the previous dynasty,
showing treasonous intentions!
Such betrayal
must be investigated!
Lord Ouyang,
-Lord Ouyang.
-Lord Ouyang!
Eunuch Gui,
has His Majesty given any instructions
concerning Yue Chi?
His Majesty said
to discuss it later.
Well... well...
To be discussed later?
Go request an audience
with the Empress Dowager!
Take a look.
No need to look.
I already know
what they wrote.
Nothing more than saying,
I'm incompetent,
Yue Chi is incompetent,
kill Jiang Yunqing,
and punish Prime Minister Yue.
Your Majesty,
how do you plan to handle this?
Let things cool off.
They've already forced your hand.
If you remain silent,
the country will decide for you.
I actually
didn't want to interfere
with political affairs.
But this time, I must advise you—
executing Jiang Yunqing
and temporarily removing
Yue Chi from office
would be the best choice.
I understand.
One.
Two.
Three!
You're here.
Come somewhere with me.
Where?
What are you going to do?
You know the answer. Don't play dumb.
No.
This is the second time you've defied me.
It's not the same.
This matter
absolutely cannot be done.
There's nothing that can't be done.
When I say it can be done,
it can be done.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
And Right Prime Minister.
Open the door.
Open the door?
But the Empress Dowager
has already ordered...
I said, open the door.
Are you defying my order?
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
I wouldn't dare.
Open the door.
Yunqing.
I'll take you away.
You go first.
You know what to say
and what not to say,
right?
Understood.
Hurry.
Report this to Her Majesty at once.
Yes.
Inside are money and medicine for wounds.
You can't stay in the capital anymore.
Leave as soon as possible.
Hyah!
About the matter with General Zhennan
back then...
I wasn't on your side.
Yes.
But this time,
you're on my side.
Back then, you didn't support me
because you were protecting
my country and its people.
Now I've chosen your side...
to protect your pure-hearted ideals.
In the end...
you were just acting out of selfishness.
It's not out of selfishness.
It's human nature.
For me?
And also for myself.
You are the Emperor!
You are the current sovereign!
There were so many other ways.
You've really gone mad.
Fake death, disguise,
jailbreak—you didn't use any of them!
What do you plan to do next?
Make myself an example
to silence them.
His Majesty has arrived!
[Benevolence and People First]
Jiang Yunqing has escaped from prison.
It was entirely my fault.
If I hadn't been so impatient
and had interrogated her alone,
she wouldn't have been able
to escape so easily.
It is I who have failed
this country and its people.
Your Majesty, you're being too hard
on yourself!
Please rise, Your Majesty!
[Benevolence and People First]
I...
also have failed
all of you who have placed your trust
in me.
I must apologize to you.
-Your Majesty, don't!
-We wouldn't dare accept, Your Majesty!
We wouldn't dare to accept
Your Majesty's apology.
Your Majesty!
So you won't accept my apology?
We wouldn't dare, Your Majesty.
I understand.
I should atone with my life.
Father.
Your son has come to join you.
Your Majesty!
You must not do this!
Please reconsider, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Then you don't want me
to atone with my life either.
So you'll just forgive me like that?
Your Majesty,
now...
the criminal has escaped.
Your Majesty
has been wholeheartedly
managing the realm.
What fault does Your Majesty have?
I think...
the most important thing right now is
to capture the criminal.
Indeed.
That makes sense.
What about the rest of you?
Your Majesty!
Is this what you all think?
-We concur, Your Majesty.
Since you all...
think this way...
quickly issue the arrest warrant.
-Your Majesty is wise.
I am tired.
You may withdraw.
Court dismissed!
-Respectfully seeing Your Majesty off.
I have a headache.
I can't attend the morning court.
My tooth hurts.
[Qian Duoduo; Wei Zi'ang;
Zhang Xuwen; Wang Shiling]
Now I've chosen your side
to protect your pure-hearted ideals.
My throat hurts.
[Visionary Insight]
Uncle Liu,
don't come here anymore.
I'm dead.
I can't attend the morning court anymore.
Dead?
That's what the Yue family's servant said.
They're really something.
Your Majesty!
Where are you going?
To pay respects!
Pay respects?
Please offer one on my behalf
as well, Your Majesty.
-What's wrong?
-Young Master.
His Majesty's here.
Why is he here?
Didn't you tell them that I was sick?
I did.
He said you should rest well,
and there's no need to
announce his arrival.
He said he wanted to look around himself.
How long has he been here?
Quite a while.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
He's the Emperor.
He wouldn't let me.
Found the right sick voice.
You're standing a bit too close.
Pull it back a bit farther.
Raise your arms higher.
The stone will drop as it flies,
so you need to aim
a bit higher
than the pear.
Shoot.
See?
Am I right?
I hit it!
Yue, look! I hit the pear!
That's impressive.
Shuo.
Why don't you go inside first?
We have something to discuss.
Go.
He's very smart.
And mature beyond his years.
What brings you here?
Not busy today?
Come to check on my supposedly sick
Right Prime Minister...
who's still able to drink.
Your Majesty, that's too much.
I finally
found a chance to rest,
and here you come all this way
to scold me.
Yue Chi.
Running away solves nothing.
What's done is done,
and the outcome is set.
Avoiding it
won't change that.
I'm not avoiding anything.
Then why didn't you attend
the morning court?
I'm sick.
Yue Chi!
Alright.
I just...
feel a bit guilty.
Since you feel guilty,
then work with me to
protect the realm.
I'm not a good Prime Minister.
And I'm not a good Emperor either.
So, let's join hands
and try to be a good pair
of ruler and minister.
And what if we fail?
Then let's bring chaos
to the court together.
Court dismissed!
-Respectfully seeing Your Majesty off.
Right Prime Minister.
You finally decided to come to court?
I have important matters to attend to.
[Fengyuan Hall]
Greetings to Your Majesty.
What's with you today?
Your etiquette is so proper.
I was worried about you,
so I came to check on you specifically.
During the court session,
you seemed absent-minded.
When the ministers were speaking,
you kept drifting off.
I had a dream last night.
Dreamed all night long.
All about Ling'er.
Dreamed about Ling'er?
What were you doing in your dream?
Shame on you!
Could you not be so dirty-minded?
I dreamed that Ling'er...
was in a thick fog.
I couldn't see her.
But I just felt
that she was in danger.
Dreams often mean the opposite of reality.
You're the Emperor—you really
believe in such things?
No.
This dream
is precisely a warning to me.
Think about it.
If Yi Qingyun,
the Crown Prince of Li,
not only bought off Cao Mang
but also turned Jiang Yunqing
into his pawn,
then imagine how big
the web he's weaving is.
Are there his people in the court?
In the harem?
There must be.
So,
our top priority is to get
Ling'er out of the palace.
You mean...
to let the consort leave the palace
temporarily to worship Buddha?
No.
Once and for all.
Of course, it's fake.
The fact that you disguised yourself
as Concubine Yue to enter the harem
is no longer a secret.
At least,
Jiang Yunqing knows about it.
So,
we might as well kill two birds
with one stone.
We can make Consort Yue
disappear for good
and have Ling'er leave the palace safely.
You don't have to worry about those things
you did before being exposed either.
How wise.
Therefore,
I'll give you three days
to come up with a reasonable plan
for Consort Yue's death.
Me?
Three days?
I should have kept pretending to be sick
and not attended morning court!
Three days.
Two plans.
There's one more thing that's a pain.
You think
Ling'er will agree
to leave the palace?
I'm not leaving the palace.
I just said you were sensible.
I don't want to leave the palace.
But you are the Emperor.
I have no choice but to obey.
The way you say it
makes it sound like I'm forcing you.
Actually, what I meant to say is,
I don't need to hide
behind all of you forever.
At least while I'm in the palace,
I can still watch over you all.
Ling'er.
You can watch over us...
while you're in the palace,
but everyone else
is also watching you.
They're even trying to use you
to find dirt on your brother.
If the fact that your brother
impersonated you
becomes widely known,
they could then charge him with
the crime of defiling the harem
and accuse me of being licentious.
At that time,
I wouldn't be able to do anything.
Alright, I'll leave the palace.
But Your Majesty, you must promise me
that no matter what happens,
you will always keep me informed.
Please don't make me worry.
Alright.
I know.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty...
An urgent report from the Magistrate
of Miyang County,
under Qi City jurisdiction.
[This morning, this subject, County Magistrate of Miyang in Qi City, discovered the whereabouts
of Princess Wen Rou of the Northern Commandery from the former dynasty]
[The princess is safe and well and wishes to come to the capital to pay respects to
Your Majesty and the Empress Dowager. Respectfully requesting permission]
What is it?
Princess Wen Rou, daughter of
the Prince of Northern Commandery,
missing for years,
has suddenly reappeared.
Princess Wen Rou...
That name sounds quite pleasant.
Our Huo family
and the Prince of Northern Commandery
have been family friends for generations.
The Prince of Northern Commandery
was also a founding hero
who died in battle.
It's just that his fate was unfortunate.
His whole family is either dead
or scattered,
and only one descendant remains.
She should be brought
to the capital to enjoy a peaceful life.
But after all these years,
there's been no news of her.
How did she suddenly
appear in Qi City?
The County Magistrate of Miyang said
she had just been rescued
from the mountains.
However, Princess Wen Rou
is quite eager to come here
to pay her respects to Your Majesty.
Then let
the County Magistrate of Miyang
escort her here.
This girl
must have also
suffered a lot.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wen Rou pays her respects to Your Majesty
and Your Majesty the Empress Dowager.
Quick, get up, get up. Have a seat.
Princess,
it's been so long since we last met.
Why did you end up in Qi City?
I apologize for not coming sooner
to pay my respects.
Please forgive me.
I...
Speak freely.
What exactly have you been through
all these years?
The Empress Dowager and I
will certainly see that justice
is done for you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Two and a half years ago,
[War Report: Prince of Northern Commandery died in battle,
and all 30,000 soldiers of the Northern Commandery perished]
when news of Father's death
in battle arrived,
my mother passed away in grief.
Then our mansion was broken into
by a gang of bandits.
I escaped in the chaos
but fell into the clutches
of human traffickers.
They even broke my leg.
Fortunately, an old lady took pity on me
and secretly set me free.
I went with her into the mountains
and hid there the whole time.
Only recently,
after my health improved,
did I finally gather the courage
to come out and inquire.
Only then did I learn
that Jingheng had already
achieved victory,
ushering Ning into a new era.
I hurried to the nearest county office.
Only then did I find out
that I had been in
Miyang County under Qicheng's Qi City
for the past two years.
All these years,
you've suffered greatly.
I will arrange
everything properly for you
to comfort the spirits of your parents
in heaven.
That's right. Jingheng,
how about
letting her stay in the capital?
It'll be convenient for us
to take care of her.
Your Majesty,
Your Majesty the Empress Dowager,
I hope to stay in the palace
to serve you.
Serve...
Your Majesty?
Silly girl,
what's so good about life in the palace?
It's much freer outside the palace.
Princess,
I have a younger brother
who is still unmarried.
If you don't mind,
you could consider meeting him.
He is handsome and intelligent.
Please forgive me, but I must decline.
I'm still fearful and uneasy.
The only ones I trust
are Your Majesty and His Majesty.
I beg for your mercy and allow me to stay.
Princess Wen Rou has had a long
and tiring journey.
Please go and rest first.
I will
discuss it
thoroughly with Mother.
Yes, indeed.
Please rise, please rise quickly.
Then...
I shall take my leave now.
Mother, what are you doing?
Here I was, worrying
you might be too shy around women.
It seems I was overly concerned.
Behind the scenes,
you're quite the seducer.
What are you talking about,
Mother?
Am I wrong?
If you hadn't been leading her on,
why would a perfectly good girl
want to enter the palace to serve you?
Because you're good-looking?
How would I know?
Have you all heard?
That orphaned daughter of the Prince of
Northern Commandery—Wen Rou—
has been arranged to stay at
Qunyu Pavilion.
Really?
That garden is quite large.
It's just a bit far from Yongqian Palace.
Far or not,
His Majesty doesn't visit the harem
much anyway.
If he does come, it will be to
Fengluan Palace.
Why are you all looking at me?
If you want to come over,
you can all move
into Fengluan Palace too.
Come on, smell this new incense I made.
How's it going?
Have you thought of the plans
I asked you for?
The preliminary plan
is that she dies of illness.
Elaborate on it.
Still working on the details.
I need to get out more.
See?
Inspiration has just struck.
I heard
there's a new arrival in the harem,
the daughter of the
Prince of Northern Commandery.
Supposedly your childhood sweetheart,
and you two were betrothed
before you were even born?
Nonsense.
So, are you going to marry her or not?
I've heard quite a few
rumors about her.
There's even a rumor...
that she'll become the future Empress.
Empress?
That she will never be.
However...
this world-renowned
Prince of Northern Commandery
died in battle.
He was a founding meritorious general.
Naturally...
I must treat his daughter with
the respect she deserves.
What's with that look?
You didn't get along with him in the past?
He's already no longer with us.
Why bring up such trivial matters?
The Prince of Northern Commandery
died on the battlefield.
He was a meritorious official.
It's only right
that I posthumously honor him
and treat his daughter well.
Then...
the position of Empress...
Shut up.
I never intended to
keep Wen Rou
in the harem.
If you really don't like her,
then just keep her in the harem.
After all, your harem
is full of concubines.
One more won't make a difference.
Every family is trying to send
their daughters to the harem.
They all want your favor.
All those concubines in the harem
were sent by their parents
to the palace
as pawns to gain my favor.
They're pitiful, in their own way.
Wouldn't keeping Wen Rou in the harem
just be wasting her life?
I'm just stating the facts.
Alright,
it's getting late.
Let's go back.
Do I have to go back with you?
Let's go, Prime Minister Yue!
There's a pile of memorials to review!
Is this plan feasible?
It's feasible.
I have everything prepared.
[Yongqian Palace]
Your Majesty.
I have prepared some
local delicacies from
the Northern Commandery.
Please try them, Your Majesty.
You shouldn't have troubled yourself
with this trip.
You could have just had someone
deliver them.
Your Majesty granted me residence at
Qunyu Pavilion,
but hasn't come to visit yet.
I also wanted to come see Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I shall take my leave now.
Well, well, Yue Chi,
running off and leaving me
to deal with this.
Prime Minister Yue has matters to report?
I will announce your arrival.
No need.
I'd like to see
if you will
betray my sister.
Let me attend to Your Majesty.
No need.
I've long heard that Your Majesty
enjoys collecting various weapons.
Now that I see
this little piece,
I'm quite fond of it too.
I wonder if Your Majesty
would be willing to part with it.
This dagger...
is indeed exquisitely crafted.
No wonder you like it.
But I'm... reluctant to part with it.
Stingy,
it's a tea knife. Just give it to her.
Is it worth talking about for so long?
Your Majesty...
truly won't reconsider?
I won't.
Princess,
go to Shoukang Palace.
Go to the Empress Dowager.
I'm too stingy.
Usually,
I don't easily give rewards to people.
He really does
look like a gentleman of upright conduct.
Princess,
won't you withdraw now?