[A Prime Minister's Disguise]
[Episode 2]
My entire family fortune is about to
be depleted.
Having hobbies is fine,
but you can't just make
exorbitant demands.
Your Majesty,
when you first came to me,
you said that the new dynasty
was not yet stable,
with wolves lurking around the court,
and that the past 2 years of implementing
new policies had been difficult.
So, you wanted my brother to be
your right-hand man
to assist you in building
a prosperous era.
So I've
contributed both money and effort,
and I've offered you my own brother.
You can't deceive me, a maiden, right?
You're so clever and quick-witted.
I'm afraid you're more likely to be
the one deceiving others.
Who was it that said
your brother was disillusioned
with the former dynasty's turmoil—
and that you and I should work together,
put on an act to keep him by my side,
show him my utmost sincerity,
and gradually win him over
to help me?
That's right,
my idea wasn't wrong.
Who could have known that my brother
would be so difficult to handle?
But you still need him.
It's not that I need him.
It's the people who need him.
Your Majesty, please have some tea.
Stop being so polite.
You don't even have a cup here.
Rest assured, Ling'er.
We've grown up together since childhood.
I may fool others, but never you.
Whether this works out or not,
I promise you
that the Yue family will reclaim
its former glory.
I give you my word.
We didn't really grow up together.
My brother and I only studied
with you at private school for two years.
And besides,
I'm not doing this for the Yue family's
wealth and glory.
Please don't say that anymore.
You don't want wealth and glory?
Then what do you want?
Name it, and I'll grant you that as well.
I want my brother to be well.
Everyone says
he's a heaven-blessed prodigy
who became Prime Minister at only 20.
It's heaven's blessing
that came without effort.
But only I, as his sister, know
that the faster he rose,
the more dangerous
the court intrigues became.
The more military achievements he earned,
the more terrible scars covered his body.
I believe that someone like my brother
should be able to fulfill his ambitions
and have his name recorded in history.
I think the same as you.
Being recorded in history isn't difficult.
What's difficult is how
your contemporaries will judge you
and how future generations
will evaluate you.
I'm not just doing this for Yue Chi
but also for myself.
I know.
However,
I'm not responsible for that history part.
I'm only responsible for our family,
and these accounts don't look good at all.
Here,
look at this, look.
Our Yue family's fortune
is about to be completely depleted.
Don't worry.
I may let the current prime minister
starve,
but I won't let you, my old friend,
starve.
However much you want,
I'll approve it.
You've been a real friend.
Of course.
But there's just one condition:
you must be very careful
not to let your brother find out.
Rest assured.
My brother
is busy as hell in your harem right now.
He has no time to deal with this.
Besides,
I'm the real expert in managing finances
for our Yue family.
My brother appreciates this skill of mine
the most.
I like it too.
What did you say?
I said I like that you're smart
and clever.
I'd be really lucky
if you were my sister.
Why did Ling'er send me all these
women's makeup and trinkets?
Are these what I need?
I need money!
Without money, how can I keep
getting good weapons for that blockhead?
Your Highness,
Consort Hui has sent an invitation
for you to attend a tea gathering.
Consort Hui inviting me to
a tea gathering?
She likely has ulterior motives.
But Consort Hui said
she has invited all the consorts
in the palace.
If Your Highness doesn't go,
it'll spoil the mood.
Your Highness,
shall we go then?
If I go and these consorts
see through my disguise, what should I do?
But if I don't go, I'll offend them,
and that will definitely bring trouble
for Ling'er in the future.
We go.
Oh my.
Yue, you've finally arrived.
[Elegant Dwelling with Spring Grace]
You've kept us sisters waiting.
Are they planning to make a fool of me?
You're late, so you must be punished.
If I don't settle the score today,
Ling'er will have a hard time
when she's here in the future.
That's fine.
[Elegant Dwelling with Spring Grace]
Qu, you decide.
Shall we settle this with words
or with fists?
Shall it be "spicy" or "plain"?
[Elegant Dwelling with Spring Grace]
W-W-What do you mean
by "spicy" or "plain"?
"Words" or "Fists"?
"Words" means with the tongue.
"Fists" means with the hands.
"Spicy" means bloodshed.
"Plain" means shedding tears.
You should all know
my usual preferences by now.
After all, I come from a military family.
So if I can settle things with my fists,
I won't waste time arguing.
Qu,
didn't we say we'd just have her
dance for our amusement?
She's playing for keeps here.
The harem has always valued harmony
above all.
As the leading figure of the harem,
the punishment should naturally be
"words" and "plain."
Naturally, naturally.
Yue,
come here.
Yes, Your Highness.
Since this is all a misunderstanding,
I'll do my best to entertain you.
Come on, come on!
Sisters, gather around!
Since it's just us sisters today,
I've specially brought some treasures.
Doesn't the pearl powder you usually use
make you look unnaturally pale?
Doesn't it?
Doesn't that give you a fake kind
of whiteness?
Yes, Your Highness!
Now, let's look at our pearl powder.
It definitely won't make you
unnaturally pale.
This is the latest Yuxuan pearl powder
from Fuchun Shop!
Yuxuan pearl powder.
If we weren't close like sisters,
I wouldn't even bring it out normally.
Now, someone might ask,
"They're all pearl powders,
so why is our product so natural?"
Why is that?
-Yeah, why?
-Why?
Because our products use pink pearls.
[Elegant Dwelling with Spring Grace]
That's right.
Pink pearls are closer to
natural skin tones.
Pure white pearls are too stark.
It makes your face look deathly pale
and lifeless.
Look, look at this!
Isn't it?
How natural, right?
However, only 10 sets were sent
to the palace.
We only have 10 sets?
100 taels
per set.
-100 taels?
That's too expensive.
You look down on me?
Today, I'll give you a special price.
20 taels!
-20 taels?
-20 taels!
-We'd suffer a big loss!
-We'd go broke!
-Don't stop me!
Today is my birthday.
My sisters have come to celebrate with me.
What's wrong with squandering
some family fortune?
I'll take five sets!
I'll take five sets.
There are only 10 sets in total.
First come, first served.
We don't just have classic ones,
but also even exclusive palace editions.
Qu, this method is too sneaky!
I'm not buying.
I'm just going to take a look.
You...
Go ahead, try all you like!
There are some over here too!
Qu,
I'll go take a look too.
I'm not going to buy anything. I won't.
You...
Try it on, try it on.
Try it.
Try it, and you buy it.
Buy this set and get a free veil.
A free face veil.
A free face veil?
This is for sale too.
-Everyone, take a look.
-Look around, feel free to browse.
A free veil!
Open them up. There is more inside.
This one looks good.
This hairpin suits you perfectly.
Why was I not informed that Consort Hui
had invited Consort Yue to
the tea gathering?
Your Majesty was in council at the time,
so I...
The other consorts are quite hostile
toward Consort Yue.
There could be danger.
Next time,
prioritize your reports.
Then... are matters concerning
Consort Yue urgent?
150 taels.
Yue,
put away these two coral bracelets
properly.
When Xia Yunshuang receives her allowance
next month,
she'll buy them back.
Indeed.
We made a killing.
Those consorts sure have deep pockets.
You bet.
Then Huo Jingheng's pockets must be
even deeper.
Let's not overlook what's
right in front of us.
Let's go fleece him
for a big sum directly!
What does he usually like?
Why are you squinting like that?
You mean telescope?
Not bad, Yue.
You've learned new things.
Last month, foreign merchants
just brought in ten telescopes.
They say you can use them to see
all the way to the lotus flowers on top of
Great Guanyin Temple, miles away.
Is that so?
Then could you see the luminous pearl
at Taoniang's waist
in Zuixiang Restaurant?
Of course.
Zuixiang Restaurant is...
is not a mile away from here.
How much do you plan
to sell one telescope to me for?
Your Majesty, what are you saying?
I certainly won't sell the telescope
to you.
I'm worried that once you see so far,
you'll forget about me here
right in front of you.
You're better with words
than you are at making money.
Thank you for Your Majesty's praise.
You think that was a compliment?
You know full well the other consorts
dislike you.
Why do you still deal with them?
Because I want to become Empress!
Of course, I need to deal with them.
I've learned from Your Majesty's lesson.
I know I'm wrong now.
How many more accounts are left unsettled?
There are still many.
Help me out a bit, will you?
Why do His Majesty and Consort Yue
get along like buddies?
Ling'er.
I'll send you all the money I've earned.
Don't spend it all.
Give half of it to Dugu Xing
and tell him to immediately purchase
various high-quality weapons
not available on the market.
By the Empress Dowager's decree:
[Decree]
Rather than sitting idle,
it's better to strengthen your bodies
and minds!
When women are strong,
the nation is strong!
You shall all set an example
to establish a new trend
and empower the backbones
for our women in Ning!
From today forth,
morning and evening greetings
shall be replaced with physical training.
Is this still the imperial harem?
Why does it feel like a military camp now?
Don't say any more.
Don't piss off the Empress Dowager.
If she gets angry,
the entire harem will suffer.
I can't deal with Yue Ling'er,
but the Empress Dowager can.
If she offends the Empress Dowager,
she'll be in trouble.
But speaking of which,
where has Consort Yue gone?
Consort Yue...
Yue?
What are you looking for?
I don't know how it happened,
but I seem to have lost
the ruyi scepter that His Majesty
gifted Your Highness.
It was there when we came back.
If they ask about it during the inventory,
will they punish me?
Don't panic.
This area isn't that big.
We'll definitely find it.
Well,
you search this area,
and I'll go check over there for you.
Okay, Your Highness.
Ruyi scepter...
Forbidden area?
[Forbidden Area]
You've got some real skills.
Who's there?
Little one,
has anyone ever told you
that those who trespass here
will face serious consequences?
I am but an insignificant nobody
who has wandered here while playing.
I apologize for the disturbance.
I'll leave right away.
I'm not bragging, but
this forbidden area is full of traps.
There, just one more step forward,
and you'll meet your maker.
Looks like we can't settle this
with a nice chat.
Are you a man or a woman?
You don't look like a vicious criminal.
You'll let me go?
I can let you go,
but first...
can you help me...
Right,
can you turn that candlestick for me?
Since you know the layout
of the traps here,
how come you're still...
If you hadn't come in and accidentally
triggered that mechanism,
would I be trapped like this?
You've trapped yourself.
Are you going to help me or not?
It's just a simple yes or no.
Straightforward.
Such formidable inner strength
in that palm strike.
You're...
the "Ghostbane" Du Sanniang.
[Du Sanniang, Empress Dowager of Ning]
Your Majesty the Empress Dowager?
I truly stumbled in here by mistake.
Even if I had the courage of a lion,
I wouldn't dare disturb
Your Majesty's seclusion.
You were so direct just now,
but now you're all delicate.
How boring.
The paths around this forbidden area
are so twisted,
and you just happened to wander in?
Not bad, little one.
You can take two of my palm strikes.
Since Your Majesty thinks highly of me,
why don't you try taking one of
my palm strikes?
Interesting.
Come on!
I'll take my leave.
You're quite good at this trick
of misdirection.
But running away like this,
do you still care about your dignity?
What's "dignity"?
If you can't eat it,
it's not worth caring about.
You...
Your Highness, Your Highness,
I've found the ruyi scepter.
It had fallen into the flowerbed.
Your Highness, where did you go just now?
I ventured into the forbidden area.
Your Highness,
are you alright?
I've heard
that the Empress Dowager used to
have a nickname
in the martial arts world
called the "Ghostbane."
Many concubines in the palace before
who wanted to please the Empress Dowager
secretly trespassed into
the forbidden area.
They either crawled out
or were sent flying.
Your Highness,
how come you neither crawled
nor were sent flying?
Who did you interact with before losing
the ruyi scepter?
I think it was a maid from Yanning Palace.
She told me that there was
a rare flower there
and asked me to go see it.
From now on, have less contact with people
from Yanning Palace.
Why?
Your Highness, wait for me.
A woman's shoe,
and it's palace-made.
Your Highness.
Why are you missing a shoe?
Oh no,
the shoe.
What's going on here?
So many servants.
I wonder what's gotten into
the Empress Dowager today.
I heard
that a consort intruded into
the forbidden area
and even had a fight with her.
That person left behind a shoe,
and now the Empress Dowager is having
everyone try it on.
Such a big shoe.
Which consort in the whole palace
has feet that large?
-Greetings, Your Majesty.
Sister,
didn't you say the shoe was unusually big,
unlike what ordinary women would wear?
I've been thinking carefully,
and I find that it makes a lot of sense.
Which consort in the harem has
a large build and big feet?
I remember now.
Consort Yue has feet the size of a man's.
Yingwan, you tell us.
Right.
Apart from Consort Yue,
there's no other person.
Consort Yue...
Let's go.
The Empress Dowager has arrived!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
So, you are Consort Yue?
Yes, I am.
A villain trespassed into
the forbidden area
and disrupted Her Majesty's seclusion,
leaving behind this shoe.
All the consorts must try on
the shoe to prove their innocence.
Yue, would you come forward and try it on?
Since the entire palace is supposed to
try on the shoe,
how did it come so quickly
to my remote Fengluan Palace?
-Sister, have you tried...
-The style of this shoe
is clearly that of a consort's
embroidered shoes,
yet the size is so large.
Among all the consorts in the palace,
who else but you would
wear shoes this size?
Right!
That shoe looks about your size.
I don't understand what you mean by that.
What if someone is impersonating me?
There are countless guards and eunuchs
in the entire palace.
I imagine there are quite a few
who can fit into this shoe.
Earlier, Her Majesty was ambushed
by a villain in the forbidden area.
That person knows martial arts.
I've heard that you come from
a military family.
I suppose in this entire harem,
only you know martial arts.
Who says I know martial arts?
I'm just a delicate woman.
Whether you do or not,
we'll know with a test.
Your Majesty,
is it just because I was born
with big feet
and a tall, strong physique,
coming from a family of military generals,
that I should suffer unjust accusations
for no reason?
Your Majesty...
Enough!
So noisy!
You speak, then you speak,
and you speak several times!
Are you going to let me speak or not?
Whether it's true or not is not something
that needs arguing.
All martial artists practice
internal energy cultivation techniques.
One test will reveal all.
Your Majesty.
Even if it's Mother,
you can't harm my beloved consort, right?
And you,
something this serious happened,
why didn't you tell me?
What happened to my son?
Your Majesty,
during your days of seclusion,
Consort Yue was summoned daily
by His Majesty.
His Majesty treasures her
and favors her greatly!
That's incredibly rare.
I used to think all of the women
in the harem
were too delicate to match my son.
So I made a big fuss
and started training the harem concubines.
Along the way, this little one sneaked
into the harem,
rather amusing.
Thought I'd catch her to be
my son's companion.
Isn't this perfect?
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful!
Consort Yue.
I like you.
I want to be friends with you.
Come with me,
let's go drink!
Go.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Let's go drink!
Don't drink too much!
Your Majesty,
it seems there have been
some misunderstandings.
Later, I'll apologize to Yue
on behalf of all the other consorts.
You apologize on behalf of
all the other consorts?
Do you want to be the Empress,
or are you preparing to be
the Empress Dowager directly?
Consort Yue.
You've been in the palace
for quite some time.
But why do you always wear a veil?
Do you have some secret disease?
I... ate too many inflammatory foods
a few days ago
and broke out in a rash all over my face.
Plus, I was born plain.
I feared frightening Your Majesty
and His Majesty.
Take it off!
I said, take off this veil.
Do you know the punishment
for defying my command?
Yes, Your Majesty.
You look very much like
an old friend of mine.
Your Majesty,
I...
You...
look like my dear mother, who passed away
many years ago.
She was also as valiant
and cheerful as you.
I really can't control my emotions.
I've lost my composure.
Quickly, rise.
Let's drink!
Back in my day, I also roamed
the martial arts world.
My son
just wanted to be like his grandmother—
someone who fights against injustice
and roams freely as a hero!
Who would have thought...
that he'd become the most suffocated
and the most caged being—an Emperor?
Can the supreme ruler still
feel suffocated?
Utterly suffocated.
Look at his harem,
not a single consort is one
he wanted to marry.
Many rumors in the streets saying
that my son has no interest in women.
It chilled my heart.
Fortunately,
now that you're here, Consort Yue.
I am very pleased!
Drink.
Come on!
People say
that the Dragon Throne is
the highest seat,
the embodiment of supreme dignity.
Only those who actually sit on it know—
it really hurts your butt!
You can't lean your shoulders
or rest your back.
It's truly exhausting.
But he insists on saying
that someone taught him,
"For a bright and clear world,
for the peace and prosperity
of all people,
bear thousands of burdens in the court
and face countless difficulties
without regret."
Isn't that from my
Outline of the New Governance?
When did I ever teach Huo Jingheng that?
Your Highness,
you're finally back.
Are you alright?
I'll never lose anything again.
Go to the small kitchen for a good meal,
and that's your punishment.
It's been a long day.
I'm going to sleep like a log.
Your Highness,
I forgot to tell you.
His Majesty is waiting for you inside.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Consort Yue has had a long day.
Would you like to take a relaxing bath?
The weather is dry.
It's not good to bathe too often.
Then, my beloved...
are you ready to rest?
I'm not sleepy at all.
This emperor is too easily bewitched.
I haven't even switched places
with my sister yet.
How did things progress to us
sleeping together?
I am... still young.
I'm not ready yet.
I ask for Your Majesty's patience.
To be honest...
my being an emperor is like being forced
into a role I'm not prepared for.
I think...
it's time... I have a heart-to-heart talk
with you.
I'll have to use this sleeping incense
to put you to sleep.
This is...
your brother's
Outline of the New Governance.
[Outline of the New Governance]
Such a masterpiece for the ages,
not only did it not earn him a title,
but it's now been reduced to a single
incomplete volume.
Sit.
Your brother was taken too soon
by the heavens.
He was the youngest prime minister
in history.
He made countless achievements
to his name.
When he died,
you must have felt regret
and unwillingness
for him and for the Yue family,
right?
The consort must not interfere
in politics.
I understand nothing of such things.
If your brother were still alive today,
he would've shaped the dynasty anew.
Of course.
Don't you... have anything you want
to say to me?
Yes.
I thank Your Majesty for honoring
my brother's name.
I am like a delicate willow
swaying in the wind,
thinking that withering and falling
were my fate.
Little did I know that heaven
had other plans
and led me to Your Majesty.
I dare to boldly
ask Your Majesty for a favor.
My beloved, please speak freely.
I will do my utmost to fulfill
your request.
I
want to be the Empress!
Weren't you just pouring your heart out
to me?
Why silent now?
Calm yourself.
This is all for Ling'er.
Your Majesty...
you haven't answered my request yet.
A treasure such as this...
how could you keep it to yourself?
How many more do you have?
Take them out and let me see.
Your Majesty,
I didn't feel it earlier,
but now I'm suddenly overwhelmed
by sleepiness
that I can't even fight it off.
So, my beloved wishes to rest
for the night?
How come I'm suddenly not sleepy anymore?
Your Majesty.
This is a floor rag.
When I said to organize things properly,
I didn't mean for you to mix
everything up completely.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
I'll go change it right away.
No need.
Go.
Help Consort Yue to bed.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
You had a good sleep?
Do I look like I got any sleep?
At this rate, I'm afraid I'll ascend
to the heavens
before I ever become Empress.
It's not even 5 a.m. yet.
Where is he going?
His Majesty goes to the warm chamber
half an hour early every day
to review the memorials to be discussed
that day once more,
in case of any oversight.
His Majesty has been like this
for so many years,
day after day, the same routine,
without a break.
He does sound like a wise ruler.
Everyone says His Majesty is diligent,
unparalleled in history, and unlikely
to be surpassed.
But, Your Highness, why did you just say
"sounds like"?
Well, a wise ruler needs
a virtuous empress to assist him.
As virtuous as I am, I'm not yet
the empress,
so naturally, he can't be considered
a wise ruler yet.
Your Highness,
you and His Majesty share
the same interests.
You two seem like a perfect match
no matter how I look at it.
I rather wish he had some other hobbies.
Otherwise, he'll soon drain my fortune.
His Majesty actually treats you
extremely well.
Moreover, he's a man who pays attention
to details despite his rough appearance.
Today, His Majesty specifically
reminded me not to mix up this floor rag
with the face towel.
I didn't say he's not good to me.
I mean...
You're saying that this is a floor rag?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Well, you didn't ask me either.
[Zuoshun Gate]
Sir,
this is not good!
The city gate is about to close!
It's okay!
Hold on.
Open the gate!
Please forgive us, Your Excellency.
There's nothing to forgive.
I'm the one who delayed
your proper shift change.
Take this jade pendant as a reward.
Take it and treat yourselves.
Hyah.
Hyah!
Who was that?
So generous.
The Imperial Uncle.
[Du Tianzhao, Brother of Du Sanniang]
The current Prime Minister, Du Tianzhao.
Your Majesty,
I have an important matter to report.