One more son of착
durch
I heard that the Eldest Prince
is just fine
and like you.
For you.
sell the paper with the state
If the crown prince is not well-informed
Find out the truth
I don't know how many corrupt officials are there
No, this paper is so funny
Can you count on these people
Really do things for the people
Yes, this time
Really angry
Not only deprived all
The workers who participated in the paper
Also ordered their family within three generations
Not allowed to participate in the examination
Officials who participated
All are interrogated
And the family's paper
Have been left a thousand miles away
We have the crown prince
Such a good crown prince for the country and the people
Have a good life in the future
Yes
Right
Let's go
Go
The crown prince is now clear
The eldest prince is now cornered
It seems that there is no big deal
But how did the third prince take the money himself
He also bought officials
I actually only punished him for three years
As long as the noble consort Shu is still in favor
The third prince will be fine
Just buying and selling official positions
If this matter is not too big
The emperor can't cover it
Even the eldest prince will be fine
why
Listen to my dad
Our emperor
Likes to play with the quq
The more the quq is played
The happier he is
You say
Now there is no reason to be poor
One quq
How can he not
In his eyes
Now the crown prince
Even more rich
Lucky or not
It depends on fate
Husband is back
Thank you for your care these days
Husband is the one
You can have a good meal these days
If I don't let the kitchen
Prepare some food for the mountain
Later
Let Uncle Liu come to massage your husband
These are not a big deal
Come
Let me take a good look at the lady
Have you missed me these days
Madam
I naturally miss my husband
You are the one in this world
Most precious person
Husband is naturally also me in this world
Most caring person
Husband has been working hard these days
I have already prepared
Hot water soft soup
After dinner
Just rest early
I'll go to the kitchen again
it is good
Then the lady also rest well
I'll come to you later
The lady has been looking different these days
How different
Much calmer
Since the accident at home
The lady has always been in a state of shock
Although I also joke with others
But I can see
The anger on the lady is not gone
These days are much calmer
I don't have a heart now
I can't calm down at a moment
If I don't forget the hatred
But lady
You calm down
This is a good thing
Calm down
To find out everything
You are right
Calm down
To find out everything
Your Highness
Madam, why are you here
Did I bother you
Not bad
Sit down quickly
I have read almost all the books I brought
Want to find from your husband
A few books
The second book on the left of the book
All kinds of travel
Look, do you like it
This Eastern Palace
Nothing is impossible for you to touch
I have found one
Can find something you like
Did I scare you
No
I read too weak?
I was too weak, right?
These notes...
Mother, you've grown used to it.
Every time you read the book,
you write down your thoughts and thoughts.
This way,
it helps to deepen my memory.
You're so brilliant.
You've opened up Chu Yun's eyes.
It's just some notes.
What's wrong?
Are you surprised?
My Lady,
you mean
the Crown Prince is not the so-called grass bag?
In a letter,
you can find the method of implementation of the national policy
and the analysis.
How can such a person be a grass bag?
But everyone says so.
The Crown Prince is not in good health.
He's not well-educated.
Either everyone has misunderstandings about him,
or he's been trying to get the good news.
If he's trying to get the good news,
why is he not hiding anything from me?
Be careful.
Isn't...
Isn't he the cleaner of the garden?
Why...
Su Zhu,
do you think the Eastern Palace we see now
is the real him?
How many secrets
is hidden in this palace?
It's really him.
Your Highness.