(6th night of their trip in Nepal)
Gosh, I'm tired.
(The Four Brothers returned
to their lodging.)
(Tough off-road experiences
in the morning)
(Swimming in freezing water
in the cold in the evening)
(Shivering)
(They dragged their exhausted bodies
to a photo studio in Nepal.)
We're taking a short break.
(Knocked out due to their tough schedule)
(Staring)
(Chuckling)
They look like dead batteries.
(Among the brothers
who are sprawled out like dead batteries)
(Rummaging alone in the corner)
Since I'm leaving earlier than you,
I brought gifts from Korea.
What?
They got up automatically.
(The youngest was scheduled
to leave earlier than them.)
(Before they knew it,
his last night arrived.)
I brought these.
(Feeling sad to say goodbye,
he brought presents for the brothers.)
Feel free to stay in bed
when I give it to you.
- I'll start with Kian84.
- Yes?
I brought Kian84's favorite.
(Ta-da)
(Fancy whiskey)
- It's alcohol.
- What's that?
I bought you an expensive one
so that you don't get a headache.
(He looked for whiskey
everywhere in the world.)
(Kian, aged 84 years)
Kian84 doesn't drink...
a lot of alcohol.
I thought that he found comfort
in alcohol.
It's a customized gift.
Whenever he feels tired...
or needs comfort,
I hope that he can enjoy it...
during the rest of their trip.
- Oh, my.
- This is for you.
You bought an expensive one.
I felt so thankful to him.
Actually, you know the thing that
people take out from their pockets...
in movies.
I bought it for him.
But it got delivered on the day
I was leaving Korea.
I'll give it to you
during our shoot in the studio.
That's a bummer.
- So I brought it today.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
That's why he was rummaging a moment ago.
(Arrived on a plane...)
You can keep alcohol inside.
- Gosh, thank you.
- Goodness.
- It's a little late.
- That's amazing.
Thank you.
I'll drink everything from this,
including soju.
- This is great.
- I should've given it to him a while ago.
(Precious)
(Satisfied)
- This is for Si Eon.
- What is it?
- These are poles.
- The ones you used yesterday?
(Trekking poles)
Surprisingly, Si Eon and I have
many hobbies in common.
Riding the motorcycle, camping...
- Right.
- That's right.
They have similar tastes.
So he probably has almost everything
that I'd like to give him.
But I thought that
he wouldn't have packed...
- trekking poles.
- They make hiking very comfortable.
Si Eon, these are very comfortable.
You ended up bringing them.
I deliberately showed...
those trekking poles to Si Eon.
To see if he was interested in them.
I wanted to see if he liked them.
- Aren't they nice?
- Yes.
I casually brought it up,
and he liked them.
I hope that during the remaining trip,
these poles will be
another set of legs for Si Eon.
I gave them to him
hoping that they'll help him.
- These are nice.
- And so...
I wanted you to use them
in case the remaining trip is hard.
(Feeling proud)
I got something special for Pani Bottle.
What do you think this is?
Shampoo for hair loss?
- "Shampoo for hair loss?"
- Goodness.
Isn't it shampoo for hair loss?
While traveling...
with you guys for a while,
I figured out what you like.
Pani Bottle is very curious,
and he likes trying various things.
So I brought a Swiss Army knife.
Right. He likes knives.
- That's right.
- I still have that.
- It includes all types of tools.
- That's amazing.
There are so many.
- Thank you.
- And...
there's one more.
Why does Pani Bottle get two presents?
I wanted to get this for Pani Bottle.
I thought that he'd love it.
I removed the packaging
in order to test it.
- What?
- What is it?
These are binoculars.
What makes them special is
that they're night-vision binoculars.
(His jaw drops.)
That's incredible.
I've really wanted these.
You can record videos with them.
- They record videos?
- When you shoot for YouTube...
He runs a YouTube channel.
(A present dedicated to Pani Bottle)
- That's amazing.
- Wait, after doing this...
I've wanted to buy them for a while.
That's an awesome present.
- Shall we test them outside?
- How do they work?
- Let's take a look outside.
- This is the general mode.
(Everyone goes outside
to check the function.)
- I'm curious about this.
- Unbelievable.
When you do this...
When you switch to IR mode,
the night vision turns on.
- The color is different.
- That's fascinating.
Do you see the dark spot over there?
- Adjust...
- Can you zoom in?
You can't zoom in, but you can film it.
- It's 4K.
- It's 4K?
- When you press record...
- How is 4K possible?
(A raspy voice)
- It's recording.
- That's amazing.
Let's say hello.
(Let's say hello to the camera.)
- Hello, Dex.
- Wait, you're too close.
Si Eon.
Si Eon, you look like you're in "Gonjiam."
- It looks like "Gonjiam."
- That's scary.
It looks like "Gonjiam."
- That's frightening.
- Right?
That's creepy.
Pani Bottle looks scary too.
- This is my son.
- It looks like "Gonjiam."
- The ghost of Nepal.
- They look so scary.
(A wandering baby ghost in Nepal)
This is how you turn off the recording.
Do you want to turn off the lights
and test it inside?
This is real infrared.
I'll turn off the lights. Come inside.
- Hide.
- I'll hide underneath.
- That's fun, you know.
- It's fun.
Why is it making me nervous?
This house has been abandoned
for 30 years.
He's definitely an actor.
I'll look and see if there are ghosts.
- "Gonjuiam."
It's Kian84. He died 30 years ago!
- Why would you kill me?
- Why does he keep killing him?
Pani Bottle's nose is stuffed!
No!
(And then there were none.)
I knew what was going on,
but it was still scary.
- This is amazing.
- Can you see?
Don't turn on the lights. I'll show you.
I didn't expect them to have so much fun.
Take a look, Si Eon.
It's very short. It's like a movie. Watch.
I'll look for myself.
- "Gonjuiam 2."
The sequel already came out?
It's because the first one was a hit.
I knew it.
This is where Actor Lee Si Eon...
tragically lost his life...
in an accident.
- What is he doing?
- Why did you kill him?
After hearing that
Lee Si Eon appears here often,
I came here to boost my view count.
- The story is interesting.
- My gosh.
(Screaming)
That really startled me.
You startled me.
(Achieving enlightenment through joy)
- Goodness.
- "Achieving enlightenment through joy."
- What?
- He was really scary.
I know that he's acting,
but it's still scary.
I knew it, but I was scared.
(Growling)
(The audience's response
makes his acting more passionate.)
The four guys are having a lot of fun
with a night-vision device.
- That was really scary.
- Dex.
It was really frightening.
- Amazing.
- I'm satisfied.
It's the first time in my life that
someone figured out my exact taste.
He was more exact than anyone else.
It made me shudder as soon as I saw it.
We're close,
but not close enough to be best friends.
I need to get permission
from Dex's manager to say that.
That's not true.
(We're best friends.)
I thought,
"How did he know that I like this?"
It gave me goosebumps.
I got very excited
while playing with the device.
Right, I've never seen him happier.
(Beaming)
- Gosh, thank you.
- Here's the manual.
(Reaching)
- I bought this T-shirt for you.
- A T-shirt?
- I bought it in the Himalayas.
- Gosh.
- I have nothing to give him.
- Thank you.
What's this? Oh, my.
What's this?
There's a drawing.
(The one and only portrait of Dex)
This is amazing.
- That's really amazing.
- Oh, my.
When did he draw that?
- Where are you going?
- It's a secret.
He kept wanting to go somewhere.
(As Sherpa84,
he carries his bag on his head.)
(In front of a beautiful view)
(Flopping down)
(My goodness)
(He takes out the watercolor.)
I brought some watercolors with me.
Usually, he travels very light.
I made a drawing for Si Eon.
I also made one for Pani Bottle
on his birthday.
I made a drawing for everyone but Dex.
Before he left,
I wanted to make one for him.
That's why I went to draw.
(Instead of ordinary drawing paper)
(A T-shirt that he bought
in the Himalayas)
Was it at that time?
What?
(After getting changed on the street)
I didn't know about that.
He knows how to recycle.
(When he met Dex
with 100 percent energy...)
(The T-shirt was peeking out.)
Oh, that T-shirt.
(In a place marked with memories
and sweat from the journey,)
(he draws Dex,
a part of his precious memories.)
Gosh, he picked a good photo of me.
(He even selected it carefully.)
(He must have been very tired
that morning.)
(Mixing each color)
He only has five colors.
(Concentrating on the painting
without moving an inch)
That's a painting in itself.
It looks beautiful.
My leg feels numb.
(Groaning)
- That's touching.
- Gosh.
- He paints well.
- His drawings are nice.
(The painting is being completed.)
(He presses down hard to write his name.)
"Dex."
"To Adventure by Accident."
He looks handsome.
(He took 2 hours
to finish Dex's portrait.)
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
It's a family treasure.
- That's amazing.
- Thank you.
- It looks incredible.
- It looks amazing.
It's too nice to wear it.
"The closing trip
of Adventure by Accident?"
That makes me sad.
It's a message to Dex...
and to myself.
Actually,
every time Dex came to shoot
Adventure by Accident,
he vomited and got an upset stomach.
(He often suffered
due to his fragile intestines.)
- He went through a lot.
- He never showed how tough it was.
However, he was willing to come back.
(However, he was willing to come back.)
Dex probably thinks
that this is his last trip.
(Dex came in a hurry
since it's his last trip.)
(They finally became complete
when the youngest joined them.)
I'm thankful that he joined us.
I'll remember this for a long time.
(The Four Brothers' closing trip)
I'm happy that he came.
I didn't expect him to give me a present.
I never imagined that it'd be a painting.
I remember feeling very envious
in Madagascar.
(Ta-da)
- That was really...
- I envy him.
This is very...
I thought,
"It should have been my birthday instead."
"That present should have been mine."
Even back then,
I didn't envy him
for getting a painting...
by a famous cartoonist in Korea.
Giving a present made with so much love...
to someone else...
That's what made me envious.
I'm happy to receive such a present.
To receive care and love from Kian84.
On the T-shirt,
there was a message
that said this was our last trip.
The date was written on it,
and that felt so meaningful.
I think the time we had together
is captured in the picture.
Looking at the picture,
well,
this trip could be the last one together,
and I thought I could remember it...
with the picture being its symbol.
I feel so thankful, and I am happy.
(I'm thankful to Kian84.)
So, I...
What is that?
This is so nice.
This is awesome.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
I should have drawn a nicer picture.
- This is good enough.
- The paint didn't soak well.
I will surely hang this at home.
It's really nice.
It's great.
It's his last day here.
How about the last drink?
- Shall we have the last drink?
- Let's have the last drink.
- Let's drink fast.
- Dex, I'll open this.
I gave it to you. Do as you like.
It's yours.
I'll cut this for you.
Do you want to try?
- All right.
- You can do it, right?
It's easy. Cut this in half.
Here you go.
That knife was very sharp.
It goes deep into the fruit.
(It tastes even better.)
- Cheers.
It should taste good with whiskey.
This is what I'm curious about.
Which gift makes you the happiest?
A picture or something practical.
- Right.
- Something I really need.
But to gift something practical,
you need to have a good knowledge
of the person you're giving it to.
I forgot the fact that I said I wanted it.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- I was so happy when I got it.
When I was serving in the military,
I was dispatched abroad.
I marched in the desert,
put up a tent in the middle of the desert,
and slept in it.
When I was a junior soldier,
things were so tough for me.
When I was lying in the desert,
looking at the night sky
with the night-vision device and focusing,
numerous stars in the universe...
unfolded before my eyes.
I was so shocked and thought that...
(Thinking over)
when I meet someone I want to marry,
I'd show her the stars with
a night-vision device and propose to her.
That's so romantic.
Oh, my.
- So Pani Bottle is the one?
- That's...
Goodness.
(What's going on between you?)
- No.
- Wait.
I'm not ready.
(Dex, I'm not ready yet.)
- Shall I move my seat?
- Come on.
This is how they do it.
(The best friends are united
by a night-vision device.)
It means that I gave him...
my favorite item, a night-vision device.
(Pleased to see them)
Where do we take the plane?
Where do we stop over?
I guess we have a direct flight to China.
It's either diesel or gasoline, isn't it?
Gosh.
He never stops.
(Very satisfied)
He's smiling.
(Fueling up laughter by force
with his dad joke)
You like these kinds of jokes.
You're smiling now, unconsciously.
It's because I'm annoyed.
You'll show it when you're annoyed.
He's half-annoyed and half-satisfied.
The fact I'm laughing at your joke
makes me annoyed.
I'm kind of immersed.
- Yes, and...
- I imagined it.
tonight, it's just like us.
- Don't you think so?
- You're right.
When a day is over,
we talk over a drink like this.
(They used to share laughs and talks
on many nights.)
Kian84 ate chicken, sitting on the ground.
(A part of "being like us")
So this trip delights me more than ever.
Really?
We have a lid on the toilet,
in the first place.
It was much nicer than I thought.
During this trip,
Si Eon was so awesome to me.
He never got angry. Not even once.
- That's right.
- Right.
- He looked gentle from beginning to end.
- Come on.
He really is a grown-up.
He really feels like a grown-up,
an elder brother.
Among these three, I like you the most.
(Among these three, I like you the most.)
I like you the most, Dex.
(Competitive)
They're nice together.
(Things get very sweet.)
It was the last day of my trip.
And the last night...
was spent between ourselves
in a small, simple,
ordinary,
and complete manner.
That felt more meaningful.
And it was nice to be with them.
(India, 2 years ago)
That was his first trip with us.
It's already been two years?
(Glad to see him)
(He met Kian84 while feeling nervous.)
(The Kim brothers
didn't even know their first names.)
(Is your name Kim Ki An?)
(Is your name Kim Dex, then?)
(With the other brother,)
(he laughed awkwardly.)
- I felt awkward in the beginning.
- Right.
(Dex was a strange man
before he became the youngest member.)
Gosh, it's suffocating.
They're turning heads.
(It was hard to make eye contact,)
(but soon they hit it off.)
They hit it off so well.
(With his energy...)
(and sweet charms)
- He's sweet.
- Isn't that Alex?
- Hi.
- I missed you.
(Snuggling into his brothers' arms)
(Having nice talks,)
(he became the youngest member
the brothers want to walk with.)
On Adventure by Accident,
Dex is an indispensable axis.
He's the ace among us.
(Enjoying the thrill...)
(in a relaxed manner)
(Welcoming challenges...)
(with passion)
(As he took the lead
in the adventure all the time,)
(he received wholehearted support.)
- Let's go, Dex!
- He's the cheerleader captain.
(The youngest became
the pride of the brothers.)
Look how they feel proud.
(Our youngest...)
(is from the Navy special forces.)
(The eldest feels proud.)
I just feel that I was so happy...
in the moment.
(In every moment together)
(Crying)
(Surprised)
Gosh.
I don't know. Why am I like this?
(Although he tries to hold back,)
(tears keep streaming down.)
I've never seen him crying like a child.
Thinking those moments
will never come back,
I choked up.
I felt so sorry that it was the last night
the four of us were spending together.
Right.
Strangely, what stays in my memory...
is not anything else, but...
In the car, on our way back from camping,
how I listened to the lame jokes.
That's the final thing I remember.
(We're in Nepal now.)
(Can't we make 4 arms in groups of 2?)
(What?)
(Which country has
the largest number of gangsters?)
(Chile?)
(Glaring)
Those vibes and atmosphere.
I just feel that I hate it, but I love it.
That's the charm of them.
And before I knew it,
I got immersed,
as if getting wet in a drizzle.
If you get immersed
by those trivial moments,
- there's no way out.
- Right.
- Dex, thank you for your effort.
- Thank you for your effort.
Thank you for your effort, Dex.
- Good luck on the rest of our trip!
- Thank you.
- All right!
When did you actually go there?
It was about six years ago.
Their conversation doesn't end.
(Feeling sorry, they keep talking.)
- Have a good night.
- Good night.
(They go to bed at dawn.)
- Dex.
- What?
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes. See you tomorrow.
- Good night.
(As they say good night tenderly,)
(the night in Nepal deepens.)
- Who is it?
- What's that?
- It's me.
- It's Dex.
(Dex can't sleep,
so he turns the light on.)
(Gazing)
(The youngest looks at
the sleeping brothers for a long time.)
I guess I had mixed feelings.
I just, alone,
got sentimental.
(Soothing his heart
by drinking alone at night)
He can't go to sleep.
(After packing the T-shirt he was given,)
(the Four Brothers all go to sleep.)
(The day breaks.)
Let's get out. We need to leave.
- We had a good time.
- Dex, put on your backpack quickly.
Put on your backpack now.
(Put on your backpack now
so that you can come with us.)
Si Eon, have a nice trip.
(Hugging to say goodbye)
Have a nice trip.
(Biting)
We need to go.
Have a nice trip.
- Thank you for your work.
- Right.
Have a nice trip, Pani Bottle. Okay?
It feels like leaving someone
who's getting discharged.
I really felt sorry.
Kian84.
Wait. How come it feels so hard to leave?
How come I hate to stand up now?
(Kian84 feels sorry
that it's their last trip together.)
Kian84, here's your hat.
(The youngest takes care of him
until the end.)
It feels like Dex keeps shoving us out.
No.
- Gosh.
- Go now, Si Eon.
Go away.
(Kidding)
- Bye.
- Have a good trip.
(Seeing off with love)
(Holding hands)
Oh, my.
Let's take a picture.
All right.
- Stand in front of me.
- Si Eon.
Ask them,
so all four of us can be in the photo.
Si Eon always took photos of us.
- So he isn't in many photos.
- Of course not.
- Over there.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Excuse me.
- Could you take a photo of us?
- Yes.
I rarely take photos of myself.
- But I had to be in that one.
- We needed a photo...
of the four of us.
(The last record...)
(of the Four Brothers traveling in Nepal)
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
Go on.
- You can go in, Dex.
- No, it's okay.
- Don't come any farther than this.
- That's right.
- You don't have to walk us out.
- I already came this far.
If you step outside these gates,
you have to travel with us.
This is my house, so you should leave now.
It's not like
we won't see each other forever.
- You're right.
- See you in Seoul.
You did a good job.
- Good luck.
- Have a safe trip.
- Let's go.
- Si Eon.
- Go.
- You have to go.
(The traveler struggles
with the house owner.)
You two are like
elementary school students.
Bye.
Have a safe trip.
- Have a safe trip.
- We got this.
- Bye. See you.
- See you in Korea.
Bye.
(Saying goodbye to his older brothers)
Did you turn around
and dive into the pool, shouting with joy?
"I'm free."
(Hurray! Dex's adventure is over.)
(Feeling sad his journey ended first)
He seems sad...
that the others are leaving.
(He can't stop watching
as the others walk away.)
It's not like we won't see him forever.
We'll see him all the time in Korea.
(The Three Brothers resume
their journey once again.)
This is the 1st time the 3 of us
traveled alone since Season 1.
- It's the first time?
- Wait.
It feels like light is shining in
from somewhere.
(Screaming)
- Wait.
- My eyes hurt.
Wait a second.
What are you doing
on Adventure by Accident, Hye Jin?
Thank you for inviting me.
Welcome.
I'm here today instead of Dex
because he is busy.
She gladly agreed to stand in for Dex.
- After we return from an overseas trip,
- Yes?
we actually travel with Hye Jin in Korea.
(Another travel mate
of Kian84 and Si Eon's)
(They've known one another for 9 years...)
(and seem like real siblings.)
(I apologize if you felt uncomfortable.)
You travel overseas on MBC
and in Korea on Hye Jin's YouTube channel.
Adventure by Accident...
shows the chemistry among the male cast.
- Yes.
- They are very open with one another.
And there are no formalities.
- No formalities.
- "No formalities?"
I think she wants to say
that you're dirty.
No, I don't.
It's similar to
when we're traveling with you, Hye Jin.
- Really?
- Yes.
Should we go to a sauna together
next time?
Gosh. You've become scary on YouTube.
(You've become scary on YouTube.)
What is it?
I think she understands how I feel.
There's something I feel
when I'm traveling with these two.
Actually, I shouldn't say "these 2."
It's more about 1 of them.
A person that can relate to
the frustration I feel is here.
Who is that one person?
I wonder who he is.
(We will keep that a secret.)
(Airport in Kathmandu)
Okay. Now,
our trip to Nepal is over.
Our trip will now...
follow the Tea Horse Road.
Tea Horse...
Horses were raised in the Himalayas.
Then the horses were taken
to be exchanged for tea.
We will go to the place
where the exchange was made.
It's the tea we drink.
We have to go through China.
We will go through China.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you.
(Travel YouTuber, Captain Brother,
who has 600,000 subscribers)
- He's famous.
- I'm a subscriber.
(He speaks Chinese suspiciously well.)
(But he's Korean.)
(He's already met several minority groups
along the Tea Horse Road.)
I was thinking of planning a route...
where we can meet
different minority groups.
Should we start with Tibet?
In Tibet,
tourists aren't allowed
to travel independently.
There must be restrictions.
Many Tibetans live...
around Tibet.
There are several well-known areas
on the way there.
There is a place called Shangri-La.
- Shangri-La?
- Have you heard of it?
Besides the Han Chinese,
there are 55 minority groups.
Half of those minority groups
live in that area.
They do?
(Around half of the minority groups
live in Yunnan, where Shangri-La is.)
We were planning to travel
along the Tea Horse Road.
We were told that Shangri-La is where
we could meet various minority groups...
and see the culture of Tibet.
So that is the final destination
of our trip.
(Final destination: Shangri-La)
I looked up the route to China.
I think it would be best
to fly into Chengdu.
When we went from Nepal to China,
we flew into a city called Chengdu
to get to our destination.
Let's say goodbye to Nepal.
Goodbye, Nepal.
(Saying goodbye to Nepal,
where they made many memories)
(They are off to Chengdu, where the trip
of the Three Brothers will begin!)
We are flying from Nepal to China.
Under those clouds...
are the Himalayas.
(The stretch of the Himalayas)
The Himalayas we saw in Nepal...
stretches out to this point.
It lies over hundreds of kilometers.
We are traveling along
the stretch of the Himalayas.
(They travel along the mountain range
of thousands of kilometers.)
(Kathmandu, Chengdu)
(3-hour flight)
We have to exchange money.
But I heard the Chinese don't use cash.
We don't need to exchange money.
They use...
Let's charge our Alipay here.
- We can use our phones.
- Then we...
Give all your money to Pani Bottle.
Do I need to give you any money?
I'm the only one paying.
That will make it seem like
you're doing everything by yourself.
- We'd just be following you around.
- All right.
We'll stay at a hotel...
in Chengdu tonight.
I'll get a taxi.
Wait a minute. Since we arrived,
you exchanged the money,
got a hotel, and will get a taxi.
You're doing everything.
- That's right.
- Come to think of it,
he did everything since Season One.
But I had no idea what to do.
That's the biggest problem.
That's right. I'm sure you wanted to help.
It's a relief that I'm used to doing it.
So it wasn't much trouble.
It wasn't anything tough.
It's a Pani Bottle Tour.
(Pani Bottle, the guide)
(Pani Bottle Tour is back
after approximately 3 years.)
We're back to where we started.
What are we doing today, Pani Bottle?
- We'll check in first.
- Check in.
There is a night market in Chengdu.
Let's have dinner there.
- Sounds good.
- That sounds amazing.
(After hearing the satisfying plan,
they head to the taxis.)
(Gasping)
They look like electric cars.
(While taking a look
at the taxis in Chengdu...)
It's a panda.
They're known for their pandas.
(Around 12 million people visit
the panda research base annually.)
We're familiar with pandas.
That's right.
(Chengdu is serious about pandas.)
- Gosh.
- So cute.
The panda must be the mascot of the city.
(Welcome to Chengdu.)
Sit in the front, Pani Bottle.
(They get into the cute panda taxi...)
(and head to their hotel.)
Since Dex isn't with us anymore,
the fangirls will gather around me.
Fangirls?
Right.
(What is he talking about?)
You're being ridiculous.
He said something totally useless.
Yes, that's right.
The Chinese must rarely use cash.
I've never seen anyone use cash.
- Really?
- Gosh.
I heard...
that even the homeless...
- hold out QR codes for money.
- That's right.
- I actually saw someone like that.
- Isn't that surprising?
- Really?
- I'd only heard about it...
- but went and saw someone.
- How does that work?
Do they beg for money
and hold up their phones?
- No, they hang it around their necks.
- They wear it.
- Really?
- It's laminated.
- Yes.
Even the donations at temples...
- are made through QR codes.
- A QR code is on the donation box.
Almost no one accepts cash or cards.
- It's all done with QR codes.
- That's right.
I'm looking forward to the night market.
Chengdu is known for its mapo tofu.
- Gosh.
- Gosh, that looks tasty.
It looks amazing.
(From the irresistible malatang...)
I'm okay with hot pot
or any type of Chinese food.
There are probably restaurants
near the stalls on the streets.
So we can eat some street food...
and go have hot pot.
Let's eat and rest today.
We're here.
(They arrive at the hotel
while deciding their dinner menu.)
That was around 40 dollars
for driving 70km.
It's slightly cheaper than in Korea.
Let's go eat.
(They head straight to the night market
after checking in.)
Look at all the pandas.
The pandas are even on the streets.
Chengdu is known for its pandas.
That's so cute.
(Souvenirs
suitable for the city of pandas)
They're so cute, aren't they?
This is called the Fuqin Night Market.
- Fuqin?
- Yes, the night market on Fuqin Road.
I think this is it.
- It's on the left.
- It's the night market.
This is where it starts.
There are so many people.
(The oldest night market in Chengdu)
- It's quite big.
- That must've been fun.
Fuqin Night Market is one
of the oldest night markets in Chengdu.
It has numerous stalls
and a variety of unique foods.
It is known for its exquisite cuisine.
(A huge night market in Chengdu)
- Skewers.
- What's that?
- Tofu.
- That looks tasty.
There was a huge variety of food
and many of them in mala flavor.
(You can taste local food
at Fuqin Night Market)
What's this?
It must be lamb.
It's either goat or lamb.
- It's here.
- It's lamb.
- That's a brain.
- I thought it was intestines.
(There is a variety
of unique ingredients as well.)
- What is that?
- It's duck.
(Duck head)
There are many seats outside.
It's very crowded.
It's a night market.
It was very crowded, although it was late.
(Waving)
- What is this?
- It looks like alcohol.
(A kiosk draws their attention
in the midst of the welcoming crowd.)
- That must be made with roses.
- He's telling you to try it.
- It's like a traditional fruit wine.
- Yes, it is.
(Welcome drink)
- It's alcohol.
- Yes, but it's light.
It's similar to makgeolli.
- It tastes like roses.
- It must smell nice.
Should we buy one since we tried it?
This one.
- How much is it?
- It's 5 dollars.
- It's 5 dollars?
I'll pay for it.
(Pani Bottle is in charge of paying.)
How do we pay for it?
I think you get a notification
on your phone.
We wouldn't have been able to buy it
if it weren't for Pani Bottle.
You would've starved
if it weren't for him.
You can't even beg for money
since you don't know how to use QR codes.
- They can't even beg.
- They would've starved.
(Pani the Guide pays
so the older brothers don't starve.)
- It's five dollars?
- Jianpasi.
- "Kian84."
- No way.
- Some people recognized me.
Gosh.
Thank you.
Your name in Chinese...
- must be Jianpasi.
- Jianpasi.
- "Pasi" is 84.
Pasi.
- Thank you. That's interesting.
- A photo.
- Take a photo? Okay.
- Okay.
- Without Dex, Kian84 is popular.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Jianpasi.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
(Laughing)
- His face reveals his feelings.
- He's happy.
I wonder if this is how Dex feels.
(He has global fan meetings
everywhere he goes.)
(Jealous)
(Numerous people ask for photos.)
- You must've been jealous.
- You took so many photos for him.
(Brother 1, who was jealous of Dex)
(He went from the jealous brother
to Jianpasi.)
I wish Dex were there to see that.
(Proud)
It's not a bad feeling.
(Smiling)
- This is interesting.
- It made your day as soon as you arrived.
(They happily go back
to exploring the market.)
- What's this?
- What is it?
They're softshell turtles.
- Softshell turtles.
- Softshell turtles?
- Gosh.
They're frogs and softshell turtles.
Frogs and softshell turtles on the street?
The frogs look tasty.
- Frogs taste like chicken. They're okay.
- Frogs...
(They continue walking for now.)
It's larvae.
(They see something familiar.)
Scorpions?
- I want to try a scorpion.
- What's this?
They sell it like that?
That looks terrifying.
They also have grasshoppers.
Si Eon doesn't eat any of that.
Jianpasi started drooling
as soon as he saw that.
(Drooling)
- His mouth started watering.
- He couldn't wait to eat it.
I want to try a scorpion.
I'm curious what it tastes like.
- Should I try it?
- That larva is alive.
- What?
- It's alive.
- Really?
- It isn't moving.
- It's moving. Watch it.
- It's moving?
- It's alive. I'm serious.
- You're right.
- It's alive.
- Right?
- It's really moving.
It's moving.
It's alive.
- Who is that?
- He came up to see it.
- Who was that?
- Who was that man?
Who was it?
Look. They're all eating it.
It must be like us eating silkworms.
Many young people ate it, right?
(Glancing)
Let's see.
- I think that's alive too.
- Are you trying the scorpion?
- Gosh.
- Really?
- I can't have that anywhere else.
- Right.
- Are you really going to eat it?
- I'm curious too.
I'll try it.
I should try it while I'm here.
(I always want to try local things
while traveling.)
(Trying local foods
is the true charm of traveling.)
(Unstoppable love for local foods)
- Won't it be okay?
- Let's see.
- He cuts off the venomous tail.
- Of course.
- Since it's venomous?
- Yes.
Scorpions look like lobsters.
I think it will taste like a lobster.
(He hopefully wishes for it
to taste like a lobster.)
(Leaning forward)
- This is tasty.
- A recommendation.
- Are you Korean?
- No.
We have this in Korea.
- It's a large-sized silkworm.
- It's bigger.
(He tries the recommended skewer.)
He's applying sauce to it.
That looks spicy. I think it's mala sauce.
(He applies plenty of mala sauce
on the Sichuan delicacy.)
(Focused)
Hello.
- Hello.
- Kian84?
- What was that?
- Can I take a photo with you?
I thought it was...
- Captain Brother.
- I'm a fan.
- I thought it was Captain Brother.
- Give me a second.
(They look quite similar.)
Are you Korean?
No, I'm Korean-Chinese.
- Can I take a photo with you?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Kian84.
- Thank you.
- Jianpasi.
- You're slimmer than I expected.
- Thank you.
Slimmer than he expected.
- Have fun safely.
- Thank you.
(Successful street fan meeting)
It would've been crazy if Dex were here.
- Dex?
- Yes, traffic would've come to a stop.
- We wouldn't be able to walk around.
- Right.
- I'm glad he didn't come.
- Without Dex here,
- I'm getting attention.
- Yes.
- It's the trickle-down effect.
- "The trickle-down effect."
(While enjoying
the trickled-down popularity)
- Thank you.
- Gosh.
- I'll do it.
How much is it?
- I don't know numbers.
- Pani Bottle speaks English, Spanish,
and even Chinese.
He's a human translator.
I don't speak Chinese.
That's all I know how to say.
(Modest translator)
How much is it?
It's around six dollars.
(Scorpion skewer and 2 insect skewers,
approximately 6.6 dollars)
(The 1st thing Kian84 grabs)
Try it and see if it's good.
It still has legs. He only cut off
the tail because of the venom.
- Eat the arm.
- The arm...
- You're trembling.
I'm scared to try this.
It's meaty.
(Crocodile meat? To my mouth)
The crocodile tasted okay.
He even tasted the Ganges River.
The Ganges River is Tier One.
Wait.
- I'm scared to try this.
- He rarely hesitates.
- It looked like it might move.
- Yes, that's right.
(Shaking)
Why are you shaking?
I was scared.
(He shakes while getting a taste
of the wild.)
(Crunchy)
- Listen to that.
- Is it crunchy?
(He takes a bite
after hearing the crunchy sounds.)
It tastes good.
It has some kind of scent.
It tastes like shrimp.
- It's shrimp but...
- It tasted like shrimp head.
- Then it must taste savory.
- Yes, that's right.
(He couldn't be more serious
while tasting it.)
It tastes like a closet.
It tastes like my grandmother's closet.
- Like a closet?
- It tasted like a closet.
- When did you taste a closet?
- It tasted like my grandmother's closet.
Go home
and bite your grandmother's closet.
- It tastes like that.
- Stale and woody?
I think I know what you mean.
Listen to that.
(Grabbing the skewer)
(The eldest grabs
the closet-flavored scorpion.)
Si Eon has a weak stomach.
(Si Eon has a weak stomach.)
Okay.
(When Kian84 was eating pupae,)
(Si Eon, the city guy, shook his head.)
I have a weak stomach.
- Try one of the arms.
- It's 33.
Si Eon is trying it.
It's scary at first.
He tried it.
(Closing his eyes)
- It must be painful.
- It must be tough for him.
I regretted not trying the pupae.
I went home and thought about it.
When else would I get a chance to try it?
I regretted it then
and thought I might regret it again...
if I didn't try the scorpion.
That's why I tried it.
I was able to grow during this trip.
It's too hard.
It's amazing that he tried an insect.
What's that? Is it a diving beetle?
- It's a diving beetle.
- Really?
Beetles are harder to eat.
(He takes a bite without hesitating.)
He eats it without hesitation.
(The eldest, who has matured,
quickly takes it.)
This is better than the scorpion.
Is he going to eat it?
- Is it better than the scorpion?
- Yes, it is.
The scorpion wasn't bad.
(He tries one.)
- This isn't bad.
- Are you okay with this big one?
- It's huge. Look at the legs.
- It's huge.
I have to eat it without looking at it.
(Looking up)
- It's like chips.
- It's savory.
What did the diving beetles taste like?
Were they juicy?
- No.
- Were they juicy?
- Juicy?
Juicy? You sound elegant.
I'm sure you're curious.
But it wasn't juicy.
That's a relief.
But I could feel the wings.
(Dizzy)
(He cleanses his palate
with the large silkworm.)
Is it tasty?
- It's tasty.
- Silkworm is tasty.
Try this.
(He highly recommends it to his brothers.)
- It was tasty. It was mala-flavored.
- It's good.
- It's the same as the Korean silkworm.
- It's the same.
- Thank you.
- How do you say "tasty" in Chinese?
- Hao chi.
- Thank you.
A lot of it is stuck in my teeth.
A leg of the diving beetle
is stuck between my molars.
I think I have something
stuck in my teeth too.
It's stuck between my molars.
(It feels unpleasant.)
(He suddenly reaches into his pocket.)
I knew it and brought floss.
(He flosses his teeth right away.)
Floss is essential when eating insects.
(Taking out the bug leg)
- What is he doing?
- It must've swam diligently.
(Kian84...)
Is it not coming out?
(I have to film this.)
How am I supposed to give you this
when you're flossing?
Give it to me.
(I'll use it again later.)
Eating something strange makes me wonder
what the frog will taste like.
Eating frogs must be easy now.
Other things must be
more approachable now.
Didn't you have them often in childhood?
- Really?
- I didn't have frogs in childhood.
Frogs and grasshoppers.
- Everyone had them.
- I had grasshoppers.
(He'll eat frogs
for the 1st time in 42 years.)
Two of these.
- Will you eat two?
- Yes.
Where else will you eat frogs?
- That's right.
- Yes. It's an experience.
You need to eat them at times like this.
- They're so big.
- These frogs must've exercised a lot.
These frogs are so big.
- They're like bullfrogs.
- Yes.
They have Dex's legs.
Those are the legs Dex wants.
- Gurkha frogs.
- They have Gurkha's legs.
(Their muscles rival
those of UDT and Gurkha.)
- Si Eon.
- They're boiled in spicy soup.
(They're boiled in mala broth.)
(They take on spicy flavors.)
It looks like chicken.
(At a glance, it looks like chicken.)
- Seriously.
- No one will know if you don't say it.
That's right.
Let's taste it.
It looks spicy.
Look at his eyes.
It's so chewy.
- "Try it, Si Eon."
- It suits his taste.
- You mean that it's tasty, right?
- Yes.
It's totally... It's 100 percent protein.
(Pani Bottle takes a bite
of the protein-rich dish.)
Weightlifting...
(My goodness)
- It's too spicy.
- I guess he can't eat spicy food.
- Is it tasty?
- It's tasty, but spicy.
It's so spicy.
The seasoning must be spicy.
- It numbs the mouth.
- That's how it is in that region.
- I can see that they use chili oil a lot.
- That's right.
People with no spice tolerance
can't eat it.
I can't eat it.
- Is it spicy?
- It's numbing my mouth. Yes.
The taste isn't the problem.
It's tasty. But it's too spicy.
(Pani Bottle is so weak.)
(Oh, my.)
I liked the dish.
I liked how chewy the meat was.
It's tasty.
(Is it that tasty?)
- I'll have a leg on standby.
- A leg.
Si Eon, try this part.
If you try it, you'll see how chewy it is.
- That's right, Si Eon.
- It's unexpectedly chewy.
To be honest, I'm a vegetarian.
So suddenly?
If they sell this dish in Korea,
I'll order it again.
- Will you order it again?
- That's how tasty it is.
Chicken breast is dry, right?
- It doesn't have that dryness.
- That's right. It's chewy.
- Yes.
- It's like chewy chicken.
You're something else.
- He's eating it with so much gusto.
- It's spicy.
Kian84 is like Heebab right now.
Seriously.
(Heebab84)
(He's eating with gusto.)
He'll eat the bones at this rate.
(Perfect deboning)
(Clean)
Did you see the bones in front of him?
- Yes.
- He ate the dish so cleanly.
I'll pay.
- Then I'll pay for the hot pot.
- Okay.
How much is it?
(How much is it?)
It's five dollars.
- How much is it?
- The prices are low at the market.
- Yes.
- It's like that overall.
So it's 2.5 dollars per frog. Not bad.
(After enjoying a light snack,)
(they move to the hot pot restaurant.)
Let's go.
You have to eat hot pot in Chengdu.
- That's right.
- It's a must.
- It's the hometown of hot pot.
- That's right.
- Is it a hot pot restaurant?
- That place was the best.
- Oh, my.
- It's nice.
- Si Eon, let's eat here.
- We could smell the hot pot.
(They follow the smell.)
- Where should we sit?
- Here.
Is it a hot pot restaurant?
(They sit at a table they see.)
Does this place have beef?
I see many dishes on the menu.
(There's only Chinese.)
- You don't see a lot of English in China.
- That's right.
(Getting up)
What's that?
(Taking photos)
Look at that. The two of them are sitting
while Pani Bottle is working.
You're right.
- It happens when you travel with elders.
- I think that's what it is.
He was about to chew the food
and feed it to us.
Look at this, Kian84. It's the menu.
Beef, intestines...
- As for this one...
- Pork stomach.
I think it's pig stomach.
There's pork belly.
"Dragon beef?"
- The translation is strange at times.
- What's that?
Order what you want.
I'm okay with everything.
How do I order?
(They set off to order something.)
(They're struggling
because they don't know how to order.)
- You write it here.
- I see.
I'll do it. I can do it.
All right. Okay.
(He acquired the order sheet
in a cool way.)
(Clicking)
What's going on?
We can mark what we want.
(Proud)
Here.
Many of those translations
will appear strange.
"Tofu skin."
- Tofu skin.
It's tasty. Order a lot.
- Three.
- "Bamboo shoot, 3."
- Bamboo shoot, 3.
Bamboo shoot.
"Hanging beef."
- Hanging beef.
- Such translations are so funny.
What's "Hanging beef?"
- I think it's aged meat.
- I see.
- "Hanging beef."
- "Tender beef."
One tender beef.
"Kung fu broke a potato."
- "Kung fu broke a potato?"
- That's right.
"Pure milk cow heart."
(What does that even mean?)
Shall we try one pure milk cow heart?
No! Try it later.
Put in an additional order later.
Let's order a lot of vegetables for now.
- Vegetables.
- Let's eat one serving each.
(Lastly, they order the drinks.)
Kaoliang liquor looks incredible.
This one.
- This one.
- Size...
- This one?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
(They complete their order
and go back to their table.)
You know,
there are so many fascinating food items.
The category of food is very broad.
- This city is famous for food.
- Duck?
- Food.
- Food?
They say that Chinese people
eat everything with legs.
- Except for tables.
They even eat mosquito eyeballs.
What did he put on his lips?
Seriously.
- His lips are red from eating frogs.
- I ate frogs.
- I became flushed.
- "What did he put on his lips?"
He isn't the type to do that.
- Is it a frog lipstick?
- Yes.
The souls of dozens of frogs.
(The heart-fluttering mala red)
This restaurant runs until 11 p.m.
(Glancing)
(A generous amount)
Didn't we order too much?
Let's eat.
- You know...
- No. There's more.
They shrink in size when they're boiled.
- There's too much food.
(Coming through)
(They get another tray.)
(What?)
Pani Bottle's eyes are shaking.
We thought that we'd get a piece per one.
You couldn't tell
how big the portion would be.
- For three people,
- You ended up ordering a lot of food.
we ordered three servings per item.
(3 servings)
- There's so much food.
- Kian84.
- My goodness.
- Why is there so much...
This is why I order.
(They understand perfectly.)
- I see.
- Otherwise, something like this happens.
- Of course.
- Kian84 and I ordered.
Did we order this much food?
(We should've sat still to help him.)
You can eat more food
once you get started.
That's right. They're vegetables.
- Will you add all of them?
- I'll add just a few.
Sichuan hot pot is the original.
It looks tasty.
(Adding the hanging beef)
There are so many hot pot restaurants.
It's as popular as kimchi stew in Korea.
Most restaurants sell hot pot.
(He takes some food.)
(He adds chilis to the sauce.)
(Mixing)
It looks tasty.
(A mouthful of original hot pot)
(Impressed)
The bamboo shoot is tasty.
I see why pandas only eat bamboo shoots.
It's tasty.
Oh, it was tofu.
(Pani Bottle takes a ladleful of food
from the white soup.)
It was nice.
Since I couldn't eat spicy food,
we ordered red soup for one side...
- and white soup for the other side.
- That's right.
(He eats the tofu dipped in sauce first.)
- It was so tasty.
- It looks tasty.
(My goodness)
(It's hot.)
- The sauce is tasty.
- The sauce is really tasty.
- It's tasty, right?
- Yes.
I think we'll be able
to find this soup in Korea,
- but this sauce is so tasty and nutty.
- Yes.
It has a bit of spiciness
and a hint of the cilantro.
(The eldest tries the sauce
Pani Bottle recommended.)
It's tasty.
It's definitely different
from the hot pot...
- you get in Korea.
- Yes.
The taste is more legitimate.
(The eldest finally found
the food he liked.)
(He eats and eats.)
(Then he eats some more.)
To be honest, it was so tasty.
Seeing you eat well puts my heart at ease.
(He inhales the food
regardless of the ingredient.)
(He eats the meat as well.)
It's so tasty.
I'm serious. It's so tasty.
- This soup is tasty too. Seriously.
- It's tasty.
When I saw you guys eat frogs earlier,
I became a bit discouraged.
Eating this encouraged me.
Do you want to try the frog tomorrow then?
(Oh, my.)
The kaoliang liquor is nice.
Just because we flew for about two hours,
the food has completely changed.
It's different from Nepali food.
- Three hours.
It's so tasty.
(Absorbed in the atmosphere,
he takes a sip of kaoliang liquor.)
(My goodness)
- It's nice.
- It must be really nice.
I'm full.
Are you full?
Hey, we need to eat all the food.
We still ate a lot.
- We ate so much.
- We ate quickly.
- He's right.
- They could eat a lot of it.
In the soup, the amount isn't a lot.
That's right. They shrink in size.
That's right. We need to talk about
the schedule for tomorrow.
I have a suggestion
since we came to China.
There's a place called Yunnan.
- It's right next to...
- Are we going to Yunnan tomorrow?
There's a place called Lijiang
inside Yunnan.
- Lijiang.
Lijiang is inside Yunnan.
It's a place many people visited
on the Tea Horse Road.
- That's right. I know.
- It's the gate of the trade route.
(It unfolds
under the snow-capped mountain.)
There's a place called
the Old Town of Lijiang.
It's like the scene you see in the dramas
about "Romance of the Three Kingdoms."
Seriously.
(Many horses have passed
the city of traditions and romance.)
The final destination was Shangri-La,
right?
Lijiang is a city next to Shangri-La.
In ancient times, horses rested there.
Since it was an important place
on the Tea Horse Road,
I thought it'd be nice to visit.
(They decide to visit the city
on the Tea Horse Road.)
I looked up tasty restaurants in Lijiang.
I found the traditional food of Lijiang.
- Traditional food?
- Preserved ribs hot pot.
- Hot pot again?
- It exists only in Lijiang.
- Only in Lijiang?
Only in Lijiang.
- Then...
- You can't eat it anywhere else.
Lijiang has many minority groups.
Nakhi people. There are Nakhi people.
Do they wear sleeveless shirts?
- What was that? For goodness' sake!
- Nakhi sounds like "sleeveless shirt."
(What kind of a lousy joke is that?)
Many people would think that.
- No!
- What a rotten joke.
They're called the Nakhi people.
- Still...
- "Do they wear sleeveless shirts?"
- You could ask them.
- Really?
- Si Eon.
- The Na'vi...
- No.
- Thank goodness Dex isn't here.
- Had Dex been here...
- No.
(Si Eon, save your comments
even when I'm not around.)
Save your comments.
Shall we spend the day
at Lijiang tomorrow?
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- I'll look up the minority group.
- It's an item on your bucket list.
You continue to be in a bad condition.
To be honest, you should've gone to Korea
instead of Dex.
- "You should've gone to Korea."
- Why did you say that?
He was in a bad condition.
That would've been nicer in many ways.
You can either rest
or hang out by yourself.
You can do whatever you want tomorrow.
I'll do the planning from tomorrow onward.
Pani Bottle, get some rest.
I'll do the planning.
From the day after,
Si Eon and I will work.
- Let's have another sip and go.
- Okay.
Cheers.
(They wrap up for tomorrow.)
How much is the total?
You need to do it.
(Please write it here.)
It's 73 dollars.
- Including the liquor?
- Including the liquor. That's the total.
- Gosh.
- You guys ate so much.
The price is quite nice.
We're paying.
(Hot pot: About 73 dollars)
- Thank you.
(The Three Brothers
leave for the lodging.)
(How will Lijiang be tomorrow?)
Let's go.
(On the 8th day of the trip,
they go to Lijiang.)
The direct flight to Lijiang from Chengdu
is early in the morning.
We're checking out.
(Pani Bottle checks out again.)
(He calls the taxi in one go.)
Hello.
- Airport.
Domestic airport.
We're going to the domestic airport.
- Okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
(Chengdu, Lijiang)
(1 hour and 30 minutes)
(Si Eon and Pani Bottle rest
as they watch videos.)
(What is Kian84 doing?)
(He's playing a game on his phone.)
- What?
- What is it?
Is he playing a game while sleeping?
(His fingers stopped.)
To be honest, I was physically exhausted.
Of course.
(They arrive at Lijiang Airport.)
This is Lijiang.
Lijiang of the Lijiang Tower.
Gosh, does that place really exist?
Is that it?
It's like a place in "Spirited Away."
- It's like a set for a period drama.
- A set.
That's what it looks like.
That's the Old Town of Lijiang.
Let's grab a taxi and go there.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry, Pani Bottle.
- Please grab a taxi. We'll do the rest.
- Yes.
You can stop working
after grabbing a taxi.
Is there anything
other than grabbing a taxi?
Just grab the taxi and pay.
We'll do the rest.
I think I'll do all the work.
You know, I had this realization.
People here can't speak English very well.
They only speak Chinese.
Still, you do most of the work.
(I know that.)
It wasn't about the language.
There wasn't anything hard.
Look at the weather.
It's nice.
- The sky is clear.
- It's nice.
It's the nicest
the weather has been during this trip.
(When they were in Nepal,)
(the sky was full of fine dust.)
(Warm sunlight welcomes them in Lijiang.)
- The weather is nice.
- The weather is so nice.
He's training his eyes
for the first time in a while.
The weather is the clearest.
(Worker Bottle looks for a taxi.)
Okay. Let's ride this taxi.
Pani Bottle grabbed a taxi.
- Don't put it down.
- Pani Bottle is doing all the work.
They'll be in trouble without Pani Bottle.
(He safely boards the taxi.)
Have you looked for a lodging?
- A lodging? No, I'll go and see.
- Yes.
Will you go and see?
It was convenient
when you booked the lodging.
I feel bad.
Pani Bottle, we're sorry.
Don't be sorry.
This place is different from Chengdu.
This place is exotic.
(The exotic scenery unfolds.)
But it's also homely.
Look at the flowers.
I can't believe we're seeing flowers
on Adventure by Accident.
They must've looked beautiful
thanks to the nice weather.
The air is cold, and the sunlight is warm.
The air is clean.
When you're on Adventure by Accident,
the scenery changes...
- after each night.
- I know.
It's so dramatic.
How did the world change so much in a day?
The snow-capped mountain is no joke.
I can see so far.
This is incredible. What's that mountain?
Yulong Snow Mountain.
Is there a snow-capped mountain?
(The snow-capped mountain looks majestic.)
Do Yeon!
We're curious about Lijiang.
It was nice.
(After the gravelly "Do Yeon")
Do Yeon, please read it.
(He's good.)
I'll tell you about Lijiang.
Lijiang is located in Yunnan, China.
It's a city that's 2,400m above sea level.
(Under the majestic Yulong Snow Mountain
that's 5,596m tall)
It was a key point in the trade route
of the Tea Horse Road...
and a stopover site for the horses.
It's also the home of the Nakhi people,
a minority group,
The majestic nature
of the snow-capped Yulong Snow Mountain...
and the ancient vibes...
make it a charming travel destination.
(Proud)
Is it okay to be so happy?
- I'm so happy right now.
- It feels wrong.
(They enjoy the beautiful scenery.)
- Are we there, Pani Bottle?
- Yes, we're nearly there.
(They arrive at the Old Town of Lijiang.)
- Thank you.
(My goodness)
It's cool.
(They see a fancy building upon arrival.)
Will you be able to find a lodging here?
- A lodging?
- Let's look for it.
- If you walk for a while...
- You know,
there won't be a sign that reads, "Hotel."
Shall we walk around?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
We hadn't reserved a hotel.
Kian84 decided to look for a place.
We decided to look for it
since we felt bad for Pani Bottle.
After all,
Pani Bottle always makes a reservation.
We wanted to find it on the spot.
That place is pretty.
That's the scenic spot.
(Gosh)
It's so big.
(The scenery makes them exclaim.)
- It's so nice.
- The town is so big.
(The tile roofs are lined up.)
My goodness.
Here's the thing about Lijiang.
When our ancestors took
the state exam in the old days,
they spent the night in Suwon...
before entering the capital.
They didn't have cars.
They had a horse or a donkey,
so they had to rest.
(A rest area for the exhausted travelers)
It's like the Meeting Square Rest Area
in Seoul.
(It's like the Meeting Square Rest Area
in Seoul.)
That's right. A rest area in Cheonan.
(An important base of the trade route
on the Tea Horse Road)
I see why people compare it to Gyeongju.
The scale is incredible.
What? I know what that is.
It's the clothes of the minority group.
Pani Bottle,
they're the clothes of the minority group.
- Was it the Hmong people?
- Really?
Was it the Hmong people?
The Miao people.
There was a comic book
I really liked back in the day.
In "33 EYES," there was...
a really cute heroine called Pai.
It looks like the clothes
of the people who live in the mountains.
It's a makeup studio.
They lend you clothes and do your makeup.
I guess people wear costumes like they do
in Gyeongbokgung Palace.
For photos?
The locals made the place very stylish,
right?
Yes.
(Gasping)
How do we enter a new world every day?
Oriental.
(Giggling)
Is it a school? Kids are chatting.
It must be an elementary school.
Where? It's a kindergarten.
How cute.
Look at them.
(Oh, my!)
Hello.
He'll make it big.
- Do you guys want to go home?
- Hello.
"Primary school."
- Elementary schoolers...
- They must be elementary schoolers.
What's "elementary school" in English?
Middle school?
- Is it "elementary school?"
- Hello.
Is it an elementary school?
No?
(We don't understand.)
- They don't understand.
- No?
No English classes?
They're so cute.
They're sticking to the gate.
It's old.
All right. It must be break time.
- Bye.
- They know "bye."
(Bye.)
Kids are cute.
We need to find a lodging now.
(We'll go and find a lodging.)
Hey. "Wan Fang An He Inn."
Is it in English?
What?
(They find a building
that looks like an inn.)
This won't do. I'll look it up.
We must call in order to make a booking.
- Who's going to make the call?
- The lodging?
Gosh, I have zero confidence.
I can't speak Chinese,
and they can't speak English.
Had Pani Bottle made the booking,
we could've gone right away.
But we wandered around.
There's one over there.
Do you want to check it out?
- The leader.
- Is he finally doing something?
The room is 37.5 dollars.
- It says this is the place.
- Here?
- Hi.
- Is it a homestay?
Hold on.
- There's one here too.
- No room?
- No.
Oh, no.
(What now?)
We'll waste too much time finding a room.
I'll look for one on my own.
Moving as a group of three lacks mobility.
Exactly, it's a waste of time.
- There aren't any, right?
- No.
- I'm going to look around the area.
- Okay.
- Let's go together.
- Let's go.
Going as a group will take too much time.
You should look around too.
It's hard to find available rooms.
- Separately?
- Let's go.
- We went on our own.
- Yes.
I'll look around.
(I'll look around.)
I realized after arriving in China.
That Pani Bottle was doing everything
without a word.
What were Si Eon and I doing?
Feeling terrible,
I went around looking for a room.
Pani Bottle never boasts about it.
He's going to steal my job.
(I'll find a room for us.)
- Did you look for one on foot?
- Yes.
If only there were signs.
(A map is a must.)
(Relying on the navigation app,
he moves forward.)
There it is.
(He finally located an accommodation.)
It's big.
(Is this the place?)
Excuse me?
Do you have a room?
I hope they do.
(We do.)
Do you want to look at the room first?
They even show you the room.
Yes.
(On his way to check the room)
- What? It even has a living room.
- It looks amazing.
- Nice.
- It's really nice.
One bed.
There are three of them.
(A room with 2 beds)
It's perfect.
He did it. Kian84 got 1 thing done.
(Touting? He passed it.)
(English? Nice.)
(Finding a room? A success.)
(Success by Accident)
He did it.
We're a variety show from South Korea.
Can we shoot here?
(He's even asking for permission
to shoot.)
Is he even getting permission?
That's very thorough of him.
(It's okay.)
- He's okay with it.
- We'll take the room for one night.
How much is it?
(Being clear)
(It's 500 yuan per night.)
That's about 100 dollars per night...
That's cheap.
Good.
(Perfect Chinese)
What does that mean?
- Good.
- "Okay."
- You didn't know what it meant?
- He kept saying, "Good."
(Smiling)
There's joy in finding available rooms.
- It felt great.
- Of course.
(Calling Pani Bottle right away)
- Hello?
- Pani Bottle.
- Yes?
- I found a room, and it's nice.
- Really?
- Yes.
- The room has three beds.
- Is it actually nice?
- Okay.
- And it's cheap. It's great.
- Let's go.
- Yes, come.
- I'll send you the address.
- Okay.
(A welcome mandarin)
There was mandarin to eat for free.
(Keeping the peels)
- Gosh.
- Come on.
He's using mandarin instead of perfume.
A mandarin scent.
A citrus scent.
I should smell good
when I meet the minority group.
Isn't that good manners? He kept it
in his pocket instead of littering.
(Keeping his manners
with the mandarin peels)
(Wiping)
(While he rubs the perfume
on his whole body,)
(Si Eon and Pani Bottle arrive.)
Kian84. I like the place so far.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
It's really pretty.
(Satisfied with the view,
he makes the payment.)
The room needs cleaning,
so we have to wait here for 20 minutes.
- Okay. Let's relax a bit.
- Okay.
Hold on. Let me ask that.
Excuse me.
Where must I go to meet the Nikhi people?
- "Nikhi?" Wasn't it the Nakhi people?
- "Nikhi?"
(While searching for minority groups
last night)
The Nakhi people?
(He found the Nakhi people.)
- The Nakhi people?
- Nakhi.
It said many of the Nakhi people
lived in that area.
Please wait. We have Nakhi people here.
So there are Nakhi people here.
Is this accommodation
run by the Nakhi people?
(His heart is pounding.)
There are 2 Nakhi people and 1 Mongolian.
We're running this place.
In Lijiang, I felt...
a lot more like a tourist.
The scenery was beautiful and all,
but I wanted to quickly meet
the minority people.
- Good.
- I wanted to ask...
where the Nakhi people mainly lived.
The Nakhi people.
- According to Wikipedia,
- Yes?
they are a matriarchal tribe.
The Mosuo people.
They don't mix their property
or financial activities.
Each household...
(He's not interested.)
- And...
- Our room is ready.
- Here. Listen to this first.
- Okay.
Information out of nowhere?
It's the happiest moment for him.
- To the Nakhi people,
- Yes?
the frog is their deity.
- I see.
- And...
Look. Si Eon.
They are a matriarchal tribe.
So...
(Thinking)
(So this is...)
It's a matriarchal society
practicing polyandry.
How do I put it?
(What is he saying?)
If a married couple has a child...
- Even if a child is born...
- He's obsessed with the minority group.
- What are you saying?
- So...
- Why don't we go in first?
- Please. Don't trust the blog...
- too much.
- I don't get it.
I'll study them again later.
(He wrapped up the private lesson.)
(Checking into the room)
I wasn't sure what the room would be like.
(I wasn't sure
what the room would be like.)
- Goodness!
- Thank you.
- Beautiful!
- The room is big.
- What?
- I was genuinely surprised.
- It even has a terrace.
- Nice.
Let's use this room.
- Unbelievable.
- It's really nice.
Kian84. I've known you for 10 years,
and I've never been prouder.
I was shocked too.
Were you shocked at yourself?
(Scenery worth 10 years of compliments.)
I couldn't believe that
Kian84 found the room.
It was hard to believe that
Kian84 found that place.
- How did you find this room?
- The sky helped him.
No way this was just luck.
- It was pure luck.
- They're saying it's luck.
- They won't admit it was his skill.
- No.
(The accommodation deity helped Lucky84.)
Pani Bottle. Let's go grab a bite.
- I'm going to rest a bit.
- Sure.
I wasn't feeling well, so I skipped lunch.
You should go easy on yourself
when traveling together.
You can't even eat
because you're always working alone.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
She was being thoughtful,
but he apologized.
- I'm sorry.
- He's shaking right now.
- I'm just upset.
- Go down on your knees.
- Why are you getting angry at him?
- I'm just so upset. I want him to rest.
What you said was heartwarming,
but it was scary.
(Honestly, you scared me too.)
(While Pani Bottle is recovering)
- First off...
- Yes?
(The others leave to get lunch.)
There's a place in Yunnan
that serves the best rice noodles.
Is it only sold in Yunnan?
When I said I was craving noodles,
Si Eon looked it up.
- I searched for a place online.
- That was sweet of him.
- I'll trust you and follow you around.
- You can trust me.
Turn right.
(Heading out with confidence)
(With every step, peaceful alleys unfold.)
This place is truly beautiful.
Walking there would be a joy.
You should come with your wife one day.
It's a decent enough place
to bring my wife.
Look at them twinning with jeans-on-jeans.
They're like newlyweds.
- Hold on.
- This must be the main street.
- Gosh. My camera!
- This is the main street.
(The place where all the alleys
of Lijiang come together)
"Sifang Street."
Are there streets on all four sides?
You're correct.
(How is it possible?)
Sifang Street,
with streets on all four sides,
is the central square
in the Old Town of Lijiang.
(The central square
of the Old Town of Lijiang)
The street is full of interesting sights
from the Nakhi culture.
(Where diverse minority cultures
have mingled)
- This must be the main street.
- Yes.
(Amazed)
Did you notice the place is filled
with the number eight?
- Where?
- Over there. Eight.
And our Wi-Fi password was 8 8s.
- True.
- Come to think of it,
our room numbers are 803, 801, and 802.
You're right.
That's why G-DRAGON is popular in China.
What? His birthday is August 18?
- Really?
- Yes.
That's some fate right there.
- We have Jianpasi with us.
- Yes.
- Jianpasi.
- If only my name were Kian88.
- It would've been nice.
- "Kian88?"
- You should've held back four years.
- I know, right?
- That should be said to his parents.
- Right. I'm sorry.
My apologies.
Let's go.
It's only one minute away from here.
We're almost there.
Hold on, Kian84. Take a look.
Let me see.
(Even when they were finding
the accommodation,)
(the map app didn't work well.)
Why does the map keep changing?
It must be because
the streets were narrow.
(It's acting up again.)
From here...
(They turn around again
and head to the square.)
From here...
We have to get to where the red is, right?
- Your destination is on the right.
- Lending my clothes...
Hold on. We've arrived.
What? Where is it?
- Sifangjie.
- "Sifangjie?"
"Sifangjie?"
Is it actually called Sifangjie?
- Is this Sifangjie?
- Sifangjie?
Sifangjie?
(Over there.)
- Over there?
- Sifangjie.
Is that a tea house?
It looks like a hot pot place.
Oh, Sifangjie.
(They head in the pointed direction.)
- It's on the left.
- The dragon...
What is wrong with this?
Why? Let me.
- What app is this?
- I'll take a look.
It's Google Maps.
Even though it's Google Maps?
Google Maps doesn't really work in China.
- China has its own map app.
- He's right.
- Really?
- It's easier to use that.
(Fortunately,
they find an information desk nearby.)
Excuse me.
Sifangjie?
- This way.
- Where?
- "This way?"
- Here?
- Yes.
- Here.
- Sifangjie...
- Yes?
must not be the restaurant's name.
Sifang means four sides.
Yes, "si" is four.
(Sifangjie)
"Sifang Street."
She was right.
Sifangjie is where they are currently.
Exactly. It's Sifangjie wherever they go.
Sifangjie must not be
the restaurant's name.
(We didn't know
the restaurant's name until now?)
Hey, excuse me.
The restaurant's name...
Let's see.
(Gosh, Si Eon.)
(Excuse me?)
(Do you have a room?)
(I've grown so much.)
Seriously?
What about me?
Si Eon tried looking for this place.
Getting lost is no biggie.
It can happen.
"It can happen?"
The restaurant's name...
Lisien?
(Misien means rice noodles.)
- Misien.
- Lisien?
- Go straight?
- Yes.
He's struggling to find the place
until the end.
Did you find it?
Go straight.
- "Go straight?"
- Yes, for 20 minutes.
- "Twenty minutes?"
- No.
No, 20m.
For 20m?
You seem very anxious.
What? No, I let go of everything.
The name of the restaurant is Lisien.
- "Lisien?"
- Yes.
(Off they go.)
Lisien?
You came the other way.
What?
- Return?
- Thank you.
You went the other way?
Oh, no.
We found it. We're almost there.
This looks like a restaurant.
"Sifang Inn."
(Sifang Inn)
- That's not the place.
- That was an inn, not a restaurant.
Tell me if you crave anything
as we walk by.
Let's just go in anywhere.
That makes you want
to find the place more.
Excuse me?
"Go straight all the way,
then turn left at the end."
- Thank you.
You guys had it hard.
(Did they finally get a lead?)
- Turn left here.
- Turn left.
- We need to go 200m.
- Go 200m?
For real?
Our room might appear
if we walk 200m more.
Darn it.
Let's try it.
I've become curious,
although I wasn't earlier.
After you try it,
you'll thank me 100 times in Japanese.
- No, in Chinese.
- In Japanese?
- Si Eon. This is bad.
- What's wrong?
Si Eon. This is bad.
- What is it?
We've come here before.
- No!
That's the worst.
(The story behind the Lisien mystery)
Is that the street we took?
- Goodness.
- You made a big detour.
- It was...
- What a big detour.
(They might conquer Sifang Street.)
- Si Eon. This is bad.
- What's wrong?
(Welcome to Sifang Street.)
- "Welcome to Sifang Street."
- Isn't that like...
an urban myth or something?
It's like an unsettling nightmare...
where you just go round and round.
Rumor has it that the Sifang Street people
found you two scary.
- Because they kept seeing them?
- They kept seeing them.
"Who are they?"
"What's with those two
wearing jeans-on-jeans?"
- Rice noodles spirits.
- That's hilarious.
We've been here before.
No, Kian84. You're just imagining it.
- Come here.
- Okay, let's go back to square one.
- Here.
- Back to square one.
Oh, no. It's actually the same place.
They must've been frustrated.
But we also get lost
in the middle of Myeongdong.
- True. It's hard.
- The place is a maze.
I think the information desk...
- told us the wrong direction.
- Sifang something?
(Trudging without a choice)
Wait. Hi.
What? Are you Korean?
- Do you speak Chinese?
- Yes.
We're looking for this place right now.
- He's Korean.
- That's great.
Rice noodles.
I don't think they'll know
since it's their first trip.
This is also our first trip.
I see.
But they can speak Chinese.
(They ask the information desk
on their behalf.)
(That way.)
- That lady again.
- We have to...
- take that street again.
- We walked 400m.
- It's over there.
- We went there, but it wasn't there.
It's over here.
- Where?
- What?
- It was right in front of you?
- Was it right in front of them?
The place next to it with the sign?
Yes.
- Is it the place with the sign?
- Yes.
- I see. Thank you.
- Thank you.
What?
Why did you thank the Koreans in Chinese?
We were just too happy.
- Did we find it?
- Yes, we did.
It's this restaurant.
They finally found it.
(They finally found
the rice noodles place, Misien.)
- Look.
- Is this the place?
Don't tell me...
(The place Google Maps
kindly guided them to.)
- What?
- It was that restaurant?
How frustrating.
Yes. We're here, Kian84.
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
What's funny is that...
I showed the person the address.
But she told me it was over there.
- It was the address of this place, right?
- Yes.
(Hesitating)
(Sifang Street)
- You asked for Sifangjie.
- The square.
- You asked for the square.
- That's right.
He's holding back. Kian84 is holding back.
(Thinking)
- Kian84 looks extremely annoyed.
- He's...
- He's enraged.
- enduring it.
Walking around made me hungry. It's great.
(A fatal blow)
And we got to look around.
Nice.
He said that while gritting his teeth.
Here.
(Feeling bad, he quickly asks
if the restaurant has a table.)
I was walking on eggshells.
I had no idea. If I had known,
I would've guided him inside.
I swear I had no idea.
Traveling alone isn't an option yet.
(Sniffling)
- But aren't such incidents fun?
- Yes.
- It's memorable.
- Exactly.
- It'll become a memory.
- Smooth sailing isn't fun.
Hard times become memories. This phrase...
is always right.
If you ever visit that restaurant,
please take a tour around first.
- Like the Si Eon route?
- Yes, the route.
- How hilarious.
- There's a lot to see.
- Okay. Come, Kian84.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- We walked around for an hour.
- Really?
- You must've been starving.
(Going upstairs for an empty table)
- Hi.
Hi.
It'd be nice
if we could eat while looking outside.
(An unexpected terrace view)
- The restaurant looks nice.
- It's really nice.
- Gosh.
- The view here is amazing.
- Not bad, right?
- No.
I'll try to order us food.
I felt bad, so I wanted to order the food.
- I found the place.
- Got it.
The rice noodles come in either...
white broth or red broth.
- I want red broth.
- Same here.
(Would you like to order?)
Thank you.
(They must select
the rice noodles topping.)
I want this one.
- What's this?
- I don't know, but I'll take it.
(Kian84 picks with his instinct.)
One of this.
Red.
- Red. And...
- Okay.
And...
Well...
What's this?
- It looks like squid.
- Fried beef.
- Fried beef? I want this one.
- Yes.
- What is it? Let me ask.
- Just order it.
(What's this?)
- Wild bacteria.
- "Wild bacteria?"
(The personalized food
is perfect for him.)
- It's mushrooms.
- Mushrooms.
- Wild bacteria. Mushrooms.
- This one.
One of this.
(Yunnan rice noodles, fried beef,
stir-fried mushrooms, about 30 dollars)
(The fried beef is served first.)
- Thank you.
- Chop steak. No, chopsticks.
This is fried beef.
(Golden)
What part of beef is it?
(Let me try.)
You studied his face.
That's pitiful.
- No...
- That's pitiful.
(Kian84, do you like it?)
We saw it. It's all caught by the camera.
You were studying his face.
Si Eon studied my face?
If that was bad...
- Of course.
- You'd feel bad.
(He quietly scans Kian84's reaction.)
I hope it's good.
It better be good.
- He approves.
- Good.
He exclaimed.
- It's good.
- This is good. I'm glad to hear that.
What if it was bad
when we came all the way here?
Things wouldn't be good.
- That's a pass.
- That must've been relieving...
- when he exclaimed.
- I was relieved.
(Yunnan rice noodles arrive.)
You ordered the yak meat.
- What's this?
- Why are there so many toppings?
I ordered regular beef.
Do you get a little bit of everything?
That's amazing.
(In the red suantang)
If this is 15 dollars for everything,
it's not expensive.
Add everything.
(Adding all the toppings?)
It's like shabu-shabu.
Do you boil it on the spot?
- It was similar to mala xiang guo.
- That's unique.
You can only try it there.
That's a good find.
I'll try it my way.
This is...
from Yangpyeong hangover soup.
- Hey, this is beef omasum.
- Beef omasum.
This is fish.
(Various toppings)
The yak meat is the main ingredient.
(The yak meat he tried with Tamang before)
This too.
(Adding all the ingredients)
It was fun to add everything myself.
And the noodles.
The noodles look really good.
These noodles are firm
because they're rice noodles.
I know.
It looks good.
(Stir it to cook, and it's ready to eat.)
Let's try it.
(Cooling)
(Slurping)
(Oh, it's hot.)
- What's wrong?
- The noodles got in my eyes.
(Blowing his nose)
- Do you like it?
- Yes, it's good.
That's a relief.
(This time, they try the soup.)
(Exclaiming)
This soup is really good.
How can it taste like this?
- It was really good.
- That looks spicy.
It was darn good.
I'm craving soju.
It reminds me of tom yum kung.
Right. It is kind of like tom yum kung.
It tastes like malatang in yukgaejang.
Yukgae mala?
Yukgae mala noodles?
I think this is the best food
I've had so far on this trip.
- Really?
- It was really good.
- We should go too.
- I want to try it.
- I can't believe I missed it.
Oh, no. After all that hardship.
When we were planning things,
we didn't feed him.
(Regretful)
What's this?
- Mushrooms.
- But it doesn't look like a mushroom.
I don't know what this is.
(While Kian84 tries the wild bacteria...)
What's wrong?
(Laughing)
Thank you.
She said,
"Hi, do you need anything else, handsome?"
(Handsome?)
Thank you.
- Did you see that?
- What?
"Do you need anything else, handsome?"
- Why aren't you answering me?
- They eat this.
What? The translation...
(It must've been mistranslated.)
I don't know how to react
when you do that.
(Does he mean it?)
What's this, Kian84?
Don't eat that. That was in my mouth.
What are you doing?
- Why did you put that in mine?
- You are like "Dumb and Dumber."
They look like they're putting on a skit.
(The jean-on-jean couple has
unnecessarily perfect teamwork.)
(When Si Eon was enjoying the flattery...)
- Oh, that's when.
- "Flattery."
(He gave birth to a baby cartilage
in secret.)
There was a bone in the meat.
Are you sure that wasn't reversed?
(He spat it out like it was reversed.)
(He put it next to fried beef.)
I thought he had finished it.
He has no common sense.
There's one left.
(Feeling leery)
It's good.
You're like family.
I have a feeling that
Pani Bottle is enjoying his meal alone.
He kept sleeping because he was tired.
I was ill.
You were tired.
We asked him too much.
It was you.
- You ask him a lot too.
- I don't.
You're like,
"Pani Bottle. Will you book the hotel?"
(Input)
(Output)
He's right.
He's almost like an AI.
- Look.
- Okay.
Did I ask him to call a taxi...
or book a hotel?
This is what you say.
"How do we get there?"
Then Pani Bottle goes,
"I'll call the taxi."
(Do we have to call the taxi?)
(The sneaky guy orders Pani Bottle
as if he's curious.)
- I'm only asking.
- "How do we get to the hotel?"
Whereas you put him in trouble.
Let's have Pani Bottle rest
for the rest of the afternoon.
At 4:30 p.m.,
let's visit the place I want to visit.
Where's that?
I can guarantee you that you'll like it.
You could say it's a place meant for you.
What? What is it?
Are we going to the Buddhist university?
There's none around here.
(Hiding something)
Are we going to the Buddhist university?
I'm sorry, but we have to drive there.
Does it take like five hours or something?
You haven't unpacked yet, have you?
What's the point of booking the lodging?
(There's no break in our memories.)
I finished it.
I gained all that weight I lost in Nepal.
(They finished the rice noodles.)
- That was good.
That was good.
(Going back to the lodging
to get Pani Bottle)
Did you pay already?
How was the food?
That was the best on this trip for me.
Pani Bottle.
(The eldest looks for Pani Bottle
as soon as he returns.)
- Pani Bottle.
- Pani Bottle's sleeping.
- Why are you shocked?
- Pani Bottle.
He's like, "Yes. Do you need help?"
"I'm sorry. I slept in."
"Yes, master."
- "What do you need?"
- "Master?"
"Just give me your order."
"Please don't hit me."
"I'll grab the taxi."
You were startled.
We're back. Did you eat?
No. I just rested.
- Let's go, Pani Bottle. Are you coming?
- Where did you go?
Where are we going?
A place I want to go.
Let me get ready.
(He doesn't know where he's going,
but he still gets ready.)
(Feeling refreshed)
- Are you okay?
- I feel so refreshed.
- Did you sleep?
- Yes.
(His eyes are shining again.)
The place I want to go closes at 5:30 p.m.
We have to hurry up.
If you tell me where we're going,
I'll call the taxi.
- His voice is gone.
- Oh, no.
I can't watch it anymore.
- I feel so bad for him.
- Watch what I say next.
I'll call the taxi. Don't do it.
- Did you make the wallet?
- What?
It's so pitiful because his voice is gone.
- Did you make it?
- Now, I know how to spend money.
We can just call the taxi outside.
If I learn to call the taxi,
I can do everything.
- We can call the taxi outside. Let's go.
- But...
I'll grab it then.
- The taxi...
- I can do that too.
Don't call it. Let's just grab one.
- But...
- You can rest.
There's a taxi coming.
The older ones are stepping forward
for you.
Do you have the address?
- Taxi!
- We were going old-fashioned.
Taxi.
- He's taking us to where he wants to go.
- Taxi.
(They decided to trust and follow Si Eon.)
- You found one.
- When I did this,
- they just stopped in front of me.
- Really?
Nice.
Wait. The address is in English.
What do I do?
(Facing a crisis already)
(Showing the address out of nowhere)
This way.
- Okay?
- It's good.
Hey, they understand you.
- You just need to give it a try.
- Yes.
Where are we going?
I'll take the lead today.
Si Eon said it was a secret.
You might like it or not like it.
Si Eon was taking us somewhere,
but I had no idea where we were going.
We're leaving the city.
(Getting far from the city)
Where are we going?
Is it a museum or what?
A museum? Or a park?
It's very secluded.
- We're here.
- I'll pay.
(They arrived at the mysterious place.)
Three, six, four, zero?
- Thank you.
I see people going in.
What's this place?
Honestly, I'm not sure if you'll like it.
- But Kian84.
- Yes?
This is for you.
What does Kian84 like?
- Close your eyes and follow me.
- Okay.
(They approach the entrance.)
A wedding?
- Come here.
- Okay.
I think this is...
Pani Bottle noticed it.
I saw it, so I didn't say anything.
- You knew?
- It's a meaningful place.
(What is this place?)
- Is it a botanical garden?
- Come in.
Are these canola flowers?
These are canola flowers.
- That's beautiful.
- They bloomed everywhere.
They must've bloomed at Han River too.
Can you find them by the Han River too?
- This is barley.
- That's barley?
Yes. It's either wheat or barley.
That place was really beautiful.
(Wheat and barley are growing)
The windmills look great.
- It's a beautiful sight.
- Yes.
The weather is...
(It looks even more exotic
because of the amazing weather.)
The mountain looks amazing.
All the seasons can be seen.
(Yulong Snow Mountain
with the outstanding view)
That's nice.
(Yulong Snow Mountain
with the outstanding view)
We get to visit a botanical garden often
with Kian84.
It's beautiful.
The flower smell.
- Nice.
- You can smell the flowers.
- Right.
- It's so rich.
(The rich scent of the flowers
gives joy to their noses.)
It was rich like fabric softeners.
- What kind of flowers are these?
- They smell so nice.
- It was nice to visit nice places.
- The flowers smell nice.
There was a reason it was nice.
I didn't expect three men to be so happy
to see flowers.
Everyone likes flowers.
(The botanical garden is filled
with the scent of flowers.)
- Over there.
- There's a wedding.
- Gosh.
- Oh, the wedding photo.
They're really getting married.
There were mostly newlywed couples.
It's worth taking wedding photos there.
(There are grooms and brides here...)
(and there.)
- Pani...
- Wait a minute.
- I thought that was Pani Bottle.
- Who?
- I thought that was Pani Bottle...
- on the left.
- Really?
- What?
- Isn't that Pani Bottle?
(Groom?)
Am I seeing things?
Yes. They look the same.
Hey, what are you doing in there?
- We're both short.
- No.
You should take your wedding photo there.
When I get married,
I must not wear sunglasses.
I'd look like him.
(There are grooms and brides here...)
(and there.)
(People are taking wedding photos
everywhere.)
(It's famous among grooms and brides.)
The photos will look great wherever.
(We're getting married.)
- That's great.
- Congratulations.
What?
Are we here to take wedding photos?
I didn't know why we were there.
- I wondered why he brought us there.
- You felt lonely.
(It's not Pani Bottle.)
Where are... Hey, I can't find them.
- Who?
- That guy.
(The guy they saw at the entrance)
(Let me see.)
Wait.
Over there.
Why are they so far?
- What's there?
(While the brothers are whispering...)
Look. The couples are multiplying.
- The couples are multiplying.
- Keep going.
Kian84, we have to go to the end.
But people are taking pictures.
Let's walk slowly.
- Kian84.
- Yes?
Over there.
(Over there.)
Look carefully.
(All he sees are the couples.)
Wait.
- Wait.
- He found something.
Si Eon.
Isn't that an alpaca?
You finally found it.
Alpaca...
(Laughing)
(Hiding among the couples)
- Over there.
- Oh, my gosh. It's so cute.
(Alpacas)
(Happy)
You finally saw it.
Alpaca. It's so cute.
- Kian84. We're here to see that.
- Yes?
For real?
I felt so bad that
I didn't let you take photos in Peru.
Go hold its neck.
Really?
(When they were traveling
in South America,)
(they ran into an alpaca on the street.)
(Kian84 wanted to take a picture with it.)
(But Si Eon was against it
in case they'd get ripped off.)
(Can I take a picture with the alpaca?)
(I want to take a picture
with the alpaca.)
(He couldn't move on.)
He couldn't take his eyes off it.
You should've let him take one.
He wanted it so badly.
My wife blamed me so much at home.
For not letting him take a picture
with it.
So my wife knitted it. It's handmade.
Oh, my gosh.
She's pretty good.
(He was soothed
by the handmade alpaca doll instead.)
I feel like I'm in Cusco.
(He was soothed
by the handmade alpaca doll instead.)
(Si Eon wanted to show him real alpacas.)
I heard there were alpacas.
So I took them there...
to take photos.
- That's touching.
- Yes.
- To show alpacas.
- You felt bad.
- You can take all the photos you want.
- You can take as many as you want.
- What a nice brother.
- My goodness.
(Oh, yes!)
The alpaca is cute.
The other alpacas are busy.
Let's meet the one that's not busy.
The alpacas were busy.
I think that one's free.
(Me?)
That's so cute. What is that, a chair?
- Does it bite?
- Probably not.
- He...
- Look at the teeth.
Its front teeth are protruding.
Get close to it.
- Closer.
- Is it nice?
How do I know? This is my first time too.
(Scared84 approaches him slowly.)
(Spitting)
- Did he spit?
- He spat.
(Screaming)
- That's cute.
- Hey.
Maybe it doesn't like you.
There was a reason no one was around it.
If there's no one around the alpaca,
there's a reason.
- It's sensitive.
- It must be sensitive.
Let's get to know it.
It's cute.
(He approaches the alpaca again.)
(Spitting)
- It hates it.
I tried to approach it like a dog.
But it didn't want me to touch it.
- Maybe I'm annoying.
- "Get lost."
Them.
They stay still even if people touch them.
- All the alpacas were so busy.
- Of course. They're cute.
Anyway,
they look cute like poodles.
Yes. They all look fluffy.
I think they had a haircut.
They look kind.
They're cute.
Are they a couple?
- A photo together?
- Stand in front of them.
(Approaching carefully)
Is it okay?
(Tapping)
- So cute.
- They're all different.
This one's still.
- They were kind.
- They don't even spit.
You're so cute.
How about this pose?
(He takes off his bag and fidgets.)
Why...
(What are you doing?)
You have the same bottom.
Stay just like that. It's perfect.
Finally,
he's taking a photo with the alpaca.
(Clicking)
That one's gentle.
(Three alpacas are
taking a photo quietly.)
I'm sure he's the only one who took
a photo like that in the whole world.
- You finally had a photo with the alpaca.
- Finally.
- After 3 years.
(His wish of 3 years became the poster.)
(Smiling)
Good.
"Denim alpaca."
Is this the alpaca's poop?
It's probably a mix of their poop and mud.
I want to touch it.
- This one's gentle.
- It's gentle.
Stay there.
(Staring)
Its neck is so long.
- So cute.
- What are you doing?
I look like a gorilla.
Kian84, 1, 2...
(A gorilla and alpacas)
That's cute.
Can you take a picture of us?
We asked the cameraman
to take a picture of us.
We must not scare them.
So walk behind them quietly and graze.
- We must not scare them.
- Of course.
Okay. Be quiet, so they won't be scared.
Oh, my goodness.
(The Three Brothers are crawling.)
Why do we have to crawl?
What did the other two do to deserve that?
(The other two)
Gosh. Poop.
- Poop?
- He stepped on the poop.
Oh, no.
- What are they doing?
- Don't eat that, Kian84.
You'd really eat it.
It was full of poop.
(Visiting Pani Bottle)
They're looking at me.
They're looking at me strangely.
They're like,
"I've never seen anyone like that before."
Let's wait until they graze.
- Are we grazing for real?
- Don't graze for real.
I feel like throwing up.
They're looking at me like I'm weird.
They're watching Pani Bottle.
It's looking at me.
I'm getting embarrassed.
Maybe it likes you.
(Are you here alone?)
(Smacking lips)
(I like you.)
(While Pani Bottle
is drawing the alpaca's attention,)
It's grazing.
(the alpaca begins grazing.)
(They're grazing together.)
(Turning)
(The alpaca leaves.)
(Eating)
What are they doing?
What a sight for the alpacas.
I wonder what he thought about them.
(They draw the passersby's attention too.)
Get closer. Hurry.
Raise your bottom, Pani Bottle.
(Raising)
- Raise your bottom.
- I did.
- Lift your head too.
- The bottoms like that?
- We wanted to stand in line.
- To take a picture from the back.
Who's taking the picture?
I don't know.
It seems no one is.
(Alpacas and bottoms)
We won't be able to take a picture
like alpacas like that again.
What's going on?
- Pani Bottle is loved by alpacas.
- I know.
They began to recognize me
as their colleague.
At this rate, people might take
their wedding photos with Pani Bottle.
(Jealous)
They were not coming to us.
(I like Pani Bottle.)
Now they got close.
(Blowing)
- It's blowing.
- It's how alpacas flirt.
I guess it likes him.
I guess they recognize a kind person.
(Sniffing)
- I got their poop on myself.
- I see.
After smelling the poop on me,
they come close to me.
- I see.
- They're smelling the poop.
- Is that so?
- "Is that so?"
How come he says, "Is that so?"
They recognize me as their buddy.
(After smelling the poop,)
(alpacas look for Pani Bottle only.)
It's amazing.
They look at Pani Bottle only.
(Bitter)
(The eldest gives it a try.)
He had poop on his hand.
(Shaking its head)
- It's saying no to Si Eon.
- It doesn't like him.
It's saying no to Si Eon.
It clearly expresses its intent.
That's amazing.
Si Eon, there is a lot of poop here.
- "There is a lot of poop here."
- It's full of poop.
Get some poop on your lips
so that you can kiss the alpacas.
What?
(Clapping)
Kian84,
you finally had your wish come true.
The dream that didn't come true in Peru.
I didn't need an apology.
I don't know
why Si Eon feels so sorry about it.
It's been about 2 years
since our 1st trip.
He's been talking about it
all along for two years.
It's fine.
Stop apologizing. It's fine. I'm okay.
Still, where the alpaca poop were,
we were rolling around
and making poses with alpacas.
I personally appreciated it,
and it felt warm.
He's receiving a proper apology.
I did that because I had the chance.
I appreciate that you thought about it.
That's true.
Stay healthy.
You're going through a lot,
taking pictures with people.
In your next life,
I hope you reincarnate as humans.
Bye.
This was my favorite place on this trip.
This is the best place on this trip.
(This is the best place on this trip!)
(Sitting down)
- We took a photo.
- Yes.
To be honest, I have no idea
what I'm going to do tomorrow.
I was going to go there with you.
- Where?
- The minority village.
- Here he goes again.
- The minority village, again.
He's obsessed with minority groups.
Find it on your phone.
You got the address earlier.
(Aren't they minority groups?)
(He talked about minority groups
throughout the trip.)
(It's something like a minority sparrow.)
(Even a minority sparrow?)
(There are many minority groups
in Lijiang.)
(He found out about the Nakhi people
by chance.)
(Where can I meet the Nikhi people?)
(Although he's not familiar
with the name yet,)
(he begins to find the Nakhi people
in earnest.)
(Here they are.)
(At last?)
(This afternoon, he got information
from the owner of the lodging.)
There's a village where real Nakhi people
live, which isn't a tourist attraction.
Tomorrow we're going there.
(He decided to go meet the Nakhi people.)
We can't reach there
by public transportation.
Then we can sleep in the car.
- Sleep in the car?
- What did he say?
Where are you going to get a car?
A car? There are many taxis there.
- Si Eon.
- What?
I think this is our chance...
- to rent a car.
- I like that. I'm in!
Let's plan to rent a car,
and this evening,
- let's make a detailed plan.
- Yes.
All right.
A rental car. It's going to be so fun.
I feel so good.
(What will happen to the Three Brothers,
going deep into the Tea Horse Road?)
(A minority group living in Lijiang)
(Nakhi people)
(Traditional music
with a thousand-year history)
(The only hieroglyphics used
in the world now, Dongba script)
(The Nakhi people keep
the long-standing tradition.)
(They go searching for a Nakhi village.)
(What journey awaits the Three Brothers?)
(Riding on a beautiful road,)
(they hit the road on the Tea Horse Road.)
(What's that?)
The fence is all destroyed.
(If we get hit by the rock,
we'll pass away.)
(To make matters worse,
the only path is blocked.)
(It's not easy to enter
the Nakhi people's village.)
(Go for it.)
- This is wonderful.
- It's a good thing we came up here.
(After passing the arduous mountain path,)
(the sight of the Nakhi village
appears before them like a reward.)
(Now, he wishes to meet the Nakhi people.)
(A man crazy about Nakhi people)
(I want to meet the Nakhi people.)
(I can sleep where this family sleeps.)
(Nakhi84 is surrounded by Nakhi people.)
(Like grandsons
visiting relatives in the countryside,)
(they receive royal treatment.)
(In the life of a minority group
he always dreamed of,)
(he's being immersed.)
(You don't have to ask me if I'm fine.)
(I'll take a rest when I need it.)
(Nakhi84 is the best.)
(The Nakhi younger sister guides them...)
(to a mysterious place.)
(The hideout
of the most respected person?)
(Significant)
(I can ask questions
on my love life for a test.)
(A desperate prayer)
What?
Amazing.
(I've never said that on a show.)
(It's revealed for the first time.)
(Pani Bottle's secret)
(What's Pani Bottle's confession
that surprised everyone?)
(Adventure by Accident 4)