Episode 4
What's a sports preparation?
Listen, I'll explain it so that even monkeys understand.
When a person tries to move their body,
their brain decides to move it already.
Huh? What do you mean?
The one with the sense of presence.
That's right.
Well...
I think I'm punching after thinking about it myself.
But in reality, I punch unconsciously a few seconds before I realize it?
As expected of you, my lady!
You're a genius when you understand it so quickly!
A few seconds...
It's time to take my life.
That's right.
In other words,
if you can overcome your conscious thoughts
and be able to take the sports preparation,
It's all thanks to you.
I struggled to avoid your noisy thoughts,
but I've got a deep-seated trick.
I won't let you hurt my precious people!
I'll finish you off like this!
Oh, no!
I can't get used to it all of a sudden.
Damn it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're having a lot of fun.
On my island...
The one who touched my family...
I'll kill him.
Who?
I'm sorry.
Alright alright, everyone.
Let's all get
everything together.
And wait just a little bit.
Aren't you hungry?
Everyone, action!
'
Right now I'm hungry.
Everyone, action!
Let's all get buscando.
And wait just a little bit.
Perfect...
Now it's here.
Ô?
Here?
lance
剛
chuck
ative
I'm sorry.
Moisture Etonol?
That's when it happened?
So that's why it's in the Water Sword Mode.
But somehow...
It feels different from the previous time I was drunk.
You guys are so weird from one to the next.
The Mafia has been underestimated.
No way!
Mafia Jogo?
Shin, it's dangerous, so back off.
Die!
Where are you?
From now on, I'll cut off the number of people you've killed.
Get out of my way, you piece of shit!
Who are you trying to...
I told you to shut up.
That hurts!
I understand.
Please, forgive me.
I won't get involved with you guys anymore.
Please.
Have you ever lent an ear to someone's life?
I'm going to die.
No, I don't want this to be the last time.
You're crazy!
The Bad End is a human's life, so it's no fun.
No, I want to live longer.
I want to kill more people.
You're not listening to me.
It's over.
Go, you bastard!
I don't care about you.
I care about you.
I heard the death penalty was killed at the same place.
What if the death penalty is gone?
Why are you making me do this?
Shishiba said he wanted to eat tonkatsu.
You're the one.
Eat slowly.
You're not eating.
Hey!
I'm approaching the target.
Can you two move with full stomach?
If you're sick, you can rest.
We don't have a choice.
It's easy, but...
Let's eat and find a place to stay.
Don't be so cool.
It's not good manners.
Shishiba, I'm leaving.
Thank you for the meal.
Be careful.
You'll die from being impatient.
I hate women too much.
I can't eat two katsu-don.
I'm full.
That's impossible.
Why is he...
I'll eat you up!
Damn it.
I won't die here.
I don't want to kill you.
Take me to the airport.
No, the customer is still...
Shut up. I'll kill you.
Just pray.
Yes!
The next day
Okay, I'll steal the money and hide for a while.
You're in a hurry.
Sorry, but your destination is a little later.
I don't care.
I just arrived.
I'm going to fire.
Hey, Rue. Wake up.
Did you get a heart attack?
He's not here.
I have to find him right away.
What's wrong?
Does your head hurt?
A new ability has been activated.
Damn it.
It's a critical time.
If so, you're dead.
Damn it.
I was rampaging in the general public area.
We're used to being floater.
Floater?
Who?
When the killer destroys or pollutes the city,
it recovers itself before the battle.
It's a self-propelled unit.
It's a big deal.
It's a bad pattern.
It's almost like a job for the killer's fairy agency.
Speaking of bad patterns,
you're completely drunk.
I was drinking.
It felt good.
By the way, where's the
shopping bag?
Oh, no.
I have to go back to the store.
I like this.
Well,
what can I ask for?
I hope you can kill the killer.
It's strange.
Why do humans close their eyes when they pray?
Wow.
I've met him.
Thank you, God.
Oh,
you're the best booth in the list.
Do you know how to thank God in Japan?
Huh?
Two bows.
Two claps.
One bow.
Oh,
I saw you before.
I've decided.
I'll make you cuter.
Osaragi.
Where did he go?
The End
You're the one who's going to make me cuter.
I'll make you die.
In the name of the Order,
Harimogura.
You're a crazy bastard.
I was just in love.
What's the matter?
You think it's a terrible thing to catch people and kill them?
You're a murderer, too.
Why are you judging me?
Judging?
No way.
If a bug enters the house, it will kill it.
That's all.
Murder is my house.
The Order is...
Well...
When it grows?
You know, the one with the sharpness.
Is this a weapon?
You're a pretty tough guy.
It's heavy.
What's wrong?
Hit me like you did before.
Can't you get closer if you don't have the courage?
One on the palm of your hand, six on the body.
Oh, that's how it's stored.
It's like a magic hand.
It's weird.
It's like a bone.
It's like a hand.
It's weird.
Is it hidden in the bone?
What should I do?
I don't want to get too close.
I don't have a version today.
Well, are you going to pray to God?
You taught me how to do it earlier.
This time, the people...
It's different.
It's hot.
The shrine's bell is a punishment.
Punishment?
Punishment doesn't work.
Because God is kind.
The one who is kind...
Suekichi.
It's always been strange.
If I were God, I wouldn't make a person like you.
Be more afraid, Busu.
You're too kind.
So...
We'll keep the order in place.
I don't need prayers for a dirty murderer.
My love has always been one-sided.
I love you.
Is it a sin to be one-sided?
Please go out with me.
Okay.
I love you, too.
I want you to love me more than anyone else.
I love you, Damp.
We're best friends, right?
I love you.
That's when fear is the best.
While everyone's afraid,
they think of me without lying.
Huh?
But why am I so empty?
If I die, they won't think of anything else.
It's hard to break up.
I have to find my next lover.
Why am I the only one who's fallen in love with someone else?
Just like everyone else!
Just like everyone else?
I just want to be loved!
We're murderers.
But because there's someone like you...
I have a reason to live today.
Thank you.
I love you.
Beautiful.
Hey, Taro.
It's been a while since I last saw you, Shikeshu.
Oh, it's okay.
I can't keep quiet when I'm beaten up.
I'll call you again when I find you.
I think I'll find these weirdos soon.
But this is the view of the peace family!
You're always flying to the great places, peace family!
You're so cool, peace family!
Okay, now I'm in super peace family mode!
Where are you going, Shikeshu?
Yes, I'm going to the Shikeshu family.
They're already dead.
But it's almost as planned.
Yes.
We were able to get the order right.
We're going to the next phase.
Yes.
Then let's continue.
For the sake of justice.
Who are you calling?
What's your purpose?
This is the apartment of the Shikeshu family.
What are you talking about?
Oh, you've been deceived.
I want to die.
You don't try to understand me either.
People can't understand each other forever
unless they reveal the contents.
I'm grateful that you got me out of prison,
but I'm sorry to be used by you guys.
I'm going to live my life the way I've lived.
You too!
Don't touch anyone other than Rist!
It's not a deal!
I want to understand more and more people.
What's going on?
I was being naive.
He's too dangerous.
If we don't do something, our plan will be ruined.
Well, it's fine, Kashima.
Let him do what he wants.
This is a difficult question.
No, it's fine.
Let's enjoy the risk.
Let's kill him.
It's fine.
Let's enjoy the risk.
This is just right to get rid of the murder.
Let's make them go wild.
Is Shin okay?
Oh, thank goodness.
I'm fine.
There are no customers yet.
Yeah, I'm fine by myself.
You too, Kir-
Sorry.
I'll hang up now that the customers are here.
Welcome.
Are you looking for something?
I'm sorry.
The ideal shadow
I want to see it until it's all gone
Our dreams are unchanged
Our taste
Dad, do your best!
Don't fall!
Dad!
That's my jersey!
I'm going to play a prank on you.
I wonder if you'll kill me.
It's okay.
It's too easy for the manager to just replace it.
Just like that!
Masugas!
Sakamoto!
He's pretty excited.
Wirings
Oh my god!
Mom!
Thank you!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.