♪Xiao Jiu leads♪
♪Unveiling truths with no retreat♪
♪Between love and hate,
on the edge of fate♪
♪Side by side
they challenge death's gate♪
♪Strange things rise♪
♪Fear takes flight♪
♪Through the storm,
true hearts shine bright♪
♪The hand behind♪
♪Shows its face in time♪
♪Love and courage pierce the night♪
=The Mystery of Dragon Town=
=Episode 9=
Detective Yang.
Detective Yang, I'm here.
Are you two all right?
Uh, um...
Well then,
I'll go check outside.
Go.
You two,
dug up a grave,
disturbed a corpse.
One had a shovel,
the other a spade.
Our groundskeeper
saw the whole thing.
Detective Yang,
didn't you promise me you wouldn't let
what happened to the Yu family's son
happen to us?
Didn't you?
And what?
My daughter Shanshan rise from the dead.
And now,
you're digging up her grave
and desecrating her remains?
What the hell are you trying to do?
Mr. He, what happened with
the rise from the dead
was a misunderstanding.
This time another misunderstanding too.
By the time we got there, someone
had already tampered with the body.
I saw it,
the cuts were made by a blade.
Neither my shovel nor Xiaojiu's spade
could have caused those wounds.
We dug up the grave
to uncover the truth.
To let He Shanshan rest in peace.
Enough!
That's enough shouting.
What is this, a marketplace?
You call this an investigation?
Who do you think you are,
coming to our police station
to investigate?
No...
Do you seriously
not get it?
Without your meddling,
this case would've
been solved centuries ago!
(Dragon Town Police Station.
Autopsy Report)
The coroner
has already examined the body.
He Shanshan's corpse
was desecrated
around 9 PM last night.
How do
you explain that?
Director.
Do you remember
last night I called you
a useless director
and said I could do your job better?
Here you go again.
Believe it or not...
That's not the point.
The point is,
it was already 8 PM when I said it.
We left the city
and that takes at least an hour.
Add in the time
it took to dig up the grave,
go back and forth...
There's no way we had time.
Director,
you're actually our alibi.
Mr. He,
aren't you suspicious?
The person who broke
into your home last time
wasn't the reporter.
It was someone else.
They ransacked your house first,
then
went to the graveyard.
So...
that person
wasn't Liao Sheng?
Then what were they looking for?
They did that
to my daughter.
I can tell you,
the people who dug up the grave
are the real killers behind all this.
Not the ghost bride.
We've already got their trail.
Give us a bit more time.
We'll give you an answer.
Yang Ziqi.
You've got six days.
I need to find a way to get the director
out of the way for a bit.
You finally get it.
Detective Yang.
You were right.
Take a look.
What's this?
(Bank withdrawal receipt)
This is the receipt from the day
He Shanshan
withdrew money from the bank.
My contact at the bank told me,
on the day she died,
He Shanshan had planned
to leave Dragon Town.
She bought a train ticket
and was going to flee overnight.
So those travel permits and
the Good Citizen Certificate, they all line up.
She must've read those papers
from the past few days. She knew she was next.
So she tried to run.
Looks like
we'll have to go back
to He Shanshan's paper.
Check it again.
Your leg...
Maybe you should stay here.
We'll take you to the hospital first.
I get it.
Fixing my leg is a small matter.
Solving the case is more important.
All right then.
We'll take you up on that.
We'll borrow your car too.
Appreciate it.
I...
I was just being polite.
You could've at least left me the car!
Thirty percent of that limp was real.
Seventy percent was fake.
It shows. One moment it's his left leg,
the next it's his right.
(Hunan Province
Dragon Town Police Station)
In here.
(Admission Ticket)
Look.
Same theatre ticket.
There's no theatre
like this in Dragon Town.
Where is this place?
There isn't?
Never heard of it.
Since we know
they're looking for something
and I've seen
that pale-faced man before.
Then we can use this ticket stub
to bait out the one behind all this.
Maybe that pale-faced man himself.
We'll bait them.
But not we, just me.
Me alone.
Are you an idiot, Yang Ziqi?
Trying to ditch your partner again.
Using people when you need them
and tossing them when you don't.
If they really believe
I'm holding a key piece of evidence,
they'll come after me.
If you get caught up in it,
it'll be dangerous.
Then that's all the more reason
I can't let you go alone.
It's better to share the risk
than to take it alone.
You're so annoying.
Stop messing around.
Reporter's body holds the truth.
Murderer hides behind gods and ghosts.
Detective uncovers new evidence.
Pale-faced man finally revealed.
Extra, extra.
(Taibai Hall)
I'm back, old man.
Old man?
Come out, I brought good food.
I got Lotus White liquor
and a whole roast chicken.
Old man?
Where did you go?
(Girl.)
(Master had to step out
of town for a bit,)
(I'll bring back
your favourite roast chicken.)
Well then.
Looks like I'll have to
enjoy it all by myself.
♪Misty moonlight in Xiangxi's night♪
♪Fog veils the entire Dragon Town♪
♪Corpse herders drift like fleeting shade♪
♪Hurrying down the nether road♪