♪Xiaojiu leads♪
♪Unveiling truths with no retreat♪
♪Between love and hate,
on the edge of fate♪
♪Side by side
they challenge death's gate♪
♪Strange things rise♪
♪Fear takes flight♪
♪Through the storm,
true hearts shine bright♪
♪The hand behind♪
♪Shows its face in time♪
♪Love and courage pierce the night♪
=The Mystery of Dragon Town=
=Episode 11=
Hello?
You know every nook and corner
of Dragon Town, right?
Of course.
Look into this place for me.
Linjiangxian Theater.
Just leave it to me.
(Why did both the white-faced man)
(Linjiangxian Theater)
(and the mysterious woman show up here?)
Can you stop scaring me?
No.
Do you know
why Master Jiu is so worried?
Is it because
of the Peace Preservation Corps?
You should stay away from Yang Ziqi.
Well...
There's nothing going on between us.
I mean
what you're investigating
is getting dangerous.
The Yin Sting Bug
showed a strong reaction
because her body
seemed to contain opium.
Yet, in order to achieve
such a great effect,
there should be at least
one jin of opium in He Shanshan's body
to make the bug go out of control.
Who would
take one jin of opium?
That's impossible.
Unless
it's not opium.
I don't know what that would be either.
That's why
it's tricky.
Oh, right.
Here's a Revitalizing Leaf.
It can mitigate some symptoms.
If my master were still around,
he'd definitely know
what all this is about.
Indeed.
If Madam Ma were still around,
she could be the old man's partner.
Forget it.
Madam Ma would never fall
for a man like Master Jiu.
You're right.
She would be too good for him.
But, you know what,
I get mad at the thought of it.
The townsfolk see me as a body snatcher!
In the eyes of the world,
people like us
have always been seen
as riffraff, unworthy of respect.
Forget what
those narrow-minded people think.
Think about it.
Miss Liu from the Falling Petals Cave,
Granny Ghost of the Mountains,
Grandma Sun,
and that...
Enough.
Stop it, Luoluo.
I know you're worried about me.
I swear.
I'll just locate Yushuang's body.
And I'll stay out
of the rest.
Who's that?
Xiaojiu.
It's that detective.
Why is that fool here
at this early hour?
Old man,
hide yourself.
Go ahead.
Sure, I'll go into hiding.
I'll hide myself.
Why do I need to hide myself?
Xiaojiu.
Stop.
What are you doing here?
Leave the Dragon Town.
(Renchunhe)
What started
as a simple corpse theft case
now involves
increasingly tangled forces.
Master Jiu's death
might also be related to this.
We're in more danger than ever
What a good friend you are.
Out of all my friends,
you're the most generous of all.
If you ever need to arrange a funeral,
just let me know.
I'll be there for you.
You're not leaving?
Yang Ziqi.
What are you doing?
Don't...
Are you nuts, Yang Ziqi?
Don't think the money you gave me
gives you the right to do as you please.
I'm sorry.
I just want to pay respects
to Master Jiu.
Master Jiu.
Today,
I came to bid farewell.
You had been
a righteous
and carefree man.
Take care.
You spoke
as if you knew my master well.
You officials
are surely good with words.
Master.
I will work hard to find out the truth
and clear your name.
You're determined to investigate it,
right?
Yes.
Well,
let me explain myself.
Detective Yang. Detective Yang!
Yang Ziqi. Yang Ziqi!
Wait, that's...
I wouldn't want to pretend to be dead
for the rest of my life.
In other words,
all of the deceased
are related to this theater.
We'll reach a breakthrough
if we manage to locate the theater.
Have you found it,
Liao Sheng?
Look.
Fuli Road.
No. 32.
Fuchun House?
Isn't that a pleasure house?
Do you know it
well?
He does.
Stop your nonsense thought.
It's not what you think.
This address was provided
by the mole
of my mole's mole.
It's said to be a sinister place.
During its construction,
a lot of human skeletons were found.
They can even enable
their distinguished guests
run businesses in netherworld.
Nonsense.
Sir.
Detective Yang.
We can't just take their word for it.
Let's hear him out.
I don't want
to rely on those rumors either.
I'd like to do interviews there.
Only their distinguished guests
get to receive intel.
Ordinary folk can just forget about it.
That's how secretive they are.
I'm doing a favor by providing you
with this clue, right?
I even took their picture
during the house's opening.
It's right there. Have a look.
Who's this?
That's the owner
of Fuchun House, Sui Wen.
Is he...
What?
Is he Sui Wen?
Can you finish your sentence
next time?
You gave me a fright.
Is this outfit necessary?
And look at this scary makeup.
If you want to alert them,
you can do without the outfit.
Oh, right.
Did you have something to say
when we were in the newspaper office?
I've figured it out.
Sui Wen owns the Fuchun House.
He's the white-faced man I met
in the Yutang House.
I knew it.
We're getting closer to the truth.
It's dangerous in there.
So you must be cautious.
I know. Stop repeating it.
I'm just not used to it.
Once I've got used to it,
I'll just breeze in it.
Mind your conduct.
I'm sick of staying home
and seeing your face.
What's wrong with me having fun here?
If you can do this,
why can't I?
I am a man.
You are a woman.
That's the difference!
What's with it?
You have fun with women.
I'll have fun with men. It's just the same.
I'm here to take advantage of them.
And you'll be taken advantage of.
It's not the same!
If you dare come here for fun,
stay out of my business, then.
Got it?
I'll do it. I'm going to
have fun with some men.
Wait... Stop right there!
What's with these two?
Sir.
Please, come on in.
Three men
made their way to the east corridor.
And they haven't returned yet.
It's a dead end there.
It's most likely
where the secret theater is.
Let's go.
We'll check it out.
I see it.
They're there with the tickets.
They enter the theater
holding those tickets.
And
they will be given
ticket stubs in return.
Those ticket stubs
look exactly like that we saw
in the newspaper office.
Well,
is this your first time here?
Yes, I came here
after your recommendation.
Sir, ma'am. Are you here to seek wealth,
for fortune-telling,
or ask about someone?
We'd like to ask about a person.
What was the deceased's name?
What?
I mean
the name of the one
you'd like to find in netherworld.
Yu Jiu.
That's right.
(Yu Jiu)
Hey.
Black Tortoise, no. 4 and 5.
Please.
Follow me.
Be careful. We'll run if things go wrong.
Liao Sheng is waiting for us out there.
Careful.
I don't feel good about this place.
- What's wrong with it?
- They're having a soul descent ritual.
Sir, ma'am.
Please be quiet. You wouldn't want
to disturb the divine being.
The ritual
is about to begin.
Please remove your shoes
and place your bare feet
on the spirit money.
Let's just play it by ear.
Please take a Spirit-Linking Pill.
Please place your palms together.
Distinguished guests
and business owners.
You're not allowed
to wear a Buddha necklace
or jade beads.
Please hand over
your talismans too.
If there's anything else,
we shall begin the ritual now.
Well, once you've reached
the Yuangong Residence,
please
return immediately
after asking all your questions.
Remember.
Don't eat what you see down there.
Now we will have the Patriarch
to lead us there.
Greetings, the God of the Land.
Yu Shuang.
Yu Shuang!
♪Misty moonlight in Xiangxi's night♪
♪Fog veils the entire Dragon Town♪
♪Corpse herders drift like fleeting shade♪
♪Hurrying down the nether road♪