♪Xiaojiu leads♪
♪Unveiling truths with no retreat♪
♪Between love and hate,
on the edge of fate♪
♪Side by side
they challenge death's gate♪
♪Strange things rise♪
♪Fear takes flight♪
♪Through the storm,
true hearts shine bright♪
♪The hand behind♪
♪Shows its face in time♪
♪Love and courage pierce the night♪
=The Mystery of Dragon Town=
=Episode 4=
Creepy.
This is way too creepy.
You again?
Let go of me,
you lunatic!
I let you get away once.
Not this time.
Psycho.
What the hell
are you doing here
this late, Detective Yang?
Don't tell me
the killer's
crying thief?
She was already dead when I got here.
Then why are you here
this late?
What, came back
to admire your handiwork?
Watch your mouth!
Look clearly
at what she's wearing.
Don't you pin this on me.
This is Black Maoshan.
So what?
I remember
it was in
our family's Forbidden Rites manual.
This is a real ghost-killing ritual.
What kind of grudge was this?
It means
they wanted to trap her soul
so she couldn't even become a ghost.
Look.
A red dress for soul-weighting,
scale weights to bind the soul,
suspended three inches above ground
to make sure
the soul can't return to the earth.
And the soul-trapping cage on her head
was made from corpse oil.
The cage has been opened.
That means
someone already
used a gourd or some container
to take away her soul.
As for why
it's hung on the door handle.
That's because
it's hard to extract
every bit of a soul.
You have to stimulate it with yin wood.
That's the only way
to make the ritual work.
Nonsense.
Utter superstition.
Yeah.
Detective Yang's got skills.
Solving a case
without even thinking like the killer.
Fine.
Since you don't believe me,
we'll investigate separately.
See you around.
Detective Yang,
I won't get in your way,
so don't get in mine.
Let go.
I need to find Yu Shuang's body.
Yu Shuang's body is missing,
rumors about his ghost bride,
and He Shanshan was killed.
All these cases
are connected to you.
You're the prime suspect.
If you want to clear your name,
then help me
get to the bottom of all these cases.
Yang Ziqi,
this is your idea of cooperation?
There was a better way,
but you didn't choose it.
Screw you!
Get back here!
Detective Yang.
Please come back.
It's cold.
Give me a blanket.
Nope.
Fine.
Then you'll know exactly how I'll answer
your questions later.
What's that smell?
Detective Yang?
He Shanshan's body
has been taken to the station.
What do we do now?
Send her to the morgue.
Right, Detective Yang.
We've already called Li the coroner.
He used to be
our local forensic examiner in town.
We're a small town,
not like the big cities out there.
Just say it.
I'm saying, we should go ahead
and autopsy her.
If we find nothing,
- I'll take full responsibility.
- the family...
Do the autopsy.
Yes, sir.
Yang Ziqi!
Are you crazy again?
What are you doing?
You want to cut her open?
She should be buried whole,
with her body intact.
You want to dissect her
just to solve a case?
If the He family comes storming in,
don't come begging me
to stitch her back together!
Where's that Detective Yang?
Come out!
Come out now!
Get out here!
Come on.
Yang!
Uncle He, what are you doing?
Director Wu!
It was him!
He's the one who stopped me from seeing
my daughter at the newspaper office!
Yang! Just because you
were transferred from higher up
doesn't mean you
can throw your weight around.
Do you even know who I am?
Even Director Wu
shows me respect.
What gives you the right
to stop me from seeing my daughter?
Crime scenes must not be disturbed.
That's procedure.
If you barge in
and mess up the evidence,
how are we supposed to solve the case?
Your daughter
died horribly in the office.
I did this
to help bring her killer to justice.
If Director Wu
is polite to you, that's his choice.
But with me,
rules are rules.
You think I'm beneath you?
I've got people
in the provincial capital!
Who do you think you're yelling at?
Director Wu.
Look at him.
Liu.
Uncle He.
Come on.
About Miss He's death...
Let's talk inside.
It's just so strange.
You need to look into it, right?
Detective Yang,
the people dying in our town lately,
they all come from powerful families.
Not the kind we can offend.
You can't...
That has nothing to do with me.
And nothing to do
with the investigation.
Don't they want the truth?
You...
Forget it.
The way He Shanshan died was terrifying.
She was murdered.
Obviously.
I...
Dear heavens.
What do we do now?
If this keeps up, we might have to
call in some Taoist priests
and hold a ritual right
in the police station.
Director Wu.
I don't believe in that stuff.
I just mean
that the town's
getting ready
to elect the next mayor soon.
If we can let these cases slide,
then let them slide.
Less trouble is better than more.
If not,
and the higher-ups
hear about the bad press,
the one who gets screwed will be me.
Just in case.
Uncle He.
Director Wu.
Today,
I must see my daughter.
I'm her father.
All right.
I have the right to!
Come.
This way.
Mr He,
you've seen the body.
I promise I won't let your daughter
die without justice.
Can you promise
my daughter
won't just vanish like that wretched boy
from the Yu family?
You have my word.
The director can vouch for it.
Mr He,
let's talk outside.
Shall we?
Come on.
Let's go.
Come.
Detective.
Master drank too much yesterday.
He's still not up yet.
Shall we just lock the body up for now,
and start
the autopsy tomorrow first thing?
Do you know
where your daughter was heading?
(Clearance Pass)
She prepared all these documents.
She never said a word to me.
She was just fine.
Why would she leave?
So your daughter
and Young Master Yu,
how did they meet?
Back when I was
doing tea business with the Yu family,
the two kids got to know each other.
Later on,
they became a couple.
What about the child bride,
Meng Lin?
That's Yu family business.
I'm not too sure.
What I mean is,
was Meng Lin widely known?
The Yu family is a big name.
Everyone knew
about their child bride.
And your daughter,
did she and Yu Shuang
have any mutual friends or enemies?
That...
I really don't know.
You're her father
and you don't know?
Let's leave it there for now.
If there's any update,
I'll inform you immediately.
All right.
All these recent deaths in Dragon Town,
none of them were nobodies.
Liu.
Send more officers to that
fake Yu Residence tomorrow morning
and continue the investigation.
You got it.
Detective Yang,
I don't believe for a second
that there are no witnesses.
(Worker Record. Name: Wu Qingzhi)
Detective Yang.
Detective Yang!
Detective Yang,
we've got a lead!
I'm starving. I want food too.
At least you have a conscience.
Detective Yang,
the newspaper where He Shanshan worked,
its outer wall is under repair.
(Name: Wu Qingzhi)
This is the list
of construction crew workers.
At the breakfast stall,
I caught one of the foremen
and asked him.
This old Wu guy,
something's off about him.
Others charge
three silver dollars a job.
But him?
Just one.
Just to get into the crew.
And what's weirder,
the foreman told me
this old Wu carried
a straw doll
with He Shanshan's name on it.
I'm guessing
he might be cursing her.
Liu,
you've got potential as a proper cop.
Darn right.
Wouldn't have guessed.
Sui'an Village.
Where is it?
I've never heard of it.
Beg me if you want.
I know where it is.
How do I know
you're not lying?
Believe it or not.
I've done plenty of funerals
in remote backwater villages.
This place?
I just happen to know it.
Come with me to find the lead.
Once we find it,
I'll let you go.
Nice try.
That's how you ask for help?
You're something else.
I'm warning you.
You're chained to me now.
Good luck with that.
No funny business.
I hope your brain
works as well
as your mouth.
Let's go.
Detective Yang.
Oh, my god.
Steel spine, huh?
Aren't we there yet?
Up ahead.
What happened
to this place?
Excuse me, sir.
Do you know
someone named Old Wu?
Is he from your village?
Old Wu?
You mean Wu Qingzhi?
Yeah.
He's from our village.
But he's been dead for over a year.
That's impossible.
People in town said they saw him.
Are you sure
the Old Wu you saw
was even human?
♪Misty moonlight in Xiangxi's night♪
♪Fog veils the entire Dragon Town♪
♪Corpse herders drift like fleeting shade♪
♪Hurrying down the nether road♪