What's the rush?
It's not gonna end that quickly.
So surprised to see me?
You scared me to death.
How are you holding up?
I'm fine.
Not dead yet.
What happened to your hand?
I accidentally blew my cover.
The Master found out I was helping you.
What are you doing?
The Master suspects you betrayed Wujie.
He ordered me to take your life.
If you return and accept punishment,
I'll plead your case.
You always show up covered in wounds.
Out with it.
What do you need my help with this time?
Don't worry.
What about Youying?
Still no match for me.
I'll stay hidden in the shadows for now.
Take care of yourself.
This is for you.
I'm leaving.
What was that...
Why does she always leave through the back door?
Idiot.
How could you be so reckless?
Dad.
Do you think he'll go and report me?
Well...
That Ye Qingxue was there too.
What if she speaks up? What do we do?
Hurry, think.
Come up with something.
This Ye Qingxue isn't someone we can handle.
In-law.
Let me tell you.
That kid Yang Yunfan,
has been with Ye Qingxue every day lately.
He's hard to deal with.
We need to get the Zhenhai Calming Manual.
Don't you think we could just
get rid of them outright?
I secured the Zhenhai Calming Manual.
I caught that kid today.
You don't need to worry about it anymore.
That's great news.
So my son-in-law's illness
can be kept under control for now.
But I'm worried
that kid Yang Yunfan
will still get in the way of our bigger plans.
So,
why not take this chance
to get rid of him?
Just be smart about it.
Alright.
Don't worry, in-law.
Then it's settled.
Good.
Pen and paper.
Mingcheng.
Go find the person on this paper to get the medicine.
Listen to me carefully.
Tomorrow, before the assessment,
swap out all of Yang Yunfan's herbs
with this batch.
Understood?
Understood.
Everyone.
Today is the Second Trial of the Five Elements,
the Earth Element Examination.
The five elements unite as one,
all things return to their source.
The theme is strengthening the foundation.
This is the focus of the assessment.
Our professional judges
will evaluate all of you.
This not only tests your skills,
but more importantly,
it tests your hearts as physicians.
I really didn't expect
to be grouped with you.
Could it be that the heavens
want your departure
to be even more tragic?
Sorry, Li Xiangyang.
Your description is so vivid and cute.
Did you secretly practice that at home?
Don't worry,
when you're coughing up blood later,
don't use your kiddie watch to call Daddy.
You...
It seems the atmosphere
of this assessment is quite tense.
Now, please, everyone,
take your positions.
This is the only match left
for you to act all cocky.
Good luck.
Just you wait.
Please.
I now declare
the competition open.
Distribute the herbs to everyone.
Come here.
Give it to me.
Get lost!
"The medicine has been tampered with."
These herbs...
They really were targeting me.
There's something wrong with my herbs.
I request to halt the trial immediately.
And replace the herbs.
I've inspected all these herbs myself.
There's nothing wrong with them.
Aren't you just a little too nervous?
Yang Yunfan.
Are you afraid you're going to lose?
So you're making excuses ahead of time?
Young Master Yang.
You claim there's an issue with these herbs.
Do you have any proof?
Pharmacy Master Lu.
Drinking this is no laughing matter.
If you have no evidence,
don't go throwing accusations around.
I'm not going to halt the trial
based on your baseless guesses.
I believe him.
I request a re-inspection of the herbs.
Even if it's just a formality.
Young Lady Ye.
Out of respect for your contributions
that I let you enter the inner arena.
If you keep making a scene,
questioning Mystic Water Hall's herbs,
then I'm sorry,
but I'll have to clear the arena.
Besides, the growing and storage of herbs
is Green Wood Hall's responsibility.
And as for you,
if you have no proof,
then get back there and compete properly.
Otherwise, I'll disqualify you.
So, the contest...
Are you in or not?
I'm in.
Good. The contest will continue.
Well-balanced blend,
and precise heat control.
Just as expected from Li Chiyao.
You're getting more masterful by the day.
It seems
this trial should be no problem for you.
What's wrong, Yang Yunfan?
Still not finished?
Are you brewing medicine,
or just pulling an all-nighter?
If you can't do it, just go home,
you little schoolboy.
Excellent technique.
Pharmacy Master Lu.
Drink up.
Cold medicine loses its potency.
It's fine, just a bit hot.
I'll finish Li Chiyao's first.
Deputy Chief Pharmacist Cheng, you first.
What's wrong with Deputy Chief Pharmacist Cheng?
This...
Yang Yunfan!
What did you do to the medicine?
How dare you poison a judge mid-exam!
You can't blame me for this.
I said before the contest started,
the herbs had serious problems.
But you insisted I proceed anyway.
Now that someone's hurt,
shouldn't you, Lu Daozai, take the blame?
How dare you!
You clearly knew the herbs were tainted,
yet still gave them to a judge.
That's even more unforgivable.
My herbs have a problem,
so why are you so excited?
Do you really have something to hide?
You...
Don't be in such a rush.
Let me show you all another little trick.
Spirits of heaven, spirits of earth
Rise!
What the heck?
You're fine?
Was something supposed to happen?
Deputy Chief Pharmacist Cheng, after you.
Deputy Chief Pharmacist Cheng.
Yang Yunfan.
You...
My assistant,
Gu Ruoqiu,
saw Lu Mingcheng
swap out Yang Yunfan's batch of herbs.
Yes, I saw it with my own eyes.
Come here.
Hand it over.
Get lost!
I didn't do it!
I...
Guards!
I'm the Young Master of the Lu Family.
I'm to inherit Mystic Water Hall someday.
How dare you lay a hand on me?
Get out of my way!
Lu Mingcheng,
Are you still holding a grudge
because you lost to Yang Yunfan?
That's what I was thinking.
He obviously has a nasty temper.
Everyone,
the way I see this matter,
someone is secretly lining their pockets,
using inferior goods,
to corrupt this exam's integrity,
and to frame my son.
But rest assured, everyone,
Mystic Water Hall will fully investigate
and give everyone a satisfactory answer, all right?
You sure know how to dodge responsibility.
Trying to clear your son with a few words?
Since we have a witness,
the investigation begins with him.
Dad, save me!
Save me!
Lu Mingcheng attempted to sabotage the Pharmacist Trial.
The evidence is conclusive.
Take him away at once.
No!
What do you think you're doing?
Let go of me!
Lu Mingcheng's case
will be fully investigated
by the Mystic Medicine Association Committee.
No need to trouble you, Young Lady Ye.
Everyone saw that, didn't they?
Lu Daozai won't let us take Lu Mingcheng.
Could it be that the swapped herbs
were prepared by Pharmacy Master Lu?
You're just a spoiled heir.
Where would you get so many tainted herbs?
You're slandering me!
You're clearly framing the Lu Family,
trying to wipe out the entire Lu Family!
Pharmacy Master Lu, it's just a suspicion.
No evidence points to Pharmacy Master Lu.
Miss Ye, no need to overreact.
The Mystic Medicine Association isn't yours alone.
Best leave it to the committee to decide.
Fine.
I'd like to see
what kind of answer you'll come up with.
Take him away.
I can walk on my own.
Move aside.
Don't worry.
It'll be fine.
Since everything has been cleared up,
congrats to Yang Yunfan on advancing.