Who is it?
Miss Ye told me to bring you some clothes.
At least she has some conscience.
Why is it you again?
Hand over the Sea Suppressor Manual.
And I'll spare your life.
What Suppressor? What Manual?
I really have no idea.
Stop pretending.
Do you know how many people out there
are hunting for Number Zero, the thief of
the Sea Suppressor Manual?
I'm just a lowly country doctor.
Where would I get that kind of skill
to steal any secret manual?
A lowly country doctor?
The Mother-Child Yin-Yang Gu
is a forbidden Gu in ancient Gu arts.
I've never seen anyone suppress its venom.
But you,
three times in a row,
helped me suppress the Gu venom attacks.
You're quite impressive.
I guess I'm okay.
Is this how you treat your lifesaver?
How rude.
Just hand over the Sea Suppressor Manual,
and since you saved my life a few times,
I'll help hide your identity
and spare your life.
How about this:
I can completely cure the Gu venom in you.
You quit this job of yours,
and then you won't have to kill me.
Please, I'm begging you.
Director Ye, what brings you here so late?
I heard
some noise in your room.
I was just training a bit too intensely.
Director Ye, I have good news.
I've mastered the Sea Suppressor Manual.
That fast?
Of course.
Do you know who I am?
Director Ye, you should rest early.
I'll keep refining my skills.
Goodbye, Director Ye.
Goodnight, Director Ye.
You've mastered the Sea Suppressor Manual.
This is for you.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
The Gu venom has reached your dantian.
If you keep stalling,
no matter how great my medical skills,
your body simply won't hold up.
Why throw your life away
for such a vicious master?
None of your business.
So...
Are you sure you were just talking to yourself?
I'm just being dedicated to my work.
Practicing my lines.
And getting some exercise too.
You should get going. Head back now.
Anything else?
Take care, I won't see you out.
What a day.
Found Zero and the Sea Suppressor Manual?
Why throw your life away
for such a vicious master?
I have failed you.
We found nothing.
Useless.
Ye Qingxue is also looking for Zero.
She collected Zero's fingerprints.
But the records show no such person.
I'll spare you one more time.
No Zero or Sea Suppressor Manual again,
you know the consequences better than me.
What are you doing?
This is your fiancé?
What a headache.
Do whatever you want with him.
Saggy skin.
Enlarged pores.
Excess oil.
And this scrawny figure, no good either.
Ye Qingxue, save me!
You said you'd be the Dragon King's groom.
I was just saying it offhand.
How could you take it seriously?
Well, I did.
Director Ye!
Don't leave!
Director Ye, where are you going?
Come on.
Pull him up.
What are you doing?
Stop taking pictures!
Give us a smile.
Smile a little.
Expressions.
Change your pose.
Am I going to a pharmacist exam,
or a beauty pageant?
Help!
Welcome to Cheng Qi's
private wardrobe.
This overall look isn't bad.
What are you doing? I'm warning you!
I'd rather die than take off my underwear!
This is my ride-or-die buddy.
My absolute bottom line.
Seriously?
Honestly, if it weren't for Director Ye,
I wouldn't bother with you at all.
Today I'll show you what a true collection is.
This is from the famous designer
Maosang Pierre's runway piece this year.
Come on.
Four sleeves? How am I supposed to wear this?
Director Ye, why not lend me two arms?
We'll try it together.
If you don't put it on right now,
I'll make sure you have no arms left.
Are you sure dressed like this,
I won't be caged as a jellyfish?
Country bumpkin.
How about this one?
Get out here!
I'm still pretty conservative, you know.
Director Ye, don't hold such a grudge.
This outfit actually shows off a nice physique.
Of course it does.
Let me show you
what real fashion looks like.
How do designer brands
end up looking like a QQ avatar on you?
What do you know?
This is chic night-walker style.
Walking down the street in this outfit,
you wouldn't even need streetlights.
You're hopeless.
Just wait.
There's an even bigger surprise.
My entrance will steal the entire show.
I'm about to blind you with my brilliance.
Your decade-old West Coast taste
really needs an emergency rescue.
Should I book you an eye doctor?
Still better than those rags you picked!
Get lost!
How is it?
Were you electrified by my charm?
Passable, I guess.
Wipe it carefully.
Well, did you wipe it?
Yes, I did.
Everyone, please gather in the main hall.
This is the pharmacist consultant I hired.
Who is this guy?
I've never seen him before.
Didn't he cause a scene at the pharmacy?
I have to say, he's pretty handsome.
Being handsome doesn't mean anything.
He probably knows Director Ye.
Could he be Director Ye's boyfriend?
No way.
He really is quite handsome.
But why does he look so familiar?
He probably just knows Director Ye.
Consultant?
Thinks a new shell makes a turtle a god?
Isn't he just the apothecary boy I fired?