Yang Yunfan
You've passed the Mystic Water Hall trial.
Take an oath before the Medicine Venerable,
and receive the seal,
to become an official Apothecary.
I shall follow the Medicine Venerable's words.
A carefree wanderer walks the healing path,
doing good deeds without seeking fame.
Yang Yunfan.
Yang Yunfan!
Do you vow to uphold this path?
This disciple, Yang Yunfan,
so vows.
Wrong.
It's Apothecary Yang Yunfan.
Apothecary Yang Yunfan
vows to uphold a healer's benevolence,
to save lives and aid the world,
never use my arts to harm,
never betray the healing path,
nor the Medicine Venerable.
The Medicine Venerable bestows the seal.
Walk the path of healing.
This is the Living Seal.
I've never seen one before.
What's that in his hand?
The Living Seal.
It's the Living Seal.
He's truly no ordinary person.
The ceremony is complete.
Everyone is dismissed.
Is the Living Seal a big deal?
Only those recognized by the Medicine Venerable
can manifest the Living Seal.
I told you long ago.
I'm definitely a peerless prodigy.
I like your confidence.
But the Mystic Medicine Association is full of confident people.
The trial is finally over.
Now I can relax a bit.
Boss Ye, don't forget to treat me to a feast.
As a little reward, you know?
The Medicine King Festival's Medicine Holder trial is soon.
Only by becoming a Medicine Holder
will you have a voice in the Mystic Medicine Association.
Only then can you actually help me.
You're kidding.
Another trial?
Why is it never-ending?
Since you're already here,
just see it through to the end.
What are you two doing?
Boss Ye.
You don't even consult me anymore.
One wrong move ruins the whole game.
If we hadn't failed the earlier trial,
how could the great Lu family
be bested by some wild kid?
It's all your fault, you fickle woman!
If you hadn't brought such a shady guy
into Heaven Number One,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Now look what's happened.
Even Brother-in-law is displeased with you.
He probably won't help us anymore.
In-law, what brings you here in person?
Have a seat.
We could have just gone over to you.
He's awake.
Or should I take him to the Mystic Water Hall?
Why is Miss Lu getting personally involved?
Does the new advisor know her?
Maybe. I just saw them whispering.
Hurry up.
Pour some water.
In-law.
Go.
Number Zero's identity is still unclear.
And now a Yang family orphan shows up?
My dear in-law.
This all happened so suddenly.
We didn't see it coming either.
It's all that damned Ye Qingxue's fault.
If it weren't for her,
we'd have taken that boy down already.
So have you confirmed his real identity?
We're looking into it.
Ye Qingxue has always been restless.
Trying to control the Mystic Medicine Association.
That country bumpkin's identity
was almost certainly forged by her.
Brother-in-law is right.
But this man can use the Sea-Calming Mantra.
Whether or not he's Yang Yunfan,
we must be on our guard.
Alright, I'll leave it to you.
Don't worry.
You know how many people are eyeing
the Mystic Water Hall's position.
Yes.
Since I helped you up there,
I can also pull you down.
Rest assured, In-law.
Rest assured.
This time, I definitely won't spare that brat.
Slow down.
After searching for so many days,
you missed Number Zero right under our noses.
Why do I even keep you?
This subordinate is incompetent.
I was one step behind you, Venerable.
However,
the Sea-Calming Mantra
has been taken back from Ye Qingxue.
Good.
Ye Qingxue.
That little girl really has
been doing a lot behind our backs.
I'll spare your life this time.
The Medicine King Festival is about to begin.
Ghost Blade, you and Shadow
take this opportunity
to get rid of that Wuming,
lest he stirs up more trouble.
Understood.
All right.
Give me a moment.
Young Master Yang.
Your bedroom isn't in this direction.
I know. Just out for a stroll.
A stroll.
This fountain...
Sure is a big fountain.
Young Master, I'll be off then.
Okay.
All right, I'll be right there.
Tell me the exact location.
Okay.
This is...
Let's see...
Why is it all investigation files and medical books?
"Notes on Sui Qi"
Sui Qi is corrupted energy.
It corrodes, devours, and destroys.
It has shadow but no form.
Ordinary people can hardly perceive it.
Master, I'll avenge you.
Could my amnesia
be linked to Sui Qi?
The Mystic Medicine Association
has a traitor.
It's him.
The grandfather Qingxue spoke of,
Fuguang, the Medicine Sovereign
Who exactly is the traitor he mentioned?
I never expected
that he'd actually return.
I was also surprised when I saw him.
It's time we set our plan in motion.
Is everything ready for the Medicine King Festival?
This is our
last chance.
Don't worry.
This time, we'll catch them all in one swoop.
You're in luck today.
You're the only one getting this treatment.
I knew Song Ci was up to something.
Could Ye Zhentian be the traitor?
Don't make a sound.
You again?
Got hurt again?
Your pulse is steady.
You seem to be perfectly fine.
I just came to warn you.
Be careful at the Medicine King Festival.
Someone will come for your life.
Worried about me?
People who want me dead?
There are far too many of those.
You're the only one who poses a threat.
I'm not joking with you.
The Master issued a kill order on you.
Knowing him as I do,
he definitely has other backup plans.
Who is the Master?
The leader of Boundless.
Actually, I don't know his true identity.
I only know he's tied to the Mystic Medicine Association.
How do you know that?
Because all our missions involve the Mystic Medicine Association.
Is everything ready for the Medicine King Festival?
This is our
last chance.
Don't worry.
This time, we'll catch them all in one swoop.
This Association is more cutthroat than a palace drama.
Anyway, I've said what I had to say.
Just be careful.
Hold on.
What?
Decided to switch sides and join me?
In your dreams.
Then please pay for the Gu poison treatment.
Or,
you could do something for me.
Just this once.
Put it on my tab for now.
I locked the back door...
How did she still get out?
No, I need to go back and look.