=Contenders=
=Episode 25=
There are many guards.
Nanping
must be here.
Boss, how about this?
One of us
will draw their attention up front.
The others will split into two groups
and flank them.
- Boss!
- Dad! Dad!
Zhongxin, come with me.
Who?
Who is there?
There's an old man.
Cheng Hui.
Today, I'll kill you.
Then I'll make a name in Lion City.
Guys, get him!
Boss, it's Cheng Hui!
Cheng Sandao!
Well, Cheng Sandao,
[*Sandao: three strikes]
three strikes for a life.
Get my gun!
Get off me!
Help!
- Help!
- Quiet!
Boss!
Old thing!
You broke the rules.
You're using a gun!
An Gexiong.
You fired first.
You shameless rascal!
You broke the rules first!
Let my niece go!
Shoot them!
Keep an eye on Cheng Hui!
Guys, go!
Hold them off!
I'll get Cheng Hui's daughter.
They'll show up and die one by one!
Nanping.
Do you want to die?
Mr. Zheng is up to no good.
He wants us all dead.
No way!
Come with me!
We can't find Nanping.
Boss, deep in the woods,
there's a small cabin.
Stop! Stay back!
Or I'll kill her!
An Gexiong.
We've taken down
all your men.
Let Nanping go,
and maybe Master Cheng
will spare your life.
Trying to bluff me?
Zhao has to die.
Otherwise, Shanhai Gang
will only get stronger.
Zhao Tiehan,
you were kicked out.
Why did you return?
A good horse never turns back.
Aren't you ashamed?
Born a Shanhai Man,
die a Shanhai Soul.
For Master Cheng
and Shanhai Gang,
I can do anything,
including sacrificing my life!
Cheng Hui,
I really envy you.
You have many talents,
smart brains
and good fighters.
No wonder you dominate Lion City.
I admire you!
Zhao!
Give me your gun.
Mine is out of ammo.
Show me your sincerity,
and I might consider
what you said.
Okay.
Zhao.
Boss, don't worry.
An Gexiong
is also a famous
gang leader.
I think
he'll keep his word.
An Gexiong.
- Zhao!
- Uncle Zhao!
Oh no.
- Stop! Don't come closer!
- Uncle Zhao!
It's still too far.
Missed the shot.
An Gexiong!
Zhongxin.
I know you're tough.
But you're so dumb.
I've never seen you as a threat.
Heihu is important, though.
Come over and be my hostage,
and I'll let her go.
Okay.
Heihu, let me do it.
You old cripple.
You mean nothing to me.
Heihu,
are you too scared to come?
Uncle Heihu!
Don't worry about me! Shoot him!
Quiet!
Well, isn't Weiyuan Hall
supposed to be invincible in Lion City?
Turns out it's a lie.
Heihu.
Boss.
Don't move.
Bin Langxiong.
You took my daughter.
Come at me if you dare.
Stop!
No way.
Cheng Sandao, I'm impressed.
You're still so strong.
I just saw it.
I'm so scared.
Heihu,
don't go further.
He's scared of your gun.
Toss him the gun.
An Gexiong.
Heihu
can drop the gun.
And I promise,
if you let Nanping go,
we won't go after you.
We'll pretend
nothing's happened.
Zhao is smart.
Heihu, why don't you give it a try?
Enough, Cheng Hui.
Put down your knife.
Come here and take your daughter.
Dad, let me do it!
Go away!
Who do you think you are?
If you come over,
I'll shoot her immediately!
Don't move.
Dad.
Dad, stay back!
Dad!
You're a reporter.
Let me show you
what I've got.
Cheng Hui.
All gangsters
have to listen to you.
As long as you're alive,
no one can rise.
Dad!
Stay back, Dad!
Stop!
Dad!
Nice shot.
Your turn, Mr. Cheng.
Boss.
Just follow Mr. Charles's
direction.
That's the best spot.
Yes.
You're not professional, I see.
He said you can't play.
Sorry, it's my first time.
Hasn't he had any lessons?
He said I didn't teach you.
He did.
I just didn't have time to learn.
Remember,
we had an agreement.
The more shots you take,
the more money I get.
Is that your intention?
You Shanhai Gang
are really a little bit clumsy
making friends.
Making friends
is all about honesty,
not pretending.
Don't worry, this is my first time,
but I'll try my best.
Well.
That's three shots.
Looks like I'll be counting the money.
He said this is your third shot.
If you miss it again,
you'll lose a lot of money.
Where's the green?
Can you see the woods?
The green is right behind them.
It's over there.
Why am I aiming
at his ball?
That's way too far.
You can't get it in with one shot.
It's the third shot already.
I want to give it a try.
Ball.
Listen, don't swing too hard.
The smoother, the farther.
Behind this tree, right?
Well done!
You're near the green.
Boss,
you're a genius.
Nonsense.
I twisted my back.
Well, let's go.
Let's head to your position.
Double, do you accept?
What does that mean?
He wants to double the bet.
Are you in or not?
I'm in.
I don't think you should.
Charles is steady at this.
He'll finish in two shots.
Even if you get a hole-in-one,
it's still a tie.
It's not a good deal.
I accept it.
Boss.
That is par.
You need this goal, otherwise
you'll be counting the money for me.
Or you'll lose.
Boss, relax.
Look,
it's all downhill.
No effort is needed.
Just push it straight in.
Unbelievable.
Mr. Cheng,
you're incredible.
You know,
a lot of people
talked bad about you.
It seems
maybe I should believe them.
What did they say?
They said you were
dangerous.
Indeed.
You just
showed that.
Can you make it clear?
Your first shot was off.
But then
you went straight for the green.
That's what gangsters do.
They hate losing.
That's why you
keep fighting all the time.
No surrender,
no giving in,
that's our people's trait.
Actually, we don't like fighting.
We prefer peace and harmony.
The reason why
I took the risk
was that I didn't want to lose.
It's hard to make money now.
I have a family to support.
Don't want to lose.
That barely makes sense.
When I said double,
you agreed, which means
you wanted more.
That's exactly
what a gangster is like.
But Shanhai Gang never takes
other people's property.
Mr. Zhao already told me
you're great at golf.
As long as it's on the green,
you only need two shots.
Think about it.
I got a hole-in-one,
and it was a tie.
If I missed it,
I'd lose more money.
I never get to win your money.
So, why did you agree?
I had to respect the host.
This is my first time.
You agreed to play with me.
It was a waste of your time,
so I wanted to make you happy.
That's also one of our traits.
That makes you
even more of a gentleman.
We don't call it "gentleman"
but "righteousness".
Unfortunately,
I'm not righteous.
To be honest,
I killed someone yesterday.
Are you reminding me
I'm playing with a criminal?
My daughter was kidnapped.
I had to save her.
So, does that make me a criminal?
That's complicated.
But why was
your daughter kidnapped?
That's also complicated.
I've always wanted
to change the situation.
Trust me.
Haven't sat in this car for ages.
Jie.
How's the car business at the pier?
Pretty good.
The car is always booked.
Who booked the car?
Mostly merchants from abroad.
Sometimes for weddings
or birthday banquets.
You must've got a lot of tips.
Yes, quite a lot.
But I still prefer driving for you.
I'm afraid it's not going to happen.
We played golf today.
I've tried
to persuade him
so many times that he finally
agreed to use the car.
It's our company's car.
I'm fine with walking.
When I'm in a good mood,
I can even pull a rickshaw
or ride a tricycle.
Jie,
just focus on the business
and make more money for us.
Take care of the clients,
and we'll get more business.
Don't worry.
If you work hard,
I'll give you a reward.
Got it.
Thank you, Boss.
Pull over there.
I'll leave you here.
(Tanjong Pagar)
Get out!
- Aunt!
- Out!
Go!
You're not my nephew!
Go back to where you're from!
Stop embarrassing me in Lion City!
Aunt, I'm so sorry.
Please don't send me back!
You won't go, huh?
Fine.
In less than
three days,
someone will break your legs.
Who's this?
Who's threatening to break his legs?
Master Cheng.
I'm sorry!
Please have mercy!
Who said I'd kill you?
- Get up.
- I wouldn't dare.
Please don't order them
to break my legs!
What's going on? I'm confused.
He talked too much.
Otherwise, how could...
It's all in the past.
Come on, get up.
Get up.
How's your business?
Good.
Ever since I modified your rickshaw,
I've been busy.
Many people want to modify theirs.
See? That's a good thing.
Hurry, get back to work.
♪I have my pride♪
♪I have my principles♪
♪Even if it's hard,♪
♪I'd keep doing
this anyway♪
♪I'll do it
my own way♪
♪I believe
what I believe♪
♪Justice♪
♪Righteousness♪
♪Morality♪
♪Keep on going♪
♪I have my dream♪
♪I would never give in♪
♪Even if it's hard,♪
♪I'd keep doing
this anyway♪
♪I'll do it
my own way♪
♪I believe
what I believe♪
♪Justice♪
♪Righteousness♪
♪Morality♪
♪Keep on going♪