THE HUSBAND
THIS SERIES IS FICTITIOUS
CHILDREN WERE FILMED SAFELY
GEN AI WAS USED IN SELECT SCENES
EPISODE 3
This way! Move!
Hayun.
Oh, my God, Hayun.
Wait, Doctor.
Can you wait until Dr. Kang gets here?
We don't have time.
Bone fragments
from her broken cervical vertebrae
are compressing her respiratory center.
If we don't operate right now,
she's going into respiratory arrest.
We'll try our best.
Ms. Ko. I have to ask you
to wait out here.
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
CALLING
HUSBAND
Come on, honey, pick up.
Please. Hayun is…
Why won't he pick up?
Where on earth is he?
Blade.
Bovie, please.
Vitals are dropping.
Give me an amp of epi.
Oh, please…
She's flatlining!
The patient is flatlining.
Keep compressions going.
Get the crash cart in here!
Ms. Ko, we're sorry.
We did our best, but…
Dr. Kang.
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Where have you been?
I said, where have you been?
Answer me!
Where the hell have you been?
While…
Where were you while our Hayun was dying?
This is all your fault.
It's all your fault.
This whole thing is your fault.
This is all your fault!
THE HUSBAND
SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
How do you know the kidnapper?
I don't know him.
He showed up when I called for a driver.
So you solicited
a complete stranger to murder your wife?
I never solicited anything.
Mr. Kang, where's your accomplice?
I really don't know.
I didn't put him up to it.
Tell us. You know where she is!
I said I don't know!
Your accomplice…
He's way more dangerous than you think.
You're going to end up
taking the fall alone.
Just how many times do I have to tell you?
You're losing time here!
Do you have any idea
what a waste of time this is?
This guy is a psycho!
My wife is in danger!
Calm down, Mr. Kang.
I'm serious!
There's no time to be screwing around!
Mr. Kang!
Calm now?
Wash your face off.
And freshen up a little.
That one doesn't work.
Use the next one.
What the hell?
Man, it's about time
they fix this place up.
Nothing works in here.
Hey, Captain Kim.
Yeah. It's been too long.
Oh, that? Yeah, it was really helpful.
Take your time, okay?
Right, I was going to come and see you.
Come on, not this again.
What the hell, man?
SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
SAFE SEONGJIN, TRUSTED POLICE
I didn't do it,
but everyone thinks I did.
No one believes me.
Who would?
No one believes you.
Why would anyone believe you, Mr. Kang?
Who are you?
I said, who are you?
I'm the only one who knows
you didn't plot your wife's death.
What?
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang!
- Mr. Kang!
- Oh, yes. I'm right here.
Why didn't you answer any…
You going to be a while?
Little bit, yeah.
Power's out, but don't panic.
And make it quick.
Okay, I got it. Sorry.
So who are you?
How do you know
I didn't have my wife kidnapped?
What's important isn't how I know,
but whether your wife is alive
or not right now.
What?
I doubt there's anyone you can trust
besides me right now.
Who the hell are you?
I told you.
I'm the only one who knows
you didn't have your wife kidnapped.
Or rather, I'm the only one
who can help you.
So…
Seyun is alive, right?
Where is she right now?
If you want to find your wife,
come to 543-7, Shinyu-dong by 11 p.m.
What was that?
If you don't,
you may never get to see her again.
Look, man.
I'm being held here as a suspect.
How am I supposed to get there by 11 p.m.?
Remember.
It's 543-7, Shinyu-dong.
Get there by 11 p.m.
For God's sake.
Hayun, Mommy's right here.
Yeah, Hayun, Mommy's right…
There's no time.
I'm running out of time.
When the girl in the red hood
gets swallowed by the snow…
It's over.
- Come on, Mom. Hurry!
- Oh, geez.
This way. Over there.
He's on the second floor. Come on.
ALWAYS WITH THE PEOPLE
SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
Mom.
Excuse me, we got a call
saying my son was being held here.
- What's your son's name?
- Taeju. Kang Taeju.
Mr. Kang is in interrogation
at the moment.
- What?
But my brother didn't do anything wrong.
How's my brother the suspect
when his wife's been kidnapped?
Look, sir.
My son would never commit a crime.
This has to be a mistake.
It's not a mistake.
Mr. Ko.
I said, it's not a mistake.
I'm a parent too.
I know you must be heartbroken.
But you know what my Taeju is like
just as well as I do.
Yeah, absolutely.
I know what kind of scum he is.
The despicable kind that plotted
to have my daughter killed.
Excuse me?
I know this is hard, but that's just…
I'd never say that to you, Mr. Ko.
Don't even say my name, okay?
It's my own damn fault for letting him
into my family in the first place!
How are you so sure
that Taeju really did it?
I saw with my own two eyes in that video,
how he asked the guy
to get rid of my daughter!
There's no way he did that.
What, you think I'm lying to you
when my daughter's life is on the line?
He's telling the truth.
I saw the video with him.
That's pretty.
Did you sleep well?
I came by earlier,
but you were sleeping so soundly.
How's your neck? Let me take a look.
This is going to take a while to heal.
Here. Try putting this on it.
LIQUID PAIN RELIEVER
Come on, take it.
You'll die when the time comes,
so you might as well
spare yourself the pain now.
Oh, well.
This is how much time you have left.
When the sand runs out, you're dead.
You all right?
Geez, okay.
Right. Apparently, the nuns use this
when they pray at the convent.
You should try praying
if you ever get bored.
Who knows?
You might impress God enough
to get you out of here.
Why are you doing this to me?
Use this, okay?
What did I do to deserve this?
What the hell do you want from me?
That driver you'd never seen
before has probably gotten away by now.
Until when do you plan on playing dumb?
If you want to find your wife,
come to 543-7, Shinyu-dong by 11 p.m.
Mr. Kang!
We need you to focus here!
We found this in the trunk of your car.
INSIDE THE TRUNK
OF THE SUSPECT'S VEHICLE
Even the blood splatter matches.
Isn't that funny?
I mean, how could this
have made it into your car?
I said, did you bring my billion won?
I have no idea.
"No idea," huh?
You were there
when the photo was taken, weren't you?
Obviously, he left it in my trunk
without me knowing.
It's also obvious
that he sent you that email.
Is that so?
In that case,
where's the memory card for your dashcam?
That'd prove your innocence.
That's… It disappeared.
Yeah. He probably took that too.
Wow, such unfortunate timing, isn't it?
People from the hospital
saw you arguing at the banquet.
Don't tell me this is
a marriage problem gone too far.
SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
The moment we get the lab results back,
you're going to be detained.
So come on.
It's not too late to come clean.
It's in your best interest
to keep Ms. Ko alive.
Isn't that right?
Do it now.
What is going on today?
I'll go check it out.
Geez.
Remember.
If you want to find your wife,
come to 543-7, Shinyu-dong by 11 p.m.
If you don't,
you may never get to see her again.
What the… Kang Taeju.
Hey, answer me! Kang Taeju!
Can't they do anything about this?
Hey, you know
we've got lines to the annex, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Give them a call.
Come on, man.
Hey, go check out the annex building!
I'll go check it out.
Don't bother. I'll just call them.
- Come over here.
- I'll check it out.
- Kang Taeju!
- Hurry up…
Get him!
Hey, get that punk!
He's going up!
Get him now!
Get him! Move it!
Third floor! Get to the third floor!
Kang Taeju!
- You two take the right side.
- Yes, sir.
You guys take the roof.
The rest of you, with me.
Quick! Go up!
-  Did you see him?
- Negative.
What about the rooftop?
- Check out the main gate.
-  Yes, sir.
- Come on, let's hurry!
-  We'll check it out!
So, guys, we've worked with
a lot of different codes so far, right?
Yeah!
But see, you don't have to memorize
what every single code does
or what you can do with it.
The thing is,
even I don't have all of that memorized.
- But Mr. Noh!
-  Yes?
How can we use the codes
if we don't memorize them?
Good point.
When there's need, you can
look up the codes online to practice,
or just let me know anytime you want.
You all have my number, right?
Yeah!
All right, shall we check out
what we'll be learning today?
Okay, turn to page 20.
Are you feeling any better?
I don't know.
I'm telling you.
It's going to get a lot worse.
It only gets scarier
and more frightening over time.
No one could ever get used to this.
How did he get you?
I got jumped from behind
while I was leaving
a fortune teller's place.
I was sleeping at home,
and he was standing right there
when I opened my eyes.
But I have no idea
why he's doing this to me.
I think I have an idea
as to why this is happening to me.
Why's that?
See, I did a bad thing.
"A bad thing"?
There's a spirit we serve in our home,
and I turned my back on them.
Things got so rough,
and I couldn't see a way forward,
so I sought out
other shamans out of desperation.
So maybe, do you think
you might have wronged someone?
Maybe you hurt someone.
You know, being here really opened my eyes
to what a horrible thing I'd done.
She's not praying.
All right, guys. Everybody done reading?
MR. NOH'S COMPUTER CLASS
SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
I found him!
Play it back.
He jumped out of that window?
He's lost it. Isn't he a doctor?
Are you admiring the guy?
Get a move on.
Let's roll.
Come on!
Mom, here.
Detective.
What's going on? Where's Taeju?
- He bolted.
- What?
Wait a minute! What are you talking about?
He ran off during the interrogation.
- I…
- What…
- What is going on?
He ran away?
You said your son is
incapable of doing anything bad.
So why would he run
if he hasn't done anything wrong?
I'm sure he had his reasons.
Just give him some time.
Reasons?
There's no excuse
for running away from the police!
My goodness.
What a mother you are.
What a loving mother!
It's just incredible! Give me a break.
Oh, Mom. Are you okay?
Let's sit you down. There you go.
- Taeyeong.
- Yeah.
- What in the world is happening?
- Exactly.
- Why would he… Why…
- That idiot!
Why did he run away
in a situation like this?
Ugh, geez.
It's okay.
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
Hey, excuse me.
Oh, hey. It's just me.
Oh, hello. Dr. Kang.
What are you doing here so late?
I forgot something in my office.
- Have a good one.
- You too.
OPERATING ROOM
ACCESS GRANTED
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Geez, you scared me.
- Hey, Chiung.
- What are you doing here so late?
You know,
I just left something in the office.
Must be pretty damn important.
What about you? What are you doing here?
I'm on call tonight.
Pharmacy wanted me
to check the anesthetics inventory.
I see.
- Hang in there, then. See you.
- Okay.
Chiung.
Hmm?
What? You got something to say?
Well, I…
I had a bit of an incident today.
Oh, what happened?
Well, it's kind of serious.
Yeah.
Now that you mention it,
you're a mess, man.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
I'll tell you later.
You know, actually…
Could you lend me your car?
My car? Where's yours?
Mine's… What's with all the questions?
You'll get it back tomorrow.
Yeah, whatever.
It's on level B3.
Is it something to do with your wife?
It is, right?
Something's going on, right? What is it?
It's okay. You can tell me.
The thing is…
Seyun got…
Sorry, let me take this real quick.
This is Choi.
Hey, Dr. Choi, it's me.
I'll cut right to the chase.
Have you heard from Taeju at all?
- Yeah, what a coincidence.
- What?
Are you with him right now?
Answer with "yes" or "no" only.
Yes.
Where are you right now? At the hospital?
Okay, he's at the hospital.
I'll make the call to the police then.
Listen to me carefully, Dr. Choi.
That bastard kidnapped my daughter!
What are you talking about?
He’s got her hidden somewhere.
He just bolted from the police station
while they were interrogating him!
To find Seyun,
we have to catch that bastard.
The police are on their way,
so you have to keep him there,
no matter what.
Do you hear me?
Yeah, I got it.
Chiung, I'm so sorry. I'll explain later!
Have you lost your mind?
- Hey, who's there?
- Go, stop him.
Dr. Choi?
Dr. Choi!
I said, go and stop Dr. Kang!
Okay!
- Hello.
- Dr. Kang.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry.
Just get out for a minute.
- Right, yeah.
- We'll talk outside the car.
- This seat belt just won't…
- Yeah, I'll do it for you.
There we go. Come on.
- No, listen, this is…
- It's just for a moment.
- Look, Chief. You got it all wrong.
- I'm sure I do.
I don't think so.
- I understand.
- Could you… I said, you can't go.
- I'll tell you later. I swear.
- Come on.
I got it.
I'll radio upstairs, so you can talk
after I hear from them. Stay right there.
Dr. Kang!
Stay away!
I'm so sorry!
Do your homework, Yuhyeon. Okay?
- Okay, fine!
- Bye.
- See you.
Oh, hey, what's up?
It's been blinking on and off
for the past few days,
and now it's completely stopped working.
I couldn't take any payments.
It's really been a nightmare.
What do you think?
You think you can fix it?
See. It's all the dust
that's built up in here.
That's why it wouldn't read.
- It should work now.
- Ah.
There it is.
My goodness! Now it works, huh?
How much do I owe you?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Oh, come on. I feel bad
you help me out all the time.
What's there to feel bad about?
Plus, who else would you get help from?
Well, thank you.
Why don't you stay for dinner then?
- Have a seat right here, okay?
- No, it's fine.
- Come on. Have a seat. Okay?
- You don't have to.
Thank you so much.
JANG SUNDAEGUK
Sweetheart, can you set his table?
Okay, Grandma.
Is that your granddaughter
you always talk about?
Yes, she is.
Your grandmother's told me all about you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
You know Woori Together Medical Center?
She works as a nurse there.
Oh.
Yeah, I've been there.
She helps me out
whenever she can, after her shift.
She's not like
the other young people these days.
I've raised a fine girl.
You really have. You must be proud of her.
Just sit tight,
and I'll get your food ready.
Thank you.
That's 22,000 won.
Do you need your receipt?
-  It's fine.
-  Moving on to our next story…
-  Bye.
- Thank you.
An armed robbery occurred
at a convenience store
in Jungang-dong, Seongjin-gu,
around 8:40 tonight.
Police took over 20 minutes to arrive
after receiving the report,
allowing the suspect to escape.
An unexplained power outage
at Seongjin Police Station
disrupted communications,
delaying the initial response.
I mean, he did seem a little off
when he came in,
but I didn't think much of it.
And then Dr. Choi told me
to stop him, so I did.
But then, Dr. Kang took my pepper gun
and sprayed me with it.
My eyes haven't stopped watering since.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But…
Listen. They're missing about six vials
of anesthetics in the operating room safe.
They're missing some scalpels
and surgical instruments
for cutting through bones.
Right.
When are you going to catch this bastard?
What if something happens to my daughter?
Just a moment. Excuse me.
Yes, talk.
Yeah, Captain. It looks like
after carjacking the vehicle,
Kang drove out of the parking garage
at 9:17 p.m.,
and took a turn
toward Angok-ro at 9:18 p.m.
He couldn't have gotten far then.
Put out an APB on the vehicle
and have dispatch track him using WASS.
Alert all nearby units for backup.
- I'm moving out now.
- Copy that.
It's go time. Let's roll.
If you can't save my daughter,
I will hold you accountable.
We'll do everything we can.
Move it!
- Head toward Angok-ro.
- Copy that.
You bastard.
You scumbag.
You all right?
He's such a bastard.
Right.
That's why he does these things.
No, not him.
I'm talking about my husband.
What?
The kidnapper called my husband
and told him I was kidnapped,
but he just said, "Do whatever
you want with her" and hung up.
He hasn't even picked up since.
But the kidnapper
may not have been telling the truth.
Maybe he made it all up.
I had a fight
with my husband before I left.
He said it to my face.
That he was glad we didn't have children.
That he wishes I would just die already.
Me dying here is
exactly what he'd wish for.
He'd be happy if I died.
Was that your husband who was crying
on the phone earlier?
Yes, it was.
You guys must have had
a good marriage going.
We're both stuck here,
but I got to say, I'm jealous.
What's your name?
Mine's Lee Seonja.
My name is Ko Seyun.
Hey, Seyun.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
When you get out of here,
can you let the police know
that Lee Seonja from Songmu-dong
died in this place?
I don't have much time left.
I'm going to die soon.
PUBLIC SERVICE CENTER
Hello?
Taeyeong, it's me.
You idiot.
Where are you?
What's going on?
Why did you run away?
I'll explain later.
How's Mom? Is she doing okay?
Of course she isn't.
She almost fainted because of you.
Why would you run from the police?
Hold on.
It wasn't you, was it?
Of course not.
It wasn't me, but…
She did get kidnapped because of me.
I have to save Seyun.
What are you talking about?
You should be getting help
from the police.
You can't do this on your own.
You think you're some kind of superhero?
Yeah.
I kind of wish I was.
Hey, listen.
Talk to Mom for me, okay?
Get back here and tell her yourself.
If you didn't do it,
it'll all be revealed in time, right?
Don't go making things worse, man.
Listen to your big brother, Taeju. Okay?
Taeju?
Taeju.
Taeju, where are you now?
You're not hurt, are you?
Hey, Mom. I'm fine.
But I can't go back there right now.
Seyun will be in more danger
if I stay at the station.
What are you talking about?
Why would you being at the station
put Seyun in danger?
Taeju.
Come back. It's not too late.
Mom, just…
Just trust me and give me some time.
I promise I'll bring Seyun home.
Taeju.
- Taeju…
- What is it, Mom?
What did he say?
RED LIGHT AND SPEEDING
SURVEILLANCE CAMERA
Captain, we got an update
on Kang's location.
- Where?
- He was at Deoksam Intersection
at 9:46 p.m.
Heading that way.
It's working.
- Just make it quick.
- Yeah. We'd like to, but…
Yujeong Intersection.
Plate number 682T 1228.
Visual on suspect vehicle.
Hey.
Yujeong Intersection?
Okay, on my way.
Let's take the long way
through Shinyu-dong.
Copy that.
- Send backup to Yujeong Intersection.
- Sir.
Suspect vehicle
is on Yujeong Intersection.
All nearby units, respond for backup.
Plate number 1228, please pull over.
Pull over, 1228.
I repeat, 1228.
I repeat. Pull over, 1228.
I repeat, 1228. Stop the vehicle.
Suspect vehicle is heading
toward Shinyu-dong.
Units two and three, in pursuit.
Kang Taeju!
Pull over right now!
Stop the car, you bastard!
This is dangerous!
Kang Taeju!
Stop being so reckless!
Pull over!
Kang Taeju!
Get in front of him.
Cut him off! Get in front of him!
Darn it.
Turn around! Step on it!
Control, we lost
the suspect vehicle during pursuit.
Plate number 1228.
Kang Taeju!
Stop the car! Stop!
You bastard!
Hey! Kang Taeju!
THE HUSBAND
Put out an APB on Kang Taeju.
A standoff erupted
between police and a neurosurgeon
suspected of orchestrating
his wife's kidnapping and murder.
What the hell? Where is my wife?
- Answer me!
- It's up to you to figure it out now.
Are you working with that bastard?
I know exactly what you're
thinking and doing, wherever you are.
Have you ever killed a person before?
For his wife…
Could Kang Taeju kill a person?
Are you out of your mind?
The three billion you have here.
I need you to hand it over to me.
Translated by Hyun Sik Yoon