Your Majesty.
I am fine.
Are you all right?
You little wretch!
You slack off and steal food!
Stop!
His Majesty is here. Do not be presumptuous.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Xie Yan
is the son of Xie Chen, the former Minister of War.
The Xie family.
The Xie family disappeared overnight back then.
It became a sensational case throughout the capital.
Although I was far away at the border,
I heard a little about it.
This was torn from his clothes.
They belong to this organization
and obey the command of the token.
In this life.
With these two clues,
Li Yunxi should be able to find out
who they are.
Does it look familiar?
It looks a lot like
the Xuanniao Totem.
However,
this is a fake.
It differs slightly from the real Xuanniao Totem
in the tail feathers.
Not only do you know about the Xuanniao Tribe,
but you can even see these details.
I have sharp eyes.
Su Kuang,
you told me that in our last life.
Where is Consort Xue?
Let her in.
Consort Xue,
why were you there?
I left the palace to visit my family,
but I got lost on my way back.
Your Majesty,
I found this token in Feixue Hall.
The assassins take orders from this token.
What do you have to say?
I...
Where did this token come from?
A mysterious man in a mask gave it to me.
With this command token,
can I really kill the one I want dead?
Of course.
How audacious!
You dare to publicly murder the Empress.
Your Majesty.
I was blinded by obsession for a moment
and committed a grave error.
Please spare me this time.
Consort Xue doesn't seem to be lying.
In that case,
someone else wants to kill my father and me.
This mysterious man is the mastermind behind everything.
Your Majesty,
please give me a chance to atone for my crimes.
What kind of mask?
It was a
terrifying ghost mask.
A ghost mask.
Could it be the person I saw at the Xiao residence?
Who exactly is behind that ghost mask?
I do not know.
He only shows himself in a mask.
You need not interfere in this matter, Empress.
I will investigate it myself.
Su Kuang.
Pass on my order. Depose Consort Xue.
Your Majesty.
Do you really intend to depose me?
She actually dares to threaten Li Yunxi.
Does she have something on you?
I don't.
Does she really have something on Li Yunxi?
Consort Xue is confined to Feixue Palace.
Without my decree,
she is not to take a single step out.
There must be something fishy about this.
This must be the truth
that Li Yunxi wouldn't tell me.
Two years ago,
I rushed back from the border
to keep my engagement with Li Yunxi.
But I suddenly learned...
Li Yunxi wants to take Liu Mianmian as a concubine.
Who is she?
Since I gave you the Phoenix Seal,
I will keep my promise
and make you my Empress.
As for Mianmian,
she will enter the harem with you
as my favored consort.
Li Yunxi.
What exactly is happening
that makes you bear this in silence?
And why can't we face it together?
When Father was alive,
he founded the Xuanniao Department to eliminate dissidents
and assassinated countless officials.
Now the descendants of the victims have appeared.
They use the same methods against me.
I suppose it's retribution.
In this world,
those who can quietly find the descendants of guilty officials
and unite them
are few.
Xiao Rushan.
You don't want the Empress to investigate this matter.
Isn't it because you've made up your mind,
fearing that if Her Highness learns the truth,
she'll be torn between you and the General?
Use the Xuanniao Ministry's list
of assassinated ministers to follow the clues
and arrest those assassins.
Between you and Li Yunxi,
what exactly is the secret?
Your Highness,
do you really want to know?
You used threats to get all this.
Are you truly happy?
But the one who actually forbade me from telling you is His Majesty.
Look at him.
He's usually so aloof.
But whenever this is mentioned,
even his greatest rage subsides.
Is His Majesty happy?
What is it exactly?
But I won't tell you even if I die.
Because once I tell the truth,
I won't have any leverage left,
and I'll even lose everything I have now.
Who is Ghost Face?
Naturally, he is His Majesty's enemy.
If only for the sake of the baby,
please eat something.
How do you know?
Take it or leave it.
You were willing to save me that day
only for the sake of
His Majesty's child.
You are lucky.
With this child,
you have a bond with him.
I want to see His Majesty.
If you ask him to come,
He will definitely come.
I have never touched you.
Who exactly is the child's father?
Your Majesty.
You haven't told the truth about that matter
to the Empress yet.
I can send you out of the palace
to be with the child's father.
Your Majesty doesn't care about me at all,
so you don't care about my betrayal.
I can save you some face,
but I hope you use your brain.
Since you know I don't care,
stop lingering in the palace.
I have nowhere else to go.
I just want to stay in the palace,
stay in Feixue Hall,
and be your Consort Xue.
Fine.
Then from today on,
Feixue Hall
is your Cold Palace.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Actually, what's the difference between us?
We both love someone so desperately.
I knew Liu Mianmian would get pregnant in my last life.
But now that it's happening,
I still get jealous.
It's late.
No drinking.
Isn't your Consort Xue pregnant?
Why did you still confine her?
Consort Xue is pregnant.
You aren't making a scene, getting angry, or jealous?
She is your favorite consort.
Her pregnancy
is a joyous occasion.
You don't mean that.
Get out.
The child isn't mine.
What?
It really isn't mine.
I never touched her.
She cheated on me.
How can you say that
so calmly?
Do I look calm?
But I swear to God it's true.
No.
How is that possible?
If I have kids,
it'll only be with you.
Your Majesty.
I once thought you were the light of my life,
always chasing after you.
Sadly,
it was all just my delusion.
Empress.
I hope you like
this final gift from me.
Consort Xue.
Empress.
I'll haunt you even after death.