How dare you hit His Majesty? How dare you!
but you didn't blame me.
No matter how hard I try,
no matter how hard I try.
Your Highness.
The Empress is a rough person.
She's not as gentle as you.
I also heard that
she used a knife to drive you away.
As long as the Empress is alive,
I will never
in your heart.
Your Highness.
The Empress has left the palace. She's not in a good mood. She's left the palace.
It's really unsettling.
What are you going to do?
Why are you still here?
I dismissed all my servants.
From now on,
I'll take care of you.
You made it?
Try it first.
You know
I don't know how to cook.
I ordered these from Tianchonglou.
I just forgot to tell them
not to put white in the dish.
I don't know how to cook.
Why are you taking care of him?
I can learn.
Enough.
Get back to your palace.
Get out of my way.
Father!
Get lost!
Tonight will be the day those assassins take action.
How could I leave?
Snow Consort.
It's you. It's me. It's you. It's me. It's you. It's me. It's me.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Are you okay?
Help! Help!
Save me!
I don't want to die.
Let her go.
I'll let you go.
Leave from me.
You bastard!
I finally killed you.
Keep him alive.
You're finally awake.
You're so weak.
Who asked you to protect me?
Who are you?
What did you say?
Did you lose your memory?
Yun Xi.
Are you trying to scare me?
You blamed me when I woke up.
I'm not blaming you.
I'm worried about you.
I'm worried about you too.
You scared me to death.
Don't do such dangerous things again.
You are the king.
Yes.
I am the king.
But I am also a person.
I have my own selfish motive.
I want to protect you.
Li Yunxi.
Do you really like me?
I...
Stop talking.
Nod if you like me.
Don't move if you don't like me.
I'll only give you one chance.
Think before you answer me.
Xiao Ling.
Once the emperor dies,
you won't be able to be the empress for long.
Who said I'm dead?
You're not dead? You're not dead?
You're not dead?
Who are you?
I'm here to kill you, the Emperor.
Watch your mouth.
The smell of blood is too strong.
You go out first.
I'll wait for you outside.
What is this?
What's your name?
Say it.
Make it quick.
This is a bone scraper.
It can perfectly
every inch of blood on the bones.
Let me tell you.
I have ways to torture you.
My name is Xie.
I'm Xie Huan.
How do you get in touch?
We'll follow the command token.
Xiao Ling.
If you don't kill me now,
I'll kill you again.
Kill that bastard!