♪Years pass in silence♪
♪Watching the flowers bloom and wither♪
♪A deep courtyard♪
♪Hides so much sorrow and loneliness♪
♪Having seen all beings♪
♪Having seen the world♪
♪Yet why is it♪
♪That I have never seen myself♪
♪How could I willingly
be trapped in this dream♪
♪How could I turn and flee♪
♪Love is a fleeting moment♪
♪Or a mere game♪
♪Exhausting my curiosity♪
♪How could I blame you, resent you,
hate you, miss you♪
♪How could I hold you tightly♪
♪Fearing a breath of spring wind
might awaken the memories♪
♪A dream passes without a trace♪
=Once Upon A Dream=
(Adapted from Luanjing's novel
"Bird in a Cage")
=Episode 13=
(Reflect on Righteousness)
(Xianxue Courtyard)
What do you want?
I want everyone who hurt me
to pay the price they deserve.
Xinglu's punishment isn't enough?
Then how about this?
Add the child in her womb.
Is that enough?
Why pretend to be clueless?
You and I both know,
the one who truly wants me dead
is someone else.
So blood makes the difference.
Only those who share
the same man-eating blood
can be considered family.
No matter how nice your words sound,
not a single thing
I want can be done.
In the future,
I'll make it up to you
with something else.
No need.
Because what I want
is something you can never give.
Shen Qingtang,
do you have to provoke me like this?
Yes.
You dragged me into the abyss,
and yet you dare expect me to love you,
to make you happy,
and to make things whole again?
You're hurt.
Quick, go find me some medicine.
Don't die here.
If you want to die, go somewhere else.
Sorry to disappoint you.
These wounds
won't kill me.
Miss,
Madam Pei is here to see you.
You must leave.
She mustn't see you.
Go, now.
I won't.
Greetings, Grandmother.
I know Congzhi protects you,
but the West Courtyard has
already been punished.
You should persuade Congzhi
not to pursue this any further.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I just caught a cold yesterday,
so my legs ache a bit.
But I'm alright now, Grandmother.
Rest early.
Another day, I'll invite
the court physician to take a look.
Thank you, Grandmother.
Leave.
My injury is too severe. I can't move.
I'll stay here for the night.
Pei Congzhi.
Don't move.
Just like this.
Just one night.
(Even if we share the same bed now,)
(our hearts remain separated.)
(What use is it?)
(Xianxue Courtyard)
If you're awake, leave now.
You may not care about shame,
but I still do.
Looks like the wound
doesn't hurt enough.
What are you trying to do now?
The promise I made
last night still holds.
I don't want to lose
the only family I've left.
What else do you wish for?
Once you know,
tell me anytime.
I want to return to Lingchuan,
to live carefree
like I did before eight,
before coming to the capital.
With or without you,
I'd be content.
Another wish that can't be granted.
Forget it.
Go.
Let me think.
Yanshu.
Yes.
Tell me, if one day I resign from office
and live as a civilian,
what would you think?
What?
Young Master,
you can't be serious.
The court can't do
without a pillar like you.
The Pei family needs you to prosper.
How can you leave?
Just joking.
What about the matter
I instructed you to do?
The Tianshui Lane affair is settled.
Just as you suspected,
though Lord Pingnan has left,
he's left many spies in the city
waiting for a chance to infiltrate.
It's all handled.
He won't grow suspicious.
Lord Pingnan holds power
and harbors ambition.
His true goal is the treasure clue
hidden on Shen Qingtang.
Find someone reliable to watch over her.
Don't let her leave here.
Yes.
At least in this Pei Manor,
I can keep her safe.
Heavens be praised!
It's cleared up.
What happened?
The new courtesan at Tianshui Lane
paraded through the streets.
They say
she looks exactly like you.
Now everyone's saying
someone must've mistaken her
for you before.
Now your name can finally be cleared.
A storm of rumors vanishes overnight.
Only he could've done that.
Was it Eldest Young Master?
Seems like he really does
care about you, Miss.
No matter what,
with him wrapping up
the Tianshui Lane affair,
you no longer need to worry.
That's good news, isn't it?
Miss, aren't you happy?
I am.
(Pei Congzhi,)
(am I just a puppet in your hands?)
(A toy whose joy, sorrow,
and even life or death)
(are all at your whim?)
(How can I break free from this fate?)
If it weren't for
grandmother's birthday,
I wouldn't have set off sky lanterns.
How have you been in the palace lately?
You still care to ask?
Even though I'm in the palace,
I've heard you lost your engagement
to Prince Yan Cheng
because of those rumors.
Today,
our brother pleaded with Crown Prince
so I could return home to visit
and talk with you.
Our brother treats you very well.
Later, you better write more lines
than others on your prayer note.
(Pei Congzhi,)
(all these years,)
(if only your indulgent
favoritism toward me)
(had stayed
within the bounds)
(of sibling affection.)
♪Blazing peach blossoms gently fall♪
♪Petals land on my heart♪
♪Yet I seek them in vain♪
♪Letting the years secretly hide♪
♪All the recklessness and naivety♪
♪Looking back at the bustling world♪
♪Is it sorrow or joy,
or all turned to emptiness♪
♪Afraid of slipping through my fingers♪
♪Fate comes and goes, all so fleeting♪
♪In my eyes, is your face♪
♪I fear time is but a fleeting dream♪
♪A fool, deeply in love for whom♪
♪And why should peach blossoms
smile at the spring breeze♪