♪Years pass in silence♪
♪Watching the flowers bloom and wither♪
♪A deep courtyard♪
♪Hides so much sorrow and loneliness♪
♪Having seen all beings♪
♪Having seen the world♪
♪Yet why is it♪
♪That I have never seen myself♪
♪How could I willingly
be trapped in this dream♪
♪How could I turn and flee♪
♪Love is a fleeting moment♪
♪Or a mere game♪
♪Exhausting my curiosity♪
♪How could I blame you, resent you,
hate you, miss you♪
♪How could I hold you tightly♪
♪Fearing a breath of spring wind
might awaken the memories♪
♪A dream passes without a trace♪
=Once Upon A Dream=
(Adapted from Luanjing's novel
"Bird in a Cage")
=Episode 11=
(Hope Meets Misfortune)
I've already stated
it was us Pei family
that refused marriage
to Lord Pingnan Manor,
so we annulled the marriage.
The ripples aren't to be crossed,
as if regretting the stirrup.
You ruined my reputation
with rumors first
and then insisted on defending me.
How calculating of you.
I lost
this round.
Do you really think
I'd use those despicable tricks?
In your eyes,
all my struggles
are a joke, aren't they?
How could I think you're a joke?
You're a clever girl.
If you don't run into a wall,
you'll never resign yourself.
You don't want to die.
You once made a deal with me.
To give me everything, so I'd save you.
Now you want to live a better life
and are fighting desperately
to escape from me.
You haven't achieved your goal yet.
How could you just die like this?
But a woman like me,
whose reputation is ruined,
has only one path, death.
Am I not
your way out?
Since childhood,
whatever you like,
I have to please.
Whatever you hate,
I have to avoid.
I should've known long ago.
What you've always wanted
was my surrender
and willing submission.
Just like now.
I've accepted my fate.
I beg you, Congzhi,
help me.
What I want
is your willing submission.
It was all my fault.
I'll never disobey you again.
Please, Congzhi,
have mercy.
(Pei Congzhi,)
(you're seeking)
(the unattainable desires
in your dreams?)
Since childhood,
whatever you like,
I have to please.
Whatever you hate,
I have to avoid.
You've always been like this.
But I'm not a caged bird.
I'm a living, breathing person
who longs for freedom and dignity.
I want to take control of my destiny,
not live the rest of my days
in this deep manor as your plaything.
You don't want to be a caged bird,
but a beast in the forest?
Even so,
I'll still pluck out your claws
one by one,
and break every bone of pride
in your body with my own hands.
Pei Congzhi.
You'd rather seek death
than say yes to me?
You always think
everything is under your control.
But in this world,
some things
won't go your way even in death.
Shen Qingtang,
you can please everyone else.
Why won't you go along with me
and love me even a little?
Maybe it's because
I'm just like you.
Equally cruel,
equally vengeful,
and equally manipulative.
People like us
don't deserve to speak of love.
So,
from the very beginning,
I was wrong, wasn't I?
Between us,
it's been a mistake
from start to finish.
I know you're heartless.
You can live in this world
without a single attachment.
If one day you dare to die,
those you care about,
Pei Ziqi,
Caiwei,
and Yan Cheng whom you long for,
will all die with you.
You...
(Even if it's a mistake,)
(I'll still keep you by my side.)
(To lean on in life,)
(and to lie with in death.)
(Never to betray in life or death.)
What's wrong, Young Master?
Nothing.
Is it about Miss Qingtang?
You haven't told her yet
that the rumors weren't your doing?
You even had a big quarrel
with Madam Pei for her during the day.
The arrangements have been made.
There will be blood at the wedding.
It won't proceed as planned.
Good.
Today, the news about Miss
ending up in Tianshui Lane
somehow got out.
It's spreading around the city
being said in the ugliest ways.
It seems
we're not the only ones
who don't want the wedding
to go smoothly today.
With such disgrace on the wedding day,
even if the marriage is annulled,
how can we salvage our reputation?
Even if she dies out there today,
she mustn't return to the Pei Manor.
Grandmother,
alive or dead,
Qingtang is part of the Pei family.
She's also mine.
Wretched child!
You'd disgrace yourself
over an adopted girl.
Put down all the betrothal gifts.
Take them away.
Go.
Madam Pei.
You truly mean well.
Why not let her know?
Now she's resented you.
In her eyes,
everything I do is disgraceful.
Why make her understand me?
But now that this has come to light,
I fear Miss Shen's days in the Pei Manor
will be even harder from now on.
Look into the matter of the rumors.
Find out exactly
who it was.
Yes.
Drink some water.
The future is long.
A real man knows when to subdue.
Moping over a woman?
Where's the dignity?
What dignity?
What future?
If I go to the frontier,
it'll be several years.
How will I ever see Qingtang again?
You really are hopeless.
All those years of studying
military strategy for nothing.
Sun Tzu's Art of War,
among the 36 stratagems,
Stratagem Eight,
recite it.
I...
Feign one thing while doing another.
Father,
are you allowing me
to elope with Qingtang?
Alright.
Stay calm.
Right now, your mother's
watching you closely.
You'll have to wait a few days
before you can return.
Yes, Father.
♪Blazing peach blossoms gently fall♪
♪Petals land on my heart♪
♪Yet I seek them in vain♪
♪Letting the years secretly hide♪
♪All the recklessness and naivety♪
♪Looking back at the bustling world♪
♪Is it sorrow or joy,
or all turned to emptiness♪
♪Afraid of slipping through my fingers♪
♪Fate comes and goes, all so fleeting♪
♪In my eyes, is your face♪
♪I fear time is but a fleeting dream♪
♪A fool, deeply in love for whom♪
♪And why should peach blossoms
smile at the spring breeze♪