DOONA!
EPISODE 1
AN UNEXPECTED TWIST
KOOK'S SEAFOOD HOUSE
CEO KOOK SU-JIN
I've had business cards made.
I'm jealous. You're already a CEO at 21.
Now that you're the boss,
get to work earlier.
The grocery boxes are too heavy
for my mom to carry.
You're that worried about your mom,
but you're running off to Seoul?
The commute has always been a problem.
And with Won-yeong now
out of the hospital,
I figured it'd be better
to use the commute time productively.
Hey, Kooksu.
Thank you.
Take care of my mom for me.
Don't even worry about it, doofus.
If, by any chance,
you happen to see Doona in Seoul,
you have got to call me, okay?
Yeah, right. As if.
WHEN THE ANSWERS INCLUDE
VERBS AND NON-VERBS
I'm sorry.
AEIHERUMUH
LOVE AND DO WHAT YOU WILL
Hello.
It's open.
Excuse me.
Have we met before?
Maybe not.
I must have mistaken you for someone else.
You looked familiar.
I'm sorry.
Oh! I'm just moving in
on the second floor.
I hope we can get along.
It's my first time living on my own.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
PLEASE KNOCK
Hello, I'm Lee Won-jun. I'm just moving--
Please refer to this notice.
HOUSE RULES
In particular, Clause Seven. Laundry.
I recommend that you use the rooftop
for your laundry.
I mean, yes.
-Newbie?
-Hello, I'm--
Senior year, Psychology.
Taek, Taek, Yun-taek.
Seo Yun-taek, that's me.
Right, I'm Lee Won-jun.
Sophomore, Civil Engineering.
There is absolutely nothing
to be worried about.
Here, you can just be yourself.
Live free.
Okay?
Yes.
No!
Oh no!
What the heck?!
There.
Perfect.
"Organic pumpkin juice."
MINSONG NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
CIVIL ENGINEERING TOP SCHOLAR
PRIVATE TUITION
KOREAN TUTOR
MINSONG KOR LIT FRESHMAN
Look, there are still some left.
Oh, thank God.
-Here.
-Thanks.
Hey, did you see his hoodie?
He must be a total fanboy.
Why would he wear that in public?
-That's actually kinda adorable.
-Agreed.
THERE'S A STALKER ON THE SECOND FLOOR
KOOK SU-JIN
Hey, CEO Kook.
Hey, bro.
Get ready to kiss
your big bro's feet, bro.
Kiss your feet?
Someone's paying 800,000 won a month?
Sick, isn't it?
And that's just for math.
Freaking sweet!
Wow, that's insane!
That will cover my rent
and living expenses.
CEO Kook, I don't know how to thank you.
Please pass my thanks on to your mom too.
How's the house? Is it okay?
Screaming out so loud…
What?
I can't hear you.
Turn the music down a bit.
Dream Sweet Lee Doona!
I love you forever!
This is how much I love Doona!
Jeez, what the hell?
Didn't you throw out their albums
and quit being a fan?
It's not that easy to give up
something you love so much.
Oh, hey, speaking of which,
give me back the hoodie
I gave you last time.
It's limited edition merch.
There won't be any new Doona merch.
Merch?
I thought it was my birthday present.
Oh no!
I was wearing it all day yesterday!
What? Who wears merch!
READ
THERE'S A STALKER ON THE SECOND FLOOR
I got this, 800,000
Per subject, 800,000
I'll sneak into your dreams
I stab
I want…
Are you messing with me?
I remember now.
You're Lee Doona, right? Dream Sweet.
It's finally come to me.
It's finally come to you. Really?
I'm sorry? I didn't quite catch that.
What did you…
Give the crappy acting a rest.
Are you insane? I could have gotten hurt!
But you didn't.
What?
How did you know I live here?
I didn't.
Did you put up a spycam or something?
What is it you want to see so much
that you'd even move here to stalk me?
I'm really not a stalker.
My friend is a fan of yours
so you looked familiar. That's why--
I'm sorry. I won't look at you again.
But you know what?
I like TWICE.
MOM
DECLINE
In terms of math, I can confidently say
that you won't find a better tutor.
I have expertise
due to extensive tutoring experience.
I can say that for certain.
You're earnest and polite. I like that.
Does that mean I can start next week?
Yes.
-Mr. Lee!
-Yes?
Well, you forgot this.
Oh. Thank you.
MATH TUITION
Are you looking for a tutor--
Won-jun!
It's been a while, Jin-ju.
I didn't recognize you
because of the short hair.
Really? I've had this
for more than a year now.
Exactly.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
That hairstyle suits you too.
Where do you live?
Are you still commuting?
Just until last semester.
I'm in a nearby house share now.
That's a shame.
I thought we could commute together.
Five hours on the road
is going to be so tedious.
What do you mean?
I'm at Minsong now too.
Come on, I got in on my second attempt.
Aren't you going to congratulate me?
Oh. Here.
Cheers!
Wow.
It's so cold.
-Here.
-Oh, you don't have to.
Take it. It's cold. And it's snowing.
All right, then. Thank you.
You're still so sweet.
This is me.
And this is me.
So that's who my competitor was.
We've always been competitors.
Only I've never beaten you.
Anyhow, let's hang out often
now that we're in the same school.
Sure.
My bus is here.
See you later.
KOREAN TUITION FOR CSAT
MINSONG KOR LIT FRESHMAN
Is she all right in this cold?
-You!
-Yes?
Don't sing.
You really suck at it.
If you sing that song around me
one more time,
I'll smash your head in.
Smash what?
Hey.
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Oh, hi. I'm at 21 Minsongdae-gil.
Someone's collapsed and is unconscious.
I think you should get here quickly.
Could you please hurry?
Yes.
JOB HUNTING STUDY GROUP
Is this only applicable to seniors?
Hey.
You're awake.
You're in the hospital.
Oh, the nurse was asking
about your guardian.
I don't have one.
You should call your family…
I said I don't have one.
Then how about your manager--
I said I don't fucking have one.
What's going on?
Why are you swearing?
There are people around.
So what if there are? Don't you swear?
No, I don't.
And I'm not a celebrity, unlike you.
I'm not either. Not anymore.
Ms. Lee Doona, is your guardian here?
Ms. Lee Doona.
I'm her guardian.
You can talk to me.
Could you please follow me?
Thanks to your quick actions,
there are no particular complications,
but her body temperature is
on the low side,
so please make sure her head,
hands, and feet are always kept warm.
A dry blanket will be useful here,
and most importantly,
make sure she wears socks.
Give her warm drinks
to help the recovery process.
I see.
Oh, and would there be
any other internal issues?
Does she need any other tests?
No, no further tests are needed.
Oh, I'm sorry, but would you happen to
have a phone charger I could borrow?
-I'll be one moment.
-Sure.
They said to put socks on you.
-So do it, then.
-Me?
Aren't you my guardian?
Excuse me.
You'll have to excuse me.
Weren't there any bed socks?
I'm sorry?
I mean, weren't there any ordinary ones?
I like ordinary stuff.
Are you laughing?
No.
It's just that you like ordinary stuff
when there's nothing ordinary about you.
Bed socks can make your feet sweat
and end up making them colder.
I got these on purpose.
And at least they're pink.
All the others looked like dad socks.
I chose these carefully.
What's your name, Mr. Guardian?
Me?
That's personal information.
KOOK SU-JIN
Hey, Kooksu.
Hey, do you smoke?
Oh, smoke.
What, me?
My mom's friend says to tell you
not to come for the tutoring job.
What?
You jackass.
She asked me three times to confirm
that you're a non-smoker, and I said yes.
But then she found that your scarf
absolutely reeked of cigarette smoke!
My 800,000 won.
I can't believe this.
YOUR ITEM HAS BEEN DELIVERED
Won-jun.
Have you had breakfast?
If not, let's eat together.
Is that my package by any chance?
What is it?
It's really cushy.
Why would you sit
on someone else's package?
I'm so hungry.
What shall we eat?
Have a nice day.
That was the day
she started waiting for me.
Won-jun, have you eaten?
Shall we go for tteokbokki?
Won-jun!
Jokbal and bossam combo?
Won-jun, let's go eat!
This is seriously driving me nuts.
Hello.
If you're here to hang up your laundry,
do it. Don't mind me.
My friend gave it to me
as a birthday present.
But he wants it back,
so I'm gonna return it.
I only wore it the other day
'cause it's fleece-lined.
It was cold that day, right?
Did I say anything?
-No, but in case you got the wrong idea.
-I didn't.
You said you're not a fan.
So that means you're not.
You dress well for an engineering major.
Does your girlfriend choose your clothes?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm hungry.
Shall we get something to eat?
Actually, can I ask you something?
Did you maybe…
fall for me?
Please don't do this.
It's making me uncomfortable.
Why are you laughing?
You're so funny.
I haven't laughed like this
in a long time.
-Look.
-Yes?
I won't fall for you.
I'll never fall for you.
"Never" is a bit unnecessary.
Let's be friends.
I want to be friends with you.
With me? Why?
Because I don't have any friends.
The first floor is for girls.
Maybe you should make friends with them?
First floor?
I have the whole floor to myself.
Wow, you're rich.
I suddenly want to be
best friends with you.
Really? Does that mean I can call you?
No.
You're a tough nut to crack.
Of course I am.
It can't be helped, then.
If I get attacked by a stalker and die,
it'll be your fault.
Why would it be my fault?
The sun's coming up. I have to make
a wish, so stop bothering me.
When did I bother you?
-Hey.
-Huh?
You forgot your underpants.
I wish I could move.
Kim Jin-ju!
Jju!
Sorry we're late.
Let's eat.
Is it good?
Lee Won-jun.
Hey.
Didn't you hear me calling you?
You can have this back.
You can keep it on if you want.
No. It smells of cigarette smoke.
Let me.
It's done.
See you later.
Yeah.
-Who was that?
-What do you mean?
-Who is he? Tell us.
-It's just someone I know.
He's good-looking.
What's with the vibe between you two?
"Just someone I know."
Can't you tell her I don't smoke?
A friend, no, what am I saying?
I mean, some weirdo…
Anyhow, it's not me.
She's found someone?
Already?
That's ten in total. 70,000 won, please.
Yes, thank you.
PART-TIMERS WANTED
RECRUITING STAFF MEMBERS FOR CAFÉ 1890
Hello.
-Take it down.
-I'm sorry?
I said take it down.
Oh, aren't we allowed
to put things up here?
You need to pay
to get this little stamp here.
You think it's okay
to post things willy-nilly?
Tutoring? That's a piece of cake!
Ladies and gentlemen!
The Brains of Yangjin!
Yangjin born and bred!
Lee Won-jun!
-I'll visit often.
-What for?
Don't forget to take the pumpkin juice.
It's in the crisper drawer of the fridge.
Won-jun!
If you get a girlfriend, send photos!
Go inside! It's cold!
Make sure you take
your medication on time!
Hello?
I got your number from your flier.
Yes, how can I help you?
I was wondering if you would
go out for a meal with me sometime.
Are you angry?
No.
You are. I can tell.
Hey, why don't you get mad at me?
I want to see you get mad.
Why are you angry though?
Didn't you stick them everywhere
so people would call?
Look here.
Are you that bored?
Is this your idea of fun?
You can do whatever you want
because you're a bum
who's rolling in time and money.
You don't care how you live your life.
Well, congratulations.
But you know what?
Not everyone can live like that.
I desperately need a job.
I also need to study.
I have a lot on my plate at the moment.
So please, for the love of God,
stop following me
and playing pranks on me.
I don't find them amusing
in the slightest.
Well, now that I've seen it,
I'm really disappointed.
I see you have no talent
for getting mad.
I understand what you're saying.
Hello?
Ms. Lee?
Let's go out for a meal sometime.
Whenever you want.
It'll be my treat.
As soon as I find a tutoring job.
Oh my god!
The presumed value of Vb
is pointing downward,
so we calculate it as a negative value.
Under the condition
that the aggregate force equals zero,
Vb comes out to 75 newtons.
Now, we'll move on to the bending moment.
We need to calculate
the aggregate bending moment
that applies to point B.
Under the condition
of the equilibrium equation,
the aggregate bending moment
at point B is zero.
Positive direction means
a clockwise direction.
Let's look at all the bending moments
that are being applied to point B.
The reaction force of 120 newtons
applying to point A
is rotating in a clockwise direction
in relation to point B.
Let's go eat.
Now?
You said whenever I want.
I want to now.
For now,
I think we need to wait
until class is over.
What should we eat?
Don't you mind being recognized?
No.
When I'm dressed like this,
not many people recognize me anyway.
You didn't either.
Actually, that was because
it felt so divorced from reality.
I'll call you.
You don't mind, do you?
Well,
if it's urgent.
I'm telling you this just in case,
but don't fall for me either.
Me?
I don't think there's any danger of that.
You never know.
Every life has its unexpected twists.
You once said to me
that you and I are
from different universes.
That though we had been living
in completely different universes…
we found ourselves sitting side by side
at the same station purely by chance.
RECENT CALLS
LEE
DOONA
Even though you may be right…
I was happy…
that it was you.