(somber music)
(grunts)
Darn it.
Get off me!
What? You can throw in a punch, too.
You used to beat me
when I didn't listen to you.
Have you given up on me now?
(grunts)
-Stop.
-Stop what...
(coughs)
Hey, are you all right?
-Darn it. Hey.
-(groans)
I said stop.
Stop what?
It's too late, man.
If you knew,
you should've stopped me sooner!
Don't hit me in the face.
Jiwoo is getting married tomorrow.
Do you have any regrets about your life?
I don't.
What's your biggest regret?
I said I don't have any.
What is it?
It's you, fool.
Letting you be who you are now.
Not doing something sooner, like you said.
Darn it. It's so you
to say something like that.
NOEUL GOSIWON
-(cell phone buzzing)
-(banging on wall)
(gasps)
(panting)
-(cell phone buzzing)
-(banging on wall)
119 EMERGENCY
(siren wailing)
(line ringing)
-TAEKROK: What?
-Where are you right now?
What's wrong?
SUNGA: Did you meet up
with Mr. Woo yesterday?
(suspenseful music)
Turn things upside down again?
Look into what?
TAEKROK: Hyunseok!
Taekrok...
-(twigs crunch)
-(taser crackles)
SUNGA: Sir.
Where are you right now?
Geumosan Mountain.
Section Chief Woo has died.
(gloomy music)
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
KIM TAEKROK
(cell phone buzzes)
NO CALLER ID
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE
MURDERER
(theme music)
SHADOW DETECTIVE
(tires screech)
(suspenseful music)
NO CALLER ID
(cell phone buzzing)
RECORD, SPEAKERPHONE
MALE VOICE:
How does it feel to be a murderer?
Hyunseok...
Did you kill him?
I told you to listen to me, didn't I?
If you hadn't been so stubborn,
he wouldn't have died.
I killed him,
but you're the one who got him killed.
If I hadn't gone to see him,
would you not have killed him?
If you refuse to do what I say again
or tell anyone about me,
another person will die.
Just like Woo Hyunseok.
And you will be framed again
like you are now.
It's no use recording this call, right?
You're a veteran indeed.
You're quick to assess the situation.
TAEKROK: What's the evidence?
-The evidence that I killed Hyunseok.
-MALE VOICE: No, it's a witness.
A witness who was at the scene
when you killed him.
And what if I say I'm being threatened?
Your sentence will only get heavier
for fabricating an alibi.
If I disappear now,
you'll be locked up in prison for the rest
of your life until the day you die.
(tires screech)
(suspenseful music)
(siren wailing)
(coughs)
You're thoroughly prepared.
MALE VOICE: Of course. I know whom
I'm up against. It wasn't easy.
What do you want?
To play a game.
A game?
(siren wailing)
(exhales heavily)
-What kind of game?
-If you win, you can arrest me.
And if you win?
You'll be arrested instead of me
for murdering Woo Hyunseok.
How is this a fair game
when I'm being cornered?
It's one-sided and dirty.
You have no choice.
But I'll give you a clue to find me.
A clue? What clue?
I will keep calling you.
That's the clue.
The only clue to catch me.
Aren't I being kind enough?
(sighs)
What if I refuse to play?
You won't.
Why? Because you're confident
that you'll catch me.
Even though the only clue is phone calls.
You're confident
that without anyone's help
and without dragging it out,
you can catch me by yourself.
Just as you always have been.
Am I wrong?
(sighs)
So what's the game?
It's very simple.
Look back on your past.
TAEKROK: My past...
MALE VOICE: You just need to do as I say
while doing what you can to find me.
In your past, you can find me
and the reason I'm doing this.
Isn't that simple?
(suspenseful music)
(sirens wailing)
TAEKROK: So you're confident
that you won't get caught.
MALE VOICE: Just hurry
and try to catch me.
I will catch you...
no matter what.
Woo Hyunseok fell to his death.
You get what I'm saying, right?
Act wisely when you deal with the police,
like the veteran that you are.
I'll call you again.
This game will not end
until one of us dies.
(tires screeching)
(crashes)
(muffled groaning)
(waves crashing)
(muffled grunt)
(muffled screaming)
(muffled groaning)
-(siren wailing)
-(gasps)
(breathes heavily)
(cell phone buzzing)
OLD BETTER HALF
(sighs)
POLICE STATION
(siren wailing)
-Has this been leaked?
-We've done everything to prevent it.
Do you think Section Chief Kook
can handle Taekrok?
Before I came in, I thought about
how I should shake up a veteran detective
with 30 years of experience.
No matter how good my questions are,
you'd know how to answer them...
to weasel your way out.
Am I right?
Because...
I didn't do it.
You're a suspect for now.
(tense music)
Why did you guys fight?
We got caught up
in some musty old memories.
More like your musty old emotional baggage
blew up.
You don't seem shocked
about Section Chief Woo's death.
Your fellow detective is dead.
A detective...
doesn't grieve
until they catch the culprit.
I see.
So you are sad, but you're holding it in
until you catch the culprit?
Jeez, that's impressive.
Mocking the suspect
to make them confess...
is an obvious trick.
Of course. You're the expert.
You're actually enjoying this, aren't you?
All we have are circumstances
and no clear evidence.
You're thinking, whatever we do to prove
you guilty, you'll find your way out.
Aren't you?
With that kind of soft attitude,
what kind of idiot...
would confess?
In your statement,
you said you went to the scene
in the middle of the night,
because you suddenly got worried
out of the blue for no reason.
It's completely random.
What's with this response?
MALE VOICE: If you refuse to do
what I say again or tell anyone about me,
another person will die.
Just like Woo Hyunseok.
And you will be framed again
like you are now.
(sighs)
-And the examination?
-Why were you in the mountain?
Because I suddenly got worried
out of the blue for no reason.
(scoffs)
You know how he died.
What's the cause of his death?
Answer my question first. Why did you go
to the mountain at that hour?
I said, what's the cause of his death?
(sighs)
Multiple traumas
by a great external force.
His liver, spleen, and everything
were damaged all at once.
We haven't found proof
of other external forces yet.
DEATH CERTIFICATE
-That means he fell to his death.
-Won't be sure until the autopsy result.
Any possibility of murder?
All of this points to one person.
Why didn't you report it right away?
Act wisely when you deal with the police,
like the veteran that you are.
I don't remember.
I don't remember how I got home.
TAEKROK: I woke up
and found myself in my room.
-Gosh.
-Hey, how did I get home last night?
-By taxi.
-Taxi?
TAEKROK: He probably used a taxi
to avoid getting his car traced.
What?
TAEKROK:
And he had the taxi driver call Gong...
Hey.
...to make an alibi...
GONG: He's freaking heavy.
...and to make him a witness.
He got Gong to put me in my room...
to leave a record of it.
You don't remember?
(sighs)
I don't understand at all.
It's true.
I don't remember.
I checked your medical records.
You've had psychiatric treatment.
Does that have something
to do with your memory problem?
-Get the chief in here.
-I'm in charge of this case.
Gwangsu. If you want
to finish this quickly, get in here now.
Where is your cell phone?
I don't know. I lost it.
TAEKROK: I said get in here!
Give us a minute alone.
-Chief.
-TAEKROK: Turn off the recording devices!
(door closes)
GEUMO POLICE STATION
What do you think
they're talking about for so long?
Beats me.
(sighs)
It still haunts me.
I wish we hadn't seen
the two of them last night.
(door opens)
I'm keeping you in custody.
Relieve him from his duties
and form a team for this case.
But for now,
report this as accidental death
by loss of footing.
GWANGSU: Do you agree?
Let's give him some time.
-Do you want to explain this, sir?
-Later.
Hey, Officer Son. Come see me for a bit.
Yes, sir.
(gloomy music)
(breathes deeply)
DETECTIVE 1: Hey, to the conference room.
HAN: Yes, I'm coming.
I should go, too.
(gloomy music)
(sighs)
-(exhales sharply)
-(seat belt clicks)
(car engine starts)
What did the chief say?
He just said I should learn
from my superiors as much as I can.
That's what he said?
By the way,
do you think this makes any sense?
I mean, I still can't believe
they're suspecting Detective Kim.
-What about you?
-Sorry?
What do you think?
I checked your medical records.
You've had psychiatric treatment.
Me? I'm certain.
(sighs)
He came to a wedding at a time like this?
He doesn't go to weddings. Only funerals.
Hmm...
Do you think he's here to investigate?
He's wearing a suit,
which he never does, and even a tie.
He does have a daughter.
(sighs)
His daughter is getting married
on the day he became a murder suspect?
That's just terrible.
GUEST 1: Congratulations.
JUNGAE: Thank you for taking the time
to come today.
-Have you seen Jiwoo?
-GUEST 1: Yes, she looks beautiful.
-JUNGAE: She does, doesn't she?
-GUEST 2: Yes. I'll see you later, then.
JUNGAE: Sure. Excuse me.
-What happened?
-What do you mean?
What did you do
with the wedding invitations I gave you?
I was at least expecting
some flowers from the police.
You didn't give them out?
-I never let anyone invite me either.
-(sighs)
The one and only detective, aren't you?
So busy catching all the criminals
that you shame your only daughter
on her wedding day.
What a great father you are.
You've got something on your face.
Don't you do anything silly later.
-Hello.
-GUEST 3: Your daughter looks beautiful.
-JUNGAE: She does.
GUEST 4: You raised her
into a beautiful woman.
JUNGAE: Thank you.
All right, I'll see you in there.
HOST: The ceremony will begin shortly.
-Please get inside the hall.
-JUNGAE: Hello.
(romantic music)
LEE JAEHO AND KIM JIWOO
OUR STORY
THANK YOU TO OUR PARENTS FOR RAISING US.
WE'LL LIVE A HAPPY LIFE TOGETHER.
(romantic music)
Gosh, we're tailing him
when we're supposed to congratulate him.
If he knew,
he'd be very disappointed, right?
(sighs)
He's out.
What? Why is he coming this way?
What are you doing?
We need to hide.
Hello.
Get out.
What a surprise to see you here.
-Come and eat.
-Okay.
I knew it was a bad idea to take my car.
We should've taken another car.
You think that would've made a difference?
Are you really going to eat?
We're his only guests.
I can't wait to be done with this.
This wedding hall must be popular.
The food here is great.
We've been assigned to the team
for Section Chief Woo's case.
So what?
(slurps)
You don't have your wallet.
Keep the receipts.
It's yours.
I'm going to splurge.
And I'm going to claim it all later.
JUNGAE'S BROTHER: Taekrok!
Why haven't you returned my calls?
-Hey.
-Taekrok.
(sighs)
I know this happened a long time ago,
but I still don't understand.
Why did you divorce my sister?
She said she didn't want to get a divorce,
but you asked for it.
Since then you've been paying her alimony,
child support, and everything.
I heard that you live in a gosiwon now.
Why do you live like that?
Seriously, Taekrok. I feel terrible.
-That's the best I can do.
-(scoffs)
Taekrok. Let's talk...
-What are you doing?
-Jungae.
JUNGAE'S BROTHER: I haven't seen Taekrok
in a while, and I feel bad for the guy.
-JUNGAE: That's enough!
-JUNGAE'S BROTHER: Taekrok!
JUNGAE: What is the matter with you?
JUNGAE'S BROTHER: Jungae.
I heard he's the one
who got Jiwoo her house.
How could you treat him this way?
(classical music playing)
Dad.
-Let's take the stairs.
-Okay.
Don't worry about what Mom and Uncle said.
I know.
Okay.
Lately, I think a lot about the old days.
I didn't realize it before.
But thank you...
for everything.
(soft chuckle)
I'll be off, then.
Okay.
(beeps)
(chuckles)
(dramatic music)
(sighs)
(inhales deeply)
(dramatic music)
STAFF 1: Excuse me.
-You're Ms. Kim Jiwoo's father, right?
-Yes.
The person who delivered these flowers
wanted me to give this to you.
I almost forgot.
I WISH YOU A LIFETIME OF HAPPINESS
FROM YOUR DAD'S FRIEND
FRIEND
(tense music)
ANSWER YOUR PHONE
(suspenseful music)
Sir, he just turned on his phone.
What do we do?
-Keep tracking him and keep me posted.
-Yes, sir.
What's the update on his whereabouts
on the day of the incident?
There aren't many operational CCTVs
near the mountain.
We're trying to trail him,
but we keep losing his tracks.
He might have been
intentionally avoiding the cameras.
Take a look at this first.
GEUMOBUDU-RO 33BEON-GIL
Call the taxi company,
find out who the driver was, locate him.
Okay.
Excuse me, sir.
-Could I talk to you for a minute?
-Sure.
(sighs)
(cell phone buzzes)
NO CALLER ID
MALE VOICE: Did you like the flowers?
I tried to pick nice ones.
That's enough.
There's a limit to my patience.
Let's meet.
I'll come alone.
Fine, let's meet.
Where do you want to meet?
Before we do that, do you remember
the fratricide case from ten years ago?
A man killed his older brother
for inheritance and buried him in secret.
After that, he was arrested.
But that case turned out
to be a total mess.
This is fake evidence.
Was it you?
It was you, Choi Kyoil.
That's not mine!
You fabricated it.
MALE VOICE: That knife was fabricated.
Find the real weapon
and reveal it to the world.
And the person behind it.
What does that case have to do
with Woo Hyunseok?
It all started because of him.
What did he do?
Do you have time to waste? I don't.
You have until tomorrow.
Hey, are you...
Choi Kyoil?
MALE VOICE: Did you think this game
was going to be that easy? Try harder.
(line trills)
TAEKROK: Why the false evidence?
Why the fratricide case?
By the way, what did he mean
when he said that's the best he can do?
That's the best I can do.
(sighs)
When his daughter was little,
she was kidnapped
by a criminal that he caught.
The criminals kept threatening his family,
so they had to move from place to place.
Why didn't he quit his job, then?
Do you think they would've left
his family alone if he had just quit?
He just did what he thought was best.
I don't know.
Not all homicide detectives are like that.
Detective Kim only went
after the most vicious criminals
that the other detectives avoided.
(cell phone buzzing)
(sighs)
-Yes?
-I need information about the culprit
from the 2012 Suam-ri fratricide case.
Okay, anything else?
That's it for now.
It's urgent.
Should we follow him?
-Let's go.
-Where?
I'm not really sure
if I should tell you this or not.
I mean, I think I should, but...
Don't, if you feel uneasy.
No. It's not that. I don't feel uneasy.
Those two committed a lot of corruption.
-Those two?
-Section Chief Woo and the chief.
You know that in a small town like this,
the local notables are all best buds, yes?
They stick together and embezzle money
in the name
of community development and all.
And Section Chief Woo
took care of everything for them,
making sure there was no problem.
He didn't have enough power
to do all that by himself.
The chief must have
backed him up in secret.
(tense music)
Let's give him some time.
Rumor has it that they've raked in...
a whopping amount of slush funds.
I'm telling you this,
because I trust you, okay?
The one that I find most suspicious
is Chief Seo.
Now that the section chief is dead,
he can just blame him
for all the corruption and irregularities
and have all that slush funds to himself.
Frankly, I think he just killed
two birds with one stone.
-Detective Han.
-Yes?
Will you do me a personal favor?
A personal one?
Trace the chief
on the day of the incident,
and look into the irregularities that he
and the section chief have committed.
I'm honored
that you asked me to do it, but--
Don't you want to make team leader?
-Do you want to go golfing sometime?
-I don't play golf.
I see.
How about we go fishing instead?
Really?
Right.
If I remember correctly,
Section Chief Woo...
used two cell phones.
NOEUL GOSIWON
A MAN KILLS AND SECRETLY BURIES
HIS OWN BROTHER
THE GEUMOSAN MOUNTAIN FRATRICIDE CASE
SECRET BURIAL AFTER INHERITANCE DISPUTE
BURIED BODY FOUND IN GEUMOSAN MOUNTAIN
CULPRIT OF GEUMOSAN MURDER CASE CAUGHT...
POLICE QUICKLY ACQUIRES EVIDENCE
CHIEF DETECTIVE IN CHARGE, SEO GWANGSU,
RECEIVES SPECIAL PROMOTION
SUSPECT OF FRATRICIDE CASE
CLAIMS EVIDENCE TO BE FALSE
It was you, Choi Kyoil.
That's not mine!
Not yours?
Then where is yours?
It was you, wasn't it?
You fabricated it, didn't you?
EVIDENCE FOUND, 19 YEARS OF IMPRISONMENT
SUSPECT MR CHOI CLAIMS "THIS ISN'T RIGHT"
(cell phone buzzing)
-Yes.
-SUNGA: I found it.
Hang on.
CHOI KYOIL, FRATRICIDE
Wait.
DATE OF SUSPENSION
JAN 19, 2022
His sentence was suspended.
His sentence was suspended?
(suspenseful music)
Where is he now?
Sir.
I could only find one cell phone
under the section chief's name.
But he definitely carried two.
Could it be a burner phone?
I think so. What do we do, then?
Trace his whereabouts and see if you
can find the number of the other phone.
-Especially before and after his death.
-Yes, sir. I will.
HANBIT REHABILITATION HOSPITAL
STAFF 2: He was in Geumo Detention Center
until his sentence was suspended
when he was diagnosed
with terminal blood cancer.
He's been staying at Hanbit
Rehabilitation Hospital since January.
CHOI KYOIL, MALE, 43
Where is the weapon?
What weapon?
Where did you hide it?
(sighs)
Darn it, you're driving me crazy.
Look, detective.
If you don't find it,
I'll be found innocent, right?
So...
let me go.
Excuse me.
Are you his guardian?
No.
-I'm a detective.
-I see.
Is he able to move around?
Is he ever conscious?
No.
He's been bedridden for a month now
after his condition started to get worse.
He regains consciousness sometimes,
but only for a short moment.
Any visitors?
You're the first visitor
since he came here.
TAEKROK: He's not the friend.
If you can reach his family, please do.
He's in critical condition.
I see. Please call me if he wakes up.
It's important.
Okay, I'll let the other nurses know.
(suspenseful music)
CIVIL AFFAIRS
INMATE VISITOR LIST
VISIT REFUSED
Who is this person?
LEE MYUNGHEE
Oh, her?
-She said she was the victim's mother.
-The victim's mother?
That's what she said herself.
I won't tell anyone.
Please just tell me where she is. Please?
Guard.
I'm done here.
Please just tell me where Seyoung is!
I beg you!
Please.
GUARD: Choi Kyoil agreed
to see her at first.
But after a while, he started refusing
and never saw her again.
By the way,
was there another victim in that case?
DETECTIVE 2: Come on!
Hurry and get in!
You're the detective
on the fratricide case, right?
Who...
This is my daughter. She hasn't come home
since the day of the incident.
Taekrok, let's go!
-You can report missing persons upstairs.
-I reported it a long time ago.
Detective. My daughter passes by the scene
of the crime on her way home from school.
She's never left home before.
-Taekrok, we're short on time!
-I'll check with the detectives.
My daughter
might have been killed by that man.
Right. Please wait at home.
Wait, detective.
(sobs)
(siren wailing)
Who is she?
You got that missing person's
report, right?
HAN: Yes, I handled it.
But the Women and Juvenile
Affairs Division took it over,
and I handed over all the documents.
-What happened next?
-Next?
Well, I don't know what happened next.
Come on. Think harder, kid.
I couldn't remember even if I tried.
It was a long time ago.
As you know, we're all assigned
to tons of cases.
I can't remember every detail
of every case.
But why do you ask...
(sighs)
(somber music)
CIVIL AFFAIRS
GEUMO DETENTION CENTER
TAEKROK: If the girl is still missing,
it's likely that Choi Kyoil
also killed her back then.
And if her remains are found now...
Choi Kyoil is the culprit.
(breathes deeply)
(line ringing)
-SUNGA: Yes?
-Hey.
I need you to identify a missing person
and get me her information.
And the contact numbers of the testifiers.
DONGYANG LURE FISHING SHOP
SUNGA: Her name is Han Seyoung.
She was in 11th grade at the time.
She's still missing.
The one you described is her mother.
She comes to the station every now
and then to check on the progress.
CHILD MISSING
The testifiers are Seyoung's friends
who left school with her that day.
Yes, I'm sure.
Something must've happened
to Seyoung after we parted ways
at the entrance of Geumosan Mountain.
SEYOUNG'S FRIEND:
What good are the police?
I told them many times.
Seyoung disappeared in that mountain.
My daughter
might have been killed by that man.
(trills)
(line rings)
GWANGSU: What is it?
Gwangsu.
Let me gather some guys.
-What are you talking about?
-TAEKROK: I need to do a search right now.
What do you need to search for
out of the blue?
Don't you want to catch
the culprit quickly?
Have you found a lead?
The fratricide case from ten years ago.
Choi Kyoil.
Come into the station first.
I can't waste any more time.
Explain why you're searching for
and what is going on first!
The false evidence.
CHOI KYOIL
(suspenseful music)
The weapon Choi Kyoil used.
Hey, where did you find this?
-Around where the body was buried.
-But we searched that entire area.
Are you certain this is it?
Check the fingerprints
and the bloodstains.
TAEKROK: You knew.
Don't make assumptions.
I didn't know then, and I still don't.
That's not true.
You chose to ignore it.
Because the evidence
you were so desperately looking for
showed up right in front of you.
What are you trying to say?
What if I tell people
that you knew about it?
Or that I fabricated it on your orders?
I'll just get fired,
but you'll have to resign with dishonor.
You want to be a city councilor?
That won't happen.
That's enough nonsense.
What does that have to do with this case?
There was one more victim.
We have to find her right now.
If we do, then what?
We'll know once we do.
Send the guys to Geumosan Mountain.
I'll meet them there.
(sighs)
Catch the murderer.
One week. I can't give you
any more than that.
And if I fail?
Then you'll be detained
and charged with murder.
Or you'll pretend like it was an accident
and bury this case forever.
(suspenseful music)
(dogs barking)
DETECTIVE 3: Unit One,
to the right! Move it!
(dogs whimpering)
(shovel rasping)
(panting)
Uh...
(whimpering)
(Seyoung screaming)
(thwacking)
(dogs barking)
(sirens wailing)
What are you doing here?
There's something I missed ten years ago.
Is it related to the section chief's case?
TAEKROK: I don't know that yet.
HAN (whispers): About his cell phone.
-Hey.
-Yes?
I don't mean to butt in
on your investigation,
but whose cell phone
are you talking about?
Apparently, Section Chief Woo
used two cell phones when he was alive.
Do you know anything about it?
A lot of detectives
use two or three phones.
-I also use two.
-Where are they?
What?
I told you I lost them.
Forget about that.
What about Hyunseok's phones?
One of them is a burner phone.
-You were saying?
-I couldn't find anything.
There was nothing in his office.
Please go back to the station
and check the CCTV footage more thoroughly
to see what the suspect was up to
on the day of the incident.
Okay.
The suspect can't remember a thing,
so we should help him remember.
I'd appreciate that.
I'll get going, then.
(clears throat)
Where are you going?
To the crime scene.
I'm going to go back there
to try to remember
if I really killed Hyunseok like you said.
Who knows?
I might turn myself in.
If you do, you'll get a lighter sentence.
What is he searching for here?
(eerie music)
TAEKROK: Hyunseok talked to someone
on the phone at the tavern.
Did you check that?
There was no call history.
TAEKROK: Hyunseok was using
his burner phone.
And he was talking to the friend.
He got Hyunseok to come out here.
Why did he want to meet here?
Is he familiar with this area?
The taxi driver said Section Chief Woo
went to the mountain alone.
TAEKROK: Alone.
That means they either made plans
to meet beforehand,
or he made the appointment at the tavern.
Meeting up...
on short notice.
MALE VOICE: Don't go,
you'll regret it if you go.
TAEKROK: He knew that I was going to
see Hyunseok.
Was it Hyunseok that wanted to see him?
Or was it him?
Come on, fill your lungs
with fresh air instead.
(Hyunseok scoffs)
Isn't this place nice?
I often come up here
and organize my thoughts.
It is nice, but it's a bit dangerous.
-Be careful.
-(Hyunseok scoffs)
Old man, you are becoming a coward.
-HYUNSEOK: Hey!
-TAEKROK: Darn it!
(laughing)
Jeez.
TAEKROK: The friend didn't lure him here.
Hyunseok must've asked to meet here.
Why did he want to meet here?
Why?
He came to negotiate,
but something went wrong.
-And in the end...
-Aah!
(thuds)
TAEKROK: The important thing is...
it wasn't their first time meeting.
That means the friend is...
Hey, I said no drugs, didn't I?
TAEKROK: Is it Mr. Cheon after all?
But he has nothing to do
with the fratricide case.
No connection whatsoever.
False evidence?
Mr. Cheon has nothing to do
with that either.
What on earth does the friend want?
(leaves rustling)
TAEKROK: Why...
is this here?
It's him.
(ominous music)
(dog barks)
(panting)
(grunts)
Pull everyone back.
Yes, sir.
Stop the search!
We're pulling back!
(panting)
(groaning)
(grunting)
(groans)
(closing theme music)
SHADOW DETECTIVE