[The film was created for entertainment purposes.]
[Characters, actions, places and events in the film are hypothetical events.]
[No intention of sexual arousal,]
[leading or inciting inappropriate or morally corrupt behavior]
[And there is no intention to cause damage to any profession]
[or have a negative attitude toward any organization or group of people.]
THE ROSE OF SIN
THE SINNER'S ROSE Episode 08
Is this Mr. Wi's market?
It's 10 times bigger than Thong's market.
Next time I will take you for a walk. There's always a lot of food.
Where is Mr. Wi's house?
After this market, enter the alley and you'll be there.
I'm so nervous.
I'm here, Thong.
Let's go, let's go home together.
[Market Office]
Come here Thong, come here and bow to your father first.
Dad, today I'm taking Thong,
The woman you love comes to our house.
She will be a new member of our family.
I hope dad will love her like I do.
And I hope dad protects Thong
Let her live in this house peacefully and happily.
Thong... I would like to rely on you, dad. That's all.
I have to say it again and again, what a pity.
I also want my father to meet Thong.
It will probably be fun to talk about.
Dad, if you want to talk to Thong
Dad can also enter Thong's dream.
Come to dream about a special number
so Thong can win on the 1st.
Thong, don't joke like that.
Better go find your mother.
Sit here first.
Oh, are you here?
The food has just finished, the table is full, come on, hurry up.
Leave it here!
Eat rice, Ms. Ieng.
Yes.
Hello mom.
Hello child.
Wait a minute, wait a minute for your rice.
It's here, the rice is here.
This is Uncle Ieng, who has worked in my mother's house for a long time.
If anything happens
Then you can call Mr. Ieng.
Hello, uncle.
Hello!
Come on, let's eat.
Wait, this, mom cooked for Thong
Those 3, 4 hours. Mom cooks very fragrant soup.
Try it, kid.
Thank you.
Do you eat?
Yes.
Okay, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
This is mine.
Yes.
Thong, what happened this morning,
what my mother said so harshly,
If you forget something, forget it.
Don't remember what to do.
Because I just want to get to know you
more, just better.
We live in the same house,
No matter big or small, let's ignore each other.
Yes, okay.
Anyway, I respect my mother very much.
Mom is so good to me.
Let Mr. Wi know you,
Then I accepted you as my daughter-in-law.
If you have something to teach, just teach it.
YES.
Eat, eat, be careful not to get cold.
Eat rice.
Eat your vegetables.
Every dish is delicious, I can open a restaurant now.
Really, child?
Mom is also thinking that
Mom will leave the cooking to you.
Mom will teach you how to cook, is that okay?
Yes, okay.
Clear the table!
Yes.
Let me help you.
Wi.
Yes?
Don't forget the tablecloth, kids.
Yes, mom.
Wait!
Wash it already.
What?
Wash this bowl, wash it too.
Our family doesn't like to throw dishes in the sink.
Lots of insects and dirty.
Oh, thank you too, wash the sink too.
Okay.
You're the one doing it and you dare to go against me?
It's better to pretend to be dirty, so you don't make mistakes again.
Come in, baby.
What do you see? Can I stay?
Can you stay?
My house in the out of town is about this size.
Small, but warm.
So that's good.
Thong! Then...
Thank you very much.
For stepping forward to add color to my life.
Before, my life was just living day by day,
In the morning, I do bookkeeping, and in the evening, I read comics.
Look, the cupboard is full.
But since I met you,
You are my motivation
wake up every day. Did you know?
Since I met you? When will we meet?
That first time, when I rented an apartment.
From that day on he had been counting to see when
You will be allowed to collect room fees again.
You're too cunning. Obviously I had a lover at that time.
But I never thought I would flirt with you.
Well... if only I could see your face,
I feel happy already.
I won't go anywhere else. I will stay with you Wi forever.
I will love you with all my heart.
Mr. Wi, let's try again.
Let me teach you.
Teach... what?
Then teach dancing.
Thong!
Pete.
What are you doing here?
We're done with each other, right?
I'm like this
have you forgotten me?
I don't forget.
I found someone to take care of me after you.
You're not angry with me, right?
Not angry.
I congratulate you.
I live with him
then behave properly.
Okay.
I will act like a good wife.
Be a good daughter-in-law.
I know I am very lucky to have met Mr. Wi.
Furthermore, his mother doesn't hate me anymore.
Pete,
I'm in a happy place.
You don't need to worry about me anymore.
Follow your path.
Good luck, Thong.
Goodbye.
Pete.
Goodbye, Pete.
I'm Thong.
Wake up, Thong.
What's wrong with Thong?
Why call him by name?
Who's name?
That's the name of Thong's ex-lover.
Are you missing him?
No sir.
Thong... It's probably just a dream.
What dream?
Dreaming of him coming to say goodbye.
It's nothing.
Don't think too much.
Don't let me hear it anymore, I won't like it.
You are my wife, sleeping next to me.
How can you remember someone else?
Understand?
I understand.
That won't happen again.
You can rest assured now.
I don't know what time it is anymore.
What is this?
Why are there still pictures of him?
Probably because Thong forgot to delete it.
I will delete it now.
Does this phone still have photos of him?
Just a little bit.
Just delete it a bit and it's gone. Mr. Wi.
I will buy a new one for you.
Don't dream about him anymore.
I'm Thong.
Where is Thong?
Hey Wi.
Mom took Thong for a walk to see the event at the market.
Go early in the morning.
Why didn't you wake me up so I could go with you?
Why do you follow?
They go to instruct each other.
If Wi intervenes
then you won't be able to teach.
I don't think we should stand here and talk anymore.
Go take a shower and change clothes
Then go down to eat porridge, I've finished cooking.
Ah, yes…
Go, kid.
Come on, let me take you there.
- When you're done, come down to eat? - Yes.
Hard-working person
people have to wake up early in the morning.
Don't you normally wake up early?
I want to wake up early
but last night Mr. Wi kept bothering me all night.
So I have to sleep late.
Hey,
is a girl
when talking, keep your mouth shut for a bit.
From now on no matter what happens
you also have to wake up at 5 am, because the market opens at 5 am.
Don't arrive later than the sales people, you know?
I know.
- Hello, sister. - Hello.
What's going on, have you got your capital back today?
- I got my capital back. - Yes, good luck.
- Hello, sister. - Hello.
- What's up? - You can also sell it again, sister.
Yes, that's good.
Mom.
Is it difficult to be the owner of a market?
Is it difficult?
First stage,
when it's not stable
it's really difficult.
But once it's stable, it's easy.
Idle is what my mother said
Sit around and not collect money?
That's right, sitting there without collecting money.
What are you asking for?
I want to know.
Who knows, maybe one day
What if Thong will manage the market after his mother?
Don't think too far ahead.
Like that,
before I took over the market
I still have a lot to learn.
Okay, mom.
Thong is ready.
Mom besides managing the market
There's also another pork stall here.
It was my mother's first job.
Such a big stall,
It must be a lot of profit, right?
That's right, there's a lot of profit.
I said, isn't that right?
That I want to continue my mother's work.
If so, then just come here to practice.
This will be the first.
Children.
From today onwards
We have someone who comes to help every day, and that's Thong.
Mom.
Sao?
Don't want to continue anymore?
I want it.
Want it right? If you want, go.
Go.
Bring a knife and give it to him.
The first thing you need to practice is
cut the pig's head.
[Insurance]
First of all,
get a knife
slit from mouth to throat
really deep inside.
I can't do it, mom.
Pick up the pig's ear.
Hurry up.
Thong!
Em Thong!
What? Go get your sniffer.
Hold it, hold it.
Come get the meat, sister.
Yai, Yai, Yai come here.
Needs some strength.
Please give me some strength.
Help someone who faints.
Now, leave the chair here.
Sit, sit, sit. Where is the sniffer?
The first day I fainted.
Who is it, sister?
Why is he such a difficult person to teach?
What's wrong, mom?
Mom, I don't say bad things.
But it's an easy job that mom told me to do
Just cutting pork can't cut it.
So if you think like this, what business can you do? What do you do to earn a living?
Mom!
It's only the first day, mom.
Please calm down a bit.
I think cutting meat and that, you have to practice slowly to get used to it.
Oh, what else is this?
Forks.
Wanted to show Thong's dishwashing skills.
Why is it so viscous?
Yesterday, I left Thong
help wash the dishes.
Looking at her attitude, she didn't seem very satisfied, seeing her grumbling.
Probably intentionally dirty like that.
Washing dishes is not clean.
Is this also teasing mom?
Mom, Uncle Ieng! I think don't rush to think deeply.
Em Thong could be
is not familiar with or not suitable for these jobs.
But if we
speaks slowly, teaches gently
she can do it.
I think we should not rush to be prejudiced against each other.
I beg you.
Okay?
- Ieng! - Yes!
We
- must use more patience than that. - Yes.
You know what?
If you are taught and willing to listen, it is good.
But if you keep trying,
No matter how much you teach, there will be no results.
If so, please allow me to go see her for a bit.
Yai. What are you doing?
What to do? Do something?
What is that? I did not do anything.
I'm just helping her feel less tired.
You don't need to say anything, I know what you're thinking. You bastard.
Wherever you go, go, go.
I'll tell mom to fire you.
Mr. Wi. Why did you punch him?
He didn't do anything to Thong.
Haven't done anything yet?
I don't like just sitting so close to each other.
You know Yai's personality well. Don't you know what he thinks?
Do you think it wants to help you feel less tired?
It's about wanting your body, understand?
Next time, don't let me see him sitting so close to you again.
Otherwise, I won't leave Thong alone. Got it?
Thong will be careful.
Thong, please sit down.
I'm Thong.
Sorry for making you scared.
It's just because I'm worried about you. Don't be angry with me.
I think you should go home and rest now.
Let me tell Uncle Ieng to cook rice for you to eat.
But Mr. Wi, Thong wants to eat at the restaurant.
The weather is so hot today, Thong wants to sit in the air conditioner.
Mr. Wi, let's take Thong to the shopping center.
That's OK. But let me collect the room rent first.
Who is that?
Oh, I know, I'm going to open the door.
Oh...
Oh, keep typing? That's the door.
Not your mother's coffin lid.
Thong.
And.
What did you come for?
Then come collect the room rent,
where you are sleeping.
You crazy.
I think you should go get treatment.
If the doctor can't cure you
Then you go find a magician to cure it.
I'm not crazy.
Before, I was just a tenant.
But now I'm the boss.
And you're still the same tenant.
So, pay the rent.
Fraudster.
Do you want to be the boss?
Are you Wi's wife?
That's right.
I will update my life for you.
My husband is no longer the young brat he was before,
The person you hired to scratch your itch
Instead of using durian peel to scratch.
And now it's Mr. Wirachay,
owner of Sod market and this apartment building.
I hope this is my husband
I won't have you sneaking around to eat me anymore.
Oh, you illusion.
Hey, I've been courting Wi for almost a year
but I can't even do it.
You've only been here for a few months and you say you have her?
That's the difference in skills.
And your skills can only lure roadside dogs.
Oh, I don't believe it.
I think I'm as beautiful as you.
You liar.
You liar, you'll see.
Wi, I have something to ask.
I Wi to Thong
Come to collect the room rent on my behalf?
So what are you two to each other?
YES.
That's it.
What did you say?
Knowing that, are you going to stay or leave?
Why do I have to go?
I have money and can pay.
20 thousand baht.
The rent has increased, just increased!
Can you afford to pay?
If not, pack it up!
Who increased?
Did you increase it yourself or did Wi increase it?
Mr. Wi gave it to the monk.
Are you sure?
Okay, let me call Wi!
The same 10,000 baht is fine, I pity you.
Since you're at this age, you probably won't be able to sell well.
Don't step into my room again.
I'm lazy when it comes to using holy water to purify myself.
Dear Wi,
From now on I will be in charge of collecting rent for you.
I will share some of the work with you.
That's OK.
Thank you, let's go!
Thong, do you want to visit this shop?
No, I've been to see things at this store before.
But the staff did not welcome me.
They look down on me because I can't afford it.
And then chase me away like a pig and a dog!
Let's go, Mr. Wi!
Thong, which set do you want?
I bought it for you, come take a look!
Really, Mr. Wi?
But this store's items are very expensive.
Man, how expensive is that?
For me, there is no word expensive.
Come on, come take a look.
Mr. Wi, if so, can I go in alone?
Don't, don't touch it.
I told you not to touch it.
So please try this outfit.
Why does he have to eat outside?
Wasting money in vain, not understanding.
When it comes to pampering your husband, this girl is good at it.
Oh, Wi hasn't grown up yet,
Anyway, I'm addicted to it.
I'm back.
Who's throwing a party?
That's why I bought so many things.
Oh, mom, it's all the necessary things.
Necessary items?
Mr. Wi bought a new phone, the old one just broke.
How much?
30 thousand.
30 thousand?
This outfit is 50 thousand 8 hundred.
- What? - This item is about 100 thousand.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you!
All this place is more than 100 thousand.
Do you think you have a husband?
Is it shameless to be a freeloader?
Mom! Don't be so quick to complain.
It's not just Thong's things, there's mine too.
That's right, Mr. Wi brought it out.
Okay.
Here, mom, this shirt Thong chose for me.
Isn't it beautiful, mom?
I like it very much.
This color, this pattern?
Yes.
I don't think you should wear it.
It doesn't suit my style.
I'm afraid you'll wear it,
The dog will chase and bite that child.
Oh, mom, it looks beautiful on me.
Can I go see it for mom?
Right? Go!
Go!
Mr. Wi! I feel so sorry for those shoes.
Discounted up to 6 thousand, but no size.
Doesn't fit my feet.
YES.
Sir!
I'm really sorry
Because I have to do this, please forgive me.
If our child
Marry this girl
then life will definitely be fishy.
Don't be angry with me.
Hey, Thong! Wipe carefully, wipe clean.
Every corner must be free of dust. Understand?
Yes, mother, I will clean the altar thoroughly.
Make dad feel really refreshed.
Pick up the jars, lift them up and clean the bottom.
For convenient cleaning.
Yes, Mom. Please allow me, Dad.
THE ROSE OF SIN