[The film was created for entertainment purposes.]
[Characters, actions, places and events in the film are hypothetical events.]
[No intention of sexual arousal,]
[leading or inciting inappropriate or morally corrupt behavior]
[And there is no intention to cause damage to any profession]
[or have a negative attitude toward any organization or group of people.]
THE ROSE OF SIN
Episode 21
Save me, don't let them take me away.
Calm down, I'll handle it.
Get out of the car.
Hands up!
I told you to raise your hand.
Let's talk slowly, policeman...
Why don't you talk slowly?
You're really good.
How dare you rob my boss's people.
I'm sorry,
- I just want... - Just want?
Want it?
This is what you want? Want it?
You're really good, really good.
You're really good, very good.
Damned!
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it.
Enough, enough.
Enough?
Enough.
The person who loves Thong the most
will take Thong home.
Obediently go home with me.
Thong will come back to you,
But can you tell your people to stop?
I'll go get my bag.
Then get in your car.
I still really like your band
and still want to listen to music from your band.
So today I let you go.
But if you want to live and follow music for a long time
Then don't touch me anymore.
Get in the car.
Thong closes his eyes.
What for?
Just keep aiming.
What is this?
I already told Thong.
I love Thong the most.
He will marry Thong.
Marry Thong?
So what about the other women?
In what capacity will they live with us?
Domestic worker.
Maid?
But don't tell anyone, Thong.
That he will marry Thong.
He doesn't want others to be heartbroken.
And don't let anyone see this ring, Thong.
Please keep it carefully.
Other people will be jealous of Thong if they see it.
I don't want it to be noisy in the house.
Keep it a secret, only the two of us know.
If you don't want Thong to talk about this to anyone
How can Thong be sure?
that you won't give this ring to someone else?
Stay with me
then don't doubt me.
Just listen to whatever you say.
Hey, good baby.
Yes.
Thong will believe you.
Now, let's talk about today.
Regarding Thong's escape,
He wanted Thong to reflect on himself.
What does Thong think?
It's Thong's fault for not trusting him.
It's okay to know what you're doing wrong.
So what should the wrongdoer do?
Thong will punish himself by staying in this room and not going anywhere.
If Thong wanted that, he would agree with Thong.
I don't want to force anyone.
I hope Thong will punish himself quickly.
My talented girl.
Wake up!
What are you doing here?
Then I'll bring you rice to eat.
Being a nanny and a maid at the same time is so annoying.
Can you help me stay still and not cause trouble?
So I don't have to be tired.
Having to worry about your business every day is a burden.
3 kila, maruee, mamie, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae, milae
I ask you something.
Have any of you guys received a ring from Mit?
Who doesn't have it?
And even get married to become his wife.
Secret, only the two of you know.
There, see? No one can get married.
I can't understand him.
Think this method is effective?
Hey, but don't say anything to him.
Just play dumb and pretend to believe him.
Let him be proud of his intelligence.
The better his mood, the nicer he is.
If he knew we were playing tricks on him
then he will lose face and become less kind, do you understand?
Is that all men can do?
Well, what day is today?
The first day you were locked up, you idiot!
What day do I mean, you crazy person!
Some kind of Monday, Tuesday or Wednesday.
I don't have a phone, I'm so locked up that I forget the date.
Monday, you idiot!
Thanks, you slut!
[Monday]
Do you scoop your own rice?
Remember to plug in the power to heat it up.
You woke up late today, where did you go yesterday?
Who are you?
Mom, it's Mont, it's your child.
It made my mother completely startled.
What crazy game are you playing, Mont?
Mom, I'm not playing.
I'm trying out a cool style for acting.
Here, isn't it cool?
What the hell is cool? Looks like a bunch of thieves.
Oh, Mom, you don't understand today's youth.
I'll go first, I'll bring the rice to the dining room, Mom.
So why not eat at the dining table?
What if you bring it to the dining room and then the whole bedroom gets dirty?
Mom.
Mom should knock on the door first.
Mont, what's wrong with your face?
It's nothing mom, it's just a little problem.
Open it for mom to see right away.
This is no longer called a little bit anymore.
What's wrong with you?
Last night the customers at the bar were drunk.
So let's have a little chat with each other.
But it's been resolved, it's okay.
Men and boys are like that, mom, fighting is normal.
Mom, don't make a big deal out of it.
Mom told me before.
Don't work in places like that. It's not good.
It's a gathering place for bad people.
Being drunk will make people lose their morality.
Quit your job and find a better job.
Just like normal people.
Mom, Mont won't talk to you about this anymore.
We're done talking about this.
Mont loves this job.
And Mont won't let anyone force Mont to take time off work.
Let Mont be more careful next time.
Have you gone to the police yet?
What are you doing, mom? The police can't do anything either.
If the police can't help
So who should people rely on?
Either way, I have to go to the police.
At least keep a daily record.
What if they come back to harm me?
Honey, I'm sure
person whose illegal detention you are reporting
and the attacker is Inspector Mit?
Do you have any questions?
You've asked this question over and over again.
Why don't you take the time to search his house?
It takes too much time.
If you can't find anything, come back and get me
for the crime of making false statements.
Don't be impatient, I'm just asking to make sure
that I want to face the consequences, that's all.
This.
Sure, then sign it.
I'll send someone to search.
Thank you, please let me know if you find anything.
Yes, boss.
Thank you.
That kid came to report to arrest Inspector Mit.
Really?
Yeah, who does he think he is?
Mr. Mit, Mr. Mit.
Mr. Mit.
- Are you back? Are you tired? - Mr. Mit.
Mr. Mit, today we are making cookies,
Be busy all day to be successful.
That's right.
Mit, would you like to try it?
If you like, we will make it for you to eat too.
- That's right. - Yes, it looks delicious.
Thank you very much everyone.
So let's put it there, I'll ask permission to go up and see Thong first.
Mr. Mit.
Older brother...
Are you back?
What's wrong with Thong?
Why are you crying?
Thong was alone in the room all day.
Thong is lonely.
But...
It's okay.
Thong will reconsider himself
about the mistakes that Thong did.
Oh, how pitiful, my lover.
Anyway, please quickly realize your mistake.
This will be remembered as a lesson, so as not to make mistakes again.
Thank you for your valuable teaching.
You are a very good thinker,
have maturity.
Thong likes
The times you reminded me to teach me, Thong.
Sure.
Stars on your shoulders
It's not because you're lucky, it's all because of your skills.
You are number one in that class.
Oh, that's great.
Thong is very proud
when you become my wife.
Police uniforms are clothes that all women want to iron.
I hope Thong will be blessed to iron your clothes.
Okay, honey.
So let's go buy something delicious for you to eat.
Thank you.
Thong is happy to be here.
What's wrong? Do you like it?
Just like every time.
I mean Malee is as good as always.
Every time I like it.
How is Thong today? Is there any problem?
Can't you stop caring about Thong for an hour?
You're lying with Malee.
What did you ask her for?
Oh, Malee, because Thong is having problems
So you have to pay special attention to her.
But that doesn't mean he doesn't care about Malee.
I care about Malee no less than Thong.
Want one more?
To feel how much he liked Malee.
Why doesn't Mit come down for breakfast?
Has anyone called him yet?
I called upstairs just now.
Mit is talking to Thong.
Thong, Thong, Thong.
Why are there all Thong's names in this house?
Makes me feel like that's the landlord or my mother.
What's wrong with you?
It's not like you said you wanted it here
so you can take revenge on him? So have you taken revenge on him yet?
Not yet. It just makes me feel uncomfortable.
Just hearing its name makes me nauseous.
Oh, Mit is here.
Thong said he was hungry.
Can you bring rice to Thong?
She wants to drink coconut water too.
Malee. Can I go buy coconut water for Thong?
I have to go to work.
If anything happens, I'll call to check on Thong's situation.
Please go first.
What's wrong with you?
[Monday - First Day]
Wait.
I have something to tell you.
Just seeing your face makes me itch all over.
Who wants to talk to you?
In this lunch box,
Have you quit smoking?
Who wants to quit smoking?
If I quit smoking, Mit will kick me to death.
Yes, that's right.
Because Mit loves me more than you.
Thong.
I told Mit.
[Gaming is illegal]
I'm here, I'm here.
[Playing cards is illegal] See!
Get out of the way so I can sit, get out of the way.
Oh, this one.
Did you get bitten by an ant or something that made you dizzy?
What's wrong with you?
Because of Thong, he made me crazy, but I couldn't do anything to him.
You just wait,
When I find a way to get revenge, you will surely die.
This! Someone go buy coconut water for him, please.
I don't want to be his child.
You.
I'm going to wash the dishes.
I'm going to wash the glasses.
I have a lot of clothes, I'm going to wash them.
I'm going to dry my clothes.
I'm going to iron my clothes.
Ah... I'm going to sew clothes.
Oh! I...
I can't stand it anymore, I'm so sad.
Oh, I'll be back in a bit, I'm about to go crazy.
These bastards have all escaped.
So who will buy it for him now? It's me, no one else.
Hey lady.
Is that you? What did you come here for?
Don't tell me you're coming to help Thong, okay?
That's right, can you help take Thong out?
It's fine to take her to the gate, then I'll take her away.
No one can help it.
And I don't want to help him either, you go home.
Wait, miss.
It's illegal to detain people in a house like that.
That means you support that illegal person, you know?
Breaking the law?
Mr. Mit
is the law. And you quickly go away,
If not, I'll tell Mit to deal with you.
Go or not go?
Miss... Listen to me.
When we meet difficult people
Then we have to help, right?
Because we all have humanity in us.
Stop, don't talk like this, I'm tickled.
I'm not human, I'm a devil.
If you still want to be human
then don't get involved in this.
Otherwise, you will definitely become a ghost.
But if you help her then you will receive that merit.
Yesterday you said you had something to tell me.
Come on, tell me.
You said you didn't want to talk.
So today I want to talk.
What do you want? Talk or not?
I want to tell you...
I just want to say that I'm in this house
No use to you, right?
Mr. Mit took time to pay attention to me
while that time is with you.
And you have to take care of me
Instead, you can stay in peace and comfort.
I'm so touched by this.
Today I talk to you
Because I have a plan to kick you out of the house.
Really?
I'm not hard of hearing, right? Are you willing to help me?
I won't help you.
I just want to get rid of you and get it over with.
You can call it whatever you want. Thank you very much.
You hug me, I get goosebumps.
I have a plan to help you.
Are you going today?
Are not. I will go tomorrow. Friday night.
I jump in the water.
- Illusion. - Let's dance.
What's your swaying position?
Mr. Mit.
Would you like to come play in the water with us?
Oh.
Mr. Mit.
Where are you going, Mit?
Mit, are you angry at Malee?
Mr. Mit.
This.
Except.
I think Mit must be looking for that Thong.
Self-locked, self-remembering, true gangster style.
I can't stand it anymore.
Since I lived in this house,
I only slept with Mit once, guys.
And Thong
Meet morning, noon, and night.
I'm so bored.
Can you hold off a bit?
Tomorrow it will go too.
From now on,
Mr. Mit will be ours,
No need to share with Thong anymore.
You're right.
So are you sure your plan will succeed?
That depends on how smoothly you can act.
Dear Thong.
Wake up.
Mr. Mit.
What's wrong?
Thong once said that
Thong doesn't love Bun,
but Thong loves him.
Right?
That's right.
So that means in this case,
you win, Mr. Bun,
right?
That's right.
But actually,
The detective beat him on everything.
Like the face
also more handsome,
Personality and speaking tone are also more polite.
One more thing is
you are an inspector,
Why are you comparing yourself to a drug dealer?
It's important
that
you are also better than him.
Both in size,
both posture.
Really?
Is Thong telling the truth?
Really.
You are the best.
That's why Thong loves him so much.
I also love Thong very much.
Now Thong understands that
the man in front of Thong
is the best person, right?
No need to look for anyone else in this world anymore.
Yes.
Thong won't go looking for anyone else.
Thong is the only one.
[It's the 7th day]
Eat so you can have strength tonight.
This place probably has enough money for the car.
Thank.
So did you tell the others to prepare?
That said.
Everyone knows the plan, it's just a matter of time.
Except.
I hope it's you and me
won't have to see each other again.
It's a good goodbye.
So I hope this life
You and I don't have to meet again,
Thong.
Guys, it's time.
Get ready.
Hey guys.
Thong is about to run away.
Catch it, don't let it escape.
Hurry up!
Quick, catch it.
Stop, don't run away.
- Catch it. - Let go.
Let me go, let me go...
Don't come here.
Don't come here, guys.
Stay away.
Catch it again.
Let me out.
Let me go, let me go.
You leave me alone.
Thong.
Why are you slapping so hard?
Oh, Thong.
Chase it.
Thong.
You stop right now.
It has escaped.
Thong.
Thong, come back here.
Thong, where are you hiding? Thong...
Don't come here.
Thong.
Oh.
Quickly chase it, it runs away.
Stupid people.
Who opened the door to let it escape?
Ladies, charge up!
Thong.
Thong, come back.
Where is Thong going?
Where are you going?
Thong, come back.
Thong.
There are no cameras here anymore.
Great!
You,
let's go home.
I think so
Now Mit has seen everything through the surveillance camera in the house.
We
certainly not exposed to us
- performed very well. - Acted very well.
Girls, let's go.
Everybody.
The house is taller, right?
Because of Thong
- aggravates the soil. - Heavy soil.
How is that possible?
So many people but can't catch even one person?
Mr. Mit.
She is very strong.
Slap Malee twice.
I see stars flying away.
I wonder what she hid in her bag.
Take a swing,
hit me and was about to fly away.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Fly away. - Fly away.
Then I saw it
How did she escape?
Is anyone coming to pick me up?
She got in a taxi.
We followed.
But
couldn't keep up.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Can't keep up. - Can't keep up.
Hello.
Contact the traffic police for me.
I'm looking for a taxi.
I want to see all the cameras on my street.
Right now.
THE ROSE OF SIN