♪The evening breeze kisses my brows♪
♪Allows a cloud to stay for me♪
♪After a long time,
I still keep looking back♪
♪The sleepless universe accompanies me
as I sleepwalk♪
♪How can we stay together in a mirage♪
♪A vast desert, with no oasis in sight♪
♪Time takes away
the eternity I promised♪
♪Who can have your gentleness♪
♪Who still stays there♪
♪Finally, I silently endure
but cannot be saved♪
♪The sorrow of the world
turns into stars♪
♪Flowing over a few hills
with the moonlight♪
♪I wish to follow behind you
until we grow old♪
♪I will silently wait♪
=Everlasting Longing=
=Episode 24=
Why are you here?
You pretend to be a merchant.
My Lady, don't trust him.
Shao Qimin,
I've just signed a contract with Qiluo.
We'll be working together from now on.
Not now.
Just now, Jiangjuan said
Xiukun has prepared the wedding attire,
waiting for my lady to try it on.
Are you getting married?
Yes.
To whom?
I'll be marrying her
the day after tomorrow.
Please stop bothering us
and leave Yannan as soon as possible.
Why?
I know you haven't let go of me.
We are just business partners.
Who I marry and when I marry
are none of your business.
(Great Blessings)
My Lady,
are you angry with me
for telling Xuan Lie
about our marriage?
He will find out sooner or later.
You still like him, don't you?
That's all past.
Saving Father and reclaiming
the family business is the priority.
Father,
how have you been lately?
Did the King give you a hard time?
Father.
I'm okay. See?
Father!
Father.
I'm so sorry.
Qiluo.
Father,
I brought this upon you
and made us lose our business.
This is not your fault.
Look,
now we're all safe and sound.
That's what matters most.
Father, don't worry.
I'll get everything we lost back.
By the way,
why did the King suddenly
let you back home?
The King said your wedding
is coming up soon,
so he allowed me to return.
Qimin,
I've always wished
for you two to get married.
Get up.
Qiluo has had a hard time before.
Please treat her well from now on.
Don't worry, Master.
I'll protect her for the rest of my life.
Father, Qimin has been
by Qiluo's side all these years,
loyal and devoted to her.
What's there to worry about?
Yes, Father.
After they get married,
they will live in the Jun Mansion.
We can keep an eye on him every day.
Father, look,
this is the wedding dress
Xiukun made for Qiluo.
Isn't it beautiful?
Xiukun's embroidery has really improved.
- Qiluo.
- Impressive.
Try it on.
See if it fits you.
I'm sure it fits since it's your work.
Try it on, come on.
Let's see how you look
in your wedding dress.
Come on, Qiluo. Try it on.
- Do it.
- Let's go.
(Double Happiness)
The first comb through,
the newlyweds honor
each other with grace.
The second comb through,
together they face what's ahead.
The third comb through,
forever they love each other.
Qiluo,
today is your wedding day.
Why aren't you happy at all?
No.
I'm just a bit tired these days.
I thought you changed your mind
and didn't want to marry Qimin.
Of course not.
I need to get changed.
You can wait outside.
I, Xuan Lie,
swear, with heaven and earth as witnesses,
that Jun Qiluo
will be my only wife in this life.
If I break my vow,
I'll suffer eternal damnation.
♪Flowers fall in front of the courtyard♪
Are you happy about
getting married?
♪Longing lingers in my heart♪
♪Memories play dumb♪
What are you doing here?
I came to see
how you marry someone else.
♪Ripples shatter the twilight hues♪
This is my bedroom,
not your backyard.
Please leave now.
♪What I wish to keep, I can't hold on to♪
♪Our love, like a moon
in the mirror, a flower in the water♪
I told you,
you are my only wife in this life.
Don't marry anyone else.
Who I marry is my own choice.
You still love me deep down.
Why can't you just admit it?
Does our relationship
mean nothing to you?
♪As the veil lifts,
our love comes to an end♪
Yes, it's nothing.
♪Scattered far away, with you not there♪
(Jun Mansion) (Wedding Procession)
(Double Happiness)
♪When the dream ends,
stars vanish, and silence falls♪
♪Just let fate fade into the abyss.
What else is there to fear♪
I need to get changed.
Please leave, General.
Don't ruin my big day.
♪As the veil lifts,
our love comes to an end♪
♪Scattered far away♪
♪With you not there♪
Miss Xiukun, Miss Jiangjuan,
the wedding sedan
has been waiting for a long time.
Qiluo, are you ready?
We're going in.
Qiluo, shall we go?
Let's go.
♪We come from a time of chaos♪
♪Our hearts have faded like dust♪
A lifetime of happiness!
Congratulations!
♪Being silent and not confessing♪
Now is the auspicious hour.
The bride enters the sedan.
♪When I decide to hold you in my arms♪
Now is the auspicious hour.
The bride enters the sedan.
♪When you decided to turn around♪
- How...
- Take her hand.
♪Everything would be clear to us♪
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
♪Becomes a shadow in my heart♪
♪Covering my scarred past♪
♪Filling the emptiness
of the past heart♪
♪I want the green, piece by piece♪
♪To fall in my heart
and turn into a star♪
♪Piecing together
the Big Dipper to guard you♪
♪Illuminating the way home♪
(Double Happiness. Wedding Procession)
♪When I decide to hold you in my arms♪
♪I bury all past matters deep inside♪
♪When you decided to turn around♪
♪Everything would be clear to us♪
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
♪Becomes a shadow in my heart♪
Cross over the saddle.
Pass the rice bag.
May you be safe and sound
for generations to come.
A lifetime of happiness!
Congratulations!
♪Piecing together the Big Dipper
to guard you♪
(Fortune and Blessings Gather)
♪Illuminating the way home♪
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
♪Becomes a shadow in my heart♪
Now is the auspicious hour.
Please, newlyweds,
worship heaven and earth.
First bow to heaven and earth.
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
Second bow to the parents.
♪The melody from nearby♪
♪Allows you to camp in my heart♪
Husband and wife bow to each other.
♪Allows you♪
♪To camp in my heart♪
The ceremony is complete.
(Double Happiness)
Qingming.
Why is it you?
You are supposed to be my husband.
Why can't it be me?
Actually, I want to ask you,
how dare you marry someone else
without my permission?
I heard that in Yannan, the newlyweds
will drink cross-cupped wine
after the bridal veil is lifted.
Come on, let's drink it.
It's okay the wine spilled.
I'll get another one.
I don't have time to waste on this.
Tell me,
where is my lady?
or I'll kill you now.
Will you?
You and Xuan Lie
planned this, didn't you?
♪The evening breeze kisses my brow♪
♪Allows a cloud to stay for me♪
♪After a long time,
I still keep looking back♪
Qingming,
we have completed the wedding rites.
In this lifetime,
you can only be mine.
♪A vast desert, with no oasis in sight♪
♪Time takes away
the eternity I promised♪
♪Who can have your gentleness♪
♪Who still stays there♪
♪Finally, I silently endure
but cannot be saved♪
♪The sorrow of the world
is carried away by the wind♪
♪My love turns into a small boat♪
♪Drifting in your eyes,
showing endless longing♪
♪Passing through every night and day♪
♪The sorrow of the world
turns into stars♪
♪Flowing over a few hills
with the moonlight♪
♪I wish to follow behind you
until we grow old♪
♪I will silently wait♪
Qiluo, you're awake.
- Qiluo...
- Let me go.
- I'm going to get married!
- Qiluo.
Let me go.
Go away!
I won't let you marry anyone else.
All you can do is force me.
What else can you do?
Go away! Go away!
Go away...
- Go away...
- Qiluo,
we're outside the city.
We can't go back tonight.
You took me outside the city?
Xuan Lie,
you'll get my family killed.
What do you mean?
Qiluo,
why do you have to marry Shao Qimin?
Qimin is a spy the King
sent to the Jun family.
Our marriage is the King's command.
The King has never trusted us.
If I don't marry Qimin, the King
will be convinced that my family is disloyal.
Then my family will be doomed.
Qiluo,
don't worry.
I'll figure this out.
I'll go back with you tomorrow.
(Jun Mansion)
(Wisdom and Grace)
Xuan Lie,
I knew it was you!
My Lady...
Qimin,
we didn't get married yesterday.
Did they blame you for it?
Why is it so quiet?
You should ask him and Qingkou
to see what they're up to.
Qingkou?
Qingming,
Lie,
you're all back.
Why do you have to marry Shao Qimin
for Miss Jun?
It's just for fun.
Jun Qiluo has disappeared,
so I can take her place.
I don't have to worry about
Qingming running away again.
What do you think of this wedding dress?
Marriage is no joke.
You can't act so recklessly.
What if you regret it?
I'll never regret it.
If Qingming marries someone else,
I'll regret it.
He can only be mine.
So you two got married yesterday,
and no one found out?
Jun Qiluo,
Qingming is mine.
We're married now.
You should keep your distance from him.
My Lady,
it's an accident.
There's nothing between us.
But we completed the rites.
We are married.
It's a pity I didn't marry you in Beixuan.
But I finally married you here,
that is quite good.
Don't try to deny it.
I didn't know you were the bride
until we entered the bridal chamber.
Then I went to find Miss Jun.
We didn't consummate.
So we're not even married!
- You...
- Qingkou.
Marriage is a big deal.
You're acting recklessly.
Who brought you here?
He Jiyao.
- Young Master.
- It's you, isn't it?
Why didn't you stop her?
Lie,
this has nothing to do with him.
No one can stop me
from doing what I want.
Beixuan and Yannan are in peace talks.
If anyone finds out we are in Yannan,
it will cause a huge uproar.
Do you understand?
He Jiyao will escort you
back to Beixuan tomorrow.
No way.
I came here to see Qingming.
I'll go if he comes back with me.
Qingkou!
Lie, aren't you here to see Jun Qiluo?
If you can do this,
why can't I?
Yesterday was an accident,
but we covered it.
Let's think about
how to handle things from here on.
But, My Lady,
our marriage was granted by the King.
I'm afraid...
We'll pretend nothing happened yesterday.
- No way!
- I didn't marry her.
- We're married.
I won't allow you to marry Jun Qiluo.
Xuan Lie,
what right do you have
to boss around here?
Shao Qimin,
I've tolerated you long enough.
Bring it on, then.
Qiluo, are you awake?
Qiluo?
(Peaceful Nation)
Qiluo,
I think I heard some people
talking in your room.
You heard wrong.
Qimin and I were talking about the business.
We've already finished
50,000 bolts of silk with other shops.
The rest need to be made quickly.
Have you been following up on the silk gauze?
Qiluo,
it's your first day after the wedding.
Put aside the business for a moment.
You and Qimin should serve tea to Father
and incense to Mother.
Qiluo,
why are you in the clothes
from before the wedding?
What was that?
Qimin is changing his clothes.
Don't go in yet.
Go do your thing.
I'll go with Qimin
to serve tea to Father.
I have nothing to do right now.
Qiluo,
your hair is also...
By the way,
weren't you going to hire some workers?
But why haven't you found anyone yet?
Workers? I...
I totally forgot about him.
Forgot about whom?
A few days ago, I hired a worker.
We agreed to meet today,
but with so much going on,
I completely forgot.
Qiluo, I have to go.
Go ahead.
Qiluo.
What happened yesterday would be our secret.
Leave here with Qingkou and He Jiyao now.
We leave,
and you two act like a couple?
Qimin and I must be a couple,
or we'll defy the royal decree.
It'll drag my family down.
You can act like a couple,
but you can't share a room.
That's none of your business.
Xuan Lie,
don't push your luck.
Qiluo...
Lie,
leave it to me.
I'll stay here and guard them.
Come here.
I won't interfere with your private life,
but things are getting tense.
Can Qingkou stay at your mansion for now?
Alright, but take them out
as soon as possible.
(Yamen)
Look at him, young and healthy,
yet begging outside the jail.
Take it.
Come on, ma'am.
She's kind, though.
Do you know
how long I've been waiting?
Sorry, I'm late.
I got held up by something.
Why didn't you
come to the mansion to find me?
But you said
you would come and pick me up.
I don't know this place.
How could I dare go by myself?
People even mistook me for a beggar.
Alright.
Now that you'll work for me,
you'll have money and a wife.
I announce, from now on,
you work for the Juns.
Come home with me.
Coming!
Your Majesty,
this is the peace agreement
drafted by Beixuan envoys.
Beixuan will take the lead
in setting up a trading post
in the Uncontrollable.
Every year, we'll pay Beixuan
100,000 taels of silver
and 150,000 bolts of silk
for the development of the trading post.
Your Majesty,
these years, all the taxes have been used
for strengthening border defenses,
and the national treasury has no funds.
Let the envoys negotiate first.
The trading post can make a profit.
The silver and silk
can be considered an investment.
How's Jun Qiluo's wedding going?
Your Majesty,
everything is going smoothly.
Jun Qiluo has been busy
managing the shop.
Nothing seemed off.
We don't have many rules.
Everyone is easy to get along with.
You just need to do your work.
Miss Jiangjuan,
I didn't expect you
to like reading novels.
Yes, do you like them too?
Of course, I even write them.
I'll write one
and show it to you.
Okay.
Miss Jiangjuan,
I've got something urgent that just came up.
Could you please
take these books back by yourself?
I'll come by later to see you.
Where are you going?
Are you backing out
and refusing to work for us?
I'm telling you.
This is a rare opportunity.
You should cherish it.
Of course, I do cherish it.
It's a blessing for you
to offer me this job.
I won't miss this chance.
I'll be right back.
Alright then,
but come back quickly,
and don't run off.
What?
The King of Yannan
betrothed Miss Jun and Shao Qimin,
but Princess Qingkou
married Shao Qimin instead?
While I was gone these past few days,
so much has happened.
Luo Qi,
Qingkou and He Jiyao
are staying at Jun Mansion.
Could you...
get me in there as well?
To protect Qingkou, of course.
Yes,
protecting Princess Qingkou is important.
But Young Master,
you have another reason,
don't you?
I told you. It's to protect Qingkou.
True.
Having Miss Jun and Shao Qimin
under the same roof
is quite annoying.
Keep your identity hidden.
Yes.
Don't trouble the Juns.
See you.
So, he's your fellow townsman,
also here to find a job?
He's De Lie, my fellow townsman,
strong and capable.
He can do any kind of work.
Like me, he only needs
10 wen per month.
You seem to be in good health,
and you look quite sharp.
Unlike Luo Qi,
you have no criminal record.
You can find other jobs.
Why do you choose to work for us?
Luo Qi,
you tell her.
We just arrived in the Royal Capital,
without a penny
or connections.
I'm lucky to have met you, Miss Jiangjuan.
You've been so kind to me,
and gave me this job.
When I left my hometown,
his parents asked me to look after him,
so I bear this responsibility.
Since I work here now,
I have to bring him along.
Miss Jiangjuan,
we are cheap,
but we'll work hard.
Please hire us.
(20 wen for two young
and strong workers,)
(this deal will surely)
(earn Qiluo's praise.)
(Although they don't seem very bright,)
(it would be fine,)
(as long as they can work.)
You poor outsiders,
with no one to turn to.
Alright,
I'll be a good employer
and hire both of you.
Miss Jiangjuan,
I've drafted the contract
and signed your name for you.
Please have a look. Here you are.
Why the rush?
Because...
If you don't hire us today,
we won't have anything to eat.
We're down to our last crumbs here.
Miss Jiangjuan, please take us home.
(Contract)
You two will get 20 wen a month.
If I break the contract
and fire you, I'll pay you...
100 taels of gold?
Life is hard now,
but De Lie and I are both loyal.
Miss Jiangjuan, I know
you need reliable workers.
That way, we can all rest easy.
(Employer: Jun Jiangjuan)
Chancellor,
how could the King let Jun Qiluo,
the Baigong's heir, marry a guard?
I'm sorry, but I have no clue
to get the reasoning behind this.
Jun Qiluo stayed in Beixuan for ages,
and she's so close with the Wolf Lord.
Their relationship is serious.
The King is obviously suspicious,
and he'd question her loyalty.
The only way to calm him down
is for her to marry a Yannan man.
As for whom she marries,
it doesn't matter at all.
Are they the workers you hired?
Yes, Qiluo.
Look at them, they're strong and healthy,
perfect for tough,
heavy, and exhausting work.
Moreover, we only need to pay them
20 wen per month.
We've made a great deal.
What about the penalty fee?
100 taels of gold.
Qiluo, though it's quite expensive,
why would we
fire such cheap workers?
Wouldn't that be foolish?
Jiangjuan, haven't I told you
that unequal contracts
will lead to countless troubles?
How could you sign such a contract?
But Qiluo, you also said
that unequal contracts
can bring huge profits.
We need workers now.
Why not take a gamble?
Is the contract government-approved?
Qingming,
you can only be mine.
Get in.
Didn't I tell you
to stay hidden?
Are you worried
that Qiluo will be in trouble
if people find out
you two aren't married?
Alright,
you have my promise.
I won't let anyone know I'm here.
But you must agree to two things.
First, whenever I blow this whistle,
you must appear,
just like you did in Beixuan.
Second,
from now on, you must do
whatever I ask.
What? You won't agree?
Then I'll just go out there
and walk around.
Maybe I'll visit Jun Qiluo's father.
Remember,
Jun Qiluo must not be seen here.
Also,
I'm hungry.
Who would've thought
the Wolf Lord of Beixuan
would end up
as a servant here in Yannan?
Because you're impressive.
You've made me, the Wolf Lord of Beixuan,
willing to be your servant.
Look, I brought you here
to talk business.
I want to talk about this contract.
Go ahead.
You want to change
the contract in two places.
First, I'd like to
borrow 500 bolts of silk
from the order for another project.
Second, the delivery period
was three months,
I want to extend it by one month.
Any conditions?
Based on the original price,
I'll pay the daily interest
for the extra month.
Since I'm borrowing 500 bolts,
I'll return you all 600 bolts
after four months.
That sounds fair.
Then it's settled.
But honestly,
it's not really appealing to me.
I reject it.
So, what are your conditions?
Lay it out for me.
You should know
what I want by now.
I don't want you living with Shao Qimin.
That's a different thing.
We're discussing business now.
To me, it's the same thing.
Seeing you two living together
makes me want to kill him.
Fine, I agree.
We weren't sharing a bed anyway.
I'll rework the contract.
You keep your word.
There you go.
Now, serve the dishes for me.
I want you to feed me.
If you try to leave again,
I'll go to see Jun Qiluo's father.
I want meat.
I've changed my mind.
Just give me that.
You barely touched anything
since the wedding.
You must be tired and hungry.
Eat it.
Alright, let's have dinner together.
Come on.
Satin for sale!
Don't worry.
This time, I won't let them succeed.
The clothes made by Miss Jun
are truly beautiful.
She seems different after the wedding.
How so?
Her voice sounded quite different.
Miss Qiluo, no rush.
Don't touch me.
You must have misheard.
How could the bride be someone else?
This is ridiculous.
Maybe I misheard.
♪When I decide to hold you in my arms♪
♪I bury all past matters deep inside♪
♪When you decided to turn around♪
♪Everything would be clear to us♪
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
♪Becomes a shadow in my heart♪
♪Covering my scarred past♪
♪Filling my once-empty heart♪
♪I want the green, piece by piece♪
♪To fall in my heart
and turn into a star♪
♪Piecing together the Big Dipper
to guard you♪
♪Illuminating the way home♪
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
♪Becomes a shadow in my heart♪
♪Covering my scarred past♪
♪Filling my once-empty heart♪
♪Then the green, piece by piece♪
♪Will blooming brightly at the borders♪
♪The melody from nearby♪
♪Allows you to camp in my heart♪
♪Allows you♪
♪To camp in my heart♪