20 YEARS AGO
Let's go.
What does it say?
I want you to write down what I say.
No! His Majesty will not
forgive you for this!
Yeong-san!
You don't have much time left
to save his life.
It's a son! You have a son!
Your Majesty!
They committed treason!
Prince Hamyeong and Min Ik-pyeong
invaded the palace
with a group of soldiers!
You must hurry up and escape!
I want you to
protect the Queen and my son.
Your Majesty.
We found a letter written by you
that was on its way to Qing.
We, the vassals,
can no longer serve a traitor
who tried to hand over Joseon
to the barbarians of the West as our king.
You threatened our country's foundation
through your social gatherings
and made the people of this country
live in misery.
Admit your faults and kneel before us.
Let's get this straight.
It's not the letter
that caused you to betray me.
It's because I refused
to listen to the scholar-officials.
I just wanted to give everyone a chance
to learn and do something meaningful.
Just like how I gave people
from undistinguished families a chance
to become government officials,
I am going to do the same
for the peasants and women.
That is what you're guilty of!
You tried to overturn
the strict moral customs of this country!
What good are those customs
when they only allow the privileged
to study academics
and spread their wings?
That is not what this country should...
Jae-gyeong!
-Hurry up and lie him down.
-Okay.
What happened? Who did this?
I made changes to His Majesty's letter.
I don't know what to do now.
Please tell me what to do.
I'll do anything to set things right!
It's not your fault.
They probably planned this
for a very long time.
Teacher.
Please protect Hui-yeon.
You must stay alive.
I am a historian. Please let me in.
His Royal Highness has ordered us
to strictly guard Nokseodang.
Even historians aren't allowed to enter?
-How is this considered "guarding"?
-Your Highness.
FINALE
Lady Hae-ryung.
I was so worried.
A bunch of men dressed in black
barged into our house
and made a mess of your room
and your brother's room.
They work for Min Ik-pyeong.
Are you sure no one got hurt?
Yes. We found a separate place to stay.
Let's go there.
I am scared to even walk outside.
Gak-soe, lead the way
and show me where Jae-gyeong is.
What?
Yi Jin did that?
Yes.
His Royal Highness placed guards
in front of Nokseodang
and forbade Prince Dowon
from leaving the place.
He must've made up his mind.
The Queen Dowager sent you a letter.
Her Majesty has finally picked a date.
My lord.
Hae-ryung.
The person who found the daily record
was Third Inspector Goo's sister?
Yes, I am Goo Hae-ryung, an apprentice
at the Office of Royal Decrees.
Did you read the daily record?
Yes.
However,
I can't tell you what it said.
I can't reveal it to anyone,
including you.
You must think that's your duty
since you're a historian.
However, that daily record
must be revealed to the world.
If we had that,
it wouldn't have taken so long
to achieve what we had planned to do.
If your plan is to set things right
regarding what happened
in the year of gyeongo,
I'd also like to take part.
-Hae-ryung.
-That day,
you two may have lost your teacher.
But I lost my father.
Why do you keep thinking
that I wasn't a victim?
His Royal Highness
refuses to listen to anyone,
and there are soldiers
guarding Nokseodang.
We can no longer guarantee
the safety of Prince Dowon.
If you have a plan,
please share it with me.
Chief Royal Secretary.
Did you really talk to His Majesty?
Yes, he told me that he'll be here.
He should've been here a long time ago.
Why isn't he coming?
Do you think
he's trying to turn his back on us
because things are getting out of hand?
I am not surprised. People have begun
to find out about the dethroned king.
And on top of that,
even the historians have started
to talk about the year of gyeongo.
Officer Min
is the one who started this.
He shouldn't have
brought that petition to the palace.
Hey, watch your mouth.
I will punish
Officer Min myself.
However, the center of all this
is Prince Dowon.
The dethroned king's son is alive.
And that's why the Queen Dowager
and the people of Seoraewon
are continuing to have false hope.
My lord, are you planning to--
There will be a banquet
to celebrate the 20th year of
His Majesty's enthronement.
And before that banquet,
Prince Dowon will vanish soon.
My gosh.
Your Highness, you should eat.
You can't starve yourself
just because you don't feel well.
No, it's okay.
How are things outside?
Well, things are very quiet.
-It's like the calm before the storm.
-What about Hae-ryung? Is she doing okay?
My gosh, I can't believe you're worried
about her even in this situation.
The situation is what makes me worried.
I got confined
just for talking about the incident.
But Hae-ryung
even wrote a petition to His Majesty.
And there's nothing I can do
to keep her safe.
Who's there?
Someone entered this place.
Have you seen anyone?
No, that's impossible.
I can't believe they're going to hold
a banquet despite the current situation.
They should consider what's going on.
His Majesty cares about his face
more than the scriptures of Confucianism.
He's trying to show
that the royal family is doing fine.
I really don't get it.
He always ignores what's important.
The Office of the Inspector-General?
What?
Hey, what brings you here?
Officer Min, step forward.
The Second State Councillor
gave orders to imprison you
for having caused trouble
and rebuked the vassals
merely with a bunch of rumors.
-Take him.
-Yes, my lord.
What? No, wait.
If the petition is the problem,
you can take me instead.
I am the one who wrote that petition.
Officer Min just did
what I asked and read it out loud.
What do you think you're doing?
How can you accuse him like this?
All he did was read the petition out loud.
You can't punish historians
for what they say.
A historian's job is to record history,
not speak of it.
-Move aside.
-We can't do that.
This is obviously a retaliation.
You're trying to shut us up!
That's enough!
Don't cause a scene.
-Stay in your seats.
-Officer Min.
But...
Are you okay?
-Yes.
-How could this happen?
How could they use such an absurd reason
to arrest a historian?
Officer Yang, aren't you
going to do anything?
Didn't you hear who gave that order?
He even arrests his own son.
Anyone who acts out
could literally get killed.
What brings you here?
Chief.
I have a favor to ask.
Your shift's over.
Get to your positions.
Your Highness.
-Hae-ryung.
-Your Highness.
BOOKSTORE
Whose house is this?
You should go inside.
They are waiting for you.
I...
So Baek-seon, the military chief,
am honored to greet the one and only heir
of the royal family.
I served the Queen
ever since she was pregnant with you.
I was there on the day
that you were born.
What kind of person
was my mother?
No one ever told me about her.
She was very wise and benevolent.
She never mistreated anyone
just because they weren't aristocrats.
And she even taught court ladies
how to read and write.
Your Highness.
We have already
passed the point of no return.
We are going to end everything
at the banquet
that's going to be held in a few days.
However, if anything goes wrong,
we'll no longer be able to protect you
by your side. So please--
Don't tell me to stay out of this.
I don't want to be a coward.
It doesn't matter.
You must stay out of this.
The Queen Dowager and I have endured
such a long period of time
just so we could protect you.
No matter what happens,
we must make sure...
that you're safe.
If we don't come back by 7:30 p.m.,
you must leave immediately.
The palace is a mess
because of the daily record and whatnot.
Must we hold a banquet?
If we cancel it last minute,
people will only be more suspicious.
And you must show everyone
that you're still standing strong.
Okay, fine.
Do whatever you want.
There's one thing you must keep in mind.
The royal family and government officials
will be there.
The Queen Dowager might use that day
to her advantage.
Therefore, don't get swayed
regardless of what happens.
What's that supposed to mean?
I am saying
you should accept
whatever I might do to Prince Dowon
and the Queen Dowager.
Prince Dowon is locked up.
He's not even allowed to leave his place.
-What more can you do--
-Everything I do
is for His Majesty and you,
the successor of the royal throne.
My judgement is not wrong.
Please do not forget
that you two can be here now
because of my decision 20 years ago.
What exactly is that duty of mine
that you are speaking of?
Just being the powerless,
weak, pathetic prince
who is confined to his residence?
Yes. That is your duty.
You cannot and should not do anything.
Your Royal Highness.
What brings you all the way here?
Did you read the daily record?
I am not asking you to show it to me.
I just need an answer to one question.
I have to check something.
-Will you not do that for me?
-As you already know,
I did many things
I shouldn't have done as a historian.
But for the first time,
I think I am doing the right thing.
Please wait here.
I wrote down a copy
because Officer Min told me to.
My lord.
What happened?
His Royal Highness set him free.
What are you doing outside?
Can't you fall asleep?
How can I sleep when your room
is right next to mine?
I was just thinking.
"What will happen to me after tomorrow?"
If things don't go well,
please don't move.
If I end up leaving,
I'll need an address to write to.
There's no need.
Wherever you are,
I'll be there with you.
You finally left the palace
and met people who wish to follow you.
So,
I can't let you become all alone again
without having anyone to lean on.
I won't allow that.
I will stay
by your side.
No.
You should live the life you want.
-Your Highness.
-The day I left the palace,
I realized something as I saw you
standing in the garden.
I wasn't locked up in Nokseodang.
I was just waiting for you.
My whole life,
I waited for you
to come and find me.
So it's okay...
even if I must change my name
and keep moving around to run away.
"I am waiting for the day
when I can see her again."
If I think like that,
I can get through anything.
Bow four times!
Bow.
All rise.
This is from all the royal relatives
and senior officials of the royal court.
"Because Your Majesty quelled the rebels
in the year of gyeongo
and protected this kingdom,
this reign of peace could begin.
Hence, all living things on this land
are indebted to Your Majesty.
May Your Majesty
live a long, healthy life
so that you can continue to leave
your mark in history for years to come."
-For years to come.
What are you doing? Get back to your spot.
Your Majesty,
I, Third Inspector Goo Jae-gyeong,
wish to confess to the crime I committed
in the year of gyeongo
and ask you to punish me for what I did.
The dethroned king's secret letter
found at the borders
was fabricated.
Min Ik-pyeong,
who was the Fourth Censor at the time,
ordered me to revise the letter
so that it reads
the dethroned king wishes to sell
Joseon off to foreigners from the West.
The dethroned king
and everyone at Seoraewon
were set up by Min Ik-pyeong.
Here,
I have evidence to prove it.
In this letter, which the French physician
at Seoraewon sent to his brother,
he wrote that the King of Joseon does not
believe in Catholicism and that Seoraewon
is a place where people study
new culture and technology.
Third Inspector Goo,
you must leave at once!
How dare you spew such nonsense
on this happy day?
Your Majesty.
I sincerely beg you.
Second State Councillor Min Ik-pyeong
dared to deceive you,
brought disgrace upon the royal court,
and caused such dishonorable tragedy
that cannot be undone.
Please take his life
along with mine.
Your Majesty,
Third Inspector Goo used to work
at Seoraewon, which makes him a criminal.
He should have been executed 20 years ago.
However, he has managed to stay alive
because he betrayed
his teacher and friends.
Who would believe anything
that comes out of his mouth?
I agree, Your Majesty.
He used to be at Seoraewon.
What more do we need to hear?
He is slandering
the Second State Councillor as well as
all other high-ranking officials.
That's right. He is trying to
drive a wedge between Your Majesty and us
for he is holding a deep grudge
against all of us.
-He must be dragged out at once.
-However,
the fact that he used to work
at Seoraewon is not important--
Be quiet!
Anyone who supports him
will be punished for treason.
Second State Councillor.
Then, go ahead and punish me first
for treason.
If believing that man's words
is considered a crime,
go ahead and take
this old woman's life first!
Are you finally revealing
your true colors?
Second State Councillor!
The Queen Dowager has been in league
with the remnants of Seoraewon
to disseminate The Story of Ho Dam,
exhibiting her disrespect
toward Your Majesty.
She is trying to sabotage me
and Your Majesty
so that Prince Dowon
can ascend the throne.
Until when must I pretend
I know nothing about her plan?
Even at this very moment,
soldiers from the Military Training Corps
are on standby waiting for her orders.
Your Majesty!
Dowon, you should not be here now.
Leave.
I am no longer
Prince Dowon.
I am the son of Yi Gyeom, Prince Huiyeong.
I am Yi Rim.
Dowon!
Shut your mouth!
You have had many chances to kill me
in the past 20 years.
So why is it
that you have kept me alive?
Is it not
because you also know
that the dethronement cannot be justified?
-I told you to shut your mouth!
-Because of your guilt
of killing your innocent brother
and stealing the throne from him,
you have kept me alive until this day.
Such insolence.
How dare you.
All historians must stop writing!
Did you not hear my royal order?
If you do not leave at once,
you will be beheaded right here!
How dare she...
A female historian is disobeying my order?
What are you all waiting for?
Drag that wench out of here!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Even if you slash my throat,
we historians will continue writing.
If I die, one of my fellow historians
will take my place.
If you kill that historian also,
another historian will take his place.
Even if you kill all the historians
on this land
and take all the writing brushes
and paper from us,
you will not be able to stop us.
From mouth to mouth,
from teachers to their pupils,
and from elders to children,
history will be told.
That is...
the power of the truth.
Your Majesty!
We historians
cannot back down.
Your Majesty, they are all traitors.
Please do not hesitate.
Take their lives at once.
-Your Majesty!
-Drop your sword.
Your Majesty.
A truly loyal subject
never tries to blind and deafen the king.
Do you still not see it?
The Second State Councillor
is the one who is trying
to sabotage Your Majesty,
your kingdom, and your people.
He is the one
who is trying to harm you.
Please accept the request
from Prince Dowon and the historians.
If anyone was falsely accused,
please reinstate them.
And if anyone committed a crime,
please punish them.
Find out the truth
behind everything that happened
in the year of gyeongo
through a special investigation committee.
Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Right the wrongs!
-Please, Your Majesty!
-Right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Please right the wrongs!
-Your Majesty!
Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Please!
-Please, Your Majesty!
Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty.
-Please right the wrongs, Your Majesty!
-Please, Your Majesty!
-Please right the wrongs...
You'll have to pour me a drink
at my memorial ceremony every year,
so I suppose
I shouldn't ask you to do it yet.
Did you have to do such a thing?
In my childhood memories,
you were always like a big mountain.
You were never stingy
when it came to books
even though that meant
you had to wear shabby clothes.
You fought against the scholar-officials
with nothing but courage and knowledge.
So why...
What made you...
What made you become like this, Father?
Do you remember?
"U-won.
We scholars must have a clear conscience.
That is our duty as scholars."
You once said that to me.
That is how you taught me.
Right.
When I was young,
I used to hate the scholar-officials.
They monopolized authority
with the highborn nobles
and completely shut the weak
out of opportunities.
However,
once I came into possession
of power myself,
I did not want anyone
to take it away from me.
Power...
is like the Spring of Greed.
You get blinded by your greed
the moment you taste a drop of it.
After all,
I was just one of those
ordinary men.
Nevertheless,
I do not regret the decision I made
in the year of gyeongo.
The dethroned king led the people astray
with the foreigners' teachings
and violated the moral standards.
He was wreaking havoc on this kingdom,
which the former kings and the
wise scholars had worked so hard to build.
Someone had to stop him.
Even if you cannot understand me now,
history will prove
that I made the right decision.
No.
You're wrong.
A new world will come.
Not the world of scholar-officials,
which the former kings
and the scholars built together.
It'll be a world created by the people,
for the people.
Joseon will become such a nation.
That is...
what I will write.
How did it go?
The special investigation
committee's hearings will begin tomorrow.
They are summoning Min Ik-pyeong
as well as everyone else
who partook in the dethronement process.
I've submitted
Officer Kim Il-mok's records
to the special investigation committee.
-Hae-ryung.
-I know
that you must be
so relieved now.
But please don't expect me
to act like I am okay.
I am barely managing to hold it all in.
I did not
choose to take care of you
because of guilt.
To me,
you have always been...
my sister.
I will
always be your sister.
Goo Jae-gyeong's sister,
Goo Hae-ryung.
You silly goose.
His Majesty said he will
leave everything in your hands.
I see.
Everyone who was involved in it,
including Min Ik-pyeong,
will receive the punishment they deserve.
As soon as the investigation is completed,
I will
step down as the Crown Prince.
I hope you won't resent me too much.
I won't, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I will leave.
No,
you need to hear this too.
Your Majesty,
please dethrone me as a prince.
-Dowon.
-I am aware that you have wished
for me to ascend the throne
for a long time.
However, that is not where I belong.
What do you mean?
You are the only son of the former king.
That is where you should be.
Even the times that I've lived as a prince
was too much for me to handle.
Instead of living the life expected of me
as someone's son, I now wish to live...
as an ordinary man,
as myself.
That is not what your fate
has in store for you.
You were born to be
the King of this country.
I do not
wish to live such a life.
You ought to do it
even if you do not want to.
The beginning
is always the hardest for everyone.
However, if you just
get through that stage,
you will become a sage king
whom everyone greatly admires.
I will assist you
to the best of my ability.
NOKSEODANG
-How did it go?
-Not well.
I think the Queen Dowager
needs more time to accept it.
What about you?
Are you ready
to leave Nokseodang?
NOKSEODANG
Yes.
It's not like
I'll forget all the memories of this place
once I leave.
Let's think of it as turning a page.
This isn't the end.
A new chapter will begin.
All right.
3 YEARS LATER
Oh, dear.
Hey, Yang!
Hey, Yang. Bang, bang!
Keep that up,
and I'll punch you real hard.
Hey, come on.
We are all seventh-rank officers.
Ease up, please.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Hey, clerks.
Finish it by three o'clock.
We are no longer clerks.
We are administrators now.
The junior ninth rank!
His Majesty gave us the rank long ago.
Why are you still calling us "clerks"?
Hey, it's not even that much better
than being a clerk.
It's very different.
There's a huge difference, okay?
Don't ever forget.
We were the ones who pulled all-nighters
and got all the work done
when you senior officers were swamped
because the Annals Compilation Committee
for both the former king
and the king before him was formed.
I am just speechless.
That little...
Until when will they go on about that?
For the next 500 years, probably.
-Officer Yang.
-Yes?
Do you have complaints?
Want some?
That rice cake won't do.
I found acorns.
-Well done. Put them down here.
-The footsteps...
Sa-hui.
Something else came for you
from the palace.
Oh, boy.
Who keeps sending you these things?
ELEMENTARY LEARNING
MYUNGSHIMBOGAM
I can finally take off
this mourning dress.
Who knew three years would feel this long?
U-hui.
What?
I am no longer married
to the Crown Prince.
I don't have to watch what I say.
Just a moment.
First Historian Min U-won.
OFFICE OF ROYAL DECREES
His Majesty has ordered you to return.
Let's go!
I suppose we still have a long way to go.
Petitions pour in like this
every time Seoraewon is brought up.
It is a lot less compared
to what we received last month.
Well, I should be able to respond to
all of them in about three to four days.
Please do not overwork yourself.
It is not something
we can achieve quickly.
That is why I am doing my best
to persuade everyone, one by one.
Seoraewon should be more
than just our dream.
Another letter came for you
from the royal villa.
I told him that I will never forgive him.
He is truly persistent.
Any word from Eunuch Heo?
He will return to Hanyang today.
All we do is pack and unpack,
travel on ships and horses.
-What an ordeal.
-That's what I am saying.
Had I known this,
I would've just stayed at the palace.
I won't come back tonight,
so don't wait for me.
My lord! You're going to that house again?
Don't wait for me.
Goo Hae-ryung.
Goo Hae-ryung!
When did you get here?
Sir.
I had a lot of work to do,
and I even had dinner with my colleagues,
so I am exhausted right now.
So can't you
just come back tomorrow?
I missed you like crazy
during the whole month
that I was away from Hanyang.
What? Tomorrow?
Well, it's not like I didn't miss you.
Do you know how many times
I saw you in my dream...
You had dreams about me? Tell me.
In your dreams,
-what were we doing?
-Well, you know.
I dreamed about how we saw those flowers
on our trip to Jeju Island.
Tell me about your trip.
What did you see on this trip?
I saw dolphins in the Yangtze River.
-Dolphins?
-Yes.
They were swimming in big pods
right in front of my boat.
It was such a beautiful sight.
They are as big as calves,
but their skin looks very shiny.
And they have pointy beaks.
Tell me more.
Any other interesting stories?
What else...
Actually, no. If you're curious,
buy my book and read all about it.
Don't be so petty.
At least you should buy my book.
I heard that only 12 copies
of the other travelogue I wrote
were sold in the entire Hanyang so far.
Anyway, you should get some rest, then.
I won't...
bother you.
I'll get going, then.
I am leaving.
Sir.
Lock the door, please.
Hurry.
Oh, dear.
They practically live together.
Why won't they get married?
I just don't get it.
They'll get married when they want to.
Right, how could such an old man like you
understand our generation?
"Our generation"?
You and I are around the same age.
Don't talk as if you're around their age.
We are around the same age?
Had you been born a few years earlier,
I would've had to call you
my ancestor. And what?
You're so funny.
It's the funniest joke
I've heard all year, seriously.
-Goodness.
-It's so hilarious.
That wench.
Why is it that
I just can't grow fond of her?
I am sure Seol-geum
isn't exactly fond of you either.
You little...
Hae-ryung, it's six o'clock.
You have to go to work.
It's six o'clock.
What? Did you forget something?
No.
This way, I can start my day off right.
See you later.
All right, have a good day.
-I am a historian.
-Stop.
Seriously.
It's been three years.
Shouldn't you remember my face by now?
I work at the Office of Royal Decrees.
Historian Goo Hae-ryung.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
ROOKIE HISTORIAN GOO HAE-RYUNG