♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my only light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ My light ♫
♫ You are my unique light ♫
[The Secret of Love]
[Episode 4]
Dominating the top 3 trending topics.
You two are blowing up bigger than celebrities.
What a fellow! Are CEO Li and Su Yi compatible?
Quickly!
The crowd of reporters that gathered early this morning still haven't left.
and your grandfather hears about this, then I'm afraid–
Feilin, I really can't leave right now.
I...
I don't have time.
In a minute, when Li Jiashang comes down and walks to his car, rush to him quickly, okay?
What if he doesn't hug me?
Of course, he won't hug you! Aren't you going to initiate the hug?
As soon as you see him, rush to him. Kiss him, touch him, anything is fine.
Create any kind of physical contact with him, okay?
Then I can take the picture! You understand?
Do you even want to make money?
I asked you to touch him, not touch me.
We meet again.
About hindering my interviewing last time,
Tao Feilin told you to do it, right?
Tao Feilin? Who's that? I don't know her.
Stop acting. There is a photo of the two of you together in your wallet.
Impossible! My photo with her is here—
Today, she instigated you again?
Tao Feilin likes Li Jiashang, right?
And you like her?
I just want her to give up.
How about this?
If you don't want Tao Feilin to find out about what happened today,
you help me with one thing.
The last compensatory payment was not a small amount.
The circulating capital is hard pressed.
It seems that this will decrease investment into supply.
As of now,
- the only problem is—
- There is a lack of supply of raw material.
Absolutely right. Lin Zi Group took most of the raw materials.
The most they can give us is 20 percent of the shipment.
Lin Zi Group, as a major cosmetics company for young people,
it's normal for them to play some tricks on the materials supply.
In any case, strive for increasing the raw materials supply once more.
By whatever means you use. This cannot affect our first batch of production.
You don't need to worry about funding. I'll take care of it.
Getting close to Li Jiashang is very important to me, you must not drop the ball.
Are they on their way?
You don't need to worry about my work.
They are professional acrobatic fighting stunt doubles, I guarantee it'll look real.
Then when is Li Jiashang coming down?
According to my informer,
if nothing especially important comes up, he should be down soon.
Then you should hurry your people.
Oh, that's right. Why are they not here yet?
No need. They're here.
Not bad, not bad. Five-star rating.
- Hello teachers.
- Who are you?
I am the person who asked for you guys. We are in a rush today,
so thanks for the hard work, teachers, but let's skip the introductions.
Let's run through the scene quickly.
What? You're not here yet?!
In a minute, when Li Jiashang comes down, start hitting him once you spot him.
But remember to be gentle. You must not actually hit him.
- No, you—
- Let me run through the scene first.
And then, when the fight becomes unstoppable,
I will suddenly appear on the scene and shout loudly, bringing you all to the ground.
Beauty saves the hero, the scene is done.
What nonsense! Why are you so wordy?!
This emotion is perfect.
Perfect my foot!
Leave, quickly!
Boss, it's him!
Hit him!
Sorry, sorry. The people I recruited went to the wrong place.
These people are for real.
Then why are you in a daze? Call the police quickly!
- Take a photo first.
- You're still taking photos in this situation?
For evidence.
Hey! You can't go, it's too dangerous!
Hey, Su Yi! Be careful!
Are you all right?
Don't come near. If you have something to say, talk nicely.
If you keep coming, I will call the police.
Call the police? Call!
You want to play hero saves the beauty? No one can run away today!
Play the sneaky trick?! I'll let you!
Halt! Don't move!
Halt!
Don't move!
- Are you all right?
- Halt!
I'm okay. Catch the yellow hair.
Don't worry.
Are you all right?
You're really loyal.
I hollered for the security here.
Five-star rating.
[Lee Group]
Were you scared just now?
Thank you.
Does your back hurt?
My back is fine.
Do you have a first-aid kit?
- Come here.
- I'm fine.
Don't move.
Endure it.
Su Yi.
Is this okay?
As long as you want it.
Tomorrow night, 7:00 p.m.
I'll pick you up.
Interview time.
Why were you there just now?
You know, CEO Li, that I'm here to interview.
Are you really not Mu Xiao?
Mu Xiao?
Who's that?
Miss Su, do as you please.
Tell me. Li Jiasheng and Mu Xiao,
what's their relationship?
Could it be the love debt you owed in the past?
Stop speculating.
But I'm also really curious.
Is this Li Jiashang a friend or foe?
He looks like a gentleman to me.
Didn't he help you cover your dress?
You might know the person's appearance but not his heart.
It's too dangerous to reveal my identity now.
- Yangyang?
- Yes?
When my father died in that car accident, did he abscond to avoid punishment?
Perhaps, only Chu Mo can give me the answer.
[Received mystery package 2016 | 2021 Ming Xiu Publisher | New Reporter Chu Mo]
Hence, I need to take down this show and gain a firm foothold in Ming Xiu.
Until the fog is cleared,
I must hide Mu Xiao's identity.
What did you find at Ming Xiu?
Ming Xiu started as a news magazine.
But since Oct 2014,
it transformed into a fashion magazine.
The missing September issue
that I received, is exactly the one about the car accident.
[FAME SHOW | Ming Xiu, 2014 September]
I asked my colleagues at work.
All printed and electronic editions of that issue disappeared.
However, this proves that
our guesses are in the right direction.
Keep on waiting. Chu Mo will eventually come back.
But I don't want to just sit and wait. It will be too passive.
Li Jiashang. If he knows Mu Xiao,
then he should know something about what happened that year,
including your lost memories.
In our search to find the truth,
he is the next best option for Chu Mo for that time period.
You are...
Takes initiative with the combination of knowledge and actions.
Let's make a deal.
Help me with one more thing.
No. I say. Why do you keep coming?
I haven't settled the past score with you yet.
Fine.
As long as it's not a fight, you can name it.
Don't ask for the reason. Help me to find the old issue of Ming Xiu Magazine, September 2014.
This small request shouldn't be difficult for you.
Fine.
As long as you don't pursue this.
Deal.
You suspect Zhang Mingda, but we don't have the evidence. We can't do anything to him.
In any case, I won't give this matter a rest.
It's the same for him. It's just more troublesome.
I can't have bodyguards with me everyday.
I will find someone to beat him up too.
I don't do such awful things.
Why don't we go boxing tomorrow to vent your anger?
No thanks. Tomorrow I'm visiting my alma mater.
[Library]
What are you doing here?
Do you not even rest on Sundays?
The Dean asked me for a favor.
Join me for a walk?
CEO Li, you majored in business for your undergrad, right?
Biological engineering.
I only started studying business when I studied abroad.
- Then why would you—
- Milk was picked up here.
♫ He knows you more than I do ♫
♫ But how do I extricate myself from this ♫
[N106, Multimedia Classroom]
♫ I can't see through, I can't let go♫
This is our old classroom.
♫ I can only be controlled silently by the emotions♫
♫ I love you more than he does ♫
♫ I can only miss the sweet dream of you ♫
♫ I wish you a good life ♫
♫ I understand. I won't reveal it ♫
What's wrong?
Nothing. Let's go.
Is there anything you want to know?
What?
Didn't you want to interview me?
Let's start then.
What's your biggest challenge after becoming the CEO?
How is it different after taking over Lee Group?
To the whole...
Your questions don't evoke my desire to answer them.
CEO Li, I still have to report back.
Such superficial and empty words can be easily found on the internet.
Do you want me to teach you how to plagiarize?
You can teach me.
Are these the only questions you really want to ask me?
I would like to ask
about your college life. Did you date someone?
When I was in college,
I really liked a professor who taught biology.
She's an elder who loves arts and culture.
After the last class ended, she told everyone,
"Happiness often comes from leisure".
As long as you are willing to spend time
to watch how a leaf falls,
how a snowflake floats,
how a wind blows,
just like this moment.
However, only when your weekdays are full enough,
the meaning of leisure can be more prominent.
It's cold here. Let's leave.
♫ Not all contacts are lost ♫
♫ Coincidentally, become insincere ♫
♫ We can be each other’s audience ♫
♫ The hug at the end, only start with no end ♫
Sorry, CEO Li. I left home in a hurry and didn't take my breakfast.
My blood sugar is rather low.
Follow me.
- Two bowls of noodles, Boss.
- Okay.
Lee Group invests in the food business too?
I like hot food.
Your noodles are here.
Eat them while they are hot.
- Thank you.
- Your noodles.
You both look familiar. You graduated a long time ago, right?
I remember you both used to dine here at least three times a week.
You probably have children now, right? Take your time to eat.
Don't mind him. I used to come here frequently with her.
Is she very important to you?
You really look like her.
Oh right, CEO Li. There are still some personal questions.
Let's talk while we eat.
What expectations did your parents have for you?
Change the question.
- Then, what is the most tragic thing you've experienced?
- Change.
How many relationships have you been in?
Sorry, CEO Li. I forgot to start the recording.
My parents passed away early, so I don't know what their biggest expectation was.
The most tragic thing was losing the most important person.
Relationship, once.
My biggest wish
is for her to return.
Are you satisfied?
- That's enough.
- What else do you want to ask?
That's it.
CEO Li, I'll go back first.
Oh right.
This is for you.
Even the surveillance cameras couldn't capture such a cunning angle.
How did you get it?
You haven't washed your hands.
The magazine is a bit difficult since they didn't officially publish it.
But I found out some other big news,
you should be interested.
A secret.
Thank you.
Su Yi.
CEO Li, do you need anything else?
Rest early.
Good night.
- Hello.
- Sorry.
But seeing you does not make me happy at all.
My sister has me to take care of her, there's no need for you!
Little kid.
Acting like this will give adults a lot of stress.
Also, your relationship with your sister exceeds the boundaries that siblings should have.
We are not blood-related siblings, anyways!
Hello?
I see. I'll go back right away.
Hey.
You're very tall.
Help me investigate Su Yi's growing experience and her life before university.
Also, check her neighbors too.
Big sister, come quickly.
- It smells so good.
- That's right.
Big sister, men actually understand men the most.
Let me tell you, no men are good!
That's in their genes.
Is our little Xiangtai like that too?
I'm definitely not.
At least not towards you.
Be honest. Do you want to buy new sneakers?
No, my hair is messed up!
Okay, okay.
I knows that you care for me the most.
But who knows when you will bring home a sister-in-law, and show filial respect to me together.
Give up on that wish.
You won't have a sister-in-law.
Could it be... that you actually like...
men?
I'm ending this conversation.
You're blushing!
Just eat!
It's not a big deal. I can handle the parents.
Do you think I'm not aware that they are embezzling?
They are old buddies who have been with me for decades.
The current development of Lee Group is not due to a single person's efforts.
If you fire them like this, how can we convince the others?
Do you know that
I was attacked by a group of men in my own parkade two days ago?
What?
Who would dare do such a thing?
How do you plan to deal with it?
It depends on what you think.
By doing this, Old Zhang has really gone to the extreme.
However, after all...
Seems like you still don't want to bring this into the light.
I can promise you that but, from now on,
you can't interfere in my decisions at Lee Group.
I've already given you full authority regarding the company matters.
But you need to remember
that everything must be done in the full interests of Lee Group.
Don't be confused by those young girls.
[Mu Xiao]
Relationship, once.
[First love]
[Li Jiashang, First Love, Mu Xiao]
My biggest wish is for her to return.
[Laboratory (1)]
♫ The time to catch up with a dream ♫
♫ Since then become a hurry ♫
♫ It's still moving forward ♫
♫ No longer being gently side by side ♫
♫ Not all contacts are lost ♫
♫ Coincidentally, become insincere ♫
♫ We can be each other’s audience ♫
The hug at the end, only start with no end ♫
♫ My tightly held stubbornness, feelings are all gone ♫
♫ Your unintentional words make my roar ♫
♫ Say less comforting words will make me better ♫
♫ If you still love me, don’t say it out ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to sing this love song ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to wish you happy ♫
♫ Distance has made our photo faded ♫
♫ My heart is still hot ♫
♫ The seasons have changed ♫
♫ How many people left to make my heart beat? ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing I disqualified by loving too much ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing our distance is like a galaxy ♫
♫ On the travelling train ♫
♫ You first get off ♫
♫ Only leave the time to heal with me  ♫