♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my only light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ My light ♫
♫ You are my unique light♫
[The Secret of Love]
[Episode 20]
Xiangtai is not here these days. I'm afraid that you might get nightmares.
You can stay in my guest room in the meantime.
Is Milk losing weight?
No, I think it just misses you.
These are...
I bought them for us.
It's so good to be your tenant.
You prepared so many necessities.
If the rent is too high, I won't be able to afford it.
I saw Zheng He purchase some, so I did as well.
Just in case.
What? You don't like them?
No, I was just surprised.
My boy has been enlightened so quickly.
I remember when we first dated, I tried to get a step closer to you,
you blushed so much.
You dare to say this again.
Jiashang, when you look at this painting now,
what do you feel?
Danger
and desire.
Is that so?
How come I see
hope?
Jiashang!
You have these kind of clothes?
I am a normal boy too.
Seems like Luo Manni was right.
Men only grow older but never grow up.
We can be each other's little friend and play together, isn't it great?
Okay.
Then what does this little boy want to play?
I've been dreaming about something for a long time.
Especially after moving in with you.
Something I want to do most.
Is that so?
This is what you wanted to do most?
Yeah.
Before, it was just me, now we can do it together.
Isn't it nice?
What?
Who said she couldn't sleep well in a strange bed last night?
So fragrant.
Alright, I need to go find Zheng Yi.
Try to see if there is any news about the autopsy and body donors.
You changed the channel way too fast.
Dating isn't the only thing on my mind.
Then I'll drop you off later.
Then pick you up.
Director Zheng.
Why are you here?
Then, let's talk in my office.
Actually, let's talk outside.
Su Yi.
The Li Mu Research Institute you just mentioned,
the car accident, the autopsy,
I have never even heard of them,
and I don't understand.
Hope in the future,
you won't ask me about these again.
Director Zheng, do you know why I didn't want to talk to you in your office?
[Save lives and help the injured]
[Documents]
Seems like I can't hide the truth any longer.
Actually, I kind of knew Director Zheng would react like this.
People who really don't understand will be curious,
and wouldn't deny this quickly.
Zheng Yi is our only lead now.
Hello?
I'm not hungry.
I will come out soon.
You didn't tell him about the recording yet?
I don't know why I'm worrying.
Actually waiting is a good thing.
Just enjoy your couple's life for now.
Okay, you should go back to work.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Sorry for the wait.
What to do?
I feel so bad even when you just leave me for a second.
What to do? I find that every day you become more "He-like".
(T/N : she means he is becoming like Zheng He)
Lotus flower? What does that mean?
(T/N: a pun of "He-hua/He-like")
"He-like". Becoming more like a glib-tongued Zheng He.
What does that have to do with him?
It's because Vice President Su is good at her job.
Oh yeah, what did Zheng Yi say?
That's all right, we'll think of a way.
Jiashang, about suspecting Zheng Yi,
and us contacting Zheng Yi, don't tell Zheng He for now.
In the recording—
Actually waiting is a good thing.
Just enjoy your couple life for now.
That recording is worthless.
Lately there hasn't been any progress.
It is alright.
You have me, I'll help you think of a way.
Let's go.
Milk? Milk?
What's wrong?
Milk is missing.
It isn't in the bedroom.
Let's split up and look for it.
Milk?
It doesn't sleep in the bed anymore.
Milk...
maybe it's time.
Milk.
You are such a strong cat.
Let's take a picture together.
Go.
[Zheng Yi : Let's meet, tomorrow at 3pm.]
When I first saw Milk at your house,
it felt so familiar.
Although I didn't have my past memories,
it was like muscle memory.
Too bad that
the time spent with it was too short.
We only gave it our free time,
but it gave us its life.
♫  The room is empty  ♫
♫  The sky is sunny  ♫
Jiashang, I will miss it.
♫  The heavy past ♫
♫  My intuition ♫
Let's not get another cat from now on.
♫  I'm not considered special  ♫
♫  Perhaps it is a kind of test  ♫
♫  The day and the night  ♫
Let's go meet with Zheng Yi.
Hello. Did you go boxing?
Did you finish the report?
Almost done, what are you doing now?
I'm not available.
Not available? Not available. You should have said so sooner.
Okay, I got it. I'm hanging up now.
What is it? How's mom?
What do you mean?
If you can't even save your own wife, what kind of a doctor are you?
She runs the house, big or small, and takes care of Grandfather, Grandmother, and me.
She has been sick for a few years and yet you didn't notice.
Now you finally show up, you don't deserve to be a doctor!
You don't deserve to be a father!
How about you certify me as well?
If I die, no one will be a burden to you.
You can keep being a good doctor, a good director.
Son.
In this life I tried to be a benevolent and good doctor,
but my past mistake keeps haunting me.
All of my regrets,
force me to live in hell everyday.
Zheng He, I'm sorry.
Please forgive your dad's selfishness.
All good and bad,
I will take responsibility for them.
Son, this is your present for your 18th birthday.
Who uses a fountain pen anymore?
You rascal, you have no patience at all for whatever you do.
Gifting you a fountain pen is to train your patience.
Step back, step back.
Don't look, stay back.
Please, step back.
Yangyang.
This is...
Director Zheng, he...
fell off the building.
Su Yi.
[Ocean City Police: Third Team]
From the investigation, it's true that your father committed suicide,
but we will continue to investigate the cause of death.
Zheng He.
Can you turn off the light? Thanks.
Call Director Zheng over.
Director Zheng requested leave. Do you want me to come over?
No, it's fine.
Make sure Director Zheng's leave is paid for.
Alright, CEO Li.
Jiashang.
Zheng He still hasn't come in yet? Yangyang said he went out.
I plan to go look for him.
I'll go with you.
A'Shang.
I don't have a dad anymore.
It was so sudden.
I was not prepared at all.
Why didn't I spend more time with him?
Even just...
To respond to a text message.
Just one would have been fine.
Then he wouldn't have...
I thought we still had time.
I don't even know what he was doing at that time.
I understand how you feel.
I don't have any family left now.
Zheng He!
You forgot what you said before,
in front of this and your dad?
You rascal, I'll overlook how you disobey my words,
but every human has to have affection and loyalty.
I don't need you to tell me,
I will treat Yangyang like family, and treat her well for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry, I didn't know it would become like this.
The Merchant Department focuses on the execution of all merchant projects,
and plans for merchant activities.
The Marketing Department focuses on market research and sales,
strategies and advertisements.
Director Zheng's spot is over here.
Please continue.
The Marketing Department focuses on market research,
sales, strategies and advertisement management etc.
The overall direction is confirmed, what do you think, Director Zheng?
I don't manage these sections.
Director Zheng is right. From now on, report those things to me directly.
If there's nothing else, let's end the meeting here.
You just returned and asked to be in this big meeting. Do you need to rest for a few more days?
I will get over it, I'm not that weak.
There are a few high positions in the company that needs to be filled.
You were filling in for me before, why don't you do this for a few more days?
The new staff will be coming.
[Secretary Jiang]
Hello.
The last person Director Zheng contacted was Chairman Li,
but Chairman Li's phone was with me the whole time.
All the notices I saw were unanswered calls.
You always do things like this!
CEO Li, Chairman Li...
I know you did not come for me.
You are conflicted and want to ask for your friend.
Jiashang, this is a human life at stake,
I can't lie.
Why did I call him?
Besides some medical issues,
what other reason could there be?
Grandpa, I didn't suspect you at all.
Then, you come to find me for another thing?
Jiashang, you must remember.
I spent my whole life building Lee Group.
I don't think you should suspect me in any way.
Go work. I'm going to rest.
CEO Li, please.
[Storage]
[Lee Group]
You're here. I'm not used to you knocking on the door.
What is the matter?
Zheng He, I talked to Grandpa.
You don't need to explain.
If I didn't trust Chairman Li, I wouldn't have come back to work.
But such a big thing happened,
it's impossible for me to remain the same, right?
Zheng He, we have been friends for so many years. You can directly say what's on your mind.
Actually, my father's last message
was sent to Su Yi to meet with her, and it just happened at that time.
I really don't know, when they became this close.
Or are there any questions regarding the new products?
But I saw in the news how both you and Su Yi were there.
Jiashang, although I look simple-minded,
I understand it all in my heart.
I have been telling myself that I overthink.
It has to be that I overthink. So you tell me.
Have I been overthinking or not?
That day, Su Yi and I were at the pet clinic,
we have our alibi.
Afterward, we went to see Uncle Zheng. It was only for business.
I even took her there.
Then let me ask you once more.
Are there other things you are hiding from me?
No.
Good brother, if you say so, I will trust you.
[Su Yi]
- Hello?
- Jiashang.
Zheng He is staying at his father's house today. I'm going to stay with Yangyang.
All right.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Also, the things we kept from Zheng He,
I feel a little guilty and worried.
Don't worry. I'll find a time to explain to him properly.
CEO Li! There's been a big problem, go look at the news.
[Lee Group "Secret" product line contains harmful preservatives.]
[It's for everyday use, how could it be harmful?]
[How could Lee Group be like that?]
♫ The time to catch up with a dream ♫
♫ Since then become a hurry ♫
♫ It's still moving forward ♫
♫ No longer being gently side by side ♫
♫ Not all contacts are lost ♫
♫ Coincidentally, become insincere ♫
♫ We can be each other’s audience ♫
♫ The hug at the end, only start with no end ♫
♫ My tightly held stubbornness, feelings are all gone ♫
♫ Your unintentional words make my roar ♫
♫ Say less comforting words will make me better ♫
♫ If you still love me, don’t say it out ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to sing this love song ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to wish you happy ♫
♫ Distance has made our photo faded ♫
♫ My heart is still hot ♫
♫ The seasons have changed, How many people
left to make my heart beat? ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing I was disqualified
by loving too much ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing our distance is like a galaxy ♫
♫ On the travelling train ♫
♫ You first get off ♫
♫ Only leave the time to heal with me  ♫