♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my only light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explain the future to me ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ My light ♫
♫ You are my unique light ♫
[The Secret of Love]
[Episode 16]
[Secret]
Hurry. Let's go to the hospital.
[Inpatient]
The Chairman has had a momentary increase in blood pressure.
However, he needs to be under observation for two to three days.
My apologies. It's not convenient for him to see you now.
Jishang,
are we the cause?
We are not. Stop overthinking.
I will stay here to keep Grandpa company. Why don't you go back now?
It's fine. I want to be with you.
Okay. Wait for me, I'm going to buy some stuff.
Shocking news. Scarface nemesis Su Yi is the victim.
For the sake of the overbearing CEO, she shouldered everything.
Today is another day to shed tears for love.
The person who spread this rumor must be jealous, right?
With a distorted mind.
How exaggerated.
Mu Xiao.
Chairman Gao,
w-what did you say?
Miss Su, sorry.
I recognized the wrong person.
Su Yi, welcome to Lee Group.
Ever since I switched off the Love Rival filter against you,
I'm beginning to find you more likable.
- Sister Manni—
- Don't.
Please don't call me that.
I will be your younger brother's wife in the future.
Fine.
Do you know the face is full of collagen?
So smooth and elastic.
- Manager Su, Manager Luo. There's something urgent!
- Slow down and speak.
The lead cast, Gu Sha, whom we booked for the commercial, wants to break her contract.
What?
Aren't we supposed to sign the contract soon?
It's fine. I will go.
I had several dealings with her agent.
Director Zhou, please review the contract again,
and check if there are any problems.
My apologies. We really don't have a schedule for this for these days.
I think Lin Zi Group must have grabbed your schedule, right?
Lin Zi Group is offering three times more than your company.
Our company has to consider the problem of realization too.
Realization can be a gain or loss.
Lin Zhi has always worked on a one-time collaboration,
they always change their ambassadors based on their popularity.
However, if you collaborate with Lee Group, we can improve Teacher Gu Sha's reputation and value.
It will allow you to have more choices for future business.
Moreover, your company doesn't only have one artist, right?
Lee Group has many high end products.
Then... let's reconsider this.
I believe that your choice
will be the same as ours.
Hello, Chairman Gao. I'm Gu Sha's agent.
We have adjusted the schedule for Lin Zhi's commercial.
You are here.
Take a seat and let's meditate together.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
- About that, we—
- Breathe in!
The posture
must be flexible.
Keep the balance
and keep exercising.
Chairman Gao.
Can we talk about what we last discussed?
- Fine.
- Next time,
why don't we sing and chat?
I prefer singing.
When you have the time, you must exercise more.
Alright. I will.
♪ Because I ♪
♪ didn't know ♪
I bumped into Uncle two days ago at the hospital.
Uncle? Does he deserve it?
No matter what, he's still a member of Lee family.
I have been overseas.
Regarding the relationship between you and your uncle...
I know why Grandpa wants me to stop launching the new products.
He wants to leave some market share to Lin Zhi Group.
- But Uncle—
- Older Sister.
- Gao Mu's mother–
- Manager Su, let's prepare for the meeting.
Alright.
Mu Xiao.
W-What did you say?
Sorry. I recognized the wrong person.
I have been looking for you the whole day.
Thanks.
You are here staring out into the distance.
Still angry?
In your eyes, am I such a petty person?
Enough.
I have a welcome gift for you on joining Lee Group.
Flowers again? They're really not practical.
I will even need to see them wither.
CEO Li bought a new toy again?
For you.
It's such an expensive gift. I won't accept.
It's the company's asset on loan for your usage.
Don't tell me you don't have a driving license.
Of course, I do.
You have a driver's license but you can't drive.
I was a racer at Waseda. Just wait and see.
This is not Japan.
There are flat shoes in the car. Don't forget to change into them.
Don't be nervous.
Turn right ahead. There's less traffic there.
Jiashang, help me to check if there are any cars on the right?
Switch on your right turn signal.
That one.
Here.
Brake!
Hit the brake!
Are you okay?
You...
Have you been overheated again lately?
I'm going to check the car.
It's okay, as long as no one is hurt.
- Please enjoy.
- Thanks.
Here's wishing you a Happy Qixi Festival in advance.
(T/N: Chinese Valentine's Day)
What about the day of Qixi Festival?
I only want to celebrate it with you at home.
Isn't this too easy for you?
- Hence, I prepared another gift for you.
- What is it?
I asked Zheng He to investigate the investment projects between Lee Group and Li Mu Research Institute,
and the investment accounts.
Isn't this your motive for coming back to China? To investigate if your father was corrupt.
If he was framed, that person who framed him
must have left some clues in the accounts.
Don't worry. I will definitely help you.
[Yangyang : What are you doing?]
Yangyang, I'm working late.
Li Jiashang is becoming suspicious.
So fierce. I don't need to think about the short marketing video for Qixi Festival.
I was here to look for Xiangtai to play video games with him,
but was caught by you to work late with you.
[Zheng He : One must have a good mood to work late but I'm starving.]
One doesn't need money to eat crap.
Yiyi, after you remarkably removed your make-up, did you meet anyone suspicious?
The only suspicious person now is Gao Mu.
Uncle Zhang and Chu Mo are merely sounding alarms for me.
Gao Mu? That guy who scared you with the pendant at the cocktail party.
- Lin Zi's boss?
- Yes.
After the press conference, at the hospital,
he even called me Mu Xiao in front of me.
This is strange. Could it be your old acquaintance again?
Do you want to probe him and find out what's going on?
Hello, Chairman Gao.
I finally get to see you.
Because I was thinking,
how could there possibly be two people who look exactly the same in this world?
I'm already aware of your motive for coming back to China.
- Hence, I advise you—
- No need to advise me.
In fact, you know that I'm Li Jiashang's uncle,
but my family name is not Li. It's because I'm an illegitimate child.
I used to be the person in charge of Li Mu Research Institute.
However, the Li family has always refused to acknowledge me.
This Li family is rather scary.
You and your father are not the only victims.
I remember that you showed me a pendant at the cocktail party.
I randomly picked that up.
I don't know where I lost it later.
Thinking about that time, it was really beautiful.
Your parents and I were very good friends.
I remember your parents brought you along when you were this tall
when we got together. Of course,
you were very young then and don't remember me.
I definitely don't remember.
After the car accident, I lost my memories.
Gao... Uncle Gao, how did you know I was still alive?
About this, I can tell you
but you must swear that you won't tell the Li family.
Because I don't want to cause any trouble.
I give you my word.
In fact, at that time, I was suspicious
that Zheng Yi's autopsy report was faked.
I installed a camera at Zheng Yi's office.
Don't blame me for such a dirty trick.
When one is old, he becomes more cowardly
and wants to have something to protect himself.
I know that you have taken actions.
However, I didn't find anything.
Take at look at this first.
Uncle Zheng, these bottles of wine were brought back from a local winery in France this summer.
With your sister's taste, she wouldn't buy anything inexpensive.
The patient is hospitalized. The doctors will do their best.
Don't spend any more money in the future.
If I'm gifting because of Grandpa, the gift will be more than this.
When you have the time,
come to my place and have a meal together.
I accept your good intentions.
Let's talk again after I'm done with all this work.
By the way, Uncle Zheng, I have something else to consult with you.
Gao Mu gave me this autopsy report by Zheng Yi back then.
[31 August 2014. The DNA doesn't match with Mu Feng's daughter, Mu Xiao.]
You must hide this from Zheng He.
- Zheng He won't talk about this to others.
- But his father is involved.
Besides, we don't know how much Director Zheng participated in this.
Jiashang!
You are here.
What are you doing here? Didn't you say you were going to the spa?
Hence, I'm here to pick up Yangyang after work. Who would expect that my period just came.
What's wrong? You want to check?
No. No need.
Okay. Do you want to go back with me? Xiangtai said that he cooked dinner.
I'm not going. I'm going to keep Grandpa company.
I'm going back now.
[Ocean City Public Security Bureau Material Evidence Verification Center. Autopsy Report.]
Where did you get this?
This can only prove our previous speculation.
But the corpse... where did the corpse who replaced you come from?
Do you still remember the list of body donors from Li Mu Research Institute?
Are you referring to the list from Lee Group's archives?
That's right.
I took a photo.
Looking at it now, there doesn't seem to be any problem. Send this to me.
I will go back and do some research.
Not drinking anymore?
I'm going back to work now. Take care of the bill.
[Wan Fu Yuan Liquor Shop]
Are you sure this is the place?
Absolutely sure. The number using Chu Mo's name to call Su Yi originated from there.
Okay. Don't disturb me celebrating the festival. Bye-bye.
Lao Song, just swipe for ¥50.
- Okay, thanks.
- I will deliver the water later.
Handsome guy, what would you like to buy?
I want that bottle of wine.
You have good taste.
This is the best wine in the shop. It's ¥988.
Boss, are you usually here alone?
Of course. Running a small business is even more tiring than going to work. It's too restrictive. I want to leave but can't.
That's right. Did anyone borrow your cell phone recently?
Borrowed my cell phone?
No.
Seems like there was one.
After buying something, he said his cell phone ran out of battery and wanted to borrow mine.
When was it approximately?
I can't remember. Seems like it was two to three weeks ago.
Do you still remember what he looked like?
It was a hot day and he was wearing a black mask the entire time. I remembered that the most.
Did he have any unique features?
He must have been a doctor. He had a strong scent of disinfectant on his body.
This is definitely related to Zheng Yi.
Thank you.
[Su Yi : Help]
Help.
Yiyi.
I'm here.
- Su Yi.
- Here.
Help me now. Look over here.
What are you looking for?
Plus One is missing.
I will make another for you. Okay?
It won't be Plus One. It will be Plus Two.
I will make more for you. Okay?
I'm most afraid of women giving names to their dolls. Once a doll has a name, it becomes a human.
Su Xiangtai, I'm asking you one last time. Did you see Plus One?
I didn't. I already said that I didn't. I'm going to buy late snacks. I won't hinder you both.
Are you okay?
Perhaps, it may show up later.
Su Xiangtai, come back!
It's okay. I probably didn't stitch it properly before.
I only need to stitch it properly this time.
But only when I have Plus One, I won't have nightmares.
What should I do before you stitch it properly?
Let me ask you something.
What is it?
Did you realize that Plus One was sewn based on me?
Of course, he's not as handsome as I am.
Before it's properly stitched, I will be with you every day.
Why don't you move in with me? I won't have to worry about you.
What about Xiangtai?
[Lee Group]
Enter.
CEO Li, these are the places Miss Su went in the past twenty four hours.
Go back to work.
[Lin Zi Group. Gao Mu.]
[Ocean City Hospital. Zheng Yi]
[Cafe]
[Ding Hang]
Gao Mu made Su Yi look for Zheng Yi, and then she asked Ding Hang to investigate Zheng Yi.
Hence, Zheng Yi is their biggest clue now. What secret is he keeping?
♫ The time to catch up with a dream ♫
♫ Since then become a hurry ♫
♫ It's still moving forward ♫
♫ No longer being gently side by side ♫
♫ Not all contacts are lost ♫
♫ Coincidentally, all insincere ♫
♫ We can be each other’s audience ♫
♫ The hug at the end, only start with no end ♫
♫ My tightly held stubbornness, feelings are all gone ♫
♫ Your unintentional words make my roar ♫
♫ Say less comforting words will make me better ♫
♫ If you still love me, don’t say it out ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to sing this love song ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to wish you happy ♫
♫ Distance has made our photo faded ♫
♫ My heart is still hot ♫
♫ The seasons have changed ♫
♫ How many people left to make my heart beat? ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing I disqualified by loving too much ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing our distance is like a galaxy ♫
♫ On the traveling train ♫
♫ You first get off ♫
♫ Only leave the time to heal with me ♫