♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my only light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ My light ♫
♫ You are my unique light♫
[The Secret Of Love]
[Episode 24]
Jiashang, it's the sunrise!
My leg...
How do you still look so beautiful, even though you didn't wash your face?
Stop licking. The more you do, the thirstier you will be.
What should we do without any drinks?
We can't drink ocean water, nor rainwater, and we can't open the coconuts.
Haven't you hear about a saying?
It says "the fish disgorged moisture for each other when stranded".
(T/N: implies very good relationship between a couple or friends)
Did you hear of this saying too? "Enough is enough".
What should we do if no one really comes to save us?
I think it's pretty good this way.
Really?
No stock prices, no power struggles, no malicious competitions,
no deceiving each other. There's only you and me.
- You won't be bored?
- It's great because of this.
Great?
You can't replace me if you are bored.
Okay, we have love,
but I still want bread.
I'll go see if I can find some sharp object to open up the coconuts.
I'll just be away for a little while. Do you have to be this clingy?
I'm thirsty.
Help is here. Wait for me, Jiashang.
Wait! There's someone here!
There's someone here! Wait!
Jiashang!
What happened?
Sister Su Yi, CEO Li, you are finally back.
What did you two do?
Why do you look like you were in a reality show or something?
Sis, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Were you worried, Older Sister?
- How did you get hurt?
- I'll explain it to you later.
What? Were you waiting for me?
I didn't wait. It's good that you are back.
Did you guys...?
You guys made up!
Oh okay! Okay! Okay!
You guys worked hard. Everyone, take the day off, no more shooting.
Long live CEO Li!
Let's go inside.
Be careful.
[Inpatient]
I'll go check the CT.
Xia Xiyang.
- I need your help with something.
- Tell me.
Actually, there's no fracture on my leg.
There is no bone fracture. However, after I was injured,
Su Yi has been completely obedient and protective of me.
- Get to the point.
- I want you to do me a favor.
I will owe you my immense gratitude in the future.
Nothing serious, he just needs to rest.
You two made up?
If you have reconciled, is there a need to be so excited? Look at your leg!
- Why are you yelling?
- Don't you know that it takes at least a hundred days to recover from muscle and bone injuries?
Rest!
Don't touch it.
Add some carrots.
The meat is burning!
Stir it! Quick! Quick!
Stop! Cilantro.
♫ At the first meeting, stupid like a fool ♫
Add some salt.
Quickly!
Put less. Spread it more evenly.
Put less. Quick, stir it.
- Chicken powder.
- What?
Forget it. Don't add it.
What do you mean?
♫ You are that him (her) ♫
♫ These are our special memories ♫
- Why aren't you eating?
- Feed me.
Are you using your feet to eat?
Anyways, it doesn't feel well everywhere now.
It hurts again.
♫ These are our special memories ♫
♫ I finally understand the reason to persist  ♫
♫ It’s getting clear  ♫
I don't really feel like eating.
What? I am sick now.
Help me.
♫ Too childish will always make people feel scared ♫
♫ If you come too close, you will let people melt ♫
Slowly.
♫ This is our fairytale ♫
♫ Holding your hand, my heart will be at home ♫
Be careful.
I'm so tired.
Since you didn't eat, drink some water.
♫ I always unconsciously thinking of you ♫
I'm not thirsty.
This leg hurts when I hop.
I'll massage it for you.
Do you want me to bring your whiskey here?
Then I want the one in the middle of the wine cabinet...
The doctor said I can't drink alcohol these days.
Yes, that's right. I was negligent.
- Are you cold?
- No.
I'll give you a blanket.
- I'm not cold.
- Just use it.
It hurts here.
I'll massage it.
Just a couple of massages is good.
- Do you feel better?
- I do.
Okay, then I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
- Home. It's getting late.
I'll take you.
I think it's fractured again.
My leg seems to have fractured again.
Do you want to stay and take care of me?
Okay. That's why I'm going home to get my suitcase.
Whatever you need, I've already asked my secretary to buy it.
It really hurts.
Okay then.
However, I should take better care of you.
Even if you want to take care of me, you don't have to do this.
Of course, I need to take care of you till you feel good.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
No. Good deeds must be done
properly till the end.
Okay, I was wrong.
Didn't you say your back hurts? I'm helping you by massaging it.
I was wrong! I was wrong! Actually, my leg is fine,
I'm fine.
What's going on? Fess up.
I swear that I only planned to hide this for a day.
Just a day?
Think about it. Even if there is no fracture,
it's still a superficial wound.
Since you said this, you should recuperate well.
I won't beat around the bush with you.
I don't have too many Lee Group stocks,
but I am waiting for the opportunity to take action.
However, the price...
The price isn't what you should worry about.
Chairman Gao, you are good. I still have some minority shareholders,
however, they are not as easy to negotiate with like I am.
When you are available, invite them as well.
- Okay. Let's have a good collaboration.
- Good collaboration.
[Lee Group]
Based on the sales curve, if we maintain this well,
we may set a new record in the next two quarters.
This influences whether each one of you
can go to Europe for team building.
The motivation meeting for the Marketing Department,
how can I not be here?
Chairman Gao, did you walk into the wrong place?
I'm giving you a surprise.
I just got my hands on some shares of the retail investors,
and am now the new director of Lee Group.
These three securities companies
are companies that the Lee Group looked down on.
However, they are just like me. No pain, no gain.
Currently, President Gao, Gao Mu holds more than 1/3rd
shares or entrusted shares of Lee Group, and this legally entitles him to be on the management board.
Moreover, this acquisition also increases the stock price of Lee Group.
Of course. It can be viewed as
Lee Group's fairness to the market.
Chairman Gao, make yourself at home. Let's continue.
I hope everyone can continue working hard.
I hope that everyone will be at the team building.
Chairman Gao, with the acquisition of Lee Group's shares,
Lin Zi has become the biggest shareholder. What do you think about it?
I think that Lee Group
is a company with unlimited potential.
It's my honor—
Gao Mu has impacted us badly.
Grandpa, our shares, and also the shares from some of our uncles,
although surpass 50 percent,
Gao Mu's shares have already surpassed mine.
If you hand over your voting rights to me,
I have the ability to solve this matter.
Don't count on me. I won't get involved.
I still have things to do, I'm leaving.
Chairman Li, are you really not going to get involved?
If he can't defend Lee Group in this situation,
Lee Group will fail under his hands too in the future.
Give him a call.
You saw the news, right?
How could I not know?
It's such a big action. Don't forget my warning.
Don't touch things that you shouldn't.
It has been tough for you lately.
The food on the flight must be bad. I will take you to have seafood later.
I can't, I'm allergic.
Okay, if you're allergic don't eat it.
- Let's have hotpot.
- It's too heaty.
Yes, that's right. What about steak?
I'm a vegetarian these days.
- You don't want to eat this and that—
- Can you focus on your driving?
Don't talk.
Let's go to Jinchi Hotel.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Manni just texted me. She said that she saw Xia Xiyang
and a strange man checking into the room.
Really?
Darling!
This won't do. It's not sexy enough.
Darling.
Darling!
Darling?
Don't look, leave.
What are you doing?
I wanted to surprise you.
Do you know I have been frustrated lately?
Can you stop giving me trouble?
I...
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to make you happy.
You don't need to do this for me.
But, you look very pretty.
I overlooked this and forgot to collude with you.
Yiyi, when will I get that kind of surprise?
Jiashang, there's something I haven't been telling you.
Then tell me, why are you so serious?
Brother Mu, you have to hurry up and leave this place. There's someone after me.
If something happens to me, it must be Li—
Gao Mu gave this recording to me.
The recording is real.
That means, someone took my dad's phone from the scene of the accident.
I did not continue investigating because there was debris from another car at the scene.
And it turned out that the owner of the car was Chairman Li.
I think I can tell you now.
Truthfully, I've always suspected
that the Li person in the recording,
is your grandfather, Li Yaohui.
Yiyi, do you know that
when your father passed away, Li Mu Research Institute was shut down?
Gao Mu was also kicked out from the Li family by my grandpa.
Before that, Gao Mu's family name was Li.
But "Brother Mu" in my father's recording,
is that Gao Mu's name?
I can't figure this out too. When your father was in the car accident,
I didn't pick up your call because I was with Grandpa.
He wanted me to intern at Lee Group.
He couldn't have arranged for someone to retrieve your father's cellphone from the scene of the accident.
Based on what you said, Gao Mu is hiding a lot of things.
Yiyi, don't worry.
Regardless of the final truth,
I will give you and your father a fair explanation.
Why did you drink so much?
Three bottles of white wine, done.
What are you doing?
I'm going to sleep here tonight.
No. Come back with me.
Don't bother me!
Today I'll sleep here.
Xiangtai,
do you know why I like to sleep in hotels?
Because you are afraid that once I know where you live,
I will cling to you even after we break up.
You're really cute.
It's because I can change hotels anytime.
I don't want to rely on any one person or place.
Why?
Because once you get close to someone,
you'll become each other's maze.
Hence, you like superficial relationships,
like to avoid deep topics,
and like to use jokes to brush me off.
What a big grievance.
You are doing this again.
But I really want to walk into your maze and truly understand you.
My love for you is not lesser than yours.
Who said boys with big chests are brainless?
You.
I'm such a badass.
Who says you aren't?
Tell me. Why do I like you so much?
Why do I fall for your tricks?
Yiyi,
do you know why I fear fire?
I remember taking an afternoon nap when I was five years old.
I was suddenly awakened by thick smoke. When I opened the door,
there was fire everywhere.
I desperately yelled for my mom and dad but there was no response at all.
I wanted to open the door to escape,
but I realized I couldn't do it.
When I woke up,
I was lying on a hospital bed.
For people who have struggled in the dark, when they see the light,
they may not dare to move forward.
Jiashang, those hurts and fears,
are not our mistakes.
We deserve to be better.
Three bottles of white wine.
Done.
You have never said such courteous words in your life.
It has been tough for you.
How are you?
Awesome.
Several directors agreed to transfer their shares to you.
Fearing that they will go back on their words, the deposits and agreements have been settled.
Then, Grandpa and I will each hold 30 percent of the shares.
We should celebrate now.
It's not the time yet.
Everyone here is my family and best friends.
I owe everyone an apology.
I have been hiding something.
Hence today, I hope to seek your understanding,
and help too.
August 2014.
Mu Feng, an employee of Li Mu Research Institute, got into a car accident.
His daughter, Mu Xiao, was also in the same car accident.
That was me.
I lost all my memories from before the car accident. I had completed my university degree in Japan,
when I received the September 2014 edition of Ming Xiu magazine.
So I returned to China to clarify this matter.
I found the clues till here, then I couldn't find anymore,
till a mishap occurred to Director Zheng.
The verdict of my father's death is finalized. You don't need to say this.
You don't need to be involved too.
Su Yi, you don't want to live a stable life. Don't take us along with you.
Even if there are other secrets, it's my personal matter.
Mind your own business.
Zheng He, everyone is upset about the death of Uncle Zheng,
but if you think this way, it's too much.
Jiashang.
Zheng He.
Let's go.
Jiashang, what are you doing?
If you want to go back, I can drive you there.
Zheng He, we will worry if you keep being like this.
You all?
I can go back myself.
Hey!
This favor is rather dangerous.
I know. Hence, I won't force you.
Thank you in advance, everyone.
However, seeing that you are Xiangtai's older sister,
and also taking my ex-fiance into consideration, based on these two points,
I will join.
I have always regarded Su Yi as my own little sister. Besides, Gao Mu is a threat to Lee Group.
If you need my help at any time, just let me know.
I avoided this before,
but now I want to redeem everything.
Frankly, I have longed for this opportunity for a long time.
Since I have already wet my feet,
why not take a bath at the same time?
Thank you, everyone.
You ask me to sign the supplies budget for the last quarter?
Go ask Zheng He.
He's not here yet? Just wait then.
Public Relations Department just said that the client's budget hasn't been approved. Can you approve this for me?
It also got stuck with Zheng He?
Don't be angry. His mood has been bad lately.
Bad mood? Is bad mood an excuse?
You said I spoke too harshly to him yesterday. You wanted me to apologize and
give in to him too. Look at what he's doing now.
He's slacking off and playing hooky. Look at his attitude.
I really spoiled him too much in the past.
[Resignation Letter from Zheng He]
♫ The time to catch up with a dream ♫
♫ Since then become a hurry ♫
♫ It's still moving forward ♫
♫ No longer being gently side by side ♫
♫ Not all contacts are lost ♫
♫ Coincidentally, become insincere ♫
♫ We can be each other’s audience ♫
♫ The hug at the end, only start with no end ♫
♫ My tightly held stubbornness, feelings are all gone ♫
♫ Your unintentional words make my roar ♫
♫ Say less comforting words will make me better ♫
♫ If you still love me, don’t say it out ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to sing this love song ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to wish you happy ♫
♫ Distance has made our photo faded ♫
♫ My heart is still hot ♫
♫ The seasons have changed. How many people left to make my heart beat?
♫ Just blame me not knowing I disqualified by loving too much ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing our distance is like a galaxy ♫
♫ On the travelling train ♫
♫ You first get off ♫
♫ Only leave the time to heal with me  ♫