♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explains the future to me ♫
♫ You are my only light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A sea of stars in this summer ♫
♫ You're the one who explain the future to me ♫
♫ You are my unique light. A different existence ♫
♫ Accidentally appear in my life ♫
♫ My light ♫
♫ You are my unique light ♫
[The Secret of Love]
[Episode 19]
Sis! You're back! Come have dinner!
Xiangtai!
I am covered in oil! I am dirty!
You don't know.
Your sister missed you so much during the time you were away!
- Me too!
- You cooked!
So fatuous!
You don't return home often.
I made all your favorite dishes.
In the end, my brother knows me the best! By the way, how is the internship going?
I was just about to tell you about it.
I am working as Wu Linjiang's trainee.
I gathered some information. Uncle Mu and Chairman Li did have a conflict in the past.
The reason was that Uncle Mu was against giving Lee Group the first-generation patent.
The first-generation patent?
Yes. Apparently, they had a huge argument back then.
It even caused serious disagreements regarding their profits.
Uncle Mu was prepared to bring the whole team with him
and leave Li Mu Research Institute.
I have been thinking about why these tragedies occurred with my father
and the reasons why those people wanted to hurt him.
Sis, the weirdest thing is
Lee Group Research Institute has displays of past patents all over their walls.
Only the first-generation patent was missing.
They said that the first generation is a confidential file,
so it is stored with the formulas.
Do you think I can use learning new formulas as an excuse
to investigate if my father's death
had to do with this secret first-generation patent?
This...
I don't know if Director Su has any other marketing requirements.
The new product's results received very positive reviews.
People want to know what is the secret in the formula.
If Director Su wants to learn about the specific formula,
you have to get the approval of our vice president or someone higher up.
Is that so? I thought it was in a storage box in the bank,
and three people must open the lock at the same time.
Director Su, are you free tonight?
If you have other questions we can discuss them while dining.
She's not free.
I am actually not free. I have to meet someone.
Really? I also have to meet someone.
Such a coincidence.
Talk.
This Zheng Yi
was involved in a huge lawsuit when he was a forensic examiner.
The plaintiff was also his own employer.
But this Zheng Yi only ended up quitting and changing his job,
and did not even receive any punishment.
What lawsuit was it?
He was suspected of reselling donated bodies at a higher cost.
So Li Mu could've got their bodies from Zheng Yi.
But Li Mu's research doesn't require the use of a body,
so what were they experimenting in secret?
You two talk, just ignore me.
Feel my pocket.
Which side? Are you kidding me?
My jacket's pocket.
Zhu Yue
I don't have much consciousness left,
so the last time you came to visit, I couldn't communicate with you.
Mu Xiao, your dad was my master.
Mu Feng knew there was danger, but he still waited until you left.
- That's why he faced such tragedy.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
You have to protect yourself well.
Don't come looking for me again.
From Zhu Yue.
Does the danger he's talking about, have to do with my father opposing Lee Group's patent?
I need Lee Group Research Institute's first-generation patent.
Why do you need to see that?
I can't start this precedent.
My approval, and you reading it, will both be recorded.
The board of directors can see it.
You two eat, I'll leave first.
[120 Emergency]
Miss Su, please.
Chairman Li.
Sit.
Secretary Jiang said you wanted to see me.
Yes. I really wanted to see you.
I heard you've been living very well recently.
If you have something to say, you can be straightforward.
I like your straightforward personality.
The money in this card is enough for you to live your entire life comfortably.
And this... you'll understand it once you read it.
Either you can do it yourself
or if not...
My patience will only last for three days.
Thank you Chairman Li.
I'll use this as my allowance.
I knew, Miss Su, that you are a smart person.
I truly hope you won't forget
that Jiashang will forever be a part of the Lee Group.
He used such an outdated strategy.
But I didn't get the short end of the stick.
Did he think I would leave like a silly, innocent girl?
He must have something to cover up, or else he wouldn't want to make me leave so quickly.
Then do you want to ask Li Jiashang?
But he did say something right.
Jiashang will forever be a part of the Lee Group.
What do you plan on doing?
I have three days to decide.
[Lin Zi]
[Popular variety sponsorship deal signed by Lin Zi.]
Miss Su.
It's a pity that you don't have much free time.
There's a Japanese restaurant near here
that has extremely fresh sea urchins.
It should be I who should treat Chairman Gao.
I came here because I need your help.
Miss Su only ever comes when my help is needed.
So disappointing.
I was joking. Here, try this.
Their dessert doesn't accept reservations
and there is only a limited amount.
Anytime I want to eat it, I have to make someone line up early for it.
But by the time they buy it, it's not fresh anymore.
I wanted the owner of the bakery to save me a box, but they didn't agree to it.
Guess what I did at the end.
I went to Japan, bought the recipe,
and found a dessert chef to replicate it.
Money indeed cannot buy everything.
But it can buy the closest replica.
I'm guessing, Chairman Li put pressure on you?
He wants me to stop and leave Ocean City immediately.
Common strategy.
But I just discovered many suspicions about Li Mu Research Institute.
I can't leave now.
Do you know that many people give this place's dessert as gifts?
But if they use a paper box, the flavor will be affected by other foods.
If they use a wooden box, the dessert will maintain its original flavor.
Miss Su, you feel stuck because you don't understand the key point of this situation.
I have evidence that will allow you to point the suspicion at Lee Group,
but once it is revealed to the public,
I will have no way of keeping them under my control.
So I need you to help me out first.
I made this just for you.
Secret formula?
It can only be viewed by Lee Group's vice president or others at a high level in the company.
With your abilities, rising up the ranks will happen sooner or later.
Say it, what do you want to tell me?
I remember that Lee Group's position of Marketing Vice president is still open.
Didn't you say that you would give up the entire Lee Group for me?
I just want this one small position, can't I have it?
Su Yi, it's not that you can't.
At Lee Group, if you want a higher position,
it's not enough to only have my liking.
So cheesy.
Don't you guys have a job to do?
I fear that it's not as simple as you imagine, Chairman Gao.
If I want to rise through the ranks, I need to accomplish something big.
Then what if I get your dream sponsorship deal?
Okay. I want to see why you are so confident.
Give Lee Group the naming rights.
Lin Zi broke their contact with S Level Variety.
Sponsorship rights are given to Lee Group.
Thank you. Thank you.
Congratulations. Congratulations, Vice President
Congratulations! Congratulations!
What's wrong? I have just got promoted! Are you not happy for me?
Do you want to make me happy?
Of course!
I am happy now!
Sis! Congratulations on your promotion! I've bought you a cake!
Where did such a considerate brother come from?
I also want a cake!
I bought it for my sister!
Is it for your sister or for me?
- The cake is mine now!
- Sis–
Hey!
Have you walked into the wrong office by mistake?
I've sat in the CEO seat for too long. I want to sit here.
New work lanyard.
This picture...
The photographer took a lot of pictures.
I was waiting for an opportunity to give them to you, but I just forgot.
How do you feel about it? Where should we go to celebrate it tonight?
Vice President Su.
Enough. I still have work to do.
What work?
I haven't yet thought about it.
Even though I have the vice president pass,
I still don't want to leave a record of my viewing the formula.
I knew you would end up saying that.
I have already prepared it all for you.
How is it?
[Data Room]
- Hello!
Please show your pass and phone.
Excuse me, where are the components for the secret product's formula?
I have to bring them for you. Please sign on the registration sheet.
Alright.
What? CEO Li is looking for me?
Okay! I am coming right now!
Then you may go attend to your duties. I will wait here, it's not a problem.
Alright. Excuse me.
It's fine.
[Secret Conservation Essence]
[Snow Lotus Conservation Essence]
[Inventor: Mu Feng]
[Prohibited from use.]
[File box]
Come to my office.
Yes. Right now.
I'm discussing something serious.
Isn't it obvious? Mu Feng's specialty was prohibited,
that's why he and Lee Group had a huge disagreement.
If only I could have taken a picture.
I was just a few seconds away.
Sis, don't you think something's weird?
Didn't it go a little too smoothly?
[Lee Group]
[Sender : Feng Yun]
[Miss Su's gift has been received. The desserts are ready. We request the pleasure of your company at any time.]
I have evidence that will allow you to point the suspicion at Lee Group.
[Voice Memos]
Brother Mu, you have to leave this place quickly.
There's someone after me.
If something happens to me, it must–
[Voice Memos]
Brother Mu, you have to leave this place quickly.
There's someone after me.
If something happens to me, it must–
This is indeed your father's voice.
Then his death...
was not an accident.
How did you obtain the recording?
Mu Feng sent this to me before the accident.
Now do you know why I keep helping you?
He warned me in the last moments of his life
so I left the Li family,
and closed the research institute.
What else did my father say?
He always told me
that you are a good kid.
He feels proud of you.
This is what the police
gave me.
Now I'm giving it to you.
[Chairman Li]
[Audio recording]
You cannot tell anyone about this.
[Sender: Li Yaohui]
Let's both take a step back.
Yiyi, you are the only one missing!
Everyone is celebrating! Be happier!
Here! Let's drink!
Let's have a toast! Oh my！
I am so happy!
Raise your glasses! Cheers!
Zheng He, aren't we celebrating your successful proposal?
Why aren't you two spending this time by yourselves?
I, Zheng He, from now on, am Xia Xiyang's fiancé.
This makes me happier than if A'Shang gave me the CEO position.
Shouldn't I flaunt a little bit?
One more thing!
We are also celebrating the completion
- of our brother Xiangtai's internship!
- Thank you, everyone!
Let's congratulate my little Xiangtai!
- Congratulations! Congratulations!
- Raise your glasses! Cheers!
- Well done, my little Xiangtai!
Thank you!
Let's also celebrate!
Congratulations to my female lead, who turned someone else's trick against them
and spied in the other company to get the sponsorship deal.
After all, it's because they met a clever opponent like you.
And you somehow ended up
being able to see the specialty documents.
Gao Mu said he has evidence that your father left for you.
The exchange for it is the formula for Lee Group's new item?
Interesting. If they had a machine that can figure out the components,
they can still figure out most of the formula.
But Lee Group's strong suit is not in the formula.
It's in putting out the product first and the brand effect.
Even if Lin Zi got the formula,
they cannot produce it as large-scale as the Lee Group. Therefore, they can't decrease the cost of production.
There's no point.
I am curious as to why he is doing this.
If you don't mind leaking the formula,
I think we might as well use it to turn his trick against him.
No.
What I mean is that we can't just give it to him.
Lee Group and the research institute both have his spies.
You have to make him know that you stole them.
You mean...
Later, you will come in again.
It's not that you can't. At Lee Group, if you want a higher position,
it's not enough to only have my liking.
And then... don't close the door.
So cheesy.
It's really like dreaming and wishing to continue.
Chairman Gao, Su Yi has deceived Li Jiashang.
I don't know if it was by accident
or if someone was helping in secret.
Then who knows?
You two are truly something.
You caused me to worry for nothing.
Li Jiashang,
brother-in-law.
Please tell me,
why was the first-generation patent prohibited for use?
Actually, that was Uncle Mu's decision.
It's because the first-generation products were flawed.
But my grandpa disagreed. He was scared that he would miss out on being the first to put it out into the market.
At the time, they argued a lot in the company because of this.
But Grandpa agreed at the end.
Uncle Mu and Lee Group worked on the fourth-generation product together.
So Grandpa couldn't fire Uncle Mu because of that.
So that's what happened.
That's good.
My little Xiangtai.
- Let's go stargazing together.
- Okay.
Bye-bye.
This drink is for you, Mrs. Zheng.
Hello Mr. Zheng.
In the future, you have to remember to be a good husband.
Yangyang, where should we go for our honeymoon?
I was just going to tell you. I got a year-long break,
we can tour Europe on a cruise.
Maybe another one. I get seasick.
Also, it's too far.
And you know, if I leave for too long,
Lee Group can't survive without me.
Then we can go to Semporna
to scuba dive. Let me tell you,
- the fish tornado there is magnificent.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I have a phobia of the deep sea.
Then we can go to Nepal.
It's close, and we can paraglide.
I'm afraid of heights. My heart will leave my body.
Then you can stay home and do nothing.
Why are you so impatient?
You say no to everything. How are we supposed to have fun?
We can stay home. Also, I didn't say no to everything.
- Whatever. I didn't get married just to have someone to argue with.
- Who said that?
How did you develop this outlook on marriage?
- My dad said it.
- That's why his marriage failed. What couple doesn't argue?
Marriage is just choosing someone to argue with.
You did not say this when you were proposing.
Well, how else would I get you to say yes?
Just nine words.
You won't get the short end of the stick.
What's wrong?
Look at others.
Didn't you tell me to look at the stars?
I'm saying look at how quickly the others are advancing.
But I'm still young, right?
Are you young?
Maybe not that young?
I don't care. I don't like to do things way behind everyone else.
But you can't bite off more than you can chew.
Then I'll take just one bite
at a time.
Then you can take one bite at a time.
You said to stargaze, but there are no stars today.
This is called a romantic vibe, okay?
What was said in the recording?
Too bad there's no helpful information.
Just things that we already know.
That's too bad. One more evidence that led to a dead end.
Oh right, how did you discover Gao Mu's spies?
Oh my.
I found that someone was secretly targeting Secretary Lin.
It's all thanks to me, who was investigating your father's financial records. You wouldn't know without investigating,
- but I found that–
- Hey, how much fake alcohol did you drink?
- Xiyang.
- Zheng He, go home.
- Oh, go home.
- Go, go.
- Then I'll go home.
- Bye, Yiyi.
- Be careful, Yangyang.
Excuse him, he had too much to drink.
Sis, I have to discuss something with you.
If I go on vacation with someone else,
would you be sad?
You just finished your internship and you're leaving again?
- Who are you going with?
- With me, of course.
Sis, this is still in the midst of discussion.
- it's not for sure yet.
- But...
you guys just started dating.
It's not even stable. If you just follow her there,
what if she dumps you during the trip?
You're going to have to come running back. How embarrassing is that, Su Xiangtai?
Sis, we are in a stable stage of our relationship.
I think that love
needs courage.
It needs the other person's company even more.
Su Xiangtai, come here.
You have never traveled alone with a girl. This time you're leaving so impulsively.
Would you really do this to your sister?
Sis, didn't you say that
people need to grow up on their own?
- You are quite impressive.
- Of course.
Xiangtai is still a kid, don't be too heavy-handed.
You need to be careful as well.
Also, I don't want to always lean on you.
Okay, I guess when a guy gets older he'll always run away from home.
Go, go go. I'll take care of your sister.
I'll take care of your brother.
- Sis–
- Don't get physical.
Don't get physical.
Sis, I'll return quickly.
Stop talking, don't say anything else.
- Let me be sad and alone for a while.
- Look how mad you made your sister.
Su Xiangtai, you are so cruel.
Let's go, baby. I'll take you to pack.
- You mean, you want me to pretend to be mad and try to prevent him from leaving?
- Yes!
Xiangtai is actually a rebellious little boy deep down.
Some things, if you don't let him do it, he'll want to do it even more.
If he is unwilling to leave his house or leave you,
then when will I ever get my love?
Yiyi.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll promise you.
Xiangtai has also gone.
You should just move to my place.
I'm worried about you living alone.
That's decided then.
No, you are a germaphobe, and I can only sleep well in my own bed.
Also, living together will quickly deplete the mysterious and fresh feeling between two people.
And will make them immediately feel like an old couple.
But it also increases the sense of belonging, happiness, and closeness.
I said no, so it's a no.
You won't move there?
Okay, I'll move here.
From today on, try to get used to it.
Who would want to get used to you?
I think we should get used to each other.
♫ At the first meeting, stupid like a fool ♫
♫ My heart stops at that moment ♫
♫ I love you so much I cannot pull myself out ♫
♫ I want to travel the world with you ♫
♫ Trust me that these are my sincere words ♫
♫ Too childish will always make people feel scared ♫
♫ If you come too close, you will let people melt ♫
♫ No matter what price, no matter the wind and the rain ♫
♫ This is our fairytale ♫
♫ Holding your hand, my heart will be at home ♫
♫ No matter how complicated the world is ♫
♫ You are that him (her) ♫
♫ These are our special memories ♫
♫ We have the most unique sweetness  ♫
♫ I always unconsciously thinking of you ♫
♫ The time to catch up with a dream ♫
♫ Since then become a hurry ♫
♫ It's still moving forward ♫
♫ No longer being gently side by side ♫
♫ Not all contacts are lost ♫
♫ Coincidentally, all insincere ♫
♫ We can be each other’s audience ♫
♫ The hug at the end, only start with no end ♫
♫ My tightly held stubbornness, feelings are all gone ♫
♫ Your unintentional words make my roar ♫
♫ Say less comforting words will make me better ♫
♫ If you still love me, don’t say it out ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to sing this love song ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing how to wish you happy ♫
♫ Distance has made our photo faded ♫
♫ My heart is still hot ♫
♫ The seasons have changed ♫
♫ How many people left to make my heart beat? ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing I disqualified by loving too much ♫
♫ Just blame me not knowing our distance is like a galaxy ♫
♫ On the traveling train ♫
♫ You first get off ♫
♫ Only leave the time to heal with me ♫