I now give my beloved daughter
to the groom.
Kiss! Kiss!
Did you rape me?
Rape?!
What did you do to her?
Praya, stop!
Hey.
They have a secret about MP Mahasamut.
Tomorrow at 11 p.m.,
a female celebrity will be lured
into providing services there.
Yiwa!
You bastard!
Hello.
Is this the editorial department?
Yes.
May I speak to Mr. Aeywiboon, please?
Mr. Aekwiboon resigned a long time ago.
A long time ago?
Yes.
Around five or six years ago.
I see.
Thank you very much. Goodbye.
That was around the same time
as the Jaiaree case.
Yes.
Do you like him?
That police captain.
That's none of your business.
What happened to your hand?
It's nothing.
What did you hit?
It's bruised this badly.
Did you crack a bone?
Come on. Let's go to the hospital.
Praya.
No matter what happens
between you and that captain,
I don't care.
As long as you don't love him.
If Mr. Wayu ends up hurting you,
can it be me instead?
Can I be the one to take care of you?
I'm hungry.
What do we have to eat?
Hungry at this hour?
It's almost ten.
Well, you made me exhausted
playing all day.
Besides,
since when does hunger need a schedule?
Eggs?
Oh?
I'll cook for you.
You're so nice.
But not for free.
Two kisses on the cheek.
Any more than that and I'll get shy.
Then I won't eat.
I'll cook for you.
Eat first, pay later. But the fee doubles.
You!
If it's not free, I'm not eating.
Hurry up too. Don't make me wait,
if you don't want to see me lose it.
Hot food is ready.
Hello, Mr. Samut.
What can I do for you?
You're blocking everyone
from contacting Fahsai, aren't you?
I know it.
Can I really stop Ms. Fahsai?
Am I that important?
Go get Fahsai.
I need to talk to her.
No problem.
But…
Ms. Fahsai is asleep.
We've been doing activities all day.
She's exhausted.
But you know how short honeymoons are.
We have to do every activity possible.
Tomorrow, when Ms. Fahsai wakes up,
I'll tell her to call you back.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to take my wife
to bed now.
I can't stand living in the same world
as you anymore, Wayu.
Mr. Samut, where are you going?
I'm going to shoot Wayu dead
with my own hands.
Wait, Boss.
What? I can't take it anymore. Move!
There's something more important.
They've been here a while.
They've walked around
almost the entire VIP zone.
Black Doc and Wayu's people?
What should we do, Boss?
Call Commander Singha.
One moment.
ROTTWEILER: STILL NO LEADS
Maybe we should go over there instead.
I'll give you something extra later.
Come on.
Why did you stop?
I think you should order more drinks.
That way, we can spend more time together.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Alright.
I'll be right back.
Found her. VIP zone, right wing.
Come.
Please cooperate.
Excuse us.
I happened to be inspecting
entertainment venues around here,
so I stopped by to inspect this place too.
No problem at all.
Take good care of the commander.
Yes, Boss.
This way, Commander.
Oh?
What happened?
The lady was very drunk earlier,
so we brought her here to rest.
I washed her face up already.
She should feel better now.
I want to go home.
Of course.
I'll call you a taxi.
This way, please.
Should we inspect
the other rooms too, Commander?
What? Was it all for nothing?
You risked your lives for this.
Hey!
This is solid evidence.
Then why the hell
are you acting all gloomy?
Had to build suspense first.
If the police hadn't shown up,
we would've gotten even stronger evidence.
They wouldn't have escaped this one.
Police?
They came to inspect the club.
They suddenly decided
to do their job tonight.
Still, I'd say
we pulled the job off pretty well.
Alright.
Here, Boss.
Just like I thought.
That bastard Wayu's been
stabbing me in the back all along.
Should I have the commander
arrest them now?
What's fun about just arresting them?
You didn't die by my hand tonight…
but tomorrow, I'm gonna
make you wish you were dead,
Wayu.
You came all the way here,
and you're not even gonna dip
your feet in the water?
Wasn't yesterday enough already?
That was a pool. This is the ocean.
Well, I'm waiting
for someone to invite me.
Then how about a race?
Whoever gets their feet
in the water first wins.
And if you win, I'll return your phone.
One, two.
What happened?
- Let me see.
- Ouch.
A shell cut you?
It's okay. I can hop back myself.
Really?
At this rate, you'll bleed out.
Hey. Hey.
You're kind of heavy, you know.
Then put me down.
I'm just kidding.
Suddenly quiet now?
You like this?
From what I found,
this should be Aey's house.
Aey.
Hello.
Do you remember me?
I'm Anawin, Peekul's boyfriend.
Hey, I can do it myself.
I told you already.
A captain has to take care of his crew.
Did you use to have
long hair or something?
That's what you came up with?
Well, you look pretty experienced
with the hair dryer.
A man
should know how to take care of his woman.
I'll dry it myself.
Guess I've been caught already…
for having impure thoughts.
Ever since I started working,
I've risked bullets and death
more times than I can count.
But nothing's ever been harder…
than going on a fake honeymoon with you.
Can it become real?
You're kind of heavy, you know.
Then put me down.
I'm just kidding.
Kull went to Heaven Club?
Yes.
But we didn't tell anyone.
Kull wanted to know
why her friend killed herself
after coming back from that club.
They trick women into sleeping with them,
then blackmail them.
They force them to entertain clients.
It's an entire operation.
All the evidence is in this camera.
This is huge, Kul.
What are you gonna do now?
Should we give it to the boss?
There's only one person I trust with this.
He's my dad's close friend from school.
That's exactly how it should be.
Good people take responsibility
for their duties.
That's what society needs.
I promise you,
I'll bring the guilty ones to justice.
I won't let them get away with it.
I'm counting on you, Uncle.
Don't worry.
Your friend won't die for nothing.
I was outside the room.
I saw Kul hand the memory card
to Commander Singha.
And I was shocked
that Kul and her mother
were murdered that night.
And every media reported the same story
that it was Kul's brother who did it.
But I never believed that.
I think there was something
hidden behind all this.
Something wasn't right.
Then why didn't you tell me
back at the funeral?
How could I tell you?
You were Captain Singha's subordinate.
And after that,
I started getting stalked.
I received threatening letters
several times.
Eventually, I couldn't take it anymore.
I quit my job and hid myself here.
I'm reopening the case.
Aey,
we have to bring the person
who did this to Kul to justice.
Can that really happen?
It's already been six years.
He became a police commander.
And Heaven Club's backer is a minister.
I don't know whose fault it really is
that Kul's family ended up like this.
Was it ordinary people like Kul's brother,
politicians,
or cops like you?
Hello, everyone.
Today we've got a spicy clip for you.
Spicy enough to burn the mouths
of corrupt politicians for sure.
Let's play a guessing game.
Which politician do you think
today's jackpot belongs to?
Take care of them.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Commander,
- I have an urgent matter--
- Commander,
the team is ready, sir.
There's nothing more urgent than this.
You'll lead the raid operation
with Sergeant Dam's team immediately.
Do these two gentlemen
look like they're helping this lady?
THE WAY SHE WALKS LOOKS FAMILIAR
POOR HER
Aw, so optimistic.
Well,
if you agree with Siberian
and think they're helping her,
hit the heart button.
Are they helping her or slaughtering her?
Yeah.
If you think it's slaughter,
smash that angry reaction.
How many people, sir?
We received a complaint
that illegal items are being kept here.
We'd like permission
to search the premises.
Here's the warrant.
Go.
Yes, sir.
Captain.
We found this, sir.
We apologize, everyone.
Please remain here
until the search is complete.
SOS. POLICE PLANTED DRUGS
THE OTHERS ARE LIVESTREAMING. COME HELP
MS. PRAPAI, MY BOSS
SOS. POLICE PLANTED DRUGS
THE OTHERS ARE LIVESTREAMING. COME HELP
Whoa, whoa! See?
Ah! See it? See it?
Let's figure out
which club this woman
is about to be sent to.
Could it be Casino M?
The one that politicians
from the pale blue party invested in?
We know somebody knows.
- Split up and search.
- Yes, sir.
Club H?
Oh? That club?
Yes!
Bingo!
Hey! You Mad Dogs!
Stop.
Don't move. Hands up.
Arrest them.
Go!
Hey!
Whoa! Why are you shooting?
The captain said to take them alive.
Hey! Why are you shooting?
I said take them alive.
Go!
Go.
Hurry up.
Go! Run first!
Who told you to shoot?!
Huh?!
Come on. Go.
Go.
Hurry.
Hey! Over there!
Hey!
Whoa.
Whoa!
Hey!
I said don't shoot.
What's with all the shooting?
Go back the other way.
Go!
Turn yourself in.
You're not getting away.
Pud! Pud!
Who ordered you to eliminate them?!
Why did you take it this far?!
Pud!
Go! Run first.
Go!
Pud!
Run first! We need to run!
Go! Hurry!
Go!
Hurry!
Come!
Go!
Get in!
Stop!
Captain, watch out!
The suspects are cybercriminals.
You chased them down
and shot them to death.
Don't you think that was excessive?
Why didn't you wait for my orders?
And where's Sergeant Pichai?
How far has the pursuit gotten?
We're tracking them down, sir.
But the vehicle
used a fake license plate,
and the escape route
had no surveillance cameras.
You reached their hideout
and still failed
and let them escape?
Instead of blaming your own people,
you should focus on hunting
them down and throwing them in prison!.
I'll do that, sir.
But I'll do it the way
police officers should.
Not like hired gunmen
carrying out executions on command.
They're not just cybercriminals.
They're drug dealers.
But we don't have concrete evidence
proving they deal drugs, sir.
You found drugs in their building
and you're saying there's no evidence?
Or do you want
to take off that honorable badge
and replace it with a dog mask instead?
Why?!
All we did was expose corrupt politicians.
What did we even do wrong?
It's obvious those bastards are evil!
Who the hell would even
want to do good anymore?
You do good and end up dying for nothing?
Those bastards even killed a woman.
I'm gonna kill them!!
They have to pay.
No, you can't, Sam.
You need to calm down first.
Sam,
even if you do this,
Pud still won't come back.
We can't lose anyone else, Sam.
But they have to pay!
They have to die!
Don't try to stop me!
- Sam.
- If you go, you'll die for nothing.
No matter how guilty I feel,
no matter how hurt or angry you all are,
we have to endure it.
If we let our rage turn us into mad dogs
and go after them now,
we'll only end up dead too.
Sam.
Do you want to lie dead beside Pud,
or do you want to get revenge
so you can bring flowers to her grave
and tell her
you finally avenged her?
You choose.
We're all devastated
that Pud died.
And we all feel guilty too, Sam.
But the ones
who deserve punishment
are those pieces of shit!
They'll pay
for what they did to us.
Just wait for the right time, Sam.
- There he is.
- That's him.
Mr. Samut,
police found methamphetamine
at Mr. Wayu's Kon La Yum restaurant.
He's your brother-in-law.
What are your thoughts on this?
I never imagined something like this
would happen to our family.
To be honest,
I'm very worried about
my sister's mental state right now.
Do you believe Mr. Wayu
is involved with a drug ring?
And is it possible the restaurant
was a major drug distribution hub?
There he is.
If you have questions,
you should ask Mr. Wayu directly.
Ask him.
Mr. Wayu.
- Mr. Wayu.
- Please give us an interview.
Did you already know the police
found drugs at your restaurant?
You know already, don’t you?
- Do you know it?
- Do you?
Please answer us.
- Mr. Wayu.
- Did you know the Mad Dog Gang
used your restaurant to commit cybercrimes
and that authorities
are currently hunting them down?
According to the police investigation,
three male employees
from the restaurant are missing,
and one female employee died at the scene.
You personally hired
all four of them, didn't you?
Sources say you were very close to them.
Did you know
they were behind the Mad Dog page?
Did you know or not? Please answer us.
- Did you know it?
- Please answer us.
Yes?
The police raided the restaurant.
They found drugs there.
I don't know which bastard planted them.
And everyone happened
to be livestreaming at the time.
The police chased us.
I managed to save everyone, but…
I couldn't save Pud in time.
Wayu,
Pud is dead.
Okay.
I’m taking Fahsai
back to Bangkok right now.
We'll talk later.
I won't deny
that I personally hired those employees.
But I have nearly 20 staff members,
not including part-timers.
How would I know
which people you're referring to?
The deceased employee
has already been identified.
Her name was Pudsorn.
You mean to tell me
Pudsorn was part of the Mad Dog Gang?
Are you sure
there hasn't been some misunderstanding?
Yes.
Once the masks were removed,
we identified her as Ms. Pudsorn.
The other three male employees escaped.
There was also one Mad Dog Gang member
who wasn't present during the livestream.
The one called Pitbull.
Can you think of anyone
who might be Pitbull?
Isn't that just a dog breed?
None of my employees is named that.
And I don’t follow
or pay attention to the Mad Dog Gang.
Ms. Fahsai.
Have you ever watched
the Mad Dog livestreams?
Yes.
Have you ever seen anyone
whose behavior suggested
they might be connected to Mad Dog?
Excuse me.
Ms. Fahsai has only been
to the restaurant twice.
She doesn't even remember anyone's face.
And besides,
she has nothing to do with this.
I'd like to take her inside to rest.
I'll come back out
and explain everything myself.
So what's the truth?
And who are the Mad Dogs?
Please answer us, Mr. Wayu.
Do you really don't know, Mr. Wayu?
Mr. Wayu, can you answer the question?
Mr. Wayu.
- Please, Mr. Wayu.
- Mr. Wayu.
Ms. Fahsai.
Sir.
Please answer our questions.
How are you holding up?
You must be terrified.
Come sit down first.
Here.
Samut! What are you doing?
Let go, Samut.
You think I'm the evil one?
You're even worse than me!
You drug-dealing bastard.
And you even created a page
to slander other people.
You're this disgusting,
and you dare mess with my sister?
Samut, let go of me.
- Yong.
- Yes, sir.
- Take Fahsai upstairs.
- Yes.
No.
I'm not going.
I'll be fine.
Go upstairs and rest. Trust me.
- Yong.
- Yes, sir.
Come on, Ms. Fahsai.
Let's go.
Now explain. What is all this?
And you're still asking him?
Isn't it obvious?
Those mangy stray dogs of his
have been attacking us
from the very beginning.
What's your plan?
You infiltrated my family
just to frame us and destroy us?
Who's backing you?
I asked you nicely.
Stop!
Jon.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Samut, please stop.
That's enough, sir.
Let go of me.
I'll make him get on his knees
and confess who sent him here.
You'll ruin everything.
The reporters are still
all over the front yard.
Go somewhere else.
I'll talk to him myself.
No one's going to believe
trash like you anymore.
Remember that.
I said let me go.
So,
those dogs
really are your people?
You ordered them to keep attacking
and harassing us all this time?
I don't know anything about this.
So it's all just a coincidence?
And don't you think
it's a little too coincidental
that the police raided the place
while I wasn't there?
I think someone
deliberately wanted to destroy me.
You're accusing Samut?
Even if he did do it, you still can't deny
that those mangy dogs are your people.
I'm really disappointed
that I trusted you.
Until you clear your name,
don't let me see your face again.
And stay away from Fahsai too.
- Sir, but about this--
- Save your excuses
for the reporters.
Normally, I only go to the restaurant
two or three times a month.
The rest is handled
by the restaurant manager.
As everyone already knows,
I have a lot of businesses
to take care of,
and nothing like this
has ever happened before.
Then let me ask something in return.
Why did something this big
happen while I wasn't there?
What if someone wanted
to destroy my reputation
by planting drugs in my restaurant?
So you're denying
all involvement in this?
The drugs, the Mad Dog Gang, all of it?
Right.
And there was a livestream room
in the building. You really knew nothing?
That room does exist, yes.
But I set it up as a studio to film
promotional clips for the restaurant.
I had no idea
some Mad Dog group
was secretly using my studio.
That's how it is.
I want to apologize to the public.
I have many businesses to manage,
and I may not have been able
to oversee everything thoroughly enough.
I'm fully willing to cooperate with
any investigation to prove my innocence.
And I want to firmly state
that I have never been
involved with drugs,
nor do I have any connection
whatsoever with the Mad Dog Gang.
Why the hell is he saying
all this bullshit?
He said we'd fight together,
and now he's just abandoning us like this?
Just because he married
a politician's daughter,
now he's lying just like them too?
Damn it!
Shut up.
I'm gonna say it!
Can't you see he used us?
He doesn't care that the police
are hunting us down.
He doesn't care whether
we even have a place to hide
or whether we live or die!
Even after Pud died,
he still doesn't care.
He doesn't know us anymore.
He doesn't know the Mad Dog Gang anymore!
I'm wondering the same thing.
What is he feeling right now?
How could he lie to the reporters
with a straight face like that?
Does he even hurt the way we hurt?
Does he know what it feels like to lose
someone you love right before your eyes?
Why wouldn't he know?
Do you think you're the only ones hurting?
Maybe Wayu didn't see Pud die,
but he watched his mother
and sister get shot dead
right in front of him.
And then he got framed
for killing them himself.
Isn't that enough to compare
to what you're all feeling right now?
It's not that he doesn't hurt.
But he endures it.
He's been enduring it for a long time.
Hiding your pain deep inside
hurts even more than screaming it out loud
like you guys are doing.
I thought you were better
than those corrupt cops I've met.
But in the end,
you're no different from them.
A bunch of police thugs
abusing ordinary people!
I wasn't bullying anyone.
You're angry because I searched
your brother's restaurant,
but I was doing my duty.
And we really did find drugs hidden there.
So now you're using drugs as an excuse
to shoot innocent people to death?
You're the worst.
You're just a politician's lapdog.
You bastard.
I didn't want anyone to die either.
I already reported this to my superior.
There'll be an investigation,
and the officers involved
will be punished.
I'm upset about this too.
Upset because
only one person got shot dead?
I should never have known
someone as disgusting as you.
And if I'm disgusting, then what about
the drugs in your brother's restaurant?
Stop using drugs as your excuse already.
My brother shut down every gambling den
and loan shark operation our father had
because he hated
dirty businesses like that.
My brother would never sell drugs.
You have your reasons.
I'm doing my duty
based on the evidence I have.
If you truly believe
your brother is innocent,
then bring me proof.
And even if he proves it,
can what's already
been lost ever come back?
You keep saying
you were just doing your duty,
that you did nothing wrong,
but it was wrong.
You know why?
It's because you don't even know
who we really are.
Of course Wayu would deny it.
Who would ever admit
to something like this?
Until we know the full truth,
you're staying here.
And you are forbidden from seeing him.
Dad,
from what I know about Wayu,
he's not the kind of person who'd do that.
Besides, if the people at the restaurant
really were behind the Mad Dog page,
didn't that page help people?
Then what about the drugs
found in the restaurant?
How are you going to explain that?
Can he deny responsibility?
And what about you?
Can you accept it?
Your husband's name
being blacklisted as a drug dealer?
I can't accept it.
Whatever you do,
think about our family's reputation too.
Yong,
did you leave yet?
Huh?
You're going to see Mr. Wayu?
Come in.
How did you get here?
Your father forbade me from seeing you.
So he probably forbade you
from seeing me too.
No one can stop me.
You must feel humiliated right now.
Everyone thinks I'm a drug dealer.
I don't believe you did it.
I'm not a good person either.
But you're not a bad person.
You remember Pud, right?
She died, and I couldn't
do anything to help her.
Everyone got dragged into this
because of me.
If I'd been there with them,
things wouldn't have turned out like this.
Don't blame yourself yet. Come on.
Please don't blame yourself.
You shouldn't have come here.
You'll get dragged into trouble
because of me too.
I know exactly how you feel right now.
I've felt this terrible before too.
And back then, someone helped me.
He stayed by my side.
It meant everything to me.
Even if I'm not a good wife,
at the very least,
I won't leave you alone.
Thank you for staying by my side.
Thank you.
Samut did this to you?
Don't you ever hurt my daughter again.
A piece of trash like you
deserves someone like me.
That's what makes us a perfect match.
I have someone who can help us.
I just got a new piece of evidence.
So, Commander, who exactly do you think
will end up standing trial?
Mr. Wayu?
Or you?
How do you know about all this?
This is between me and Kul.
Because I'm not an outsider.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon