(Yuk Seong Jae)
(Kim Ji Yeon)
(Kim Ji Hoon)
(The Haunted Palace)
(All places, organizations, characters, )
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Child actors were accompanied by family and were kept safe.)
I am not your enemy.
The royal family is your enemy.
So, why would you...
attack me?
What nonsense are you talking about?
He suddenly ran away?
Stop right there!
The warding stone.
He could come back at any second.
We must get out of here now.
Kang Chul.
Always keep the warding stone with you.
(Episode 11)
I found them where Yeo Ri was locked up.
(Fire)
They are the same, Your Majesty.
It is the same talisman, used to summon the Eight-feet Spirit.
Master Pung San.
I am certain he is Aguji.
The evidence is clear. What are we still doing here?
We must take him down now.
Because of him, Yeo Ri...
He had already dispatched the officers of the Royal Guard...
to find him.
They are also combing through the cave found in his shrine.
It is just that the cave is too deep and intricate.
The search will take some time.
What about the Bureau of the Blind?
It has already been shut down.
Any close shamans and servants of Master Pung San...
have been apprehended.
The premier is interrogating them as he is the current justice.
I am greatly relieved that you are unharmed.
Are you all right?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Yes. It is a relief that I am unharmed.
But this is odd.
Why did he spare my life?
What are you doing?
But we cannot let her go free.
This wench knows everything.
We cannot kill our bait.
Quietly take her to Sugumun Gate.
He called me bait.
I am the bait.
But bait for what?
Darn it.
The military officers are all over the Palace.
What do I do now?
Oh, no.
Master?
General of Heaven and Earth.
Your Majesty.
Where is Pung San's shrine?
This way, Your Majesty.
This is the place.
The secret path to Pung San's shrine...
was hidden here.
Oh, no.
Master.
Master!
Good grief.
What is going on now?
Oh, no.
Master, wake up. Please.
That...
I apologize.
We tried pouring water and scattering sand.
But it was only temporary.
The flames kept returning.
I want everyone...
to leave.
- Your Majesty. - I beg you not to order us to go.
We cannot remain here alone.
- I told you to leave! - Yes, Your Majesty.
I will remain close by.
I will kill all of you.
I will wipe out...
the royal bloodline.
You have been...
breathing down on my neck for far too long.
Where are you hiding?
You evil spirit!
Come out now, and face me.
I have come down myself as I have something to tell you.
I have denied your existence time and again for so long.
I did not want to believe it.
I dismissed it as bad luck...
and told myself that it was a passing tragedy.
I tried to believe that it only happened...
because I was not benevolent enough...
as a king.
However, I know it clearly.
That you are trying to destroy me and my family.
And that you watched...
and took delight...
in my bottomless fear and unending rage.
Show yourself at once!
Go ahead and see if you can take me down.
I will never let you bring me down.
I will never succumb to you.
I will look you in the eye...
and take you on.
You will never...
defeat me.
I am not your enemy.
The royal family is your enemy.
So, why would you...
attack me?
Do not pay attention to it.
Do not let it bother you.
What do you mean?
What should I not worry about?
Spirits are known to speak in riddles...
and lies.
That is how they play with our mind.
What could have led you...
to forge a cursed connection with the royal family?
I know.
Then why are you sitting out here in a daze?
Th Eight-feet Spirit knew everything.
That a century ago during the war,
I fell to the ground while ascending to the sky.
It sounded as if...
he had watched me fall that day.
Then could he have been born on the day you fell...
to the ground?
The wind is chilly. Get back inside.
I...
It is him.
The feast I settled on.
Malice festers within him.
Does it not?
Yes.
The stink of his malice...
has made its way to me too.
What is going on?
My lord, it is nothing.
You over there.
Make way for Lord Hong Kwon Woo.
Clear the path now.
How dare he? I told you to move aside!
Just look at that.
He must think he owns the entire street.
He could easily have walked around me.
But he is forcing me to move.
He has no idea it will only hasten his end.
Why are you just standing there? Get rid of him.
Yes, my lord.
Move!
What is that?
No.
Yeo Ri.
I apologize.
Please forgive his rudeness.
Yeo Ri.
Gosh, that little wench.
Explain what I just saw.
You saw everything. Why are you asking?
He was helping me feast on him.
But you ruined everything.
A recently deceased man named Kwak Sang Chung also had...
ripped talisman as well.
Were you behind his death too?
Is that so?
That...
Yes. I was behind it.
But he abducted Yoon Gap's mother and tried to kill her.
Offering an evil man like him to Bi Bi...
is not a big deal.
And the man from earlier is no different.
Without that darned talisman,
Bi Bi would have eaten him up a long time ago.
Did I not tell you?
For Bi Bi to devour noble men who commit evil deeds...
is regarded as a righteous act.
Why are you so angry at the work of a deity?
The work of a deity?
Fine.
For you deities, ending someone's life...
must be a trivial matter.
But you see,
when a deity ends someone's life, it is considered a punishment.
But when a man kills another,
it is only murder.
- Murder? - Yes, murder.
The one who stole my myeongdu and tore the talisman...
was not you, Kang Chul.
It was done by the human body of Young Master Gap.
My gosh.
Did I not tell you?
For Bi Bi to devour noble men who commit evil deeds...
is regarded as a righteous act.
Why are you so angry at the work of a deity?
The work of a deity...
My gosh.
The more I dwell on it, the more enraged I feel.
She is angry because I used Yoon Gap's precious body...
to kill a man?
It was only recently she professed her feelings.
Is she still troubled by the concerns for him?
You could not sleep either?
You startled me.
What about you? Why are you not asleep?
You usually snore loudly enough to shake the roof...
the moment you put your head down.
Yeo Ri told me what happened in the afternoon.
And that had me worried.
It is odd that the Eight-feet Spirit...
disappeared like that.
So listen.
Are you certain...
what you told me before is the only way?
I mean...
my glowing pearl.
Is using up the serpent's glowing pearl...
the only way to send off the Eight-feet Spirit?
Are you certain that is the only way?
I am sorry.
I do not know any other way...
since I am just a quack as you call me.
How useless you are.
(Episode 11: Bi Bi)
Your Majesty.
We found a good number of letters and items...
from the Dowager Queen's Palace...
in the basement of Pung San's shrine.
Is it safe to assume that the Dowager Queen...
has been behind Pung San?
How interesting.
Just recently, you told me...
that even if someone...
had cast evil spells against the royal family,
the one who suffered the most and faced the biggest pain was...
the Dowager Queen. Did you not?
Do you actually believe that...
evil spells and shamans...
hold such power to end a life? Did I understand you correctly?
Unfortunately, Prince Young In...
passed away due to excessive drinking.
The Dowager Queen was heartbroken by her son's death.
So naturally, she was deceived...
by the wicked, blind shaman.
This is a set-up.
I have kept the blind shaman,
Pung San, by my side for a long time.
I know him better than anyone.
Someone is pinning everything on him.
And who might that be?
As for that,
you must know who it is better than anyone.
Your Highness.
Who recommended Pung San to you?
Who is behind Pung San?
- Your Majesty! - Please open your eyes!
You may not have been an affectionate mother.
But you were never a fool.
Can you still not see it?
That you offered your son as a sacrifice and caused his death.
What do you mean?
That is absurd.
Pung San is a shaman who serves an evil spirit.
Yes.
The same evil spirit that drove the late king to death.
It is Prince Young In's undershirt.
No.
No, it cannot be.
I do not think you are entirely blameless.
But I will not hold you responsible...
because...
you are already facing the cruelest punishment.
No. That cannot be.
No...
Say a chant to chase all spirits.
So that...
the spirit I summoned will stay away from him.
Remove this.
This cannot be true. No.
No.
No, it cannot be.
No...
No.
You must have no shame to come back to me after everything.
You.
Do you know the trouble...
I must endure to clean up after your mess?
Please...
grant me one more chance.
Your existence itself...
has become a grave threat to me now. Understood?
- No, my lord master. - Darn.
Oh, please. My lord master.
Do you truly believe you can get your way...
and dethrone the King without my help?
What?
Prepare a place for this blind man to hide.
The world you seek is now within your grasp at last.
My goodness.
Oh, dear. Master.
Good grief.
Are you all right?
Master.
My gosh.
It was Lord Kim's family shrine a long time ago.
This place goes unnoticed by others.
Do not behave carelessly here.
My gosh.
I understand.
All right.
My gosh. Oh, my.
My goodness.
Master.
Oh, no. Master.
My goodness. Please wake up.
My goodness. What is going on?
Se Won.
Oh, dear. You are awake.
Yes.
There.
You saw it yourself, did you not?
I mean when the General of Heaven and Earth possessed my body.
The lord master could not do a thing.
Yes. I saw it clearly with my two eyes.
Do you understand now?
As long as we have the General on our side,
nothing in the world can scare us.
Yes. You are right.
Is there a brazier nearby?
"It is time to pluck and enjoy the ripe persimmon."
The General of Heaven and Earth has spoken thusly.
(Yeonjong the Great, Prince Young In)
Did you...
mark the ones killed by the Eight-feet Spirit?
Yes. You are spot on.
Remember what Yeo Ri said before?
The Eight-feet Spirit has...
a long-standing grudge against the royal family.
These are the royal relatives who met sudden and strange deaths...
in the past 13 years, following the passing of the late king.
However,
the spirit could not kill off every single member of the family.
(Lee Hwa Sung)
These must be the people the Eight-feet Spirit did not kill.
- Yes. - Then...
the one the Eight-feet Spirit holds a grudge against...
must have lost all of his offerings to it.
(Yeonjong the Great)
This must be its nemesis.
It seems to me the Eight-feet Spirit holds a grudge...
against my great-great-grandfather,
Yeonjong the Great. The king who ruled this land a century ago.
A century ago.
The Eight-feet Spirit said he was born a century ago too.
This cannot be a coincidence.
Considering how he knew Kang Chul fell to the ground...
while ascending to the sky on the same day,
he must have been in Yongdam Village...
when he faced his last moment.
Yongdam Village?
Yongdam Village is located in Ducheong County.
Around that time, a dreadful war hit the village.
The sight of dead bodies...
would not have come as a surprise that day.
All the secrets related to the Eight-feet Spirit...
were buried in Yongdam Village a century ago.
A century ago when the outlanders from the north...
invaded our land and waged war,
a man served Yeonjong the Great faithfully by his side.
He was named a meritorious servant for his service.
His family put down roots in Ducheong County...
and became a prestigious family for generations.
His descendant...
might know something about this.
Who is the descendant?
It is Lord Choi Won Woo.
- Pardon? - What?
I will visit Yongdam Village in ten days.
Once I arrive, I will be sure to reveal the true identity...
of the Eight-feet Spirit.
Please.
I am going to the council meeting.
Stop following me and go your own way.
I need to go this way too.
What is it this time?
What is the problem?
So... About that man.
That Yoon Gap.
What was he like?
Yoon Gap?
You could not have found a man more loyal.
He was a true scholar.
"A true scholar?"
The Yoon Gap I saw was a shallow coward.
He duped Yeo Ri...
to bring her here to catch the Eight-feet Spirit.
But you and Yeo Ri both.
Why do you like him so much...
that you never stop talking about him?
I am sick of it.
What is the matter?
Are you jealous?
You have one incredible skill...
that Yoon Gap never did or could possess.
What is that?
You turn the King of a nation...
into a man more childish than one you find in the marketplace.
Sure. And does that King know...
his nation has so many rotten nobles,
they are on every corner?
Do you think I do not?
I will fight them with all the power I have,
and in the end, I will sentence them...
by law to a punishment that suits their crimes.
Leave the worldly issues to a human king...
and just stay aside and watch as a deity does.
For example,
do not punish the rotten nobles yourself.
If you know what I mean.
Yes?
That will protect you from the Eight-feet Spirit.
Thank you for gifting him something so precious.
This is a warding stone, is it not?
How do you know that?
My father showed me his glasses made with...
a warding stone.
Yes. You must keep that warding stone...
with you at all times, Your Highness.
What did that King mean?
Does he know what we were doing?
- Know what? - My goodness.
I told you not to appear like that.
Bi Bi?
Are those two...
I saw...
where Yeo Ri hid the myeongdu.
I also found the noble...
I did not get to eat that night.
Right now,
he is at a gisaeng house getting drunk.
Come with me.
Help me set up a feast while Yeo Ri is busy in the Palace.
Bi Bi.
I will not go with you.
- What? - Yeo Ri was right.
Now that I possess a human body,
I should not do what a deity does.
- Kang Chul. - Pung San has fled.
He cannot write the nobles any more Haeilbu.
Humans never fail to age each year,
so each year,
you will find more greedy men over 60 to eat.
I am sorry the pig spell talisman delayed your ascension,
but it is just a few years.
In just a few years, your feast...
Enough of that!
- Bi Bi. - You do not want to do...
anything that girl does not like.
At this rate, you might even offer up your glowing pearl...
to send the Eight-feet Spirit to the afterlife.
How...
- do you know... - I heard everything!
To fight the Eight-feet Spirit,
you must use up the energy of your glowing pearl.
That means you must die.
At first you said...
you were...
just using Yeo Ri to ascend.
Look at you now.
Take a good look at yourself.
You have not possessed a human body.
That body has swallowed you whole!
Kang Chul the Serpent...
has gone too far.
Because of that girl, Yeo Ri.
That idiot.
That moron.
He let down a brother for a girl...
who will not even live a century?
Will he...
actually give up his glowing pearl?
He does not have a Haeilbu to stop me.
Show yourself.
So you noticed.
Did you enjoy your meal,
my lord serpent?
No wonder.
This explains the disgusting, fiery stench.
Oh, you are so scary.
My servant had a terrible time catching...
and tying up your prey.
Do not glare...
when we went to such lengths to serve you.
What are you up to?
Nothing much.
Just hand over that wench named Yeo Ri.
What?
The shrine room in the Bureau of the Blind.
Bring the girl there,
and I will offer up some nobles...
for you to eat just like this.
I wrote the pig spell talismans.
I know...
who has one and who does not.
Catching them for you is no problem at all.
Was this...
why you sold the Haeilbu talisman?
Neither I nor the General of Heaven and Earth...
have anything against you serpents.
But because of that girl Yeo Ri,
Kang Chul the serpent...
keeps getting involved.
It has become a great headache.
If you just get that girl and bring her to the shrine room,
I will offer her to the General of Heaven and Earth.
Then Kang Chul will no longer get in our way,
which would benefit us, and you get to ascend as you wish.
Would that not be a deal that would work for both sides?
I will use the paper talisman to confine the Eight-feet Spirit.
Then you will stab it...
with the crescent dagger,
using the power of the glowing pearl.
That was why that time...
What have I demanded of Kang Chul?
Look at you now.
Take a good look at yourself.
You have not possessed a human body.
That body has swallowed you whole!
Kang Chul the Serpent...
has gone too far.
Because of that girl, Yeo Ri.
Bi Bi...
seemed extremely angry.
How do I appease him?
So...
Yes? What is it?
I am sorry for touching your belongings.
Oh, that. Sure.
Your warding stone. Where is it?
- Oh... - Where is it?
Well...
- I gave it to the young prince. - What?
We will go to Yongdam Village in a few days.
What if the Eight-feet Spirit were to harm...
the Queen or her son while we are away?
What about you, then?
I could finally relax knowing you had...
the warding stone.
I cannot have it. I will go to the Palace...
and get it back from that boy.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Let go of my robe.
You are smiling?
You hated my warding stone so much, just a few months ago,
you did all sorts of things to get rid of it.
Yes. You took over Young Master Gap's body...
to keep me away from my warding stone.
Things have changed since then.
Kang Chul.
I no longer need the warding stone.
You do not need it?
- What nonsense... - You are my warding stone.
Back in Yongdam Village and here in the capital.
It was always you.
When I was left alone, you watched over and protected me.
You are...
my warding stone who protects me.
So...
I do not confuse you...
with Young Master Gap.
And...
And?
I can only do this without my warding stone.
- Hey, you. - Goodness.
Why are you grinning at the table?
I was not grinning.
I was looking for something to pick up with my chopsticks.
Stop it. Barley porridge has a lovely flavor on its own.
Yes.
I enjoyed the porridge so much,
I was done in three spoonfuls... No, I was done in three gulps.
This is all we have to eat because you wasted your salary.
We have no choice.
I am sorry to say this,
but from today, barley porridge is all we eat.
- Ma'am. - Yes?
What about the money I gave you last time?
I dare not spend that.
I will keep it all and return it on your wedding day.
Do not worry.
Stop complaining about my darn pay.
I will ask the King to pay me once more...
when we meet tomorrow.
Will you cook something nice...
That is just nonsense.
Do you think the King is your friend?
Can we talk, Monk Gaseop?
Yeo Ri. How do you know that?
You knew, then.
That the serpent's glowing pearl...
can send the Eight-feet Spirit to the afterlife.
Is there another way?
His Majesty once said...
Neop Deok was the only shaman...
to silence the Eight-feet Spirit.
What did Grandma do?
She used all the methods and spells she knew,
and also tried to identify...
the Eight-feet Spirit but could not.
In the end,
she summoned the Spirit of Death.
That could cause the shaman's sudden death.
Yes.
Neop Deok was one of the few who could pull it off.
But you know as well...
that it did not work in the end.
But Grandma...
did not know...
who the Eight-feet Spirit was or about the blind shaman Aguji.
When we visit Yongdam Village and identify the Eight-feet Spirit,
summoning the Hwadeok Chasa might be enough to do it.
Hwadeok Chasa?
One of the Spirits of Death...
that takes souls who were burned to death?
What is it?
You need one more thing to summon the Hwadeok Chasa.
Did you hear what we talked about?
That is not the point right now.
The Eight-feet Spirit's identification tag.
Do you not need that?
The identification tag?
Having it would be ideal, but how could we ever find it?
No.
Aguji might have the identification tag.
That was how he was able to summon it.
I saw it in the shrine room he used to use.
- Is that true? - I am telling you.
If you do not believe me, leave it.
Wait.
What?
Do you want me to come with you?
- Shoot. - Come with me.
Do not tell Kang Chul...
that I know about the glowing pearl.
He cannot know.
I will make sure Kang Chul is not sacrificed...
to eliminate the Eight-feet Spirit.
This girl...
cares deeply about Kang Chul.
That is why...
you are an even bigger threat to him.
If Kang Chul accepts the feelings you have for him,
he will never allow you...
to be in danger.
Even if he does not forgive me for a thousand years,
I cannot help it.
Tomorrow night, I will bring Yeo Ri...
to the Bureau's shrine room.
Good, good.
Very well.
That said,
I am sorry, but I need you to die.
What brings him here?
It is none of my business.
I just need to separate her from Kang Chul...
and enjoy the feast.
That is how I can save Kang Chul.
(Do not enter)
You scared me.
Must you always show up like that?
Why are you so late?
What about the Eight-feet Spirit's identification tag?
Come with me.
I could not take a good look last time.
I must say, this shrine...
It is truly impressive.
It collected the energy of the fire spirit...
and made sure its powers could be used to the fullest.
The identification tag must be inside.
Where is it?
- We meet again. - How is this...
Why is he here?
Bi Bi.
You tricked me?
But why?
Kang Chul changed because of you.
If I do not intervene now,
he will give up everything he worked so hard for all those years.
I will not let him do that.
I will never let Kang Chul make such a sacrifice.
You heard it too.
I came here today to look for a way to...
Right.
You must feel that way now.
But because of the way you feel,
he will not stay out of it.
It is fine even if he hates me forever after this.
If only I could save him...
You are...
Bring that serpent to the shrine safe and sound.
(Do not enter)
Yeo Ri.
You truly are asking to get killed.
Bi Bi?
This time, you cannot get in my way.
Bi Bi the Serpent has kindly agreed to help me.
You. What do you think you are doing now?
Bi Bi!
What is this?
Blame yourself.
I am doing this for you have changed!
- What did you say? - This is actually good.
Today, I will kill that wench right here...
and free you from that darned body.
That is enough, Bi Bi.
I do not want to have to fight you.
Neither do I.
However, this is how I am going to protect you.
Bi Bi!
Bi Bi, that is enough.
No.
I must free you from that body.
That body is not yours!
This entire shrine is filled with this intense fire energy.
If they keep this up,
they will soon be completely drained for they use the energy of water.
Good. We are almost there now.
So, I was not the one he was after.
Now,
please leave...
that body!
No, Bi Bi! Please stop.
The two of you should not be fighting now.
That scoundrel is waiting for one of you to die!
- What? - What do you mean?
The glowing pearl.
He is after the glowing pearl!
What?
Bi Bi.
Bi Bi!
Bi Bi, it is okay.
No. Bi Bi, no!
Something is wrong with me.
You will be all right.
No.
The glowing pearl...
No!
Kang Chul, we must get out of here.
We do not know what might happen now that he has swallowed the pearl.
We must hurry.
The General of Heaven and Earth has swallowed the glowing pearl!
Bi Bi, hang in there.
Kang Chul.
Can you put me down?
Sit down.
Bi Bi.
Bi Bi, you will be okay. All right?
I made a complete fool of myself.
I foolishly let that blind scoundrel...
trick me.
The King's maternal grandfather...
He has been backing the blind man all this time.
Stop talking.
The glowing pearl... I will be sure to retrieve it,
so please hang in there until then.
Have you ever seen a serpent...
without the glowing pearl?
Bi Bi.
I was simply...
trying to protect you.
You were going too far.
It made me sad and scared.
You know, right?
Yes. I know, Bi Bi.
Bi Bi.
Bi Bi!
(Special thanks to Song Jae Hee)
(The Haunted Palace)
My heart aches so much.
What is wrong with me?
We finally figured out who is behind the Eight-feet Spirit.
It is Lord Kim Bong In.
That cannot be possible.
Yeo Ri must be mistaken.
The General of Heaven and Earth became more powerful.
We must hurry.
We will set out as soon as the sun rises tomorrow.
Have that ghost...
kill the king at once!
Once His Majesty goes to sleep,
make them leave in secret.
Choi Won Woo was hiding something.