(Fate of Southern Love)
(Episode 4)
This is your first visit to the palace after the wedding.
We should go together as husband and wife.
You must be Lady Luo Li.
Don't you think I'm right?
The Princess Consort of Ning?
- What is she doing here? - Exactly.
Right? Wasn't she sick?
So, who's this Lady Luo Li?
Princess Consort of Ning?
Why did she come back?
Isn't she just asking for trouble?
She's actually pretty smart.
She knows how to fight for her own survival.
Li.
The imperial physician will check your pulse.
Nan Zhi. Maybe I shouldn't go.
My chest still feels uncomfortable.
I promise I'll cure you.
No matter what it takes.
Careful.
His Highness must be out of his mind.
He wants to kill you and use you as medicine.
My lady.
Will our plan work today?
It depends on him.
Chancellor Lou, please wait.
Chancellor Lou.
- Chancellor Lou. - I don't care what you want.
Just don't involve me.
If Prince Ning really wants me dead,
the carvings on my body and my undergarments
will point directly to you.
When that happens, your secrets
will probably be impossible to hide anymore.
Or I could just go with the flow.
Once Zhou Nan Zhi kills you,
I'll burn your body to ashes.
What do you think, Princess Consort?
I bet you will come to save me.
Since both killing and saving you are a hassle,
why don't we make a bet?
Let's see if I'm willing to go through the trouble to save you,
or to kill you.
Sit down.
Li, the Imperial Medical Bureau is just ahead.
Hang in there a little longer.
Nan Zhi.
My illness came out of nowhere.
I'm afraid I won't recover.
I won't let you die.
Would you really sacrifice innocent people just to save me?
(Host, the story is about to begin.)
(Lou Si Yi will realize his pouch is missing.)
(He'll come back to look for it.)
Pouch.
Nan Zhi, my chest suddenly hurts so much.
Could you bring me the medicine yourself?
Okay. Sit here and rest for a bit.
Li can't wait any longer.
I've already sent someone. It'll be handled cleanly.
Hurry up.
(Jin Zhu.)
(Lou Si Yi doesn't have time to help you this time.)
Didn't they say the pouch was here?
Who are you?
(This is the next part of the story.)
(You and Lou Si Yi run into the Emperor and Empress.)
(The Empress tries to embarrass you.)
(Unexpectedly, it makes you shine in front of the Emperor.)
(You then earn Lou Si Yi's admiration.)
(Complete the story and you'll earn 500 points.)
But where is Lou Si Yi?
That's a condemned prisoner.
I put a packet of pig's blood on her chest.
Her appearance was altered too
so that she could take your place.
You really can predict everything.
How can you be sure the Chancellor will help you?
Good at predicting things, you said?
I bet you will come to save me.
You really are shameless.
You keep threatening me again and again.
How boring.
A plan doesn't have to be novel as long as it works.
As for being shameless,
I'll just take that as a compliment.
Within the Great Jing,
no one knows
that I have so many secrets.
When I leave Jingdu safely with Fu Gui,
your belongings
will be returned to you.
As for your secrets,
as long as I'm alive,
they will be safe.
Next,
it's time to see what Lady Luo can do.
Where is Lou Si Yi?
Why are you spacing out?
Aren't you going to kneel?
Greetings, Father, Mother.
So, you're an acquaintance of Prince Ning.
No wonder you're so disrespectful to His Majesty.
Nan Yan
would've never been so unruly.
Father, Luo Li isn't from the Great Jing.
(Zhou Nan Zhi is back.)
(Did the medicine work?)
(But why didn't Lou Si Yi come?)
(Why is the story going off track again?)
No matter who comes to see the Emperor from other regions,
they must all kneel according to the Great Jing's customs.
Perhaps
she's in cohorts with Prince Ning?
She has no respect for the Emperor.
Water can carry a boat,
but it can also overturn it.
His Majesty is like the boat,
and the people are the water.
Boat and water support each other.
So why is water considered inferior?
Why should water kneel to the boat?
This is the first time I've heard such an argument.
Interesting.
What's your name?
My name is Luo Li.
(You impressed the Emperor.)
(You earned 100 points.)
Insolent! A woman like you
actually dares to speak to His Majesty like that.
(Lou Si Yi was supposed to speak up for you here.)
(But he still hasn't shown up.)
The medicine is ready.
Li.
The medicine!
Here.
Are you feeling better?
It's cured.
I can't believe it's cured.
My chest doesn't hurt at all anymore.
This medicine...
Why does it taste like blood?
What's really in this?
It's blood.
Blood?
Peace to Your Majesty.
Peace to Your Highness, the Empress.
(The second male lead is here. Host, he missed)
(the last scene.)
(Earn his admiration)
(to earn the remaining 400 points.)
You used human blood as the medicine base, didn't you?
Do you know there's no scientific basis for that at all?
What you're doing is pure superstition.
For you, I'd pay any price.
That's because you're not the one paying the price.
Do you think this will make me happy?
Everyone is equal in this world.
You have no right to decide someone else's life or death.
Jin Zhu did nothing wrong.
Yet you took her life just like that.
This is the tragedy of being a woman.
This is the tragedy of the fengjian system.
(Host, Lou Si Yi is about to notice you.)
- (Complete the story and...) - Lady Luo Li, you truly have a big heart.
Peace to Your Majesty. Peace to Your Highness, the Empress.
How are you still alive?
You were just standing up for me.
What's the matter? I'm alive,
and you are not happy about that?
Happy.
Why wouldn't I be happy?
What Lady Luo just said,
I'm sure everyone heard it.
The heart's blood didn't help Miss Luo Li's illness at all.
It would only hurt Your Highness and Lady Luo Li's relationship.
Let's
drop this matter now.
Wait.
So that bloody taste earlier was...
Pig's blood.
It seems like your illness
can be cured with any medicine base.
To make way for Your Highness's true feelings for Lady Luo Li,
I'm willing to get a divorce.
You really mean it?
Before Your Highness decides,
I'll stay at Yongxing Hall in the palace.
I'll copy scriptures and pray for Lady Luo Li.
Prince Ning left without taking his leave.
So rude.
Nan Zhi is getting more and more rebellious.
Chancellor, Her Highness requests your presence.
Tonight, I'll send the departure medallion.
Tomorrow, quarter past Xu hour, follow the merchants and leave the city.
Feng Yan will meet you.
Make sure everything is explained clearly.
After that,
you're not allowed to set foot in Jingdu again.
It's a deal.
Tonight, I'll wait for you at Yongxing Hall.
The taste of pig's blood is absolutely disgusting.
Not only did Jin Zhu survive,
she made me lose face like this.
Thanks to her,
Lou Si Yi didn't notice me like he was supposed to.
(Jin Zhu has been obsessed with Zhou Nan Zhi since childhood.)
(She shouldn't act like this.)
(But if you want to move the story forward,)
(you can let them divorce first.)
- (Then...) - I'm the real main character here.
Everyone else is just here to advance the plot.
Who gave her the right to ruin my story,
my moment?
(Host, we can ignore Jin Zhu for now.)
(As long as we pick up the next plot,)
(everything can get back on track.)
Now that there's no need to make the medicine,
Zhou Nan Zhi has no reason to kill her.
(Host, you can't go against...)
I know. Enough with the nagging.
Peace to Your Highness, the Empress.
Since when
did you begin to care about Princess Consort of Ning?
You never meddle in other people's business.
At Mingyue Gazebo,
you said more than you should have.
Your Highness, you're overthinking.
You'd better remember your place.
You're impotent.
You have no children.
The only one you can rely on is my son.
Yes.
If Nan Yan takes the throne,
you'll be the emperor's uncle.
But if Zhou Nan Zhi becomes the emperor,
what do you think will happen to us?
I don't have to spell it out, do I?
28 years ago, His Majesty
had the eldest prince with a lowly embroideress.
Half a year after I entered the palace,
I made sure both mother and son were gone.
If the former empress hadn't watched Zhou Nan Zhi so closely,
the only prince in Great Jing
would be Nan Yan.
In my hands,
there are many lives.
Women, princes, servants,
even your family.
Even if you're my own brother,
so long as you stand in my way to the throne,
you'll die like the rest.
Do you understand?
Lou Si Yi.
You were away from the Great Jing for 16 years,
and as soon as you returned,
I granted you the position of Chancellor.
But I still can't figure you out.
In your eyes,
there's no desire for power or fame,
nor any obsession with love.
Now I'm starting to doubt you.
Are you plotting something?
What do you think, Your Highness?
Prove it to me.
Show me you won't betray me for Zhou Nan Zhi.
What I mean is
Prince Ning shouldn't be alive.
Do you understand?
She wants me to kill Zhou Nan Zhi.
In the palace?
If I succeed,
Zhou Nan Yan will be the only prince of Great Jing.
If I fail,
Prince Ning will definitely kill me.
Then I'll have no choice but to depend on her.
For 20 years,
she harmed princes and consorts,
eliminated the Lou family's enemies,
and built her own faction with ruthlessness.
Now she's just one step away from becoming Empress Dowager.
Of course,
she can't afford a single mistake.
It looks like the Empress never truly trusted you.
She really shouldn't trust me.
Because I'm not actually her brother.
I'm the son
of the lowly embroideress she mentioned.
(Forget your identity as the crown prince.)
(Forget your name.)
(Forget Jingdu.)
(Forget everything.)
(Never come back.)
My lady,
I've kept the sachet with me all this time.
No one noticed.
Normally, hawthorn flowers are white.
But this one's red.
It's really unique.
I have no idea where it came from.
That doesn't matter.
As long as Chancellor Lou brings the medallion,
we can leave Jingdu tomorrow and reunite
with my father and brother.
I'm going to stir up trouble in the Great Jing.
Then use her to bring down Zhou Nan Zhi.
And right when she gets what she wants,
I'll kill Zhou Nan Yan.
Let her watch
the son of the lowly embroideress she burned alive
take the throne she's schemed for her whole life.
Second male lead?
What does that mean?
My lady,
did something appear in the sky again?
What's the plot this time?
Fall in love with Luo Li.
Who's supposed to fall in love with Luo Li?
But, this doesn't really have anything to do with us.
- Let's just wait for Chancellor Lou to arrive. - No.
He's not coming.