[Being A Hero]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
[Episode 25]
[Lin Dezan]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
(Through Wu Zhenfeng,)
(we acquired information)
(on K and Mengka's members.)
(Given that this is a huge cross-border)
(drug manufacturing and trafficking network,)
(the Provincial Public Security Bureau)
(has reported the matter
to the Ministry of Public Security.)
(The next step will be
for the Provincial Public Security Bureau)
(to make the deployments accordingly
to do a drug sweep in Yunhe)
(and paralyze our enemy.)
(Also,)
(we found the information)
(you wanted on Yang Xingquan)
(outside China.)
(You were right about Yang Xingquan)
(being involved in drug dealing.)
[Will you actually go?]
Now that I'm about to leave Yunhe,
there are only two people
I can't bear to leave behind.
One of them is you.
We've known each other
for so many years.
The other guy...
Twenty years ago,
he was my informant.
His wife was killed
and he was forced to flee the country
because of me.
When his daughter
first knocked on my door
in the middle of the night...
When I first sent
his seven-year-old daughter
to the welfare home...
I felt like I owed him
a debt of a lifetime.
[Yang Xingquan]
[Mixiang]
I'm back.
Chen Yu.
My dad is upstairs.
Mr. Yang.
What's going on between you and Lingling?
We're fine,
Dad.
Don't lie to me.
You've been coming home in a bad mood
these past few days.
I'm sorry,
Yang Ling.
I won't get you involved
in my work anymore.
It's inappropriate.
You checked my accounts.
Mr. Yang,
I just wanted to check if there was any problem
with Wan Heda
through the tea factory.
What did you find?
Nothing.
Just the usual freight traffic.
Yu.
Are you suspecting me?
Mr. Yang,
I will not suspect anyone
without proof.
If you want to look me up,
go to Director Lin.
Given my relationship with him,
you'll only need to say the word.
Mr. Yang,
I'm curious.
How did you become his informant
back then?
(I met him)
(20 years ago.)
He was a waiter
at the tea house.
I frequented the tea house
to gather information.
Chief Lin.
Let me refill that for you.
Thank you.
(He knew I liked Pu'er tea.)
(We would talk about the art of tea)
(a lot.)
Yang Xingquan.
(Until one day...)
Someone is selling drugs
at night at the karaoke hall
next to our tea house.
Selling drugs?
Are you sure?
Positive.
-Don't move!
-Nobody move!
(I brought my men and seized the place at once.)
-Don't move!
(I caught the drug dealers)
(in the act.)
(Later, he told me another location.)
(The bus and coach station at Wuyi Square.)
(His intel was always spot on.)
(We never left empty-handed.)
Chief Lin,
I'm doing this
because I consider you a friend.
Most importantly,
I don't want to see people falling prey to drugs.
(For this reason,)
he gradually provided us
with less and less information.
But oddly,
the number of drugs we would seize
increased time after time.
And because of that,
I was awarded.
(Later on,)
(the drug dealers got to me.)
I had no choice but to leave Lingling behind
and flee the country alone.
Mr. Yang.
Things must have been even harder for you
after you crossed the border.
I found work at a tea factory.
I did menial work.
I remember
that tea mountain.
The entire mountain was covered by tea trees.
(We would weed them, get rid of the pests,)
and take good care
of every tree.
When harvesting season came,
we would pluck the tea leaves.
(We would then send them to the factory)
(to be processed,)
(sorted, and carefully selected.)
(After processing,)
(the leaves became)
(tea cakes.)
It was hard work,
but when we saw
those tea cakes,
we felt a sense of fulfillment.
We were happy.
Through our hard work,
the tea plantation expanded.
(Business boomed.)
(We received many customers.)
(Then,)
(I met a woman.)
(She was the daughter of my boss.)
Ms. Qiong?
(Ms. Qiong.)
(The other key member of Mengka.)
(Her real name is Li Yiqiong.)
Yu,
what's on your mind?
Sorry.
I spaced out.
The daughter of the owner of the tea factory.
What happened after that?
(One time, she fell terribly ill.)
(Her father sent me to Walin Town)
(to get medicine for her.)
Why does he beat you?
One day, I'll kill him.
Here. Drink the medicine.
(When she recovered,)
(she taught me)
(many things about how to grow tea as thanks.)
(Her father started arranging for me)
(to deal with the business side of things too.)
(Then,)
(our business grew.)
(It attracted the attention)
(of the local armed forces.)
(Finally, they made their move.)
(To repay my boss,)
(I risked my life)
(and saved his daughter.)
(We survived.)
And after that,
to repay me,
she used what her father left her
and helped me start a new business.
(We secured a new tea plantation)
(and hired new workers.)
We made new partners.
But then,
I missed my daughter.
So I returned the tea plantation
to her
and came back to Yunhe alone.
I owe that woman.
It was she
who gave me a new life.
(Ten years ago,)
(he sent me a letter out of the blue,)
saying that he could come back now.
He wanted to start a tea business.
(We agreed to meet)
(at the welfare home.)
(I returned his daughter to him)
(personally.)
Let's go home.
Lingling,
he is your dad.
Look.
I... I'm your dad.
I'm your dad.
Mr. Yang,
you've certainly had
quite the life.
I've said so much.
Do you believe me?
Mr. Yang,
this is your life story.
Does it matter
if I believe it?
I heard you returned to the station.
Yes. I just reported for duty.
Why didn't Lin Dezan
have you stay?
Maybe...
Maybe it's because of my relationship
with Wu Zhenfeng.
What's your relationship
with him?
Someone said
I was protecting him.
He must be your informant.
I always thought
he could become
my informant.
Just like
you and Director Lin back then.
We're not the same!
Remember.
I am not Wu Zhenfeng.
Mr. Yang.
You are not him indeed.
He only lied to me
and used me.
Would you arrest him
if you ever saw him again?
I used to hate him.
But as time passed,
I couldn't help but wonder
if I would turn out the same way
he did
had I encountered the same experiences.
Just like you.
Meeting good people
might turn you into a good person as well.
But fate brought him
to a drug dealer.
Now that I think about it,
I feel kind of bad for him.
Do you
still consider him a friend?
I guess
time will tell.
(He deceived me)
[Yang Xingquan]
for 20 years!
He used my guilt toward him
to do
all those unspeakable things
behind my back.
He was already in it 20 years ago.
He reported all those people
to eliminate his competition
in Yunhe.
He was clearing the way
for his own business.
And I, Lin Dezan,
only found out about it today.
But I will not tolerate him
now that I know his deeds.
The higher-ups
are transferring me away from Yunhe.
I've given it some thought.
Before I leave,
I will do a sweep in Yunhe.
No one move!
-Stop!
-Don't move!
-Take them away!
Come out!
Don't move!
-Don't move! Get down!
-Nobody move!
Don't move!
Stay still!
[Cherish life. Stay away from drugs]
[Say no to drugs]
♪My feet are numb, I want to stop♪
♪But there is only one way out♪
[Leilei]
♪Too many mysteries yet to be uncovered♪
♪Regrets can only be stored in bitter smiles♪
♪Can't be erased, this mark I was born with♪
♪An unrelenting soul♪
Don't touch that.
Dad.
Mr. Yang gave you this.
♪All these regrets
because of my stubborn persistence♪
Leave it.
♪All my woes left in silence♪
[Honorary Credential]
Stop going through them.
[Mr. Lin Dezan]
I already packed everything.
[2015 Annual Outstanding People's Police]
I didn't take any of the collective awards.
♪Can't forget even if I want to♪
I've made a lot of mistakes in my life.
[Mr. Lin Dezan, Exemplar Officer
in the National Three-Year War on Drugs]
So
these mean nothing.
♪Fate had already planned everything♪
They can't make up for my faults.
♪Can't forget these painful memories♪
[Honorary Credential]
Leave them.
♪How can I offset love and hate?♪
Are you upset?
I'm curious, actually.
Why have you
been unwilling to leave Yunhe
all these years?
I had ambitions
left unfulfilled.
♪Can't be erased, this mark I was born with♪
♪An unrelenting soul♪
♪All these regrets
because of my stubborn persistence♪
♪All my woes left in silence♪
♪I can't let it go♪
♪Can't forget even if I want to♪
♪Bitterly, I say it's because♪
♪Fate had already planned everything♪
♪Can't find what I'm looking for♪
♪Can't forget these painful memories♪
♪How can I offset love and hate?♪
♪Where can I find the cure?♪
(I bought a lot)
(of your favorite foods.)
(I put them in the fridge.)
(The black sesame dumplings
are on the first shelf.)
(The pork buns are on the second.)
(The scallop and shrimp dumplings
are on the third.)
Take care of yourself
from now on.
I won't be coming over
for the next few days.
Too many things have happened lately.
I need a break.
Have...
Have you thought about
finding another place to stay?
I've been thinking
about what Wu Zhenfeng said
these past two days.
He said my dad was lucky.
That he was able to make it back alive.
That there was someone
who could prove his innocence.
He didn't want
to live as the son of a drug dealer
forever.
So he came back.
Do you remember?
I believe you.
You wouldn't suspect anyone
without reason.
But I can't change
who my father is.
Chen Yu.
I'm asking you this seriously.
Are you right
about him?
You know
I've been waiting for a clear answer
from you.
You know
I would never lie to you.
Yang Ling.
The only thing I can hold on to now
is to do
what I think is right.
I must find the evidence
and uncover the truth.
You want that too,
don't you?
He's here.
Hao Dong,
my men
have been asking for
the Yellow Capsules every day.
Zhuo,
I explained to you, didn't I?
But you didn't refund my money either.
It's not the best time
to do this.
I don't care about that.
You either give me the goods
or the money.
I must have one of them.
Zhuo.
Goods it is!
And I want them fast.
I want to make sure that nothing goes wrong.
Listen up.
Your feud with Mengka
has given me a lot of trouble.
I've already lost two shipments.
I don't want to lose another shipment.
Otherwise,
you and I both won't like
the consequences.
You're good, Ms. Qiong.
You had it all planned.
I told you
I'm not doing this anymore.
As if
you get to decide that.
Once you get into this business,
you're no different
from those who can't live without drugs.
You can't get out of it.
Even if you want to quit,
do you think your brethren in Yunhe would let you?
You heard
the buyers.
Even if you promise
to quit today.
Can you guarantee
that you won't pick it up again tomorrow?
Let's talk.
About how we're going
to deliver our shipments now.
I want to see Mr. Yu.
I won't go back to Yunhe
or talk business
until I see him
That's my condition.
[China]
Dong.
You've had it hard.
The car is ready.
Let's go.
Erliang.
Ms. Qiong.
Keep an eye out.
Yes, ma'am.
I want to see Mr. Yu.
I'm here.
Dong.
We can finally talk
face to face.
Let me introduce myself.
I am Yang Xingquan.
Thank you
for burning this place for me.
No wonder...
Lin Dezan.
Yang Xingquan.
So you
can rest assured now.
Lin Dezan
will be leaving soon.
Liu Kaihua isn't here either.
Wan Mengmeng hasn't regained consciousness yet.
She won't be able to say anything.
Now is the perfect time
to deliver the goods.
I can buy that Kun didn't sell me out.
But I refuse to believe
that the police haven't caught on to Wan yet.
You don't have to worry about anything.
Wanlutong Logistics is safe.
I've considered it from multiple aspects.
I want full control
of this delivery.
All right.
And
I want 20 percent more of the profits.
Dong.
We may call you Dong,
but do you really think you get to call the shots?
I've been on this path
for too long.
I want out.
These
are Yaba
and the latest Yellow Capsules.
You can have all of them.
You've thought about everything.
Thank you in advance.
I'll leave my words here.
Should you ever
need my help in the future,
tell me,
and I will
be there.
Don't bother hiding it.
I saw it.
Did you guys actually break up?
I'm here.
There, there.
Don't cry.
I'm here.
Kun.
Lei.
It's time to go back to your mother.
You can't stay in Yunhe anymore.
You're still young.
Be good.
There is no future
for people in this line of business.
Don't be like Kun.
One last hurrah.
Leave it up to fate.
200 kg.
We'll leave after we're done.
Nothing can go wrong
with the ingredients.
[Yunhe PSB Counter Narcotics Detachment]
How are things?
Director Lin.
Hao Dong and Wan Heda
entered the wood carving workshop
and Wanlutong Logistics last night.
After entering the border,
Hao Dong disappeared
from the unsupervised roads
for three hours.
We don't know where he went.
After that,
he went back to the wood carving workshop.
What about Jiang Lei?
He went to the border to pick up Hao Dong
last night.
He has been with him since.
He never came out
after entering the wood carving workshop.
Hello? Deputy Chief Chen?
Report.
Wan Heda and Hao Dong
have entered Yunhe
and met up with Jiang Lei.
It looks like our appeasement
had an effect.
Good.
However, we're still unclear
about the purpose of their gathering
at the moment.
We can't be sure if they're producing drugs
or trafficking drugs either.
Any news from Wu Zhenfeng?
Not since
the last time
Chen Yu contacted him.
In that case,
the only thing we can do right now
is monitor them closely.
Remember.
Be careful.
Do not let them discover us.
Yes, sir.
Stop him!
Since you are
standing here,
I'm sure you've made up your mind.
It's either
you won't leave this place alive
or...
Are you threatening me?
♪The wind♪
♪Continues to blow tirelessly♪
♪Above the sky♪
♪Exists an empty space♪
♪Taking a path♪
♪Adhering to my original aspiration♪
♪Wounds and pain♪
♪Are medals honoring my bravery♪
♪This story♪
♪It may not be eulogized♪
♪But I remain passionate♪
♪And willing to give you my all♪
♪There are always some people♪
♪Bearing the burden during the peaceful years♪
♪When breaking out♪
♪The blazing fire and the raging flame♪
♪Who can see clearly♪
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪The only way out♪
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪Deep down♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
♪Fly over♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪And never ask what if♪
♪Who can see clearly♪
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪The only way out♪
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪Deep down♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
♪Fly over♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪And never ask what if♪