[Being A Hero]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
[Episode 19]
Based
on the above investigation result,
on behalf
of Yunhe Public Security Bureau,
we now pronounce
that your father, Wu Gang,
was being framed.
We are deeply sorry
for what happened to him
three years ago
and for the wrongful blame
he took these three years.
Wu Zhenfeng,
we will do our best
to capture
all suspects
involved in this case.
[Yunhe Public Security Bureau]
Wu Zhenfeng.
This is not a personal vendetta.
Have faith in the laws.
Have faith in justice.
(I promise you.)
(From now on,)
(I will cooperate)
(with all your operations)
(and will tell you)
(everything I know.)
(This is the promise from me,)
(an ordinary person,)
(an ordinary person)
(with an ounce of good conscience...)
an ordinary person
who views drugs
as his sworn enemy.
Please believe me.
This is not
just about my father.
I want to help you.
[Detention Center]
Feng.
Guishou?
Buried in the public grave in Nanshan.
Let's visit him.
Erliang.
You're out.
That's fast.
The police did not find any evidence.
So they only charged me for the brawl.
I was detained for 15 days.
My police buddy
helped me too.
K
screwed us up this time.
We can't let it slide.
Feng.
You just came out.
Rest in Yunhe.
I will contact you if anything.
We have contacted all police stations
and have requested all the check-in records
of the hotels
within their jurisdictions.
We also gave them Wan Mengmeng's
photo and personal info.
We requested
their assistance in our investigation.
Kaihua.
We need to visit Wan Heda's home.
Director Lin.
The security footage shows
that Wan Mengmeng did not go home.
If we approach Wan Heda now,
will we alert them?
You will surely alert them
if you don't
send someone to Wan Heda's house.
Yang Yi, Lan Anran.
-Yes, sir.
You two will go.
Yes, sir.
Remember.
One,
only ask
about Wan Mengmeng.
Don't ask anything else.
Two,
we don't have a warrant.
Search where you're allowed.
Don't force him to let you search
where he doesn't want.
Noted.
Understood.
All right.
That's all.
Dismissed.
Director Lin.
What's the matter?
Kaihua.
Wait for me in the office.
Speak.
You released Wu Zhenfeng just like that?
Isn't it too hasty a decision?
No,
I mean...
Is it not possible
to investigate
Wu Zhenfeng further?
How?
The security brigade gets to decide
if we keep or release Wu Zhenfeng.
But Director Lin,
we even have the photos
of him with an armed
organization
near the border.
Of course, it's insufficient to be the evidence,
but it is enough
to raise suspicion.
If we free him now,
what can we do
if he exits the country and never comes back?
All our leads
will be done for.
Oh, the documents
you barely retrieved
from Wan Heda's office,
have you looked into them?
If not, keep at it.
Do not worry
about Wu Zhenfeng's whereabouts.
Bowen.
Can you give me
Wu Zhenfeng's location now?
Chen Yu.
Don't make me break the rules.
Is the place you found
safe?
No check-in is needed.
It's safe for the moment.
It is a matter of time
before the police find Mengmeng.
Dong.
I once killed someone outside the country.
You saved me.
From that day onward,
I decided to follow you.
Three years ago,
we returned to Yunhe
to avenge your father.
I have done all that was dirty or tiring
for you.
Never did I complain
or ask for anything.
I owe
half my life to you
and another half
to Mengmeng.
Tell me now.
Where is she?
Get up.
Give her back!
Enough.
Enough, Mr. Wan.
I'll take Mengmeng away.
You?
She is my daughter.
He's right.
Mr. Wan.
Do you have
a better proposition?
The police are looking for Mengmeng.
Let him take her away.
I can't possibly
let my daughter
flee with a drug dealer.
Flee
for a new life.
Are you defending him?
I worked
with you and your dad for many years.
And you're defending him?
Mengmeng said
she would leave with me.
Mr. Wan.
We're a family.
Anyone can help anyone.
A family?
No.
We never are.
You are a family.
I'm the outsider.
When did I
become part of your family?
Let me tell you something.
Wan owns this road.
When your dad was alive,
Wan owned it.
And now, Wan still owns it.
If you don't believe me,
take the route tomorrow.
What are you trying to imply, Mr. Wan?
Kun.
Mengmeng.
About Mengmeng.
Mr. Wan.
You can't rush it.
The more desperate you are,
the more frantic it will be.
Give me time to think.
I'll be waiting.
If this carries on,
I'll have to leave this batch out in the open.
We have to try Wan.
Has it ever worked
in these three years?
It's all Wan Heda's fault.
He's a coward.
He fears Hao Dong.
But this time, it's different.
Hao Dong set us up.
Wan Heda was fooled too.
Contact Wan again.
We have no other option.
We only have Wu Zhenfeng left in Yunhe.
He's your man.
You'll deal with it.
I still think he is fishy.
Everything goes too well for him in Yunhe.
Mr. Yu wants to test him again.
Mr. Yu?
Officer.
I did not steal it.
I picked it up.
[Deshan West District Police Station]
Why are you staring at me?
Work on it now.
Wait.
Why are you here alone
to see the camera footage?
My bureau is flooded with cases lately.
We're understaffed.
Give me the footage.
But your detachment
has visited once.
They were looking for Wan Mengmeng.
Why are you looking for Wu Zhenfeng?
Didn't I say
that we're flooded by cases?
Hurry up.
Check the camera on Zhang Hui's home
next to Liugang Bridge.
His nickname is Hui.
Fine.
Wait.
The system in your detachment
is more advanced than ours.
Isn't it easier if you do it in your detachment?
Can't you just do as I told you?
I want you to check the footage
because I trust you.
I have faith in our three years
of camaraderie.
Just get on it.
Chen Yu.
Are you committing another mistake?
Guang.
I was looking for you.
Director Wang.
Chen Yu.
Why are you back?
He came here to ask me
to get him something.
Guang.
Come to my office.
Isn't the son of Ms. Wang in Jinhui Village
applying for a residency here?
Stop gawking. Hurry up.
[2019-10-09, Thursday]
Feng.
I am never
a smart kid.
So I dropped out
of high school.
I tried to get a footing in this world.
And every a few days,
I'd get beaten.
Until
[Li Shougui's Tomb]
I met Gui.
From that moment onward,
I followed Gui.
Feng,
Gui followed you
and so will I.
If Gui
could die for you,
so will I.
Who do you think you are?
Talking about chivalric codes
with thugs and gangsters?
I'm telling you.
Your life belongs to no one,
except for you.
Come.
Look at him.
He said I shouldn't get in touch with K.
I didn't listen to him.
He died because I was stubborn.
He died because of me.
Do you get it now?
You want to be the second victim?
Get a proper job.
Take good care of your family.
Feng.
I didn't go to school. I went to jail
and the rehab center.
What kind of job can I find?
My life will be like this.
Only by following you
can I achieve something
and be successful.
You came from Mengka.
You said you wanted to be the Drug King.
I remember that.
Feng.
Hello.
Wan Heda's place?
Okay.
Follow me.
Feng.
I'll wait for you in the car.
Keep an eye on Kun's shipyard.
Let me know if there's anything.
Noted.
Can I help you?
Is Wan Heda home?
Mr. Wan is not home.
Mister.
Where are you going?
Mr. Wan is not home.
He truly isn't.
Mr. Wan.
I couldn't stop him.
He barged in.
Erliang has questions for you.
He called you
many times.
Why didn't you pick up?
You're with Mengka.
I'm with K.
Tell that to Erliang.
You can leave now.
We were all set up
that day in the tea factory.
Erliang asked me to come here
because he still respects you.
Do not take it for granted.
Try me.
You two are...
Hi, is Mr. Wan here?
We're from Yunhe Counter Narcotics Detachment.
Why do you want to see him?
We'd like to know more
about Wan Mengmeng.
I hope he can cooperate with us.
Mengmeng?
Mengmeng is not here.
You see...
What's the matter?
Mengmeng left on the 17th
and hasn't come back since.
Hi, Mr. Wan.
Hi.
On the 17th,
there was a death reported
in Yundian Disco
due to
drug use.
Your daughter
was with the victim,
and according to the evidence on the scene
and the camera footage,
we suspect
that Wan Mengmeng
is involved in an illegal drug trade.
Can we talk inside?
Mr. Wan.
How many people occupy this house?
Just Mengmeng and I.
And the housekeeper.
What time
did Mengmeng leave that night?
After nine.
She left after dinner
and said she was hanging out with friends.
She hasn't returned until now.
I can't reach her phone either.
By the way,
can you
investigate thoroughly?
My daughter does not deal drugs.
Like I said,
we are only suspecting her.
We still hope
that she
can come to us
and explain everything.
If you see her
or know where she is,
please advise her
to come to us
to tell us the truth.
We'll appreciate it.
Oh, Mr. Wan.
Where is Mengmeng's room?
Can we have a look?
Mr. Wan.
Is this the only room on the second floor?
Yes, only Mengmeng lives on the second floor.
Mengmeng
is not a bad kid.
She has her temper, that's all.
I don't think
she'll ever
commit a crime.
Anran!
I truly don't know about this.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm not aware of it.
I truly know nothing about it.
What is this?
I don't know.
If you have
any news,
please inform us right away.
It's the best you can do
as her family.
Chen Yu is calling?
Look to your right.
Behind the gray car.
Why are you here?
Get in first.
We'll talk later.
Hurry.
Mr. Wan.
Your family is in deep trouble.
Bugger off.
Erliang wants you
to call him back.
I'm here on his order.
Tell him I won't.
Erliang.
What are you trying to do?
You sent someone to my house
to intimidate me?
Make him
leave my house.
Wan.
It's not nice of you
to set us up.
Mr. Yu is very angry. He wants to get his revenge
on Hao Dong
and he wants you to work for us.
What he means by that
is that since we go way back,
we cannot fault you for the feud
between us and Hao Dong.
This has nothing to do with me.
I wasn't aware that Hao Dong
was setting you up.
Tell your man
to get out of my house now.
Erliang.
It's me.
Wan is in trouble now.
The police are looking for her daughter.
Wan.
What happened to your daughter?
Wu Zhenfeng?
Why is he here?
He went in before you.
Listen.
Wu Zhenfeng
must be close
to Wan.
He came...
Chen Yu.
You're now
on a temporary suspension.
Stop making more mistakes.
I have told Director Lin about this.
I said Wu Zhenfeng would do something
once he is out.
Director Lin refused to listen.
Yang Yi is right.
Stop spying here.
Go back.
Don't tell them I was here.
Why are you so stubborn?
Go back now.
Do not waste your time
on me.
Your vendetta against Hao Dong
has nothing to do with me.
I just want
my daughter's safe return.
What do you want us to do?
I don't want you to do anything.
I want my daughter.
Feng.
Yes, Erliang?
I don't care what you do.
Make sure Wan Mengmeng returns in one piece.
You hear me?
Yes.
Bring me my daughter
and we'll talk.
This is what
my colleagues in the technical department and I
got from sieving through a huge volume
of security footage.
It is taken from somewhere
nearby Donghu.
It was the night when someone died
in Yundian Disco.
After that, she wasn't
in any of the footage.
It was raining heavily that night.
Many streets do not have security cameras.
Who is the driver?
Using the vehicle information
and facial comparison,
we can confirm the driver is Wang Yikun.
He owns a shipyard in Yunhe.
Wan Mengmeng used to mention
that she has a boyfriend called Kun.
It should be this Wang Yikun.
Using Donghu as the center,
contact the police stations nearby
and go through the nearby hotels,
motels, bed and breakfast,
to find Wan Mengmeng.
Yes, sir.
[Kangxitang Pharmacy]
Director Lin.
Chief Liu.
I just received the news.
Wan Mengmeng
appeared in Donghu District.
She bought medicine at Kangxitang Pharmacy.
Bowen.
Tell me
the closest motel.
The closest one is Xingrong Motel.
I just checked.
That night after
Wang Yikun left the shipyard,
he went in that direction too.
Get ready to move.
Xingrong Motel.
Yes, sir.
Qiang, Anran. Move.
Yes.
Mengmeng.
What's the matter, Mengmeng?
Take me away.
Listen to me.
We can't now.
This place is safe for the moment.
I'm still looking for a way.
No.
Take me away now.
Now!
I don't want it. Take me away.
Take one if you can't deal with it.
No.
No more Yaba.
I'm pregnant.
No!
I can't have Yaba anymore.
Let's not take it.
Your body is weak.
We can't have that baby.
No.
I can have the baby.
Kun, I can.
I can stay clean.
Why can't we keep it?
We can have babies
in the future.
But not now.
Let's leave.
Take me away.
Mengmeng.
We'll leave now.
I won't take drugs.
I won't take Yaba.
I don't feel sick at all today.
Not at all.
Feng.
I have been following him.
Kun went inside the motel
and hasn't come out.
Which room?
No idea.
Stay here.
Okay.
[Xingrong Motel]
What can I help?
Where is Kun?
He told me to come here
to deliver the medicine to his girlfriend.
Hurry up.
If she has an episode,
the police might be alerted.
Room 208, on the second floor.
My meal.
Let go of him.
Wu Zhenfeng!
Mengmeng.
Wu Zhenfeng.
We can settle the score ourselves.
No need to drag Mengmeng into this.
Let her go.
Wan told me to take her away.
You think
I'd let it happen?
If I can find you
here,
do you think the police can't?
If you won't let me take her away,
I will bring both of you
to the police.
Look at her now.
How long do you think
you can hide here?
You want to die
with your girlfriend?
Sending her off
to Wan Heda's care
is the safest option now.
To you and to her.
Wu Zhenfeng!
Hui, take her away.
Hop on in.
Don't get in my way, I'm telling you.
Feng, get in!
Wu Zhenfeng!
Get out of the car!
Chen Yu's car.
Chen Yu.
Chen Yu is there.
Why are you here?
I followed Wu Zhenfeng
here.
He escaped with Wan Mengmeng!
Didn't I tell you
to keep an eye on him?
Why did you refuse to listen to me?
How did you come here that quickly?
We tracked Wan Mengmeng to this place.
When?
Lan Anran.
What's the situation?
Chief Liu.
Wu Zhenfeng escaped with Wan Mengmeng...
Chen Yu.
before our arrival.
Why are you working on your own?
Why is Chen Yu there?
Why didn't you tell us first?
If you had done that
or called us,
we would have caught him.
Chen Yu.
Where are you going?
Chen Yu!
Mengmeng.
Hang in there.
I called Dr. Yu.
He'll be here soon.
Dad.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have touched drugs.
Just let me go.
Let me leave with Kun.
I'm pregnant.
After Wu Zhenfeng was released,
he went to Wan Heda's house right away.
Then, he escaped with Wan Mengmeng.
Don't you think
something is fishy?
I watched over
Wu Zhenfeng all day long
and I found Wan Mengmeng.
If you had listened to me
and planned an ambush,
he wouldn't have escaped.
Look at you now.
I get it.
Go back home.
Treat your wounds.
We cannot just sit by and do nothing.
Director Lin.
I want to keep watching Wu Zhenfeng.
My work
has been suspended anyway.
I have plenty of time to keep an eye on him.
I know where he lives.
Do not follow
this lead anymore.
You.
Write a reflection report tomorrow morning
and give it to Chief Liu.
A thorough
reflection.
Call Erliang.
Get off my back.
Dr. Yu.
Where is she?
On the third floor.
Come in.
Dr. Yu.
Mengmeng is pregnant.
Be mindful of the dosage.
Can you call him now?
You are relentless.
How many times have I told you
I'll do it later?
Dong.
Wu Zhenfeng
rescued Wan Mengmeng.
Will Wan
work for Mengka now?
Will he betray us?
Dong.
I don't think
Wan Heda has the guts
to bet with her daughter's life
against me.
I'll go to him.
Erliang.
You still want to eliminate Hao Dong?
In a week,
they will deliver a batch from Kumon Range
to Shengjiang.
Yellow Capsules.
Is Wu Zhenfeng there?
Erliang.
Your work is done there.
Go back first.
♪The wind♪
♪Continues to blow tirelessly♪
♪Above the sky♪
♪Exists an empty space♪
♪Taking a path♪
♪Adhering to my original aspiration♪
♪Wounds and pain♪
♪Are medals honoring my bravery♪
♪This story♪
♪It may not be eulogized♪
♪But I remain passionate♪
♪And willing to give you my all♪
♪There are always some people♪
♪Bearing the burden during the peaceful years♪
♪When breaking out♪
♪The blazing fire and the raging flame♪
♪Who can see clearly♪
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪The only way out♪
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪Deep down♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
♪Fly over♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪And never ask what if♪
♪Who can see clearly♪
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪The only way out♪
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪Deep down♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
♪Fly over♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪And never ask what if♪