♪Thinking of you,
the sky turns light blue♪
the sunlight feels gentle♪
♪Thinking of you, the clouds look pink♪
♪One bite, so sweet♪
♪Loving you
is like honey melting in the sun♪
♪Even the coldest winter feels warm♪
♪Since falling for you,
I only want your company♪
♪You see through
all my sweet little schemes♪
♪What should I do?♪
[My Sassy Girl]
[Episode 20]
What are you doing?
I've thought it through.
I was too reckless
in the last few days.
To find the culprit,
I carried out careless investigations.
I was full of myself
and arrogant.
I caused trouble
for the people of the capital.
You didn't bring the branches
of a chaste tree?
Mr. Zhou might have done
many evil things,
but he treated me well.
Whether it's for public
or personal gain,
I also hope the case
can be solved soon.
Go straight to the point.
Mr. Lin,
please join me in the investigation
and help me find Mr. Zhou's murderer.
What if I refuse?
Lin Qingqiu!
Don't go overboard.
Now,
that's the Lu Bai I know.
You...
All right.
Oh,
I remember one thing.
What is it?
That day,
when we were holding
a farewell banquet for Mr. Zhou,
he told me something.
Now that I think about it,
it sounded cryptic.
What did he say?
He said karma was real.
What went around came around.
He told me
if something happened to him one day,
he hoped I wouldn't investigate it.
He knew
he couldn't hide it any longer.
Tanghulu.
Nanyi,
has Fu Wenyuan left?
Yes.
That's good.
Qingqiu finally has one less love rival.
Qingqiu never has any love rivals.
I have always been loyal to him.
What do you plan
to do next?
As long as he is in the capital,
I'll accompany him.
Sigh.
But all the leads
of the case are gone.
I don't know how to carry on
with the investigation.
Perhaps
it might be a puzzle
that will never be solved.
What do you think we can do?
The case is closed.
All four tomb robbers
of the Grand Preceptor's daughter's grave
died a horrible death in coffins.
The case is heading into a dead end.
The murderer cannot be found.
[Qinjiu, Gu Shan, Shi Kaiyang]
However, no one knows
that there was a fifth person
who robbed
the Grand Preceptor's daughter's grave.
No.
I don't agree.
I am the author of the storybook.
If I tell the world with the storybook
that there were five tomb robbers
and add a vivid description
of the incident back then,
the murderer will strike again
to kill the fifth robber.
I know.
But I can't
put you at risk to solve the case.
The murderer is still at large.
I can't sit here and do nothing.
I'm Jinzhou's prefect.
Arresting the murderer
is my duty.
But
this is the only way.
There will always be other ways.
I can't let you put yourself in danger.
I can't do it.
Hey.
Qingqiu.
Ji Xinshi murdered someone
because he read one of my storybooks.
I don't want my storybooks
to mislead people to commit crimes.
My storybooks can also uphold justice
and help people get rid of evil.
Besides,
I came up with this idea
because I knew you could protect me.
I know
you won't let anything happen to me,
right?
You always act like this.
Once you've decided on something,
no one can talk you out of it.
I will protect you,
but you must promise me
not to go
to dangerous places alone.
Absolutely.
Don't even
take one step away from me.
Sure.
[Love's Betrayal:
The Fifth Person in the Tomb]
The fifth tomb robber
held a steel hoe in his hand.
When this fifth robber made his command,
the other four people
pried open the tomb's red coffin.
The fifth tomb robber
looked greedily
at the treasures inside the tomb.
Speaking of which,
the fifth tomb robber
is cruel
and sly.
Shi Kaiyang and the rest never expected
the female body
to revive.
They were so scared and ran immediately.
However, the fifth person
was not afraid of deities or ghosts.
He rushed in with a knife.
He only saw
an attractive woman.
She didn't look like a ghost.
He grabbed the woman's hair
and stuffed her inside the coffin alive.
Shi Kaiyang and the rest
were no longer afraid.
They had to
get rid of the witness.
The five of them
stuffed the girl inside the coffin.
No matter how much
the girl was crying for help,
they were still unmoved
and suffocated her
to death in the coffin.
Ever since
they've obtained
the treasures of the dead.
Great!
One more story!
Mr. Lu.
Sir.
Miss Lu's storybook
has spread all over the capital.
With our lead,
all the people of the capital
believed that this story
was adapted from a true incident.
"Love's Betrayal:
The Fifth Person in the Tomb"
is selling really well.
Miss Lu is worthy of her reputation.
Do people even praise themselves
like you do?
Huh?
Do you know
how much danger you were in just now?
It's all right.
As long as you are around,
I am safe.
When this case is over,
we will get married.
I haven't become famous yet.
If you want
to keep writing storybooks,
I will grind ink for you
and serve you every day.
Sounds nice.
Sigh.
Where are you going?
Go to sleep.
How can you protect me
when you're so far away?
Tonight,
I'll protect you here.
This red string
will bind us together.
Even if monsters come here,
I will also be with you
and protect you.
Since we are tied together,
I will also protect you.
It's a promise.
Pinky promise.
The promise of a century.
Nanyi!
What's wrong?
Where's Miss Lu?
Nanyi is gone.
She's gone?
Qingqiu.
Sir.
Sleeping Incense?
Qingqiu, are you all right?
No wonder.
No wonder I was sound asleep.
What's that?
Limestone powder I put on Nanyi.
Lei Yu,
open it.
Yes.
This is...
Let me go!
Ji Xia?
It seems like
you know the incident back then
quite well.
Mr. Yu?
It's you?
Hmph.
Miss Lu,
there's no need to be surprised.
This is
just a disguise.
This...
Is this the Frozen Coffin?
Yes.
This is the Frozen Coffin.
It protects Xia's body
from rotting.
I want her to see
how I killed the people
who caused her death.
Tell me.
Who is the fifth tomb robber?
What?
Are you planning to kill again?
Shouldn't I?
They killed the person I love.
Am I wrong to get them
to pay with their lives?
Mr. Yu,
you are a physician
who saves countless people.
How did you end up
becoming a cruel murderer?
Their crimes
will be punished by the yamen.
Punished by the yamen?
Hahaha!
Miss Lu,
you are too naive.
The yamen couldn't even
solve the murders I committed.
How would they care about a case
of the daughter of a criminal
who has been dead for years?
Tell me.
Who is
the fifth tomb robber?
Actually,
this person doesn't exist.
I created
the fifth person.
I did it
to lure you.
This is the pouch
containing the limestone powder.
It seems like the culprit
found the pouch
and left it here.
Miss Lu,
we are acquaintances.
I want to hear an honest answer.
What you witnessed back then,
was it true?
I was young.
I went to play on the hills one day
and accidentally
found the tomb's entrance.
I went inside to explore it
out of curiosity.
I saw
Shi Kaiyang and the rest
stuff Ji Xia inside the coffin
and suffocate her to death
with my own eyes.
She was suffocated to death?
Xia,
it's all my fault
for letting you suffer this fate
because I was late.
But there's no need to worry.
The four people who harmed you
were killed by me.
I avenged you.
In the future,
no one can harm you again.
Mr. Yu,
I've told you the truth.
Can you
also tell me the truth?
What happened between you
and Ji Xia back then?
Why haven't you gotten over it
after getting revenge for 10 years?
I was a wandering physician.
When I passed by the capital,
I treated Grand Preceptor Ji
from the Snow Cold Spider Poison
of the Snow Spirit Painting.
After that,
I was treated as an esteemed guest.
Later,
I met Ji Xia who caught a cold
by coincidence.
I treated her.
We fell in love
with each other at first sight.
So,
we got engaged in secret.
However, I was poor.
I couldn't marry into her family.
Grand Preceptor Ji found out
and got angry.
Immediately,
he married Xia
to a noble family.
We didn't want to separate
and decided to elope.
So, Xia ingested
the Breathless Pill I created.
She would be in a fake death state
for 20 hours.
I guided the Grand Preceptor with words
and persuaded him
to bury Xia as quickly as possible.
Soon,
the Grand Preceptor
buried Xia.
Everything
was going according to my plan.
After she was buried,
I would rescue her.
Unexpectedly,
the tomb robbers
went ahead of me.
We've made a fortune this time!
Yes!
This is great.
Who are all of you?
Suppress her!
Let me go!
Don't let her escape!
Close the coffin lid!
No!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Let me out!
I could be together
with Xia
until we were old,
but the robbers
caused us to be separated
into two worlds.
Tell me.
Didn't they deserve to die?
This is Nanyi's handkerchief.
Mr. Yu,
did you steal the two-fish jade pendant?
It's better
for you to not know everything.
In Jinzhou,
I was influenced by
the murder method of your storybook.
So,
I murdered by imitating your storybook.
You were the one
who amended the storybook?
[It was a dark night at the hour of Zi
on the sixteenth day of the fifth month]
[Nimbly sneaked into Tianyi Teahouse]
[Looking around anxiously]
[Slit his throat]
However,
when the tomb was robbed,
you came late.
How did you find
the tomb robbers who had escaped?
♪I tried to break free♪
♪No longer holding tight♪
♪Even if I returned to loneliness♪
♪Like I'd never fallen in love♪
♪No more new memories♪
♪No more news from you♪
♪I chose to forget♪
♪Intentionally♪
♪I tried to accept the wasted time♪
♪Pretending that I didn't care♪
♪I had to close my eyes♪
♪And act blind to that side of mine♪
♪Until it became hard to tell♪
♪If my love for you was true or a lie♪
♪I've fooled time♪
♪But not myself♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪What a perfunctory farewell♪
♪Without even a goodbye♪
♪The coward in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪
♪I tried to accept the wasted time♪
♪Pretending that I didn't care♪
♪I had to close my eyes♪
♪And act blind to that side of mine♪
♪Until it became hard to tell♪
♪If my love for you was true or a lie♪
♪I've fooled time♪
♪But not myself♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪Your love eludes me♪
♪What should've come never did♪
♪This ending♪
♪Is more unexpected than the truth♪
♪Unexpected♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪What a perfunctory farewell♪
♪Without even a goodbye♪
♪The coward in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪