♪Thinking of you,
the sky turns light blue♪
the sunlight feels gentle♪
♪Thinking of you, the clouds look pink♪
♪One bite, so sweet♪
♪Loving you
is like honey melting in the sun♪
♪Even the coldest winter feels warm♪
♪Since falling for you,
I only want your company♪
♪You see through
all my sweet little schemes♪
♪What should I do?♪
[My Sassy Girl]
[Episode 2]
Let's go.
Quickly.
[Yunze Book Society]
Lu!
My Lord.
Ladies and gentlemen,
she wrote story books and killed people.
She's the murderer.
Murderer!
Arson suspects
need to be punished hard by the law.
Lei.
Yes.
Bring the troublemakers
to justice now.
Take them.
My Lord.
Mercy, My Lord.
Lu Nanyi has triggered public upset.
Take her back to the yamen right now.
She's under my watch
until the real culprit is caught.
You...!
Yes.
Ms. Lu.
This way.
Lin Qingqiu.
I thought
you would actually follow the rules.
Lu was right.
You are playing cat and mouse.
Wenyuan.
Take it easy.
Lu.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
[Clear Governance Leads to Clarity]
How long do I have to stay here?
When the real killer
is caught,
I'll let you go.
The killer has not been arrested.
You'll be in danger
if you leave here.
Then I'll work with you on this
and find the real killer.
So what would you do?
Since the murderer imitated
the plot in my story book...
So...
Who knows my story books better than me?
When I'm designing a story book,
I usually
think of the crime scene first.
Right.
Let's start with the Tianyi Teahouse.
Okay.
[Tianyi Teahouse]
Why would he let me mop the floor?
Where's the investigation?
My Lord.
I've got what you asked for.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I just cleaned the floor.
I see.
It's vinegar.
Lei.
Open the window for me.
What are you doing, My Lord?
I am really confused
about your behavior.
Blood!
How...
How did this happen?
Did you add alcohol
to the water in the mop?
Yes.
Then spill some vinegar
and reflect it with red light.
Then the blood
will be visible.
See?
What does this mean?
The blood focused in the central tiles.
But there's only a bit
along the way to the stage.
It means...
It means
that's where the murderer did it.
Yes.
Then he dragged him to the stage
and put him in the coffin.
Waiter.
Your teahouse
always closes late at night.
But
why did you close
on the afternoon of the 16th day?
Our boss, Mr. Bao,
said he was meeting an important guest.
He said
he would be rich
so it was okay to close early.
Who did he meet?
If he knew,
would he still be alive?
Let's go.
They're pretty good together...
[Jinzhou Yamen]
Yin.
I didn't expect Lord Lin to be so smart.
He tested the blood
only with a red umbrella and vinegar.
Of course.
Qingqiu
is my master's favorite student.
Oh,
right.
When he went for an investigation,
he brought Lu Nanyi?
Yeah.
I see these two
work together pretty well.
I don't like them being together.
[Clear Governance Leads to Clarity]
The road is narrow for enemies.
We run into each other again.
But
the world is fair.
Qiugqiu was a little hurt.
But luckily,
he saw through someone.
Just say
whatever you want to say.
He got a serious disease
and missed the Imperial Examination
just because you left him.
Lu Nanyi.
Let me tell you.
Don't you dare hurt him again.
Don't you worry.
I
never make the same mistake.
Good.
Get out.
It's too much to stay here.
I'll look into it myself.
Ms. Lu.
Write it down.
Yes.
I saw Mr. Ji five days ago
in the east side.
East side?
On the street of the east side.
Write it down.
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Fu.
Mr. Fu,
I'm here to give you a lead.
Write it down.
That night...
What are you doing?
Lu.
Why are you here?
Write it down.
I'm helping you gather clues
about the victim.
A western object for a clue.
I'm sure we will find the murderer.
I have my idea.
Start from those close to the victim.
They must
have important clues.
Let's go.
Wait.
Lu.
Slow down.
[Virtue Hall]
Remember.
Three times a day.
Take it on time.
[Ji Xinshi, adopted son of Ji Fanghai]
Hello.
Are you seeing a physician
or getting medicine?
We are...
[Jinzhou's Judicial Office]
From
Jinzhou's Judicial Office.
We are here
to bring justice for your Mr. Ji.
It's okay.
We're just here to ask a few questions.
Please, My Lord.
Mr. Ji
has been a physician for years.
Did he have any enemies?
My foster father was a good man.
He had never offended anyone,
let alone any enemies.
Foster father?
Yes.
I was deserted by my parents as a child.
My foster parents took me in,
raised me,
and taught me medicine.
How could someone do this cruel thing
to my good foster father?
Mr. Ji,
Lord Lin is here.
Here.
Lord Lin.
[Effective Medicine]
[Excellent Medical Skill]
[The tablet of my late father
Ji Fanghai]
My foster father
once helped these people.
They are here
to tribute to him.
I thought he was gone.
Why can this clinic
still receive patients?
Lucky for us,
Mr. Yu wants to stay here.
Are you talking
about Yu Huaigu, that Miracle Physician?
Yes.
It's him.
Where is he now?
He's there treating someone.
Let me pay a visit.
Hide somewhere.
Go.
Go inside.
Master.
He should be here.
Wait here.
Why are you here?
It's obvious.
To see a physician.
Really?
I guess you
are the Miracle Physician, Yu Huaigu.
[Yu Huaigu, the Miracle Physician]
I'm flattered.
I
am Yu Huaigu.
This is...?
Mr. Yu.
Oh.
I've been waiting for you.
See what's wrong with me.
My stomach hurts so much.
Ouch...
Ouch!
I remember
my appointment
was for cutting corn.
Corn?
What's that?
Clavus.
Alas.
Whatever it is.
Just...
Just do it then.
Come on.
Just do it.
OK.
Master,
you don't have to work hard for life.
So there won't be any callus
in your hand or foot.
There is one!
If you can't remove it,
that means you are not skillful.
Please, Mr. Yu.
Just show me
what you've got.
Uh...
Hurry up.
Let me try.
Do it.
Hold on a second.
Okay.
Hey,
don't move.
Don't move.
No.
Don't...
Don't move.
Yes...
Keep still...
Mouse!
Ah!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mr. Yu.
Help...
Patch me up.
It's bleeding.
This is the best trauma medicine
from Mr. Yu.
Remember to put it on regularly.
Okay.
I'm OK, Lu.
Do keep an eye on Lin Qingqiu.
He
is a bad boy.
Mr. Fu.
Get some rest.
Don't move around
or talk too much.
Be careful.
Lu.
Why are you out by yourself?
Do you know how worried I was?
Want some wontons?
My treat.
Sir.
Two bowls of wonton.
Large ones.
That's too much for me.
Get yourself full.
So you can solve the case.
You were out on the case by yourself.
Do you get any clues?
I haven't found anything
on the killer yet.
How about you?
Did you get anything?
The weapon.
The weapon used on Bao Sheng
is small and thin.
It doesn't look like a regular blade.
I think
it's for a special purpose.
Like butchers
use a scythe.
Headsmen
use a jackknife.
Once we know the weapon,
we can trace it down
and lock the murderer's identity.
Here's your wontons.
Anything else?
Tell me more.
No more for now.
It's like looking for a needle
in a haystack.
What's on your mind?
I'd say
that stories come from life.
We only focused on his method,
but not his motive of killing.
Tell me about it.
If Mr. Ji didn't have any enemies,
why couldn't it be a family member?
Solving a case
is more about evidence.
It's not like writing a story book.
You can't rely on your imagination.
I wasn't just imagining things.
When I wrote story books,
I'd first design
killers' methods and motives.
Step by step.
Logically and rigorously.
Your stories are not real.
They can't be compared to reality.
Trust my instincts.
Ji Xinshi is the most likely suspect.
An adopted son
killed his adopted father.
I think you've gone too far.
You don't have a clue now anyway.
Is that the murder suspect,
Ms. Lu?
I thought she was in jail.
Why did they let her out?
You tell me.
Who knows...
Waiter.
Yes.
Check.
Alright.
Look, dear.
Why is she here?
People have stigmatized you.
You didn't kill anyone.
But they believe you did.
You'll remain a murderer
to the people
until the real murderer is found.
Isn't that the murderer?
Why is she still out here?
So...
Come back with me.
Alright.
[Jinzhou Yamen]
In this retest,
I found Ji Fanghai
and Bao Sheng
both have the same bloody dander
[Story book Homicide Case]
under their fingernails.
Which means
the victims had a fight with the killer
before they died.
So the murderer
must have left
obvious traces of scratches
on his body.
What about the weapon?
The wound of the victims
is one cun long and half a cun deep.
Thin as a sheet. Fast in and out.
So the weapon could be
three cun long
and less than one cun wide.
Bao Sheng died in a coffin.
Mr. Ji was hanged by a red silk.
Both are extraordinary,
almost ritualistic ways of killing.
If we look
into the details of the rituals,
we can find some clues.
[Feiyun Tower]
I'm done.
A red silk fell from the sky
circling and twisting
between the lamp stands.
A part of it
tied in a herringbone knot
wrapping around the neck
of the unfaithful man.
Have you ever tried
this delicate plan?
Of course not.
You think I will kill someone
just for an experiment?
They are all stories.
Don't take it seriously.
But all the stories you wrote
are so detailed
and so vivid.
I wonder
what went through your mind
when you wrote such brutal stories.
Of course it was you.
Well...
Am I knotting it right
just like in her story book?
Yes.
That's it.
Well.
Good.
A red silk fell from the sky.
The red silk is done.
No.
It's too dangerous.
Let me do it.
Here.
What's this?
Dumb.
There's another one hanging.
What's going on?
Move aside, please.
Who is he?
Are you alright?
Lei.
Are you okay?
Luckily...
So
the regular herringbone knot
can't hold the weight of a grown man.
It will untie.
This murderer
is not a rigid man.
If he had tied a herringbone knot
as it is written in the story book,
the body
would have fallen straight to the stage.
Let's go.
Let's go back to yamen
and get the evidence.
Right.
[Jinzhou Yamen]
My Lord.
This is the red silk knot
that hung Mr. Ji
on the night of the temple fair.
It's a different knot
than the one in my story book.
It's very special
and firm.
And it will be getting tighter.
A normal person
wouldn't go through all that trouble
for tying this knot.
Looks like the killer
has done a lot of research on this.
It's understandable
that he would kill a gambler
like Bao Sheng.
But why a nice physician?
What's the murderer's motive?
If Mr. Ji didn't have any enemies,
why couldn't it be a family member?
An adopted son
killed his adopted father.
Lei.
Yes.
Go to the Virtue Hall now.
Let Ji Xinshi
make a prescription
for the disease on this.
Remember.
Make sure Ji Xinshi writes it himself.
Since the story book has been falsified,
there must be some clues
by comparing the handwriting.
Got it.
I'm on it.
I thought
you didn't believe my word.
Well.
You are investigating Ji Xinshi?
Sometimes
solving a case
is like writing a story book,
and you'll need some intuition.
My Lord.
This is the prescription
written by Ji Xinshi.
My Lord,
you got anything?
It doesn't match at all.
Perhaps
it's the injury on his hand
which affects
the strength of his strokes.
He has an injury on his hand?
He said he got it
when he was grinding medicine.
Lord Lin's rash was caused by food.
Mind the diet
and take some medicine. He'll be fine.
Mr. Ji.
Your hand...
I hurt myself
grinding medicine.
It's nothing serious.
Oh.
I see.
Be careful then.
Thanks, Lord Lei.
I'll get back then.
Thank you.
Take care, Lord Lei.
Keep this between us.
Yes.
[Jinzhou Yamen]
Now,
the most crucial weapon
has yet to be found.
Where do you think
it will be?
In Jinzhou,
it's easy to find a person
but it's a needle in a haystack
to find a weapon.
The killer killed twice,
with the same weapon.
Which means the killer uses it often.
Leave Bao Sheng's case aside.
Ji Fanghai's body was found
only an hour after he was killed.
The murderer didn't have time to escape.
He didn't have time
to throw away the weapon either.
Today is the Snow Praying Festival.
It must be
very busy out there.
Have a look.
We got all the story books.
Come and have a look.
Hey.
Masters, check our story books.
Sir.
Why do you put Ms. Lu's story books
at the end?
To tell you the truth,
I was going to use it for firewood.
Now
no one dares to read her story books.
Nice cloth.
Come.
Have a look.
Sell them to me.
I'll take them all.
One day her books will be hot again,
and then the price will double.
Pastries.
- Fresh pastries.
- Golden bracelet.
Sir.
Give me the best pastry you have here.
Madam.
Give me your most expensive jewelry.
It's fresh.
- This one looks nice.
- Take it.
Here you are.
Gadgets.
Hmm.
Poor taste.
Petty.
Lu is from a merchant family.
Why would she look
at a small piece of jewelry?
I knew well about her appetite.
How can she like a small flower cake?
Lu and I were childhood sweethearts.
I know everything
she likes.
It tastes so bad.
It looks so ugly.
I...
Happy Snow Praying Festival.
Qingqiu.
Lu.
You don't like my gifts?
Shut up.
I think
she prefers the one I gave her.
And you too!
I'm exhausted.
Oh.
Isn't that Ms. Lu?
It's her.
She thought we wouldn't recognize her
if she dressed as a man?
It's her.
Lu Nanyi from Yunze Book Society.
How dare a killer come out?
She's planning to poison us
for inspiration.
Yes.
Where is the law?
Murderer!
Take her!
She is the murderer!
Ms. Lu is not the murderer.
If anyone tries to embarrass her again,
I will not spare him.
But My Lord,
what if...
What if the murderer kills again?
Yeah.
I swear with my official position.
I'll resign
if I don't catch the culprit
within three days.
Qingqiu!
Lord Lin has done a lot of good
for the people of Jinzhou.
Since Lord Lin has guaranteed,
we'll wait for news
of the culprit's capture.
Let's all go home.
Let's go.
Go.
How do you guarantee to find the killer?
What if you're really asked to resign?
If I can't even protect you,
how can I be the world's best judge?
[Jinzhou Yamen]
[An adopted son
killed his adopted father.]
[A red silk fell from the sky.]
Right.
That makes sense.
[Virtue Hall]
Lu.
Will this work?
I've reconstructed the case of Mr. Ji
in the same way
that I write my story books.
Then I found
Ji Xinshi
was a perfect match
for the killer I set up.
So,
do what I say
and we'll get him.
Alright.
Let's go.
Mr. Ji Fanghai was beloved
for helping people in his lifetime.
But the killer has yet to be found.
These 100 taels
are a small pension from our office.
Please accept it, Mr. Ji.
You two are so kind.
My foster father...
His soul
will be comforted.
But I can't
accept this money.
Since Mr. Ji won't take it
and it's busy here,
we'll leave you to it.
See you.
Take care.
Okay.
Is this murderer really that cunning?
I heard they've found the weapon.
The weapon was found indeed.
They say
it's something less than three cun long
and less than one cun wide.
Now that they've found the weapon,
why hasn't Lord Lin arrested him?
Because
the weapon...
Mr. Ji.
No need to see us off.
Oh.
My Lords.
Goodbye.
Take care.
My Lord, what are you doing
with these things?
The scalpel
is made of stone.
The blade is smoothly polished.
The blade is sharp,
so the cuts are very smooth.
That's exactly the same
as the cuts on the body.
The coroner's scalpel
and the physician's lancet
are very similar.
Qingqiu.
You mean...
My Lord.
You are right.
This is the medicine
packed by Ji Xinshi himself.
Let's go to the Virtue Hall
and arrest Ji Xinshi now.
♪I tried to break free♪
♪No longer holding tight♪
♪Even if I returned to loneliness♪
♪Like I'd never fallen in love♪
♪No more new memories♪
♪No more news from you♪
♪I chose to forget♪
♪Intentionally♪
♪I tried to accept the wasted time♪
♪Pretending that I didn't care♪
♪I had to close my eyes♪
♪And act blind to that side of mine♪
♪Until it became hard to tell♪
♪If my love for you was true or a lie♪
♪I've fooled time♪
♪But not myself♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪What a perfunctory farewell♪
♪Without even a goodbye♪
♪The coward in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪
♪I tried to accept the wasted time♪
♪Pretending that I didn't care♪
♪I had to close my eyes♪
♪And act blind to that side of mine♪
♪Until it became hard to tell♪
♪If my love for you was true or a lie♪
♪I've fooled time♪
♪But not myself♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪Your love eludes me♪
♪What should've come never did♪
♪This ending♪
♪Is more unexpected than the truth♪
♪Unexpected♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪What a perfunctory farewell♪
♪Without even a goodbye♪
♪The coward in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪