♪Thinking of you,
the sky turns light blue♪
the sunlight feels gentle♪
♪Thinking of you, the clouds look pink♪
♪One bite, so sweet♪
♪Loving you
is like honey melting in the sun♪
♪Even the coldest winter feels warm♪
♪Since falling for you,
I only want your company♪
♪You see through
all my sweet little schemes♪
♪What should I do?♪
[My Sassy Girl]
[Episode 5]
[Prison]
I asked Lei Yu
to check with the Jiang family.
She was a good girl
and had no enemies.
Fu Wenyuan said
there was a maid at the scene.
We can get some clues from her.
I'll have Lei Yu check it out.
You...
You say it first.
I know
you think I'm impulsive.
But
this case is a matter of human life.
Let me go with you on the case.
OK?
OK.
Eat it.
It turns out
that Jiang Mengyu,
who was said to become a carp fairy,
died in the wine jar.
There must be something wrong
in the carp pond
in the Sun Residence.
The murderer
wanted to use a supernatural story
to cover up the truth.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I found
that before you eat,
you are extra sober.
What is this?
Open it and have a look.
My bracelet.
I managed to redeem it.
It is a beloved thing.
You should cherish it.
Let's go.
We will go to carp pond
and figure it out.
Yes.
Young Master just recovered
and is still in a bad mood.
He always likes to be alone.
Did he know what happened?
We can't keep it from him.
They love each other.
I thought Ms. Jiang had become a fairy.
Even if the young master missed her,
he knew she had a good ending.
But now,
the body is right in front of him.
Young Master
seems to be possessed.
He doesn't believe that she is dead.
Mr. Sun, I am touched
by your deep affection.
Sorry to bother you.
But we have to.
Please forgive us.
Everyone says Mengyu is dead.
But I don't believe it.
She became a fairy right before me.
How could she die?
Do you know
it is rumored that your wife
has an affair with Fu Wenyuan?
Impossible.
Mengyu and I have a deep love
for each other.
The night she became a fairy,
she still said goodbye to me.
I heard
Ms. Jiang disappeared
on the wedding night.
She was not missing.
She became a fairy.
A fairy!
Please tell us what you saw that day.
That night,
in the middle of the wedding banquet,
I heard Yu, the maid,
say that Mengyu was eager to see me.
I left the table halfway
and came to the backyard.
Mengyu.
What are you doing?
Come on down.
It's dangerous.
My dear.
Our fates have parted in this life.
Sorry for letting you down.
Farewell.
May the rest of your life be healthy.
Don't fail my love.
Mengyu.
Don't go, my dear.
What's going on?
Where's the bride?
Mengyu.
Since Mengyu left,
even the colored carp
in the pond became abnormal.
They leaped out of the pond
one after another
and then died,
as if they wanted to go with Mengyu.
There is no such thing
as ghosts and fairies.
As her husband,
you should recognize the truth
and find out the culprit for her.
No.
That's not her body.
She's a fairy.
Did you drink on the wedding night?
You might have got drunk.
Even if I made a mistake,
what about the leaping colored carp?
Everyone at the banquet saw it.
Mr. Sun loves his late wife so much.
I feel pity for that.
So it looks like
it is true that the pond is abnormal.
In the past six months,
is there any change in the pond?
Since half a year ago,
after Mengyu left,
nothing has changed here.
I even buried
the dead colored carp.
I built a fish grave.
Fish grave?
Where is it?
[Fish Grave]
The fish bones
are all black.
The toxin went into the bone marrow.
Only then would it appear black.
Are you saying the fish were poisoned?
Could Jiang Mengyu
have been poisoned as well?
Didn't Yin check the body?
Let's go and see.
The environment
where the body was stored
would affect our judgment of the body.
We have to go to the ice cellar
in the Sun Residence first.
[Wine]
It's really cold enough in here.
It is a great place to store corpses.
But
don't you think it's strange?
Why?
The murderer could destroy the body.
Why did they put the body
in a place so easy to find?
It means
the murderer had one and only plan.
To set someone up.
But who wanted to set up Fu Wenyuan?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Have a taste.
Well, I don't think
you should drink the wine here.
But if I don't taste it,
I will have no clue.
How is it?
Soft,
delicate,
and mellow.
Obviously, it is Ice Spring Wine
that has lasted enough time.
[Wine]
And that one with Jiang Mengyu inside
is strong
and microacid.
Obviously, it hasn't had enough time.
I thought you didn't drink that day.
Since I came here to investigate,
I have to prepare for it.
Sun's well-known Ice Spring Wines
are all stored here.
By convention,
the wine jars are sealed
every summer solstice.
No one is allowed to enter here.
You cannot open the wine
until the first month of the lunar year.
That is to say
that the one with Jiang Mengyu inside
has not lasted for enough time.
It was brought here
after the wine was sealed.
Yes.
The suspect was able
to enter and exit the ice cellar.
Presumably,
the suspect should be someone
in the Sun Residence.
Right.
It seems
there is someone who doesn't want us
to find out the truth.
[Wine]
Feeling better?
Do you think
we're going to die here?
No.
Lu.
We'll find a way.
There's gotta be a way.
Dongling Stone.
What Dongling Stone?
To preserve the temperature here,
this place
is all made of Dongling Stone.
This kind of stone
can also spark.
Let's heat up the stone gate
and sprinkle ice wine.
The stone gate will crack.
Now.
Yes.
Let's go.
[Jinzhou Yamen]
I see.
No wonder I took a long time
but still couldn't figure out
the specific time of death.
It turns out
the body has been kept
in the ice cellar for half a year.
The fish bones I brought back
were black.
Judgment by appearance,
they were poisoned.
So
the reason why the fish
jumped out of the pond
was someone poisoned them.
But
what poison
could let the fish
jump out of the water one by one?
For what kind of poison is it,
we still need to test it.
Yes.
Yin.
Next, it's your job.
Yes.
Oh.
By the way, My Lord.
Whoever tried to kill you this time
must be the murderer.
Did you see who locked the door?
My Lord.
Qingqiu.
Are you not feeling well?
Sick?
Just a little tired.
I need to take a break.
Are you asleep?
So hot.
You have a fever.
Take the medicine.
Come on.
Take it.
Then I'm leaving.
Take it yourself.
Don't move.
I'm so cold.
Shameless.
Lin Qingqiu.
For the sake of your illness,
forget it.
Yin.
Where is she?
I saw her just now.
It smells good.
Stop!
Did you just have this soup?
Yes.
Did you make it?
Yeah.
I made it.
Oh.
No wonder it tastes so good.
Spit out.
Just one sip of soup.
Why?
Spit out.
You fool.
I...
Why would I throw it up?
You fool.
That's the poisonous fish bone
I used to fumigate.
What?
The bones of fish in the Sun Residence.
Yin.
You must be joking.
I...
Am I gonna die?
What's wrong with him?
He drank poisonous fish bone soup.
What?
Another sick man.
I'm so hot.
I feel a raging fire
in my chest.
Hey.
I'm so hot.
Boss.
I am Liu.
Not Ms. Gong.
Boss.
Go away.
What's up?
He drank poisonous fish bone soup.
Ah.
Hey.
You guys catch him now.
Don't run.
What kind of poison is this?
I thought people would only bleed
when poisoned.
Why does he suddenly go crazy?
I'll go and have a look.
According to Sun's housekeeper,
Ice Spring Wine was sealed
on the 16th day of the eighth month,
and the winemaker would
add yeast on the 13th or 14th day.
But
the winemaker did not notice
anything unusual then.
Then the killer
could only do it on the 15th day.
Jiang Mengyu must have been killed
on the wedding night.
If we shorten the period,
it should be the four hours
between Jiang Mengyu was sent
to the bridal chamber
and when Sun Ren last saw her.
Sun Ren didn't look like
he was talking nonsense.
Is it possible
that he used the fairy story
to cover up the truth?
What?
♪I tried to break free♪
♪No longer holding tight♪
♪Even if I returned to loneliness♪
♪Like I'd never fallen in love♪
♪No more new memories♪
♪No more news from you♪
♪I chose to forget♪
♪Intentionally♪
♪I tried to accept the wasted time♪
♪Pretending that I didn't care♪
♪I had to close my eyes♪
♪And act blind to that side of mine♪
♪Until it became hard to tell♪
♪If my love for you was true or a lie♪
♪I've fooled time♪
♪But not myself♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪What a perfunctory farewell♪
♪Without even a goodbye♪
♪The coward in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪
♪I tried to accept the wasted time♪
♪Pretending that I didn't care♪
♪I had to close my eyes♪
♪And act blind to that side of mine♪
♪Until it became hard to tell♪
♪If my love for you was true or a lie♪
♪I've fooled time♪
♪But not myself♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪Your love eludes me♪
♪What should've come never did♪
♪This ending♪
♪Is more unexpected than the truth♪
♪Unexpected♪
♪I think I will understand in time♪
♪And stop relying on you♪
♪I can only draw in memory♪
♪A version of you that loves me♪
♪What a perfunctory farewell♪
♪Without even a goodbye♪
♪The coward in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪