♪NG after NG,
are you pleased this time?♪
♪Changed the topic
and focused on reading your expression♪
♪You don't need makeup. You can be
more beautiful than the moonlight♪
♪You said the world is fickle.
I just want love♪
♪I put a spell on you
and fill up your affections for me♪
♪This world is a gift from you♪
♪Even stunning beauty♪
♪Is no match for your blushing cheeks♪
♪Escape a world
of pleasure and debauchery♪
♪I'll doodle with you
in another universe♪
♪Drift past sweet words and romance♪
♪You're the best expression of love♪
♪Traveling through time and space,
loving and hating each other♪
♪Meeting you
is the most beautiful love story♪
=I Am Not Your Enemy=
(Adapted from "I Am Not Your Enemy"
Author: Black Circle and White Dot)
=Episode 19=
Drag her out.
You must stay alive
and watch me
destroy everything
you hold most dear.
(It Started with a Kiss)
Why are you out alone?
Where's Chu and Buxiao?
Did something happen to them?
We found traces of the lady in red
in the palace.
Chu hasn't recovered her martial arts.
What if the lady in red captures her?
Don't worry.
They're fine.
We found out that the lady in red's case
isn't as simple as we thought.
Speaking of which,
where's the painting?
Why are you looking for the painting?
I found that Father and Consort Shu
are looking for a painting an old eunuch
took out of the palace.
I suspect
it's the one you have.
I finally find out
why you're so hostile to me.
Did you know
that the man in the painting
was my father?
The palace is dangerous.
For the safety of Youchu
and the whole country,
I hope you can help me.
Su Buxiao.
Why are you still in the palace?
I found out
who the lady in red really is.
There seems to be nothing wrong
with the painting.
But why did the old eunuch
give you the painting?
And why is Father
in such a hurry to find this painting?
No.
Something must be wrong.
Look.
I got this
from Consort Shu's palace maid.
It's the same fabric
I found earlier
from the imperial garden.
So
Consort Shu's the lady in red?
Once we capture Consort Shu
and unravel their plot,
you'll be completely safe.
Buxiao.
Thank you.
Why have you been acting
so weird lately?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
Did...
I?
Are you regretting it?
You don't like me anymore?
I don't dislike you.
You like me then.
I...
Can't you just speak your mind?
Youchu, you know
we're from different worlds.
That's why I'm afraid that one day...
Buxiao.
You're the one I've been looking for.
The one willing to treat me well.
You've
changed a lot.
You'll protect me,
cherish me,
and even
risk your life for me.
I think
we have to live in the moment.
It doesn't matter what the outcome is.
What matters
is that I trust you.
As long as
I'm still in your world,
I'll try my best to treat you well.
His Majesty has an order.
Mi Youchu is asked
to meet His Majesty immediately.
Ms. Mi.
Come out.
Sir.
It's late.
I wonder why His Majesty summoned me.
I don't know either.
Please follow me back.
Hurry.
Alright.
(Looks like we need to
catch the lady in red soon)
(so that Youchu
can get out of the palace)
(and avoid
being bothered by the emperor.)
What are you doing?
What is this?
What's the matter?
(If I die, the throne
will be passed to Second Prince.)
Posthumous edict?
How is it possible?
I was assassinated
by the emperor's cronies,
Imperial Iron Guards.
Why would he have someone
send me the posthumous edict?
Are you saying
the men who assassinated you
were assigned by Father?
No wonder Father changed over the years
and asked Youchu to enter the palace
to join the maiden selection.
Turns out he had long been
under the lady in red's control.
Oh no.
They're in danger.
Your Highness.
Let me enter the palace with you.
Let's not alert them yet.
I'll enter the palace first.
You can standby outside the palace.
Your Majesty.
Mi Youchu is here.
I wonder why you summoned me
late at night.
I've had someone send General Mi home.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Since you're here,
have a chat with me.
Eat.
You despised me,
now
you have to rely on me to feed you.
Eat it.
Eat.
You...
If it wasn't for my son,
you think I'd take care of you?
I don't think she'll live much longer.
I knew it's her.
Gosh.
This country will be my son's.
Do you suspect it's her too?
Turns out that the lady in red
had infiltrated the palace
and disguised herself
as Consort Shu to control Father.
That's why Father sent a painting
containing a secret edict
to General Youmao.
It's to prevent someone else
from taking over the country
if something bad happens to him.
Who's there?
Sit.
I wouldn't dare.
I heard you were injured some time ago.
Looks like you haven't recovered fully.
I ordered someone to make it.
Try it.
Who?
Speak.
Come out.
Stop being sneaky.
Who?
Witch!
Second Prince?
Why does it feel different?
- Have I gotten stronger?
- Father.
How come the lady in red's skills
have deteriorated so much?
Father.
My son.
Youchu...
Drink it.
Yes.
You're not the emperor.
Do you think you can get away?
I didn't expect you
to disguise yourself as the emperor.
Wang Niuniu.
It's too late even if you find out.
The two of them
have fallen into my trap.
Tonight,
no one's coming to save you.
Turns out Consort Shu
is part of your plan.
That's right.
This time,
I want nothing to go wrong.
Wait.
I have something to say.
What do you have to say?
Is it worth it
for that unfaithful man?
He was the first person
to be nice to me,
but he also hurt me the most.
Your Majesty.
- Am I pretty?
- Yes.
You're the prettiest tonight.
Your Majesty.
Look at me.
Sure.
Who's there?
Niuniu?
You're having so much fun
together.
♪I've said all I can,
but my longing is still churning♪
♪It's like a dream♪
♪Love has grown deep.
What should we do?♪
♪Do you understand me?♪
♪Love is so lingering and heartbreaking♪
♪Tears trace the clues of memory♪
♪My heart rises and falls with you♪
♪Loving you makes me feel alive♪
♪The world is so vast.
I can do whatever i want♪
♪Why bother with fate?♪