♪NG after NG,
are you pleased this time?♪
♪Change the topic
and focus on reading your expression♪
♪You don't need makeup. You can be
more beautiful than the moonlight♪
♪You said the world is fickle.
I just want love♪
♪I put a spell on you
and fill up your affections for me♪
♪This world is a gift from you♪
♪Even stunning beauty♪
♪Is no match for your blushing cheeks♪
♪Escape a world
of pleasure and debauchery♪
♪I'll doodle with you
in another universe♪
♪Drift past sweet words and romance♪
♪You're the best expression of love♪
♪Traveling through time and space,
loving and hating each other♪
♪Meeting you
is the most beautiful love story♪
=I Am Not Your Enemy=
(Adapted from "I Am Not Your Enemy"
Author: Black Circle and White Dot)
=Episode 1=
Hurry!
- Catch her!
- Stop!
- Follow her.
- Catch her!
Hurry. Keep up!
- Over here.
- Hurry.
- Over there.
- Over there. Catch her!
Keep up. Over there.
Hurry!
Over there. Catch her. Hurry!
Stop!
(Prince De's Residence)
Go. Split up and get her.
Yes.
- Hurry!
- Here.
- Catch up!
Darling!
My father didn't rebel.
He was set up.
This is the proof.
Please help me give it to His Majesty.
Sure.
Xiaowu.
Grab her!
Darling!
Darling, what are you doing?
Let go.
No!
Have you ever wondered
how the dragon robe
got under your father's bed
and how the secret letter of rebellion
reach the emperor?
No.
You're my husband. You won't do this.
If it wasn't for Mi Army,
why would I marry
a boring innocent lady like you?
Your Highness.
Save her.
Send her to Zuihong Brothel.
Fuling.
You...
You'll all get retribution!
Retribution?
All right.
In your next life.
Why?
Throw her into the lotus pond
and feed your favorite koi fish.
Sure.
Let's go.
(If I have another life,)
(I'll make you pay.)
Am I
reborn?
(A Wife's Revenge)
(Mi)
(After Rebirth, Mi Youchu)
(After Rebirth, Three Years Old)
(After Rebirth, Eight Years Old)
(After Rebirth, 13 Years Old)
Good job.
- Good job.
Chu.
Father, Sister-in-law.
Did you gain your muscles
from eating too much protein powder?
Should you be a little more subtle?
All right.
Father, Sister-in-law, what about now?
That's more like it.
Good. How beautiful.
Youchu.
This is the husband
my father-in-law found for you.
It's Prince Su's recovery party today.
Go check it out.
Charm him
and bring him back
so that he asks
for your hand in marriage.
My mother-in-law is no longer around.
We have no news about your elder brother
after he went missing.
My father-in-law just wants
to find a good man to take care of you.
Father, Sister-in-law, don't worry.
I have the same idea.
I'll go get ready first.
Sure.
(Su Buxiao.)
(You ruined my family in my last life.)
(Fortunately, God was kind)
(to give me a chance to be reborn
and seek revenge on you.)
(Su Buxiao.)
(You're doomed.)
(Come to think of it,
I was just like them in my last life.)
(We competed with each other)
(to win Su Buxiao's favor.)
(Su Buxiao accidentally fell into
a monster cave at the recovery banquet,)
(and I saved him.)
(Let's see)
(how I'm going to kill you today.)
(Is it her?)
(Could it be her?)
Your Highness.
How shameless.
Xiaowu.
Your Highness.
What's wrong?
Do you feel a hint of murderous intent?
A murderous intent?
Your Highness.
The monster cave is ready.
Not bad.
All of you knows
that I fell off a horse a month ago
and was in a coma for a long time.
My father found an exotic animal
and said it could cure diseases
and ward off disasters.
I invite all of you
to see it today.
Your Highness, we have an assassin.
What assassin?
What's all the fuss?
How could the ladies bear to hurt me?
Yes.
But
you refuse to watch with me.
I feel
very upset.
I'm very upset.
- How could it be?
- Go.
Are you coming?
May I ask your name?
Your Highness.
I'm dizzy.
Dizzy?
Why do you look weak
but is actually strong?
- Your Highness!
Your Highness.
Do you think
this is a good way to find the one?
I wanted to jump myself just now,
but
it doesn't affect the plot.
- You can't leave.
- Don't leave.
Isn't the one...
Your Highness.
Miss.
Spare me.
I've done nothing to offend you.
In your next life.
Send her to Zuihong Brothel.
(You deserve to die.)
What a sunny day.
(Recovery Banquet. Three Days Ago.)
(Tofu Lady, Fortune Teller, Blacksmith)
Dear Su Daxiao,
you're about to enter
an unprecedented game
and start a new journey.
Gosh.
(Entering Game)
This game didn't trick me.
It's so realistic.
You will play as Su Buxiao.
Good luck.
♪I've said all I can,
but my longing is still churning♪
♪It's like a dream♪
♪Love has grown deep.
What should we do?♪
♪Do you understand me?♪
♪Love is so lingering and heartbreaking♪
♪Tears trace the clues of memory♪
♪My heart rises and falls with you♪
♪Loving you makes me feel alive♪
♪The world is so vast.
I can do whatever I want♪
♪Why bother with fate?♪