♪A silent world in the vast universe♪
♪A night where light and shadow intertwine♪
♪From chaos, I pen my tale♪
♪Through storms of wind and snow♪
♪Grandly descending into the mortal world♪
♪My sword cleaves the heavens apart♪
♪Through countless trials, my comfort found, blessed by the divine♪
♪Forging a sword with blood to pierce the dark night♪
♪Defying fate, rewriting destiny♪
♪Through fiery resolve, cleaving the heavens, unyielding to the storm♪
♪Bearing the scorching weight of the world♪
♪Risking everything for all beings♪
♪In this moment of rebirth♪
♪Burning through this lifetime's blossoms♪
[The Blossoming Love]
[Adapted from The Blossoming Love on com.duyao.poisonnovelgirl by Sui Yu Er An]
[Episode 7]
Alright.
The array is complete.
It will take just ten breaths to reach the Snow City.
Let's enter the array.
Don't forget what you promised me.
I promise.
Once we reach the Snow City,
I won't cause any trouble for you.
If I detect the scent of the Dark Clan,
I'll tell you immediately.
What's going on?
Someone reversed the array,
changing the teleportation into a killing trap.
Feng Yao, assist!
Sir,
the array is about to collapse.
- Are you okay? - Sir!
I'm fine.
No problem.
Fortunately, you've regained
60% of your spiritual power today.
Otherwise, we would have died
in the array.
There was no intrusion into the Greenview Heights.
How was this manipulated?
It must be the materials
for the array.
The teleportation array materials are already scarce.
Some of them were got from outside.
Someone must have
planted a killing spell
in the materials in advance.
It's...
it's all my fault.
I didn't detect
the killing spell's aura in time.
It's not your fault.
The killing spell was hidden from the start.
It's hard to detect.
Plus, the array requires refining the materials,
making it even more hidden
and harder to detect.
You're still so young.
If you could detect a killing spell,
you wouldn't need to absorb treasure energy for training.
We're all here.
You don't need to blame yourself.
This whole thing
was part of Sang Qi and the Decaying Immortal Pavilion's plan.
Perhaps from the Mirage Palace onward,
it was a two-birds-with-one-stone trap.
You mean,
when something happened at the Mirage Palace,
one goal was to steal the jade token,
the other was to mislead us
to give them a chance
to mess with the teleportation array?
You're the most skilled in arrays.
If you'd been here,
you'd have easily noticed the problem with the materials.
So, they created a huge distraction,
luring you away as well.
True.
Mr. Nan's research
on the teleportation array was no secret.
After you came out of the Dark Abyss,
you didn't go straight to the Snow City,
but chose to come here at Greenview Heights.
They must have guessed
that your spiritual power wasn't fully restored,
and wanted to use the teleportation array to go back to the Snow City.
It's all so cleverly connected,
a deadly trap.
Right now,
I'm more concerned about the situation in the Snow City.
I don't know how they will strike.
The paper crane was sent a few days ago.
Leader Xie must have received the message by now.
You don't need to worry too much.
Since the materials are destroyed now,
how long will it take
to gather them again?
Well...
it might take another ten days.
Is there any other way
to quickly return to the Snow City?
Actually,
there is something might help.
The Cloud Floating Airship?
That's right.
It belonged to Fu Lansheng, the former young master of the Jade Sky Palace.
He lost it to me in a bet long ago.
I haven't used it in many years.
The teleportation array
takes just ten breaths to reach,
but this one will take a bit longer.
That's why I didn't consider it at first.
But given the current situation,
it's better
than flying on a sword or riding a horse.
It's just a small boat.
How are we supposed to fit people on it?
A boat needs water to sail.
We can head out now.
How do we?
The Jade Sky Palace is truly wealthy.
What about the Snow City's finances?
You pulled me out of the Dark Abyss,
and I didn't bring any money with me.
As a disciple of the Snow City,
is there an allowance?
Let me give you some advice.
When you get to the Snow City,
it's better to listen more and talk less.
If you get into trouble and anger someone,
I won't help you.
You're saying this now,
but during the crisis earlier,
who was it
splitting his shield to protect me
with only 60% of his spiritual power recovered?
Xie Xuechen,
just admit it.
You can't bear to see me die.
Not wanting you to die
and not letting you die
are two completely different things.
You're just stubborn.
Xuyue,
this crisis
is much more serious than I expected.
You are not from the Immortal Alliance,
so you don't need to take further risks.
Don't go to the Snow City.
It's too late
to say that now.
Sang Qi and the Decaying Immortal Pavilion
joined forces against my Greenview Heights
and ruined my precious materials.
I'll definitely
get back at them for this.
Otherwise, how can
Greenview Heights survive?
Xuyue!
I have a plan.
Since we've come this far together,
let's continue this journey together.
Miss Mu,
do you mind?
The more friends, the more support.
With you joining us,
I couldn't be more delighted.
That's good.
Feng Yao,
guard here well.
If anything happens, contact with the paper crane.
Understood.
It's getting late.
Let's head out.
Bao,
stop being so upset.
Come out.
If father finds out
I'm such
a useless sniffer,
will he abandon me?
Fine,
you've never even met your father.
How could you have such deep feelings?
A father is a father,
even if I've never met him.
If you've never met your parents,
do they count as parents?
Of course, they do!
Mother said Father...
Ah...
are we... in the sky?
We're on our way to Mr. Xie's home.
Don't be scared.
Take a look around.
Isn't the moonlight beautiful?
I...
I'll wait until we land,
then I'll come out.
With your little courage,
you still want to follow me?
Yes,
I want to learn some skills.
Miss Mu.
Mr. Nan, you're here to enjoy the view too?
I must congratulate you, Miss Mu.
You've gotten what you wished for.
Thank you.
I've never been to the Snow City.
It should be quite interesting.
I would say,
because of your arrival,
the Snow City will become very interesting.
So,
you also find Xie Xuechen boring,
right?
You actually know.
It's not that he wants to be boring.
Those born with the extra sense
carry a lot on their shoulders.
They are expected to achieve much.
They are bound by many things.
Sometimes,
they can't even tell
whether what the world admires
is truly the person themselves
or merely the power they hold
to protect the world.
Mr. Nan, are you talking about Xie Xuechen,
or are you talking about yourself?
After all, you used to be someone
born with the extra sense.
Miss Mu, you're truly insightful.
But as you just said,
that was in the past.
Now, I've lost my three senses.
At most, I'm just...
an ordinary person who can draw symbols.
As the head of the Greenview Heights,
the top array master of our time,
and exceptionally intelligent,
if you consider yourself just an ordinary person,
then what are those truly ordinary people
supposed to think of themselves?
Alright.
I misspoke.
I'm just a straightforward person.
Please forgive me.
I just think
someone who can carve a new path
out of a deadlock,
and rise again to the peak
doesn't need
such cheap comfort or sympathy.
I don't want
nor do I have the right
to show any self-righteous kindness.
That kind of pity
is a sign of looking down on you.
I think you wouldn't agree
and would definitely not be happy.
Though you're from the Spirit Clan,
you see through people very clearly.
Likewise.
You're here to enjoy the view too?
Xuechen!
I'm here just getting some fresh air.
You're so unromantic.
In this regard,
you should learn from Mr. Nan more.
Once we reach the Snow City,
if you speak like this again,
I'm afraid you'll be expelled
in a few days.
We haven't even arrived yet.
Besides,
I only say
this kind of thing to you.
Fine.
Forget what I said.
What did you promise me?
Control myself.
I got it.
My mood is so bad,
even the moonlight isn't as beautiful now.
You guys talk.
Miss Mu really says
whatever she thinks
to you.
That's not always a good thing.
Isn't that fine?
Didn't you want to see through her
from the start?
I have one more thing to ask you.
What is it?
Why did you agree to take Miss Mu
back to the Snow City?
The war between humans and spirits lasted for so long.
Since I was young,
I've witnessed countless lives suffer.
Now, the war has ended,
but the scars
have never healed.
To this day,
the humans still enslave the spirits,
and the conflict between them has only deepened.
Hatred is like burning hot oil,
requiring countless bloodshed
to extinguish.
It's time to actively embrace the Spirit Clan.
It starts with allowing them into the sect.
And Miss Mu
is the first.
That's all?
Otherwise?
Then let it be,
human-spirit coexistence,
and a world of harmony.
I wish you will get
what you wish for.
[Two days later]
So, this is the Snow City.
It doesn't look like much
of an interesting place.
Interesting?
Once we reach the Snow City,
you will be an external disciple.
Everything must be done according to the rules.
The Snow City has strict rules.
No disciple will be tolerated for breaking the rules,
not even me.
Of course,
I've always followed the rules
and been the most obedient.
You know that.
The Snow City is very different
from the Mirage Palace.
Miss Mu,
you will soon realize this.
What's the difference?
The five sects of the Immortal Alliance all handle matters differently.
The Mirage Palace is vibrant,
but harsh and ruthless towards the Spirit Clan.
As for the Snow City,
as you can see,
snow-covered,
towering above the cold, steep cliffs,
pure and spotless,
leaving no room for any impurity.
Indeed,
the Lord of the Snow City
is a decisive and ruthless leader,
a man of unwavering fairness.
But it's okay.
If he's harsh with me,
I believe Mr. Xie
will definitely protect me.
Right?
[Snow City]
Welcome, Young Lord!
Young Lord.
[Elder Cang]
Elders,
it's good to see you.
Mr. Nan,
It's been many years.
Your elegance surpasses the past.
Elder Cang, you're joking.
Young Lord,
who is she?
This is Mu Xuanling.
Starting today,
she will be a disciple of the Snow City.
Naturally, she will begin
as an external disciple.
New disciples are managed by you, Elder Cang.
Elder Cang?
Should't I learn from you?
Young Lord,
this is very sudden.
She...
We will discuss her matter later.
I must see the Alliance Leader immediately.
[Elder Yu]
The Alliance Leader will leave seclusion tonight.
Please take a rest for now.
The Alliance Leader is still in seclusion?
Yes.
Since you left,
the Alliance Leader hasn't left seclusion.
You've exceeded your return deadline.
We've been very worried.
We wanted to report to the Alliance Leader
and headed to the Two Realms Mountain to find you,
but alas, he was in meditation.
We feared disturbing him
at a crucial moment,
worried he might fall into madness.
So, we had no choice but to wait.
I sent him a message via paper crane.
Was there no response
or arrangements?
A message?
No.
Did the message mention anything?
[Yongqian Pavilion]
Sir,
I, Xie Xuechen, request an audience.
Blood!
I detected the smell of blood!
Sir!
The Alliance Leader...
passed away.
Sir...
This is impossible.
How could this happen?
This is Snow City,
our own place.
How could this happen?
With the Leader's Spiritual Form stage
and disciples patrolling outside the Yongqian Pavilion,
how could he have been assassinated
without anyone noticing?
Who could have done this?
It's our failure to protect the Alliance Leader.
It's all my fault.
Why didn't I
go in to check on him earlier?
Investigate!
We must find out who the murderer is!
Sir,
Sang Qi collaborated with a traitor from the Immortal Alliance,
attempting to seize the Chaos Pearl.
Be careful.
I will return soon.
Elders,
the death of the Alliance Leader
brings great sorrow to the Snow City.
However,
you are the pillars of our sect.
You must not collapse.
This is not the time for self-blame,
nor for despair.
Please, Elders,
lock down the Snow City
and send word of the loss.
For the rest of the matters,
I will make arrangements.
Understood.
This paper crane hasn't been opened,
but it's stained with blood.
It seems the Leader
was murdered shortly before the paper crane
arrived.
The killer came for the Sect Leader's jade token.
It...
it is a fake.
Sword cultivators
must never
abandon their sword.
You did it.
Yan Tong.
Here.
Guard the Alliance Leader's body.
Understood.
Where are you going?
He's going to check on the Chaos Pearl.
It seems the matter with the Mirage Palace
wasn't a two-birds-with-one-stone situation,
but a three-birds-with-one-stone.
The enemy's target
[Pearl Tower]
is not just the Mirage Palace,
not just killing Xie Xuechen,
but also the Snow City.
They set up a killing spell
in the teleportation array,
aiming to destroy the array,
delaying Xuechen's return to the city,
so they could
kill the Alliance Leader
and seize the jade token.
Their ultimate goal
is the Chaos Pearl.
He saved the Mirage City,
but failed to save his own father.
How guilty must he feel?
This is an unsolvable trap.
Since returning to the Snow City,
he hasn't had a moment of rest.
He keeps distracting himself with various matters.
If this continues,
he will collapse.
He knows the Alliance Leader's expectations:
the Chaos Pearl,
the Snow City,
humanity,
and all beings.
All of them come
before the sorrow of losing his father.
He can only act like this.
But has he ever thought of himself?
Mr. Nan,
you've known him for many years.
Has he always been like this?
Well,
that was a long time ago.
Because we were both born with the extra sense,
I was always compared to him.
But for a long time,
we never met.
Until one time,
a crack appeared in the Immortals Array,
and many from the Dark Clan were running wild,
causing chaos in the human realm.
Xie Xuechen and I
were both sent to the Two Realms Mountain
to block the Dark Clan.
That was our first meeting.
Back then,
he was very different from now.
Kill!
♪Forging a sword with blood to pierce the dark night♪
♪Defying fate, rewriting destiny♪
♪Through fiery resolve♪
♪Cleaving the heavens♪
♪Unyielding to the storm♪
♪Bearing the scorching weight of the world♪
♪Risking everything for all beings♪
♪In this moment of rebirth♪
♪Burning through this lifetime's blossoms♪
Foolish!
The Dark Clan members will revive time and time again.
What you're doing now is meaningless!
Then we will kill faster than they revive.
Isn't that enough?
♪Forging a sword with blood to pierce the dark night♪
♪Defying fate, rewriting destiny♪
♪Through fiery resolve♪
♪Cleaving the heavens♪
Be careful!
♪Bearing the scorching weight of the world♪
I've predicted it before.
So, you're the one
who can predict the future.
Why don't we have a little competition?
I'm ahead by one point.
I scored one more point than you.
How about it?
Can you handle it?
No problem.
I knew I wouldn't die here.
I've often heard of you.
Are you interested in visiting the Snow City?
So,
Xie Xuechen also has moments
where he's quite competitive?
His father has always been strict with him,
but back then, he was full of youthful pride,
always rebellious.
He always thought
he should live his life
his own way.
I, too, thought
he could live life so freely.
But then, ten years ago,
he suddenly went to the Moonlight Heights
and suddenly entered seclusion at the Snow Cliff.
When we met again,
his character
had changed drastically.
Or rather,
he became a completely different person.
He became cold,
restrained,
and distant.
I don't know what exactly happened to him,
but he became the person
his father always hoped he would be.
[Half a month ago]
It's been ten years.
You've improved a lot.
You've become stronger than me.
Sir.
The Immortals Array is incomplete now.
You should go and fix it.
Understood.
When you return...
Well, let's talk when you return.
Cultivators must not have emotions.
They must dedicate themselves to their faith!
Did you forget?
Is your faith rooted in saving lives
and caring for all beings?
If so,
then you must sever all emotions.
If you have private favorites,
how can you embrace all beings
with great love?
You shouldn't favor any person
or anything,
not even yourself.
When you return...
Well, let's talk when you return.
In the dead of night,
you're practicing swordplay here at the Snow Cliff.
Aren't you afraid of causing a snow collapse
and burying the whole Snow City?
What are you doing here?
Leave here.
You're upset,
and now my bracelet is flashing with it.
How can I sleep?
I told you to leave here!
Xie Xuechen,
there's no shame
in showing weakness to others.
If you want to see,
I can cry for you right now.
Leave here.
I don't need your comfort.
Xie Xuechen,
why do you suppress yourself so much?
Is it because your father said
cultivators can't have emotions?
Back when we were trapped in Desire Demon's cage,
I saw you as a child.
Your father believed
that being heartless
was the only way to avoid having favorites
and to achieve great love.
I can't say he was wrong,
but I believe
the path of faith may be heartless,
but cultivators should value emotions.
If a person
doesn't even understand small love,
if their heart is left with only desolation and indifference,
how can they understand the true meaning
of all things in the world,
and how can they truly love all beings?
Just because you were born with the extra sense,
rare since ancient times,
your father
saw this as your destiny.
But, Xie Xuechen,
actually, no one can define your future.
Humans are born with emotions
and desires.
They must exist for a reason.
I am from the Spirit Clan,
and even I have emotions.
You are human,
how couldn't you have them?
If you have emotions,
you must release them,
express them.
Suppressing them deep inside
will cause problems.
Xie Xuechen,
you are just like everyone else,
flesh and blood.
You've already done enough.
Enough?
I used to refuse to listen to his words.
I was very rebellious.
And in the end, I made a huge mistake
that I can never undo.
Now,
I thought I had let go
of emotions and love,
but it turns out
his expectations were something I could never fulfill.
On the day I said goodbye to him here,
I really wanted to call him father,
but in the end, I didn't have the courage.
I am this hesitant,
this timid.
I will never hear
the words he wanted to say.
If the Alliance Leader were still here,
he would want to say this to you:
Xuechen,
all these years,
I have been very strict with you.
But actually, I always knew
how difficult it was for you.
From the day you were born,
I bound you with the responsibility
of the world's fate.
To force you to sever all emotions,
I even destroyed what you loved,
clipped your wings,
and imprisoned you in this small cage.
And all of this
was just to prepare you
for the challenges
you might face one day.
I often wondered
if I
worried too much,
if severing emotions was truly the only way.
Without my pressure,
you could have lived
freely and brilliantly,
soaring under an open sky.
Father...
Severing emotions and love
is easy to say,
but how many in this world can truly achieve it?
If even I cannot achieve it myself,
should I
have forced it upon you?
Xuechen,
I'm getting old.
There will be an end someday.
One day, I will leave.
Maybe my way
has grown outdated as well.
The future belongs
to your generation.
Go walk your own path.
I believe in you.
You will shoulder the responsibility
in your own way
and protect everything you need to protect.
Xuechen,
actually,
I'm also very timid.
There's something
I've always wanted to tell you.
I...
love you...
I love you deeply.
♪Searching for your face in the cycles of life♪
♪If the tears in my heart remain unseen♪
♪Can I still remain tireless?♪
♪Because my heart holds longing♪
♪A devoted soul asks not how far the road goes♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪