♪A silent world in the vast universe♪
♪A night where light and shadow intertwine♪
♪From chaos, I pen my tale♪
♪Through storms of wind and snow♪
♪Grandly descending into the mortal world♪
♪My sword cleaves the heavens apart♪
♪Through countless trials, my comfort found, blessed by the divine♪
♪Forging a sword with blood to pierce the dark night♪
♪Defying fate, rewriting destiny♪
♪Through fiery resolve, cleaving the heavens, unyielding to the storm♪
♪Bearing the scorching weight of the world♪
♪Risking everything for all beings♪
♪In this moment of rebirth♪
♪Burning through this lifetime's blossoms♪
[The Blossoming Love]
[Adapted from The Blossoming Love on com.duyao.poisonnovelgirl by Sui Yu Er An]
[Episode 22]
Are you still awake?
Have you been staying up
because you are worried about me?
Don't flatter yourself.
We are enemies.
If it weren't for String Bonding,
I'd gotten rid of you long ago.
Don't worry.
It's not that easy for me to die.
That's one more reason for me to worry.
I hope that the Lotus of Life dies
from the explosion caused by Feng Xiang today.
You can give up
and I can stop wasting my time with you.
I will try again
no matter what.
I hope the Lotus of Life is fine
and we will see the day
that we get lotus seeds.
I will be back.
What if…
What if you can't get back?
In that case,
the String Bonding will disappear on its own.
If that happens,
you can get back by yourself.
Why didn't you start with that?
I don't want to hear anything else.
I think that since Feng Xiang
is dead now,
the danger in the woods must have disappeared with her.
Even if there are still any,
I've been here yesterday.
I'll be fine.
Mu Xuanling.
If we are in danger,
don't mind me.
You are telling me that?
The Lotus of Life is no common plant.
It's not damaged at all.
Even the plants around it
are recovering fast.
The Lotus of Life.
The Lotus of Life!
It does exist.
Feng Xiang?
Saint.
You are all right?
Who are you?
We met yesterday.
Don't you remember?
My memory is not so bad
that I can't remember things happened yesterday.
The Lotus of Life.
Life.
Who are you?
Who sent you?
What are you doing here?
Did Feng Xiang come back to life
because of the Lotus of Life?
Saint,
we got into this place by accident.
I wonder what that is?
You mentioned
that it's the Lotus of Life.
Absorbing the aura of the world
and forming the Waterless Land,
nothing can do that
other than the Lotus of Life.
Can people gain immortality
by taking the Lotus of Life?
Can they recover
even if they suffered
an unrecoverable injury?
Of course.
The Lotus of Life can give people immortality,
let alone physical injuries.
You are already in the spiritual form stage.
You will live much longer than common people.
Why are you after immortality?
Immortality
is the goal of all cultivators.
With enough time,
one might break through the spiritual form
and ascend to a higher stage.
Besides,
I don't have much time left.
According to the records in the Immortal Alliance,
when the Dark Clan invaded the human realm,
the Dark Abyss kept pushing its boundary
toward the human world.
The top cultivator, Qian Guang,
mustered the power of all immortal sects
and formed the Immortal Alliance.
They paid a great price
to form the Immortals Array
which stopped the invasion of the Dark Clan.
You are not aged.
You should still have hundreds of years to live.
Is your lifespan shortened
because of some severe injury?
That's correct.
But it has nothing to do with you.
I don't know how did you wander into this place,
but you don't belong here.
Please leave.
This is a place with sufficient spiritual power.
We want to
train here.
Find someplace far away.
I don't like seeing
strange people.
Are you suspecting
that Feng Xiang revived after died yesterday,
plus she has lived for 6,000 years
because she ate the Lotus of Life?
But why doesn't she remember anything
that happened yesterday?
I don't understand that either.
Maybe there is something strange
about the Lotus of Life.
When I saw her yesterday,
it was as if she saw the Lotus of Life
for the first time.
I even speculated
that she had an accident
that caused her lifespan to shorten.
She knew that she didn't have much time left,
so she relied on the Lotus of Life
to live longer.
She probably has guarded this place
for the last 6,000 years.
That means
she has attained immortality,
yet she doesn't know it at all.
She thought she needed to wait for the Lotus of Life to bloom.
In that case,
she might have tried
to get the Lotus of Life multiple times.
If she has kept any of the lotus seeds
which are useless to her,
then we wouldn't have to wait
for the lotus to bloom
or fear that we don't have enough time.
What do you plan to do?
Let's keep waiting
and see all the things
that are abnormal about her.
She's still there.
She… She disappeared!
Feng Xiang has disappeared!
How did she disappear into thin air?
The Dark Cloud Mountain
just keeps surprising us with strangeness.
The sun is going down.
If Feng Xiang is still around,
the spirit fog will move with her.
It seems that she's no longer here.
But she couldn't be far away
so that she could
get here first thing tomorrow morning
to get the Lotus of Life.
To figure this out,
we need to find her first.
Maybe we can find some lotus seeds
at her resting place for the night.
I'll go search for Feng Xiang's aura.
You wait for me in the cave we stayed.
Why?
I've been following you around for a whole day
and you are ditching me
when we are so close to the truth.
My eyesight is not worse than yours.
I'm not afraid
after nightfall.
I'm just worried about you.
What for?
Now that we've traveled so long,
I have to know.
Don't even try to exclude me.
Fine.
Let's go check things out together.
What is she doing here?
Let's get closer.
Is she dead?
She's just feeble.
She'll wake up when the sun is up.
Isn't it dangerous for her
to be defenseless like this?
Even if she dies,
she'll revive tomorrow.
Right?
If there are lotus seeds left,
where could they be?
He…
Is he a human or a ghost?
Qian Guang!
Yes.
I am Qian Guang.
[Qian Guang]
How did you recognize me?
According to historical records,
Qian Guang was the first leader
who founded the Immortal Alliance.
He and Feng Xiang are companions.
They fought evils together
and were nightmares for the Dark Clan.
Yet, the two top spiritual form cultivators
disappeared after setting
the Immortals Array
and were never seen again.
The legend has it
that Qian Guang and Feng Xiang
are in love and formed a bond.
They were in seclusion.
No one has seen
these two saints again.
When I saw Feng Xiang,
I wondered about you.
Who would have thought
that my guess was right?
It has been 6,000 years.
If you didn't barge in here,
I'd have forgotten the time.
Sir,
how did you and Feng Xiang
get trapped in the Dark Cloud Mountain for 6,000 years?
Besides, it seems that Feng Xiang
is in a cycle.
Is it because of the Lotus of Life?
You have accurate intuition.
You are close to the truth.
Every day when the sun comes out,
Feng Xiang
would wake up here.
And when the sun goes down,
she would lose all her consciousness and memories
and get back here.
Then she'd begin
another repeated day here.
So,
she lived for 6,000 years,
yet it's just
one repeated day for her.
Is this the immortality brought by the Lotus of Life?
People dream about immortality.
They go to extremes for that.
But how can there be no cost?
Feng Xiang and I
encountered an evil cultivator
who tried to steal the Chaos Pearl.
He seemed young and decent,
yet he claimed that he learned
an evil method that absorbs the souls of others
to get immortality.
I can't believe that someone would cultivate
that kind of evil method for the Chaos Pearl.
To achieve immortality
with the Lotus of Life
also requires
a great sacrifice.
When Feng Xiang
ate the Lotus of Life,
she didn't get immortality.
She entered
a Realm of Power Inhibition.
There's nothing
but a lofty ladder
in that realm.
The cultivators' spiritual channels will be sealed off,
and have to take
the 38,000 attacks
from the blade-like wind
and get to the end of the lofty ladder.
Cultivators who haven't reached the spiritual form stage
will be shredded into dust
by a mere touch of the wind.
Those who are in the spiritual form stage
still have to suffer from the pain of slow-slicing
to end up meeting
the High Cyclic Divinity.
The High Cyclic Divinity?
He claims to be the deity of time in the divine realm
and has been guarding the realm for ten thousand years.
He said that he was waiting for someone.
Maybe a human,
or maybe not.
There are…
still Divine Clan members in the world.
I heard of a legend
that ten thousand years ago,
the Divine Clan protected all living beings
and was worshiped by them.
Yet, a human emperor, Zhao Ming,
misguided the inner demons of human beings
and attacked the Divine Clan.
The Divine Clan put him down
and he was reduced to a degenerated deity.
He was kept under the Lava
and thus the Dark Clan was born.
The Divine Clan found human beings repellent because of that
and stopped offering protection to the world.
So, how could there
be a Divine Clan member who's still guarding the world?
When I saw him,
he was filled with divine power.
If he's not a Divine Clan member,
who could he be?
He told me
that Feng Xiang ate the Lotus of Life
and bore the pain of countless slices
to meet him.
The High Cyclic Divinity
claimed that he was a kind deity.
Whoever meets him…
Whoever meets me
can make a wish.
I will make the wish come true.
But you have to know
that fate has its way.
If you are wishing for too much,
fate will make you pay.
That's the cost of wishes.
The more you wish for,
the greater the cost.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I wish
for immortality
and forever youth.
Once your wish is granted,
it can never be revoked
no matter what happens.
The same
with the cost.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Since then,
Feng Xiang has been stuck
on the same day forever.
The realm of the High Cyclic Divinity
only opens once for an individual.
It doesn't matter
how many Lotuses of Life
she eats after that.
Immortality
is where the Divine Clan's power lies.
It's not for human beings to get.
Immortality in that form
is a punishment.
That is the cost
that Feng Xiang paid.
But you have also existed for 6,000 years.
So,
did you make a wish to the High Cyclic Divinity as well?
You are brilliant.
Yes.
In the second year that she left,
I searched the world
and finally found her here.
She was already in the cycle.
I tried to take her away,
but once the sun went gown,
she would be brought back here.
I kept her company
for a hundred years.
That was over 36,000 days and nights.
But whenever she woke up,
her memories reset,
and she forgot what happened the day before.
Humans have a short lifespan.
I was out of time,
and I didn't want to
leave her alone in this world.
So,
I took the Lotus of Life
when it was
mature again.
Eventually,
I met the High Cyclic Divinity.
A hundred years ago,
she also came here
and wished for immortality.
I gave her that.
But she's stuck
in the same day forever.
Isn't that also immortality?
She got what she wished for.
So,
what is your wish?
Can I wish for her to get rid
of immortality like that?
Wishes granted cannot be changed.
Otherwise,
I'd be breaking my promise to her.
Can you restore her memories?
That would be the jurisdiction of the High Fate Divinity.
He never gives back
what he took away.
You should focus
on a wish for yourself.
I'm not
quite patient.
I wish
I could live and die with her
and never be apart.
Granted.
Feng Xiang.
Since then,
I have become her shadow.
I'm always close by,
yet she never knows.
Are you and Feng Xiang
a couple?
I owe her.
Back then,
the Dark Clan overrun the human world,
and I traveled around
to found the Immortal Alliance.
I heard of
Feng Xiang often.
They said that she made a name for herself at a young age
and that she's outstanding.
The Strike of Phoenix she developed
is a horror to the Dark Clan.
There were a lot of saints
who expressed their love
openly or secretly,
hoping to become
a couple in cultivation with her.
Yet Feng Xiang
was famously cruel and detached.
Cultivation was the only thing she cared about.
Romance
was the most annoying thing for her.
Having a no-good partner
will only delay my cultivation progress.
Men are always a drag.
You are different from them.
You are foolish,
yet you have more talents than me.
If you focus on your cultivation,
you might break through
the spiritual form one day
and achieve immortality.
Yet you are wasting your time
in fighting evils.
When bothered by all the trivial things,
you get distracted from your cultivation.
That slowed down your progress.
Your goal in cultivation
is to explore the limits of humanity.
My goal
is to maintain peace on this land.
Immortality
is not what I'm after.
I want to do as many things beneficial
to humanity as possible
in a limited lifespan.
So,
what's your answer?
Will you join the Immortal Alliance
and fight the Dark Clan with us?
Why would I?
I'm not attached to the mundane world in any way.
Cultivation
is the only thing I'm after.
Have you ever thought about
why you haven't broken through
the spiritual form stage
after a hundred years of cultivation?
Do you know the reason?
If you don't know the mundane world enough,
how can you break through the spiritual form stage?
If you don't do things that matter at the moment,
how can you achieve immortality?
You
are interesting in some ways.
So,
are you agreeing?
Come on.
I'll follow you
to get to know the mundane world
and deal with what matters at the moment.
You and Feng Xiang
are always together.
Are you
a couple now?
Saint Feng Xiang
is divine-like.
How can I offend her?
Since you don't have a partner,
what do you think of my sister?
Thank you
for your kindness.
I already
have someone on my mind.
By that, did you mean
Saint Feng Xiang?
Yes.
Have you told her?
No.
During the time we were together,
she never expressed any interest
in a romantic relationship with me.
I thought
she didn't see me that way.
After that,
I got busier
with affairs in the Immortal Alliance.
Feng Xiang
showed up less and less.
Someone else told me
that she was in seclusion in the East Sea.
She didn't even tell me
that she was leaving.
Feng Xiang!
How's your life
on the Osprey Island?
Thank you for showing your care, Leader Qian Guang.
I'm fine.
Since you love Feng Xiang so much,
why didn't you tell her?
Is it because
you were angry?
I've never been angry with her.
I didn't say anything
because I thought I'd die.
When forming the Immortals Array,
ten saints shall each take a star position
and face the power of retribution
of the array with the help of the Chaos Pearl.
That's how the array can be connected.
In the ten star positions,
one of them is the death position.
The one who takes that position
will take a lethal strike.
I kept that position to myself.
I thought
about telling her my feelings
before I die.
Maybe she'd laugh at me,
or
feel annoyed.
Or, maybe,
she also feels something for me.
But what then?
I had no chance to survive.
Why bring her bad feelings?
The Immortals Array was a success.
The Dark Clan was sealed.
Peace was returned to the human world,
and I was lucky enough to survive the hit.
I passed out for days,
and when I woke up, I learned that…
Saint Feng Xiang was severely injured
and is in seclusion on Osprey Island.
What?
With Feng Xiang's power,
she shouldn't be severely injured.
Half of the saints in the other positions
are dead.
Let alone
the death position.
Even with Saint Feng Xiang's power,
the Thunder Trial Fire is still too much.
That's the karma used to slay deities.
It was me
who was in the death position.
Saint Feng Xiang
asked for the death position for herself.
She switched the array diagram
and asked me to keep that from you.
She said that she was more powerful than you.
She'd be able to
survive the death position
and complete the Immortals Array.
I'm going to her now.
Leader Qian Guang,
Saint Feng Xiang never got back.
Where could she be?
We don't know.
Her heart was never on the Osprey Island.
If she wants to leave,
we can't stop her.
So, where did she
put her heart?
Since you have no affection for Saint,
why act so sentimental here?
She risked her life to complete the array
and never wanted anything in return.
If you care about her,
how can you not know her affection for you?
She's such a proud and respected person.
If it weren't for her feelings for you,
why would she stay by your side the whole time?
The world sees you as a benevolent person
who takes the world on his shoulders.
Who knows that she…
For you,
she wasted her time
and delayed her cultivation.
Why do you think she did that?
Why?
I've never thought about that.
Maybe I just didn't have the courage.
How could I not love Feng Xiang?
But Feng Xiang said
that I was different from the others.
I didn't admire her or fastened onto her.
That's why she was willing to hang out with me.
If I told her
about my feelings,
I would have been no different
from the others.
I was afraid that I'd lose her.
Saint Feng Xiang
is divine-like.
How can I offend her?
Since you don't have a partner,
what do you think of my sister?
Thank you
for your kindness.
I already
have someone on my mind.
She heard my lie,
and I never had the chance
to tell her my feelings.
I have no chance to do that.
This is how the world works.
You don't always get
a second chance.
Qian Guang.
You've been guarding Feng Xiang for 6,000 years
and never left her side
I believe
that you value human connections.
If you know where the lotus seeds that were produced are,
please tell me
so that I can detoxify the Disillusion Water
and save someone's life.
People drink the Disillusion Water
to forget about sentiments.
Since she had a realization,
why force it?
If she did have a realization,
she doesn't need assistance to control her mind
and force herself to forget.
She was forced to become detached
and it's conflicting with her faith,
hurting her both inside and outside.
That's why she's in danger.
Xie Xuechen.
Who are you talking about?
What is
the Disillusion Water?
She and I were enemies.
We met by accident and got to know each other.
She risked everything to help me,
and I haven't gotten a chance
- to repay her. - The things
- that Xie Xuechen is talking about… - She was set up by a treacherous man
- are so familiar somehow. - and was forced to take the Disillusion Water.
- Now her life is in danger. - Is it because…
I'm worried that she can't wait
for the lotus to bloom.
When the lotus seeds fall, she'd be…
Xuanling!
You want the seeds of the Lotus of Life
for me.
Qian Guang.
If it was her choice,
I could let go
as long as she could be free.
But you can see how she is.
The more she's suffering,
the more she's not willing to forget.
If we don't cure her,
the Disillusion Water will be lethal to her.
If you can tell me
where the seeds are,
I would be in debt to you.
I will pay you back,
wherever, whenever,
and however.
No need to feel that you owe me.
Feng Xiang got all the Lotuses of Life
that bloomed over the years.
She just doesn't remember.
I buried all the lotus seeds
that Feng Xiang left behind here.
Thank you, Qian Guang.
The seeds of the Lotus of Life
are also known as Worldly Bitterness.
The Disillusion Grass is a poison,
and the lotus seed is the medicine.
People think that becoming detached
and having their feelings cleared
is the realization.
But the true realization
is still being benevolent
and loving the world
after tasting all the bitterness of the world
and feeling all the sorrows.
That
is
disillusion.
Being benevolent
after tasting all the bitterness of the world.
That's the true disillusion.
You can have
the lotus seed.
Leave this place
and never come back.
Thank you.
Each lotus seed
represents a hundred years.
Qian Guang.
Is there anything we can do for you?
This is the power of divinities.
No one can change it.
I'm grateful
for your kindness.
Have you tried to communicate with the High Fate Divinity?
Maybe he can
lift the curse.
Curse?
Right.
This wish is no different from a curse.
I thought about finding the High Fate Divinity.
But there's only
the High Cyclic Divinity in the vast divine realm.
There were no other divinities.
The High Cyclic Divinity
is strange.
He's not as kind as he claims.
Maybe
he was lying.
He did say
that someone
was lying.
Who is it?
He said…
[High Cyclic Divinity]
This world
is just a lie.
The sun is about to come up.
I wish I could enjoy
the sunrise with her.
Take the lotus seed.
What if I'm not recovered
after taking it?
What if I still don't like you?
This time,
I'm not letting you go no matter what.
I'm curious
how I feel
about you.
Mu Xuanling.
Mu Xuanling!
I said
that I would protect you no matter what.
I will stay by your side.
Enough!
Xie Xuechen!
Do not get closer!
Mu Xuanling!
I don't have romantic feelings for Mister,
but for you, I do.
So, you are able to avoid me.
Are you
willing to take me with you?
[Swirling Snow Pavilion]
You can live
a normal life here.
This is Snow City.
It's my decision.
I don't want to go back to the Dark Abyss.
I want to live under the sun.
When we have a chance,
I'll show you the real human world.
Mu Xuanling.
♪Can I still remain tireless…♪
Wait for me.
♪Because my heart holds longing…♪
Mu Xuanling.
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting…♪
Xie Xuechen.
Xuanling!
You remember now!
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets…♪
Xie Xuechen.
I'm sorry.
I hurt you so many times.
You must have hurt every time.
I remember everything now.
They didn't hurt.
Not at all.
I deserved all those.
Think of them
as my punishments.
No.
Not punishments.
They are…
What?
♪If the tears in my heart remain unseen♪
♪Can I still remain tireless?♪
♪Because my heart holds longing…♪
Xie Xuechen.
Thank you for bringing me back.
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets…♪
Mu Xuanling.
Thank you for coming back.
Thank you.
Guys.
Any reason that you are here?
We got into the Phoenix Perch Forest by accident.
We are leaving.
Saint,
I know
that you are searching for the Lotus of Life.
But it will be some time for the Lotus of Life
to mature.
You could go to the cave
in the southeast of the Phoenix Perch Forest.
I heard that the cave is extremely dark
and no light can get in,
but there are rare plants
that can prolong one's life.
You don't have to bring light
to discover
things that deserve your attention
more than the Lotus of Life.
She still went to the Waterless Land
to guard the Lotus of Life.
Is there no chance to break the curse
of the High Cyclic Divinity?
I know.
You are thinking that the cave is dark
and Qian Guang might be able to show his physical form.
Even so,
it's just one day of happiness for them.
Right?
For Qian Guang,
this one day
allows them
to live happily
and show their affection to each other.
That triumphs many days
in the past and the future.
Detachment doesn't mean freedom.
Sentiments don't mean pain.
For those who have loved,
even miserable death
can't change their hearts.
It's the same for Feng Xiang,
for Qian Guang,
and
for us.
Where are we going now?
Where can you go?
Snow City guards the Chaos Pearl,
and I will guard you.
No matter what you think about that,
you have to come back to Snow City with me.
I don't know if I should call you unreasonable
or scoundrel.
Call me whatever you want,
but you are not getting away.
Xie Xuechen.
Your String Bonding is still effective.
Why are you holding me so tight?
Are you worried that I might get away?
Does holding one's hand
mean keeping someone from getting away?
Don't you know that String Bonding
is the bonding of marriage?
Miss Mu.
You don't care about the Immortal Alliance
or humanity.
You are helping Xie Xuechen
because you want to see
what interesting things you can find
in this boring world.
What you really
care about
is me.
Am I right?
What are you doing here?
It seems that you've found the lotus seed.
It took some effort,
but we found it.
Xuanling has returned to her normal status.
She remembers everything now.
Shouldn't you be waiting in Greenview Heights
for our news?
What brought you here?
I sensed the alert
from the jade I gave Miss Mu.
It seems that some sort of attack
triggered the array on it.
I was worried that something might have happened,
so I rushed here.
Alert from the jade?
But I didn't sense
that alert.
Maybe I have triggered
the array by accident.
It might be me.
Let's not waste our time here.
Let's talk outside.
Sir,
she seems to be avoiding you.
♪Searching for your face in the cycles of life♪
♪If the tears in my heart remain unseen♪
♪Can I still remain tireless?♪
♪Because my heart holds longing♪
♪A devoted soul asks not how far the road goes♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪