♪A silent world in the vast universe♪
♪A night where light and shadow intertwine♪
♪From chaos, I pen my tale♪
♪Through storms of wind and snow♪
♪Grandly descending into the mortal world♪
♪My sword cleaves the heavens apart♪
♪Through countless trials, my comfort found, blessed by the divine♪
♪Forging a sword with blood to pierce the dark night♪
♪Defying fate, rewriting destiny♪
♪Through fiery resolve, cleaving the heavens, unyielding to the storm♪
♪Bearing the scorching weight of the world♪
♪Risking everything for all beings♪
♪In this moment of rebirth♪
♪Burning through this lifetime's blossoms♪
[The Blossoming Love]
[Adapted from The Blossoming Love on com.duyao.poisonnovelgirl by Sui Yu Er An]
[Episode 34]
Yan.
Are you upset?
I'm upset too.
Tomorrow
is Qingyang's birthday feast.
The kitchen
has prepared a lot of fine wine for the feast.
I stole two pots out.
Do you want to drink?
Thank you.
I don't have parents.
I've never celebrated a birthday.
How about you?
I have parents,
but I've never celebrated a birthday either.
I heard your story from He Zhou.
Zhao Ming said
some people
are destined to never prioritize love.
But I believe
love cannot be hidden.
Yan,
when you recall Qingyang's feelings for you,
were they real?
Could it be that she was lying
about the last words she said to you?
Have you thought about asking her again?
You really have a lot of questions.
But can't you answer one of them?
I'm going to find Zhao Ming.
He always has many answers for me.
Wine can heal wounds.
You...
don't waste it.
[Graceful Palace]
You've been drinking.
You once said
you've only ever used me,
that you never loved me.
Was that true?
It was true.
I'll ask you one last time.
Can you stop lying to me?
If you're willing to tell the truth,
I'll help you.
No matter how many times you ask,
my answer will always be the same.
You are just my knife,
a tool that makes my life better.
Of course,
I still need you now.
If you're willing to help me,
I can keep pretending to like you.
Even after marrying Zhao Ming,
- I can still continue... - Enough!
You're truly heartless.
[Everbright Palace]
Have you been drinking?
Yes.
I've drunk
such a big jar of wine...
How did you get hurt?
I fell.
How did you fall so badly?
Because I'm a pearl...
Pearls roll easily!
This is a gift
I prepared for a long time.
The material
is from the prize you helped me win.
Inside, I've engraved
"Zhao Ming."
I didn't plan to give it to you,
but after thinking about it,
I decided to give it to you
to congratulate you and Qingyang.
He Zhou said you've made a noise lately,
as if you're working on something.
Turns out you were making this.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'm glad you like it.
Pearl,
don't drink so much wine again,
okay?
But if I hadn't drunk so much,
I wouldn't have the courage to give this gift to you.
What's this?
This?
This is...
a popular tattoo style recently.
Does it look good?
♪If not...♪
You're drunk.
I'll take you back.
♪In the vast wildness, we sing and enjoy the moonlight...♪
Are you cold?
If you're cold, just hold on tighter.
♪It's like a gentle kiss from warm winds...♪
How I wish
this journey could be a little longer.
Zhao Ming,
in the years to come,
I wish all your dreams come true,
and may you live in happiness and peace.
♪Because you've stayed the same♪
♪The brilliance endures♪
Thank you, Your Majesty,
for hosting this birthday feast for my daughter.
I offer a cup to Your Majesty.
Please!
- Please. - Please.
I would like to offer a dance to Your Majesty
as a token of respect.
My daughter has practiced dancing since childhood.
Her dancing skills
are well-known
in our Xilin Kingdom.
I'm looking forward to it.
Nice!
Very nice...
Qingyang, what are you doing?
Kneel!
Princess Qingyang dares to murder His Majesty!
Truly an act of rebellion!
An unforgivable crime!
The King of Xilin cannot escape his punishment.
The whole family is to be executed!
The second bet
is that human nature is changeable.
Even family and friends can betray you.
This matter has nothing to do with me.
Please, Your Majesty, see it clearly!
Take them away.
- Yes! - Yes!
Move!
Zhao Ming,
you can't kill me.
I am the king of Xilin!
Behind me,
there are tens of thousands of Xilin soldiers
waiting for my return!
The King of Xilin and the princess conspired to murder me.
In front of everyone, there is no denying it.
Legally and morally,
I have the right to kill you.
The people have their sense of justice.
The war has just ended.
I believe the soldiers of Xilin
will not risk another war
with Dongze
for such a vile king.
Take them away!
Yes!
You...
Behave yourself!
Move!
- Zhao Ming! - Move!
You can't kill me!
Oh...
are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you think the King of Xilin
has gone mad?
His courage is too great.
Yeah.
How will His Majesty deal with them?
What crime is it to murder an emperor?
You should know better than I do.
But there's one thing,
perhaps,
you should take a look at.
[Everjoy Palace]
You shouldn't get used to all this.
You're truly heartless.
This ruined life
has come to this point.
It's enough.
You once said
you've only ever used me,
that you never loved me.
Was that true?
I'll ask you one last time...
I'll ask you one last time!
Can you stop lying to me?
What are you doing here?
Leave!
I won't leave!
You still won't tell the truth,
will you?
You risked being burned alive
just to ask me these questions?
When did you become so crazy?
To deal with someone like you,
of course, I must use crazy methods.
Is the answer really that important?
Yes.
I've told you
that no matter when,
the answer is always the same.
Leave.
Leave!
You're not even afraid of death,
yet you use a better life as an excuse
and push me away.
Do you think I'll believe that?
I was using you the whole time.
Stop imagining things!
I just saw the fragment of the Celestial Ladder.
That's the treasure of Nanyuan.
So, you hid it back then,
didn't you?
You're right.
I'm just a fool.
I couldn't see everything you did,
every word you said was a lie.
You meant to push me away.
You wanted me to give up,
because you know,
as long as the King of Xilin is alive,
he will never truly set you free.
He will keep using you to control me,
until I die.
Right?
Does asking these questions matter now?
In this situation today,
Qingyang must die.
Then I'll die with you.
I don't need that.
This is my vow.
Yan
will always protect the princess.
This was the vow I made in my heart.
In the years I left Xilin,
I broke my vow.
But today,
I won't leave.
♪Can I still remain tireless?♪
♪Because my heart holds longing♪
♪A devoted soul asks not♪
♪How far the road goes♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years...♪
I believe you.
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms...♪
I believe you!
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms...♪
Is the situation resolved?
From today on,
there will be no more Qingyang and Yan in this world.
♪I desire nothing else...♪
Death,
is it fortunate?
Sometimes it is.
Has Fate
mentioned where the divine child is?
Well...
he hasn't.
Since Fate does not answer,
I no longer wish to wait!
Now go to all the water sources in the human realm,
whether by poisoning or emptying them,
bring forth a dry spell
as a punishment!
And inform the humans
that the source of the disaster
lies with Zhao Ming,
and to end the disaster,
a sacrifice of young boys and girls
must be made!
Understood.
The area affected by this dry spell
and the duration of it
hasn't been seen or heard of
in nearly a hundred years!
Dongze is filled with starving people.
They've even resorted to man-eating.
The nobles collectively request Your Majesty
to follow the divine edict
and sacrifice 3,000 young boys and girls.
Please, Your Majesty, follow the divine edict
and sacrifice 3,000 young boys and girls!
He is a foolish ruler!
A disaster!
It's all his fault!
- Kill him! - Kill him!
He's not fit to be a wise ruler!
Kill him!
He's not even human!
He doesn't want us to have peace!
A beast!
When the war ended,
the army returned to the city,
the people cheered along the way.
How little time has passed,
and yet things have turned out this way.
They probably forgot
who was protecting them all along.
May the deities bless us.
Please forgive them.
Bless us...
What are you doing?
This is for the deities!
That chicken is mine.
That duck is mine.
I'm so hungry.
Me too.
Guarding these dead things,
yet treating human life like dirt.
What dead things?
This is great disrespect to the deities!
Get away from here!
Who do you think you're talking to?
I don't care who you are.
The deities are the highest in this world!
Exactly.
They're causing trouble here.
- Exactly. - Exactly.
They're dishonoring the deities...
Stop that!
The deities will punish us!
This is unacceptable!
This will anger the deities!
It's not allowed!
- It's not allowed! - It's not allowed!
Why?
The deities will punish us.
The deities will bring down their wrath.
You're Saint Emperor Zhao Ming!
Your Majesty, spare us!
Dongze forbids sacrifices.
You can't even feed
your parents and children,
yet you still sacrifice to the deities!
Please spare us!
May the deities forgive us...
You have a lot of nerve,
daring to secretly capture young boys and girls.
Your Majesty, spare us.
We were just following orders.
The act of capturing young boys and girls
started in many villages long ago.
It was not just here.
The law doesn't punish the masses.
Please, Your Majesty, spare us!
He Zhou,
gather 3,000 young boys and girls,
and bring them to the palace immediately.
Yes!
You're bringing the young boys and girls to the palace
to protect them,
right?
Only then
will they not be captured by others for sacrifice.
Your people
have made you sad.
Are you angry with them?
They were just scared.
The humans have no divine channels, except for me.
They can't cultivate.
Facing a disaster far beyond their own strength,
they will be fearful,
confused,
complain,
and even do wrong things.
I admit, I have been disappointed,
but I will not give up.
I know,
what you see
is not just about one person or one thing,
it's about the whole world
and all affairs.
I remember you once told me
that people are simple,
yet also complex.
They're weak,
yet they can also have strength.
There's one thing
I've never told you.
Actually,
I already know I'm the Chaos Pearl.
When did you find out?
But...
I want to stay by your side as Pearl.
Do you know
why I came to the human realm?
The Chaos Pearl is kind and merciful,
unwilling to see the suffering of the people.
So it sacrifices itself to mend the heavens.
Mending the heavens
was Hao Tian's order.
Although I can't recall things from the past,
I faintly remember
that Hao Tian once told me
that the existence of me and the Book of Fate
was only to maintain the order and operation of the world.
As for the life journey of all beings,
and the rise and fall of fortunes,
it has nothing to do with us.
My connection with this world
is you.
You taught me
what it means to be human,
what love is,
what it means to protect.
Once the young boys and girls arrive,
I will protect them with you.
Just like you said...
that's the resolve to protect.
He Zhou,
we found a few new divine servants,
four boys and two girls,
all born in the year of Cang Hao.
Come with me.
My mother said,
once you ascend to the heavens, you can never return home.
What's there to be sad about?
To be chosen as a divine servant
is a family's honor.
That's a good thing.
Becoming a divine servant means being sacrificed.
We will die!
Don't talk nonsense.
That's not death.
It's just leaving this mortal body
and going to the Celestial Realm
to serve the deities.
His Majesty has given orders
to take good care of these children.
Understood.
Does His Majesty want us to die?
Don't misunderstand him, dear.
His Majesty was born to be favored by the heavens.
He should never be tainted by the mortal world.
But I have been by his side for over ten years.
I have seen him work tirelessly every day
for ordinary people like you and me.
Hasn't your village
received his protection
and blessings?
Even the Saint Emperor
has his difficulties,
but we must trust him.
He will give us the best of the world.
Your Grace, you summoned me.
What's it for?
I want you to help the Emperor Zhao Ming
become the strongest in the world.
Zhao Ming intends to slay the deities.
Helping him
is like destroying the Celestial Realm.
Now, the two realms are in chaos,
the divine artifact falls in love,
the four seasons are out of order,
and disasters are widespread.
Relying solely on you to act on my laws
is not enough.
Only the strongest in the world
can be my vessel
and help me descend.
Your Grace,
you actually decide to personally correct the errors
and save the world?
Rather than fixing the mistakes,
it's better to start over.
What does starting over mean?
When the time comes,
you will know.
Off you go.
Your Majesty,
the advisor has returned.
You have been away for days.
Are you returning
because you're concerned about the palace
and the people here?
What I'm concerned about
is your will.
The Jun Tian Sword...
Your Majesty, you were born with divine channels,
and also own the sovereign fortune.
If the Jun Tian Sword can acknowledge you as its master,
you could fight against the Divine Clan.
I've figured out the Jun Tian Swordsmanship,
and even visited the entrance to the Guixu.
However,
I can only sense a strong sword energy,
but cannot make the Jun Tian Sword appear.
During my time away,
I searched for ancient texts
and found a record.
The Jun Tian Sword
originates from the primal chaos energy.
To draw it out of its sheath,
we need to use killing aura as bait.
Using killing aura as bait?
Your Majesty,
you can use human blood as a sacrifice.
Other's blood
or your own will work.
Thank you for your guidance.
Since you've returned,
will you stay?
No.
By fate,
I will meet with Your Majesty again.
[Graceful Palace]
[Ming]
Pearl,
[Bright Palace]
I will leave the palace for a few days.
What are you going to do?
Retrieve the sword from the Guixu.
When will you depart?
Today.
Right now.
I will go with you!
No,
I will go alone.
The Guixu is dangerous.
How can Your Majesty go alone?
I will accompany you.
My mind is made up.
But Your Majesty...
You should stay in the palace,
protect the children well,
and make sure nothing happens to them.
Alright.
I will stay in the palace,
behind you,
waiting for your return.
Take good care of yourself.
In ten days,
I will return.
Go ahead and do what you need to do.
I will do my best to protect here.
I trust you.
I trust you too.
I'm leaving now.
[A few days later]
You've almost worn out this book.
What are you looking for?
Since I am transformed from the Chaos Pearl,
how could I have no Chaos Power?
When you first took form,
we were also puzzled.
His Majesty guessed
that your spiritual power was exhausted
when you mended the heavens.
Although he gave you one soul,
it was still too weak
for an ancient artifact.
Is there no way
to quickly recover it?
The matter of the divine artifact
is even more mysterious than that of the Divine Clan.
Don't worry too much.
The palace has increased its defenses.
I'll go check things out now.
Pearl,
you seem
a bit different now.
Different?
You seem
to be more and more like His Majesty.
But don't learn from him to work without rest.
His Majesty is not here,
so you must take care of yourself.
By what means
could I help Zhao Ming?
If I can recover all the memories,
will that restore my Chaos Power?
Yan.
Che.
Give it to me.
Yan,
this is the bread you gave me yesterday.
There are two pieces left.
I'll return them to you.
Why not keep them for yourself?
No need.
I need to go to the palace with them today.
The foolish Emperor lied to us, saying there would be a sacrifice,
but he secretly left the palace and is enjoying himself.
We plan to gather the divine servants
and make the sacrifice immediately.
I've heard that the palace has enough water and food.
We can bring some back
to relieve everyone's immediate suffering.
Yan,
do you want to come with us?
Who is spreading these rumors?
This is no rumor.
The high-ranking officials in the palace said it themselves.
If we want to survive,
we can only rely on ourselves.
If you want to join,
meet me in the palace later.
I'm leaving now, Yan.
If you're worried about a palace rebellion,
I'll go with you.
You should stay here
and take care of your mother.
Yan,
Zhao Ming is not only your Saint Emperor,
he is also my savior.
If he hadn't solved the crisis for me,
we'd have been separated long ago.
Isn't that right?
The Soul Scattering Poison,
given by the Divine Clan.
They wanted you to kill me?
Why didn't you follow their order
but chose to tell me instead?
I'm not that righteous.
I did indeed consider killing you.
But even if
I managed to kill you,
this ruined life wouldn't end.
For the rest of my life,
I would be a puppet controlled by them.
And my mother
would suffer endless abuse,
never seeing hope again.
I ask Your Majesty
to exchange my life
for my mother's safety
and freedom.
If you want to solve this situation,
you can.
Just kill me.
But do it at your birthday feast
in front of everyone.
Rising from the ashes,
reborn like a phoenix.
Zhao Ming has already told me everything.
This is a Fireproof Stone.
It will protect you from the flames.
But after today,
there will be no more Princess Qingyang in this world.
Princess Qingyang should have died long ago.
But I find
you're quite different from others.
If there were more time,
I would definitely be friends with you.
If there is another chance,
I'd like to get to know you again.
I also have to thank Pearl.
The blood of the Divine Saintess
can cure the divine poison.
It was her blood
that cured the poison for me and my mother.
She saved us.
If we are to discuss gratitude,
it should be
that you stay, and I will go.
All along,
I could never outtalk you.
You won't let me go.
We agreed.
No matter what happens,
we will face it together.
Alright.
Respect the divine edict, and overthrow Zhao Ming!
Humans
truly can't stand the test or stirring up.
I only arranged a few people,
gave them a little push,
and so many people joined.
Truly foolish and laughable.
Breaking his heart with the people he cares for.
Brilliant!
I really want to see
Zhao Ming's expression
when he faces the rebellion of those
he fought to protect.
It's coming soon.
Where are the people you arranged?
Respect the divine edict, and overthrow Zhao Ming!
Just those two leaders.
For a few bags of rice,
they sold their souls to me.
Now they are no longer
ordinary humans,
but servants of me!
As for dealing with Zhao Ming,
they likely stand no chance.
But against ordinary humans,
they're more than enough.
Hand over the divine servants!
Where are the divine servants?
You have disregarded your agreement with His Majesty
and barged into the palace.
What are you trying to do?
The sacrificial offering was promised for tomorrow,
but where is the foolish Emperor?
He lied to us,
but wants us to obey him?
Do you think we're fools?
- You... - I'll hold them off here.
Hurry and leave!
I'll go find reinforcements.
Find a way to get to the divine servants' residence.
Protect the children.
Be extra careful.
She's the foolish Emperor's trusted one.
She must know where the divine servants are.
Catch her!
Hand over the divine servants!
See it now?
This is human nature.
Can you calm this rebellion?
Divine artifacts cannot interfere with human affairs.
Then just watch here.
You lost the bet.
The third bet:
Human nature is selfish.
They repay kindness with hatred.
According to the bet,
you should return with me.
♪Searching for your face in the cycles of life♪
♪If the tears in my heart remain unseen♪
♪Can I still remain tireless?♪
♪Because my heart holds longing♪
♪A devoted soul asks not how far the road goes♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪
♪For love, braving the storms, crossing the years♪
♪Never regretting our meeting♪
♪Only wishing for thousands of blossoms♪
♪To bloom for you that day♪
♪Gazing at that one person, those eyes♪
♪I desire nothing else♪
♪A life with no worries or regrets♪
♪Staying by your side♪