(Impression Of Youth)
You treat me to dinner.
I'll make you coffee.
Wait for me.
Sure.
The coffee is so good.
Well,
thank you for the coffee.
And thank you
for letting me be the first person to try it.
Every cup of coffee has its own story.
Now you know my story.
Do you want to tell me your story?
Done.
Okay, let me see.
Your drawing is overall good.
The strokes are well-controlled.
There's basically no fault to find.
The weight of the watermelon,
the texture and quality of its surface
are all depicted.
You are really talented in drawing.
Who am I? I'm Xu Luhui.
You really haven't studied before?
No.
Luhui's composition is very bold and unconstrained,
bold yet meticulous,
showing a delicate side of his personality.
Indeed,
one drawing can reveal the artist's character.
What do you think?
It's really good.
Great, then I'm heading out.
Wait.
Don't get carried away too soon.
There are still some small details
you can pay more attention to.
Your observation could also be more delicate.
But don't worry.
I'll teach you more in the future.
Alright, I'm going to cut the watermelon now.
How is it? Is it okay?
I don't think so.
Try it.
Okay.
Why are you laughing?
Your face.
I helped you fix your bike, and you're laughing.
Go away.
Go away!
It's dirty. You've gone too far.
Alright, I apologize to you, okay?
Don't come any closer.
Apologize.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Your hands are...
so dirty.
Okay, leave the bike here.
I'll get someone to fix it.
I'll take you back first.
Alright.
Before an accident happens,
we rarely think that
the people we see every day
might
suddenly leave us one day.
After my parents passed away in a car accident,
Luhui gave me the courage
and made me decide
to bring him back here.
Here, it feels like home.
That's why I named it
Homelike Homestay.
I also hope that the guests who come here
can feel like they're at home.
Back then,
Luhui would always look at our parents'
photo and draw them,
as if they were
still alive in the world he drew.
I want to try yours too.
Delicious.
Xu Luhui, give me back my popsicle.
Where are you going?
What did you say?
Give it back.
No.
Give it back!
Stop it.
Come here.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have asked.
Maybe you're not ready to talk about it yet.
It's okay.
I can talk about it now,
which means I've let it go.
We have to move on.
Let bygones be bygones.
Learn to cherish the present,
and live every day seriously.
You're mature.
I hope you're not saying that I look old.
No, I mean...
Well, I was just kidding.
Since we both know each other's stories now,
we'll be friends from now on.
Friends should help each other.
So don't be polite with me anymore.
Okay.
Got it.
Luxi, thank you.
By the way,
you just said your brother is good at drawing.
Could I ask him
to help me paint the exterior of the cafe?
Of course.
I'll talk to him later.
Friends should help each other.
Thank you.
You actually look good when you smile.
You should smile more.
What?
No.
You should smile more.
You look good when you smile.
Lanxin used to say that all the time.
Sorry for disturbing you.
I have to go now.
Thanks for the bento.
See you the day after tomorrow.
See you.
You two...
look weird.
-No.
Really?
Then why don't you look at each other?
I'm going to take a shower.
Since when does he like to shower so much?
I'll go inside too.
Wait.
What's up?
Let's eat together later.
Sure.
Go and rest.
Okay.
If you need any help,
just let me know.
Let's eat.
Since when
have you become so tacit?
By the way, Xu Luhui,
come to the cafe next door with me the day after tomorrow.
The owner wants to finish the renovation
before his late wife's birthday.
He needs someone to paint the exterior.
I don't want to.
Do you even get a say?
Xu Luxi, am I really your brother?
I seriously suspect that I'm just a staff at Homelike Homestay.
I can't even take a day off.
Stop complaining. Just do as I say.
Why don't you ask Yu Xing to go?
He's an art teacher.
He'd paint a hundred times better than me.
That's right.
Yu Xing is an art teacher.
No, Xu Luhui.
I'm talking about you.
Don't try to change the subject.
Get up at 6 a.m. the day after tomorrow.
No sleeping in.
If you do,
I'll dig you out of bed with a shovel.
Do you hear me?
Alright.
So...
this is what touch feels like.
Is everything okay?
Yes...
I think.
Look,
the tall one with long hair in a ponytail,
that's my ideal type.
Give me back my popsicle.
Give it back!
Stop it.
I like the one with short hair
and a cute look.
Luhui, your ideal type...
Xu Luhui, what's wrong with you?
This was my first kiss.
Why does it feel different?
Lv.
Let me try.
How petty.
That was my first kiss too.
What do you think we should paint?
I have no idea.
What about you? Any ideas?
No.
Just one more accessory and it'll be done.
It's much faster with more helpers, right?
Yes.
This way, we can finish it before Lanxin's birthday.
Thank you.
Take a break.
I'll make you some coffee.
By the way, besides coffee,
what else will the cafe sell?
I'm still thinking about that.
After all, I only know how to make coffee.
Have some coffee.
-Thank you.
Maybe this will spark some inspiration.
I was wondering,
why did you want to
open a cafe here?
My wife loved watching the sea.
We used to stay at the beach
for a whole afternoon.
She always felt that watching the sea was very healing.
Every time, she would insist on
opening a cafe where we could
see the sea.
This cafe
is like the last birthday gift I gave her.
It's really beautiful.
How is it? Not bad, huh?
You're the only one who's been here.
Since your wife loved watching the sea,
how about we imprint the sea
on the wall of the cafe?
What do you think?
Right, in this way,
the guests who come here can feel
the leisure of the seaside.
I think it's a great idea.
It's also my original intention to heal
every guest who comes to the cafe.
If there's no problem,
we'll paint it this way.
Thank you.
Bingchen, come in and help.
Coming.
If you need any help or tools,
just let me know.
No problem.
Go ahead.
Sorry.
You first.
Weird.
Why did I just feel a tingling?
Yu Xing.
What?
Xu Luhui, you're dead!
Don't come over.
Can't catch me, can't catch me.
Can't catch me.
Don't come over.
Come here!
Yu Xing.
Get up!
You're dead!
Come here.
Stop it!
Xu Luhui, what are you doing?
Come here.
Come on.
Xu Luhui.
Xu Luhui, stop it.
Come here!
Yu Xing, help me!
Wait.
What do you think if we add
some yellow ones?
It's okay.
Let's stack it up, make a few layers.
Stack it.
Or make it into a pyramid?
Okay.
We've made a lot of this.
Where do you want to put the PET bottle?
Do you want to put it on top or on the table?
This way,
there will be a subtle green feeling, you know.
Yeah, add it in and let's see.
Okay.
It's so beautiful.
The guests who come here will definitely love it.
I give this painting 200 points.
Hello, Xu Luxi.
Did you see me? I painted too.
Shut up.
Thank you for your company.
You've added
a different kind of vitality to this place.
Once the interior is finished,
I'll properly thank you all.
Bingchen, don't say that.
After the cafe is finished,
let's go to the homestay
for a barbecue and drinks to celebrate.
Barbecue! Barbecue! I want barbecue!
Barbecue! I want barbecue!
Luxi, I want it too.
Teacher first. Where's your manners?
You haven't finished yours yet.
Hurry up and eat.
So cute.
Send the photos to Luhui and Yu Xing for me.
Okay, thank you.
Good night.
Did you find it?
No.
Do we really need a plaster cast?
Generally,
before we have students do portrait sketches,
we have them practice with plaster casts
to test and train their sketching abilities.
But since I
rarely draw portraits myself,
I don't have an example for you to reference.
Or can I draw you?
Me?
Yes.
You've already told me about
the three sides and five values of sketching last time.
I'll give it a try first.
You can tell me how to adjust later.
Alright, but let me explain something first.
Last time I mentioned that
there are some small details in your sketching
that you could pay more attention to.
It's not about technique.
What I told you last time was about observation.
You need to observe more carefully.
Come on, stand up.
Stand up?
Yes.
Stand back. Stand away from me.
Back.
Okay, stop.
Now, look into my eyes
and observe me carefully.
Is the me you see now
a little different from
the me you usually see?
It seems so.
Okay.
Now, slowly walk towards me.
Slowly.
Move forward.
Don't look away.
Look into my eyes.
Keep your eyes on mine.
Come on, move forward.
Forward.
Move forward.
Now,
feel the object you're going to draw。
Feel the texture.
So I can touch you?
Yes.
Touch my hair.
Come on.
Rub it.
Feel its texture.
Now touch my face.
Feel the texture of my skin.
Finished.
Congratulations.
Let's take a photo.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll make you some coffee.
Lanxin, happy birthday.
Remember those feelings
and digest them slowly.
Then express them
fully through your sketching.
That's the essence of portrait drawing.
I don't know if it's the sun or you,
but it's so dazzling I can't look directly.
What's wrong?
I suddenly have a stomachache.
I'll draw it another day.
Luhui.
What are these feelings?
These feelings
are too much for me to draw.
Is this
what it feels like to like someone?
Do you feel anything now?
You should let Yu Xing know
how you feel about him.
When will you be ready
to accept a new relationship?
Did you
bring him to me?
I just want you to know my feelings.
It's okay if you don't respond the same way.
Feel your own emotions.
I thought you were here to see me.
I wasn't.