BASED ON MAURIZIO DE GIOVANNI'S NOVELS
SARA - THE WOMAN IN THE SHADOWS
A FEW DAYS EARLIER
-Hello?
-Hi, Morozzi. It's you, right?
-Is this still your number?
-Yes. Who's this?
It's Di Blasio.
I was in the operations room.
Giorgio Alberti is your son, right?
Yes.
Okay, listen… You need to come
to Cardarelli Hospital.
Cardarelli Hospital?
What ward?
AUTOPSY ROOM
My condolences.
May I?
Do you want to sit down?
I have to send your son's belongings
to forensics.
It's procedure.
She's a colleague. She knows how it works.
What happened, exactly?
You can talk to the first responders.
We can't spend any more money.
What am I going to do with you?
You're still betting?
It happened again last night.
20 teams, over 1.5. And Monza? 1-0.
You never win. You're only wasting money.
Don't you get it?
Here they are.
That's our colleague.
She looks like a bum.
They killed her son.
You think she'd
waste time picking out her clothes?
Major Sara Morozzi on leave.
Agents Silvani and Fregoli,
from the Fuorigrotta precinct.
My condolences.
I really need to go back now, Morozzi.
Be strong.
I need to know how it happened. And where.
It was right outside his house.
He was walking his dog,
and… as he was crossing the road…
What's the address?
We hadn't seen each other in a while.
He lived at 20 Piazza D'Annunzio.
The man who hit him
said he had no time to brake.
He's devastated.
He said he died
in the ambulance as he held his hand.
He rode along because your son's partner
wasn't up to it.
Did you know he had a partner?
No. I know nothing about him.
I need to talk to that man.
Maybe he's still at the ER.
His name's Ludovico Terzani.
I'm the mother of the young man you hit.
It wasn't my fault.
I'm a doctor.
I should save lives. And yet…
Tell me about the accident.
I didn't see him in time.
I saw the light on his phone first,
then his silhouette, and…
I think he was texting someone.
I don't know.
He hesitated, and…
What do you mean, he hesitated?
When I saw him…
I instinctively slowed down
and flashed my lights.
And he stopped.
But as soon as I sped up again,
he let go of the dog
and jumped in the street.
And I couldn't avoid him.
I'm sorry.
Sara!
Sara! Please stop, Sara!
You don't know what you're doing.
You're crazy!
I can't fake it, Gennaro.
What? Being with your son is faking it?
-I can't give him what he needs!
-Dad, where is Mom going?
Dad will be right back, sweetie.
Go home. Go on.
Sweetie.
Di Blasio, what is this woman doing here?
I get it, but she's the kid's mother.
She wants to talk with her son's partner.
Why does she need to talk to us?
Really?
I get it. But it's late, Di Blasio.
Honestly, if what you're saying is true,
it's also a little late to get involved.
-Don't you think?
-Did it happen here?
Di Blasio, my colleague's here.
I'll call you back. Bye.
Sorry. I didn't see you.
Inspector Davide Pardo.
You asked where he was hit, right?
It's difficult to tell.
The asphalt's wet,
and there aren't any skid marks, but…
Okay, got it.
Musella!
Inspector.
I'm going up to the dead kid's partner.
You stay with her.
Who is she?
The kid's mom. A former colleague too.
-The kid's mom?
-Yeah.
My condolences, ma'am.
And you are?
Sergeant Attilio Musella.
You're no more than a kid yourself.
You have nice eyes, you know that?
Thanks.
My son Giorgio's phone was missing
from his personal effects.
The guy who hit him
said he was holding it.
I have it.
I found it about 30 feet over there,
in the dark. But it's broken.
-So you haven't handed it in yet?
-No.
I mean, not yet.
I'd like to see it.
That's not possible, ma'am.
For you young people, your phones
are like snapshots of your life.
It's been ages
since I knew anything about my son.
Sir?
Yeah, Giovanni. Go on.
The tow truck hasn't arrived yet.
Should I call him again?
-Yeah, good. Call him.
-Okay, sir. I'll call and keep you posted.
Thank you.
Ma'am, I'm really sorry.
-Imagine the state she's in.
-How, if you don't let me in?
Tell her I'm here.
If she doesn't want to see me, I'll leave.
Excuse me.
Your partner's mom is here.
Giorgio's mom. She wants to talk to you.
She had the nerve to show up now?
Tell her Viola doesn't want to see her.
My daughter's pregnant.
You need to leave her alone.
Sorry, I need some information.
I'll send her away if you want.
How far along are you?
Eight months. It's a boy.
What do you want?
What was Giorgio's job?
He was a researcher at Napoli Biochimica.
Did he ever have problems at work?
Any arguments?
Everybody loved Giorgio.
He was really sweet.
What time did he get back?
At 9:00 p.m.
It had just stopped raining,
then he took a shower…
He had dinner and took our dog Rita
for a walk, just like always.
I don't understand what's going on.
-I just need to understand.
-Understand what? It was an accident.
You answer now. I have a question.
How do you abandon your own son?
Like you did. He was seven.
I fell in love,
and Giorgio didn't want to see me anymore.
-Sara Morozzi?
-Yes.
Please come in.
-Do you want some coffee?
-No, thanks.
Naples Police, right?
Listen, my goal is to assemble
a team of skilled agents,
ready to commit totally to the job.
We have new challenges,
and I can't afford mistakes.
Naples is a new challenge every day.
I'm not talking about Naples.
Or about raids or arrests.
What is it, then?
Outside the bar
where I had coffee this morning,
I saw this graffiti on the wall that said,
"After the chilling Years of Lead,
let's enjoy these warm years of shit."
It's true. The Years of Lead
are a thing of the past.
But the subversive cells, they keep going.
They're just subtler,
more hybrid, more hidden.
I believe that's
the Secret Service's duty.
Shovel the shit.
-Coffee?
-Yes, thanks.
Coming.
God, you've aged.
So have you, but you hide it well.
I'm sorry about your son.
Is the guy who just left
a friend or a new recruit?
-He's someone we can use.
-So, work's going as usual?
Well, a lot has changed.
Now they gave us this American software
that crosschecks data
and flags any suspects.
But you're still in charge
of audio surveillance?
Yes, of course. We are.
Did you hear I'm the boss now?
No. But I'm glad. You're good.
That's not true.
You should have taken
Massimiliano's place, not me.
What we were doing
only made sense to me with him.
Seeing him die
like that must've been horrible.
We were keeping track, in our way, but…
You know the rules.
We couldn't get in touch.
You didn't come here
to talk about the past.
No.
It's about Giorgio.
It was an accident, right?
He was writing or reading a text
when he got run over.
I want to know
who he was communicating with.
And whatever you might get out of this.
I think he took his own life.
But I need to know if that's the case.
I can't do it on my own.
I need your help.
Considering how you left,
I shouldn't talk to you.
You know that?
-I'll be in touch, okay?
-How?
The old way. That hasn't changed.
ACCESS FORBIDDEN
DANGER OF DEATH
-Hi, Teresa.
-Good morning.
Everything okay?
All good.
Hey. What's up? How's it going?
-Dead, more or less.
-Mm.
-See what Sergio does?
-What?
He has this habit. Every time he enters
Tarallo's office, he looks at the camera.
Does he know he works
for the Secret Service?
It's okay.
Those guys have no fucking clue.
What can you get out of this,
apart from what's on it?
-Whatever's stored on the cloud.
-Good.
I need all of it, including call logs
and location history. Everything.
I can't ask the phone company.
-I have to hack in?
-Hack away!
What a drag, though.
This way, I lose my focus.
When you were still in diapers,
I teamed up with an agent who,
with no mics or headphones,
without any fucking thing,
just by looking at the guy's lips,
could have told me everything he said.
No one could read lips like she could.
What happened to her?
She thinks she's dead…
but maybe she's not.
Your gift is still incomplete,
but you were always the best at waiting.
GIORGIO: WHO ASKED YOU THAT?
LO GIUDICE: DAVIDE
What are you doing here?
Do you regret it?
I miss him.
NAPOLI BIOCHIMICA
-Good morning.
-Morning.
I'm Giorgio's mother.
I'd like to talk to his boss.
Of course. Follow me.
We're sorry for what happened.
Thank you.
Andrea, may I? Please wait here.
How's that possible?
Giorgio told me she was dead.
Fine, let her in,
and tell them I'll be 20 minutes late.
Colonel Prati is waiting
for you at the base.
Let her wait.
There's no point in sending someone else
if I'm taking Giorgio's place.
-Please.
-Thank you.
We're all devastated about what happened.
My deepest condolences.
Was he happy?
Yes, I think so.
He liked his job.
And he was about to have a kid.
The day of the accident,
Giorgio took your place in "LP."
According to the messages you exchanged,
he insisted on it. Why?
He needed the afternoon off.
I don't know why. I didn't ask.
What does "LP" stand for?
Sorry, ma'am, but why are you asking
so many questions?
Why are you so interested?
Because Giorgio's gone.
I'm curious about everything.
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you.
We have important clients.
They demand confidentiality.
Did he have specific duties?
A position of responsibility?
-Did he make a mistake?
-No mistakes.
Was that his?
Yes.
To Giorgio, I really was dead.
-Hello.
-Andrea Lo Giudice. They're expecting me.
Let me check.
-Sir, we need to do a check.
-Sure.
Mr. Lo Giudice!
Colonel Prati, good morning.
I'll handle everything, at least for now.
I already accessed the data
Giorgio collected before the accident.
They're encrypted files. Don't worry.
UNKNOWN
PIZZA. YOUR PLACE.
How the hell can you live in this dump?
Massimiliano wouldn't approve.
Massimiliano is dead.
The dead don't care either way.
The rest of Giorgio's phone data.
Is there a minibar in this dump?
There is.
I took the liberty of taking a look,
if you don't mind.
Does the former Proto NATO base
ring a bell?
No. Why?
Your son went there every day,
from 2:30 to 8:30 p.m.
But he didn't go on the day he died.
He went to Lago Patria, the new base.
Why would he go to Proto if it's closed?
The area was given to the city.
As far as I know, they're dismantling it.
If you know more,
and I know you know more, brunette,
don't bullshit me and say it.
Storage, personnel in hazmat suits
and masks.
That's what I saw.
And Giorgio wasn't emptying storage rooms.
He had a chemistry degree.
Yeah, but now you have to sit tight
because the army is involved.
Being cautious used to piss you off.
It still does.
It's not being cautious. It's tactics.
But what if Giorgio got hold of something
he shouldn't have.
Don't look for conspiracies,
hoping he was like you.
Could be collateral damage.
Maybe he couldn't handle something
he found out and killed himself.
Let me look into it.
This beer is crap.
Bye.
I always like having pizza with you.
As for the kid you're staring down at,
yes, sometimes I use him as a driver.
But mind your fucking business, okay?
Who is it?
I need to talk to Viola.
Viola isn't feeling well, and she has
no intention of talking to you.
I'll wait. Tell her it's important.
His work stuff and diary are in here.
I found nothing weird.
Take a look, if you want.
How long were you two together?
A couple of years.
How did you meet?
What do you want from me? Huh?
I shouldn't even talk to you
out of respect for Giorgio.
You're right.
I have no right.
Not even to feel upset seeing
that his name disappeared from the buzzer.
What are you talking about?
Where did you come from? Stay.
Boris!
Boris.
Good evening.
Look who you found.
-How are you?
-Fine, thanks.
Listen, I would've called you tonight,
but since I ran into you…
Yeah, by chance.
This is where you take your dog to pee.
I live nearby.
I always walk the dog here,
only he never stays still.
He runs away
before I can put a leash on him, okay?
Anyway, I wanted to let you know
that we questioned Terzani again.
From how he describes the dynamics,
it looks like
your partner committed suicide.
I'm sorry.
Is that why you were asking
so many questions?
To know if he had a reason
to kill himself?
Maybe you thought
abandoning him messed him up?
It's bullshit. Giorgio was fine.
As he left, he asked me
to pick a movie to watch together.
You think someone would say that
and then jump in front of a passing car?
If that's what happened,
get ready to fight the insurance guys.
What insurance?
Your partner… took out
a life insurance policy.
For you. You and the baby.
I knew nothing about that.
I'm tired.
You can keep that.
If it's your son's,
you have to hand it over.
Hey!
-That's not going to happen.
-Excuse me?
You're not even on duty.
Summon me officially, if you want.
Have a nice walk.
LAGO PATRIA MILITARY BASE
Yeah?
From 7:00 to 10:00 a.m.
Sure, we can bring it to your room.
There's a little extra fee.
All right. Fine, good night.
Did you see this, Sarè?
We have a guy with balls now.
-And who might that be?
-Tarallo.
No, I don't like him.
You too, going on about
how he's a fascist.
There are no fascists anymore.
He's good for us. The fascists…
We'll see about that.
TARALLO'S COMEBACK
THE CANDIDATE LEADS IN THE NEW POLLS
You'll smoke later.
Hey.
Are you really making coffee?
Can't I surprise you for once?
-Isn't it late?
-Very. I wanted to serve it in bed.
I should have picked Tarallo over you.
That's what I'm paying you for.
-Yeah.
-What are you doing for him today?
I have to go through the speech
for his meeting
with the Islamic community.
He asked me to add
that he worked in Lebanon for ten years,
that he's like a brother to them,
but that security is a universal asset,
for Christians and Muslims both.
So that he can end his speech
with the usual,
"More security for all…"
"More freedom for all."
That's it?
Yeah, and the usual six-hour meetings
full of pointless talk.
Yeah, but sometimes what you need is
in all that talk.
You just have to find it.
In the years of the strikes,
reports from assets like you were crucial,
you know?
Is that right?
Let me get this straight.
You brought these assets home
back then too?
Obviously.
Except I'd kill them afterwards.
Listen…
Why are you so interested in Tarallo?
I mean…
No. If you start asking questions,
I'll have to kill you right away.
No! But… I mean, if you think
there's more than what you see…
Tell me.
I'll work better if I know.
I don't think anything.
I'm on Tarallo like I'm on the others.
You're the one
who has to keep his eyes open.
You got that?
Come on, go. Hurry up.
-Morning. Your ID, please.
-Morning. Yes.
-You may go.
-Thanks.
Morning.
Morning. The service providers
need to use the back entrance.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
I didn't know. It's my first time here.
I'm filling in for Pinelli.
-Oh, the substitute. They notified us.
-Yeah.
-Is your colleague sick?
-No, he's fine.
He had to take a trainee
to the regional offices.
-I see.
-We train too, in our own small way.
Listen, since you're so kind,
my boss said that
a Colonel Prati, maybe…
-Silvia Prati, sure.
-Silvia Prati, yes.
She complained about the vending machine.
-I wouldn't know where to find her.
-Yes. Okay, let me check the floor.
Yes.
First floor.
Thank you.
ELECTRICAL PANELS
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
ITALIAN AIR FORCE
Morning, Colonel Prati.
It's solved. It was a false alarm.
-Morning, ma'am.
-Excuse me. What are you doing here?
I'm sorry. I'm a cleaner.
I remembered that yesterday
I lost my necklace while cleaning here.
In fact, I found it.
-I'll leave right away.
-No, wait.
What was your name again?
I didn't say my name. Why?
I feel like I know you. Have we met?
Well, maybe… I don't know.
Because I work here, maybe.
But it's not likely.
My face is so generic. Bye.
Where the fuck do you think you're going?
Stop. Don't turn around.
Found her.
You're spying on me now?
No, but I know you.
What did you steal in there?
What did I steal?
Nothing.
I broke into the office of a colonel
involved in Proto's dismantling.
And I found jack shit. Who's that guy?
Someone who owes me lots of favors
and doesn't ask questions.
You must've told him something
to get me caught.
I told him that if he saw a loony
dressed like a bum wandering around,
he should tell me.
And here we are.
One, I'm not dressed like a bum.
And two, I didn't sneak in, I walked in.
Well done. Who helped you?
Someone who owes me favors
and doesn't ask questions.
Listen, brunette, fuck you.
I asked you to give me time.
But you just did what you wanted.
You made a big mess.
Get in.
Listen.
There are two sets of keys
with Giorgio's personal effects.
I need the one with the plastic tag
and two numbers on it.
One and 15.
It'll be worse
if I get them on my own, right?
All right.
Tomorrow, 1:00 p.m., in front of
the usual bookshop in Port'Alba.
Okay?
But this is the last favor
I'm doing for you.
They're all over me. You get that?
Any excuse is good to shut down the unit.
Lembo's doing what he can to defend us.
Lembo is a puppet.
What the fuck do you know?
About what we've all become?
About what Lembo's become?
What do you know?
Look. This can't happen.
Tamburi.
-The big shots are paying us a visit.
-Who's that?
Lembo.
I'll go say hello. After all,
we have him to thank for getting paid.
Hey. Translate for me.
"Not bad,
considering what all this stuff cost us."
"Come, I'll introduce the new recruits."
Fuck. I should've gone to the hairdresser.
"Wait. Tell me
which one you're fucking first."
Mr. Lembo, Pandolfi, and Morozzi.
It's a pleasure.
Ma'am, you dropped that.
Thanks.
NAPOLI CHAMPION OF ITALY 2022/2023
PIAZZA ORIENTALE THANKS YOU
Fuck!
No!
-No! What the fuck do you want from me?
-Don't worry.
Colonel Silvia Prati.
I'm Giorgio's mother.
That's where I'd seen those eyes.
"SG." A present from Giorgio, right?
Were you having an affair?
It was one of those encounters
where there's no going back.
We met on the job three years ago.
Then, one year later,
I found out I was sick.
And I left him without an explanation.
I don't know how,
but he found out about my illness
and came to see me the other day.
He said he'd rented this place
and that he'd wait for me here.
I let him wait.
But why?
I knew he was about to have a kid.
And it's not right to ask a young man
to be with a woman
who doesn't even know if she'll make it.
Ludovico says it's this love
that's killing me.
But it's because I didn't want to live it.
Ludovico?
My oncologist.
Ludovico Terzani.
After I left Giorgio,
I don't even know why…
Maybe to try and forget him,
but we had a brief relationship.
He's married, but that's not the point.
I just didn't love him.
ONCOLOGICAL HOSPITAL
He decided to stay with me anyway.
As a patient, I feel protected,
but… at times, it's suffocating.
I'm a doctor.
I should save lives. And yet…
We were both right. As always.
There's no sinister plot
behind Giorgio's death.
We're not bound together by mystery.
That's why I can't give you the keys.
I tossed them.
I don't want Viola to get them
with Giorgio's personal effects.
-She can't think he was cheating on her.
-Why? Was he cheating on her?
It's way more complicated than that.
Jealousy doesn't give a fuck
about details.
Subtitle translation by: Paola Porciello