Julia:
Chester's mill is a place
like any other.
At least it used to be
Until we were cut off
from the rest of the world
By a mysterious dome.
Invisible, indestructible,
And completely inescapable.
We're trapped.
Julia:
We don't know where it
came from or why it's here,
But now that we're all trapped
under the dome together,
None of our secrets are safe.
Yesterday,
Norrie and I, we found
This... Egg
With its own little
dome around it.
The monarch will be crowned.
You don't want to make
an enemy of me, barbie.
There's two sides
to that coin, jim.
What do you think of when I say
"the monarch will be crowned"?
Uh... What are you
talking about?
I wish I knew.
It's not much further.
You said it's an egg?
With its own little
mini-dome around it?
Yes, you've only
asked me 20 times.
Well, you got to admit,
it sounds kind of out there.
Yeah, I guess I
wouldn't believe it
And joe thinks that
this thing could be
What's powering the dome?
Yeah, he just
didn't know how.
You ever been
to a planetarium?
Once in high school.
Why?
That egg is projecting the dome
around us the same way
A planetarium projector
surrounds you with stars.
Well, you're gonna get
to test that theory,
'cause here it is.
I don't see an egg.
I am not crazy.
It was clearly right here.
Where'd it go?
Linda:
Barbie, you around?
Yeah, linda. Go ahead.
Shots fired on greenway street.
I need you here now.
I'm on my way.
I should go help.
I have to find this thing.
When you do, come find me.
Joe:
Norrie?
There's only one
rule when it comes
To catching a chicken.
Which is?
It ain't easy.
Yeah, but you have to kill it.
I think they're
kind of cute.
Okay, so when
your apparition told julia
That the monarch
will be crowned,
What do you think that means?
Guess somebody in here
gets to be king.
Or it could have something to do
with those monarch butterflies
That were outside the dome
three days ago.
Well, we should go back out
to that mini-dome.
See if we can get your
apparition to explain himself.
After we catch dinner.
Good morning.
Very good,
judging by that smile.
Well, things are looking up
in this town.
Yeah, I heard, uh, barbie got
the water flowing again.
A lot of chester's millers
made that happen.
And I just, uh, hammered out
A food deal with our farmers.
We barter goods and services
For vegetables, meat.
'cause I want
to keep this place open.
Really?
Yeah.
I know I can't run it
as good as rose did.
Probably can't offer more
than one or two items a day.
But I think it's important.
Ah, so, from waitress to manager
In a little over a week, huh?
From waitress to owner.
I want the deed, free and clear.
For the first time in my life,
I want to be responsible
For something.
The only way to do that,
sink or swim,
Is for it to be on me.
Let me give it some thought.
You do that.
Hey.
What happened?
Is he okay?
By pure luck.
The bullet only
grazed him.
So who fired the shot?
His neighbor,
ted utley.
And I'd do it again.
Barbie:
Whoa. Whoa, whoa,
Whoa, whoa.
I'm sorry about
Mr. Feldman.
I wasn't shooting at him.
My property. And that freak,
he was banging on my door.
What freak?
At my house.
He's still inside.
Weird-looking guy showed up,
ranting that he had to hide
From the voices coming
from the dome.
I said I had a gun,
but he wouldn't leave,
So I fired off a couple shots
to scare him off.
Except you hit your neighbor.
And that freak
Didn't even run off.
This thing started off
by killing people,
And now it's just driving
the rest of us crazy.
You know, we're all
gonna die in here.
Just calm down, mr. Utley, okay?
We're gonna go get the guy
out of your house.
Preferably without anyone else
getting shot.
Stop talking to me, dome!
Get out! I need quiet!
Get down!
Get back!
Let me see your hands!
Let me see your hands! Get down!
Please don't hurt me!
Hands behind your head.
I just got
to stop the voices!
Larry?
You know this guy?
Yeah, I've busted him
a million times for drugs.
Oh, so it's not the dome talking
to you, is it? It's the drugs.
Yeah, what is it this time,
larry? Meth? Crack?
Rapture.
Never heard of it.
It's like every
kind of high combined.
Coggins promised it'd
be like seeing heaven.
The-the preacher sold you drugs?
Yes, right there
at his funeral home.
I need more!
Hi, ange.
Get the hell out of here.
Please, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just...
Wanted
something to eat.
No, junior. No.
This is my place now,
And I reserve the right
to refuse service to anyone,
Especially psychos who chain up
their ex-girlfriends.
I only did that because the
dome was making you sick.
I'm not sick, junior.
The dome has nothing
to do with me.
Angie.
Angie!
The pink stars are falling.
The pink stars
are falling in lines.
The pink stars are falling.
You got one second to tell me
Why I shouldn't
blow your damn head off.
Because you don't want
to ruin this beautiful face?
Hi, jimmy.
Let me out!
Angie, angie...
help!
Angie, relax.
Calm down, okay? You're safe!
somebody help me!
- You're safe.
- until what?
Until you lock me
into the fallout shelter again?
You had a seizure.
You kept saying:
"pink stars are falling."
I only put you back there
to keep you safe.
And I took care of you.
Like I am now.
See?
I brought you home.
You're really letting me go?
I think I'll see you again.
The mini-dome's gone?
Just a pile of leaves
and a hole in the ground.
You guys didn't move it,
did you?
No. Why would we?
I don't know,
but we need to find it again.
I just wish my mom was
still here to help us.
I can't believe she was
alive just two days ago.
How's carolyn doing?
She's still grieving.
Should you stay with her?
We had a long talk
this morning, and...
She said she just needs
some time alone.
And I need to do this.
hey.
joe:
Angie.
You...
Look like crap.
Thanks.
I just had a seizure
at the diner.
What do you mean
you had a seizure?
Angie:
I mean I was just standing
there and then I...
I went blank and... Collapsed.
Did you say, "the pink
stars are falling"?
How did you know that?
Because norrie and I have had
the exact same seizure.
What? Why didn't you tell me?
You haven't exactly
been here a lot.
Oh, my god.
Angie...
junior's right.
I am sick.
Julia:
Honey, why don't you
sit down for a minute?
No, I need to get
a glass of water first.
Joe...
Did you know that angie
has a butterfly tattoo?
Yeah. My parents almost
killed her when she got it.
And now she's having seizures.
Maybe she's the monarch
who will be crowned.
My sister? No way.
And monarch butterflies
are orange.
Angie's is blue and yellow,
So there goes that theory.
Well, the only way
we're gonna get answers
Is if we find the mini-dome.
What about that contraption
that dodee made--
The yagi?
It locates energy
sources, right?
Yeah. If the egg's
what's powering the dome
Then the yagi might help us
track it down.
Let's ask her to borrow it.
Dodee got a little weird
the last time
She was around the two of you.
Better let me go talk to her.
Big jim at a loss for words.
Never thought I'd see the day.
What are you doing here, max?
I can't just drop in
on an old friend?
I mean inside the dome.
Did you get through it somehow?
Like I would try
and break in? Please.
No. I don't like being in
this crappy town on a good day.
So you got trapped.
The one day
I decide to leave westlake
to come see you
And that thing just...
Comes down out of nowhere.
You were coming to see me?
Yeah, I kept hearing
About problems
with our little arrangement.
The one you assured me
you had under control?
Which I did.
So... Duke perkins
wasn't getting antsy
About looking the other way?
And the wacko preacher wasn't
making up his own batches
Of our product?
Rapture... Is your product, max.
Which I never could
have gotten off the ground
Without you and your supply
of my secret ingredient.
Duke and coggins
aren't a problem anymore,
So you can relax.
And, uh...
If you got caught in here
like the rest of us...
Where the hell you been
The last eight days?
I found a house.
The people who are
Living there, they got
caught outside the dome--
Lucky bastards--
and, um...
Been there.
Hoping that someone
would free us from
this nightmare,
And when that didn't
happen, I...
You...
Decided to make the best
of a bad situation.
You know me
so well, jimmy.
What's that expression?
Uh, "never let a good
crisis go to waste"?
: Well, I
would say chester's mill
Is in more than
a crisis, so...
You and I need
to get to work.
And you're the man
to make it happen.
I'm not sure
I've ever seen a town
Where the preacher
was also the mortician.
Reverend coggins always said
He ran a one-stop
"body and soul" shop.
So let's see what
he left behind.
I really can't believe this.
What, that coggins
Was making drugs?
I've known him
since I was a little kid.
Well, he was probably
taking them, too.
Guy seemed high as a kite
every time I met him.
This is the recipe
he was using.
Denatured alcohol,
chemical stabilizers...
Liquid propane.
I've never heard of that
being used to make drugs.
Well, still, if
you need propane,
This town seems to have
a hell of a lot of it.
This one goes out to wybs's
regular deejay, phil bushey,
Who was dumb enough
to try and stop a bullet
With his shoulder yesterday.
Feel better, philly.
Holding down
the fort, huh?
I also send out an all-bandwidth
sos every three hours, but...
Let me guess-- no word
from the outside world.
Not even a peep.
So, what are you up to?
I was wondering if I
could borrow the yagi
for a couple hours.
Why?
Dome has to
have some kind
Of power source.
Thought I'd take another
shot at wandering around,
See if anything
makes it ping.
I know,
it's a long shot,
But it's still better
than nothing, right?
The yagi's not gonna help you,
'cause it stopped working
after joe and norrie
Touched the dome
the other day.
Really?
Yeah. It's another
freaky thing
That happened
because of them.
Wait, this wasn't
their idea, was it?
No, this one's all me.
Good, 'cause I still
don't trust those two.
Have you told
anyone else that?
No.
Like I promised I wouldn't.
Look, are we done here?
'cause I've got a
lot of work to do.
Yeah, sure.
Thanks, anyway.
Heard you had a shooting.
A junkie broke in to
ted utley's house
and he shot at him.
Luckily no one
was seriously hurt.
Hope we can say that next time.
Next time?
Someone opens fire.
You know it's gonna happen.
I've been thinking--
a lot of folks have
guns in our town.
The only reason ollie was able
to cut us off from his well
Was because he and his crew
were armed to the teeth.
So what are you saying,
we collect all the guns?
We might want to think about it.
Jim, people have
a constitutional
right to bear arms.
If we're still
a part of america.
Of course we are.
Really?
With that dome cutting
us off, I'd say we're
Looking more like
our own country every day.
I mean, resources
Are only gonna
get scarcer,
Tensions aren't going down
anytime soon...
That's only gonna raise it more.
Look, I know it's
gonna be controversial,
But what's the harm
in proposing the idea?
I mean,
come on, barbie,
You saw neighbor
turn against neighbor in iraq--
It's never pretty.
So let's not
Have that happen here.
I go on the radio,
I float the idea--
It's a totally
voluntary program.
I mean, hell, mine... Mine's
the first on the stack.
All right.
As long as it's voluntary
and temporary.
But the moment
this dome comes down...
People get their guns back.
Course.
You're gonna need help
making that happen, so...
That should be me.
Only if I can count on you.
You made the sale,
jim, so... Let's go.
You really on board with this?
Hell, no, but I'm
gonna stay close to him;
I want to see what he's up to.
This is councilman
jim rennie with a very
important public message.
Folks, I need your help
to make our streets safer
And our citizens more secure.
I'm starting
a firearm turn-in program.
This program is
completely voluntary.
No one's coming to your home.
This is just a way for all of us
to show each other that
No one means
anybody else any harm.
And of course...
As soon as this
crisis is over,
You all get your guns back.
And as a reward,
anyone who participates
Will get extra food,
Extra propane.
So come on down
to the sweetbriar diner,
And bring your rifles,
Your handguns, your ammo,
whatever you got.
And remember, as always...
We'll get through this...
Just as long
As we all pull together.
And this is me
on my first birthday.
Cute.
Dressed up
for my cousin's wedding.
Aw, sweet.
Oh, I didn't mean
to put that one in there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
go back to that one.
You're shirtless.
Let's see those
abs of yours.
Moving on.
Hey, guys.
Where's the yagi?
Broken... If dodee
is to be believed.
Either way, we need another
way to find the mini-dome.
We could go door-to-door.
: Ask anyone if
they went out for a walk
And happened to bring back
a mysterious orb the size
of a beach ball.
Or we could use his nose.
He sensed the mini-dome
before we could even see it,
And started growling.
Maybe he'll do it again.
Come on, we're taking a drive.
Where to, boss?
Propane warehouse.
Reverend coggins was using
that stuff to make drugs.
Junior.
Uh... Sorry, but do
you mind if I don't go
with you on this one?
You can't just bug out
on the job whenever
you feel like it.
I know,
But this is important.
Angie...
...Needs my help.
Keep your radio on.
Thanks, linda.
I knew you'd come find me.
Why have you always said that
the dome is making me sick?
Because it's true.
So you've locked me up?
In the bomb shelter,
to keep you safe.
But now you're out
and you're even sicker.
But there's more,
Isn't there?
Yeah.
But I didn't realize it
until this morning,
When you had a seizure
and started talking
about pink stars.
What about them?
Come on. I want
to show you something.
Okay, I'm coming.
Much appreciated,
mr. Danbury.
Come down for
some extra propane.
Thank you, sir.
Big jim: I can't believe
how many of our gun owners
Showed up already,
and on such short notice.
Big jim talks,
and people listen.
They do
When it's the right idea.
Here you go, jim.
Hey, listen, if you see
ted utley, tell him
I was hoping to see him
down here today.
Well, I saw him earlier.
He said you'll have to kill him
before he gives up his guns.
Damn it.
Hey, a guy like utley,
You knew he was
never gonna comply.
Ted has always been
a gun collector.
He hasn't always
been wound so tight.
Until the dome came down.
His wife was driving
their kid to camp.
Smashed right into it;
both of them died.
Been worried about him
ever since.
The man's clearly
troubled, barbie.
Whatever happened
to "we're not coming
into your homes,
This is a voluntary program"?
: Yeah.
Ted's gone cuckoo.
It might be necessary.
Hey, jim...
If he's so cuckoo, you're
gonna need some backup.
Come on, truman,
where is it?
Where's the mini-dome?
He's too busy showing us
the best places to pee.
What if it didn't move,
And it just disappeared?
Maybe we hallucinated it.
Things don't just disappear
into thin air.
Norrie: Really?
Just like things don't just
appear out of thin air
And swallow towns whole.
There is a rational
explanation for this.
Okay? For all of this.
There has to be;
we just have to find it.
Good boy, truman.
That's it, that's it.
Great. Birds.
Come on. Let's keep going.
About time the cops decided
To see what's going
on with this place.
I saw you drive up
from my porch over there.
I seen a lot of suspicious
things from that porch.
Like?
Boomer's truck blow
up the other day.
Oh, but that was an accident.
He was smoking.
Lot of other trucks
coming and going, too,
The past couple of months.
People here day and night.
And why's our town
stockpiling all this propane
In the first place?
Seems awfully convenient
once that dome came down.
Why didn't you come and tell me?
I told our former sheriff,
God rest his soul.
Duke knew about this?
Maybe it just slipped his mind.
Or he didn't
want you to know.
When I called him,
he just about hung up on me.
Never heard the man
sound so nervous.
Go talk to julia shumway.
She'll tell you I said
something here was fishy.
You didn't have to come.
I'm going in to talk
to ted utley.
Make your way around the side,
see if you can
Find a window
and get a bead on him.
But do not fire
Unless things
go sideways.
That sideways enough for you?
Don't worry, angie,
I promised you
And my dad I'd never hold you
against your will again.
But where are you taking me?
Right over here.
Your mom's studio?
Seems like yesterday
she was in here.
Not nine years ago.
She loved making art.
I remember.
I took her pottery class
in junior high.
But what does any of this have
to do with my seizure?
A couple months before she died,
she had this dream about me,
And she... Woke up,
she came out here
And she just started painting
this as fast as she could.
Now, in her dream,
I was on this hill...
...Looking up at these.
Pink stars.
Ted?
It is jim rennie.
I'm coming in,
So you're gonna put
that gun down.
Got that?
Ted:
Yeah.
Big jim:
I'm guessing that
shot at my car...
Was a misfire
'cause I know you, ted.
You're no killer.
Expecting that gun to be down.
Good.
Now I'm gonna put my gun away...
...And you and I are gonna talk.
What's going on, ted?
I can't do it, jim.
Turn in your firearms, you mean?
That dome's
already taken
Enough from me.
I know.
Janice and scott.
I'm not giving up
one more thing.
Ted, listen to me.
I know how you're feeling.
Okay? I lost
Pauline out of the blue,
nine years ago.
There's not a day that goes by
where she isn't on my mind.
It'll get better,
I promise you.
I'm sorry, jim.
But there's nothing here
for me anymore.
No!
See if they can sedate
him for the night.
Let's go back there and
pack up those firearms,
Get 'em ready to go.
Will do.
Listen, barbie,
I could practically feel
That red dot on the
back of my head so...
Glad you kept your cool and
didn't accidentally ice me.
Duke?
What the hell were you up to?
But I don't understand
why your mom would paint these.
I don't know either.
Maybe way back then,
she knew the dome was coming.
Or... The stars
are something
That will happen
now that the dome is here.
You think
she could see the future?
If she did, then you can, too,
because you started talking
About the pink stars
during your seizure.
I-I was just babbling.
And you saying it
was a coincidence?
I don't know what to think.
Yes, you do.
You know I've been right
about this all along.
I'm not crazy.
And my mom wasn't either.
She knew something was coming.
And... I must be part of it
because I'm in this painting.
And now obviously
you're part of it, too.
Don't you see how great that is?
Great?
How is any of this great?
It's great
because we're in this together.
I always loved you, angie.
And now we're connected
through something even bigger
And better than that.
So... Now what?
And tell her everything
was on the up-and-up after all.
max:
Good job with the guns.
Now, that is
what I call a success.
Uh, you didn't have
to come by here.
And miss the chance
to congratulate you in person?
Since when did you turn down
a pat on the back?
This is, uh,
dale barbara. He...
Oh, barbie and I
know each other.
Norrie:
That was a whole day wasted.
Maybe we'll come up with a way
to find the mini-dome tomorrow.
Hey, truman.
Where's your bowl?
Let's get you fed.
I'm gonna go
check on carolyn.
All right.
Norrie:
what is it this time?
A squirrel?
Probably a barn rat.
♪
You're not gonna say
anything to me, barbie?
"long time no see"?
"hey, you look great"?
Hello, max.
Anything to say to me?
After claiming
all this time
To be just a guy
passing through,
Never been to chester's mill
or anywhere around here?
Oh, kind of how you claimed that
Collecting all these
was your idea? Because she
Put you up to it.
No, I did what's
best for this town.
Oh, yeah.
Lying through your teeth
every step of the way.
Girls, girls, girls,
you're both pretty.
Which is why I'm cutting
you in on our plan
for chester's mill.
Step one: Disarm the opposition.
Hard times mean
desperate people.
Especially in this
pressure cooker. And...
Everything that
big jim said,
that was true.
We only want people to
be safe and... Happy.
Let me guess, next,
you're gonna give 'em a little
Black market to occupy
their time, am I right?
Huh? Some booze? Drugs?
A little gambling?
See? You have nothing
to worry about.
Who the hell said that
I'm gonna help you?
Who says you have a choice?
You have quite a few secrets
buried in your past, barbie.
I would hate for those secrets
To get dug up
for everyone to see.
Big jim:
Oh, please, please, dig 'em up.
Careful what
you wish for, jimmy,
Because while I'm digging,
I might accidentally reveal
A few of the pies
you've got your fingers
stuck in around town.
You both have been
working for me,
Even if you didn't
know about each other,
And now is not the time
to grow a conscience
Unless you want to
face a jail cell.
Or a lynch mob or...
Whatever it is
That passes for justice
around here these days.
You're not bulletproof, max.
Which is why I have
an insurance policy in place.
Anything bad happens to me,
your secrets still come out.
All right.
Like I said, great
job today. Jimmy,
Make sure these get
loaded up and delivered
to the cement factory.
Truck's waiting out back.
Give her a kiss good-bye
for me, will you?
Look at us.
Back in business.
And to think, it all
started...
With you buying me
that drink,
Oh, so many months ago.
No, you bought me the drink.
And then two days later,
we came up for air.
Look, whatever
you and jim
are up to here,
You are making
a huge mistake.
And you're right
there with us.
No, I don't think so.
So... You
don't care if
Julia shumway hears you
murdered her husband?
E-excuse me?
Oh, please.
You called me from
your car afterwards.
You were frantic
because he fought back.
And then I start
hearing rumors
That dr. Shumway
has vanished.
The pillow talk
between you and julia
Is gonna be done when she finds
out you're the reason why.
What?
Oh.
You're surprised that I know
you're screwing the widow, too?
For the past eight days,
I've been watching you,
And big jim, and everyone
in this hellhole.
So keep that in mind
before you even think
About opening
your big mouth.
I can't believe
it's here.
Yeah, and still...
Doing whatever
the hell it does.
That's what you found
in the woods, isn't it?
What you started
to mention earlier?
Yeah. Two days ago.
And you're not
freaking out about it?
Believe me, I want to.
But I can't deny
that I'm a part of this now.
And besides...
It's kind of cool.
Norrie: It was
in the woods.
How did it get here?
Joe brought it.
What are you
talking about?
Did you lie to me?
No, I did not bring
that thing here.
Joe, you don't remember
last night?
What's there
to remember?
I was in the kitchen
at, like, 3:00
Getting something to drink,
and then you...
Came down the stairs and
half scared me to death.
I asked you what you were doing,
and you said that you were
Going out on a walk all...
Zombie-like.
And then you
just walked out.
And you didn't stop me?
I mean, didn't you think
that that was weird?
Of course!
But what isn't these days?
Can't argue that.
Okay.
So I...
Guess I was sleep-walking.
But why did I bring
this thing here?
Julia:
But we couldn't find
the mini-dome anywhere.
I told them there has to be
a logical explanation
For why it disappeared.
I mean, this whole time
I have been holding on
To the belief
that there is some...
Explanation
for why this is happening.
After today,
I don't know.
Maybe we'll
never understand.
: Maybe it's better
to just say screw it,
And stop looking for answers
we're never gonna get.
Be grateful
for what we do have.
Right, yeah.
You want to tell me
about your day?
Nah, it can wait
till morning.
Is that right?
Mm-hmm.
Well, do you want
to take me to bed?
Actually, I'm gonna
stay up for a while.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
Fine.
♪
Well, maybe you brought it here
'cause no one else
is allowed to see it.
You think?
I don't know.
But that time you
shushed the camera,
we thought the dome
Was telling us not
to talk about our seizures.
Okay, so maybe only
people who've had them
Are supposed to
interact with it.
Which means we
probably shouldn't tell julia
That we found this again.
Okay, but...
Even if it's only
for us to know about,
What do we do with it?
Did it do this before?
No.
It's almost like...
These are locks...
And our hands are the keys.
I think we need a fourth hand.
I guess we need to find them.
Captioning sponsored by
cbs
Captioned by
media access group at wgbh
access.Wgbh.Org