Thank you for the food.
Yutaka,
having you here is enough.
(Ueda Minoru -I'll take Tane
to the zoo next weekend.)
(Do you want to come with us?)
"Our Dining Table"
"Episode 3"
(Ueda)
This is for you.
This is for me?
Yes.
(Kitazakiyama Zoo)
Yukata, bring a lunchbox on that day.
Lunchbox?
Yeah. Can you also put octopus in it?
Octopus?
Octopus.
Mr. Octopus Sausage?
Yeah, Mr. Octopus Sausage.
Thank you.
This kid.
Since he saw Mr. Octopus Sausage
in a friend's lunchbox at school,
he's been so noisy,
asking me to "make it."
I'm not noisy.
You're bad for not making it for me.
It's such a hassle,
who would want to do it?
I want octopus.
Too hard.
- Octopus.
- No.
- I won't make it.
- Octopus.
- No.
- Anyway, let's just make it.
- No, I won't make it. - I want octopus.
With Mr. Octopus Sausage too.
Yutaka, you can make lunchboxes too?
Yeah.
Really? That's amazing.
Amazing.
Yukata's lunchbox.
(1.Put filling in the rice, wrap it,
and make it into a triangular shape.)
(2.Cut the boiled red sausage in half.
Use a heart-shaped cutter to cut it.)
(3.Boil a carrot and cut into a circle.
Use seaweed to make the eyes and mouth.)
I made a lot because Yuki likes it.
When was that?
In kindergarten?
Don't join a lunchbox making club
or something like that.
All right.
I'll go buy some drinks. Wanna come?
No, thank you. I have mine.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hozumi.
What's wrong?
Uh... Nothing.
I just realized you brought
your lunchbox today.
Yeah, sometimes I do.
Do you want to sit and have some?
No. It's not like that.
Well...
Do you have some time?
(OST Design)
What is it?
Please...
Well...
Can I ask you to teach me
how to make a lunchbox?
Huh?
I made a promise to
my friend's little brother.
But after thinking about it,
even though I can say I cook for myself,
I'm only good at making rice balls.
I've never made a lunchbox.
And Ohata, your lunchbox looks so good.
If it's not too much of a bother...
It's not a bother, but...
It's like it came out of nowhere, right?
I'm sorry. It's totally okay.
It's not like that.
It's just that it's the first time
that you asked for help.
Of course, I'll help you.
I hope the boy will be happy with it.
Here.
(How to make rolled egg.
How to make Mr. Octopus Sausage.)
You can do it.
Thank you so much.
(How to make rolled egg.
How to make Mr. Octopus Sausage.)
Ugh.
This is hard.
It seems...
like there's room for improvement.
Thank you.
Hmm...
When you made the rolled egg,
did you add water to the beaten egg?
I didn't.
If you add around three tablespoons
of water, the egg will be fluffier.
Thank you.
And... maybe the way you fry it.
- The way I fry it.
- Yeah.
(Tips for making rolled egg.
Tips for making Mr. Octopus Sausage.)
Next...
- I'm a penguin.
(Good news. Seems like we can
have lunch in front of the gorillas.)
Why are you smiling?
- Who's smiling?
Is it Yukata?
No.
Stop it. You left the stove on.
Tane.
(Ueda Minoru
Minoru sent a video to you.)
Can I open it?
Yes.
It looks very good.
Amazing.
Thank you for the food.
Okay.
You did very well.
No.
Mm.
It's very good.
- Really?
- Mm.
When he sees this
he'll definitely be happy.
I hope so.
Are you going to the zoo tomorrow?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just suddenly feel a little nervous.
Nervous?
Mm.
I can do most of what you taught me,
but when I think about
if he'll really like my food,
I suddenly feel nervous.
Hozumi.
You must really like him, right?
That boy.
Or else you wouldn't feel nervous.
When we talk about lunchboxes,
both of the kind
that you make for yourself
and the kind the you make
for someone else are good.
When you think the person
you like will say "It's delicious,"
then it's definitely worth making it.
Mm.
- Can I have rolled egg too?
Of course.
- Yay.
What are you filming?
I'm sending it to Yutaka.
- Yukata?
- Yeah.
Yukata.
What are you doing?
You try acting like an animal too.
No way.
Act like one.
What a pain.
Then...
A gorilla.
You're so weird.
Stop it. I'm going to pee my pants.
Wait. Stop.
No.
You already did, didn't you? Oh, no.
All right.
- That's it for the new
and popular cartoons.
- Next will be the weather report.
- Moving on to you, Ms. Kodera.
- Yes, I'll report today's weather
across the country.
- From the movement of the air front,
we may experience a temperature drop.
The weather in the eastern part of
Japan can change quite frequently.
- There may be rain in some areas.
- Please bring rain gear.
- Done.
- When you go outside.
Please allow me.
Yukata.
Tane.
I can't wait to eat the lunchbox.
You have to wait for lunchtime.
Let's eat when you feel hungry.
Okay.
What's up with you, Tane?
You're pretty obedient today.
It's normal.
Normal, right?
You've been looking forward to it.
Yes.
Is that all your stuff?
Yeah, it is.
I just need to check the doors
because Dad isn't home today.
Okay, I'll take it outside for you.
Thanks.
Huh?
- Ahh!
Maybe it's a short downpour?
Let's just wait for a while.
- Right.
- Mm.
It will stop soon.
No way. No.
No.
The zoo.
Crying won't help.
The weather is unpredictable.
No, I want to go to the zoo.
Tane.
Tane, it's too bad,
but let's go there next week instead.
No.
Stop it, Tane.
This way.
Wow.
Welcome to my homemade zoo.
Wow, the zoo!
It's clearly a zoo.
This is so you, Yutaka.
Didn't you send me
the video of Tane playing?
Yeah.
I remembered there were
plushies in the room.
That video is really adorable.
I lost count on how many times
I've watched it.
Yukata, I want to eat the lunchbox.
It's only 11 o'clock. Can you eat now?
Yes, I can.
Really?
If so, let's eat now.
Okay.
Here. This is yours.
Wow.
What do we say...?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here's yours.
There's one for me too?
That's really too much...
It's totally fine.
I already made it. Just eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yukata, can I open it now?
Of course.
Wow.
Amazing.
Can I eat now?
Yes.
Thank you for the food.
Yummy.
Really?
That's a relief.
Great. I'll eat too.
(Thank you so much!
It's so amazing.
(Thank you as always.)
Amazing.
I used a cutter to make it.
I woke up at five to make it.
Five?! Are you serious?
But...
I'm so glad.
Now... I feel bad that I have to eat it.
Just eat it.
Thank you.
Then...
Thank you for the food.
Mm.
It's yummy.
I'm so relieved.
It's super yummy.
It's yummy, right? Mm.
I'll have some too.
Thank you so much for today.
Thanks for making Tane a lunchbox,
and for making one for me too.
I'm really glad.
Thanks to the both of you, I'll
have good memories of today.
Thank you.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
To be honest, I...
I've never made a lunchbox before.
Huh?
I said, "Let's just make it,"
without really thinking about it.
And I just couldn't back out.
Honestly, I was really anxious.
For the past half month,
my colleague taught me a lot of things.
The flavour and the appearance.
I was so nervous
until the moment you both ate it.
When the person you like says it's good,
it really makes you happy, right?
The sun is out.
Let's go to the zoo.
The sun is out? Shall we go now?
Okay.
All right, then let's get ready.
Which one first?
Panda.
Okay, this one.
Put it in.
What about the head?
The person you like...
Right.
(Next episode)
Yutaka.
(A wound that won't heal)
Bro...
(Past memories)
When he's around,
the food suddenly tastes bad.
(Emotional wound, hesitation)
Yukata,
just think of us as family.
(It takes a while for the snow to melt...)
Don't worry about it.
(This story is a work of fiction)
I guess it's not only our family
that went through a lot of things.
(Characters and organizations
appearing in this work are fictitious)