(OST Design)
Finally, time for lunch.
I'm taking a lunch break.
Okay.
Shall we grab something to eat?
Mei, let's go.
Okay, let's go.
What should we eat?
Right...
My body mostly consists of...
rice balls, salad,
and stuff in supermarkets.
I have the same food
and live my life
with the same routine every day.
Thank you for the food.
(Can you come home for
Dad's 60th birthday next month?)
(I got it. I'll go.)
(I can't make it on that day.)
Well...
Who are you?
This is super yummy.
Is that so?
I made it myself.
Really?
Man, you are a genius.
"Man"?
Where is your family?
I have an older brother.
Where is your brother?
Hey, Tane.
Didn't I tell you to wait
at the checkout counter?
What the heck are you doing?
What are you eating?
I got it from him.
Sorry for giving it to him
without asking you.
Don't take his important rice ball
just because you want it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Come on, let's go.
Come here.
What was that?
"Our Dining Table"
"Episode 1"
All right, all right.
Since the construction of the hall
in front of the station has finished,
let's have some drinks.
That's a good idea.
- Are you coming? Come on.
- Yeah, let's go.
- Are you coming?
- Yes.
Hozumi, do you want to come with us?
I'll pass.
Oh...
Thank you for all your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
He's so bad at socializing.
(30% off)
(Can you come home for
Dad's 60th birthday next month?)
That kid yesterday...
Teach me how to make that rice ball.
Watch it.
Don't you have something to say
before that?
Sorry for eating
your rice ball yesterday.
Sorry
for taking your lunch.
Don't be. It's okay.
I also need to apologize for giving it
to him without asking you.
You came here just to apologize to me?
That's part of the reason.
But this guy,
he kept saying the rice ball was so good
he wanted to eat it again.
I wanted to know
what kind of rice ball it was.
It's just a normal rice ball.
It's like a grenade.
Oh.
It does look like a grenade.
It's a mix with the purpose
to fill the stomach quickly
and give you complete nutrition.
It's almost as big as your head.
No, you can't eat it.
I'll make one for you later.
Yours doesn't taste good.
If I set my mind to it, I can do it too.
No, it's awful.
But I do it all the time.
Fine, I won't do it anymore.
- No, it's awful.
- Will that be okay?
It's okay if I don't do it?
No, it's awful.
- Don't say you don't want it.
- But it's awful.
Nothing.
I just thought you two
seem like good siblings.
Right.
Shall we share this?
Yes, thank you.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I'm glad you like it that much.
Then I'll give you this in return.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Thank you.
Mm.
You know...
If you don't mind,
can you teach him
how to make the rice ball yourself?
Is this weekend convenient for you?
(Ueda pottery workshop)
I couldn't say no
because of the kid's sweet little smile.
And he gave me candy.
But more importantly,
the biggest reason is because...
the older brother seems pretty scary.
(Ueda pottery workshop)
I guess it's here.
Oh, you're here for
the hands-on workshop?
Wow, I'm glad.
Please come inside.
No, I'm here to see the older brother.
You're Minoru's friend?
No.
Really?
So, he has a friend.
I see.
Minoru is inside. You can go ahead.
Well...
Hey.
I have a question for you.
Poop flavored curry
or curry flavored poop,
Which one do you want?
Of course the curry is better.
Then...
Stew-flavoured vomit,
or vomit-flavoured stew?
Of course...
Wait.
Which one?
Wait a sec.
Vomit flavored...
Vomit flavored?
Well...
Excuse me...
Oh, it's Mr. Rice Ball.
You really came?
I'll take it.
Don't drop it. It's dangerous.
Here. Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I didn't expect you to actually come.
Oh...
But I promised.
We're going to make
a grenade together, right?
Yeah.
Well...
Mr. Rice Ball, what's your name?
Mr. Rice Ball...
It's Hozumi Yutaka.
My name is Ueda Minoru.
And this guy...
I'm Tane.
Mr. Rice Ball, nice to meet you.
Tane, it's nice to meet you too.
Mm!
Sir, please begin.
Even though you said that,
it's just a normal rice ball.
But Tane kept saying it's "yummy."
There must be something different.
Different?
Like, maybe your hands
are a god's hands
made specially for rice balls.
Don't you think your rice
seems a bit yellowish?
Is that so?
And the smell...
Did you clean the back of the lid
of the rice cooker?
I guess you didn't.
Oh, I never thought the difference
would be the rice cooker.
But I use a clay pot.
That's it. That must be it.
Last year, my rice cooker broke down.
I used a clay pot instead and it
turned out great, so I keep using it.
Do you live alone?
Yes.
But my parents' house is not far away.
It's good to live alone.
You have freedom.
I guess.
It's very loud in my house.
Isn't it quite lively?
Oh, no, that's not lively at all.
He's a monster.
It must be difficult for you.
At first, use high heat.
After it has boiled, lower the heat.
When there's no steam coming out,
it's done.
Using a clay pot is faster
than I thought.
Oh, right.
Do you like the burnt rice
at the bottom of the pot?
I do.
Let's make a lot of that, then.
Before you turn off the heat,
use high heat again.
Leave it for around ten seconds.
It's ready.
Come on.
It smells great.
It looks yummy.
Before we mess it up,
the middle part tastes the best.
Who would take it?
- Me.
Mmm.
Yummy.
Yummy, right?
Put seaweed and rice on a plastic wrap.
Sprinkle a little salt.
Tane, what's your favorite filling?
I love kombu and salmon.
Then let's put those in.
Sprinkle the salmon around.
Good job.
Yukata, what's your favorite filling?
It's "Yutaka."
Mine...
I'd say rolled egg and fried chicken.
Can you use those as fillings?
Rice balls are freedom.
I see.
Are you done? Then make it round.
Pull it up and press it.
That's right.
Wow, so many grenades. Let's dig in.
I'll make some tea.
I'll help serve it.
- Wait.
- You know,
I should probably go.
You have something to do?
It's not like that.
Yukata, you should eat with us.
Well, it's already done.
Please don't worry.
Let's eat together.
Yutaka.
You...
don't even know how to eat, do you?
I'm...
not good at...
eating around other people.
Here.
It's the one I made.
Eat it.
How is it?
A little too salty.
Ew.
But...
it's good.
Yummy!
It's yummy when everyone eats together.
Yeah, right?
Here.
I'll have some too.
It's so big.
I'll eat now.
It is a little too salty.
Thank you so much for today.
Same here.
Well...
Can you come visit again?
Tane had a lot of fun.
If you could come
and eat with us sometime,
he'd probably be so happy.
What do you say?
Okay.
My body is mostly made up from
rice balls, salad,
and stuff in supermarkets.
I have the same food
and live my life
with the same routine every day.
But now...
something different
has got into my body.
Something warm,
whole,
and sparkling.
Sorry for what I asked for today.
- It's totally fine.
- You helped a lot.
Hello, Tane.
Yeah.
Let's make it again this week.
Any special request?
Okay, curry it is, then.
Whoa, that's rare.
What kind of curry do you like?
Maybe that something...
is what I've always been longing for.
(Next episode)
Even if it's a luxury meal,
if you couldn't eat it
with a smile on your face,
it would be more painful.
(Unspoken memories from the past)
Having Yutaka here is enough.
(First meeting)
(Someone who wants me)
(This story is a work of fiction)
Thank you for the food.
(and has no relation to
any real person or organization)