The Legend of Chusen
Episode 16
Lady Hua.
Lady Hua, I need to talk to you.
The Legend of Chusen
Ye Tian.
Brother.
What did you do to my brother?
I did nothing.
I knew you were up to no good.
But you came too late.
Guards.
Yes.
Arrest him.
What are you doing?
I don't know what happened.
I didn't touch him.
Do you think I would believe you?
Arrest him.
Wait.
Mr. Gu.
The power of the spirit is so strong.
Who hurt Prince Liu like this?
I saw the registration form.
You are a key master of the martial arts world.
Your name is Hua Zhaoyang.
I know.
My name is Hua Zhaoyang.
Am I right?
Yes.
But I didn't hurt Ye Tian.
You are still lying.
Since you are both
guests invited by Prince Liu,
I won't offend you.
I have a Aura of the King.
If the one who is the master is lying,
the spell will not work.
If you are lying,
the spell will be activated.
The more you are sincere, the more you are fierce.
Would you like to prove your innocence?
Yes.
How could it be?
What are you doing?
Wait.
This key master is not lying.
But...
The King's Mansion will not be wrong.
The truth is more serious.
Master, my brother...
I will take Prince Liu to heal first.
Thank you, Master.
Demon.
I said I didn't lie to you.
Do you believe it?
I thought Prince Liu
had a full meridians.
Thank you for saving me.
As far as I know,
you have some old wounds.
But they have been healed.
Did you get any medicine?
No.
I have sent some to my father.
I thought I was healed
by the master.
It seems that I didn't serve you.
How did you get the wound today?
You don't want to tell me?
The key master who was in the Sixth Prince's room
is strange.
It was just a coincidence.
Do you know who he is?
The key master doesn't believe in the key master.
I can assure you that
the key master is not a bad person.
I don't know
what you have been through.
But I have something to say.
I have said a lot.
Although the meridians are healed,
you are seriously ill.
You are in the lung.
It's hard to find a cure.
There is no cure.
This is strange.
I am just worried that
the key master is not good for you.
But if you can
protect the key master,
I want to ask you
if you have
any time to be poisoned?
What is this strange idea?
I don't understand.
Your Highness,
evil thoughts should not be kept in mind for a long time.
If there is something unpleasant in daily life,
I am willing to listen
and share your worries.
You are worrying too much.
Never mind.
Prince Liu, rest in peace.
Take care, State Preceptor.
Three taels of wine, five points of tar,
half a inch of hook, two thousand of love flowers.
This poison is my best antidote.
It can solve the past hatred.
Maybe
I will help you hide the secret
until the last moment.
Anyone who has the poison on us
should take the medicine
and rest in peace.
State Preceptor,
I am so worried about my dead body.
I am really sorry for you.
Your Majesty,
it's not what you should say.
To be honest,
I feel guilty.
State Preceptor,
why are you feeling guilty?
I feel guilty.
For many years,
I have been only concerned about spiritual power and magic.
I have the title of the best magician in the world,
but I can't help you.
State Preceptor, you worry too much.
I have never expected to be cured.
I just want to
be able to hold on
until the moment when I am forgiven.
His mother
died in a war with State Preceptor.
His younger brother is in love with Rong'er.
It's hard to tell.
I am also heartless.
I can only hope that
he can be forgiven in time.
When he can be at ease,
I can rest assured and rest assured.
I will try my best
to help you with the Sixth Prince.
State Preceptor, you are considerate.
When Tian'er grows up,
I can let you out of the palace
without worrying about you
and finding the Sura.
I will try my best
to help you.
Why are you...
Didn't he
lose face in the palace?
So I changed my clothes.
Did Ye Xun
laugh at you?
How dare he laugh at me?
I...
I think
I'm used to it
and want to change clothes.
Does it look good?
It fits you.
By the way,
I came here
to explain to you.
Bye.
No need.
I believe
you didn't mean it.
You believe me?
You saved my life.
I believe you.
But
how did you
get in here in the middle of the night?
The guards at your door
didn't let me in.
So I jumped out of the window.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
The spirit energy
is the best in the world.
The body that has been
healed overnight
is still in the body.
And the strange
qi poison that is deep in the bone.
I'm not happy
and angry.
But I'm still
in the doubt.
Ye Tian.
What are you planning?
The soul that I'm looking for
is you, right?
I'm here.