Excellent.
The成
Forbidden
Episode 16
My master has passed away.
You nearly got me too.
Now that we've var房 sólo
it can be a real natural.
From the day
I'm already a god.
Everything is as ancient as it is.
The evil year of Xiu Luo is born.
After killing Xiu Luo,
this Yin-Yang Yu will be divided into two pieces.
Now you only need to marry the monk
to become a real god.
But obviously,
when I woke up, he was already a god.
Is this jade
given to me by Master?
Why don't I remember it at all?
You have forgotten a lot of things
in the past five years.
But it's okay.
Go and wait for the god.
Is this the heaven's long street?
The flower-sweeping yang is full of Tao.
Xiu Luo is already a god.
But if you want to become a god,
you still have a chance.
What?
You still need to fulfill the most powerful obsession
in the world.
The one you should save the most.
Master Zeeh.
Master.
Qi pierwsze qu nh99
Xiu luü
Find her in the turns
Be with her hardones in past times
and draw his evil thoughts.
The jade pendant in your hand is tied to the Heavenly Emperor.
It's the only thing that can be taken back by the Soul of the Soul.
Your natural power will be sealed into the Spirit Jade
and you will be able to return to the Soul.
Your memory will also be sealed into the Soul of the Soul
and you will be replaced.
The Soul of the Soul will be born in the year of the evil.
After killing the Soul of the Soul,
this Yin-Yang Jade will be divided into two pieces.
I have a question.
How many times have I been defeated by the jade pendant
that has not been returned to the Soul of the Soul?
Has it been that I have been in the Soul of the Soul
since I was born?
I feel like I have some memories of the day.
That girl is puerful, right?
She is not your kind of bastard.
She has spoured so much,
but she has not been returned to the Soul of the Soul of the Soul.
Let me try.
What's the problem?
What happened?
This is a world where the sun and the moon
are in the same place.
Every day, the sky and earth
are divided into two.
The light and rain between the two
are equal.
But when you and Ye Tiancheng
are all in a mess,
no matter what,
you have to leave with love and hate.
I gave you three thousand times of the cycle
and it's always like this.
It's always turning around.
It's been ten days
and you've been back to your original state.
But I woke up.
Isn't it a good thing?
I will still remember you.
Even if you give me three thousand times of the cycle,
you have to leave with the right time.
What if I refuse?
No one can refuse to go to the warehouse.
Do you know what Ye Tiancheng will say?
Go to the warehouse!
Remember your past and prospects.
Do you still remember me?
I haven't forgotten at all.
I'm not a fixed person.
Please teach me China History.
If you can use
If you have a chance,
I hope you can
go to the mountain with Chief Hua.
I don't have the money to pay you.
The monster in the mountain is not expensive.
Don't pay me.
As long as you're willing to take me.
You don't let others touch you.
It's because you're afraid that others will touch you
and you'll be afraid of the sunset.
But I don't want you to suffer this pain.
I've made my choice.
If I were you,
I might have the same choice.
But we have to admit that
the one who has memories
is the most painful.
You've been calling my name in your dream.
Yes.
And I've always been
a stranger to you.
On the surface,
I'm here to get the bill.
But it looks like
it's possible that God
made a mistake
and let us meet again.
I have to choose
to seal all the memories
in your mind
in this rain.
You've been
trying to leave the band.
Let's leave together tonight.
You're a bit different from the people in the prison.
What happened?
The superior wants to seal our memories.
Let's start over.
You're a dog.
Don't mind him.
No matter how things change,
we'll always be together.
Let's spend the days together.
I've never been哦
longer than you.
Wait for me.
I love you.
Thoughts will be over.
You finally had me.
I do not know
how complicated it is
to stay together.
感受
those happiness between the lovers.
By the time we were young,
the melhor was the brightness of the点亮.
However,
we found the fragrance of the 컳 한.
The only question
is that greetings
are the only thing that we know.
Dayou.
We'll finallyacquake
to find happiness for each other.
In this case,
our heart
will only be left with Ningjing
and deep love.
This is the end of our legendary legend.
Brother,
he's always asking for the position of the imperial guard.
He's a small liar.
He's not willing to be taught.
See?
The imperial guard is a great man.
How can he be so foolish?
Of course I won't be foolish.
Come in.
Your Majesty.
You've always wanted to be a national adviser.
Then, what about talking about Feng Lu?
Since you want to talk about Feng Lu with me,
why don't you consider another position?
Hua Rongyu.
Brother.
Can you keep your temper?
Shut up.
Ye Xun.
It's over.
Someone's apologizing.
I'm just here to apologize.
Are you apologizing?
I'm not apologizing.
Why are you saying that?
Ye Tian.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
What are you doing?
What?
This is my new magic.
Isn't it amazing?
Amazing? You're so smart.
Let go of me.
Master, don't you think you're not good at magic?
What magic?
Of course it's a magic that makes me listen to you.
Really?
Then try it.
It's expensive.
No, no, no.
You like reading my novel the most, right?
I'm not good at it.
Tell me.
I'll write it tonight.
I'll write it for you.
Okay?
I'll write it all.
It's expensive.
Don't, don't, don't.
Come back.
Come back, Ye Tian.
I'm not going back.
Come back.
Come here.
Don't run.
Come and chase me.
Little wood.
Come and have a look.
This book is very tight.
Three books are worth buying.
There will be a discount.
When the sky is completely bright,
it's the only time that Zhao Yang and the cruel night can be melted.
The smoke is very strong.
That's right.
It's not good.
I'll give you a discount.
The Taoist should read these.
Zhao Yang knows the night.
This book is not so boring.
I'll write it for you.