[English subtitles are available]
[War of Faith]
[Episode 9]
Why did you get hit this time?
Business.
Because of the Communist Party?
Why don't you quit?
You tire yourself out every day without getting any benefits.
Just quit.
I'll feed you.
You'll feed me?
I eat quite a lot.
It's just a matter of tricking some rich heirs.
It's not a big deal.
Are you taking me as a boy toy?
You've got guts.
I'm talking to you seriously.
If you don't work as an official,
there's still a possibility for us.
Resign.
I'm serious.
I've saved some money these two years.
Even if we just run some small business,
we can still live nicely.
Don't be like this.
I told you
I can die anytime.
I also told you
I'm not doing this job
just to get promoted and get rich.
I don't come to you to be a rich official's wife either.
You won't be included in the family tree,
but
after I die,
if you don't mind,
you can be buried with me.
You can also write on the tombstone,
"Madam Song,
wife of Lin Qiaosong."
[The Central Bank of China]
Hello?
Okay, let me check.
Please wait a moment.
Sorry.
Mr. Shen's schedule
doesn't have this event.
Mr. Shen asked us to go over immediately.
Hurry.
Come in.
Sir.
From now on,
cancel all the scheduled appointments
and activities.
You two must be on standby at all times
and can't take leave.
Yes.
Come here, Ruolai.
This is
the import and export data
of major commercial associations and banks from recent years.
Memorize them all for me.
These days,
you'll visit these
finance industry bigwigs with me.
When I need it,
you must tell me with complete accuracy.
Yes.
I'll memorize it now, sir.
S...
What's wrong?
Sir,
what are your plans for me?
Stay and look after the house.
I'm your secretary.
Besides,
I have dealt with
those financial bigwigs before.
I'm more familiar with their situation,
sir.
I'm leaving you here
to do more important things.
We will receive a lot of
invitation letters and phone calls recently.
Some people will rush over here directly.
None of them will be easy to deal with.
I'm leaving you here
so you can deal with them
in my place.
Yes, sir.
Well,
are you up to something big recently?
You'll know soon.
The Central Bank of China announces
that starting today, the Treasury Department and the Central Bank
both appoint Special Advisor Shen Tunan
as the plenipotentiary
to lead the matter in taking back tariff autonomy
and decide whether it will be approved by a democratic vote.
All parties must cooperate actively
without delay.
From the Treasury Department.
Shen Tunan
is crazy for money!
Hello?
Mingquan.
Mr. Yu.
Have you read the Treasury Department's newest telegram?
Just read it.
Does Shen Tunan want to die?
How dare he provoke a tiger?
He's using Mr. Song's name.
This is an overt strategy.
It's obvious that they want to cut off our flow of wealth.
Exactly.
Back when Yuan Shikai
borrowed money from HSBC,
Banque de l'Indochine and Yokohama Specie Bank,
he used the tariff management right
as a mortgage.
It's a huge deposit
with financial stability.
It's also the trump card
to control the government's finance.
Without this weapon,
the interests of all foreign traders
will be severely damaged.
He's just messing around.
Calm down.
Mr. Yu,
how can I calm down?
Shen Tunan already snatched the Imperial Bank.
It's thanks to you
that I'm working at HSBC now.
What I'm responsible for now
is borrowing money from the industries under your name
and other private banks.
I use the money from the tariffs.
If we don't have this,
we won't be able to survive.
Shen Tunan is forcing us to rebel.
Don't panic.
Chess
is about going back and forth.
He's already made his move.
Next,
it's our turn.
The Central Bank is treacherous.
The Central Bank is corrupted and incompetent.
[The Central Bank destroyed the country's finance]
The Central Bank is treacherous.
The Central Bank is corrupted and incompetent.
Mrs. Wang.
Madam.
The people in the yard
are here to protect us.
So,
make some soup for them later.
Don't neglect them.
Okay.
Ruolai.
What do you think about the tariff reform?
I support all of your decisions.
I didn't know before,
but after reading the report,
I realized that our country is so poor.
It's not just poor.
It's long been unable to make ends meet.
A war requires guns and ammunition.
Construction
requires oil, coal, steel, and cement.
We can't do anything without money.
This time,
we must have the control
of the tariffs in our own hands.
For this,
even offending those with vested interests
or even infuriating the foreign powers
is worth it.
But true reform
requires bloodshed.
Are you afraid?
No.
My father said before
that even if the sky falls down,
the tall ones will hold it up.
Let me ask you.
If someone wanted to kill me
and shot a bullet suddenly
or put a bomb under the car,
would you be afraid of being implicated?
No.
If that really happened,
I hope you could give me some
compensation fee
and mail it to my father.
My life is not worth much anyway.
I'll give it all to you.
Where is he?
Tell Shen Tunan to come out.
Shen Tunan!
Come out!
Come out now!
Mr. Zhang,
sirs,
sorry to keep you waiting.
Here, enjoy your drink.
Cut it out.
Where's Shen Tunan?
Is he seeing us or not?
Tell him to come out.
Didn't I tell you?
Mr. Shen
went out to meet a guest.
I don't know
where he is now either.
Okay.
We'll wait.
We'll come here and wait every day.
I'd like to see if he'll return to the Central Bank or not.
Mr. Zhang,
sirs,
how do I put it?
You're all big figures.
There's no need to make a scene with us small figures.
What did you say?
Who's making a scene?
The blade is against our neck.
Can't we call for help?
Shen Tunan
is blatantly targeting us.
Don't we have the right to air our grievances?
Where's Shen Tunan?
We must see him today.
Tell him to come out.
Guards!
Please help Mr. Zhang move.
Yes
Don't move. Let's see who dares to move.
Who dares?
Let go!
What are you doing?
I'm telling you,
I must see Shen Tunan today!
You know what this is, right?
Kill me if you dare
and I'll die in the Central Bank today.
I—
Mr. Zhang,
this is the Central Bank,
not HSBC
and definitely not the Imperial Bank.
By the way, I'd like to tell everyone
that if you follow the rules,
the Central Bank welcomes you anytime.
But if you make trouble,
don't blame me for changing my attitude.
Take him away.
What are you doing? Don't touch me!
Go.
Huang,
who do you think you are?
Wait.
Mr. Zhang.
Take the gun.
Take care.
Give it to him when he's out.
Yes.
Go.
Let go of me!
Secretary Huang.
Why are you so brave?
You're so amazing.
You dared to shoot the gun.
Go back to work.
Awesome.
Give me a hand.
Tunan,
you're still so impatient.
It's a mess outside now.
I had no choice.
If we don't do this,
the country will be destroyed.
It's not at that point.
Yes, it is, Mr. Jiang.
Do you remember
how the Ming Dynasty was overthrown?
Li Zicheng?
That was just the trigger.
The main reason was financial bankruptcy.
If a country can't collect money
or taxes,
it can't raise the army.
If there is a natural disaster
and the government's finances are in a tight situation,
they'll have no money to help the refugees,
leading to riots everywhere.
To be honest,
the state's financial situation now
is almost the same as it was in the late Ming period.
Do you remember
how the Qing Dynasty was overthrown?
The Railway Protection Movement.
Thank you.
A greedy court
that disregards its reputation,
destroys contracts,
and embezzles the people's money
will surely cause public resentment.
Moreover,
tax reform touches the interests
of the Western powers.
If you push them too hard,
you might have
another disaster with the Eight-Nation Allied Forces.
I don't think so.
What did you say?
Sorry.
I'm used to interrupting in class.
I was talking nonsense.
It's okay.
Just say whatever you're thinking.
We're not having a meeting.
We're just chatting.
Don't be hesitant. Just speak.
I may have a different opinion
on the Eight-Nation Allied Forces you mentioned.
I'd like to hear it.
The Qing Dynasty emphasized agriculture over commerce.
The government was hostile to overseas trade,
so they couldn't communicate normally
with the Western powers.
But it's different now.
The government values trade
and follows the game's rules.
It has a business perspective.
So, I don't think
there'll be a large-scale armed conflict.
Do you think they will just sit and watch
if their personal interests are affected?
If there are enough benefits,
I think we should take the risk.
Mr. Jiang,
this kid is a fresh graduate.
He doesn't hold back when talking.
Please forgive him.
This is the best.
We're all pushed to the top.
It's hard to hear the truth.
Go on.
Let's see what benefits
are worth us to take risks for.
I have a landlord called Ms. Zhou.
She runs a laundry shop.
She works from day to night,
but she still complains that she doesn't make money.
It's because she borrowed money
from a bank
with shockingly high interest.
But the bank's money
was borrowed from those
foreign investment banks.
This means that Ms. Zhou made one loan
but pays interest to two parties.
If we can
get the tariff autonomy back,
then the Central Bank can lend money
with relatively low interest to the people who need it.
Once the people have good lives,
they'll start loving the country
and the country will be stronger.
How will
us industrialists
benefit from a successful tariff reform?
Mr. Jiang is asking you. Why are you looking at me?
Answer him.
Mr. Jiang, with all due respect,
the Yongcheng Bank under your name
has always been supporting
the manufacturing of fabric, flour, ships, and other industries.
But in recent years,
our country's industries
have been under the pressure of foreign capital.
The loans you released
have many bad debts already.
If we don't change this situation,
how much longer do you think you can hold out for?
He has the style of the School of Diplomacy.
He uses fear tactics immediately.
So if we take back the tariff autonomy,
the Central Bank will have more tariff balance
to support the industries.
This is a great benefit for you.
That's a nice promise.
Did you teach him?
No.
I didn't teach him, Mr. Jiang.
My actions represent the country.
I state things as they are.
There's no need to bluff, Mr. Jiang.
I can take my old friends
to vote for you
and support you in the tariff reform.
Really?
But I have a condition.
Go ahead, Mr. Jiang.
I need a guarantee from Mr. Song.
What guarantee?
Promise to never apportion
war debt to us again.
Mr. Jiang,
you make it sound like
the Kuomintang government
are robbers.
Since the Beiyang government,
the government's bank
has always been a tool to raise money for war.
The old warlords never planned on
repaying the war debts they apportioned.
We don't want Chiang Kai-shek to be a another warlord.
We also don't want
the Central Bank to become the next war tool.
Don't worry.
The Central Bank is definitely not the old type of bank.
As long as I'm here,
I won't let this happen.
Good.
I hope you keep your promise.
Have some tea.
Young man, have some tea.
No, thanks.
Drink it.
You spoke well earlier.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Jiang
is a leader among national bankers.
Since he expressed his attitude,
we're halfway to success.
Then,
is the other half Yu Shiqing?
Yu Shiqing.
He's the actual controller of the Commercial Association of Suzhou and Shanghai.
He started from trading with foreigners.
To put it bluntly, he is a big comprador.
Foreign banks like HSBC
are on his side.
Someone so powerful like him
won't be easy to deal with, right?
Of course.
We can't do it just by chatting.
In fact, Yu Shiqing should be
the biggest obstacle for this reform.
If we push him too hard,
will he cause trouble?
Of course.
Without considering political influences,
assassination is the most economical solution.
Sir, how about I apply for a gun?
No.
You are my assistant,
not my bodyguard.
Just do your job.
Yes.
Mr. Yu, what a shame!
Even Shen Tunan's dog is so arrogant.
If he gets the upper hand,
we won't be able to survive anymore.
You can't survive
by yelling.
You must use your brain.
The director of HSBC
is already pressuring me.
If I can't keep the tariff management rights,
I have to resign.
At worst, we'll just die together.
It's not at that point.
Politics is an art of compromise.
Violence is not the way.
We are not bandits.
If we don’t act now,
I really won't be able to survive, Mr. Yu.
What’s the hurry?
He must want to meet me recently.
Let's hear his thoughts first.
If you have time,
you can make preparations.
Some blood
is okay when necessary.
Are you okay?
Why do you need a gun?
Mr. Qian,
it's not safe lately.
I just want a gun to protect myself
and the people around me.
It doesn't have to be a great gun.
It's fine as long as it's repeating.
I don't have any.
We're an axe gang.
We never use guns.
Then, Mr. Qian,
can you ask someone for one for me?
It's quite urgent.
Little friend, tell me the truth.
Are you in trouble?
If someone bullies you,
tell me and I'll stand up for you.
No, Mr. Qian. Really.
I'll give you an axe.
It's manganese steel.
You don't have to use strength to chop off someone's legs.
No need, Mr. Qian.
This doesn't really suit me.
[New Show Club]
I'll shoot you.
Thank you, sir.
Hope you have fun.
It's late. Are you going out?
I have a family banquet.
You have to go too.
Me too?
Yu Shiqing's wife,
the boss of Menghua Pictures,
said she just got a script.
The female lead suits me well.
The female lead suits you well?
They have an ulterior motive.
Since they're expressing kindness,
we have to respond.
You want to act in a movie, right?
Guess.
You do.
No.
But I thought
that if I rejected them,
you'd have no more room for maneuvering.
So, I thought to just deal with them
and play it by ear.
With a wife like you, what more can I ask for?
Good that you know.
Which one is prettier?
This one.
Nothing is going smoothly lately.
Mr. Zhang, that's enough.
Don't be mad.
What are you looking at?
Look again.
Stop singing.
Drink with me.
Mr. Zhang.
She's with Lin Qiaosong.
Captain Lin.
Lin what?
Lin Qiaosong.
He's the captain of the Shanghai Garrison Command's Investigation and Arrest Unit.
You should know him.
Why would I know a servant?
I don't even respect Mr. Kang.
Mr. Zhang.
What are you waiting for?
Come and drink with me.
Let's go.
It has to be...
Get out of the way!
Stop her!
No, Mr. Zhang.
Meijuan, accompany him well.
It hurts.
Who told you to stop?
Keep singing and dancing.
Drink.
It's a waste of this good wine
if I drink it alone.
Okay, I can accompany you.
Do you know how to play dice?
Yes, but I'm not good at it.
I always lose.
It's okay.
I can teach you.
Drink if you lose.
You'll get better after losing more.
But my alcohol tolerance is low too.
You get alcohol tolerance with practice.
Come on.
Open.
You're just pretending to be bad.
Impressive.
You can't cheat with the alcohol.
Mr. Zhang,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
I need to use the bathroom.
Go away.
Get me some water.
Mr. Qian.
You haven't gone home yet?
Mr. Qian, I helped my friend do something.
It's almost New Year's Eve. Robbers are everywhere.
Don't wander around at night.
Yes.
Mr. Qian, you go on ahead.
I'll go home now.
I'll take you to the tram station.
No need, Mr. Qian.
Get in.
Yes.
I've always wanted to work with you.
I never had a chance.
All these years,
you haven't changed at all.
This time,
we can finally work together.
It's so lively
when women are together.
Thank you for your exaltation.
They can
talk about movies, beauty, and fashion
for days without stop.
Cishu is just too happy
after seeing Mrs. Yu.
Come.
Here.
Have one.
No thanks, Mr. Yu.
I quit.
It's good to quit.
It's good for your health.
Yes.
I just can't quit.
Listen, people who can quit smoking
all have wills of steel.
It seems
that I have no strengths other than my will.
You're too modest.
I'll get straight to the point, since there are no outsiders here.
You've made
quite a ruckus recently.
I've been worried for you.
Worried about what?
I should say
that you have good intentions.
As a Chinese,
I agree with you deep down.
But have you thought about it?
The government in Nanjing gave you your power.
Can you guarantee that everyone in Nanjing is united?
Mr. Yu,
what advice do you have?
It's not advice.
I
just want to help you with a business deal.
The Commercial Association of Suzhou and Shanghai
needs a capable director.
I've thought about it for a long time.
I trust you the most.
If you don't mind,
I'm willing to transfer all my shares in Xinya Department Store
to you.
I can't accept undeserved rewards.
What? Is it not enough?
If so,
I can give the shares of Zhabei Cotton Mill—
You can give me all your assets,
but I can't accept them.
No.
It's that
I don't dare to accept them.
I know.
You're just worried
that Mr. Song will find out.
You know
Mr. Song's temper.
If he finds out
that I accepted your benefits,
he will view this as my betrayal.
With his power,
I'm afraid it won't just be me.
It'll also be disadvantageous
towards you
and the Commercial Association of Suzhou and Shanghai.
Don't worry about Mr. Song.
I'll take care of him.
It's still up to you if you come or not.
This is how big the reward is.
I've put it on the table now.
If you don't come,
someone else will come to take it.
Mr. Yu, how about this?
Let me think about it.
No hurry.
I’ll wait for your good news.
Mr. Yu.
Okay.
Why are you here?
Madam Liang called me,
saying you were bullied.
Fortunately, the headquarters is close enough.
Do I look like someone who gets bullied?
If I can't even handle this kind of person,
I might as well quit and be a housewife.
But Zhang Mingquan
is not easy to deal with.
He's rich
and smart.
Is he generous to women?
What's wrong?
Are you jealous?
I wasn't going to do anything.
If you offend others, I can deal with them,
but Zhang Mingquan has Mr. Yu behind him.
You can't offend him.
Can't I play with him?
You'd best not.
Where is he?
What are you doing?
Showing him who you belong to.
If you have a conflict with him later,
I can explain it to the higher-ups
that I warned him before.
Why can't this door open?
Open the door!
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
What are you doing in the ladies' room?
The Investigation and Arrest Unit is investigating on a case.
What kind of case
needs you in the ladies' room?
What are you two doing?
I'll arrest you if you keep talking.
Who do you think you are?
Arrest me!
There's no one in Shanghai that I'm scared of.
Meijuan,
how many times have I told you?
Stay away from this man.
He doesn't have money.
He doesn't have money, you know?
What are you doing?
Someone is inside.
The door is locked. There must be someone inside.
What is this?
My service fee?
Stop drinking your cheap liquor.
It's going to mess up your brain.
Where did you get the money to buy wine?
Do you want it or not?
He can't even say something nice.
How was your talk with Yu Shiqing?
It's the same old trick.
He'll use money to open the path first.
I guess he'll find someone to do the dirty work later.
These people are really something.
They've been here for so long.
Can't they change their tactics?
Tactics don't have to be new
as long as they work.
How about you?
I saw Mrs. Yu was around you all night.
What did she say?
The audition is next Tuesday.
She said I'm the best candidate for the female lead
and she'll support me.
The female lead?
If you get famous
and become a superstar,
I'll be on the financial page
and you'll be on the entertainment page all day.
People will see us whenever they read the newspaper.
It'll be so lively.
Is it lively?
Yes.
Cishu.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I acted on my own
and caused a lot of trouble for our family,
especially for you.
You're always worried
and you don't dare to go out alone.
I'm sorry.
Do you think
I married you
because you are rich
or because you're handsome?
I'm quite rich
and kind of handsome too.
The main thing is that I treat you well.
I'm perfect.
Perfect.
Cishu,
let's grit our teeth
and get through this period.
I believe
China
will rise up.
If you believe it, I believe it.
But no matter how busy you are, take care of yourself.
If...
If I get old too soon, you won't want me anymore.
I know.