[English subtitles are available]
Jinzhen's in the city?
Yes, Ruolai too.
They must be looking for Qian Fengshi to buy salt.
Do whatever you need
to get evidence of Qian Fengshi's communist ties.
But before the deal,
don't meddle with them.
What about Shen Jinzhen?
She's my sister
but also a communist.
Pardon me then.
Wait.
Let me remind you.
Jinzhen's great at shaking off pursuers.
Don't worry.
Since they're here for Qian Fengshi,
we just need to keep an eye on him.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello.
Mr. Yan.
Long time no see.
What can I do for you?
Ganzhou's account
this month is atrocious.
It's all because of the new special commissioner.
I've investigated.
His
real name is Shen Tunan.
He's sent by Chiang from Nanjing.
He blocked Sanjiang Kou.
We can't get our goods out.
We have no choice.
You have one month
to solve the problem,
or you can retire and go back to Jiangmen.
Mr. Yan.
Mr. Yan!
These darn debtors.
I'm not made of money!
Where are you from?
I'm returning from visiting relatives.
We are together.
Go.
The pass code book of Sanjiang Kou's boats
must be with your brother.
If we get it,
we can end the lockdown.
I know.
But my brother is very vigilant.
I've to find the right time to do it.
Okay, be careful.
You too.
We have
something on Qian Fengshi.
I'm afraid he'll get desperate.
Got it.
Boss.
The money's on the table.
Okay. Take care, sir.
Fortune telling.
Get some advice.
Want a reading?
Fortune telling.
Get some advice.
Sir.
Sir, want a reading?
Stop.
Let me read your fortune.
How dare you
swindle people here?
Sir, things mustn't be going well for you lately.
Mr. Liu.
Your forehead, cheekbones, and lifespan
are all red.
What do you mean?
It means
you recently lost money,
a place,
and maybe even met with death threats?
I'll kill you if you keep talking nonsense.
Brother.
Where are you from?
Ruijin.
Sir.
Lin Qiaosong found traces of Ruolai
through an inspection at Qian's area.
What about Jinzhen?
We lost her.
After they separated,
she disappeared.
Got it. Go back to work.
Yes.
Brigade Commander Qian.
I'll make it short.
I'm the negotiator of Chinese Soviet Republic National Bank,
Wei Ruolai.
I'm here to discuss business with you.
Communism suppression is tight now.
Cooperating with you again
will get me killed.
What if it's a dead end?
On the surface,
the fight for control of Sanjiang Kou
appears to be
between you and Shen Tunan,
but it's really between
Chiang Kai-shek and Chen Jitang.
Shen Tunan is doing well now.
But how will you explain
to Chen Jitang?
A communist like you
doesn't have to worry about this.
No matter what,
I am the general of the army.
I have
a lot of your accounts.
For the past few years,
you've been supporting Jiangxi Soviet's construction.
How dare you threaten me?
If I have the accounts,
Shen Tunan has them too.
You're now Chen Jitang's beloved general.
Shen Tunan's wary and can't provoke you.
But if you
can't offer Chen Jitang money,
you'll be useless to him.
By then,
will he still protect you at all costs?
What goods do you want?
Salt.
We have salt.
Brigade Commander.
We have a batch of top-grade salt
from Guangdong.
Unfortunately, we don't have a new pass.
It's at Taojiang Pier.
It can't get in.
So we're going to
send it back.
Deputy Chief Wei.
If you really have a way
to transport salt out of Tunan's hands,
I will
do business with you.
Okay.
You're forthright.
We'll take this batch of salt.
Hello.
Excuse me.
It's time for her medicine.
But she just fell asleep.
Let's wait a while then.
Yu, look.
Let's eat a little.
It's okay.
Then I will
peel your favorite oranges for you, okay?
Then I'm sure
you will eat it.
Aunt?
Is that you?
Aunt.
I missed you so much.
Where have you been?
I couldn't find you.
It's okay.
I'm here to see you.
Okay, be good.
You'll get better.
You will.
Yu.
I'll talk to your mom.
I'll be back soon,
okay?
Aunt.
Don't go.
I'm not leaving.
I'm going to talk to your mom.
I'll be back soon.
Liar.
Once I let go,
you'll run away again.
I promise you
I'll visit you often from now on.
So, promise me
to get better, okay?
Promise.
I'll put you to sleep, okay?
Lie down.
Close your eyes.
Sleep.
Are you here
for a mission?
Can I help?
Yes.
But I don't need it.
Why?
Because it'll hurt my brother.
I'm sorry.
I have no choice.
If
your mission is completed,
what will happen to him?
If Sanjiang Kou can't be sealed,
his capabilities will be questioned.
He might be fired.
Really?
Because of me,
Nanjing
doesn't trust him as before.
And he's a sinner now.
He can't afford this.
I mean,
he'll only
be fired?
According to normal procedures,
he'll be interrogated first.
After he's cleared of communist suspicions,
he'll be expelled from the party
and fired.
His career will be over.
Let me help you.
I said I don't need it.
I'm also
helping myself,
him,
and our family.
Only in this way
will our family
have hope.
Go and trim that side.
Be careful.
Be gentle.
What are you doing?
You too.
Don't fool around all the time.
Be careful.
Look at the flowers.
Thank you.
Pour it properly.
Look.
Pick up the leaves.
Madam, you're back.
Hello, Madam.
Mrs. Zhang.
Call everyone to the kitchen.
Recently, Yu's food
has been getting worse.
Is this the best you can do?
Sorry, Madam.
I'll get everyone to the kitchen now.
Xiaoju!
Everyone, put down your work.
Follow me
to the kitchen now!
The study is there.
I'll take you.
Hello, Sir.
You're back, Sir.
Mrs. Zhang.
Madam is back.
She was so angry.
Why?
She complained about the food,
so we made a few more dishes today.
Where's she now?
I saw her go to the study.
Jinzhen.
It's me.
Sister-in-law.
Your brother's back.
Leave!
It's too late.
Take this.
Take a look.
Ganzhou's too dangerous.
Don't ever come back.
Leave.
Sister-in-law.
Thank you.
Bye.
Go.
Go now.
Why are you back?
I was bored in the hospital.
So I came back to get a book.
But I saw your bookshelf
was too dirty,
so I wanted to wipe it for you.
I said
no one's
allowed in my study.
Me neither?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
What's the use of saying sorry now?
You could have left then,
but you insisted on coming.
I was going to
suggest Kuomintang take over Jiangxi,
so everything can go back on track.
But what I saw
at Jiangxi Soviet this time
was not what I thought.
I heard
Ruijin's doing well
in the Communist Party.
The people live and work in peace,
and prosper.
Jinzhen must've told you this, right?
Come in.
Have a seat.
How was it?
I've got the code book.
Sanjiang Kou's finally unsealed.
Great.
Contact Qian Fengshi
to prepare the salt
and send it back safely.
Okay.
You've been exposed many times in the hospital.
Leave Ganzhou now.
Leave the rest to us.
Okay.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Brigade Commander Qian.
I'll leave the salt to you.
Please hurry.
The ship is ready.
What's the code?
Use other goods to pass customs.
Then switch it with the salt.
After it passes Sanjiang Kou,
in the guise of armed robbery,
we'll get the goods.
Even if Shen Tunan finds out,
you can explain it.
If it can pass,
let's do as we agreed.
Okay.
Thank you.
Same to you.
Come on.
Listen.
Once the goods are sorted out, set sail.
Yes, Sir.
Where are the porters from?
I’ve checked.
They're Su’s.
Those bastards.
They do anything for money.
Once this deal is done,
kill them all.
Understood.
Brothers, retreat!
Do it!
Sir, it's salt.
Special Commissioner, you want to see me?
I heard you had a special operation last night.
Aren't the communists buying salt?
Last night,
we caught Qian Fengshi's ship transporting salt for them
on the spot.
Good.
We also put arsenic in the salt.
In a few days,
the Communist-controlled areas will be in chaos
due to the poisoning,
and we can make a sneak attack.
Lin Qiaosong, how dare you act on your own?
You're evil!
Special Commissioner.
Calm down.
I knew you'd disagree,
so I didn't inform you.
I’ll let Shen Jinzhen go too.
For what?
It doesn't matter.
You can report directly
to Nanjing
if you're against the poisoning.
Let's hear what Nanjing has to say.
I'll leave if there's nothing else.
Goodbye.
Do you like it?
Let's go back and rest
after getting some sun, okay?
Okay.
Yu.
Look who's here.
Mom, I'm scared.
Don't be.
Come on, baby.
That's Dad.
Call Dad.
Dad.
Yu.
Have you learned anything recently?
Tell Dad.
It's "Enlightenment of Vocal Rhythm".
Really?
You've learned "Enlightenment of Vocal Rhythm"?
Can you recite it to me?
Tea versus wine. Ode versus poetry.
Swallows versus warblers.
Planting flowers versus planting bamboo.
Falling catkins versus gossamer.
Zhi Bo is wise and giving,
so his state councilor swallowed burning charcoal for him.
Mr. Yang is virtuous,
so people erected a monument of tears for him.
Yu, you're amazing.
You memorized everything.
Do you know what "Mr. Yang is virtuous" means?
Mr. Yang is Yang Hu,
a virtuous general in ancient times.
Yes.
Do you know what Yang Hu's virtuous act is?
I'm not taught that yet.
Then let me tell you, okay?
Sure.
Let me tell you.
Let's sit on the chair.
Come.
Let me tell you.
Once,
Yang Hu
led an army to Wu State.
When he got to Wu State,
he acted in good faith
for the people and army of Wu.
Their battles were always
arranged
and never a sneak attack.
Once,
Wu generals attacked Yang Hu.
So Yang Hu killed them.
But he also gave them proper funerals
and reciprocated with courtesy.
Because Yang Hu
admired them for their bravery.
Just like how you killed Xiaoyun’s dad?
Something like that.
You're like Yang Hu.
Yang Hu's a good person,
so you're also a good person.
Am I right?
Dad?
Yes.
You're right.
There are things a gentleman should and shouldn't do.
I promise you that no matter what I do,
I'll do my best
and try to be a good person,
so as not to let you down, okay?
Okay.
You're the best.
Congyun.
What's wrong, Sir?
You're like Yang Hu.
Yang Hu's a good person,
so you're also a good person.
Pass my order.
Contact the Communist Party with plain code.
Yes, Sir.
What should I tell them?
The salt is poisoned.
Sir.
Lin Qiaosong's been planning this for a long time.
Is it appropriate?
Why not?
We want to impose an economic blockade
on the Communist Party,
not to poison the people.
There are things a gentleman
should and shouldn't do.
But you're suspected of colluding with communists.
I know you're worried about me.
But it's fine.
I'm upright.
I'm not afraid.
Also,
don't let Lin Qiaosong find out.
Get it done as soon as possible.
Yes, Sir.
This is a plain-code telegram from Shen Tunan,
saying the salt that's transported back
is mixed with arsenic.
He advised us not to eat it.
What do you think?
Chief Lei.
I think it's fake
and he's trying to scare us,
so we dare not
eat the salt we risked our lives
to bring back.
He's too cunning.
It's possible indeed.
But from what I know about him,
I don't think he's lying.
But
our people were involved throughout the process
from Guangdong Army
to the salt warehouse.
It couldn't have been poisoned.
It could've been poisoned beforehand.
Impossible!
Qian Fengshi's greedy for money.
If he sold us poisonous salt,
we'd stop doing business with him,
and he'd have to deal with us getting revenge.
The salt concerns
the people's safety.
Seal the salt first.
You have three days
to find out if it's poisoned.
Yes.
Ruolai, how is it?
Did you find anything?
The salt bags were sealed well
to prevent moisture.
But some salt bags
have surface damages of about 7 mm long.
This isn't right.
How about this?
Check the salt from the damaged bags
for me.
Okay.
I'll go now.
Ming Da, I'm loyal to Kuomintang.
We're against communists,
not the general public.
We shouldn't poison
the salt.
The people
in Jiangxi Soviet will just
hate us more
and we'll lose more trust.
Tunan, your previous arrest had already
aroused much suspicion about your loyalty.
They might
use this to create a narrative.
So,
you must be wary,
especially of Qian Fengshi.
Don't worry.
I have a plan for him.
If he's colluding with communists, even Commander Chen can't save him.
Sir.
Fortunately, Nanjing didn't pursue this matter.
You sent the telegram to Jiangxi Soviet?
It's me.
You're especially concerned about the communists
after coming back from Jiangxi Soviet.
They aren't communists.
They're innocent people.
I don't want to poison the salt
and kill innocent people.
I don't want to be evil.
Am I wrong?
Communist Party members are not innocent!
They're Kuomintang's enemies.
Special Commissioner.
You can't be sympathetic.
There's no world without bloodshed.
Don't forget
they once wanted to kill you.
Lin Qiaosong.
I'm warning you.
You're here to cooperate with me.
If you keep acting on your own,
our cooperation is over.
I'm warning you too.
My loyalty to Kuomintang
comes before everything else!
Ignorant.
Say that again.
I said you're ignorant.
You don't understand Mr. Shen's ambition.
I can shoot you anytime.
Are you done?
Just you wait.
Think about how to deal with Qian Fengshi
with that energy instead!
We found
five bags of poisoned salt on that ship.
They used
cone-shaped objects to poke a small hole
to add the arsenic.
The purity of the arsenic is high.
They are crystals,
not the usual minerals
available at Chinese medicine shops.
It's a highly-concentrated
compound purified in the lab.
A total of about 5 to 700 grams.
That much arsenic
would've killed many people!
Those bastards.
Around the holes,
we also found
high concentrations of phosphoric acid,
commonly known as gun oil.
The holes must've been made with bayonets,
which are maintained with gun oil.
Can you separate out
the poisoned salt?
Yes.
The lab is still checking.
It'll take a week.
We can give it out then.
That's great.
Never
buy salt from Guangdong Army again.
We were lucky to be warned this time.
We might be tricked next time.
But I don't understand why
Qian Fengshi did that.
It was discovered in time
and no harm was caused.
We'll look into
the poisonous salt later.
A Mexican dollar machine
is about
to arrive.
Through a water route, the transportation line comrades
have transported it from Shanghai to Yudu.
That's great.
Both southern Jiangxi and Guangzhou acknowledge Mexican dollars.
We can make them ourselves with the machine.
We can trade directly in Kuomintang-controlled areas.
It's much more convenient.
Yes.
It's all thanks to our comrades in Shanghai.
Such an important machine
must be transported back to the money factory as soon as possible
so the enemy can't wreak havoc.
I'll go then.
I'll protect it
with my life.
Get Chunmiao too.
She's in Yudu.
She can come back with you.
Stop!
Stop running!
Did you take care of everyone else?
Yes.
Sir.
We've taken care of them.
Brigade Commander.
Everyone involved has been eliminated.
We'll stop selling salt
to the communists.
Shen Tunan's trying to mess with me.
Bring it on.
He'll die in my hands.
Brigade Commander Qian.
What a coincidence
to meet you here.
Captain Lin.
Working
at this late hour?
This is...
Captain Lin.
I just met a few communists and killed them on the spot.
It doesn't matter.
Brigade Commander Qian.
I'm officially arresting you
for communist ties.
Lin Qiaosong.
Get it straight.
This is Ganzhou.
Messing with me when I have countless men backing me?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Are you trying to
resist arrest?
Stop labelling me.
Show me the evidence,
or get lost
right now!
You used Su's Porters to send salt to communists.
It was even in batches.
Su’s has 70 to 80 porters.
Could you have
killed them all?
Captain Lin.
Your words are too cryptic.
Now,
it's getting late.
I have work to do.
If there’s nothing else,
goodbye.
Thank you, guys.
Those bastards.
How dare he arrest me
when he couldn't stop cars?
Now it's up to Shen Tunan.
Brothers of the Guangdong Army,
you've been fighting wars all year round.
This money
is to reward you.
How could a special commissioner
get so much money?
To be honest,
the money
is not mine.
It belongs to Brigade Commander Qian.
He's in Ganzhou
earning dirty money
by intercepting your military pay.
Just in
the past six months,
he withheld three months of your pay.
I really want to know
if he's poor
or evil!
Not only did he
do something so despicable for money,
but he also colluded with communists to smuggle tungsten ore.
I've reported all his crimes
to the Suppression Headquarters.
Soon,
he'll be put to trial.
In less than half a month,
the Guangdong Army will send other officials
to take over his work.
If any of you
are not convinced,
stand out now
and I'll convince you.
Okay.
Line up.
Take your money!
Yes!
Yangchun noodles and wontons!
No appetite?
Yeah.
I've been busy lately.
I can't sleep or eat well.
How about you catch up on sleep
and get some Chinese medicine?
It's okay.
I can push through.
I've been looking for you.
So you're here.
How is it?
Is the Mexican dollar machine here?
Yes,
but one of the bearings is faulty.
Faulty bearings?
Maybe it got damaged during the transport.
It's our responsibility.
Can you fix the bearing?
I'm not sure. It depends on the model.
I'll try with other tools too.
Let's go.
Okay.
Wait.
Eat first.
I'll eat after it's fixed.
Let's go.
How is it?
Change it.
It's fixed.
Great.
This machine
is so important to us.
In this way,
we can make the Mexican dollars ourselves.
It'll be convenient for us in Kuomintang-controlled areas.
Now that it's fixed,
I'm suddenly hungry.
Make me something delicious.
Sure. Come on.
I'll make you some noodles.
Add more chili!
Song Shoutian!
Don't move!
To think it's you.
I'm here to help!
Help with what?
To avoid misunderstandings,
I set up a trap in the bearing
on purpose.
As long as it's forced damage,
the engine oil will spray out onto you.
Anything else to say?
Did you blow up the mine too?
Speak up!
Is your boss
Lin Qiaosong?
Nonsense!
Don't slander revolutionary comrades like this!
When you blew up the mine in Pangu Mountain,
we found the residuals of explosives at the entrance.
It was picric acid ammunition,
the filler for artillery shells.
It's powerful but unstable.
Jinling Arsenal once exported it,
But it was eliminated soon.
When Lin Qiaosong was in Shanghai's Dare-to-Die Corps,
he used it often.
He's the only user in China now.
Why did you
betray the revolution?
To save my sister.
Kong.
My sister is my only family
in this world.
Have you ever thought
if your identity is exposed,
your sister will be doomed?
I know.
Lin Qiaosong won't let her go.
You still have a chance.
As long as you don't expose yourself,
you still have a chance to save your sister.
You want me to
keep in touch with Lin Qiaosong?
If you cooperate,
you'd be earning merits.
You can only live
if Lin Qiaosong dies.
Brother!
What's wrong?
I couldn't find water.
Something's up ahead.
Hide.
Hurry!
What happened?
I saw Niu Chunmiao
leading a team.
Everyone, work harder.
When we get to the Yunmen Ridge,
we'll get a good rest.
Okay.
Be alert.
What are they transporting?
I don't know.
Be on guard.
Biao, come with me.
Yes.
Yunmen Ridge?
It's really top-grade tungsten ore.
Where's the map?