[English subtitles are available]
[War of Faith]
[Episode 28]
Sir.
I don't know
when you retrieved the transaction list
because last night,
the archive where the list was stored
was already burned down by Yu Zhiying.
The one I have here
was saved from the fire.
The culprit is not
some Japanese speculator.
It's the wife of a high-ranking Treasury Department official.
She is the biggest market maker.
There's also Yu Shiqing,
Kang Shaojie,
Zhang Mingquan,
and Huang Daowu.
They worked together
to maliciously act as the opponents of the Central Bank
and earned up to 15 million silver coins.
These are all the transaction lists and records.
The evidence is all here.
These are rumors.
Sir.
We already have solid evidence.
If we expose this report to the public,
the public will believe us.
Ruolai, what exactly do you want?
I just think it's unfair. I want justice.
Justice?
I'll give you justice after this passes.
It's chaotic enough now.
If you insist on acting alone,
the country will be the one that's harmed.
Do you understand this?
No
and I don't want to either.
You're trying to cover up a blatant mistake
to help the tyrants, sir.
I told you before
that politics
is the art of compromise.
I don't want to compromise.
They must be punished for their evil deeds.
Even if I have to risk my life,
I will fight them to the death.
Wei Ruolai,
if you insist on your own way,
don't blame me for being cruel.
From now on,
I am no longer your mentor.
Our ties
are severed.
Putting all the blame
on a Japanese speculator?
How could they think of that?
The people are the most united right now
and yet, they did this.
Chiang must be crazy for money.
A tyrannical warlord
needs money and guns.
To them, the lives of the people
are just pawns
that can be sacrifice at any time.
The most important thing now
is to send Wei Ruolai's investigation report
to the major newspapers.
I'll do it.
There are many leftist newspapers in Shanghai.
They will cooperate.
This time, we must show the people
Chiang and the Nanjing government's true natures.
Xu,
I don't dare to publish this.
Don't worry.
These records are definitely real.
The background information has been thoroughly investigated
and verified.
The people of Shanghai are suffering because of the treasury bills.
Countless families have been destroyed.
I can publish it,
but I'm afraid it'll infuriate Nanjing.
They'll shut down
the newspaper agency and even arrest journalists.
Can it be printed privately
and distributed to the public with the newspaper's circulation channels?
Xu,
this won't have enough credibility.
A privately printed paper would look like a rumor.
No one would believe it.
Is there any easier or faster way
to let the people know what Nanjing has done?
There is,
but you might take some risks.
[Hong Fang Clothing Shop]
Wei?
Why are you here?
Do you need more clothes?
Sort of.
Can we talk privately?
Come in.
Mr. Xu,
I want to ask you
to do me a favor.
No need to be so formal.
What can I do for you?
I want you to help me find a media outlet
to publish a report.
The Nanjing government and rich merchants of Shanghai
worked together to manipulate the treasury bills.
They screwed over the banks and the people,
earning 15 million silver coins.
I'm just a tailor,
not a reporter.
I remember your voice.
That night, you asked from behind me
to give the seal to Li Shengda.
You lowered your voice,
but I could still tell it's you.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Mr. Xu,
only the Communist Party can help me.
Mr. Wei,
you really got the wrong person.
Miss Shen said
she can publish the report on the newspaper.
Then why don't you go to her?
Because her identity is too special.
I can only come to you.
You are the only communist
that I know.
I'm not.
How many times have I told you?
Are you deaf?
So you're afraid, right?
Fine.
I'll figure it out myself.
I don't believe that among all the media outlets in Shanghai,
not one dares to stand up for the people.
Don't be impulsive.
This matter
is too complicated.
It's beyond the ability of a newspaper agency.
Then I'll go on the street and write a poster.
Then you will be arrested immediately
and this time,
no one can rescue you.
I know you're not afraid of death,
but even if you get killed,
you still won't be able to spread the news.
Do you think your death will be worth it?
I found a newspaper agency earlier.
The editor-in-chief didn't dare to publish it,
but he gave me an idea.
What idea?
The law doesn't punish the public.
If one newspaper agency
publishes it,
they'll be shut down.
But if everyone publishes it,
the Nanjing government won't be able to shut everyone down.
Let's hold a press conference first.
We must have hundreds of media agencies
get the news on the spot.
What if
they still won't publish it?
They will.
Reporters have their dignity.
They may be cowardly in private,
but if they continue to play dumb
about such a big news
in front of their peers,
how will they be able to work in the future?
[New Dance Hall]
[Hong Fang Clothing Shop]
How did he know?
He's always known.
He just never said.
He heard my voice before.
He's really good at hiding.
He's very angry.
He saw clearly the darkness and corruption
of the Kuomintang.
This country must change.
So...
I want him to join the next step of the operation.
No.
He's not a party member yet.
I told him
we'll hold a press conference,
but we fear
the news will be leaked
and the Investigation and Arrest Unit will cause trouble.
He thought about it for three minutes
and drafted a plan.
[Hong Fang Clothing Shop]
How did he come up with such a plan?
I was surprised too.
This kid
was born to be a revolutionist.
Ruolai,
are you done?
What are you printing?
At twelve o'clock on Thursday,
the construction treasury bill's dark truth
will be announced at the intersection
outside Great Star Theater.
All are welcome.
Ruolai,
if you do this,
you will be arrested.
If it benefits the country, I can risk my life.
How can I go toward fortune and avoid misfortune?
I used to think the national affairs
had nothing to do with us commoners.
But now, I feel that
if I don't do anything,
I'll feel guilty towards my conscience
and the friends and family who were affected.
Chief Editor Huang,
Your letter.
[309 Hankou Road, Shandong Middle Road]
[To Mr. Huang Yijun of Shen Bao Newspaper]
Thank you.
[Lin Qiaosong was reinstated and returned to the Investigation and Arrest Unit due to his contributions in the battle against Japan]
Who sent you this letter?
A reporter this morning.
It's one of my drinking buddies.
He felt that the letter was problematic,
so he told me immediately.
He also asked about it.
Many reporters have received it.
Many reporters?
Have you found out who sent the letter?
It's not written,
but the postmark is from Zhabei.
[No. 442, Route Lafayette, Shanghai]
[To the editorial department of the Life Post]
I've sent someone to check.
Twelve at noon on Thursday.
They're so high profile.
Aren't they scared of getting caught by us?
I guess
they invited many reporters,
so they think we won't dare to arrest them.
Yes.
There'll be many reporters there.
If we arrest them on the spot,
it will make us seem guilty.
Sir,
if it's not convenient to act in public,
I'll go to the Axe Gang.
We'll just say that the people wouldn't pay their debts,
so the Axe Gang attacked them.
Then we'll handle the case as malicious public security,
go through the motions, and release them in a few days.
You've improved.
Let’s do it.
Find Qian Shaoliang directly.
Have him to send more men.
The money
will be paid by the Garrison Command.
Yes.
[Wen Youtian's Tomb]
Did Wen send you a message in your dream?
I dreamed of him last night.
He asked me to apologize to you.
He said he borrowed a pair of leather shoes from you.
He wanted to wear them for a few days before returning them,
but the sole fell off
and he didn't have time to fix it.
He told you to buy a new pair.
He'll find a chance to pay it back in his next life.
Wen was my best friend.
I wanted to rent a nice house in Huangpu
after making money
and have him live with me there.
There are many rich people there.
He'll make good money pulling the rickshaw.
It's a pity.
Wen,
I will avenge you and Ms. Zhou.
If I don't,
I will never be at ease.
[Great Star Theater]
Didn't they say it'll start at twelve?
Why is there no one here?
There are three minutes left.
Be patient.
Even if there is a big news, do you dare to expose it?
I will if you will.
I was the one who exposed
Mr. Du's relationship scandal.
I'm just scared it's Nanjing.
The effect is too horrible this time.
This news will shake the morale of the army.
Boss, who are we axing later?
Axe whoever speaks publicly.
Remember,
don't kill anyone. Just chop their limbs.
Just make sure he can't talk,
understand?
Yes.
Dear reporters,
welcome to the press conference
about the construction treasury bill's dark truth.
Today,
we will tell you everything
about the construction treasury bill.
As you all know,
the Central Bank was entrusted by the Treasury Department
to host the distribution of the construction treasury bills earlier.
The total amount was eight million silver coins.
Its intention was to
raise funds to develop industries
and revive Shanghai.
This action should've benefited the country and the people,
but it was used by people with ulterior motives
to make profits.
He won't be able to escape.
Search along the cable.
Yes.
How did you know they would search there?
Thinking habits.
There are many obvious cables under the speaker.
Normal people would think
that those cables are connected to the microphone,
so they'll be able to catch the speaker by following the cable.
Who would think to look for
the cables hidden underground?
I found it. It's here.
He just left.
I'll go up and you two go down.
Don't let them escape.
Yes.
Balloon?
What is this balloon?
Why is there a box on the balloon?
What is this?
Is that a balloon?
Look.
What is this?
What is it?
Yes.
Tell the Axe Gang to get ready.
If anything happens, just attack.
Okay.
It's falling.
Don't read it.
Don't read it!
Guys, go!
Why didn't you distribute the leaflets directly?
Isn't the speaker unnecessary?
There are only reporters,
the Investigation and Arrest Unit and gangsters on this road.
If I only distributed leaflets,
the reporters could be bribed and threatened.
They could keep playing dumb back at the newspaper agency.
But if I use the speaker,
the residents nearby can hear it.
It'll become a public incident.
If the reporters don't publish it,
they will be looked down on by their peers
and doubted by the public.
As long as half of the media outlets publish this,
it'll be a success.
I'll be happy to have two or three media outlets.
Don't worry.
There are many responsible reporters these days.
Be confident.
I hope so.
[Shen Bao Newspaper]
[Truth News]
The construction treasury bill has become a scam,
ravaging the people
to benefit the rich.
[Financial disaster was man-made]
The financial calamity ruined the country. It's unforgivable.
What are these
government officials?
[Wife of Treasury Department Official, Zhang Mingquan, Yu Shiqing, and Kang Shaojie are the Masterminds Behind the Construction Treasury Bill]
Twenty-seven newspaper agencies
reported extensively on it.
Most of them are headlines.
This battle was well-fought.
I didn't expect
that Wei Ruolai really has some skills.
If it weren't for him,
we wouldn't have gotten such a good result.
I wanted to help him,
but I didn't even get the chance to do anything.
You and Ruolai are both actionists.
You can see
his potential from this mission.
Yes.
He made such a
detailed and meticulous plan
without special training.
You and Ruolai
have different personalities
and different abilities,
so
your future paths will be different too.
In the future,
You still plan on using him?
Jiangxi Soviet needs him.
He'll make greater contributions for the party
in the financial system.
I really want to see
how he'll look when reciting the oath under the party flag.
Doggie,
we've taken revenge.
Let's go home.
It's still early.
This is just the beginning.
The newspapers have published it already.
What else do you want?
The mastermind is still at large.
They haven't been punished yet.
I think they will.
The newspaper has already published it
and the people are very angry now.
They will organize marches.
Marches?
Will that work?
[Construction Treasury Bill, Financial Calamity Ruins the Country, Punish the Traitors, Give Us Justice]
Financial calamity ruins the country.
The leaders are corrupted.
Punish the traitors.
[A heinous crime]
Give us justice.
[Maintain financial stability]
Financial calamity ruins the country.
The leaders are corrupted.
[A heinous crime] [Maintain financial stability]
Punish the traitors.
Give us justice.
Financial calamity ruins the country.
The leaders are corrupted.
Punish the traitors.
Give us justice.
Financial calamity ruins the country.
The leaders are corrupted.
Punish the traitors.
How is it, Mr. Yu?
The police station is enough
to deal with the mob.
Why are you here too?
I'm here under Mr. Kang's orders
to assist you.
We're friends. It's fine.
Besides, Mr. Lin,
you are brave and resourceful.
Since you're here,
would you like to say something?
Come on.
Okay.
Financial calamity ruins the country.
The leaders are corrupted.
Punish the traitors.
Give us justice.
Financial calamity ruins the country.
Everyone,
let me give you a piece of advice.
You are marching illegally.
If you
take another step forward,
we will kill without mercy.
Punish the traitors.
Give us justice.
Students, don't be afraid.
Punish the traitors.
Give us justice.
There are really people who are not afraid of death.
Fine.
I'll grant your wish.
Captain Lin,
let's do it.
Everyone,
get ready.
Give us justice.
Punish the traitors.
The march was cruelly suppressed.
It means they are scared.
We need to continue
spreading this report to more media outlets
and getting more people to fight together.
Stop!
Shut down any newspaper agency
that reports on the treasury bills.
You lowly lackey,
shut us down!
Shanghai has more than 100 newspaper agencies
and three million people.
You can't shut everyone down.
Shut up,
or else I'll kill you.
The truth can't be sealed.
Burn it!
Kang Shaojie,
your Investigation and Arrest Unit is useless.
Do you want to keep your job or not?
Mr. Yu,
we have closed down more than ten newspaper agencies,
but
we don't have enough manpower.
There are more than 100 newspaper agencies like this in Shanghai.
Big Sister is very angry now.
How can there be
so many leftist newspapers in Shanghai?
They're communist sympathizers too.
Isn't this self-destructive behavior?
Mr. Yu, don’t worry.
All communist-sympathizing newspaper will be shut down
and all the newspapers taken back
and destroyed.
The transaction list is critical.
Who leaked it?
We must find out.
No matter who it is, if you find him,
shoot him.
Yes.
You're back.
-Mr. Xu, why are you here?
-Who are you?
A friend.
I said he's a friend.
Did you not hear me?
Go.
I'm sorry.
Did you write this?
[Report on the Communist Region's Farmers Banks, Wei Ruolai]
Yes.
What do you think about the future of Jiangxi Soviet?
I...
It's fine.
You can say whatever you want.
After the press conference ordeal,
we are friends now.
I must thank you
about the press conference.
Well,
I don't know much about politics,
but economically,
the Communist Party
is more stable than I thought.
Really?
Take this report for example.
The vast majority of the people in China
are farmers.
The Communist Party
established farmers banks at their base.
They quickly raised
the support and credit of the local farmers.
Credit is the foundation of banks,
while the foundation of credit is people's support.
Although these banks are not big now,
as they keep growing,
the financial war between the two parties
will intensify.
But agricultural value can't compare to industrial and commercial value.
But you have the tungsten ore mines.
That's hard currency.
Jiangxi is rich in resources
and the water and land transportation is very advanced too.
In the long-term, it's suitable for industry and commerce.
It can be said that you chose
a very good base.
Are you interested
in working in Jiangxi Soviet?
I...
After the press conference,
the Investigation and Arrest Unit was held accountable.
They'll definitely look to the Central Bank
for the leak of the transaction list.
Shen Tunan
might not protect you
due to political pressure.
He won't.
Mr. Shen and I
are no longer mentor and mentee.
Shanghai is no longer safe for you.
Jiangxi Soviet
is your future.
After the counterfeit coins and the construction treasury bill incidents,
I believe
you've seen
the darkness and corruption of the Kuomintang.
Working under such a political power
is akin to aiding the monster.
The Kuomintang is indeed bad.
But...
I don't know much about your party either,
so I can't make a decision now.
It's okay.
I'll give you time.
Whether you return to Jiangxi or not,
you can't stay in Shanghai anymore.
You have to leave as soon as possible.
Tomorrow,
I want to give this report to Mr. Shen
as my last farewell.
Can you
do me a favor?
What is it?
Make us seem weaker
as if we'll go bankrupt anytime.
For them to underestimate you?
Is that okay?
The revised report
will buy us more time to develop.
After all, we just started.
Please give us a chance
and give your hometown a chance too.
Thank you.
I'll arrange for the special line to send you away as soon as possible.
I sincerely hope
that we'll still have the chance
to fight together in the future.
How's the report I mentioned yesterday?
It's done.
Give it to Wang Shanbin
to bring to my office.
Okay, no problem.
Why are you back?
Secretary Huang.
This is
the report that Mr. Shen asked me to write.
I've completed it.
Please give it to him for me.
You're no longer an employee of the Central Bank.
From now on,
you will no longer be welcomed in the Central Bank either.
Please leave immediately.
Sir.
You can't enter the Central Bank if you're not an employee.
Which rule says that?
What is it?
Report on the workers and farmers banks in the communist region.
Detailed evidence.
What's the conclusion?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Of course.
They're just a group of people who can't afford to eat
and can't read.
Where do they get the guts to run a bank like us?
Exactly.
The Communist Party being weak
doesn't mean the Kuomintang is strong.
Wei Ruolai,
enough.
Let him talk.
Sir,
I don't know much about the Communist Party.
I don't know what step
their financial situation will reach,
but I'm sure they won't harm the people.
They won't hold back the people who genuinely want to work
and they won't turn the people into enemies
for their family's benefit
and their personal hunger for power.
So?
Are you joining the Communist Party?
No,
but even more, I won't join the Kuomintang.
Even if you wanted to join,
who would want you?
Secretary Huang,
I saw many bloodstains
on my way here.
They said that the people who marched
to protest against the manipulation of the treasury bills
were violently suppressed by the police.
Don't you feel any guilt
when the police do this?
Sir,
you've changed.
In the past,
-you wouldn’t let us suppress marches.
-I would.
They are not ordinary people.
At least, the people leading the chants are not.
They're an organized group
of thugs
with a plan to create turmoil for society.
Really?
They must be!
Otherwise, your guilt
will defeat you sooner or later.
Ruolai,
I know you feel wronged.
I'm just like you,
but unlike you, I care for the big picture.
Yes, sir.
You endure humiliation
to negotiate with the predator.
How dare you mock Mr. Shen like this?
Who do you think you are?
If it weren't for Mr. Shen,
you would be a ruffian on the street.
Congyun.
Let him go.
There's a fire in your heart.
Don't let the fire go out
and don't turn into the kind of person you hate the most.
Move.
Get out of the Investigation and Arrest Unit's way.
Mr. Shen,
we need your cooperation in a case.
This way, please.
Captain Lin,
am I a suspect
or an informant?
Is there any difference?
Yes.
If I'm a suspect, then you need
a warrant to arrest me.
If you don't
and just want me to cooperate with the investigation,
you should ask my secretary
if I have time
and if it's convenient.
Is it convenient for you now?
No.
I'm busy recently.
I have no time to cooperate with the investigation.
I'll save time and ask here.
Go ahead.
You were the one who conducted the investigation on the construction treasury bill.
Yes.
The investigation results have been released, right?
All the losses
from the treasury bills were caused by a Japanese speculator.
As for what the newspapers said
about it being related
to the Kong family or Yu Shiqing,
that's their theory.
What does it have to do with me?
How did the transaction list get leaked?
Ask the stock exchange.
This is the Central Bank.
Looks like we're unable to communicate.
Mr. Shen,
I'm sorry.
I have an order from the Garrison Command
to bring relevant personnel back for investigation.
Go!
The Investigation and Arrest Unit is working.
Anyone who gets in the way will die.
Captain Lin,
I did all this.
It has nothing to do with Mr. Shen.
You've already resigned.
This is none of your business.
I also got the transaction list from the stock exchange.
I asked him to get it.
He was just the messenger.
I'll take full responsibility.
You two can come together.
Let's go.
Lin Qiaosong!
I did this.
I gave the transaction list
to Mr. Shen at the Central Bank's meeting,
but he didn't use it.
I also handed out the record.
It has nothing to do with Mr. Shen.
Wei Ruolai!
I was the one who did it!
Sir,
I'm not your student anymore.
I will never forget
all of your kindness.
Please take care.
Sir, are you alright?
Sir.
Are you okay, sir?
I'm fine.
Everyone, disperse.
Go back to work.
Wei Ruolai, no one can save you this time.
When you get to the execution ground,
I'll kill you myself.
Sir.
Sir, where are you going?
The Yu Residence.
[Shanghai Arsenal of the Military Administration Department]
Miss Shen.
Chunmiao?
What's wrong?
Doggie was taken by the Investigation and Arrest Unit.
When did that happen?
Just now.
It was led by Lin Qiaosong.
Calm down. Take your time.
What is this?
This is all the money I have.
Your brother is a big official.
Ask him to find a way to save him.
If the money isn't enough, please cover for me
and I'll pay you back later.
It's not about money.
Let me ask you first.
When they left,
which way did they drive in?
I don't know.
I'm not familiar with Shanghai.
When they left,
did they turn right or left?
Left.
Are you sure?
Oh no.
Left...
That means they went straight to the execution ground.
You can't go in. You can't go in.
What are you doing?
I'm Shen Tunan from the Central Bank.
I have something urgent to ask Mr. Yu.
You can’t go in.
-Mr. Yu.
-Master.
You may leave.
Mr. Yu.
Advisor Shen,
what brings you here today?
Have a seat.
No need.
Mr. Yu, I'll make it short.
Lin Qiaosong
came to the Central Bank
and arrested my assistant Wei Ruolai.
You should ask Mr. Kang about these things.
Why are you here?
What does it have to do with me?
He was arrested for leaking the transaction list.
He's in trouble.
No one can help you about this.
He's going to be executed.
It's non-negotiable.
I know.
So I’m here today
to ask you, Mr. Yu.
Please talk to Big Sister.
It's really hard for me to help.
Shanghai has been a mess these days.
Big Sister hasn't slept well for days.
Please call Big Sister
and ask her.
I will
definitely repay this favor.
Don’t worry. Take a seat.
It's very urgent.
Please, Mr. Yu.
This matter
really puts me in a difficult position.
How about this?
Wait for me.
Sir,
you're negotiating with the predator.
It's a matter of life and death.
I'll do anything
to save Wei Ruolai.
If he dies, it's his own fault.
How is it, Mr. Yu?
Tunan,
I just asked.
Big Sister
is still angry.
However,
she also said
she's willing to make more friends.
Advisor Shen,
do you understand what I mean?
Yes.
If Big Sister needs me in the future,
just let me know.
Sir.
Shut up.
I accept this friendship.
That kid
will never be able to repay this favor.
Hello?
Did you arrest Wei Ruolai?
I sent Lin Qiaosong to the Central Bank
to arrest Shen Tunan.
Arresting Wei Ruolai was a misunderstanding.
I've asked Big Sister already.
Release him now.
Please wait a moment. I’ll ask.
Mr. Yu,
there's indeed such a thing.
Wei Ruolai pleaded guilty on the spot
and was taken directly to the execution ground.
What?
Listen.
Inform them immediately.
Do not execute him.
Do you hear me?
Thanks, Mr. Yu.
I’m afraid it’s too late.
How about this?
I'll send someone over.
But...