It is the 1950s,
following the devastating Korean War.
Female gukgeuk, or traditional theater,
captures the heart of the public,
and many girls dream of becoming princes.
Playing the role of Yoon Jeongnyeon,
a pansori genius
who dives into the world of stars,
is Kim Taeri.
Playing the role of Heo Youngseo,
an elite trainee skilled at singing,
dancing, and even acting,
is Shin Yeeun.
Playing the role of Moon Okgyeong,
the undisputed Prince of Maeran,
is Jung Eunchae.
Playing the role of Seo Hyerang,
the beautiful flower of Maeran,
is Kim Yoonhye.
And last but not least
is the director of all the girls
who dream of becoming princes,
Kang Sobok played by Ra Miran.
We want to thank you for your patience
as we proudly present
the story of Jeongnyeon!
"Jeongnyeon: The Star Is Born"
"Narrator: Cho Yeongsuk
First-generation female gukgeuk actor"
All characters, places, organizations,
and events in this show are fictional.
The show contains Japanese expressions
to reflect the time period.
Act 8
♪ To reach excellence in singing ♪
♪ One needs to discern the five sounds ♪
♪ And transform the six rules ♪
♪ To cajole one's innards ♪
♪ And sing from within ♪
♪ It is difficult indeed ♪
- ♪ To have excellence in… ♪
- Stop.
There are still a lot of you
who aren't singing from your core
but from your throat.
You, Park Chorok.
I can see you're out of breath
even from here.
How are you ever going to reach
the audience way at the back?
The play for this joint performance
is notorious for its difficult songs.
Whether you make it or not
will come down to your singing.
Keep in mind what I've taught you
and make sure to practice consistently.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's pick up where we left off.
Are you going to audition
for the joint performance?
No.
Ondal's songs are too difficult for me.
They're way too high,
and you need to use aewonseong expertly.
They're not something a trainee can sing.
The only trainees
who have a chance at playing Ondal…
would be Jeongnyeon or Youngseo.
The rest of us
would only make a fool of ourselves.
Hong Jooran!
You haven't…
already decided to audition
with Jeongnyeon, have you?
Not yet.
Then give me a chance.
I'd like you to be my partner.
Uh…
But there must be a lot of people
wanting to audition with you.
I don't need anyone else.
I can only be the best if I'm with you.
Could I have some time to think about it?
-Hey, Jooran.
-Hey.
I was looking all over for you.
We need to start practicing
for the joint performance audition.
We have a lot on our plate.
There are a lot of difficult parts
for the young leads in the script.
Mm.
Wait…
Have you partnered up with someone else?
Is it Youngseo?
It's not like that.
You haven't, right?
You're auditioning with me, right?
You already read the whole script?
Of course.
When I read the script,
I thought that Princess Pyeonggang
suited you perfectly.
She's cute and lovable.
As for Ondal…
…I'm just worried about his songs
since they're a bit tricky.
You'll do well.
Well, we've got to practice to do well.
Let's start tomorrow morning, okay?
Oh, my goodness, that's hot.
I'll wait for you in the rehearsal room.
You better go to bed early for tomorrow.
Good night.
The Princess and the Fool
Hey, what took you so…
Let's start practicing.
I want to audition with you.
I… want to audition with you.
Oh, but I'm already waiting for someone.
Jooran's not coming.
I saw her with Youngseo just now.
-Have you read the script?
-Yes.
The scene we're auditioning with
is where young Pyeonggang
and Ondal part ways, right?
What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Let's start.
Where are you going?
You haven't given me an answer.
I have to go somewhere, so not now.
Hey!
What to do of my dear princess's…
We need to talk.
Talk when we're done.
I said we need to talk.
-Hey, Jeongnyeon.
-Youngseo.
I can't believe this.
I thought you were partnering up with me.
So why are you with Youngseo?
Answer me.
Why?
Why did you partner up with Youngseo
instead of me?
I'm… afraid of you.
Afraid?
What do you mean?
What are you so afraid of?
I'm afraid that you might get too immersed
in your character again.
When that happens, not only do you end up
devouring your own character,
but also your partner's character
and the whole show.
And the only thing that's left is you.
But…
I can control that now.
Sure.
But you're still learning how.
Who knows what's going to set you off
like last time?
You can't fully control yourself yet.
And when that happens,
I can't be as grounded as Hyerang
and save the scene.
So that's why…
you chose Youngseo over me?
Youngseo is stable.
She calculates how to act
with the whole narrative in mind
and doesn't stray from that.
I can rely on her…
but I can't rely on you.
-Jeongnyeon…
-I'm a bit tired right now.
Let's talk later.
Hey,
I also want to do well in this audition.
And I can do just as well as Jooran.
I'm also desperate!
You and Youngseo aren't the only ones
who want to do well in this audition.
I want it just as much.
I'm not a genius like you,
nor as skillful as Youngseo,
nor do I have any hidden talent
like Jooran.
But I want to do well too.
It's not like
you're giving up on the audition
since you don't have Jooran.
I know you hate me.
And you have every right to do so
because I was so mean to you before.
You might think I'm ridiculous
to ask to audition with you
after all that,
but I still want to.
I want to audition too.
So please give me a chance.
Youngseo is stable.
I can rely on her,
but I can't rely on you.
You and Youngseo aren't the only ones
who want to do well in this audition.
I want it just as much.
The Princess and the Fool
♪ To reach excellence in singing ♪
♪ One needs to discern the five sounds ♪
♪ And transform the six rules… ♪
♪ The six rules ♪
♪ To cajole one's innards ♪
♪ And sing from within ♪
♪ It is difficult indeed ♪
You're still not singing from your core.
You need to pull your strength
from deep within you.
Flex your lower abdomen
and straighten your spine.
I know.
Aren't you afraid…
that I'll ruin everything…
like I did with the soldier?
If you partner up with me…
I might ruin your performance too.
But you're working on controlling that.
What if it happens again though?
From what I've seen,
you don't repeat the same mistakes.
And…
your skills improve at a frightening pace.
You're always miles ahead
of your past self.
Is that so?
So why are you hung up
on something so stupid?
Why else would I want
to audition with you?
Jooran says--
Why would you listen
to someone who rejected you?
She's a fool.
She doesn't even know what she rejected.
But why are you asking me
when you won't audition with me?
You can't partner up with me…
with that kind of voice.
My voice would overpower yours
the moment we sing together.
You think I don't know that?
Wait, what did you say?
Did you just say…
Let's partner up for the audition.
Let's do it.
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me
you've already changed your mind!
No!
I'll do it. Let's do it.
Then I'll be counting on you.
Me too.
Me too!
I thought you were going to say no!
Thank you!
Hmm…
My goodness, is this your office?
It's smaller than I expected.
Still, your troupe itself
is rather sizable.
I guess Maeran really is quite popular.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you hear?
I'm the representative
for the judging panel.
-What?
-Aren't you going to offer me a seat?
Sure.
Aside from me, the panel includes
Professor Min Gyeongsik,
Mr. Kim Jaeseok of Gukmin Manufacturing,
and Assemblyman Jung Ilson.
You're going to judge an audition
that your daughter is a part of?
What are you plotting?
Plotting?
How rude.
I knew
others would misunderstand me like you,
so I even offered not to give a score
for Youngseo's audition.
And I hope you know,
I didn't volunteer to be a judge.
Director Jung Namhui was the one
who begged me to be on the panel.
You think I don't know
that you don't approve of
Youngseo joining my troupe?
So why are you sticking your nose in now?
I know that Gongseon's daughter
is also here at Maeran.
I think her name was Yoon Jeongnyeon.
I want to see it for myself.
Chae Gongseon's daughter
versus Han Kijoo's daughter.
I need to know who's more talented.
This joint performance…
…will be a combined effort
of seven different theater troupes.
Moon Okgyeong will be playing
the role of Ondal
and Seo Hyerang will be playing
the role of Princess Pyeonggang.
And the upcoming audition
will decide who will play
the roles of the young leads.
We heard that Ms. Han Kijoo
is on the judging panel.
Is it true that her daughter,
Ms. Heo Youngseo,
is auditioning as well?
Yes, Ms. Heo Youngseo will be auditioning.
But Ms. Han Kijoo will not be scoring
her daughter's audition.
Regarding Ms. Yoon Jeongnyeon,
who was praised
for her stand-in performance as Precious,
many are saying
that she is the daughter of Chae Gongseon.
Will Ms. Yoon Jeongnyeon
be auditioning as well?
Yes.
Ms. Yoon Jeongnyeon
will be auditioning as well.
Is it true that the two
who pass the audition
will become the successors
of Moon Okgyeong and Seo Hyerang?
Yes, that is true.
Over here, Ms. Moon.
- Ms. Seo, over here!
- Director Kang!
Ms. Seo!
Extra, extra!
Read all about it!
A showdown between two geniuses
Daughter of pansori genius
vs. daughter of opera genius
A battle for the throne
We'll take them all.
Our only prince is Moon Okgyeong!
Only Moon Okgyeong!
We don't need a successor!
We don't need one!
Let's protect Okgyeong!
Protect Okgyeong!
Moon Okgyeong!
Moon Okgyeong! Moon Okgyeong!
"A showdown between two geniuses"
So Jeongnyeon is
the daughter of Chae Gongseon.
It must be so much pressure.
"One born with skill…"
Behind you.
A showdown between two geniuses
A battle for the throne
Who do you think will win?
-Of course it's Youngseo.
-I think Youngseo will win.
Youngseo?
Daughter of pansori genius
vs. daughter of opera genius
That Kang Sobok really knows
how to raise the stakes.
Well, this much publicity
is quite expected
for an audition
my daughter will participate in.
What is it?
Is all this publicity too much pressure?
-Not at all.
-Good.
You can't be phased
by something like this.
In fact, you need to be able
to enjoy your nerves
and channel them
to elevate your performance on stage.
Yes, Mother.
After I heard Gongseon's
Blooming Autumn Field,
no other pansori performance
has ever gotten me excited.
They all seemed fake.
You need to prove to everyone
with this audition
that you, my daughter,
know what it truly means to sing pansori.
Do you understand?
Yes.
♪ I shall look for you, my love ♪
♪ I shall dry my sleeves of my tears ♪
♪ Treasure the marriage vows ♪
♪ We have taken together ♪
♪ And swear never to cry ♪
♪ Until I find you ♪
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
♪ I shall sharpen my wits ♪
♪ To rival those of a dragon ♪
♪ And become as strong ♪
♪ As a tiger ♪
♪ On those treacherous mountains ♪
♪ As I wait for you ♪
♪ My dearest love ♪
You're crying.
What?
You were just touched by my acting.
Hey, that's just because
you were looking at me all sad.
Anyway,
I think we'll be fine for the audition
if we keep going like this.
It's not enough.
What's not enough?
Oh…
…if you mean me,
I know that I need more practice.
I don't mean you. I mean me.
I can't seem to focus on the song…
…and my mind's somewhere else.
This has never happened before.
I'll get my head on straight next time.
You're curious
about Youngseo and Jooran, aren't you?
That's what's bothering you.
No, I'm not.
Fine, I'm a bit curious.
I wonder how they're practicing…
and how good Youngseo is.
Don't even think about
peeking into their practice.
Listen to me.
You really can't, okay?
It's just going to ruin your focus.
Just focus on us
no matter how curious you are.
You guys better be on your toes.
Youngseo and Jooran seem to have
amazing chemistry.
♪ I shall look for you, my love ♪
♪ I shall dry my sleeves of my tears ♪
♪ Treasure the marriage vows ♪
♪ We have taken together ♪
♪ And swear never to cry ♪
♪ Until I find you ♪
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
♪ I shall sharpen my wits ♪
♪ To rival those of a dragon ♪
♪ And become as strong ♪
♪ As a tiger ♪
♪ On those treacherous mountains ♪
♪ As I wait for you ♪
♪ My dearest love ♪
How were they?
That's the power of good chemistry.
They bring out the best in each other.
And it's only possible
because Youngseo has a solid foundation.
She has the skills
to not only focus on her own acting…
but also to match her partner freely.
Compared to her,
you still have a long way to go.
But there's no need
to be so down, Jeongnyeon.
You have an amazing voice.
This role has a lot of difficult songs,
so you can win with your singing.
But…
Youngseo's good at singing as well.
Then you just have to get even better.
There's a cave in the mountain nearby.
Try singing inside that cave.
You can practice by hearing your voice
bouncing back from the walls.
Repeat that 100 times a day
until you cough up blood.
You'd be able to master pansori
within half a month.
Then no matter how good Youngseo is,
you'll always come out on top.
Right now, you should try
everything you can to get better.
If Youngseo beats you this time,
it's over for you.
Don't listen to her.
It's really dangerous for you
to strain your voice like that.
Do you hear me?
We've only begun to practice,
but I think we have good chemistry.
I knew it'd be easy with you
since we get each other.
What is it?
Is that why you chose me?
Because it'd be easy?
What?
I heard your talk with Jeongnyeon
the other day.
You said I was stable
because I calculate everything as I act.
Uh…
Youngseo, I meant that--
When we were rehearsing for Jamyunggo…
you were seeing someone else.
So I thought
it was weird that you chose me.
But I think I know now.
You didn't really want me as your partner.
You actually wanted to partner up
with Jeongnyeon.
I'm just your second pick.
It wasn't like that.
Stop making me feel miserable.
Fine.
I don't care why you chose me.
All I needed was a partner
to audition with anyway.
♪ Never have I ♪
♪ Lamented the fate ♪
♪ Given to me by… ♪
I need some water.
You've been stuck on that part
for ages now.
I told you not to listen to Hyerang.
I don't think your throat's doing okay,
so let's call it a day
and try again tomorrow.
No, let's keep going.
Jeongnyeon.
Let me try a bit more.
I'll go rest if I still can't do it.
♪ Never have I ♪
♪ Lamented the fate ♪
♪ Given to me by… ♪
I went to the gambling house
that Mr. Ko frequented.
But they said
they hadn't seen him in a while.
And anyone who might know his whereabouts
is saying the same thing.
It's clear
that he's been using our money…
but I have no idea how much.
And this ledger is giving me a headache.
Are things pretty bad for us?
We'll be able to pay off
our immediate debts
if this joint performance is a success.
I see.
We'll get through this.
Yes.
Let's pray
that this performance does well.
Okay.
♪ Come ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
♪ I shall sharpen my wits… ♪
What are you doing?
You're going to ruin your throat
at this rate.
I can handle this much.
And my throat feels fine.
Taking care of your throat
is a basic skill for a pansori singer.
You should rest for today.
But if I don't put in this much effort,
I won't get the part.
My acting's still mediocre,
so all I've got is my singing.
If I'm not ahead of the others in singing,
then there's no way I'll get the part.
What are you so anxious about?
You've been doing well until now.
But that's not nearly enough.
Youngseo's improving every day
while I'm falling further behind.
So you're pushing yourself this hard
to get ahead of her?
At this rate,
you won't even make it to the audition.
You're wrong.
I will.
I'm going to get through this
and show everyone how I win.
♪ Never have I ♪
♪ Lamented the fate ♪
♪ Given to me by… ♪
♪ Never have I ♪
♪ Lamented the fate ♪
♪ Given to me by… ♪
You need to rest, Gongseon.
You can't strain your voice like this.
You might ruin it forever.
This isn't just about
the upcoming performance.
Gongseon.
Just say that you can't perform this time.
No.
Everyone's looking forward
to hearing me sing.
They're so excited for the pansori genius.
So how could I not perform?
Since my father has passed away…
…I have…
nothing left for me except pansori.
Then all the more reason
to rest your voice!
Look at the bigger picture!
Who are you trying to teach?
What do you know?
How could you understand?
You've never been anywhere near my level.
Maybe it's okay for you
to ease up and take it slow…
but not me.
I'd rather kill myself
than lose my position.
♪ Dear husband ♪
♪ Please take me with you ♪
♪ Please… ♪
Jeongnyeon.
Look at me, Jeongnyeon.
Do not be so hard on yourself.
This is a marathon, not a sprint.
But what if Youngseo
is significantly better than me?
What if while I'm struggling,
she's already gone miles ahead of me?
Jeongnyeon.
Jooran said
that she could rely on Youngseo,
but she couldn't rely on me.
That's how far behind I am,
so how could I take it easy?
The reason why Youngseo
can get in sync with her partner
is because she has years of experience.
You can't hope to cover that
in just a few days.
That's impossible.
But Jeongnyeon,
you have other talents
that Youngseo doesn't.
Is that…
how far behind I am?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm trying to say…
that you and Youngseo
have different strengths.
This is not the time
to be worrying about Youngseo,
but to focus on
your own interpretation of Ondal.
All right?
What?
-Jeongnyeon's not here?
-No.
What am I going to do with her?
What is it?
I thought she was out early
every morning to practice with you.
With me?
Don't even get me started.
She's been going
to the mountain every day.
The mountain?
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
♪ I shall sharpen my wits ♪
♪ To rival those of a dragon ♪
♪ And become as strong… ♪
Hey.
How did you know I was here?
Were you practicing like this
all this time?
Are you crazy?
Are you trying to ruin your voice
before we even audition?
Come on, let's go.
You're burning up.
You can get heated up
when you practice singing for hours.
It's nothing serious.
Yes, it is serious.
Come with me.
Let go of me.
Let go.
Leave me alone.
Why are you being so stupid?
Your voice is already hoarse.
You're straining your throat
to sing right now.
And what's it to you?
I don't want to care either,
but you're being insane.
I just have to push through this.
And if I do,
I can master pansori.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Mastering pansori is something you hone
through years of practice,
not something you get
by straining your throat for a few days.
If you lose your voice,
you can't ever perform.
If I can't perform,
then you'd have one less rival,
so it'd be good for you.
What?
What, am I wrong?
You cried yourself sick
because you wanted to beat me.
You're right.
I want to beat you.
But I'm going to beat you with skills!
If I wanted to beat you with cheap tricks,
I already would have.
Why do you think I'm practicing to death?
I'm going to beat you with my skills
when you're in your best condition.
So stop with this nonsense.
I won't.
You!
Have you seriously gone insane?
You have everything.
You can't possibly understand me.
Singing, dancing, and acting…
You've perfected everything.
I only have my singing.
How could you possibly understand
my desperation?
I'm different from you.
I came all the way here
relying on my voice alone.
I left home by relying on my voice,
and I was able to get up every time I fell
because of my voice!
My voice is my earth and my sky!
It's my everything.
And you're telling me to stop?
If I stop now,
I'll only be staring down
an endless cliff!
So how could I possibly stop?
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
Ah…
I'll tell you
why I couldn't choose Jeongnyeon.
There was a time…
when she and I were practicing Jamyunggo.
When I looked at her,
I felt nervous for some reason.
I don't think I can think straight…
if I act with her.
I felt that I wouldn't be able
to tell the difference
between Ondal and Jeongnyeon.
And I'd be so confused.
And if that happens,
I wasn't sure I'd be able
to focus on my acting.
So I got scared.
That's enough.
I understand.
There's something I realized
while practicing with you.
Good acting isn't something
I can achieve by myself.
It's something you have to hone
with a good partner.
I relied a lot more on your acting
than I thought.
It's now time for you to rely on me.
Come on, Jooran.
Let's go show everyone
at the audition today
what we've been working on.
Let's protect Okgyeong!
"The Princess and the Fool
Young leads audition"
"We don't need any other prince
than Okgyeong!"
"There is only one throne under the sky!"
Do you have anything to say
to Ms. Heo Youngseo?
How do you feel
about your daughter's audition?
We'll be doing our best.
Have you heard
Chae Gongseon's daughter sing?
Ms. Han!
Have you gotten in touch with Ms. Chae
regarding this audition?
Hello, everyone.
You're all here early.
-Here, let me.
-Hello.
Oh my, thank you so much.
There.
How did you all get here so early?
Hey, Geumju. That's Heo Youngseo.
Hwaja saw her
at Maeran's last Jamyunggo production,
and apparently,
she was amazing as the lead antagonist.
An antagonist is different from this role.
She can't possibly make a fool of herself
as Ondal should.
I'll definitely get this role.
But…
is this everyone from Maeran?
Where's that girl
who already played a supporting role
when she just joined their troupe?
The genius girl.
Ah…
Yoon Jeongnyeon.
Yeah, her.
Where is she?
We will now begin the open audition
for the young leads
of Princess and the Fool.
Aside from the judges,
we are also joined today
by Maeran's Ms. Moon Okgyeong
and Ms. Seo Hyerang as observers.
Then let's start
with Yeonggwang Gukgeukdan's
Kim Gyeonguk and Cho Sunrye.
Uh…
Is Jeongnyeon here yet?
Is something wrong?
She wasn't in her room this morning.
-I think she went to the mountain.
-The mountain?
Didn't you know
that she's been practicing singing
on the mountain?
Hong Jooran!
Yeah?
We're next.
Let's go.
My goodness, Princess!
You may rise.
Did you say that you would cry with me?
Yes, Your Highness.
It is something…
my sick mother used to say.
♪ There is no such thing ♪
♪ As small tears or big tears ♪
♪ Light tears or heavy tears ♪
♪ So if you see someone weeping ♪
♪ Do not just pass them by ♪
Jooran?
Huh?
Next is Maeran Gukgeukdan's
Heo Youngseo and Hong Jooran.
I'm Heo Youngseo of Maeran Gukgeukdan.
I'll be playing Ondal.
I'm Hong Jooran of Maeran Gukgeukdan.
I'll be playing Princess Pyeonggang.
♪ How can I be separated ♪
♪ From my beautiful love? ♪
♪ My lazy body and foolish head ♪
♪ Are to blame ♪
♪ Do not cry
Oh, please do not cry ♪
♪ My beautiful love ♪
♪ Do not shed ♪
♪ Your pearly tears ♪
♪ On your jade-like face ♪
♪ Oh, please do not cry ♪
Look at my little girl.
Is there anyone else in your troupe
who possesses such perfect technique
and emotional depth in their performance?
She still has a long way to go.
She's supposed to act like a fool,
but she's acting much more like a prince.
Hmm… you could just compliment her,
you know?
I do admit that her gaze has gotten deeper
and her acting has gotten more detailed.
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling… ♪
How is she singing
such a difficult song so easily?
There's no one
who can beat Youngseo in singing.
Damn it.
♪ On those treacherous mountains ♪
♪ As I wait for you ♪
♪ My dearest love ♪
Where the heck is she?
Just wait till she gets here.
Yoon Jeongnyeon!
I'm sorry I'm late.
What's wrong with your voice?
It's fine.
It just sounds weird when I talk.
It sounds fine when I sing.
Hey, wait.
You look terrible.
You're burning up!
I just didn't get enough sleep.
I'll be fine if I rest after the audition.
This is why I told you
to stop going to that mountain every day!
Why in the world
did Hyerang give you such terrible advice?
What was she trying to do?
What are you talking about?
Tell me.
What did Hyerang tell you to do?
Oh!
I was looking all over for you.
Come on, everyone's waiting.
What is it?
You pushed Jeongnyeon to sing in a cave
until she coughed up blood?
You really don't know
when to give up, do you?
I'm so sick and tired of you.
All I did was tell her what she could do.
She was the one who went and did it.
No.
You put her in a trap.
You knew how desperate she was
and that she'd walk right into it!
Okgyeong.
These are the last contestants.
Maeran Gukgeukdan's
Yoon Jeongnyeon and Park Chorok.
Yoon Jeongnyeon?
She's the pansori genius
Chae Gongseon's daughter, right?
I'm guessing she has an amazing voice
like her mother.
Having a genius mother
doesn't always mean you're a genius.
I'm Yoon Jeongnyeon.
I'm Park Chorok.
♪ Never have I ♪
♪ Lamented the fate ♪
♪ Given to me by the heavens ♪
♪ But now, my family and I are accused ♪
♪ Of betraying our country ♪
♪ How can I be separated ♪
♪ From my beautiful love? ♪
♪ My lazy body and foolish head ♪
♪ Are to blame ♪
♪ Do not cry
Oh, please do not cry ♪
♪ My beautiful love ♪
♪ Do not shed ♪
♪ Your pearly tears ♪
♪ On your jade-like face ♪
♪ Oh, please do not cry ♪
♪ I shall look for you, my love ♪
♪ I shall dry my sleeves of my tears ♪
♪ Treasure the marriage vows ♪
♪ We have taken together ♪
♪ And swear never to cry ♪
♪ Until I find you ♪
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
♪ I shall sharpen my wits… ♪
Why did she stop?
I think her voice is shot.
Will you stop the song here?
She doesn't look all that well,
so I think we've seen enough.
Let's end the audition here, shall we?
Wait!
Please… Please give me one more chance.
We've already given you a chance.
And you've just used it up.
I'm begging you.
Please just let me sing until the end.
That's enough.
You shouldn't sing anymore.
Let's stop here, Jeongnyeon.
I'm going to keep going.
-Jeongnyeon.
-Just one more chance.
I'll just sing until the end.
If I don't sing right now…
I can't go on.
All right.
Director Kang.
This may just be…
her last chance.
Please allow her to sing.
Please.
Start from Pyeonggang's
"If you leave now, when will you return."
♪ If you leave now ♪
♪ When will you return? ♪
♪ I'll miss you a thousand times ♪
♪ I'll miss you ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ I will miss my dear husband ♪
♪ To no end ♪
Princess.
I do not care
what happens to my lowly self.
But what to do…
of my dear princess's sorrow?
♪ I shall look for you, my love ♪
♪ I shall dry my sleeves of my tears ♪
♪ Treasure the marriage vows ♪
♪ We have taken together ♪
♪ And swear never to cry ♪
♪ Until I find you ♪
♪ Come, my love ♪
♪ I shall wait for you, my darling ♪
♪ I shall sharpen my wits ♪
♪ To rival those of a dragon ♪
♪ And become as strong ♪
♪ As a tiger ♪
♪ On those treacherous mountains ♪
♪ As I wait for you ♪
♪ My dearest love ♪
This is impossible.
Her voice was completely shot.
Jeongnyeon: The Star Is Born
Translated by Jin Yu