Hurry up!
Come on.
Come here.
longevity noodles are here.
I didn't expect our doll
such a big table of dishes.
Brat.
You're lucky.
Of course.
Master.
Today is your 60th birthday.
I didn't prepare a gift.
Only this table of dishes
represents my sincerity.
I promise you
After I clear your name,
I will hold you
a grand birthday for you.
Okay. Here.
Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers.
Master.
Here you go.
You just recovered.
Don't drink too much.
You're right.
You
don't be so polite to me.
Here.
This
is my secret medicine manual for years.
Take it.
Thank you, master.
I passed the disguise technique
to King of Culture.
You passed the secret book to Lunar.
We are a perfect match.
Senior.
I learned that secretly, didn't I?
Yes.
Learn secretly.
Look, I'm talking nonsense again.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Why are you here?
Your Highness, please save my father.
He was taken away.
Isn’t this King of Cultivation?
Ten miles away from the city, by the Luo River.
Where did you collect the information?
It's none of your business.
Report!
We found the place where Luo Mingyue and Prince of Prowess are staying.
Why are they in the same place?
When they are together,
everything will be clear.
I'll report to the Regent now.
Go after them.
When I came back from the snack,
he was already arrested.
Looks like Yun Shang Zhou...
let Grand Mentor Xie go.
In fact,
a way to deal with him.
King of Culture.
Luo Mingyue.
You can't escape.
They used Xiao Ran
to find our location.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Old man.
Kids.
Follow me.
Go.
This is the escape route I've prepared for ten years.
I didn't expect
It's finally useful today.
Yeah. Come on.
Tianchen, help me.
Be careful.
If you don't come out,
if you don't come out.
Ready.
Hurry, let's go.
Hurry.
Sir.
Senior.
My good disciple.
Live well.
Master.
Lunar.
If you go up now,
I'll let you down.
Master.
Let's go.
Master!
Granny.
Are you scared?
As long as I can be with you,
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Granny.
We fought all our lives.
In the end,
I'll be with you.
Let's go.
Go.
Kill!
Search carefully.
What should we do now?
I know a place.
It's safe for now.
Come with me.
Xiao Ran is asleep.
Come on.
This place
is Soju-senpai's place.
Stay here for now.
I've informed Leng Fu.
to come to me.
Their revenge...
our revenge.
No matter what happens in the future,
I will do my best to protect you.
Your Highness.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
After I got your news,
I came here immediately.
to be at your disposal.
Before Grand Mentor Xie was arrested,
he came to me.
that the Crown Prince's residence is fake.
The Crown Prince's mansion is heavily guarded now.
Do you have any idea
to find out the truth?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I know what to do.
Go.
Yes.