[Six months ago]
This leaves a cleaner aftertaste.
- It's good.
- It's good, but I haven't tried it before.
- How is it? How is it? How is it?
- It's good...
An expression of shock!
Drink! Drink!
- Drink! Drink!
- Bae Yu Na! Bae Yu Na!
Bae Yu Na! Bae Yu Na!
Bae Yu Na!
What the?
Drink every last drop!
Tipsy, I'm tipsy.
[Love Class]
[Episode 2 of 6]
Seonbae, I'm joking. Just joking.
Wow, why is it so hot?
The hot cocoa is pretty hot. Is it because it's "hot?"
- Because it's hot—
- Hold on.
There.
- Yu Na.
- Ji Wu.
Help...
Help me.
Yu Na.
Why did you send Seonbae Ro Ah away earlier?
I can't trust men.
What?
But I'm also a man.
[That's it for today]
[Eonni, why do you always wear the same t-shirt? Pretty.]
Shucks, what is this?
[loveuna.s2]
What the heck...
[What's so funny?]
Who is it that's being so friendly?
[loveuna.s2: Why did you close the curtains?]
[9184, right?]
It was the pass code to my house.
I never told anyone, though.
Did you file a police report?
It's been submitted, but...
there was no direct harm done, so...
- they said they will patrol more frequently.
- What?
I mean, shouldn't they investigate it undercover?
I became afraid of men at one point.
Even if they just talk to me, or come near me...
Y-Yu Na, a-are you okay with me?
- If it's hard for you, I can—
- It's all right.
You're my friend.
What?
Yeah...
We're friends...
[Ji Wu, did you get home all right?]
Seonbae, by any chance... do you like men?
He came at me out of nowhere.
Who?
There's someone like that.
Who is it? Let me see!
Why the hell are you embarrassing me in front of everyone?
- If you have something to say, say it.
- What the... Did someone catch your eye?
Say it!
Ugh, you have nothing to say, huh?
Stop making useless excuses. I'm leaving.
Wait.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
About what?
For everything.
Everything?
- For everything?
- Nam Jun.
Is there more beer?
- How's that any different from saying
- Are you crying?
- you did nothing wrong?
- I'm not crying.
My eyes are just sweating.
Just bring some beer!
You go get it, you asshole.
Ouch! Why did you hit me?
That asshole. He has no sensitivity since all he does is work out.
Ignorant bastard.
Oh, my gosh! Did you talk to him?
- I saw that eonni and oppa together.
- Let me drink that.
I have a blind date today.
That's so funny, right?
How great of you.
Hey!
Hey, are you okay? Are you okay?
Why would you step on that?
- Yu Na.
- Huh?
- Hello.
W-Wipe it off with this.
- You keep it!
- Oh, my gosh.
- You can keep it!
- What the?
- Thanks!
- What's going on?
Who is that?
- Tell us!
- Who is he?
- Let us know!
- Is today day one?
Is today day one?
[Fire Hydrant]
Your footsteps are too soft today.
Professor, can't you just pretend to fall for it just once?
I told you not to smile like that if you're not going to accept my confession.
It gives me butterflies.
There you go again.
Student Kim Hye Won.
Read another book if you have time to tease your professor,
and spend your life meaningfully.
Youth is a mere moment, and flowers last one season.
Stop teasing your professor
during the most important time of your life.
I'm telling you that I will love you with all my might in that one season.
Ji Wu!
Seonbae.
Did you get home all right last night?
You didn't reply, so I was worried.
Oh, I lent an ear to Yu Na yesterday.
Seonbae, hold on.
- Why?
- Just come.
What?
That's too dangerous.
I'll take her home with you.
She says no men.
That's why she told you to leave first last night.
What about you?
You're a man, too.
Me...
She said she was okay with me.
I don't know why...
You said it was a stalker.
Don't you think you might be in danger, too?
What?
Seonbae, I may look like this, but I know jiujitsu.
- Do you know jiujitsu?
- This is a problem for the police to resolve.
You could get into big trouble while trying to show off.
I'm doing this because that big trouble might be headed for Yu Na.
I understand how you feel, but just do as I say for now.
- Report it to the police—
- Seonbae.
What?
By chance, do you like Yu Na?
Is it because you don't want me walking Yu Na home?
It's not like that.
You're sure, right?
Yeah.
Then don't stop me.
Ji Wu!
Let's go.
You smell like sweat.
Wash up.
I'm tired.
Hey, give me a massage.
Why? Why?
Like this?
Yeah, there. A little harder, though.
I said, press a little harder!
Hey, move aside.
Geez, you lie down.
Anyway, you only know how to receive.
I know.
I told you to get one from Min Ji since I lack the skill— Ouch!
Relax! It will hurt if you tense up.
Hey, what's wrong with your wrist?
- They keep touching it.
- Who?
Why aren't you answering?
I'm tired.
Whoa. Hey, Nam Jun.
Massage my shoulders, too.
I've been binge-watching "Penthouse" these past few days,
so my shoulders really ache.
Fine.
Let's switch places now.
Thank you.
Okay.
Wait! Wait, hold on!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Kim Nam Jun!
You're nice to Lee Ro Ah!
Why do you always mess with just me?
Shit, so annoying.
- Are you listening to me?
- Yeah.
So you're saying you became afraid of men because of that stalker, right?
Is that why you said you will pair up with me?
But it's a class where you pair up with a man you don't know.
I wonder if it might have been better for you not to take this class.
To be honest, I took it because Professor Lim recommended it to me.
He told me that I would overcome my fear of men if I took this class.
Stop.
What?
What's your relationship with my professor Lim?
Oh.
Professor Lim is my uncle's student.
Daebak.
Yu Na.
Can you ask your uncle what Professor Lim's taste in women is like?
- Huh?
- I can ask him, but...
I'll ask him!
Hey, your answer was so ambiguous.
But why did you say you want to pair up with a girl?
I'm... making him think about me.
You know...
someone constantly hangs around you and makes you uncomfortable,
and at one point, you are subconsciously thinking about them.
You did it intentionally so he would think about you?
Exactly. Oh, and there's also this message.
"I don't want to pair up with any of these punks."
Why?
"Because my partner is none other than you, Professor Lim."
Aren't I so cute?
Yeah... you're cute.
Right.
Professor Lim should recognize it, not you.
That girl from earlier was Hye Won.
Oh, from that time...
That's right. The one who argued with you—
No, please forget about that. Please.
Hey.
Your hair is a mess.
Let me see.
- Hey, you have gray hair!
- Huh?
Hold on.
- Wait...
- Ouch!
Did it hurt a lot?
No, it's fine. Is there another one?
No.
I should plant it.
Back into my head.
Bye.
Yeah, bye.
Yu Na, sweet dreams.
[It's raining later. Take an umbrella when you meet Yu Na.]
[Thank you.]
Why isn't he replying?
He's making me worry.
[Where are you right now?]
Where are you?
Ji Wu?
Hello? Ji Wu.
Please help me!
Who told you to loiter around her? So annoying.
Seon– Seonbae. Seonbae...
You scumbag.
[Love Class]
... got drunk and fell.
What the hell are you doing these days?
You didn't even come home last night!
- There is someone, isn't there?
-Thanks for worrying, but
let's not overstep our boundaries.
Ji Wu. What should I do?
Let's talk it out! Ouch!
Don't play around with someone's heart, acting all innocent.
Multiple people will see blood because of you.