Dedicated to the unsung heroes
of our lives.
EPISODE 3
Subtitle distribution Magico.club Team
Taken, Katerina2020, Suri, Trelokomeia
And the brains in the blender
Sit here and don't make a sound.
Oh, my goodness,
are you smoking again?
- I thought you cut it off.
- And I thought you were gonna bring me a witness.
In particular I remember someone
making a big deal out of it.
Something came up.
Doesn't it always come up?
So you have no evidence
to hold my agent.
Come on.
Because you're like that,
you know how these jobs go.
In such a case
of industrial espionage,
your government is not cooperating
because they're profiting from it.
So we have no choice.
We have to catch the thief.
All this, you don't do
just for Harrison.
What's really going on?
Cunning fox.
Okay, but on one condition.
For more Korean series
visit our page.
You will find us at
w w w w. M a g i c o. c l u b
- Okay.
- Okay?
I bought you some time.
You have 2 weeks
to find the killer,
and bring the files
that he was going to give to Helmes.
Listen well. You must
we have to use Harrison.
We want to cooperate
to take a serious shot at Helmes.
Okay.
Do you wear contact lenses?
Your eyes are blurry.
- Were you crying last night?
- Of course not.
Since it affected you.
This is no time for tears.
I told you not to call
to take cases personally.
That's how mistakes are made.
Yeah, what's up?
What, the National Intelligence Agency
won't allow it?
What the hell are you talking about?
Okay.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR WISHES
TO OUR NEW LEADER
Arum.
Doo Le...
Sophie...
Yeah, Sophie.
Our little bride.
Our friend.
How did this happen to her?
INFORMANT
SOFI IF
ECLIPON
The unthinkable happened.
Yeah, but even though it happened.
they didn't even mention it on the news.
Sophie was known.
They wrote articles that she was a genius
and that she was the youngest scientist,
in charge of the National Chemistry Department.
Look at this report
to her death.
"The genius scientist, Sophie Anne,"
"dead from an overdose
of opioids."
Are they referring to Sophie?
I can't find this article anymore either,
they deleted it.
What's the matter?
You said someone was after her.
Maybe he was murdered.
But the media
are talking about an overdose.
"Sophie started the opioid
while she was studying."
"On the eve of her wedding,
she was seen drinking heavily."
What website is this?
Who wrote it?
Chon Gook-Gill?
I'll give him a hand.
Wait, my cell phone.
Hello,
News Party office there?
I want Huang Chun Gil...
Excuse me, can I talk
with Chon Gook-Gill, please.
How?
Is it missing?
- We have a directive from headquarters.
- What is it this time?
Not to mention
that her death,
occurred under unclear circumstances
because it makes sense.
They prefer to be seen
like an overdose at a party.
Doesn't that make sense?
There will be reactions
from other countries,
that the international project manager,
wanted to sell research secrets.
That's why they want to cover it up.
How will they cover something like that?
If no theft report is made
then the thief will get away with it.
Damn them.
Okay.
The dead do not speak.
Now it's a race
to put the puzzle together.
Yong-gu, did you find anything?
Anne Sofie, South Korea.
PhD in Physics, USA,
and a degree from the Institute of Technology.
While residing in the United States,
WITNESS PROTECTION PROGRAMME
FOR TURTLE INFORMATION
was selected as chief scientist
for Ekosan,
that investigates energy
nuclear fusion.
- I read her thesis...
- What do you know about physics?
Chief, Yong-gu
may seem stupid,
but he's the smartest of us all.
- He is a graduate of the Institute of Technology.
- Really?
To write a thesis
in nuclear fusion,
you have to be diligent,
dedicated only to research,
so I don't know
because he was selling secrets...
Don't you read comics?
The bad guys are scientists
who want to destroy the earth.
Like when they get their doctorate
they become evil.
We must not let
the mad scientists out.
That's why I'm so afraid of them.
And that's why I don't let
Yong Gu working outside.
You recognize the perverts
from the well-manicured nails.
A skilled spy,
is a mommy in disguise.
What better cover...
by a scientist
dedicated to research?
How he got into trouble
with industrial espionage?
Our job is
to unlock its secrets.
Secret?
Yeah, I think Sophie
had a big secret.
What secret could he have had?
Another man? Debts? Family?
A man with financial issues,
or financial issues about a man.
A man with family issues,
or a family with a man issue.
No, Sophie wouldn't have
that kind of trouble.
You're wrong.
There is no man without secrets.
Your life may depend
on a secret.
But this secret
was so big,
who couldn't stop it
from getting out.
In a way,
it caused her death.
You mean the secret of
killed her?
Maybe not.
- All Sophie knew was research.
- People like that are easily manipulated.
She was always the best student,
a genius to her peers.
Her parents had a tutorial
in Decie-dong.
Thanks to their daughter's reputation, they attracted
many students and made a lot of money.
But her father,
lost a lot of money in a real estate scam.
TRAINING.
REAL ESTATE TAX
That's when Sophie,
she was asking everyone for a loan.
SOFI IF
He even published a book,
and started lecturing.
Wait a minute.
Then it didn't start
her own company?
Find out where he got the money.
Check her parents' finances.
Debts do not always push
to selling secrets,
- but we have to take it into account.
- What about her husband? Him?
They went to the same university.
His alibi checks out.
He has left the country.
Return to the USA
when his wife died?
NAME: CHEN LEE, CHINA
What? Is he back?
Really?
Who is doing this? It's cold.
Yeah, okay.
When the wife is murdered,
the husband becomes a prime suspect.
Why would he do that?
His family has money.
Do you think it was a crime of passion?
The one who was watching her.
Someone was following Sophie.
- There is no proof that he did it.
- So Ra will bring the evidence,
that he picked up in Jeju
and the crime scene.
Find if the formula
is related to other hypotheses.
And look at this.
Find as many calls as possible
to this mobile phone.
I didn't find anything,
he must have had another cell phone.
Chi Hun, which email
was Sophie communicating with you?
Dr. Philip Yoon has her e-mail.
He approached us first.
Philip and Sophie
were colleagues.
Can you find him?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Check everyone who
who had a relationship with her.
Speaking of which...
we have someone very interesting,
too close to us.
NAME: KANG ARUM
You chose the photo,
Yong-gu?
Change it.
The other side is better.
What did you say?
Did you meet Chi Hun?
Why?
You broke up with him and said
you'd never speak to him again.
You said you'd never see him again.
Why did you two meet? And especially in Jeju.
I wouldn't meet him
under normal circumstances.
How was it? Was he the same?
He was at work,
and he had a huge smile.
- Good thing it works.
- He was working with his body.
Work is not shameful.
He was sweating a lot.
Sophie's bachelor party.
He was a male stripper.
- What?
- Don't you have any pictures?
To laugh after so many tears,
is not good for health.
I'm sorry.
But I can't get my head around it.
What the hell was Chi-Hoon doing there?
Always appears
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
So he ruined my life too.
But he has to stay away from you.
Now where is he?
After the divorce, Arum started
her own company and remarried.
NAME: CHION DE CHION,
DEREK HION
She married him?
He's a diplomat.
He's handsome, he's got a degree and money.
And I would have married him
if I were a woman.
After she dumped Chi Hoon,
she found the man of her dreams.
After she took her junior
when she married Chi Hun.
Chon Chi Hoon.
- Investigate your ex-wife.
- What?
That's who Sophie saw before she died.
He was also on stage
of the crime.
In a way,
he's the prime suspect.
This is absurd.
- I was with her all that night.
- You were?
Think about it.
Wherever he went,
bad things happened.
Did you feel that something
was wrong?
Feel what?
Since when did Interpol
is based on instinct?
Why don't you pick a suspect
by lot?
Always listen to your instincts.
When you fall in love,
do you research everything?
When you face her,
your heart rate goes up.
That's when the control starts, no, wrong,
that's when the sparks fly.
And if your instincts
is wrong?
Love begins...
when you realize
that you've ceased to be rational.
So to love,
I mean in an investigation,
you have to turn around
when your instincts betray you.
It's a wonderful thing.
Please get authorization for this.
I will not participate.
Chon Chi Hoon.
What was the last message
you got from your source?
I want to invite you to my party.
Before you meet the VIP at the wedding,
you have to find the bride.
I'll show you where the VIP is
and where to find your gift.
He was going to show you the wedding VIP
and a special gift.
What does it refer to?
VIP
Probably some guy in charge
Helmet agent.
Why? Because he invited
that agent.
- One guest was Agent Helmes.
- Then what's the gift?
Hidden archives of Project Ekosan.
So Sophie called
Chi-Hun to the party,
to verify his identity.
And his ex-girlfriend was there
when Sophie suddenly disappeared.
He was also at the scene of the murder.
But mostly,
she was a guest at the wedding.
That makes her very suspicious.
- I'll start with the guest list.
- Start with your ex-wife.
He knows something, I'm sure.
It has nothing to do with this.
Okay, let's say
he doesn't know anything.
But if a vital secret
was accidentally revealed to her,
while he was at the crime scene
without his knowledge?
Then it will be in danger.
Who will he ask for help?
Arum hates me.
Great, you won't have any sparks.
- Yong Gu.
- Yes, sir.
You wanted an outside job?
Help him.
- Sit down, chief.
- Really? Yeah.
Chief, I told you
he's a scientist.
We are running out of time.
Since So Ra is coming.
She can help him.
Putting Yong-gu on the case,
we make Chi Hoon more cautious.
Lately it has been unstable.
He's lost a source.
He took it badly
last time too.
Then it was very bad,
because that's when she got divorced.
But they didn't break up
for that reason.
But why would it happen
the same thing again?
I'm beginning to feel sorry for him.
It doesn't make him look
that he has a history?
That makes me more nervous.
- Find out what's going on in the nuclear lab.
- They're not allowed to talk about the project.
You can always find someone chatty.
Use your persuasion.
You're a spy at last.
What did I miss?
FRIENDS
What I did wrong
and I couldn't protect her?
I could have saved her.
Sophie asked me for help.
Last time
he picked you up at the hotel.
The ultimate message.
He may have told you
something important.
Don't tell anyone,
keep it to yourself.
Do you understand?
Don't trust anyone.
Even the one next to you.
"Do not trust
the one who is next to you?"
You son of a bitch.
I knew it was you.
You.
It was you, wasn't it?
You killed Sophie, didn't you?
I didn't kill her.
- I'm not that kind of trash.
- Yes, you are.
That's you.
You scare me.
Pil Ho, get a grip.
Phil Ho.
Take this one.
What do you take me for?
Why would I kill the woman
you loved, buddy?
It's very evil,
I would never do it.
That's why we are not moving forward
on this job.
The good heart is a bomb
ready to explode.
We end up dead.
Are you telling the truth?
Look, I just pawned
my expensive watch.
You know how important
the watch was to me, wasn't it?
When a man
sells his watch,
then surely
he's broke.
It was like selling my kidney,
when I pawned my watch.
If I had made a deal with Sophie,
I wouldn't be in this situation.
Did you really leave Felix?
Phil Ho, I have nowhere to go.
You're my last hope.
I need your help.
Because your hands
are sweaty?
Do you have hyperhidrosis?
They are my tears.
- You really didn't?
- Damn it.
If you think I did,
then come and forget about me.
If you find out who did it,
then I'll seriously consider your offer.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna find that son of a bitch
who killed Sophie.
Let's avenge her death.
Thank you, Phil Ho.
That's how friendships work.
Give and take.
I did it
to get my money's worth.
Now we're even.
The security camera
wasn't working that day.
Yesterday we called
someone to fix it.
You called your ex-girlfriend
after you got back?
Don't call her an ex.
And what should I call her?
The one who broke up with you a long time ago?
Don't say anything.
Your wife never knew,
that you were a spy
during your marriage?
- No.
- Is she stupid?
I was careful.
I wonder how he would react
if he found out now?
Having a good time?
We are not private detectives
looking for the dirt on the world.
Awesome.
You've never been here before?
Why would I come?
It wouldn't be surprising.
Some people when they get drunk,
they go to their ex-girlfriends.
I can imagine you drunk
visiting your ex-wife.
Or be sober
and suddenly you're in her house.
General Kim
cut off his horse's head,
when out of habit that
he went to his courtesan's house.
Too bad about the horse.
- I guess he missed his courtesan.
- A general beheaded a horse.
What's your conclusion?
What?
What are you doing in my car?
I haven't paid it off yet.
Would you send the car to the junkyard?
You still owe on it?
Why would I throw it away?
Breaking up with someone
is no different from this.
Like flying a car
that you haven't paid off yet.
Like the general
who cut off the horse's head.
What kind of person does that?
Do you still have feelings?
No.
I cut off the horse's head.
That's what I did.
And now what do we do?
Follow her.
- Yes, darling.
- Did you call me?
It's very strange.
I read a strange article about Sophie,
and when I picked up the paper,
I was told that the columnist
went on vacation.
And that her fiancé
has returned to the United States.
I can't find her parents.
Is this reasonable?
I guess they're all probably in shock.
Are you driving and talking on your cell phone?
Don't exaggerate.
You must be tired of crying.
Maybe you should have taken the day off.
No, I have to work.
Although it was cancelled
Sophie's wedding,
I have other marriages
on my schedule.
Don't worry.
I'm going to meet Mrs. Kim.
I'll see you at home.
Okay.
HARRISON YONGK
E'I'LI
Hey, Ailey, I called you.
because I can't find Harrison.
We were supposed to meet today.
Sudden business trip?
Okay?
Yes, I'll wait to eat
for skewers from your little hands.
Thank you.
Yeah, see you.
You learned it from a book
to follow a car?
What book?
"Become a spy in 100 days"?
Then he says how to go undercover?
Or "Think like a CIA agent
and acted like the KGB"?
- Which one?
- I do what I can, you know.
Not to be detected,
or miss the target.
- Zero to two.
- Better to miss the target?
No, you only get one chance.
The target may be headed
to the most important appointment.
So don't ever lose him.
Your ex-girlfriend, she's in there
in circulation all the time.
But it does not violate the C.O.C.
That's her style.
It is tender but also rough.
She is cold and generous.
When he passes by,
he does so at a controlled speed.
They say that life goes on.
That's life.
Do you want to die?
Watch where you're going,
do you want to die so badly?
You won't live long
if you drive like that.
She's tough. Hard as a rock.
Speed up.
We're not going for a walk in the country,
just step on the gas a little bit.
Okay.
Does she like paintings?
Not exactly.
What a beautiful painting.
She likes to watch
her reflection.
Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Parking properly.
Get in.
You're still here?
Shall I go in?
Find out why he came here
and who he will meet.
Who when,
where, what, how and why.
Report everything to me.
I will evaluate
your performance, right?
You're lucky.
The gallery is a public space
and you won't arouse suspicion.
Why didn't anyone tell me
that I was going undercover?
What is this?
Is this the '80s?
There is no way
I won't impress you.
Isn't it perfect?
Just as I expected.
Yong Gu.
When are you going to impress me?
He met with a woman.
Which woman?
Hello, Mrs. Kim.
I'm Kang Arum from Arum Bridal.
It must be the director.
How did it happen?
They tried to kill me,
by greasing the stairs.
- Excuse me?
- They tried to kill her,
greasing the stairs.
He broke his leg.
Yong Gu,
I'll break yours too.
Someone wants to kill me.
- Excuse me?
- I'm going ahead with the wedding.
design my wedding dress,
please.
A wedding dress discreet,
but also with character.
Okay, we'll fix you up
a beautiful wedding dress.
Do you like
a special design?
Door-to-door sales?
Arum sells her a wedding dress.
This woman reminds me of something.
You said she's the manager?
GALLERY DDK
KIM DONG RAN
That's her, Kim Dong Ran.
She is the daughter of the founder of DDK.
Her name is Kim Dong Ran.
She's the secret illegitimate daughter
of his father and his second wife.
Catering in the "Dawn" programme
was a great success,
and with the stepson
brother Kim Dong-taek,
competing for the company.
It's like the Hong Gil Dong of the rich.
That's why she's so authoritarian,
like any typical millionaire.
Do you know my half-brother?
We look alike, he just has a moustache.
You mean Mr. Kim Dong-Tek?
No, she knows him.
but my husband does.
They met in a shop
and became friends.
But my brother
doesn't have any normal friends.
- Excuse me?
- He hangs out with psychopaths.
Are your wedding dresses nice?
If you want some
a specific plan...
I don't like wedding dresses.
They're so white and pompous.
Like a cake you can't
you can't eat more than one bite.
They are indeed very sweet.
I hate sweets.
Well, draw something
that will suit my style.
I want a wedding dress
that represents who I am.
Okay, I'll do my best.
What size shoes do you wear?
Thirty-seven.
Your legs are swollen.
Take them off for a while.
You'll feel more comfortable.
But who is she?
They fit me perfectly.
They are my favorites.
See you next week.
Okay.
Right, it must be difficult
to live with constant attention.
He tries very hard
to sell her wedding dresses.
Now he's going for ramen.
Very strange, this woman,
she really scared me.
She told me they want to kill her.
And she seemed to be telling the truth.
So the rumours are true.
Her half-brother,
is from the father's first wife.
Despite the drugs and illegalities,
the father supports him.
But the sister is going to have a huge wedding
and the husband is a millionaire,
something he doesn't like.
She's spreading the word that she's going to get
father's company.
I don't understand.
He wants me to design the wedding dress,
when my brother is a friend of my husband's?
Never mind that she insulted him.
What right did he have to do that?
I was furious at what he said.
She didn't like the plan.
- What? Why?
- He found it cloying.
I'm exhausted.
How I did
on my first mission?
I recognized the person he met
and did a quick check.
But nothing important came up.
Why not?
Is the choice of wedding dress unimportant?
Excuse me?
Look.
You want me to see where you're pointing.
Is there a moon tonight?
No, see if it's
her nails are painted.
When you watch a woman
pay attention to every detail.
HUANG SO RA
Chon Chi Hoon.
You're the best.
What is this?
Who's the dancer?
Wait a minute, is that you?
- Let me see it.
- Give it back.
Did you take dance lessons?
I bet you had a teacher.
Yes.
Chang Du Bong
pawned his watch?
Find out where he is in Jeju.
I'm looking for it. See you.
- Where are you going?
- To gather information.
- In her shop?
- Yes.
You said he hates you.
I can charm
a woman if I want to.
No, you can't.
Let's reconsider.
See you.
There's something strange
about Sophie's death.
I called her lab.
- And?
- I mentioned the article,
that said he got
an overdose of opiates.
And I asked them why
they didn't do something about it.
And what did they say?
That there is no
a person responsible for this.
The one you spoke to
was definitely the one in charge.
I agree.
The death of Sophie
is a mystery.
A leading scientist dies
under mysterious circumstances,
and someone wants to cover it up.
It's like a horror story.
Whoever tries
to know the truth...
He will be in mortal danger.
I was scared.
Director Kang,
you have a visitor.
- Did I have a date?
- He's a man.
Did you call a courier?
It's called Chon Chi Hoon.
He says you know him.
What are you doing here?
You got the good one.
You own the building, too?
It's the bank's.
I own the toilet.
I'm impressed that you called
a loan to buy it.
Hey, Doo Le.
How dare you come
in my shop?
Come with me.
I said, come with me.
It'll be done to the poor woman.
Why did you come here all of a sudden?
Nice suit.
Leave it. Don't touch him.
She reminds me of my mother-in-law.
He was telling me how much they suit me
about evening suits.
Is your mother all right?
It's fine. We just broke up.
her blood pressure stopped rising.
You haven't told me what you want here.
I saw the article.
For your friend.
I know that night
you did everything you could.
But Chi Hun...
there's something strange.
The article states that he died
from an opiate overdose,
and her fiancé
returned to the United States as a fugitive,
and I can't find her parents.
From the laboratory of
they're not saying anything.
I was with her
the day it happened.
And I saw her right away
after her death.
How did you get there?
Sophie called me crying.
I should have gone earlier.
Did he call you?
What did he say?
He asked me for help.
He told me that someone
someone else was helping her.
Anyone else?
I don't know.
It was like he was delirious.
It sounded like she was being chased.
What others
had she invited to her wedding?
I know about some
friends from college.
Doule, and...
- My husband.
- Your husband?
My Sophie met him.
She had invited me to a party
and that's where I first met him.
What? Does it bother you that I mention him?
I am a progressive man.
Why would it bother me?
I'm not old-fashioned.
I don't care at all
if you are or are not a progressive.
When are you coming back to Jeju?
I'm not coming back.
- You're not going?
- No.
- I'm going to write my book here.
- Where here?
You got a place to stay?
Since you brought it up.
Can you lend me some money?
- What?
- Only 40,000 euros.
Chi Hun is very confident.
Although I don't know why.
Wait a minute.
Who's that?
Mrs.
Where's Director Kang?
Her appointment is here.
I'll go.
Welcome.
Arum is in a meeting.
What? We had a date.
I'm in a hurry.
Houses,
are very expensive in Seoul.
You're crazy.
Yes, things are happening today.
What's going on?
I completely forgot.
How did this happen to me?
Hang on, I'll be right back.
Wait for me here.
I'll go get a pair of sharp scissors.
Good evening.
The Director
is in the dressing room.
What a romantic man.
APPLICATION INSTALLATION
DO YOU WANT TO INSTALL
THE ARUM LOCATOR?
LOCALISATION INSTALLATION
THE LOCATOR IS INSTALLED
INVITATION TO THE WAKE
OF THE LATE SOPHIE ANN
Come on in.
Only here can
a man can relax.
Yes.
Have we met?
Do I remind you of anyone
a friend from the army?
I'm often told.
- What corps did you serve in?
- I was in the Special Forces.
- As a doctor?
- As a shooter.
Very impressive.
How you become
a sniper in the army?
You have to aim well.
I trained in marksmanship.
I was an interpreter in the army.
You should speak good English.
I smoke American brand,
but I don't know English.
I always wanted...
- to learn how to shoot a gun.
- Like this?
I can teach you.
Is it possible?
Come to the shooting range
in Jongnum.
Are you a freelancer?
How did you know?
You're struggling with your tie.
I find ties stuffy.
- I'll do it.
- It's okay.
When arrested
the accused in a trial,
they don't let them wear the tie.
You know why?
Why?
So they don't kill themselves.
So the men carry
a potential weapon around their necks.
I feel safe
when I wear a tie.
Especially when he's tying me up
by my wife.
When he looks at me
and ties my tie,
it's like looking at her
kissing me.
I like it very much.
I see you're married.
- Hello? Hello?
- What are you doing?
Why don't you go out?
That man came.
- Your ex-husband.
- I know.
- Did you see him?
- Yeah, I saw him.
Does he know who you are?
I hope not.
You had a fight?
Not yet.
Wait for me.
I have to go.
It was nice talking to you.
And me.
Congratulations on your wedding.
- See you at the photo shoot, have a good trip.
- Bye.
- What did Chin Hu say?
- He asked me for $40,000.
I don't believe it.
He wants me to give him the stuff,
that he didn't get after the divorce.
You still have them?
It's only
some old albums and stuff.
They keep these at their parents' house,
why do you still have his albums?
It just happened.
Do you really think he's here for a loan?
Do you think he came
because he still loves me?
You're both joking.
You were here?
Your husband came in, and I said to him.
he'd find you in the dressing room.
You came without warning?
Welcome.
Long time no see.
- Last week I was here.
- You were?
- Looking for something?
- What?
Does this?
There it was.
I'm a forgetful person.
I thought I'd cheer you up.
I was worried about you.
How the meeting went
with Kim Dong Ran?
I left barefoot.
Let's have dinner tonight.
I'm sorry, but I have plans.
Go somewhere with Du Le.
You're leaving now?
I came to see you and you're fine.
I'm leaving.
- Hey, Doo Le.
- Why are you leaving in such a hurry?
They used it
for strangulation?
I was worried about you,
but you weren't crying after all.
I've told you before.
Here we are like the smiling ones
postmen.
I can't receive
brides with tears.
We tell the bride only good news,
before her wedding.
What's the matter?
See you later.
BEST ESCAPES
Jesus.
CHON CHI HUN
Sucker.
But you're not?
How long has it been?
Are you all right?
I was living abroad.
That's why I haven't seen you in a while.
Your girlfriend comes here often.
- My girlfriend?
- The girl you brought the other day.
No way.
It's her.
Now she is a very good shooter.
KANGRAK DONG CHURCH
Hello, Mr. Park Sang-wan.
I am a recruiter for GV.
My name is Chon Woon Sang.
I was surprised by your email.
I didn't know Sophie
was so appreciative of my research.
I talked to Sophie
and I asked her,
to suggest the best
in nuclear fusion,
and the first to mention,
was you.
GV is an up-and-coming company
with capital,
The compensation package
will be very competitive.
He wrote you a letter of recommendation
before her death.
Dr. Anne Sophie...
I admired her a lot,
but in the factory
there was a shortage of staff.
That's why I, too.
I was thinking of going elsewhere.
- He tried to help me...
- Dr. Anne Sophie,
is a
a very caring man.
I guess...
was a caring man.
He had a big heart.
Dr. Sophie.
Her death
is a loss to the country.
- How sad.
- The bastards.
He died, and they...
I mean the people in charge
of the laboratory.
I never liked them,
but why are they so malicious?
They do not accept requests for interviews,
related to her death.
And let me accept that.
They also ban scientists
to speak to the press.
That makes me nervous. And the employees
following orders, one of the same.
What did Dr. Anne Sophie do wrong?
It's tragic that he died
so young.
The world is a very cruel place.
To see
if they'll come to the memorial.
You arranged the memorial
and sent out invitations, didn't you?
Yes.
I felt I had to
to say goodbye properly.
That was the right thing to do.
That's why I sent an invitation
to her colleagues.
I already had their phone numbers.
- I'm sorry.
- You have to wash it.
It doesn't matter, it doesn't burn.
- It burns.
- Excuse me.
Don't worry,
I'm going to the bathroom anyway.
Excuse me.
Good.
Do you think the VIP
we're looking for will come?
Someone important is coming.
- Who?
- Someone I met in church.
CURRENT POSITION OF THE ARUM
Excuse me.
You're Park Seung-hwan, right?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for coming
to the memorial service.
I had to come.
But yet, very few came.
The lab didn't let
the staff to attend.
Only a few of her neighbors
and a talent scout.
I wonder where they're sitting.
I have something to ask you.
It's something I couldn't
I couldn't ask over the phone.
Sophie had problems
with anyone?
He always behaved professionally
around everyone.
Of course, that's what it was like.
But...
in case someone was provoking her
trouble?
- Was she being followed?
- What?
I don't know.
She spent all her time
in the workshop
and then go straight home.
He had no time for meetings.
He certainly didn't.
Did anything strange happen...
before the wedding?
Before the wedding?
Did he have any visitors?
Yeah, I remember something.
Something strange happened.
- What?
- You asked me to house-sit for her
when they were on their honeymoon.
So I went to her house
to tell me what plants to water.
And it struck
her landline phone.
Nobody has a constant these days.
But she had one.
It was dusty.
As if he rarely used it.
When he answered, he went outside.
I was out in the garbage too.
It looked like he was cheating.
It was very strange.
Who would come to see her
a few days before the wedding?
- Doesn't that seem strange to you?
- Absolutely.
- Did you see who it was?
- No, I didn't make it.
But I remember the sound.
- Was it a sports car?
- Yes.
Lives in a quiet neighbourhood
and the noise was too loud.
SOFI IF
Hello, Mr. Park?
I'm Sophie's friend.
Do you make
Sophie's door?
I think you should come here.
Okay.
Who are you?
It's here, right?
CURRENT POSITION OF THE ARUM
What are you going to do?
You there.
Go and help her.
Do you need an ambulance?
Call the police,
please.
Don't be in a hurry.
Yes.
Chin Hoon's ex-wife
is brave.
Although he was bleeding
he treated it like a man.
Okay, I'll be back.
I was driving like I was holding a formula
on a country road.
The guy was a pro.
Most likely to
he had a fake license plate.
- How's Arum?
- Yong-gu took her to the hospital.
Looks okay.
You have the guest list
for the wedding?
Hurry back to the office.
Rest.
Okay, thanks.
Please?
Where are you?
- Hospital. I'm shutting you down.
- Hospital?
- Why?
- If it's not urgent, I'll see you.
It's urgent.
What?
It's about that loan
I told you about.
Can I borrow it?
And 30,000 euros again is possible.
No, I'll give you 40,000.
But I'm gonna hit you
for every 10 euros.
When you come to pick them up
come in an ambulance.
Looks fine to me.
Come here.
Do you eat flowers?
AN ERROR OCCURRED
Emergency.
The radiator's broken.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Did he go there?
Done.
WIFE
I have a meeting.
Sorry, I'll call you later.
Excuse me.
Do you know where I can find
the pretty boy who brought me here?
I didn't see him.
Is he gone?
I never got to thank him.
Did he leave his number at all?
I don't know.
Okay.
A good-looking pretty boy.
Over here.
What's going on?
You said you saw a sports car
that night, right?
Subtitle distribution Magico.club Team
Taken, Katerina2020, Suri, Trelokomeia
And the brains in the blender
I'M IN SESSION.
SORRY, I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
If you want to be the first to know
for subtitles and translations in kdramas
visit the group on facebook
Korean Beauty's Victims
(Community of Greek Subtitlers)
Subtitles Available
Magico.club / Greeksubs.net
Contact us at
magicosubteam@gmail.com
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
- Don't treat her like a suspect.
- Get Arum.
We must protect
the witness.
What kind of karma is this?
They are not finished
Your troubles are over.
Don't be like that, please.
If I told her my real job
would we still be together?
I have a responsibility.
It is not only fate that unites us,
but also separates us.
I'll handle it.
A sheriff?
Would he save Sophie?
Who could it be?