Since we don't love each other,
we should just call off our engagement.
That's because he feels slighted.
I know.
I will never call off my engagement with Nu-Kuea.
Why?
You know nothing. There's more to it than just an engagement.
I can't let him know what I do in my free time.
That includes being a singer and a drummer named Kirin.
Kirin...Do you think you can fool me, Annabelle?
It's just a promise that you gave to my grandpa. Is that all?
You don't have any siblings. You only have me to play with.
Maybe that makes you think that you-
You said that you will propose to me.
That's right. I will.
But when I asked you...
If you ask me whether I love you or not,
I don't think it's love yet.
How the hell could it not be?
You should find one good reason...
and prepare to explain why I want to call off the engagement.
I will say this very frankly.
I want to marry a human.
I don't want to marry a doll.
Annabelle.
Do I look like Annabelle?
Does he mean that I look like a ghost?
I will go get a skinhead cut then!
Nu-Kuea, what kind of hairstyle do you want?
I want to do what Hia Lian likes.
Sure. That's not hard to do.
Mommy, make sure I look exactly like him.
Sure.
I always dress up and do everything the way he likes.
Kuea, what's the matter?
I have decided...
I will not go back to the UK.
How come?
I want to stay here.
I will study at a university in Thailand.
But we've prepared everything for you to continue your study in London.
I know that.
But...
I miss grandpa.
And...
I want to spend more time with Hia Lian.
Since we'll get married in the future.
Okay.
If that's what you've decided, I won't object.
Have you decided what major you want to choose then?
I want to study engineering.
I thought you wanted to study political science.
But it's okay.
I think computer engineering is okay too.
He can study whatever he likes.
As long as he's obedient and well-behaved.
I'm just worried that you will live apart from us.
But if Lian is there to take care of him for me, I think it should be okay.
Okay.
I want you to be Nu-Kuea's guardian while he's living in Thailand.
Keep us updated on his schedules as well as his grades.
Yes, sir.
I don't think that is necessary.
I can take care of myself.
But I'll will be less worried if Lian is also there to look after you.
Please take him out sometimes.
I don't want you to look after him like you're his parent or brother.
Look after him like he's your life partner.
Can you do that?
Of course.
It's my pleasure.
I will take him on a date every Friday night.
Starting from this week.
That's great. Then I can him stay in Thailand.
I'm okay with it too.
Kuea!
I want to ask.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Come on. Only you want to know this.
Yeah. I want to know.
Answer or drink? Answer or drink? Answer or drink?
I...
I don't have a girlfriend.
But I have a fiancé.
What?
Fiancé?
Our family planned our engagement since we were young.
He's like a brother to me.
What?
Brother?
It might sound weird.
It seems impossible, isn't it?
My family and his family are very close.
Everything is possible in this world.
Wait. So, you two have been in an arranged marriage since you guys were kids?
No.
They didn't force us.
Well..
I've loved him for a really long time.
But it still seems a bit weird.
Gosh! Because a person like you exists in this world,
that's why our society will never be open-minded.
Do you know that our society has become more diverse than you could imagine?
Keep your eyes, your ears, and your heart open.
And stop that kind of thinking.
Calm down, mom. I'm just asking because I want to know.
What about your fiancé? Does he love you too?
Where there is love...
there is also pain.
Shit.
Amen.
I think he must've come from the Shaolin Temple.
Let's drink!
Cheers.
Nu-Kuea.
Are you awake?
I bought snacks for you.
Look!
I'm relieved.
I'm glad that you're still alive.
I know.
I'm not dead yet.
I don't want to become a haunted doll like what Hia said.
You two haven't reconciled yet?
It's his fault.
He hasn't contacted me since last night.
He's probably dead in the office by now.
It's okay. Let's focus on this instead.
Deep-fried dough stick.
And congee from your favorite restaurant.
A perfect breakfast for this lovely morning breeze.
Are you possessed by a Disney princess?
I think I'm pretty normal.
But look at you.
You look so depressed it's like there's a black cloud hanging over your head.
Whoa. It's so gloomy.
Look at that.
I'll help.
Just sit still and wait.
I'll do it for you.
Why are you doing so much for me?
I'm afraid that you will burn down the whole kitchen just like the first time we met.
You'll probably starve to death if I didn't come here.
I know how to use an app to order food.
Alright.
Anyways, thank you.
I miss those times when we were in the UK.
Me too.
Damn it! Why is there smoke?
What should I do?
How do I open this?
What are you doing?
You will make the smoke detector go off.
I'm hungry.
I saw this on the table so I just...
I just want to eat it.
This is so basic. You don't know how to cook this?
When you're in Thailand, someone always cooks for you, right?
This is my first time.
First time cooking?
First time in the kitchen.
Alright. I will help you to do this then.
This should be okay.
You can eat it in five minutes.
Okay.
By the way, my name is Kuea.
Kuea.
Kuea Keerati.
You're the famous young master, Kuea Keerati?
I'm not famous.
Who told you that?
You are descended from a very old aristocratic family.
I remember it on the TV that they looked for the treasure from the Ayutthaya period at the Keerati Mansion.
That belongs to my grandpa.
But I live in there too.
What about you? What's your name?
Kon-Diao.
No, I'm not living alone.
No. I mean, my name is "Kon-Diao," not as in "alone."
Sai-Prik-Mai.
Your name is weird.
Your surname is weird too.
I mean, "Sai-Prik-Mai" as in "do you want to put in the chili sauce?"
Oh.
Of course!
No one in the world would have Sai-Prik-Mai as a surname.
Yeah.
Here.
Put the chili sauce too.
Okay.
Kuea!
Are you going to eat?
Wow.
You can do this much?
I just put everything I bought on a plate.
Can you come marry me instead?
I don't want to marry Hia Lian anymore.
Are you crazy? God will punish us!
How can I live alone for the rest of my life?
Come back to your senses first.
You have to decide first whether you will call off the engagement or not.
Look at that. You're still wearing the engagement ring.
I will take it off after we officially end our engagement.
I will definitely call of the engagement.
I will never go back to him.
There will be no more Kuea Keerati who's crazy in love.
I don't care about Hia Lian anymore.
I will remove my engagement status with Hia Lian.
I'll let the whole world condemn me if I go back to Hia Lian.
Shit!
Dude.
What?
Hia Lian called me last night. Three missed calls!
You should call him back immediately!
He must be really angry at me.
What should I do?
I don't want to get involved.
I know now.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
If you win, I will call him back.
If I win, I will not call.
Let's do it.
Rock, paper, and scissors!
You're really not going to call me back, Nu-Kuea?
Are you sure you're going to do this?
I am sure.
I guess.
I just don't want to force anyone.
Then you have to be patient
and be strong.
Thank you for worrying about me.
Thanks for listening to me whine last night.
Oh right.
Did Hia Yi scold you for coming back late?
Nope.
Hia Yi likes to pretend that he's fierce.
But actually, he never scolds me.
Then why are you so afraid of him?
Don't you think it's scarier when he's like that?
It makes me feel obligated all the time.
He's so scary.
That's so him, Phayak Chen.
Exactly.
And last night...
When I got back home.
I'm home, Hia.
He went right back to his condo.
Why did he come back home then?
Hia Yi and Hia Lian are so confusing.
Why do they have to act all mysterious and hard to figure out?
Kuea...
Huh?
Can I ask you something?
Did you two...
do "it" yet?
What do you mean?
I've never!
Have you?
I've never done such a thing.
As for me...
It only goes that far.
My crazy-in-love corner.
It's not that I don't want to do it.
But I think he respects me.
He's probably waiting until we get married.
Don't you ever want to...
hold his hand?
Or kiss him?
Kiss?
Yeah.
Well...
I guess I do sometimes.
The weather is lovely, isn't it?
This place is nice too.
The decorations are also very beautiful.
It reminds me when I was in the UK.
Do you like...
Is this the 'magic moment' between us?
It's finally time, right?
I should give him my first kiss.
Kiss me, Hia.
I'm ready.
Nu-Kuea, you should walk carefully.
This close...
But it was just a short moment. It comes and goes.
I'm sad that I missed that chance.
But it's okay.
I can wait.
But right now...
I don't even know what I'm waiting for.
Maybe...
This is the real reason.
What do you mean?
The reason they've never shown us that they love us
is because they don't.
That's why they never act caring towards us.
You're crazy.
You're thinking too much.
I saw you calling off the engagement last night.
And I can't stop thinking about my own situation.
I think both of us shouldn't be alone.
How about you come with me?
Since I can't practice music today anyway.
Where are we going?
We haven't eaten anything yet.
I will go surrender myself.
Young master Kuea Keerati! Where have you been all night?
Why didn't you tell me that you're going to stay over at that house?!
Do you know how worried I was!? I couldn't sleep because you didn't even pick up my phone calls!
I was going to call the police!
I'm so sorry!
I was so tired last night. I fell asleep right away.
Mrs. Kewarin told me to take good care of you.
What if something happens to you?
My head would be chopped right off!
You're the best auntie ever!
Is there anything to eat today?
Do you know how much I missed your cooking when I was in the UK?
Can you cook something for Kon-Diao and I today?
Please, auntie Ja?
Please?
Young master, I'm too old already. My cooking is not as good as before.
You're not old at all!
I've never eaten any Thai food that tastes as good as yours.
Please, auntie Ja.
Aww, my young master.
Of course. How can I say no?
But it has to be for dinner because I have to buy ingredients first, alright?
Young master Diao.
Please stay for dinner.
Of course!
I will do my very best!
I don't have a lot of time, I should go now!
Okay, auntie Ja. I will wait for your cooking!
Me too!
Goodbye...
My beloved high-end brands.
Don't you feel sad that you have to donate all these clothes?
I am.
But I don't want to be the young master Nu-Kuea Keerati that Hia likes anymore.
From now on, I will just be Kuea.
Kuea, the drummer, the singer, the biker.
Be the person I want to be.
I understand what you're trying to say.
But look at all these clothes.
They're all in good condition.
And they're all very expensive, too.
If there's any that you like, you can have it.
Mr. Lian.
Mr. Lian!
Here's the summary of the problem yesterday.
Foei.
Did Nu-Kuea say something while you drove him home last night?
You asshole!
What?
Let me explain this to you. I was driving quite fast.
The road was very dark.
I thought a person was coming out of nowhere.
And something did!
It was a dog!
The first thing that came right into my mind was to figure out its breed.
Was it a Dalmatian? Or maybe a Bangkaew?
Turns out it was actually a Poodle!
It ran out in front of the car, so I had to slam on the breaks.
I turned around to check on young master Kuea.
And then young master Kuea said...
You asshole.
That's it, sir. I'm sorry, sir!
Okay.
Okay...
It's Saturday. You can go back early.
And do not tell anyone about what happened last night.
It will ruin the image of young master Kuea Keerati.
Yes, sir.
You even called me an asshole, Nu-Kuea?
I don't think you can completely get rid of the young master Nu-Kuea inside of you.
It's just too much.
At least I have to try.
I don't want to be the young master Nu-Kuea Keerati anymore.
But you're still Nu-Kuea in auntie Ja's, your mom's, and your dad's eyes.
You're right.
But I don't have to pretend or try so hard like when I'm with Hia.
What about that picture?
You don't want to keep it anymore?
I don't think you two can be apart,
even if you guys break up.
Being Nu-Kuea is still a part of who you are.
You can't throw away or donate that side of you.
'My fiancé.'
Your fiancé is calling you.
Ex-fiancé.
I should change his name now.
Are you going to pick up the phone?
No.
He just wants to hear that I'm still okay.
Not that he cares.
But since we're no longer engaged.
He doesn't have to do this anymore.
You're so naughty, Nu-Kuea.
Same table tonight.
Book it for me.
I know you already have a band playing tonight...
but can Kirin join too?
Well yeah, of course you can.
But the problem is...
you use so much time to set up the stage more than any other band.
Today.
No, not today.
I mean from now on, there's no need to do that.
What?
Don't tell me that you're going to reveal yourself?
That's right.
I will stop hiding behind the curtains.
I'm going to be myself.
You're not afraid that your fiancé will find out?
I don't have a fiancé anymore.
I already called off the engagement.
What?
Didn't you just go on a date with him the other day?
Things have changed.
Kiddo.
Aren't you being too hotheaded?
You should think carefully about revealing yourself.
All the secrets that you've kept...
Everything you've kept hidden will end right here.
That's right, Kuea.
Think carefully.
Don't be too impulsive.
I don't care anymore.
The reason that I keep everything a secret
is because I'm afraid that Hia will find out.
But right now...
I just want to sing.
I just want to be myself.
And I also want to know that if I reveal myself...
will anyone recognize me?
Will they still want to find out...
who Kirin is?
How about this?
You just do whatever you want tonight.
And after the show, I'll buy you guys some drinks.
Okay?
What?
Where is Kon-Diao?
How am I supposed to know?
You're calling me but asking for him?
Whatever. I can't contact Nu-Kuea, so I thought they might be together.
I don't know.
I don't keep tabs on Kon-Diao's whereabouts all day like you do to Kuea.
Thanks for being useless.
What the hell is wrong with him?
Why is he taking it out on me?
Whatever. I can't contact Nu-Kuea, so I thought they might be together.
♪ No matter how much I've changed, you're still the same ♪
♪ No matter how hard I try, nothing changes ♪
Doesn't he sound just like Kirin?
I think you're right. It must be him!
♪ No matter how hard I try, nothing changes ♪
I think you're right. It must be him.
♪ Even if I do better than this ♪
♪ Even if I do everything you want me to do ♪
♪ It seems that I can never please you ♪
♪ You said that I'm not good enough for you ♪
♪ But is the real reason is you already have someone else? ♪
♪ If you no longer love me ♪
♪ If that is the real reason ♪
♪ There is only one thing that I want to change ♪
♪ I will change to love someone who loves me ♪
♪ I will change to love someone who cares for me ♪
♪ So that my heart will not get hurt ♪
♪ My heart will not be in pain ♪
♪ There will be no more tears ♪
♪ I will change to love someone who loves me ♪
♪ and accepts me for who I am ♪
♪ I won't feel tired and worthless ♪
♪ It will be easier for me to love someone else ♪
♪ Things that used to be good are now bad ♪
♪ I just want to know if you ever love me ♪
♪ If you have forgotten everything that we used to do together ♪
♪ There is only one thing that I want to change ♪
♪ I will change to love someone who loves me ♪
♪ I will change to love someone who cares for me ♪
♪ So that my heart will not get hurt ♪
♪ My heart will not be in pain ♪
♪ There will be no more tears ♪
♪ I will change to love someone who loves me ♪
♪ and accepts me for who I am ♪
♪ I won't feel tired and worthless ♪
♪ It will be easier for me to love someone else ♪
♪ If you have something to say, say it to me now ♪
♪ Don't make me aimlessly change myself for nothing ♪
♪ I want to love someone who loves me ♪
♪ I want to love someone who cares for me ♪
Hello, Hia.
I'm helping Kuea at the moment.
Helping him do what?
I'm helping him pack some clothes.
For the whole day?
There are a lot of clothes.
But I will be back within thirty minutes.
Good.
I'm waiting at home.
Huh? How come?
Usually you don't come back home on Saturdays.
I can come back whenever I want. This is my house.
Okay, Hia.
I will be back soon.
Should I ask him?
Ask him!
Are you Kirin?
Yes.
I am Kirin.
Kirin is the mask that I used to hide myself.
But today...
I have decided to take off that mask.
My real name is Kuea.
No title.
No surname.
No fake names.
Just 'Kuea'.
This is the real me.
I hope you guys will welcome me the same way you did towards Kirin.
Kuea! I can't stay any longer! I have to go back home now!
Thank you.
(Kon-Diao is with Kuea at the Keerati Mansion.)
(Wrong.)
Kon-Diao!
You dare to lie to me nowadays?
Are you okay? You seem so drunk.
Let's dance.
Kuea.
Let's call it a day. Let's go back now.
If you don't want to be alone, you can sleepover at my house.
Please?
Hey!
How do you feel when you don't have to keep it a secret anymore?
It feels great!
I feel so good.
I can sing what I want to sing.
I can make eye contact with the audiences.
It means a lot to me.
I'm so happy for you, man.
Let's go!
It's time to celebrate.
Jay.
Um...
We have to leave now.
How come?
We already made a deal.
But...
You can go back first.
I really want to celebrate this moment.
But I'm worried about you.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm not the old Nu-Kuea who didn't even know how to cook instant noodle.
I know.
You won't be mad at me, right?
I'm not mad at you.
I know that Hia Yi cares about you.
It's not like it's his job to look after you like this.
But he does it anyway.
It's because he loves you.
Fine.
Jay, don't let him drink too much.
He becomes another person when he's drunk.
Don't worry.
I'll look after him.
You should go back now.
Okay.
Take care.
Go. Don't make Hia Yi wait for too long.
See you then.
Jay.
I'm serious.
Don't trust him when he's drunk.
Okay.
See you.
Hia...
Since when did the Keerati mansion move to Thonglor?
It's-
Go on, tell me more lies, why don't you?
I really came from Kuea's house.
But...
Kuea is still inside the club.
As for me...I will go back home now.
And why does Kuea have to come to a small club like this?
When Lian's Pentagon is right at the opposite side.
Kuea is not allowed to go inside Pentagon, Hia.
So that's why you guys are here?
You know how much I hate liars.
Don't you lie to me.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
Let's talk at home.
Cheers!
To Kuea Keerati!
Excuse me, can I have one more drink?
Just call me Kuea.
No need to mention my surname.
I'm used to it already.
Just Kuea sounds weird to me.
Or...
Should I just call you Kirin?
No.
Kirin means Qilin.
Qilin means Kilen.
Kilen is Hia Lian.
You still love him?
You know my Thai is not that good.
Kirin equals to Hia Lian.
Got that?
Fine. Okay.
You're too complicated.
Who will understand you?
I don't want to be Kirin anymore.
I just want to be Kuea.
What's wrong with being Kuea?
I'm not saying that it's bad.
I just want to help you figure out which choice is the best.
I don't want that.
I don't need your help.
Are you okay?
You seem very drunk.
Do I look drunk?
Do whatever you want then.
I don't want to fight with you anymore.
Young master Kuea.
I just told you I'm not a young master!
Okay. I know. I know.
Can I join you for a drink?
Join me?
Yeah.
You're Kirin, right?
Hey! I'm Kuea.
My name is Kuea.
Okay, okay. Let's dance.
Yeah, sure.
Come with me right now.
Who are you?
Hia...Lian.
Are you Hia Lian The Asshole?
Nah, you're not him.
You just look like him.
You look very similar to him.
Hia Lian, is that you?
Hia!
You're way too drunk.
Come with me.
No!
Who are you?
Don't touch me.
Stop being so difficult.
Come with me.
Hia...
Jay!
Jay, where are you? Help me.
Kuea Keerati!
Hia Lian?
Why are you here?
No way.
You're not him.
He'd never dress up like this.
Don't bother trying to trick me.
Let's go. I'll send you home.
I'm not going with you. You're not Hia Lian!
I didn't expect you to be this drunk.
No! I'm not going with you!
Nu-Kuea!
Nu-Kuea.
Where are we going?
I'm not going to go with you.
Nu-Kuea, walk carefully and don't push me.
Don't call me Nu-Kuea!
Only Hia can call me that!
What do you want me to call you?
Anything!
Except 'Nu-Kuea.'
What about...
Annabelle.
Annabelle...
Don't call me that.
I hate it!
Why are you smiling?
Don't laugh at me.
Stop it!
You don't like it when I smile?
No.
I don't want to fall for you.
Do not flirt with me!
You don't want to like me?
No.
I don't want to like you anymore.
You're a bad person.
Don't think that I will like you just because you look like Hia.
But I want to flirt with you.
Are you Hia Lian?
You sound like him.
You smell like him too.
No way!
It can't be.
You must be a top-grade replica.
I thought this kind of situation only exists in dramas.
You're talking nonsense now.
Let's go.
I'll send you home.
Where are you taking me?
Where are we going?
Let's go.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Young master Kuea, this way.
What's wrong with you? What's gotten into you?
Should we go straight to his house?
No! You can't!
I can't go back home!
Auntie Ja will tell my mom.
She will also tell Hia.
Go to my secret house.
Can you tell me the way?
Here.
Take a look for yourself.
'The dragon's lair'?
That's right.
Foei.
Yes, sir.
You have the same ring as Hia?
You must be Hia.
But it can't be.
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever wanted to hug me?
Have you ever wanted to kiss me?
Nu-Kuea...
You don't love me...
That's why you've never wanted to do that, right?
Why don't you ever love me?
Can't you love me just a little bit?
Just a bit is enough for me.
Why?
Why don't you love me?
I want you to love me.
I've always been a good boy.
I want to marry you.
But why don't you want to marry me?
Why don't you love me?
I love you so much.
I didn't want to call off the engagement.
Can you love me back?
You can just pretend to love me.
♪ Love ♪
♪ Just tell me that you love me ♪
♪ Is it too hard to do that? ♪
♪ How you feel? ♪
♪ What am I to you? ♪
♪ Am I special to you? Or I'm just nothing ♪
♪ How much do I mean to you? ♪
♪ How you feel? ♪
♪ If there's me inside your heart ♪
Diao, do you know how I got back to my secret house last night?
Did you talk to Hia Lian yet?
I will be busted if I asked him that!
Where were you yesterday?
I will not put up with this anymore!
Kirin. Qilin. The dragon's lair.
What else are you hiding from me?
I can't let this go on.
But I vaguely remember...
I met a guy who looked exactly like Hia Lian.
Are you actually Hia Lian?
Nu-Kuea, you should sleep.
What are you going to do if it's actually him?