♪Mysterious person, don't ask for now♪
♪First, disguise and behave♪
♪The eyes of love are probing♪
♪Revealing the tension♪
♪Impatience also requires waiting♪
♪Countless possibilities
have confirmed♪
♪This identity♪
♪Intricate clues have stirred up♪
♪That restless mind♪
♪Mind reader, read the lips,
read the dreams, read the souls♪
♪We have become one♪
♪Turn around,
guess confidently, guess accurately♪
♪Guess who I am, the game score♪
♪Mind reader, read the lips,
read the dreams, read the souls♪
♪Tell me, who will ultimately win?♪
♪Without contention,
how will we recognize who we are?♪
[Guess Who I Am]
[Adapted from Yi Jin's original novel
"Hao, Please Don't Be Friends with Me"]
Song Yao!
Hello?
I want you to sign an agreement
to not hold me accountable for all this.
Once I get far away
from here,
I'll tell you
where they are.
[Episode 17]
Song Yao.
Wake up.
Qin Hao?
Why are you here?
Don't be scared.
I am here.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Don't move.
The more you struggle,
the more this rope will hurt you.
What should we do then?
Wait.
I felt a piece of iron.
Come on.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What is this place?
Anyone there?
Anyone?
Anyone out there?
There's a door.
Anyone there?
Open the door!
Anyone hear us?
Hello?
[Ji Honglin]
I'll find a way
to contact Kang Liping immediately.
No matter what Kang Liping wants,
she'll be satisfied.
Got it.
Before we find Mr. Ji,
we won't do anything rash.
I've already called the police.
We'll do our best
to cooperate with the police.
We can't afford any mistakes.
Dad!
Good news.
Kang Liping, that traitor, is dead.
[Chengtian Group's Whistleblower
Found Dead in Hotel]
Mr. Ji,
Now no one knows
where Mr. Ji and Ms. Song are.
What should we do now?
We'll assist the police
in their search.
Okay.
My phone.
Find them...
You go, as well.
Anyone there?
Help!
Hang on.
We're probably not far from the sea.
Yes.
We're supposed to be
at a container terminal.
It's 2:48 AM.
Let's wait until the sun comes up.
Since there will be more people by then,
people are more likely
to hear us knocking on the door.
Okay.
According to the worst-case scenario,
we'll have to find them
within 64 hours.
Otherwise,
they won't be able to make it.
Any clues?
I went through
the surveillance footage
provided by the amusement park.
This vehicle is the most suspicious.
The license plate
was also deliberately covered.
This van is too common.
It'd be hard to track it.
From what I know,
Ms. Kang
only had an Audi A5.
This vehicle is probably a rental.
I will contact
car rental companies
in the east of the city.
Leave the west of the city to me.
I'll let the police know.
Wei.
Go.
Get me the red wine
my uncle
opened last month.
Mr. Ji.
That bottle is treasured by Mr. Chen.
He himself is unwilling to drink it.
I'm telling you to go and get it.
Cut the crap.
I'm the one who's my uncle's treasure.
Go get it!
Don't give it to him!
Uncle...
Go do your thing.
Don't you know the situation right now?
You're still drinking here?
Uncle.
Well,
Ji Chengchuan is about to die anyway.
Right?
I
am going to be
the company's first heir.
You idiot.
Now is the time
for you to project yourself.
You need to go back
and help your dad look for them.
Uncle.
You're right. I'll go right away.
Wait.
I'm telling you to help them,
but not actually do it.
Look for them.
Pretend you are looking for them.
Kang Liping is dead anyway.
Nobody knows
where they are.
Go to your dad
and pretend you're doing something.
Keep them busy.
Got it.
Qin Hao.
Do you think we'll die?
No.
Don't be scared.
I won't let you die.
Who said I was scared?
I'm sorry.
This happened all because of me.
We are partners.
No need to say sorry.
Do you think
they are looking for us?
Of course.
Don't you trust Shen Shuangshuang
and Gu Zijun?
I don't know about that.
Normally,
at this moment,
they've packed their bags
and gone to the train station
getting ready to run away.
According to you,
Jiang Nanxuan would already be
on the plane
flying to another country.
Don't worry.
Trust them.
Just a glance, sir.
I told you.
We can't check this.
Just a quick glance, sir. Please.
I'm off work. Shop's closed.
Just a glance, okay?
Shop is closed!
You...
Don't you know what "closed" means?
[Shunda Car Dealership]
Hello.
This is a car rental agency, right?
Could you tell me if you rented out
a Jinbei Haise recently.
Sorry, we didn't.
Sir.
Could I take a look
at your surveillance footage?
I'm busy.
Sure, follow me.
This way.
Hi.
May I know if you rented out
a Jinbei Haise recently?
Sorry, we didn't.
Okay, thanks.
I've given you the account
of our dealership's surveillance system.
You can take a look yourself.
Hello, is this a car rental agency?
Could you tell me
if you rented out a Jinbei Haise
recently?
No.
Thank you.
Open up!
Anyone out there?
- Anyone there?
- Open the door!
Anybody?
Can anyone hear us?
Anyone?
Help!
Anyone there?
Help us.
Hello, Ms. Kang.
The Jinbei Haise commercial van
that you rented from our company
three days ago
has been issued
a traffic violation at the entrance
of Jianghai Port.
You're required
to go to
the Traffic Management Bureau
with your driving license
and pay the fine within 15 working days.
Have a good day.
Thank you.
Have a good day too.
Song Yao.
Don't fall asleep.
I'm so sleepy.
Don't sleep.
Let's...
Let's play a game.
Okay?
What game?
Truth or Dare.
Okay.
When was the happiest time
of your life so far?
It was the time when I was young
living on Yuzhou Island.
What about your unhappiest time?
Definitely the time when you dragged me
to get the marriage license.
Then
do you regret meeting me?
Of course...
not.
Don't fall asleep.
I'll just sleep for a while.
Hang in there.
Don't sleep.
Long, long ago...
Yes.
Song Yao.
Do you know
why I asked you to come
to the amusement park yesterday?
That was the last
car rental agency.
We still couldn't find any clues.
It's been 50 hours.
What should we do
if we still can't find anything?
We must have missed something.
I've talked to the police.
They haven't got any clues either.
Wait!
I think I've found it.
Look.
There is a row
of annual inspection marks
on the windshield.
There's no reflection in the middle,
meaning one's missing.
This is the car.
You must be Conan.
No kidding.
Shuang managed to pinpoint
the car
where her favorite idol was in
among over 30 same vehicles.
Awesome, idolater.
Okay.
Yeah.
You can go ahead and check it.
Can you restore it?
It shouldn't be a problem.
Although the records were cleared,
all car navigations are linked
to a satellite positioning system.
Once we locate one position,
we'll be able to restore all the tracks
through the BeiDou System.
Found it.
I'll notify the police right away.
The police, ambulance and Sheng Silin
will be here soon.
Let's help find them.
Okay.
Guys.
Follow my lead.
Each of you is responsible for one zone
and do a blanket search.
Understand?
Yes!
Go, go, go!
Song Yao.
Song Yao!
Rescuers are here.
They're coming.
Song Yao!
Yao!
- Song Yao!
- Yao!
Qin Hao!
Hao!
Not found in Zone A.
Not found in Zone B either.
Not found in Zone C either.
Qin Hao!
Yao!
Song Yao!
Qin Hao.
Hao!
Song Yao!
Hey,
boss said there's something going on
in Zone B, No.13.
Nothing was there.
Just a few rats.
Wait for me to go back
and play cards.
Hurry up!
There's something in Zone B.
Hurry!
Attention, guys.
In Zone F07,
there's smoke coming out
from a container.
Everyone meet at Zone F07.
Repeat...
Over there.
Qin Hao...
Qin Hao!
What are you laughing at?
I was afraid you'd die.
Thanks to you,
I am still alive.
Are you feeling sick?
No.
I'm as strong as a horse.
That's great.
We are both alive.
Yeah, pretty nice.
Your savior is here.
Ji Chengchuan, get up.
Let Song Yao lie down.
She's not well yet.
Let her rest.
Is that
how you treat your savior?
Song Yao.
As the one who saved your life,
I'll just give in a little more.
I'll devote my life to you.
Chengchuan.
Mr. Ji.
We'll leave you to it.
We'll leave first.
Sit down, please.
How are you feeling?
I'm pretty well now.
Don't worry.
Get well first.
Take care of yourself.
As for Kang Liping,
I'll make it up to you.
Let's have a talk.
Sure.
Have a seat.
Do you like me?
What about now?
You don't like me that much right?
So,
you don't really like me.
Wait a minute.
You...
Take off the glasses.
Let me feel it again.
Are you a fairy coming from heaven
down to earth?
Take care of yourself.
See you.
Chengchuan.
I'm here to visit you.
I've heard
Kang Liping
was targeting Song Yao.
You are implicated.
I told you
Song Yao's of unknown origin.
She's not a good person.
But you wouldn't listen.
Who knows
what did she get herself into this time?
Shut up!
This is my last warning.
Don't ever speak ill of my wife again.
But...
I'm just worried about you.
Liang Jingyi.
You have too much time huh?
Hello?
Hey, Jingyi.
Where are you?
School's about to start, right?
Listen,
tomorrow,
I'll get someone
to take you to the airport.
I'm telling you this
because I regard you as a friend.
Keep it a secret.
I knew it.
How could a god like me
fall in love with you?
You're just a normal girl.
Thank you.
So, don't pester me anymore.
Sure.
Why are you eavesdropping, Mr. Ji?
Thanks.
Is this all you have to say
to your savior?
From now on, we're friends.
Who wants to be your friend?
Don't forget.
I am always your savior.
What?
Wait...
Mr. Sheng.
I just wanted to say thank you.
What?
You...
Sheng Silin.
How could you bully a patient?
I...
I did not.
I was just...
Wait...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's go.
I just
gently...
Ji Chengchuan.
You're behaving like a jealous man.
You must be feeling tired.
You should rest early.
Get some sleep.
Stay with me.
I'm going to rest in my own room.
I...I've got a headache.
I've got a headache.
Let me do a massage for you.
Okay.
Here.
Well,
Why are you in such a hurry
to leave the hospital?
You're not fully well yet.
I don't like the smell of disinfectant
in the hospital.
Besides...
What?
Sheng Silin went there every day.
I only want you to take care of me.
Okay.
Mr. Chen,
I've gone through the medical records.
This person should be
suffering from severe PTSD.
The main trigger is fire.
I recommend
that he get professional psychiatric help
as soon as possible.
Got it.
Thanks, Dr. Wang.
Ji Chengchuan
is about to join the board of directors.
You need to take action.
Yaqin.
Honglin made the arrangement.
What can I do?
Medium rare.
Perfect.
Any news about Kang Liping?
The killer's methods were spotless.
There were no clues left behind
at the scene.
But the police
have investigated from other sources.
Her death was too strange.
I think
it's closely related to
what happened 15 years ago.
Come in.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Chairman asked me
to give this to you.
He said
[Chengtian Group]
this is how he makes up to you.
Thanks.
What is it?
Looks like Ji Honglin
will be appointing me
as a member of the board of directors
at the annual meeting.
I suppose it's his way
to pacify me.
I will make use of this chance
to join the board
and find out
to whom the cuff link belongs.
I think we are very close to the truth.
[2021 Chengtian Group
Corporation Annual Meeting]
Are those two
Mr. Ji and his wife?
They're really popular
on the web lately.
Mr. Ji.
- Mr. Chen.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to Chengtian Group's
annual grand event.
First, let's welcome
the Chairman,
Mr. Ji Honglin, to the stage
to perform the long-time tradition
of Chengtian,
which is to light up the beacon
representing Chengtian's bright future.
Please.
Honglin.
Since you're planning
to nominate Chengchuan as a partner,
why don't you invite him
to light up the beacon together?
It's a chance for him
to be formally introduced.
You're so kind, Uncle.
Chengchuan.
♪Hiding on the rooftop
nearest to the night sky♪
♪You ask if we can
be considered deserters♪
♪Drinking neon-toned whiskey♪
♪Is it the moonlight
or can't we distinguish it?♪
♪Drink to my long-hidden concern♪
♪Drink because I'm not happy♪
♪The city pretending to sleep
takes off its mask♪
♪Finally, I find the most real you♪
♪Guessing while intoxicated
which star you belong to♪
♪I'll try to pick it and give it to you♪
♪Now it's your turn to guess
which star I came from♪
♪Did I save the Milky Way
in the past life?♪
♪The night wind
brings us closer together♪
♪You ask if shooting stars have secrets♪
♪Is the moon pretending to be awake?♪
♪Just like me, just like you,
inconsistent inside and out♪
♪A pair of eyes that are discerning♪
♪A garment adorned with stars and moons♪
♪The sleeping city steals dreams♪
♪I've accidentally entered your game♪
♪Guessing with sincerity
which star you belong to♪
♪I'll try to polish it
and give it to you♪
♪Guess with your true heart,
which star I come from♪
♪In the past life,
I must have saved the Milky Way♪