♪Mysterious person, don't ask for now♪
♪First, disguise and behave♪
♪The eyes of love are probing♪
♪Revealing the tension♪
♪Impatience also requires waiting♪
♪Countless possibilities have confirmed♪
♪This identity♪
♪Intricate clues have stirred up♪
♪That restless mind♪
♪Mind reader, read the lips,
read the dreams, read the souls♪
♪We have become one♪
♪Turn around, guess confidently,
guess accurately♪
♪Guess who I am, the game score♪
♪Mind reader, read the lips,
read the dreams, read the souls♪
♪Tell me, who will ultimately win?♪
♪Without contention,
how will we recognize who we are?♪
[Guess Who I Am]
[Adapted from Yi Jin's original novel
"Hao, Please Don't Be Friends with Me"]
How can I make Song Yao
change her opinion of me
if I don't make sacrifices?
We must have a long-term plan.
Step by step
I'll gain his trust.
Only by earning her trust
could we
find what we want.
I'm sending you home.
[Justice Committee]
His data is everywhere at home.
[Special Operations Team]
If he saw it, I'd be done for.
I'm heading to Song Yao's place.
Pay attention and provide assistance.
[Episode 4]
Come on.
I'm online.
Bros,
I will show you today
the most epic Yunlu equipment
in the world.
How about that?
Not bad, right?
I'm flying like a dragon in the sky.
[Justice Committee]
Who was that?
Gu Zijun, do you have a death wish?
That's right.
Wait for me.
Yes.
Support me.
[Song Yao]
JCC is coming.
JCC?
Jiang Nanchen?
[Ji Chengchuan]
Ji Chengchuan?
Goodness!
Oh, no!
What is he here for?
Curses, Song Yao.
You can really cause trouble for me.
What else?
[Two Days to D-Day]
[Qiao's daily schedule]
Here.
It's okay.
I already feel much better.
It's all right, I'll help you.
Our house may be a little messy.
Gu Zijun, you better put in some effort.
If those documents aren't hidden well,
we will be totally screwed.
It's all right, I won't mind.
Let's go.
Look at how thoughtful Hao is.
I almost fell in love with him.
See?
I told you that you're not fine yet.
Let's go upstairs and take the medicine.
Look.
I just bought this painting.
What do you think?
Help yourself.
I'm going to drink some water.
Get out of here quickly.
Where should I go?
Anywhere will do.
Don't get in my way.
So dizzy.
What's wrong?
I told you that you're not fine yet.
You're right.
Quick, sit down.
What is that?
He used to be
my friend's idol.
But his image is now ruined.
She can't bear to see him anymore.
She likes him now.
Weren't you dizzy just now?
Yeah.
I always suffer from this.
It comes and goes.
I can feel it again now.
I'll get you some warm water
so you can take your medicine.
What's the matter?
My head hurts.
Here.
Take the medicine.
Sit there.
Come on.
Thanks.
What's the matter with you?
Why don't you sit down and rest?
Sure.
What was that noise?
Our area has a lot of stray cats.
That was a cat.
Wait...
Isn't that Song Yao's follower?
Get out of the car.
Why?
We can't let him go up
and bother Qin Hao.
I'll deal with him.
Come on, get out.
Keep an eye on the entrance.
Don't let anyone in.
Get out of the car now.
Okay...
Close the door.
At critical moments,
we still have to rely on Ling.
She's tough but doesn't say much.
Hello, miss.
We are temporarily closed today.
Sorry about that.
This, this,
and this,
wrap them all up for me.
Miss,
all the flowers you chose
are no longer fresh.
Did I say I wanted fresh flowers?
I happen to like dried flowers.
Your interest is quite unique.
Wrap them all up for me.
Thanks.
Sure.
Your outfit
is quite unique too.
Why isn't he leaving yet?
I'm a little tired.
I should get some rest.
I'm worried
about leaving you home alone.
You go ahead and rest.
I'll keep you company here.
You've been here for so long,
I haven't even got you a glass of water.
I'll make you some tea.
It's all right.
Aren't you still feeling unwell?
I'm fine.
I'll splash him with water.
I refuse to believe
that he won't go home to get changed.
Is chrysanthemum tea all right?
Yes.
Watch out.
How did he catch that?
Miss,
your bouquet is ready.
Thank you.
Can you help me carry it to my car?
What's the matter?
Does this flower shop not
provide this service?
Nonsense.
Which store gets their clerk
to go outside dressed like this?
This lady is gorgeous.
Who would've thought
that she was a wolf in sheep's clothing?
Forget it.
It's important
to get her to leave immediately.
Of course we do.
The customer is always right.
Great.
Let's go.
Look, you've had the tea.
Well...
Can you get me coffee?
I'm not used to drinking this.
Sure.
Where have I
seen this person before?
[Shen Shuangshuang,
Song Yao's capable assistant]
[Good at disguising]
Goodness.
[Different professional personnel]
Isn't this Song Yao's friend?
[Shen Shuangshuang]
Why is she back?
No,
I can't let her get in to ruin things.
You...
What?
Don't you have eyes?
I was standing right in front of you,
yet you still bumped into me.
I'm going to kill you!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Here!
Why are you resorting to violence?
I'll compensate you.
Here's 500.
It's all right to scold me.
Do you think this is only worth 500?
Do you know how I got this?
I caught the first subway train
and queued for one whole day in the cold
to buy this.
Do you think this can be settled
with just 500 yuan?
How long?
One whole day?
Girl,
you are being disrespectful
towards time.
Do you know what I could do
in one whole day?
That's a long time.
Let me check.
Look,
my financial products
already helped me make
372.56 yuan today.
Just this amount?
I find happiness in pursuing my idol.
What do I get from managing my finances?
You can get
372.56 yuan.
Please be gentle.
Handle it with care.
I'm going to give this bouquet
to someone very important.
Sending a bouquet of dried flowers
to someone very important?
Is she visiting someone's grave?
You...
Look.
The same exact one
is only worth 40 yuan.
Your happiness is worth 40 yuan.
However, if you invest,
the joy you obtain is
nine times
or even more.
What do you think?
Isn't it a sudden enlightenment?
Do you also plan to
get into financial education
to gain nine times the happiness?
No.
I want to use this happiness
to buy your life!
[Little Bee - The Pro]
I have sent Ji Chengchuan's
newest information to you by fax.
I can't let her get in.
Wait.
What's with your attitude?
♪Oh, there's a little troublemaker♪
You jerk!
I'll show you
what true happiness is.
I was wrong.
Not the face!
Stop beating my face!
Ji Chengchuan's information
will be sent today.
Chengchuan, your coffee.
Sure.
Thanks.
It turns out that the necklace
is on Yuzhou Island.
I haven't been back
to Yuzhou Island in a long time.
How about
we go back for a visit tomorrow?
If I go back with him,
the risk of exposing myself
seems a bit high.
However,
it seems that he's missed the place.
Perhaps...
It's all right if you don't want to.
I actually quite want to go back.
Wait.
Doesn't returning to Yuzhou Island
mean that
we're revisiting old places
and recalling past memories
that might stir up emotions.
When the atmosphere is up,
I might get the necklace.
All right, let's go.
Laugh if you want to.
Jiang Nanxuan,
you have put yourself into
your investment, huh?
How dare you make fun of me?
Song Yao's follower's face
was flushed red
at the florist's entrance just now.
He was acting shy
like a newly-wed.
Tell me.
What have you done to him?
Qin Hao, how's it going?
Any new clues?
Gu Zijun,
do you have any idea
that I just met a pervert?
Are you listening to me?
Do you believe in fate?
I do.
I believe in karmic fate.
I had a feeling just now.
It was like being struck
by Cupid's arrow.
With a snap, I was hit.
Miss, relax.
Don't be afraid.
Jerk!
This can't be patched up at all.
What's wrong with the neck?
Someone ripped it apart.
I'll help you pull it.
[The Intelligent Investor]
[Pressure sensitive tape]
[One Day to D-Day]
Yao,
today is already the last day
of the mission.
If we can't complete it, we can't answer
to the client.
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
No matter how well Ji Chengchuan
conceals himself,
he remains a jerk.
Don't get soft.
Hao,
I won't accompany you this time.
I'm still recovering
from the injury I suffered yesterday.
It hurts so badly.
I guess this counts as
a work-related injury, right?
Qin Hao,
the last return ferry ride
from Yuzhou Island
is at 8 PM today.
You have to get the necklace
before then.
The agreement will be signed
tomorrow morning.
Don't worry.
[Boat Jie Fu]
We've arrived.
Here.
Careful.
How long has it been
since you last came back?
A long time ago.
It's still the same here.
Nothing has changed.
Let's go.
Hurry, get on the boat.
All right.
The small town
only had one park at that time.
All the children came here to play.
It should be right to bring him here.
I always came here to play
when I was a kid.
I didn't expect it
to turn out like this.
Her eyes
lingered on this swing the longest
while she was speaking.
This swing, especially.
I remember it's your favorite.
I guessed it right.
That was the only swing.
We had to fight
to take turns to play on it.
Fight to take turns?
I still remember
you couldn't beat anyone else
every time.
Nonsense.
I used to be
a thug who oppressed
the old folks' homes
and kindergartens in town,
all right?
I never could get it.
Careful.
What a coincidence.
Stop telling me
that we met by chance again.
Of course not.
I came here
specifically to find the goddess.
How did you know I was here?
Don't bother,
I am Sheng Silin.
This guy
just won't give up.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Can I tag along?
If he's following,
something bad's bound to happen.
We're going there
to get something to eat
because we're heading out to sea soon.
Our boat ride is 4 PM,
and we already got the tickets.
There's only one trip per day.
Right, Chengchuan?
There are not many tickets left.
You should hurry and get a ticket
if you want to join it.
The dock is right there.
I'll get a ticket right now.
See you on the boat later.
See you.
Sure.
Bye.
Sir?
Sit down.
My friends haven't arrived yet.
The boat has left the dock. Sit down.
Wait, we...
Sit down now.
I'm serious, my friends aren't here yet.
Wait for us!
Why is the boat leaving already?
Sir, stop the boat.
My friends have arrived!
It's all right, you go first!
Call me!
No...
Don't worry.
We'll find you.
Sir, please stop.
Bye!
Let's go, I'll take you somewhere.
Sir?
Sir,
can you send me
to the other side of the shore?
That'll be 100 yuan.
Fine.
How about this?
I'll pawn my clothes for you.
A tailor from Paris, France
customized it just for me.
There is only one set of this
in the world.
[Guchi Village]
How about this?
Sir,
do you have a phone?
Let me use your phone.
I'll just make one phone call.
Thank you...
Siqi,
help me.
Wait for me here.
I knew it. It's still here.
When I was young,
I used to love sneaking over here.
My mother thought it was too dangerous,
so I hid the key here.
Keep it a secret for me.
Go on in.
Ji Chengchuan's childhood name
was Zhuang.
[Jiang Nanxuan]
You're not done yet?
The last ferry ride
is
in two hours.
If you missed it, it would be too late.
When I was young,
my mom was very busy working.
Thus, she always left me alone at home.
I was terrified.
Then, my mom...
However, once the light
of the lighthouse
shone into my home,
I stopped being scared.
There.
That's my home.
I happen to have left something
at home.
Can you come with me?
Sure.
My home is up there.
Wait for me here.
I'll go up to retrieve something.
Sure.
What happened to Mom?
She had a car accident.
She is being treated
at the hospital now.
We hope
that an adult can bring you here.
I...
We... We don't have
any other adults here.
I'm thinking about
my childhood.
The feeling of
opening the door
and not seeing Mom there
is really painful.
But you don't understand.
I actually do.
Really?
[Jiang Nanxuan]
Hao, how's it going?
Have you boarded the ferry?
[Qin Hao]
I will catch
the earliest return ferry ride tomorrow.
[Jiang Nanxuan]
Qin Hao,
we're signing the agreement tomorrow.
Do you know
what you are doing?
Do you really want to give up everything
without a fight?
Did you forget
the reason
why we returned to the country?
Of course not.
I must find the truth
behind what happened then.
When everything is over,
I will also accept
the punishment I deserve.
Yet...
♪Hiding on the rooftop
nearest to the night sky♪
♪You ask if we can
be considered deserters♪
♪Drinking neon-toned whiskey♪
♪Is it the moonlight
or can't we distinguish it?♪
♪Drink to my long-hidden concern♪
♪Drink because I'm not happy♪
♪The city pretending to sleep
takes off its mask♪
♪Finally, I find the most real you♪
♪Guessing while intoxicated
which star you belong to♪
♪I'll try to pick it and give it to you♪
♪Now it's your turn to guess
which star I came from♪
♪Did I save the Milky Way
in the past life?♪
♪The night wind
brings us closer together♪
♪You ask if shooting stars have secrets♪
♪Is the moon pretending to be awake?♪
♪Just like me, just like you,
inconsistent inside and out♪
♪A pair of eyes that are discerning♪
♪A garment adorned with stars and moons♪
♪The sleeping city steals dreams♪
♪I've accidentally entered your game♪
♪Guessing with sincerity
which star you belong to♪
♪I'll try to polish it
and give it to you♪
♪Guess with your true heart,
which star I come from♪
♪In the past life,
I must have saved the Milky Way♪