(Autumn when the foliage starts to turn vibrantly red)
Gosh, this is nice. It's from the past.
Hello.
This is Yongsan,
- Dragon Mountain. - How was your Chuseok holidays?
Yes.
What's wrong with your hair?
I tried to style it.
- Just a little... - I got compliments from everyone...
- except you. - Your hair looks very strange.
What are you talking about?
- It's a trendy style. - You must be jealous of me.
- Seok Jin... - Isn't it trendy?
He's jealous, isn't he?
Recently, Seok Jin brought up...
- Young Sixty very often. - Yes.
Now, Young Forty became a meme.
Seok Jin was wrong about what it meant.
- Really? - Yes.
- And so... - I didn't know what the meme meant.
He just jumped on the bandwagon.
(Seok Jin jumped on the bandwagon just by seeing "forty.")
And I kept calling myself Young Fifty.
It's a type of mockery, isn't it?
Why do people mock me when I try to dress young?
- I mean... - You look great.
Thank you.
(Kyung Pyo's sweet comment makes his heart melt.)
Yongsan looks great.
This is Gyeongnidan Street.
- Is this Gyeongnidan Street? - I see.
Gyeongnidan Street.
(Sixth Sense: City Tour 2)
(The sixth city)
(Yongsan)
(Yongsan, the birthplace of hip places in Seoul)
(Yongnidan Street)
(Gyeongnidan Street)
(Haebangchon)
(And...)
(A new rising hip place in Korea)
(National Museum of Korea)
(I am real.)
(Full of iconic popular places)
(How?)
(What is today's fake hidden in Yongsan?)
- I've only heard about it. - I didn't have a chance to come.
Me neither.
- Have you been here? - I come here often.
- Really? - Seriously?
I often come to this store next to us.
- Really? - Really?
- Is that so? - This is a popular place.
Is this Yongnidan Street? Mimi, you must know about it.
- Yes, but it's my first time here. - It's very popular here.
- Really? - I come to Yongsan often,
but it's my first time on Yongnidan Street.
Aren't there many restaurants here?
Yes, there are.
Instead of franchise restaurants,
there are many small, independent shops.
Unique shops and restaurants.
That's what people like.
(Yongnidan Street is full of popular places...)
(that are unique.)
This is a pizza restaurant that I go often.
- Is the pizza good? - Is it a pizza restaurant?
This place?
(Kyung Pyo's favorite pizza restaurant is also here.)
You amaze me.
- You have to be diligent. - There's a reason why...
you have a hard time losing weight.
- It will become popular... - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- So early in the morning... - What kind of place is this?
- It's a clothing company. - A clothing company?
- So that's why. - You look so stylish.
- You have a great sense of fashion. - That's why.
All of them are dressed well.
All of us are wearing matching outfits today.
- We're wearing... - Right.
- Mimi and I are... - Our outfits match perfectly.
Everything you're wearing matches.
- Yes, everything matches. - We're wearing black shoes.
Mimi, you dress very well.
- Thank you. - That's what I always think.
- Don't you choose your outfit? - Yes.
- She dresses so well. - Thank you.
- You're like her father-in-law. - Yes.
My daughter-in-law.
Do I look okay today, Father?
Yes, you look good.
"Do I look okay today, Father?"
They're each other's in-law,
but the son who connects them ran away.
- The son ran away. - There's no son.
- He doesn't come home. - He's still in the US.
- Is he in the US? - Yes.
- I didn't even know that. - You didn't?
- Hello. - Hello.
- A good day, please. - Hello.
- It's already different. - "A good day, please?"
- Whom are you asking? - Whom are you asking?
He's talking without thinking.
- A good day, please. - He's not used to doing it.
- I'm clumsy. - So he's talking carelessly.
- It's hard to force myself. - He doesn't know what to say.
Whom are you asking for a good day?
(While they're laughing at his awkward greeting)
Let's look this way.
They might not recognize us from the back.
We're two girls. They'll probably recognize us.
Let's make an acrostic poem since we're bored.
"Six."
Be quiet.
(Be quiet)
That's good.
That's a good start. You have nice energy.
- This is how you do it. - Do I have to tense the fingers?
- Yes, the tension is necessary. - I see.
- Seok Jin, don't close that. - I shouldn't?
- There's something here. - Why would you close it?
I saw the door open.
- Seok Jin is... - I'm sorry.
- Ever since he asked... - I shouldn't have closed it.
For a good day, he has lost his mind.
I'm not completely awake yet.
By the way...
Is that your bed head?
Did you style your hair last night before going to bed?
No, I didn't.
- It looks suspicious. - This morning,
- it was done by a hairstylist. - Really?
- A hairstylist styled my hair. - Is that so?
Your hair is so puffy that it makes your face look long.
Yours is so flat.
By the way...
Your hair is not puffy enough.
Until a few minutes ago, you complimented...
- on each other's looks. - You said you liked her outfit.
- Your hair isn't puffy enough. - What's gotten into you?
- Gosh, my stomach hurts. - All of a sudden...
- Yours is the opposite of mine. - after a terrible greeting...
(They go inside before it gets too late.)
- My goodness. - They're looking at the wall.
I can tell by looking at them from the back.
(Today's guests with familiar backs)
Aren't they the two sisters?
- Hello. - Hello.
(The irreplaceable queen of trusted hits)
(Their unexpected real-life sisterly chemistry...)
(captured their fans' hearts.)
(Korea's longest-running national treasure female duo)
(Davichi)
Davichi is here with us.
Davichi.
They're Korea's comedy duo.
- Yes, a comedy duo. - Yes.
- A comedy duo? - A comedy duo.
- Hello. - My gosh.
I saw Min Kyung a few times,
but I've never seen you with your hair up.
- Yes. - That's right.
Since it's an outdoor shoot,
I didn't want my hair to get in the way.
- Your hair is completely up. - It's a trendy hairstyle.
- Really? - Yes, it's one of my favorite.
- We have similar... - They have similar hairstyles.
- You pressed your hair down. - Yes, I like it.
You have similar hairstyles.
Pressing it down is trendy. Don't puff up your hair.
But your hair is too flat.
It should be slightly puffy.
What do you think? It's been a long time.
- Do I look bad? - It looks a little too puffy.
Did you hear that?
(It looks a little too puffy.)
Wasn't I right?
- It's a little... - As expected, she knows.
- Right? - She's telling the truth.
- She hasn't seen me in a long time, - Hae Ri knows.
- so she must be telling the truth. - Just a little...
What did I tell you? It looks too puffy.
When it gets humid, it will come down.
- It's okay. I like it. - Your hair...
(Mimi is satisfied.)
Davichi, are you having another concert soon?
That's right.
(Davichi came with good news.)
Our concert will be on January 24 and 25.
It's coming up soon. Please invite us.
- Please come. - Please invite us.
- Last time, Jae Seok came... - I went to their concert.
- He came last year. - The concert hall was packed.
That must be why they hold a concert every year.
- It's hard to fill up the space. - It's hard.
- It was at a gymnastics arena. - Right.
- That's big. - It was packed with audience.
- Really? - Yes.
(Last January, Davichi's 17th solo concert)
(The first female duo to perform at a gymnastics arena)
(Sold out the moment the tickets went on sale)
- The two of them are also fun. - Right.
(Glancing)
- Have you seen them? - Please come.
Me?
- It's the perfect timing. - Thank you so much.
(Smiling big)
It will be when Seok Jin turns 60.
- He won't go. - Hey.
He won't be able to deny that he's 60.
That's not true.
You've been delaying it enough.
Is there any discount on concerts?
- A discount on what? - A discount on concerts.
You mean a discount for seniors?
- Yes. - Is there? I don't think so.
You can get a senior discount when you're over 65.
(Seok Jin assumes a senior discount from the age of 65.)
Thank you. Look at that.
- Are we having yogurt this morning? - Honey.
Is this your order?
(A healthy dessert that's fresh and sweet)
- Is that Kaymak? - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It must be Kaymak.
- Is this Kaymak? - It must be Kaymak.
When you dip some bread in Kaymak...
- It's Greek yogurt. - It's Greek yogurt.
It wasn't Kaymak.
Everyone heard about it from somewhere.
- But it looks like Kaymak. - Right.
- At the end, Seok Jin... - Why was my voice...
the loudest at the end?
(As long as it's not me)
(Everyone shares a bite of the dessert.)
- This looks amazing. - Try it.
Won't we go to the restroom after eating this?
(On one side, )
(the owner stands there naturally.)
(Absent-mindedly)
Sir, do we have to pay in advance?
- Pardon? - Do we have to pay in advance?
No.
(I'm sorry?)
- I wanted to explain. - Oh, I see.
- This... - Excuse me.
What was that about? The owner...
(Feeling embarrassed for Jae Seok)
- He was standing there. - He kept standing there.
I thought...
What was that about?
- Why are you embarrassing him? - I'm sorry.
- Are you making a mistake already? - He wanted to explain to us.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
It reminded me of my past when I was in school.
- Thank you for coming. - Sure.
- It's strawberry Greek yogurt. - Greek yogurt.
- That's an acai bowl. - This is an acai bowl.
- It's yogurt called Real Honey. - It's very healthy.
I heard that you open early in the morning.
Yes, it's a bakery where we sell yogurt in the morning.
That's amazing.
(Adding to the appearance with colorful toppings)
(A popular place of healthy pleasure that's both tasty and healthy)
This place always wins first place in the food delivery application.
(Yongsan's hottest spot that Min Kyung also knows about)
Min Kyung knows about it.
(Shall I taste it?)
The acai bowl.
- Isn't it acai? - Is this...
- Acai berries? - Acai bowl.
- Are these red beans? - What's that?
- Acai. - Acai?
"Red beans?"
(Laughing)
What's so funny?
- He said... - He thought it was purple beans.
- What? - How could you call it red beans?
The owner just told us that it was an acai bowl.
(Father?)
- He doesn't listen to anything. - Gosh.
- That's refreshing. - He doesn't listen to others.
- Did he call it red beans? - He doesn't listen to others.
He only talks about himself.
They could be purple red beans.
It's been a while since Min Kyung responded so coolly like this.
When Seok Jin thought that it was red beans,
- she said, "Acai ball." - Acai.
(Cold)
Min Kyung, are you a thinker type in MBTI?
The acai bowl was mentioned about 20 times.
He called acai red beans.
Think of today as the winter solstice.
(Think of today as the winter solstice while eating.)
Enjoy it while imagining that it's red beans.
(Enjoying the acai bowl at the winter solstice)
- By the way, - They're talking in English.
- the acorn bread... - Their acorn bread is famous.
The acorn bread?
- Let's go see the acorn bread. - Okay.
- He doesn't ever get up. - You aren't going...
even though you're sitting at the end.
Mimi is the expert.
The bread...
- It's over here. It looks pretty. - Where's the tray?
This place looks like Studio Ghibli.
- Right? - Yes.
(A cute, cartoon-like atmosphere)
(Small and cute bread that matches the vibe perfectly)
(And their signature acorn-shaped madeleines)
- It looks so cute. - I know.
They must be cartoon characters.
- Matcha? Chocolate? - Sure.
When it comes to desserts,
you make great choices.
I just buy them all.
They're here.
This is the acorn bread.
- It's the acorn bread. - Acorn bread.
I'll eat the best one before Seok Jin starts.
But you can't eat it all.
Shall I cut it?
- Do you want it like this? - No.
- What's wrong? - No.
- Do you want me to do it? - Yes, do it for me.
Oh, my.
- She uses a knife... - "Do it for me."
She's cutting it so elegantly.
- Jae Seok cut it... - I mean, the angle.
Did I cut it poorly?
Did he cut it poorly?
No, but he cut it into small pieces.
- You're right. - Yes.
(Min Kyung cuts it again elegantly.)
(Taking a bite of the acorn bread gracefully)
- Is it good? - Right?
Tear it.
I'll tear it.
(Exclaiming)
The madeleine is tasty.
- It's good. - Right?
Okay.
We have places to go today.
Do you find them on the map?
- Yes. - That's so classic.
The cameramen...
(The classic staff)
(A classic map)
- What's wrong? - Are you mocking us?
- No. - She keeps...
- She keeps mocking us. - Min Kyung.
- I really didn't mock you. - You developed...
a lot of mockery technique since the last time.
- She mocks us so elegantly. - I agree.
- So it's hard to dispute. - I know.
(They calm down and take a look at the classic map.)
What's this?
"The Owner's Double Life in Yongsan?"
"Owner Who Does This Too."
"Owner with Lots of Jeju."
"Owner of Meat Restaurant with Lots of Smoke."
(This too?)
(That too?)
(Is the owner a pro at juggling multiple jobs?)
(Owner Who Does This Too)
(With dazzling hand skills...)
(Could it be juggling?)
(Owner with Lots of Jeju)
(Appearing from the smoke)
(Is the owner a genie?)
(Owner with Lots of Smoke)
(The owner's...)
(double life)
(Which is the one and only fake?)
I heard that Min Kyung knows a lot about Yongsan.
I live in this neighborhood.
- Seriously? - Really?
- Do you live here? - Yes, I live here.
I bet she has visited many places.
I honestly think that today will be very easy.
Is that so?
- I've been to everywhere. - I see.
- Then we can count on you. - I feel reassured.
- Seriously. - Today, you're done for.
You're done for. Brace yourselves.
We're sure to get it right today.
We have a huge advantage now.
Min Kyung is the type to visit all places...
that are trendy or new.
At a quick glance,
I see a few fake ones.
Which ones?
- Min Kyung, those are real. - Yes.
- All of these are real. - Min Kyung.
She just pointed...
at real places.
You fooled us.
Min Kyung, these are real.
She just pointed at real places.
(Her pointing of the finger stirs the public sentiment.)
Suddenly, I feel worried.
- You must have been startled. - I was.
In the list of real places, she said that she saw fake ones.
I will do my best.
- Shall we go outside? - Yes.
- The coffee was also delicious. - I love games.
Min Kyung, please do your best today.
Yes, I'll work hard.
Here we go.
I've been here for shoots,
- but I've never walked here. - Me neither.
- It's my first time walking here. - At night,
Yongnidan Street is extremely popular.
Yes, I heard that.
- At night? - Yes.
Many major corporate head offices are here.
There's also a big floating population.
(A commercial district shaped by major corporate offices)
(The streets of Yongsan at night are ideal for unwinding after work.)
(Yongnidan Street is full of new, hot places.)
- This place was on the map. - This bakery?
- This one? - Right, this place.
(One of the hip places on the map)
(A popular bakery in Yongsan that's packed even on rainy days)
(From croissants, its signature bread)
(A place that's popular for its various types of pastry)
(Extremely popular for its crunchy and moist texture)
- Yes, right here. - This place is amazing.
I bought a cake for you at this place...
- on your birthday. - Really?
(What?)
- I bought it on your birthday. - Okay.
(Laughing)
Shall we go to an accessory shop?
- It's pretty. - It looks cute.
It has so many pretty items.
It's adorable.
(A place that's full of small and cute items?)
(A small, charming accessory shop that faces the bakery)
(A place full of handmade knitted items crafted by the owner)
Hello, ma'am.
Gosh, it's so cute.
(There's a knitting fever even among the idol singers, )
(including Sakura and SOYEON.)
(Knitting became a hobby for the MZers.)
("Reason Why MZer Grabs Knitting Instead of Smartphones")
("Knitting Is Popular Again, A Way To Reduce Stress")
She must make them by hand.
(Full of popular knitted items made by hand)
They're really handmade.
- There are so many pretty items. - It's so pretty.
- I know. - Do these sunflowers move...
when I clap?
- I guess not. - No.
They won't move no matter how many times you clap.
Keep clapping.
- Such a toy exists. Don't you know? - I think I've seen it.
- Right? - Doesn't it run on batteries?
Yes.
There are also Tom and Jerry.
These are so cute.
Tom and Jerry.
(Tom and Jerry capture Jae Seok's eyes.)
Seok Jin, why don't you get one of these with Jae Seok?
- Shall I? - Tom and Jerry.
- This looks good. - This is perfect.
- Other items are too cute. - It's cute.
- Let's call them Tom and Jeery. - "Jeery?"
"Jeery?"
You might wet your pants.
- How could you say that? - Wetting your pants is...
"Jeery?" It could make you wet your pants.
- "Tom and Jeery?" - It's pretty.
Isn't it cute?
To be honest, when I look at things like this,
I don't really want them.
Don't say that in front of the owner.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - He said it right in front of her.
"I don't like things like this."
(Embarrassed)
Like he was breathing.
Wait, what about this?
- Yes. - A hair tie.
A hair tie like this.
(There are knitted hairpins too.)
I can get something for Na Eun.
You should buy one for Na Eun. It's adorable.
She has her own taste.
- She doesn't like everything. - Really?
- In the past, she liked everything. - Does she refuse it?
- Kids these days have their taste. - Right?
- Having her own taste is cute too. - She has her taste.
I want to buy a calculator.
- Which one? - A calculator.
(A calculator out of the blue?)
- Why a calculator? - Don't you have it on your phone?
No.
Why would you buy a calculator, Mimi?
- Tapping. - Why would you buy it?
I use it when I get my allowance.
When I win money while playing Go-Stop.
(That's cute.)
These are slippers and hairpins at the same time.
(These are slippers and hairpins at the same time.)
- The look on their faces... - They aren't interested.
They aren't interested.
- By the way... - They aren't interested.
The look in their eyes said,
"How could he pick something like that?"
- I didn't know how to react. - You two are...
You two are cold today.
I don't think Na Eun would wear these,
but I'll give them to her anyway.
- They're slipper hairpins. - They look cute.
(The dad ends up buying what he likes.)
I'll buy these.
- Gosh, that's a lot. - Why are you buying so much?
These are hairpins. Just in case...
- They're for Na Eun. - They're for Na Eun.
- You're a good dad. - Oh, my.
- I can feel love. - I'm so jealous.
- I wish I had a daughter too. - I know.
I'll pay for everything.
- Really? - Thank you.
Why are you paying for everyone?
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Goodbye.
- Your shop is lovely. - Thank you.
Have a good day.
Where are we going now?
Min Kyung, you must...
- look carefully from now on. - Okay.
Starting with the first place that we're going now,
we have to figure out if it's real or fake.
- Okay. - I see.
- I'm confident. - It should be here.
Here's the place.
Owner Who Does This Too.
- Owner Who Does This Too? - Yes.
Over here?
"T Pork Skirt?"
- It doesn't look fake. - Are we heading there?
"T Pork Skirt?" Is it here?
(Pork Skirt)
(The first popular place located on Yongnidan Street)
(It has a secretive vibe.)
- It looks amazing. - This place is fake.
- It looks amazing. - This place is fake..
- Is it fake? - Min Kyung says that...
- it's fake. - Seriously?
- How so? - You guys are in trouble today.
What should we do?
Why do you think it's fake?
(Is it a place that a Yongsan local knows?)
- This place is real. - I just gave it a try.
This place is real.
I gave it a try.
You don't seem very sharp.
This is very old.
How is this maintained...
- By the way, the door... - This is...
- And the smoke. - What?
This place is fake.
- It's real. - Does it look fake?
Is this real?
This place...
(Pass through the long corridor at the entrance...)
(and open the door...)
(A big charcoal barbecue restaurant)
I feel like they decorated it...
to make it look old.
It seems excessively detailed.
"Owner Who Does This Too?"
What could this be?
This restaurant could be real...
while the owner...
Whether the owner is real or fake?
Or the owner's personality...
The pig skin sounds so delicious.
The smell.
It smells like they ran...
- the restaurant until yesterday. - I'm hungry.
(A real restaurant that was running until recently?)
- Owner Who Does This Too. - This Too?
Yogurt and raw fish?
(Yogurt and raw fish?)
It means that he does something.
Could it be that he has 2 or 3 different jobs?
Could the owner be someone famous?
- Right. - He might do several things.
He has 2 or 3 different jobs.
First of all, it's a real restaurant.
- Yes, it's real. - The restaurant looks real.
- There's a lot on the menu. - I know.
(Filled with a variety of dishes)
What catches the attention is...
the green onion pork skirt.
(Among them, the green onion pork skirt stands out.)
I agree.
Let's get green onion pork skirt.
That sounds amazing.
It's unbelievable. I didn't even think of it.
Hello, sir. What?
What?
- What? - Gosh, you startled me.
- The acorn... - What?
(Who could the owner be?)
- What? - Gosh, you startled me.
- What? - Let me put this down first.
I mean...
Weren't you the owner at the cafe?
That's correct.
(The yogurt cafe owner, the meat restaurant owner)
- Remember what you said? - This has to be fake.
(What is going on?)
Thank you.
(The Sixth Sense members left the cafe a moment ago.)
(Getting off work)
(Moving)
(As soon as he gets off work at the cafe)
(Going to work)
Is that why you kept standing there?
- So that's why. - That's why.
- Do you also run this restaurant? - Yes.
I had been doing work related to baking.
Then I wanted to try something else in the restaurant business.
- And so... - Gosh.
But the direction is completely different.
It must be fake.
This and bakery...
- They're far from each other. - They have nothing in common.
After running a bakery,
- he could open a dessert place. - Right.
Most people stick to similar businesses,
but this is a totally different field.
While running a Greek yogurt cafe,
I had an idea...
of fermenting meat with yogurt.
(I see.)
- Fermentation with yogurt? - I see.
While running a bakery cafe,
I realized that yogurt could be used in many ways.
I was also interested in meat restaurants.
With advice from a probiotics specialist,
I spent three months working on meat fermentation.
(He developed yogurt optimized for meat fermentation.)
People are surprised by the taste.
It's quite popular.
(Is this strange combination real?)
It doesn't sound natural.
- I know. - It doesn't seem natural.
- Fermentation sounds possible. - Right,
but something about yogurt...
- Remember the butter pork belly? - It seems...
It was created by a pastry chef.
- Once we taste it... - We'll know once we taste it.
Will it taste like yogurt?
I'll prepare your order.
- Okay. - Okay.
This place seems suspicious.
- It's like he memorized his lines. - It seems fake.
He looked way too nervous...
about forgetting what to say.
Also, the cost of yogurt is high.
Selling pork and pig skin for ten dollars won't cover it.
The vibe of this place and pork belly fermented with yogurt...
- They don't match each other. - I don't think so.
- This place is more like a pub. - Right.
(Yogurt fermentation at a pub like this?)
The food is here.
I'll go to the other side.
(They're here to set the table.)
(Looking around)
This is what's served at a typical meat restaurant.
Is that yogurt...
on the table?
It's yogurt.
- This is yogurt. - You're right.
That's why you brought us naan.
- He gave us naan. - To dip naan in it?
Wrap meat with naan...
- and dip it in yogurt? - No way.
- That sounds delicious. - That sounds good.
It's called prata.
- It sounds so good. - Like kebab.
- That's how you eat kebab. - Like kebab.
- I think it's fake. - Why?
Kebab seems so out of context.
Naan came out of the blue.
(He prepares charcoal for the grill.)
- It's hot. - Okay.
(Staring)
Are you the restaurant owner?
- Yes. - Do you run it together?
(Someone suspicious appeared suddenly.)
Am I wrong?
Who are you?
- What's the matter? - Are you a server?
Are you the restaurant owner?
Do you also run it?
Who are you?
He must be the real restaurant owner.
He isn't answering me. I asked who he was.
Maybe he's the real restaurant owner.
(What's going on here?)
- This is our sixth shoot. - Yes.
We only got 1 out of 5 right.
So we have to get it right today.
The production crew didn't expect us to be this bad.
(Exclaiming)
They didn't expect us to be this bad.
What is it?
Look at this.
This can't be true.
It looks like cake.
(Even a Yongsan local is shocked.)
(The look of yogurt pork skirt)
At our restaurant, pork skirt is...
served with whole green onions.
(Green onions and pork skirt came together.)
Pork skirt is a cut near the pig's heart.
To remove its strong smell, I found out yogurt fermentation method.
As probiotics help break down protein,
it helps tenderize the meat.
(It removes bad odor and tenderizes the meat.)
I ferment the meat in pure yogurt for one day.
That's what makes it special.
(It's ready to be served after fermentation for a day.)
(A unique combination of green onion pork skirt and yogurt)
(Yogurt pork skirt is really good.)
(Enthusiastic reviews on social media)
This month's sales will be about 100,000 dollars.
Sixth Sense members,
is this place real?
- It's like cake. - I'll put it in the middle.
- Sir, this is... - What?
Do you remove the yogurt before grilling?
- So this is green onion pork skirt. - Is this it?
- Green onion pork skirt. - Really?
Green onions are whole, right?
- Look at that. - Do you grill it like that?
Do you grill it even though it's covered with sauce?
Yes, grill it like this.
(Surprised)
When the color changes clearly,
- cut it with scissors. - Cut it?
Otherwise, the green onions might fall out.
(Quiet)
Enjoy your food.
I've never seen anything like it.
In my entire life...
I've lived the longest,
and I've never seen anything like it.
- You finally accept it. - Yes.
(Oh, I forgot.)
It happens a few times a day.
- You lived over half a century. - Yes.
This one...
It's charcoal.
It's not very cooked.
- We have to keep flipping it. - Exactly.
Pork skirt is a cut...
that takes a long time to cook.
- You have to flip it often. - Right.
- You have to keep flipping it. - Right.
Despite that, the outside gets burnt fast.
Usually, this is partially grilled before serving.
It's served completely uncooked.
Pork skirt is usually partially grilled before.
By the way, why is everyone so angry?
- Right? - They're dying to get it right.
You're angry even before tasting it.
When it comes to meat,
- Korean people are sensitive. - We are.
- By the way... - Pork skirt...
He usually grills it for his customers.
- Right? - With things like asparagus...
I don't think customers can grill it.
- I keep thinking that this is... - How will it taste?
Made by real chefs.
- Exactly. That's what I thought. - Me too.
Right?
It looks like something that chefs would make.
In Season One, the butter pork belly was...
real.
(Butter pork belly was a real place on Season 1.)
By basing on that idea,
this time...
- Yogurt pork belly? - Yes.
To be honest,
I find green onions strange.
(She agrees.)
- It's pretending to be hip. - Instead...
Right.
- What? - It's pretending to be hip.
There's a popular grilled green onion dish.
- Really? - Is it a Spanish dish?
Everyone sounds so angry.
We have to find which is fake.
We only got 1 out of 5 correct.
- So we're sensitive today. - We're sensitive.
It's because we've been terrible at guessing.
Please understand us.
Can you hand me the scissors?
Mister.
- Mister, give me the scissors. - Is your arm too short?
- Mister. - You just need to stretch it out.
- Goodness. - Kyung Pyo grilled it well.
- I agree. - It's exactly like galbi.
This is exactly like galbi.
Now that it's cooked, it looks very delicious.
(The yogurt coating kept the meat moist and juicy.)
(Cooked pork skirt with whole green onions)
(When it's cut nicely into a bite with scissors)
(Green onions inside the pork skirt)
- It looks similar to tripe. - Yes.
Right.
(How does the yogurt pork skirt taste?)
- This is... - I'll try it.
Try and see how it tastes.
- Is it cooked? - Let's see.
- How is it? - It comes out.
- How is it? Is it really good? - I bet it tastes good.
Is it good?
- It must be good. - I guess it's good.
Is it incredible? How is it?
It's really good.
- Really? - Is it good?
Everyone changes their opinion after tasting it.
- Did you try it with green onion? - Yes.
- It looks... - The owner...
nice enough to be on social media.
- Is it good, Seok Jin? - Yes.
(Surprised)
- Is it good? - Yes.
With the green onion flavor...
I don't know if it's the yogurt, but it's very tender.
Yes, it's so tender.
- This is my favorite texture. - Seriously.
It tastes like pork galbi instead of yogurt.
(It tastes like juicy pork galbi without the taste of yogurt.)
- This is really good. - It's not greasy.
What's with this meat?
- It's very tender. - How is this meat so good?
Nicely grilled pieces look good enough...
- The owner... - to be on social media.
- I agree. - The owner isn't sloppy.
This is...
(Both the taste and the look are excellent.)
It'd be strange if it wasn't popular.
The meat tastes so good.
The meat tastes really good.
I totally agree with her.
- It tastes so good. - It really does.
- I'll cut it for you. - Please cut it.
Can you just cut the green onion? It's too big.
- No. Just cut it. - Okay.
- Cut it like this? - Cut it.
(Moving about)
Stay still...
- so that I can cut it. - Okay.
- Wait, I'll cut it for you. - Thank you.
(Enjoying a bite thanks to Min Kyung)
(Exclaiming)
- Is this our sixth episode? - Yes.
Among everything we've tasted, this is the best.
You should work more.
(We still have many places to go.)
- It's too early to tell. - It's too early.
- It's too early. - Right.
- It's early. - We still have four more episodes.
The meat tastes so light and delicious.
It's so good.
- It tastes like tripe. - Yes, it's excellent.
The production crew is looking at us like...
- What's wrong? - They must think that we're fools.
They really want some.
(Jealous)
- They must want some too. - I know.
- More food is coming. - Is there more?
This is doenjang stew rice.
- He's serving doenjang stew rice. - For the chilly weather,
- Thank you. - this is for you.
(A deep flavor from the seafood broth...)
(made with Manila clams, crabs, and shrimp)
(Finishing the perfect meal with doenjang stew rice)
- You can find this menu... - It's tasty.
- at a tasty restaurant. - The stew rice is always good.
Right?
- It's tasty. - You find it at a tasty restaurant.
- I've never had it before. - It's made with crabs.
How does it taste?
(What?)
- What's the matter? - It's good.
It's good?
(It's good.)
I thought that you were doing a skit.
(Flustered)
"It's good."
(A skit from back then)
(He loves it.)
- Gosh, a skit... - You can't hide your age.
The comedy duo.
- Hae Ri. - It wasn't a skit.
- It's not what you think. - Hae Ri, isn't that it?
- No. - The comedy duo.
- I think it is. - It's delicious.
They're a comedy duo indeed.
"It's good."
- "It's good." - It's delicious.
Anyway, this restaurant has...
- too many details. - I know.
It has many suspicious aspects.
- Right. - It has many.
Most importantly, I'm a social media addict,
and I've never seen this before.
When you look up tasty restaurants, they always come up.
They keep coming up.
When you look up tasty restaurants in Yongsan-gu,
- only those in Yongsan come up. - Right.
However, I've never seen this before.
I think that it's real.
I think the food happened to be good.
(Aren't I right?)
Delicious dishes...
- that couldn't become mainstream... - Right.
- Among those they created, - After creating them...
- this is the second dish. - You know why? The price...
Did someone punch you in the stomach?
(A hard blow in the abdomen)
Hae Ri.
- Your reaction is... - Did you get a punch in the belly?
Your reaction is incredible.
You can't resist the shift of generation.
- I knew it. - Old-school comedy.
Your sense of humor comes from the old generation.
(Her sense of humor is labeled old-school.)
(Gosh, my stomach hurts.)
- Anyway, let's go. - We've gotten fooled...
like this so many times.
One, two, three.
- The food was delicious. - If this place were real...
- It was amazing. - Hey.
- Let's take a photo. - All right.
- Where shall we take the photo? - Sir, where shall we take it?
- Sir. - I...
- In the front... - Can't we take it at the cafe?
We can only take it here.
He keeps wanting to take it at his cafe.
- He's an expert. - At the cafe?
- He seems disappointed. - The owners don't agree.
They care more about their own place.
Why does he want to take a photo...
- at the cafe instead? - The owners are different.
That's exactly what I mean.
This place must be fake.
There's someone else in the back. He's the real restaurant owner.
Which one is our next?
Next is Owner with Lots of Jeju.
(Shall we go and meet the second owner?)
I'm not very experienced,
but based on my experience, it's very confusing.
- We have to visit all of them. - Right.
- We can't tell after the first one. - We can't tell.
It's impossible to know.
(What kind of real or fake popular place awaits them?)
- Do you like old city centers? - Yes.
I don't like flashy places.
- You don't? - No.
(Low buildings)
I understand why Kyung Pyo likes old city centers.
- Isn't this the vibe? - I love it.
- It's really nice. - There's an open view.
(Namyeong-dong)
Before that, we'll go to a cafe.
- Really? - Yes.
- Okay. - Okay.
- We're here. - It's not very far.
Goodness.
(The Sixth Sense members arrived somewhere in Namyeong-dong.)
Shall we go to the cafe?
She loves cafes.
- What's this? - We're going into an alley.
- Oh, my. - It looks very hip.
It used to be an arcade.
(An unusual entrance to an alley beneath an old signboard)
Is this a film set?
- It looks so beautiful. - It looks really nice.
Is this the beauty of a retro vibe?
It's pretty.
(The world of wood color starts.)
- It looks beautiful here too. - It's a daisy.
- It's so pretty. - It's nice.
This is unbelievable. The street is so beautiful.
(Inside the unique space of a different world)
- What is this place? - It's really nice here.
- It's very beautiful. - Hello, sir.
- It's pretty. - Hello.
- He looks cool. - Even the owner looks handsome.
- Hello. - He looks hip.
(You can feel his hip aura right away.)
Sir, how long have you been running this?
It's been five years since it opened.
- That's quite long. - It's been a while.
- Five years? - This place wasn't...
like this before, was it?
It was a market that opened...
during the Japanese occupation.
After the Japanese military withdrew,
Korean merchants started opening shops here.
(A remnant of early modern architecture)
It feels like we traveled back to the 50s.
- You're right. - It looks amazing.
I didn't know about that history.
It was built during the Japanese colonial period.
- These walls are genuine. - Yes, they were preserved.
These are genuine.
(Inside where the appearance from the past was reinterpreted)
- Like the walls used back then. - Exactly.
When you take photos of this alley when it's deserted,
- the photos come out well. - They would be beautiful.
- They look amazing. - I imagine so.
Sir, do you roast the coffee here?
- Yes, I roast the coffee beans. - He has a roasting machine.
You're right.
Everyone, you can choose your coffee beans.
- I'd like the nutty flavor. - Nutty?
- Me too. - I prefer the nutty flavor.
- Me too. - I'd also like it nutty.
Everyone wants the nutty flavor, so can we get the MV blend?
- That's right. - "MV blend."
- You know a lot about coffee beans. - You know well.
- It's written on here. - It's written.
(I see.)
It's written.
I'd like an espresso...
- with the F blend. - Okay.
I've never had an espresso before.
Would you like an espresso?
Sir, is an espresso...
- served this much? - That's right.
- You drink it fast? I'd like one. - As a shot?
- I'll make you a good one. - Please.
- That sounds good. - Goodness.
Seok Jin, it could make your heart beat fast.
- I'd like an espresso too. - Let's try it.
- Espresso? - Let's try an espresso.
Three espressos with the F blend, please.
- Okay. - That sounds cool.
- What's the F blend? - You do it very well.
How you talk is very important.
When Min Kyung says something, it sounds very sophisticated.
Let me try it.
Can I have a sweet one?
- Okay. - "A sweet one."
- Is that sophisticated to you? - Don't I sound sophisticated?
Could you recommend me a sweet drink?
(Mimi also makes her order elegantly.)
(Laughing)
I will get them ready for you.
- Thank you. - We look forward to it.
Thank you.
(While the beverages are made in a sophisticated way)
These days, this type...
- of vibe is really... - Right.
A place like this would look good in photos.
It looks amazing in photos.
Does anyone know how to take good photos?
- I'm good at taking photos. - No, you aren't.
- I'm good. - He's terrible.
- When it comes to composition... - Really?
Jae Seok finds taking photos bothersome.
That's true. Do you want me to take a photo of you?
(Yes, it's annoying.)
- Not really. - I can't trust him at all.
You're bad at taking photos.
- I'll take a photo right now. - I'm curious.
- I bet he takes them carelessly. - Instead of taking it directly,
could you take it when I'm turning around?
(When you're turning around?)
(I want to do it too.)
- I'll take a photo right now. - Instead of taking it directly...
(Seok Jin who's turning...)
(and Jae Seok who's raising it)
Jae Seok, that method is outdated.
(Absorbed)
(While they turn diligently in an old-fashioned way)
- Are you taking a selfie? - Hey.
I took a selfie. It's been a while.
He's been taking a selfie.
- Min Kyung, could you take... - You look great right now.
He really looks like someone from the Japanese colonial period.
(He really looks like someone from the Japanese colonial period.)
(Japanese colonial period)
She mocks me so elegantly.
Doesn't he look like someone from that time period?
(Take a look.)
He's posing like someone from that time.
- You're right. - He seems like a person...
- of integrity. - You're right.
Why do I look this good?
Isn't it great? I'll take another one.
You look determined.
Can you pose with a bit more feeling?
- Got it. - You were too stiff.
Try to look more arrogant.
How about this?
- This. - Okay, that's cute.
Doesn't this look like an old album jacket?
It's like a remake of his song, "I Know."
You look cute.
This is cute.
We got a shot for your new album.
Why are you also taking one?
I have the shot.
Wait, he looks great!
He looks like a prankster.
(Taking photo after photo)
This is cute.
What's with the burst mode?
- Look how natural this is. - He looks so good!
- That's a great one. - Doesn't this look natural?
- Doesn't he look good? - He looks amazing.
- Right? - It's like an album jacket.
Look how natural he seems.
- I look great in this. - See how natural this is.
- Doesn't he look great? - You look amazing!
- That's nice. - He looks amazing in this.
- Can you send me this? - Sure.
I took too many.
How do I choose out of all 100 photos?
Wait, when was the last one I took?
Send just the two from before.
- You took 100 photos? - Hey, that's ours.
- Espresso! - There's our espresso.
- The cups are so pretty. - The cups are beautiful.
I haven't had an espresso before.
(All eyes are on the cute cups.)
The cups look like they're from Portugal.
You're right.
The cups are so pretty.
(Espresso is served in adorable cups.)
- The cups are stunning! - I know. They're beautiful.
Hey, that looks great. What's that?
- Mimi, did you order that? - Who ordered that?
- It was me. - What's that?
I wanted something sweet.
(Making itself known among the small espresso cups)
That looks delicious!
(Tangy and sweet, berry granita)
(Trying a bite before it melts!)
Try it.
- Is it coffee bingsu? - It's coffee bingsu.
Is it a bingsu?
(Under white cream)
- This tastes like coffee ice slush. - Yes, that.
There's ice slush in there.
I'm going to think I'm in Italy.
Hold on.
He shook his head side to side without actually smelling it.
- He was faking it. - Exactly.
He moved his head without inhaling.
What's the matter? What is it, Seok Jin?
(Exclaiming)
Isn't it super bitter?
Gosh, that's strong.
(Oh, no...)
- It's acidic, isn't it? - This is really good.
It's like poison.
So this is what an espresso is like. I quite like it.
(Anyone can tell he hasn't had an espresso before.)
Why aren't you drinking your coffee?
(You said you liked it.)
(Why do you think I'm not drinking it?)
I'm going to take my time.
You should have what I'm having.
You're right.
I bet that's way better.
This is the one, right? This is up your alley.
(Yes!)
(Seok Sam's such a child.)
I should've taken a photo of him drinking the espresso.
Yes, take one.
Just pretend to drink it.
Shake your head left to right like before.
(This time, he points!)
(Ambushed while watching)
Who are you waving at?
(Ending it by striking an 80s pose and looking into the distance)
- Why did you raise your hand? - That was cute.
- We have the shot. - She's got it.
Can you delete the ones where I'm smiling widely?
Sure. Actually, I only took photos of your hand.
(Chuckling)
She only took photos of the cup.
She's a menace.
- A menace? - She's quite annoying.
Gosh, Min Kyung.
- She's been like that all day. - She puts you down elegantly.
- Yes, elegantly. - Her teasing is graceful.
- I wasn't putting him down. - She does that all day long.
- The cup's cute, that's all. - Seriously?
(What's that?)
(Only leaving behind the cup that was so cute in Min Kyung's eyes)
- Shall we get going? - Sure.
- Are we off to a restaurant? - Yes.
We're off to see the Owner with Lots of Jeju.
The Owner with Lots of Jeju?
I wonder what we can expect from him.
Why is it "Jeju" and not talent?
The Owner with Lots of Jeju.
That must be it.
- Where? - Over there.
Dongchimi?
- Hey, it's Ddolraemi. - Ddolraemi?
- Isn't that a Jeju dialect? - In Jeju, that means...
Isn't "ddolraemi..."
- from the Jeju dialect? - It is.
You get charcoal barbecue here.
(A Korean charcoal barbecue place named with a Jeju dialect word)
(Charcoal-grilled galbi)
(Salt-grilled meat)
(Inside)
This is a cute establishment.
(A clean and cozy Korean barbecue place)
(A Jeju dialect expression that shows where the owner is from)
Everything's new.
Everything's new. Check it out.
(The restaurant seems newly opened.)
(Who's the Owner with Lots of Jeju?)
He must be from Jeju.
There's a photo of Song Ga In.
- What? - Where?
(A real photo of Song Ga In)
(The photo zone by the door)
There's a myth that touching it brings wealth.
(Wall Street, New York)
(Photos she took traveling the world)
(The owner is a true extrovert.)
- This must be the owner. - "Miss Trot?"
- Was she on "Miss Trot?" - Trot?
(Photos from when she competed in the show)
I think she's a trot singer.
The owner is a singer.
(Does this place really exist?)
What does "ddolraemi" mean?
- Ddolraemi. - Of course!
I was born there.
I was born there, but I didn't live there much.
- Is it from the Jeju dialect? - Yes, it means "daughter."
(Ddolraemi, a Jeju dialect word for daughter)
How was this place described exactly?
- The Owner with Lots of Jeju. - The Owner with Lots of Jeju?
From what I can tell, she's a singer.
- I get it! She's from Jeju... - She's from Jeju.
And she can sing, which means she's multi-talented.
A singer from Jeju.
- That's it. - A singer from Jeju.
(The secret is revealed thanks to Ms. Detective.)
(Coming up)
(Startled)
Can she actually do that?
(Talented)
(With many talents)
(The owner from Jeju)
(A talented soul from Jeju Island)
(With lots of Jeju)
(A dish you never expected)
- This is amazing. - Right?
- Hello. - Hello.
Hi.
(The owner enters.)
It was her in the photos.
It's her.
I'm sorry, but aren't you a singer?
I'm a singer,
- and a restaurant owner. - Right?
Hi, I'm Jung Ji Won, a trot singer...
and the owner of the Korean barbecue place.
Growing up with my grandmother,
I used to sing a lot of trot songs.
It naturally made me want to become a trot singer,
and I applied for an audition after seeing one on TV.
I made it to the top 100,
but it was disappointing to get eliminated immediately.
(Unfortunately, she got cut in the 1st round.)
Still, I didn't want to give up on that dream,
so while I was working at my dad's restaurant...
(She worked at her dad's Korean barbecue restaurant in Jeju.)
I saved up enough money.
(She saved every bit she could to pursue her dream.)
I thought working in Seoul...
would make it easier for me to continue as a trot singer,
so I moved here.
(She left Jeju and opened...)
(a Korean barbecue restaurant in Yongsan.)
It opened on August 18.
(It only opened 2 months ago.)
(I see...)
When did you start out as a singer?
I started out as a singer in 2023.
- It hasn't been that long. - Yes, it's only been two years.
- You only just got started. - You took a photo with Song Ga In.
(How do you know Song Ga In?)
(The two seem close.)
I once released a digital single album,
and that got me a chance to be on a TV show.
That's when we took the photo.
A digital single. So, you only released one song?
Yes, just one. Can I sing it for you?
Sure thing.
- Will she sing it live? - Right here?
(Excited)
- Are you going to sing for us? - That's right.
- Really? - Yes.
- Please clap along. - Sure.
("Welcome")
(Swinging)
(Swaying)
She's adorable.
(This is so much fun.)
Here we go.
("Welcome" by Jung Ji Won, An autobiographical song...)
(about leaving Jeju for Seoul to chase big dreams)
Three, four.
(With the Jeju wind on my back)
(I made my way to Seoul)
(There you go!)
- To "Welcome," say "Yes." - Got it.
(Welcome)
(Singing her heart out at a Korean barbecue place)
(Dance moves that line up with the lyrics)
(Senior trot singer Yu San Seul is enjoying every second of it.)
(Jihwaja!)
(Singing without looking at the audience)
- Ms. Jung. - Yes?
The lyrics are bold,
- but you're being so shy. - With hands above your heads
(Still, she ends it on a confident note.)
(Good job!)
Of course she'd be nervous.
- Ms. Jung. - I bet you were nervous.
I grew up watching "Infinite Challenge," you see.
I wasn't this nervous during my audition,
- but... - Really?
Jae Seok, I blame you.
I wouldn't have been as nervous if you were sitting here.
- What? - What does that make me?
It's your fault, Jae Seok.
(The issue was with the seating.)
(We're sorry.)
Didn't you grow up watching "Running Man?"
- Big Nose, I'm a huge fan. - It's all right.
Anyway, the owner is in the entertainment industry.
- That's right. - But just opening a restaurant...
won't get her immediate attention.
- Exactly. - The food must taste good.
There must be a special dish.
Why don't you go ahead and figure out what it is.
- Really? - Is it a quiz?
- This is it. The matcha. - Matcha galbitang.
- Is this it? - Matcha.
- Matcha's all the rage right now. - Matcha. Yes, of course.
(Jeju matcha galbitang, 25 dollars)
- Jeju matcha? - Matcha galbitang.
(It makes sense since the owner's from Jeju.)
(How far have you experimented with matcha?)
(A worldwide craze for matcha)
(Matcha cake)
(Matcha tteokbokki)
(Matcha pasta)
(Matcha fever is taking over everywhere.)
Since this is a business district, I needed a lunch special.
I thought about my options,
and because matcha is all the rage...
among young people, I came up with matcha galbitang.
That's how I released matcha galbitang.
Matcha is all the rage right now, but...
But matcha in galbitang?
- I think it'll be too sweet. - Actually, this makes sense.
- How so? - Think about...
what we end our meals with at Japanese restaurants.
Something fried is placed on rice. Right, an ochazuke.
An ochazuke.
Green tea is poured over rice.
(Ochazuke, a dish of rice steeped in matcha tea)
(Just like Korea's barley gulbi)
(Matcha tea is used in many dishes.)
This is like jumping on the bandwagon.
But these days, unless you follow what's trending,
you end up falling behind. So first...
Are you just going to squash my opinion?
(He's only joking.)
(Watching "Infinite Challenge" toughened her up.)
I urge you to get on the bandwagon.
(Edgy)
- Yes, let's do it. - It might be fun.
Got it.
- I hear you, Ms. Jung. - Spoken like a zoomer.
- But... - Okay, then. Ms. Jung.
It's supposed to be 28 dollars. Why are you charging 25 dollars?
(What's the reason behind the 3-dollar discount?)
It's an opening event.
(Impressed)
- It's an opening event. - That's fun.
(The boomer is flustered.)
This and...
- She's relaxed. - this.
(Full of Generation MZ-style reactions)
- They point their hands upward. - They point upward.
- You're right. - I told you.
You kept making downward gestures.
(His reaction droops downward.)
(Like this.)
(He can't hide...)
(his old gestures.)
(Physically low reactions)
All the way down.
(Mimicking Big Nose)
(Feeling bitter)
You should do it up here.
For this restaurant,
we need to try the food and decide.
Honestly, it doesn't appeal to me.
- Can I say it tastes bad if it is? - Sure. You know,
customers around Seok Jin's age...
ask, "What's this?"
How old do you think he is?
(He suddenly asks her a question.)
(Grinning)
(Overbearing)
(Making an eye contact)
In his 40s?
You're right.
(You're right.)
The food looks delicious.
(She convinces him successfully.)
- The owner is... - She's talented.
- definitely talented. - She is.
You're witty.
(The owner is the king of sales.)
You'll get a lot of regular customers.
- I'll get it ready. - Let us try.
This is a bit...
Even if someone else took me here,
I wouldn't order it.
As soon as she left...
(He changes his attitude in 0.1 second.)
You started talking immediately.
You were clapping her hands.
You high fived her.
For those that are fake,
they make fake menus.
(The staff adds fake menus to existing restaurants.)
- It's perfect for that. - And matcha...
- seems perfect for it. - It's perfect.
It feels like a chef came up with it.
- It's here. - It's here.
The menu itself is something she could've come up with herself.
At the early stage of her business,
she could've developed it with passion.
- She could've since she's a zoomer. - Matcha is...
From what I know,
there's not enough matcha supply...
- nowadays. - That's right.
Because it's so popular globally.
Globally, really. You're right.
She said she used Osulloc matcha.
(The owner uses matcha from a large company.)
So I'm not sure how sustainable...
it will be...
to use it on food.
That's an important point.
- It's too highly in demand. - Yes.
Korean matcha became so popular too.
They add it to mayonnaise.
(Eyes opening wide)
(At that moment, )
(matcha galbitang arrives.)
(Eyes opening wide)
- Is it green? - It's not green.
- It doesn't look green. - She could've added just a bit.
- It's not green. - This...
- She could've added just a bit. - This is 25 dollars?
I don't think you added matcha, ma'am.
It won't be fun if I served matcha galbitang as is.
We have a performance ready.
(A performance?)
- You have it. - I have it.
You can't survive without one.
There aren't too many ingredients.
It's very simple.
Potatoes and meat. That's all.
Since our signature menu is ribs,
we have not-so-pretty leftover parts...
that are cut out from the big chunk.
(Leftover parts which are a waste to throw away)
I decided to add more back ribs to it...
and make pork galbitang out of it.
That's how I came up with the menu.
(Pour water onto pork that was boiled once.)
I add potatoes cut into big chunks.
(Add whole garlic, ginger, and radish for the soup.)
I stack up the back ribs high like a dome.
(Pour the broth made using back ribs.)
(Clear galbitang is ready.)
It's very simple.
- So it looks... - If it was...
made by a chef,
- it would've been a lot flashier. - That's right.
- She has a performance. - It would've been a lot flashier.
- A performance? - Yes, a performance.
We must check how it's done.
Here she comes.
She's going to do that?
What...
This is the performance.
- She'll whisk it right here. - What...
(Whisking: The act of making the foam to drink matcha)
I pour hot water...
onto Jeju matcha we use.
(Add hot water.)
I use the whisk to whisk it.
(Mixed finely)
(Green Jeju matcha)
(Pour it on galbitang.)
(It went viral on social media.)
(Matcha galbitang)
After adding matcha galbitang to the menu,
we're earning 1,000 dollars more each day.
Sixth Sense members,
is this place real?
(Sixth Sense members, is this place real?)
(Confused)
This looks way too fake.
- It... - Now it's...
(The whisking performance looks suspicious.)
Won't it be bothersome?
Exactly. To do this every time...
If you don't do this much nowadays,
you can't garner people's attention.
- Is this for marketing purpose? - Yes. When I do this,
the customers whip out their phones immediately.
(The performance makes people want to film it.)
(Matcha mixed finely from the whisking)
I'll pour it.
(It enters galbitang.)
You pour it into the soup?
(Falling onto the clear broth...)
(and giving you a boost of green dopamine)
(The taste of Generation MZ, matcha galbitang)
It now looks like seaweed fulvescens soup.
- You're right. The color. - The color.
(It looks similar...)
(to the green seaweed fulvescens soup.)
It doesn't look too strange.
It smells amazing.
I want to try the soup.
(How does the soup taste?)
(He takes a sip of the soup first.)
(He takes another sip right after.)
It's light and nice.
It's tasty.
(Seok Jin was hostile toward matcha.)
It's delicious.
I think I'll come back for it.
Really?
(What's with him?)
Because...
it's not too strong. I like how it's mild.
I also like its light taste.
It's mild, just how I like it.
It isn't oily at all.
(The mild taste of matcha and the light taste of galbitang)
Thank you.
Try it. How is it?
- Try it. - It smells like...
- ordinary Korean dish. - I want to add sujebi into it.
- Exactly. - Really?
I thought so too.
(Drinking from the plate)
How is it?
Why does it have a bitter aftertaste?
- Really? - It's fine for me.
I don't think she calculated...
- the amount she needed to add. - She added too much, right?
I think she just played it by ear.
(Just now)
(When she added matcha, )
(Hae Ri observed carefully.)
(Did the owner add the wrong amount?)
It's not bad,
but it doesn't taste amazing.
Same here. I don't feel the urge to keep eating it.
(What about Mimi, the zoomer of Sixth Sense?)
- It's delicious. - It's not bad.
You're one of the zoomers that like it.
- I think so. - It's nice.
I like clear soup...
- over spicy soup. - Me too.
Even for spicy fish stew, I sometimes prefer...
- the mild version. - Yes.
- That... - It's nice.
You can't stop until you finish it.
(You keep craving it because it doesn't taste strong.)
- You either like it or dislike it. - That's right.
Those who like this...
will come back for it.
- It's a bit... - Yes.
I guess you could compare it to Pyongyang naengmyeon.
(The black sheep of galbitang)
Because it's matcha galbitang,
I thought it'd cater...
- to younger people's tastes. - No.
You and I like it.
I like it. It's nice and warm.
Let me try the meat, then.
- I should try the meat. - Try the meat.
- Try the meat. - Give her the one inside.
- The one inside. - Cut it using the scissors.
(Soaked in matcha, )
(so it's green outside.)
Some of them are already separated from the bones.
(Eating the meat)
(Humming)
(Taking a big bite)
(Nodding)
(Kyung Pyo holds it in his hand and bites the meat off.)
The meat is so tender and nice.
(Mild matcha galbitang, is it real?)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok can't stop eating.)
I like it.
- You're eating so well. - It's delicious.
I really like it.
This is so good.
Have some chives.
(Friendship blooms over matcha galbitang.)
Did these two come here by themselves?
Seok Jin, have some chives.
Doesn't it feel like...
we were dragged here when we didn't want to?
(It feels like they're forced to be here.)
We had to follow the directors.
- They insisted on coming here. - This is...
The two superiors are driving you crazy.
Do you now understand why I wanted to come here?
- It's so delicious. - It's amazing.
Senior Manager Kang, why won't you eat up?
Are you not hungry?
- It's nice to see you eat well. - It's so good.
- It's amazing. - I understand now.
- I feel refreshed. - Why won't you eat?
- Eat up. - I'm eating.
(The younger staff members don't seem to like it.)
It's so nice.
Right?
- Director Yu, you're... - Excuse me.
(What's wrong, Director Yu?)
Excuse me. I'm your superior at work.
(I'm your superior at work!)
I'm your superior at work.
(A plot twist)
I'm sorry.
Oh, dear.
(Feeling the secondhand embarrassment)
I didn't know that.
I just assumed since I'm older.
- I'm sorry, Director. - Senior Manager Jee,
you must be very drunk.
I'm a senior manager?
- My apologies. - Senior Manager Jee.
- Don't make such mistakes. - Sober up.
I feel so suffocated in this atmosphere.
(Let's just not eat together.)
- You guys eat really well. - But you know...
I really like it.
-This is real. - I really like it.
(Director and Senior Manager are in love with matcha.)
- I think it's fake. - Why?
You say that after eating it so well?
What if it's like ice cream tteokbokki?
They placed ice cream on tteokbokki.
Yes, they did.
(It's fake here.)
(Could this be another fake combo that only looks real?)
But doesn't yogurt pork skirt resemble...
ice cream tteokbokki more in that sense?
Can you remove this from your list? I really like it.
Ice cream tteokbokki...
Why are you forcing her to remove it?
I was wondering what he was going to say.
- This is real. - Ice cream...
Aren't you making it too personal?
I'm not a big fan of matcha,
so I was skeptical of it.
But adding matcha in it lessens the greasy taste.
The aftertaste is clear.
I was looking forward to it before I ate it.
I thought it made sense.
But when I tried it, the taste was a bit iffy.
- Is this necessary? - Exactly. Is this necessary?
- Why... Competitiveness... - It would've still tasted good...
without matcha.
If it's about competitiveness,
she should've put up a fancier performance.
But it ended so fast.
Will people react favorably to the uploaded video?
I don't think so.
You seem to be very angry.
- You are quite angry. - She might hear you.
(I'm sorry.)
- She might hear you. - Yes.
"Will it?"
(A terrible reenactment)
"That's right."
(Embarrassed)
- You... - I was too into it.
I really like your attitude.
That's how you reveal the truth.
You look cool...
- when you're focused on work. - I am.
- I'm completely immersed in it. - You're immersed in it.
Before we actually end up fighting,
- let's stop talking. - The conversation isn't going well.
We don't think alike on this one.
We went along well before.
(Owner with Lots of Jeju: A fake menu based on the trend?)
We'll only be sure once we arrive at the last place.
I agree.
Next is, "Owner of Meat Restaurant with Lots of Smoke."
I think that's a wordplay too.
- The owner might be an actor. - Exactly.
- Acts as in acting. - An actor?
- That could be it. - That might be the case.
He's a stage actor.
(That sounds plausible.)
Smoke as in stage smoke effect.
For the second place, it had the drawing...
of Dolhareubang of Jeju Island, right?
- Yes. - On the map.
(The keywords are the key to finding the fake today.)
"Owner with Lots of Jeju" had Dolhareubang.
"Owner Who Does This Too" had another drawing.
- Right? - Is that so?
"Is that so?"
I don't actually speak like that, do I?
- You actually do. - You actually do.
You speak like this.
- Really? - Yes.
- I love it. - I'm so stressed.
- It's stressful. - I'm stressed.
(Her clones are everywhere.)
Look at how she put tape behind her ears.
- What? - Isn't it cute? Behind her ears.
(Mimi used her ear tape today too.)
Why did she paste it? Is it for motion sickness?
No, to make her ears...
- To lean them forward. - lean forward.
It makes you look younger.
There's a tape for this.
- Making your ears lean forward. - I heard about it.
You should do it too.
- I don't like stuff like that. - You should do it as Young Fifty.
It feels too strange.
- Shall I give you one? - No.
- I have a lot. - Doing this would feel strange.
I heard there was a tape which makes your ears...
- lean forward. - Yes.
That's what Mimi used.
- That's what we're talking about. - I'm using it now.
- That's what we're talking about. - You're using it now?
(Seeing it for the first time)
- You didn't know? - All this while.
He doesn't pay attention to what others say.
But this is too much.
- They're like yours. - You know what?
His ears are stuck flat to his head.
People with such ears don't listen to others.
- Really? - They don't listen to others.
- He doesn't listen at all. - I tend not to listen to others.
- If you speak like this... - You don't listen to others either.
(Suddenly getting angry)
- My ears are wide open. - You still don't listen.
- That's odd. - What's happening?
- "That's odd." - You said you wouldn't get angry.
I'm not angry.
- You seem to be very angry. - I'm not.
It's a bit hot.
It's true I don't listen to others.
I think so too.
Did you know we were a great fan of yours?
- Really? - Yes.
Jong Kook and Seok Jin...
- were in a cafe. - Yes.
We went to say hello.
You know this kind of action?
He did that, and it looked so cool.
- Really? - Yes, for real.
Really?
Did you discuss this with me?
(The other Davichi member has no clue what she's saying.)
Will you keep quiet?
- Min Kyung. - Hae Ri.
At moments like this, just don't say anything.
Min Kyung didn't feel...
comfortable enough to say it was her story.
- I think that's the case. - You...
But you were really fun and cool,
so we talked with you for quite long.
I don't think it's a "we."
- "Did you discuss this with me?" - She doesn't think so.
We're here.
We must be going to Gyeongnidan Street.
(You can see Mount Nam from here.)
(A foreign vibe...)
(and full of unique hot spots which are popular on social media)
(The original hot spot, Gyeongnidan Street)
There are a lot of hip places...
- in each and every alley. - That's right.
We're going to a back alley.
- Amazing. - Behind here is...
I've never been to all the way back here.
(The last hot spot is in a back alley?)
We come to this neighborhood very often.
- Really? - Yes.
- Have you been on this street? - Yes, I have.
You know every place.
But...
There's a smoke meat place here?
- It's acting. - An actor?
- I think so. - An actor.
(Walk up the uphill street all the way.)
It's this alley.
(Unusual props welcome its guests.)
(Who is the owner of this place?)
(Looking around)
- It's here. - This place...
This is a meat restaurant?
- Where's this place? - I don't know.
(The exterior doesn't look like a meat restaurant.)
What's this now?
(They enter the shop dubiously.)
What's this place?
(When you open the iron door, )
(you come across a romantic and cozy space.)
(The interior is decorated thoroughly and meticulously.)
(What kind of place is this?)
What's this place?
(When she's distracted by the romantic interior design)
- It's really nice here. My gosh. - This is...
(She spots something.)
The owner here is...
(A photo frame placed next to the entrance)
- "Big Mouth?" - There's a drama...
titled "Big Mouth."
- He's an actor. - What?
- Is he? - Yes.
- He is. - I watched it too.
Isn't that the drama starring Lee Jong Suk?
Hold on. The owner...
- He must be an actor. - This...
Is that Director Bong Joon Ho?
(Director Bong Joon Ho!)
(He shocked the world with his movie "Parasite.")
(The master of the generation, Director Bong Joon Ho)
- It really is him. - It really is.
(The owner is acquainted with Director Bong Joon Ho?)
- It's Director Bong Joon Ho. - It's him.
- Does he know Director Bong? - Here.
(Shocked murmurs)
The owner really is an actor.
I think I worked with him too.
- With this actor? - Yes.
Right, you would know, Kyung Pyo.
- I... - Let's have a seat.
- Look. - Yes.
- Hold on. - Have a look.
Did he say he owned a steakhouse?
He didn't say that.
His fellow actors would come and...
(Peeking)
- My gosh. - Hello.
(The owner has appeared.)
Hello, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
Hello.
I'm the owner of this shop and an actor,
Hong Ju Hyung.
"Pump Up the Healthy Love,"
"Queen of Divorce," and "Big Mouth."
I do stage plays in Daehak-ro.
(He does stage plays too!)
I met Director Bong Joon Ho...
at an after party of a film festival.
Sir, do you work both as an actor...
- and as the owner here? - Yes.
(That's impressive.)
(And...)
(Thinking)
- When did I meet him? - Which dramas were you on?
(The owner looks very familiar.)
Have you worked with me before?
You look very familiar.
(Has he really worked with Kyung Pyo before?)
I've worked with Kyung Pyo once.
- Right? - Yes, back then.
- It was some time ago. - Yes.
It was "Cross."
Yes, that's right! I knew I worked with him.
(He remembered!)
("Cross" was a drama aired in 2018,)
(and Kyung Pyo was the protagonist.)
(Door suddenly opening)
(The owner enters.)
(Even after that, )
(Kyung Pyo and the owner acted together in many scenes.)
(It's a rather painful memory for the owner.)
(Kyung Pyo and the owner)
- You were in the ambulance... - That's right.
- wearing a suit. - Yes.
- Actor... My gosh. - So he really is an actor.
Then this place must be real.
But you don't know if he actually runs the restaurant.
That's what I don't know. This is crazy.
I think this place is real.
(Is he the real owner? Or is he an actor cast for the role?)
What do customers like to order in this restaurant?
We have a signature menu.
- It's ghee butter steak. - Ghee butter steak!
(Ghee butter steak)
(Ghee butter?)
We must be here because it's very popular.
But ghee butter... Min Kyung knows right away.
- Exactly. - This.
(Do you still eat normal butter?)
(Ghee butter)
Ghee butter is 100 percent pure butter.
You refine various energy sources like lactose and protein.
Only butter will remain, and that's called ghee butter.
(It's already popular overseas for its various effects...)
(like antioxidation and intestinal health!)
It's very healthy butter.
- Yes, ghee butter. - Ghee butter.
That...
(How did this restaurant become popular?)
(It's more ordinary than I imagined.)
The most unique aspect of this restaurant is...
that we don't use fire.
- What? - What?
How?
Is that even possible?
(How do you cook a steak without fire?)
Using only the heat of ghee,
we cook meat.
(They cook a steak using only the heat of ghee!)
(Usually, a steak is cooked with fire.)
(Is it possible to cook meat with only ghee?)
It'll take all day long.
- No, it takes no time. - Does it take no time?
Does it get cooked in no time?
(Coming soon)
(Their jaws drop.)
(Exclamations burst out.)
(Cooking with ghee is the most fascinating.)
(The dish that charmed everyone, )
(ghee butter steak is coming!)
- Sir, please prepare the dishes. - Okay.
- Right away. - We're in your care.
The spot with the light over there is called the steak zone.
When we're ready, you'll get a show.
- Okay. - Okay.
- He's so relaxed. - Yes.
He's a real deal.
Min Kyung and I noticed something while he was talking.
You know how chefs have burn marks from splattered oil.
He had them.
- He had so many on his right arm. - He had them.
Look at his arm.
He has burn marks from splattered oil.
You're right.
(The owner's arm was full of burn marks.)
You can't make those marks...
- on purpose. - They weren't fake.
I think this place is real.
- It has the vibe of a real place. - It's totally real.
- Why do I feel like it's fake? - It's totally real.
- Do you think it's fake? - Am I the strange one here?
- Do you think it's fake? - I think it's fake.
Why? What seems fake?
Ghee butter steak is a dish...
that's in the realm of an expert.
Seok Jin, have you had ghee?
- Yes, I have. - Really?
My family eats it at home.
If it's in the realm of an expert...
- I mean... - That's different.
- He eats ghee. - I eat ghee.
- I see. Not ghee butter steak. - I don't cook a steak with it.
I've heard about it since it's known as the diet butter.
I had no idea that it could be used like this.
I've never had it.
It's the realm of an expert I've never heard of.
(Seok Jin has never heard of ghee butter steak, so it's fake!)
(In that case, how do you make ghee?)
We make ghee by boiling butter.
(Boil unsalted butter for 10 minutes.)
When butter melts,
impurities rise to the surface in the form of bubbles.
I scoop them out.
(Scoop out the impurities.)
When you keep boiling it, the liquid becomes murky yellow.
Then more bubbles will rise to the surface.
(Scoop out the impurities for the 2nd time.)
(You repeat the process.)
During the boiling process, moisture evaporates...
and only clear butter remains.
(Clear butter shows itself.)
Then I sieve the liquid and extract ghee.
(Sieve the last remaining impurities.)
(Then the ghee extraction is over.)
(Lastly, the liquid is cooled.)
(The 100 percent pure ghee is complete.)
During the clarifying process, I lose about 30 percent of butter.
(460g of butter yields 310g of ghee.)
(What kind of a steak can be made with this precious ghee?)
(The owner prepares to cook in earnest.)
Is that ghee?
Yes, I'm boiling ghee.
(What's this pot?)
It's called a cezve. It's a pot where you make...
Turkish coffee.
(Ghee is boiled in a cezve with high heat conductivity.)
- I can hear the boiling sound. - I know.
(The temperature rises fast and the smoke comes up.)
This is the Meat Restaurant with Lots of Smoke.
(That's right.)
You're right.
- That must be the smoke. - That must be it.
(Excited)
- Nice. - Oh, yes.
That explains the description about the smoke.
(When smoke comes up and ghee boils, )
(it's time to prepare the meat.)
It's a cut that brings out ghee.
That's why I use the chuck flap tail.
(He uses the chuck flap tail that has been aged for 3 days.)
(What kind of a steak will ghee and chuck flap tail make?)
The meat isn't cooked at all.
How fascinating. It's raw meat.
I've never had it.
(Will meat really get cooked without fire?)
It's called ghee.
Ghee is 100 percent pure butter.
We bring up the temperature of ghee from 250C...
to a bit over 300C if it's momentary.
The temperature goes a bit over 300C.
(Startled)
- It's 300C. - Is it 300C?
(It's the most fascinating.)
(When ghee is boiled)
Is that butter?
He pours the butter first.
(Butter heats up the plate.)
(Smoke rises.)
- There's so much smoke. - Does he pour the butter first?
Sir, I'm excited.
(He can't wait.)
- It's actual smoke. - Now...
(The meat goes on the plate.)
It's getting cooked.
(On top of ghee that's as hot as lava, )
(chuck flap tail gets laid down gently.)
This is incredible.
(It gets cooked as soon as it touches ghee.)
It's so fascinating.
It looks tasty.
- He doesn't do it haphazardly. - You're right.
(Impressed)
He must've done this a lot.
This is incredible.
(This is how you cook meat without fire.)
- This is insane. - Right?
It looks so tasty.
(When all the meat is on the plate)
- I think he'll pour it now. - Be careful.
(A ghee shower)
- Look at the smoke. - What a performance!
- The smoke is insane. - This is incredible.
(When you pour the remaining ghee, )
(meat gets cooked in 1 second like magic.)
Using only the high heat...
the butter contains,
the steak gets cooked as if it was being deep-fried.
- It's cooked. - Look at the meat.
This is incredible.
It looks tasty. This is incredible.
(The sight makes their mouths water.)
(Gulping)
- I've never seen such a thing. - Me neither.
(He sprinkles salt with the back of his hand!)
- What's this? - I told you.
(It's entertaining to watch.)
(There's always someone who copies it.)
- What a performance. - What a performance.
It bounded off of his hand.
We should've seen that...
- with matcha. - That's right.
- Then we would've been impressed. - Yes.
It's the real deal.
- This... - It's the real deal.
(While meat gets salted and cooked in ghee, )
(the owner picks up baguette.)
- It's cooked. - He'll lay the bread.
(The next ingredient that'll get a hot taste of ghee)
The plate must still be hot.
(Tasty food next to tasty food)
This is amazing.
There's one reason why I cook the ingredients like this.
It prevents the flavor loss due to the heat loss.
On the ceramic plate that's heated up,
I pour the heated ghee and cook the ingredients.
Then there's no flavor loss in the butter.
The baguette soaks up...
the flavors of the butter.
(Impressed)
- What a description. - It sounds delicious.
He didn't stutter once.
Even the description was perfect.
(Even the description was perfect.)
This is... This is real. Totally.
Didn't you say it was fake earlier?
I said that earlier. But the way he tiled it,
- the ventilation system, - Exactly.
And his comments changed my mind. If this is fake...
- It's not acting. - No.
It looks tasty.
(I don't care if it's real or fake. It looks tasty.)
I'll also serve pasta and fried rice.
(Impressed)
Will they be cooked on the plate?
The ghee is seasoned already.
(He adds pasta.)
I add one egg yolk.
(One egg yolk and grana padano get added.)
(Then the pasta is mixed well.)
Thick carbonara is ready.
(Ghee butter carbonara with the flavors of butter and meat)
He added it right away.
(A round of applause)
- This is incredible. - Seriously.
- This is incredible. - Bravo.
This is incredible.
(This is insane!)
Let's exclude this place and choose between numbers 1 and 2.
Let's choose between numbers 1 and 2.
- You can't do this at a fake place. - You just can't.
- Look at Min Kyung. - Oh, my.
Their reaction is genuine.
I'll come back here.
This is incredible.
(He grates cheese that'll add the flavors.)
Cheese!
I missed it! Please do it again.
I missed it.
I'll do it again.
(Here comes the fan service.)
(She films it properly this time.)
What a delicate touch.
- Thank you. - This carbonara is a real deal.
(Highly satisfied)
- Can we rent the whole restaurant? - Yes, you can.
(The last item is ghee and kimchi fried rice...)
(toasted in a waffle pan.)
- What's this? - Fried rice.
(Exclaiming)
- Waffle. - Fried rice waffle.
(Full of the rich and buttery flavors)
It looks delicious. There's everything I like.
(The ghee butter steak set is complete.)
(It's the most popular restaurant on social media!)
My restaurant went viral through social media.
Through texts and calls,
I got over 170 reservation requests.
The monthly sales is about 35,000 dollars.
(The secret double life...)
(of the actor with 15 years of experience)
Sixth Sense members,
is this place real?
- I'm so curious about the baguette. - I want that baguette.
Me too.
It's unbelievable.
It's bound to be tasty.
(It looks unbelievably good.)
(My goodness)
The smell is no joke.
I'll help you with plating.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
He even helps with plating.
Baguette goes to the bottom.
- So that's how you eat it. - I'll plate it like this.
You'll cut it this way...
so that you can have the first bite with baguette...
and a bit of salt.
(He recommends that they dip it in salt.)
I can't wait.
(How does it taste?)
Let's dip it in salt.
Jae Seok, it looks so tasty.
You sliced it so prettily.
It looks tasty, Jae Seok.
(Curious)
(How does it taste?)
How does it taste?
(Impressed)
Oh, my!
(A feel-good bite)
(Just how does it taste?)
(Impressed nod)
- He means it. - Is it insane?
- Is it that good? - Oh, my!
- Do you mean it? - He means it.
- It's Jae Seok's honest reaction. - Oh, my.
Try it. I'm serious.
- What am I going to do? - I'm close to tears.
It's insanely rich.
Oh, my.
- I'm so sad to see it go. - It's insanely rich.
(Seok Jin takes a bite right away.)
(Moaning)
(What was that sound?)
Is it that tasty?
- Is it that good? - Really?
Oh, my. Hold on. I'm nervous.
I feel like...
- it's overly tasty. - Really?
- I'm nervous. - What am I going to do?
Hurry up and try it.
(Eating)
Try them together. How is it?
(Insanely tasty)
Bravo!
It's so tasty.
- The baguette is insane. - Try it, Min Kyung.
The baguette.
The meat is tasty as it is,
- but the baguette provides a kick. - Yes.
Seriously.
People will be curious about...
why we're obsessing over the baguette.
It's tastier than meat.
It's crispy and soft.
The savoriness of the meat...
and the crispiness and richness of the baguette...
are perfect together.
- It's crazy. - The baguette.
You need to eat it with the baguette. Hurry up.
(Min Kyung takes a bite.)
Isn't it incredible?
(It's incredible!)
Isn't it insane?
(Moved)
- And there was a show. - That's right.
- We had a fun show before eating. - Yes,
- it was so much fun. - It's so tasty.
(It's a treat to the eyes and mouth.)
(I can't believe I didn't know about the taste.)
It's so tasty. It's insane.
- Let's eat it with radish kimchi. - Hurry up and try it.
(Hae Ri tries it first.)
(Chewing)
(What's this?)
(In ecstasy)
- The kimchi is insane. - Is the kimchi insane?
It cleanses the palate.
(The clean taste gets rid of the greasiness.)
I'm seriously angry.
It's so tasty.
(It's so tasty!)
- She's angry. - Why are you angry?
- Isn't it tasty? - Pasta.
It's the taste I've never had.
It's so tasty.
- Shall we try pasta? - Pasta is insane.
- Seriously. - Pasta is insane.
(Jae Seok tries it first.)
(Impressed)
(This is the taste.)
(Seok Jin slurps pasta as well.)
(Impressed)
Pasta is really tasty.
It's really savory.
It's totally creamy.
(Min Kyung tries the ghee butter pasta.)
(Her eyes go wide.)
I love dishes like this one.
(What was that?)
Isn't it the tastiest?
(She can't even describe the taste.)
(This is incredible.)
- Look at her face. - Right?
Pasta takes first place.
- I agree. - Pasta takes first place.
So this is how you use ghee.
I shouldn't have eaten it with food that tasted bad.
I thought "Ghee" meant...
that it was butter with special energy.
(I thought that it was butter with special energy.)
- Only the fried rice remains. - Do you want it?
- We should try it. - We should try it.
It's the taste of kimchi fried rice that was made with animal fat.
- This is... - It's so tasty.
- Right? - He should train other chefs.
Seriously.
The flavors play with my tongue.
I don't know I can say this,
but this is number one among all the places on the show.
- What? - Really?
This is number one among all the places on the show.
- Here comes ramyeon. - Thank you.
Beef hangover ramyeon.
- Beef. - Beef hangover ramyeon.
It's bound to be tasty.
I boil the leftover meat from shaping the steak...
in butter.
Then I add insanely spicy Vietnamese chili powder.
It becomes a dish that resembles the Chinese beef noodle soup.
(Ghee butter beef hangover ramyeon)
In case the food was too greasy,
the soup will wash it down.
(My goodness)
I bet it's the taste I love the most.
- Have you tried it? - Just now.
(Hae Ri takes a big mouthful.)
(Humming in approval)
It's so tasty.
- It's so spicy. - How is the soup so rich?
(He blows on the noodles.)
- It's so tasty. - It's so tasty.
- It's so spicy. - How is the soup so rich?
It's so tasty.
(Nodding)
- Seriously... - The noodles...
(The taste makes him laugh.)
Have you tried the soup?
- I want to copy the recipe. - I haven't tried the soup.
This isn't ramyeon.
- This is a proper dish. - This isn't ramyeon.
From the spiciness,
consistency,
and noodles...
It's perfect.
(It's perfect in every way.)
Try the soup. Jae Seok, try the soup.
Gosh, this dish...
The taste goes beyond my imagination.
(The taste settles the stomach.)
Look at the oil on the surface.
It's perfect.
(Savory ghee oil floats on the red soup.)
It's so tasty that I'm going crazy.
I have children, so I know that this ramyeon is...
- too spicy for them. - It's spicy indeed.
- But they'll love everything else. - They'll love everything else.
But I can think of it this way. If I come here with children,
this ramyeon will be mine.
- Only you can eat it. - I see.
- Only you can eat it. - That's right.
It makes you happy to have a dish to yourself.
- "You guys can't eat this." - He's the dad.
I see that even dads have such a thought.
Of course, they do.
Later on, you'll find yourself fighting over a piece of ham.
A piece of ham?
The last piece.
It was really tasty.
- I really enjoyed the food. - Sir.
We've never done this before, right?
- We've never clapped before. - Even if it appears simple...
This is the first time. We've never been in agreement.
- We've never done this before. - I know.
I've already excluded this place.
- It isn't a candidate in my heart. - You're right.
- But we need to be suspicious. - We need to be suspicious.
If I must choose a point that feels fake,
the overall setup...
- is something a chef would do. - It seems like a chef's work.
It seems like a chef's work.
(The Sixth Sense members...)
(have been fooled by the fake dishes...)
(that were created by the team of chefs!)
This is a course...
a chef might come up with.
Here's what I think.
Why did that chef share this recipe?
They should've sold it themselves.
Perhaps they didn't know...
that it'd be such a hit.
(Maybe they didn't know.)
I bet they were shocked.
Perhaps they developed a recipe...
the actor could recreate...
- without a lot of techniques. - Right.
He just needed to boil ghee and pour it on the plate.
That might be the case.
(That's plausible.)
(When you think about it, )
(the recipe didn't require a lot of techniques.)
Since the recipe didn't require a lot of techniques,
an actor could act and cook at the same time.
- Right. - That might be it.
- Now that I'm seeing it... - That's right.
As a possibly fake place,
the things that seemed perfect before...
- They were too perfect. - They were too perfect.
There were a lot of them.
- Such things... - The owner's comments?
- They were too perfect. - The comments.
He showed that moment when he made comments while cooking...
without stuttering once.
An actor can do that.
He can do that, right?
- You just need to memorize it. - He can treat it like a line.
Things are becoming complicated again.
(A real owner who's too perfect? A fake owner who has been hired?)
The taste and...
Once you become suspicious,
- there's no end. - There's no end, right?
- There's no end. - Now, this place seems fake.
But just a moment ago, we were cheering.
"It's so tasty. Bravo."
We didn't suspect it one bit.
If this place is fake,
the owner should run this business.
- I agree. - I agree.
(Owner of Meat Restaurant with Lots of Smoke)
(1. A performance that entertains the eyes and mouth)
(2. A fantastic taste everyone likes 3. Overly perfect explanation)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Your hands are covered in scars.
(Checking the scars)
- The owner... - I saw his hands just now.
They're covered in scars.
They're covered in scars from splattered oil.
Even if you learn the recipe in a hurry,
- you can get red marks like those. - Right.
- If you practice for 2 months... - If he has done it for 2 months...
- Then you can get those marks. - Yes.
If you practice for two months...
But you can't get those marks in two months.
For an actor, his body is his fortune.
So he would've worn arm guards to prevent any injuries.
I've become confused toward the end.
If it's fake,
I'll open that restaurant.
Will you open that restaurant?
- You'll copy the recipe. - There you go again.
He wants to open a business.
(He showed his desire to open a business.)
I'm certain...
that number three isn't real.
- It can't be real. - Do you think it's fake?
- I'm certain that it's fake. - Why?
It was too perfect.
That came out of nowhere.
Can't you give that performance...
- if you practice for two months? - You can pull it off.
- I bet you can do it. - You can pull it off.
I don't think it's number three.
We need to be suspicious.
It's so hard.
To be honest, I don't know.
(As always, choosing one won't be easy.)
Why don't we decide on a place that isn't fake?
- Number 3 isn't fake. - I'll exclude number 3.
- You don't think it's number 3. - Let's exclude number 3.
I want number three to be real. Seriously.
- Let's exclude number 3. - I think number 3 is real.
- I want to think... - Number three is real.
- less. - I think it's real.
- I want number three to be real. - Yes.
- I want number three to be real. - It can't be fake.
Min Kyung doesn't agree.
- I think number three is fake. - You think it's fake.
- Then are numbers 1 and 2 real? - Yes.
- Is number one real? - I think it's real.
Number two is real as well.
I think she's a young owner who isn't used to running a business.
(Number 2, Owner with Lots of Jeju's matcha galbitang)
(Seok Jin was unsure about the use of matcha.)
(It's tasty.)
(It seemed to captivate both the old and new generations.)
(But the reviews on the taste were mixed.)
(This place is fake because it has a strange dish.)
(The owner who used to be a trot singer?)
(Did a former singer get hired to play a fake owner?)
That was the key point of number one.
Does the owner run a cafe and a meat place at the same time?
(Everyone was shocked.)
(The owner who runs a yogurt cafe and meat restaurant?)
(Owner Who Does This Too's yogurt green onion pork skirt)
(This is it.)
(What does the meat taste so good?)
(She gets angry when the food is good.)
(But I keep getting this thought.)
(It feels like this was made by chefs.)
(Is this a new menu developed by chefs?)
Can the unit cost be met with all that yogurt?
Surely not.
- Whenever we thought about that... - Gosh!
(Gosh!)
- What is it? - Number one.
- Did you get hit again? - Gosh!
(She has been getting a lot of stomach pain today.)
(Gosh!)
- "Gosh, my stomach!" - "Gosh, my stomach!"
Jae Seok! Menu-wise, I think it's number one.
And there was a man who couldn't answer us.
- It felt off. - He avoided us.
- Like this. - Right.
(Who are you?)
(Are you the owner?)
(Keeping silent)
Should we go for number one then?
- Number 1. - I choose number 1.
- Do we only get 1 chance? - I'll choose number 1 as well.
- We only get one chance. - What about you, Min Kyung?
- Number 1. - Number 3?
- I think it's number 3. - No. It's number 1.
I think it's number two.
- I choose number 1 as well. - Do you think it's number 2, Mimi?
Let's have a show of hands. I will go for number one.
- Number one. - Me too.
- Number one has the most votes. - Right.
- I have a good feeling about this. - After a few times...
- It's number 1. - Number 1?
- Number one. - Hold on. Excuse me.
Listen to what I have to say.
- You're turning against the camera? - Oh, right.
This is what I think about number one.
It feels like a trick to seem like a fake place.
It feels like a trick instead?
It feels like a trick to seem fake, Jae Seok.
If that's the case,
- all places feel suspicious. - Right.
- Let's go with number 1. - Let's go with number 1.
- The majority vote. - One, two, three.
- Number 1! - Number 1!
(She still is firm about her vote for number 3.)
Gosh, I can't watch!
Gosh, I don't have a clue.
We can't get it wrong once again today!
I'm so curious! Please!
(Will number 1 be the right answer?)
- We're awful at this. - We have to get it right today.
(Sixth Sense: City Tour 2)
(Today's travel destination, Yongsan)
(Every place is a hot place.)
- Hey! - For some reason...
(Overflowing with hot places)
(Yongsan-gu)
It does seem fake from here.
(Find the hidden one with a double life!)
(Source from Studio Dragon)
It's me!
This person is real.
(There's just one fake spot!)
(Pork skirt and green onion...)
(drenched in yogurt?)
Yogurt? This one can't be real.
I think we got it right.
(Number 1, Owner Who Does This Too)
It's number two.
(Matcha with galbitang)
- This one was good. - This was good.
I enjoyed it.
(Number 2, Owner with Lots of Jeju)
(Chuck flap tail must be grilled with ghee butter.)
- The one was... - It was amazing.
- It was amazing. - It was truly amazing.
I think things will go wild if it's number three.
(Which place is fake?)
I feel nervous. Why do I feel so nervous?
Gosh.
- I want to get it right. - Let's get it right today.
It does feel like number one is the right one.
(Who is the fake hidden owner with a double life in Yongsan?)
(Which place is fake?)
Oh, gosh.
Gosh, which one could it be?
- Here it comes. - Please.
Gosh, I feel nervous!
(Which place is fake in Yongsan?)
- Here it comes. - Please.
Gosh, I feel nervous!
(The place hidden in Yongsan)
Please.
(Which place is fake?)
(Number 2, Owner with Lots of Jeju)
(Fake)
- I told you! - What?
(In vain)
(Stunned)
(Mimi...)
(Sighing)
(I also want to go with number 1.)
I told you this one felt fake!
I told you that it felt fake!
- I get this feeling at times. - Number two is fake?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy!
(Groaning)
Gosh, we...
(A heartbreaking pain)
(Sighing)
(Current score: 1 win and 5 losses)
(D-65 before the Episode 6 shoot)
This was worked on two months before the shoot again?
(The production crew was looking for hot place ideas for Yongsan.)
(Yongsan hot place)
So this actually appeared.
What is that?
(A banner with feet?)
(The daughter from Jeju who learned how to make galbi from her father)
So the restaurant was real.
(There are extraordinary messages on it as well!)
(How is there a human banner?)
Gosh, she went through so much.
That was great of her.
That was truly great of her. Gosh.
(Take coffee for free)
(Who are you?)
We watched a short video of you.
You were working hard to promote the place with a banner on you.
I did whatever I could.
There wasn't much I could do while the place was under construction.
That was why I decided to go out...
- and do anything... - That's amazing of her.
- on my own. - She seems to be very bright.
She's an amazing person.
Hello. It has been one year since I have come from Jeju Island.
I have been a meat restaurant owner for a month now...
and my name is Jung Ji Won.
My father runs a meat restaurant.
I worked at my father's restaurant...
- for around 4 and a half years. - She saved 100,000 dollars?
While working at the meat restaurant,
- I saved 100,000 dollars... - She's amazing.
And I got a loan of around 50,000 dollars.
So it cost me around 150,000 dollars for the restaurant.
(She opened a meat restaurant with 150,000 dollars.)
(She's a young owner that deserves praise.)
I got a loan,
and going out of business is the last thing I want to do.
That is why I'm giving it my all for this.
(The human banner came to life...)
(out of the desperation of the rookie owner.)
She's amazing.
(She's a Gen MZ owner who reveals her own place of origin.)
(She uploaded her business story...)
That's amazing of her.
(and promotional short videos on social media.)
(The young owner who is working hard every day for her dream)
She went through so much.
(However!)
What is it?
(When the production crew visited during lunch...)
I'm not getting many customers during lunchtime.
(The restaurant is empty during lunchtime.)
This area is full of office buildings.
(The place in Namyeong Station is located by an office complex.)
If there isn't a lunchtime menu,
I don't think many office workers will come.
It would be hard to grill meat for lunch...
as it would make the clothes smell.
(There needs to be a solution for the young owner who is stuck!)
Gosh, it perfectly worked out.
(A special helper for the rookie owner!)
Who is it?
(Do you remember the AI omakase?)
AI omakase?
How will we ever get it right?
It might end with us getting it right just once.
(The members were completely fooled.)
You guys are getting it wrong even on screen.
(Shutting his eyes tight)
- We mostly got it wrong. - Hey!
We only got it right once.
(Michelin 1 Star for 4 consecutive years)
It's him!
Chef Kim.
(Chef Kim Do Yun)
- She's from Jeju Island. - He was the one that helped?
- She runs a meat restaurant. - Surely she got help from him.
(If that's so...)
First of all, Jeju Island...
is known for its green tea.
Right. Jeju Island is known for its green tea.
It was a bit strange that Osulloc green tea was used.
- I'm really sorry, Mimi. - Osulloc...
- We missed all of what you said. - Right.
- No one listened to me. - Right.
- No one listened. - I'm sorry, Mimi.
- You should've mentioned it. - I did!
- You should've mentioned Osulloc. - I did!
(And so, )
(we went to Jeju Island to develop the matcha galbitang!)
Gosh, that's just amazing.
(Will they be able to find the right tea for galbitang?)
(They taste the matcha noodles...)
(for the development of the matcha broth.)
(Satisfied)
- This one tastes clean, right? - Yes. It's delicious.
The matcha makes it feel like boiled pork.
(It's time to choose the right tea.)
(Starting from the green tea newly harvested this year, )
(they tried many different types.)
This will be perfect for soup dishes.
(The tea with a rich flavor and less bitterness was chosen.)
It will enhance the gamey smell when put in hot water.
Potatoes will be added to add a savory flavor.
Just match it to this level of concentration.
(She even learned how to whisk the matcha.)
So after doing that, the tea was added to the dish.
(The matcha galbitang with a rich broth is ready!)
That was really good.
(However...)
What?
(The owner was called a trot singer.)
Gosh, what is all this?
(Is she really a trot singer?)
The theme of Episode Six is The Owner's Double Life.
What kind of double life would be right for her?
She's always full of energy.
She dreamed of becoming a celebrity.
- She was full of talent. - Right. A lot of talent.
She knew how to do many different things.
As she's full of energy,
how would it be if we make her into a trot singer?
- So she's not a trot singer? - She's not a trot singer.
No wonder her singing wasn't that...
- Her singing was... - Right?
I couldn't mention it as...
-I didn't want to hurt her feelings. -Right?
She looked so shy...
when she was supposed to be a professional singer.
She even kept her eyes closed.
(What is the secret behind this song?)
(Who are the ones who made the fake trot singer?)
Hold on. Is it someone I know?
(How to make AI music)
(How Gen MZers make music these days)
- AI? - Gosh.
So it was made by AI.
(Which AI came up with the lyrics?)
Even the lyrics?
(ChatGPT)
No wonder. "Welcome..."
- sounded too corny. - Right.
That was such a corny title.
(Which AI came up with the song?)
(AI music creator, Suno)
(The owner's voice was taught as well.)
(The digital single album is ready!)
(Song written by Suno)
- "Soon Ho." - Gosh.
"GPT."
(Lyrics by Gwon Pil Tae)
Gosh, there were clues everywhere.
(What about the pictures at the entrance...)
(that fooled the members?)
- Right. - The pictures.
We talked about them.
We talked about them until the end.
Hello. This is the Sixth Sense team.
We are trying to make the fake owner...
- a trot singer. - Did she meet a trot singer?
- Right. - May we use your audition photo,
- Ms. Kim So You? - What?
- My photo? - See? It wasn't taken with her.
That's fine.
That sounds like fun.
(She allowed her photo to be used.)
(Hello, Manager. May we use her photos taken with Kim So You?)
(Yes. You may use them.)
(Both of them allowed their photos to be used.)
- So it was Photoshopped? - It was edited?
But... Gosh!
(The owner's face was edited in.)
(The original photo that looked like this...)
- That's just... - Gosh!
That was done so well.
(Photo editing is easy, isn't it?)
- It did feel quite awkward. - Right.
(Another helper was met in person.)
Yes?
- Hello. - Hello.
It's Hong Ja.
(Trot singer, Hong Ja)
It's so hard to predict.
Gosh, how are we supposed to figure that out?
This was done so meticulously.
(From a regular meat restaurant owner, )
(she made a great transformation into a trot singer.)
Yongsan has many famous meat restaurants.
While I was torn about what to do...
to survive in this red ocean,
I felt really grateful to get this opportunity.
I will do my best...
to make this place a top meat restaurant in Yongsan.
Sixth Sense,
I am not a trot singer...
and this dish is fake.
(Matcha galbitang)
(Fake)
- We really wish you the best. - Right.
- Make it big! - You deserve it.
- In the future... - During the next shoot,
I should definitely follow Mimi's opinion.
I'm sorry, Mimi.
- I'm quite good at this. - Well...
Can you cut out the part of me saying it's number three on my own?
I feel so stupid.
You never mentioned number two a single time.
She kept saying it was number three.
- Right. - You're totally off.
Gosh, what do we do?
We got it wrong again.
Gosh. We got it right once out of six attempts.
Last week...
It's time to decide on who will serve the penalty.
Do you know what our penalty is?
(The penalty is to upload a cringeworthy post for 24 hours.)
(Hae Ri sticks in her hand naturally.)
- Just pick one? - Yes.
- Oh, no! - That just drives me crazy.
Hold on! Why did she get to pick?
- I don't know. - I thought everyone picked one.
It's over once one name is picked.
- That's not it. - It's over once one name is picked.
- You thought everyone went. - Do I just open it now?
- Yes. - Please don't be me.
- It must be. - I don't think it's me.
- No way! - It's not me.
- Who is it? - It's me, isn't it?
It's you!
(It's you, Kang Min Kyung.)
- Gosh! - Nice one.
There you go.
- Nice one. - That was great.
Nice one, Min Kyung.
(The penalty post can be found on her social media page now!)
(Seventh City Tour)
(A tourist city...)
(with culture and art)
(Paju)
(Today's strange theme, Drama City Paju?)
(Shocking...)
(and even more shocking)
(A fake place with a dramatic twist is coming.)
(For the Paju Tour with the most stunning sights, )
(which special guest will join them?)
(Wonpil and Young K of DAY6)
(Has a rising star of deduction appeared?)
(He points things out with a smile.)
(Each item is looked at sharply.)
(Thinking)
(I can't stand being curious!)
(Rising star of deduction, Wonpil)
(Hold on.)
(Eyes opening wide)
(Right!)
(The members get surprised by Wonpil's hunch.)
(While everyone is making their deductions seriously...)
(Have you tried the risotto?)
(No.)
(It's really good.)
(You aren't interested in finding the fake place.)
(Eating)
(Eating some more)
(Eating again)
(Foodie K lets Wonpil make the deductions.)
(A page of the City Tour written with the DAY6 members)
(I want to see it.)
(I'm curious.)
(Why don't you come and check it out next week?)