♪Traversing the vast expanse of time♪
♪Smiling proudly
in the mortal world alone♪
♪Cold moonlight♪
♪Earth as paper, sky as brush♪
♪This life like ink splashed on paper♪
♪Indulging in ups and downs♪
♪Coldly confronting
the approaching edges, sword and blade♪
♪My heart is narrow,
only holding heaven and earth♪
♪Boundless sea,
countless surging waves in the dark♪
♪Aeons just like a fleeting moment,
using youth as color♪
♪A silver-white hue climbs up
the temples, undaunted by setbacks♪
♪In the eyes, an unquenchable light♪
♪A body of proud bones,
unbending in the face of wind and frost♪
♪Smiling at the thorny webs♪
♪Being a lone wolf,
born to be solitary and independent♪
♪My pride alters not a jot♪
♪Resounding loudly through the clouds♪
♪In the cold world,
a heart burning hot for you♪
=Snow Eagle Lord=
=Episode 6=
Young Master, Young Master.
Young Master, be careful.
Be careful, Young Master.
Young Master.
You don't need to help me. Step back.
Young Master, Young Master, be careful.
What are you afraid of?
This is what I carefully developed,
Flying Seal.
As you stick it on,
you can fly
without using Dou Qi or spells.
Young Master, Young Master.
Are you alright, Young Master?
Are you okay, Young Master?
Young Master, are you fine?
Next time,
I will definitely make it.
Young Master,
you've said that
215 times already.
Are you questioning me?
No, no, no, not at all.
Young Master, in my opinion,
studying on your own here
isn't the solution.
You need to find an expert for guidance.
That way, you'll definitely
be able to fly sooner.
Yeah.
Guidance from a pro.
Sister,
where are you traveling
this time?
Take me with you, please.
This time,
I am going on cultivation.
I am trying to get into
the Changfeng Academy.
You?
Changfeng Academy?
You are pulling my leg, right?
You rascal.
Keep laughing.
Ouch, ouch.
But,
how did our father agree to it?
I told him
I'm going out to find him
a good son-in-law.
You're so bold.
In the Changfeng Academy,
there are all
the most outstanding young talents
from Dragon Mountain Empire.
And their martial arts skills
are the best in the empire.
Especially that Dongbo Xueying.
You just said that
Changfeng Academy
is full of the strongest
who are adept at martial arts
from the empire?
Of course.
The Knight Changfeng, Chi Qiubai,
personally teaches
and instructs his disciples.
Chi Qiu...
Wait for me.
Kong Hao, I haven't finished yet.
I'm going to Changfeng Academy too.
(Blessing Pavilion)
Take care on the way.
I wish you both success
in passing the assessment
of the Changfeng Academy.
Rest assured, Master.
Thank you
for your hospitality, Master Sikong.
I'll take my leave.
(Water Daoist Temple)
Sister,
why aren't we going in?
What exactly are we waiting for?
(Changfeng Academy)
Finally here.
I want to see if this Changfeng Academy
can really help you
become a Transcendent
when you graduate as it is said.
Is it that amazing?
(Changfeng Academy)
Girl.
The exam is still some time away.
Don't tire yourself standing here.
Why don't you
rest in my carriage for a while?
Who are you?
Stay away from my big sister.
I didn't do anything.
My apologies.
My younger brother is a bit unruly.
I'll take him away right now.
Changfeng Academy
is not like other places.
The examination is extremely important.
Follow me.
Don't be careless.
Alright.
Understood, brother.
Oh no.
I didn't wear a nice hairpin.
I need to go buy a hairpin now.
Brother,
later on,
if Dongbo Xueying comes,
remember
to call me right away.
W-Where are you going?
Sister, isn't that...?
I don't even know
what Dongbo Xueying looks like.
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
Fantastic!
Miss, feel free to browse.
Too small.
Miss,
what about trying this one?
You have such great taste.
I'll take this one.
Here, thank you.
Come, take a look, have a look.
I want this little duck.
Sweetie, but we don't have money.
I will
make you a doll duck when back home,
okay?
I want it.
Little girl, which one do you want?
I will buy it for you.
I want the little duck.
Little duck.
That won't do.
It's fine, it's fine.
Sir,
how much for this?
Miss,
please have a look.
These items are not for sale.
As long as you answer
the questions here correctly,
you can take the corresponding prize
home.
Then there you go.
Miss, don't be impatient.
If you want to answer a question,
you need to spend a hundred coins
to buy a ticket.
(All businessmen are profiteers indeed.)
(You're even better
at business than my father.)
Fine.
I'll buy a ticket.
Miss, please listen to the question.
There are a hundred monks
and a hundred steamed buns.
One big monk eats three steamed buns,
while three little monks
share one steamed bun.
The hundred steamed buns
are just enough to be divided.
Please tell me,
how many big and small monks
are there in total?
There are 25 big monks
and 75 little monks.
Great. Bravo!
You are really amazing.
What a smart girl.
Take your prize and leave now.
We wanted this one.
How could you give us this?
I said it's this one.
How come you don't keep your word?
If you don't leave now,
don't try to do it ever.
You.
Stop.
Come back.
(Shadow Steps)
Someone's stealing.
Come back!
Don't run if you dare.
There you off.
Warrior, please spare my life.
I don't dare to do it again.
I'm telling you.
Admit defeat for the bet.
You promised to give this
to her.
Warrior, whatever you want,
I'll give it to you.
I'll listen to you.
Here.
Thank you.
Little girl, this is for you.
Thank you, miss.
Listen to your mother.
Say goodbye to the miss.
Big sister, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Thank you for your help.
Your move is quite special.
No.
When I was a kid,
my father always hit me.
And when he hit me,
my mother would ask me to run.
I became good at it
after practicing a lot.
Where's my hairpin?
Hairpin? What hairpin?
I must
lose my hairpin
when the crowd was pushing through.
Use your move to help me find it.
Alright. I...
I can't, miss.
I have something urgent to do.
I have to go to
Changfeng Academy for the exam.
Changfeng Academy?
I'm taking the exam too.
Let's go together.
Really?
Let's hurry up.
We're running out of time.
(Changfeng Academy)
Sister.
Xueying, you're here.
You're here too.
So you're Dongbo Xueying.
Ever since the last time we met
at Snow Stone Fort...
Xueying.
You know them?
We're running out of time
for the exam. Let's go.
The Changfeng Academy exam
now begins.
The exam is
to pass through this door
and enter that door.
Those who pass through that door
will become
the disciples of Changfeng Academy.
Ms. Tanshi,
you've been talking for so long,
but you didn't tell us
where on earth the doors are.
This door is right here.
As for where that door is,
it's up to your own abilities.
Although this passage seems ordinary,
it must hide a mystery.
I think so too.
The exam of Changfeng Academy
won't be this simple.
We should still be careful.
Don't rush.
Let's make clear the situation first.
In the world of martial arts,
only speed is invincible.
It's just a door, right?
Once I pass this door,
I'll be
a disciple of Changfeng Academy.
Watch me.
Why am I still here?
Try again.
Sister, let's use wisdom.
Look at my Flying Seal.
Hao, be careful.
Isn't this very simple?
Let's go.
Hao.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
The passage you see before you
is not as easy
as it seems.
The real challenge is yet to come.
If you can't overcome
your own weaknesses,
you won't pass the test.
How do you know that?
I've been taking the test for 38 years.
It's not that easy.
It's okay.
Just follow me.
(Why are there)
(so many men in black?)
(What's going on?)
How did I end up here?
My father never allows me to come here.
I didn't expect
my father actually allowed me to see
the Kong family's account book.
My father actually agreed to
let me do business.
Changfeng Academy is great.
They're afraid I'll
get hungry during the exam,
so they prepared
so many delicious things.
No.
It is not real.
This is an illusion.
My mother was taken away.
This is my demon.
(If I lose my Flying Snow Spear,)
(I will definitely fail the exam.)
(I can't panic.)
(I must stay calm.)
(Since it's an illusion,)
(I can do anything.)
Jingqiu, Jingqiu, wake up.
Jingqiu, Jingqiu.
It was just an illusion.
It wasn't real.
These were all dreams?
Not real?
Not real.
Xueying Territory.
Xueying.
That's not right.
I came to take the exam
at Changfeng Academy, didn't I?
Xueying came to Changfeng Academy.
I need to find Xueying.
How...
How did I end up sitting here
and reading the account book?
Hallucination.
This works too.
Kong Hao, that silly boy.
He must be thinking
his spell seals succeeded.
Our father said
you would be in charge of
the Kong family's business.
No, no, no.
Wake up.
You're still biting? Look.
Look what you've bit it into.
The chicken feet, the pig's trotters...
A-All were...
We are eliminated?
Fine, let's go.
Xueying, look.
Qian.
There are also Kun, Li, and Gen.
These are all directions.
I understand.
As long as we defeat the nightmares,
there will be new characters.
If we can figure out
the pattern of these characters,
we may be able to break the array.
Quick.
Let's wake everyone up first.
Rude. One more.
So rude.
Wake up, wake up.
You smell good.
Wake up.
Boring.
How can this be a dream?
It's so real.
Situ Hong, wake up, wake up.
(Now that you've joined my Si Family,)
(you must work hard to cultivate)
(as we Si Family
never raises the useless.)
He'll die if this continues.
I'll figure it out.
I will become
the first place at Changfeng Academy.
These were all dreams. Not real.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Everyone, step back.
Be careful.
(Changfeng Academy)
I'll be back next year.
Xueying, look.
These characters
though seem move
chaotically and rapidly,
in fact,
the sum and difference of each row's
horizontal and vertical lines are seven.
Look,
the center.
No matter how the characters move,
it will always form
the shape of the Big Dipper.
Presumably,
as long as we move towards
this Big Dipper,
we'll definitely reach "that door."
I'll give it a try.
Hold on.
The stars that form the Big Dipper are
Dubhe, Merak,
Phecda, Megrez,
Alioth, Mizar, and Alkaid.
Each star has its own attributes.
Dubhe is the hub of the seven stars.
Merak is responsible for rotation.
Phecda masters change.
Megrez holds power.
Alioth balances weight.
Mizar opens Yang Qi.
Alkaid represents brightness.
Among these seven stars,
Merak and Phecda,
rotation and change,
are the most difficult to control.
I'm afraid there might be danger.
When landing,
try not to land on
these two stars.
Why don't you give it a try this time?
I'll do it.
The Dipper's handle points east.
Alkaid is in the west.
Merak and Phecda are at the bottom.
Dubhe is for heaven
and Merak is for earth.
Phecda for men,
Megrez for time, Alioth for sound,
Mizar for law, and Alkaid for stars.
Among these seven stars,
Alioth is the brightest,
while Megrez is the dimmest.
Just find the positions
of these two stars
based on brightness,
and then determine
the different directions
according to the Dipper's handle.
Great.
Sister!
Congratulations, everyone,
for passing
the Changfeng Academy's exam.
Passed!
Great, bravo, great!
Finally passed.
Good.
Great.
Bravo.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Don't you hurry up and greet your Dean,
Knight Changfeng?
Greetings, Dean.
You all are
the future guardians of
Dragon Mountain Empire.
I hope you can
practice diligently,
maintain your true nature,
and forge together
to protect Dragon Mountain Empire
and the Xia Clan.
Yes!
Not bad.
Yes.
Look at that mountain.
(Orchid & Bamboo Yard)
Yes.
This is Orchid & Bamboo Yard,
your dormitory.
Go in and have a look.
The living conditions here
are too simple, aren't they?
It's simpler than my kitchen.
This is not like
the conditions you had at home.
Coming here
is mainly for cultivation
to improve your martial arts skills.
Yes, Dean Changfeng.
I'm okay with living here.
That small Practice Field,
where you
practice martial arts.
Without my permission,
do not trespass anywhere else.
That's it?
It's not enough for me
to show my skills.
Alright.
Get settled and rest early.
I live in the row behind,
in the westernmost room.
If you have any questions,
you can reach out.
Master.
I just want to ask
where the female disciples live.
Why? What's so funny?
I want to find a Transcendent
to be my wife.
Of course, I need to know
where my wife lives.
I think
you are
aiming at the moon.
Borong.
The female disciples
live in the Flower Pavilion next door.
You'll have classes together,
so you'll meet them.
Get some rest early.
Farewell, Dean Changfeng.
I'm exhausted from working all day.
This bed is too hard.
How can I sleep, brother?
Don't be so picky.
It's not like being at home
when you're outside.
Just make do.
Yeah, you can make do.
But we still have to be here
for three years.
The big beds we slept in at home
are made of Phoebe sheareri.
The soft cotton wadding
stitched with silk and satin
is so comfortable.
Have you ever slept
in such a comfortable bed?
I know, I know.
Just like lying on a cloud,
it dissipates all the fatigue
from your body.
Alright, alright.
Stop living in castles in the air.
Face reality instead.
Everyone,
my younger brother and I
are from the Si Mansion in Nanqin.
From now on, we are fellow disciples.
Please take care of us.
Take care, take care.
The Si Family? I know.
Is it the one that
had an accident guarding the Demon Well
and letting the demons enter
Dragon Mountain Empire?
It is said that the Si Family
optimized your martial arts system
based on the local conditions
during your guard in Nanqin
and you can play the martial arts
more nimbly and easily.
I'd really like to
have a look at it someday.
You're welcome
to come and learn anytime.
You're also welcome
to visit the Si Family
in Nanqin anytime.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean that just now.
I think you did it on purpose.
Borong.
I've heard about
the Si Family for a long time.
Today, I see that
both of you are indeed extraordinary.
Hello, Mr. Situ.
I'm from the Kong Family in Yishui City.
I've heard about
your high martial arts skills.
Please give me
some guidance in the future.
No need to be so polite.
The Kong Family's armory is famous.
I heard about it long ago.
It's a great honor
to be fellow disciples this time.
Your name is Dongbo Xueying?
My name is Puyang Bo.
Thanks for your help just now.
Don't you have luggage?
I didn't bring much.
I've been used to living a carefree life
since I was little,
eating at other people's homes.
Moreover, everything
is provided here,
so I don't need anything.
I'm not that particular.
You're not particular.
But can't you
consider others?
How long has it been
since you washed your clothes?
They stink.
Do they stink?
I think they're quite good. Smell good.
Why don't you smell me?
Okay?
Don't come over.
So stinky.
Yu Jingqiu,
when did you
get to know Dongbo Xueying?
Not long ago.
How long ago is "not long ago"?
A month ago?
A year ago?
I can't remember.
Miss Youyue,
we still have to practice tomorrow.
Get some rest early.
What makes you so proud?
Pretending to be aloof.
Cold as ice, just like your spells.
Come with me.
Who is that?
Help!
Let go of Youyue.
Who are you?
I just came to
see my new roommates.
Changfeng Academy is so boring.
You'll miss me soon.
She does this every year.
She hasn't gotten tired of it
after all these years.
I was scared to death.
Who is she?
She is Senior Lanxin.
She keeps failing the assessments,
so she has been practicing
in Changfeng Academy.
This year should be
her seventh year.
Seven years.
Such a long time.
She has wasted her prime
in Changfeng Academy,
practicing martial arts?
Yeah.
That's why she knows Changfeng Academy
like the back of her hand
and has mixed feelings about it.
She likes to bully
newcomers the most.
You girls,
do remember not to provoke her.
I won't provoke her.
Let's go.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
(He seems to be
a martial arts fanatic too.)
(The stronger the people around me,)
(the more I know about)
(my own shortcomings.)
(The strong is stronger.)
(Only by becoming stronger myself)
(can I have a better chance of
defeating Moyang Chen.)
(Flower Pavilion)
(Yu Jingqiu)
(isn't so bad after all.)
(Although not as pretty as me,)
(her martial arts skills are strong,)
(so she can protect me.)
(Wait, no.)
(She and Dongbo Xueying.)
(Even though she just helped me,)
(their relationship)
(is a bit ambiguous.)
(Bad luck.)
Greetings, Masters.
Starting today,
Ms. Tanshi and I will
teach you the basic courses.
What are basic courses?
Basic courses are designed to
provide some basic concepts
and basic knowledge
for your future learning.
When can we take
more advanced spell courses?
When you truly master
the basic courses,
you will be able to improve
your advanced spell skills
and the use of Dou Qi
according to
your cultivation categories.
Different colored crystals
merging together
will have different effects.
For example,
when pink and white crystals merge,
they can heal wounds
and help with recovery.
That's amazing.
Then,
what will happen
when red and green crystals
are combined?
You can try it.
Pink and white crystals
are the two most basic crystals.
To control and merge
crystals with higher energy,
it's not an easy task.
You shall
start with the basics.
What's so difficult about it?
I'll show you.
This may seem simple,
but it's the best way to train
your natural control power.
Whether you are a knight or a mage,
you need to
establish a solid foundation.
Only with a solid foundation
can you flourish
and bear abundant fruit.
Yu Jingqiu,
show everyone an example.
So beautiful.
That's amazing.
Awesome.
Fantastic.
It's quite impressive.
Can this
create something edible?
Is that true?
It's a real fish?
Is it edible?
I see.
Amazing. Yeah.
(What kind of fish is this?)
(The fish grilled by
Dongbo Xueying, Snow Eagle Lord,)
(must be snowfish for sure.)
Alright.
Everyone, take Yu Jingqiu as an example
and practice more.
Yes.
(Soul Spear is basic.)
(Martial arts is the foundation.)
(However things change,
they will still retain their essence.)
(Master is right.)
Xueying is amazing.
Master.
Well done.
This lesson is about
mastering the Dou Qi accurately
in a stable, sharp, and severe way.
Although you have mastered
the essence of basic law,
do not get distracted
when practicing.
Yes, Master.
Jingqiu.
Uncle Master.
At the Water Daoist Temple,
I am your senior.
But after you entered Changfeng Academy,
you are the same as everyone else,
so you could just call me Master.
Yes, Master.
Get out of the way. Make ways.
Watch out.
Be careful, be careful.
Careful.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Master,
I-I couldn't control it.
Your speed is fast.
You need to learn how to control it.
You all continue practicing.
Yes.
The sword moves forward,
while power lies in the heart.
Yes.
Brother,
why did they assign us
to Master Cold Blood?
Whenever I see her face,
I don't want to practice.
There's nothing special
about what Changfeng Academy teaches.
Well,
is it because Dean
has some unique techniques,
like his move,
True Meaning of Void Cleavage,
and he wants to keep it for himself,
not teach it to us?
Can you stop talking nonsense?
Practice seriously.
With your current level,
even if they taught you
more advanced spells,
you wouldn't be able to learn them?
How come I wouldn't be able to?
Although I'm not as good as you,
I'm much better than
Puyang Bo, Kong Hao, and Mo Zhu,
aren't I?
Studying with those trashes
makes me embarrassed.
Well,
as we've already known
these things,
why are you still
practicing so seriously?
You.
You what?
Si Borong.
Ms. Tanshi.
What can I do for you, Ms. Tanshi?
Show me what you just learned.
Yes, as you command.
Ms. Tanshi,
what do you think?
Since you performed a good show,
I'll reward you
keep smiling for three hours.
Slacking off in class.
Not serious at all.
Since you love smiling so much,
today I'll let you smile enough.
Anyone who wants to be like him
may step forward now.
I'm so smart.
Secretly brought
these delicacies from home.
After my second processing,
they look, smell, and taste good.
Xueying will definitely
look at me with admiration.
Master Tanshi is so cruel.
Her heart harder than stone.
You should avoid her in the future.
Provoke her less.
Why should I avoid her?
Why should I be afraid of her?
Let me massage it for you.
- Massage, massage.
- Go away, go away.
Try my Soothing Seal
to see if it works.
How about it? Here you are.
How is it? Does it work?
What's the use of this thing?
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't worry, try one more.
What is this?
Take it away, take it away.
Don't people say not to hit his face
when beating someone?
What kind of mistake did you make
to have your face beaten like this?
Puyang Bo, you...
Let me tell it, let me tell it.
Borong
angered Master Tanshi.
Master Tanshi
punished him to smile for three hours,
so his mouth is crooked from smiling.
What a special punishment, huh?
Come, Borong.
Let me have a look.
What do you mean?
Imitating me?
Stop right there.
I'll hit you.
I can't stand it.
Forget it, forget it.
Don't run.
You can't catch up with me.
- You.
- Be careful.
Miss Youyue.
Sister, why are you here?
Miss Youyue,
what delicious food did you bring today?
Where's Xueying?
Xueying hasn't returned yet.
He might be at the Practice Field.
Then I'll leave now.
Miss Youyue,
don't be in such a hurry to leave.
So, your things
are meant for Dongbo Xueying
himself.
Usually, the one
who gets in the way is either a ruffian
or Yama.
May I ask who you are?
I...
I just want to
talk more with you.
Listen,
it's better not to
get close to my sister.
I can't get close to anyone
in Changfeng Academy?
As I can't get close to teachers,
can't I get close to my classmates?
Alright, alright.
Come, come and have a seat.
(This Kong Youyue is interesting.)
(She is bold.)
(But I like it.)
Xueying.
I'll accompany you for a few moves.
Okay.
The spear is not only in your hands
but also in your heart.
Actually,
you should try
not to think about the formulations.
Focus
on how your body
feels right now instead.
After you forget the formulations,
indeed, you can
control yourself at will.
Don't be restrained by the formulations.
Follow your heart when using the spear.
Only then can you achieve unity
between the spear and yourself
and unleash
the greatest power of the spear.
Thank you, Mr. Situ, for your guidance.
I wouldn't call it guidance.
I've been practicing martial arts
since I was young.
So for some things,
I just understood earlier than you.
Yes.
I'm already very grateful
that you shared
this valuable experience with me.
I just don't want
someone to miss dinner
because of martial arts practice.
Puyang Bo asked me to give this to you.
Why didn't he come?
He said
that after having a full meal,
one should go to sleep quickly.
That's his style for sure.
You eat quite fast.
Finish it and continue training sooner.
Come on.
Practice with me.
It's a deal.
♪Like an orchid
in isolation from the world♪
♪In the past, young men spoke joyfully♪
♪The past vanishes.
Still, the crane lingers in my mind♪
♪A game of chess,
a pot of wine, a lifelong journey♪
♪Boiling wine and tea,
at peace in leisure.♪
♪Asking myself, the grove deep,
clouds dense, can I find him♪
♪Boiling wine and tea in my dreams,
not seeing the distant hometown♪
♪The old city and years gone by
fill me with melancholy♪
♪I want to light
the candlelight with moonlight♪
♪Not masking the sharp-edged resolve,
sighing that the world is not in vain♪
♪The worldly love
is fickle and changeable♪
♪Walking leisurely,
hoping old friends are well♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
Wishing to enjoy it with you♪
♪I want to hide the starlight in time♪
♪Forgetting each other silently
at the ends of the earth♪
♪Worldly people love
indulging in joy and revelry♪
♪Gradually moving further away,
adding poetry to the wine cup♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
I wish to enjoy it with you♪
♪Together on this journey♪