♪Traversing the vast expanse of time♪
♪Smiling proudly
in the mortal world alone♪
♪Cold moonlight♪
♪Earth as paper, sky as brush♪
♪This life like ink splashed on paper♪
♪Indulging in ups and downs♪
♪Coldly confronting
the approaching edges, sword and blade♪
♪My heart is narrow,
only holding heaven and earth♪
♪Boundless sea,
countless surging waves in the dark♪
♪Aeons just like a fleeting moment,
using youth as color♪
♪A silver-white hue climbs up
the temples, undaunted by setbacks♪
♪In the eyes, an unquenchable light♪
♪A body of proud bones,
unbending in the face of wind and frost♪
♪Smiling at the thorny webs♪
♪Being a lone wolf,
born to be solitary and independent♪
♪My pride alters not a jot♪
♪Resounding loudly through the clouds♪
♪In the cold world,
a heart burning hot for you♪
=Snow Eagle Lord=
=Episode 23=
This is the charm
of the demonic technique.
It can make you
instantly powerful.
As long as you follow
my orders from now on,
this is yours.
I guarantee
the next Xueying
will be you.
Don't bother.
Why don't you think carefully
before answering?
I don't even have to think.
You want me to be like you,
living in this dark chamber
and serving as a lackey
for the Demon Clan?
In your wildest dream!
I'm done
playing nice.
Face the consequences
of your stubbornness.
(What new martial arts)
(is Moyang Chen testing again?)
(How could it make someone
scream so miserably?)
Thank you.
Did you make this?
The scent is very special.
It was made by Kong Youyue.
She made one for everyone,
saying it's a way
to recognize people by their scent.
She
made one for everyone?
Well, I'll leave first.
Kong Hao,
wake up.
Wake up,
Kong Hao.
Situ Hong.
Don't be afraid.
I'll save you.
How are you here too?
Were you
caught
by that bad guy too?
Never listen to him.
Don't give in to him.
Our master and the others
will be here soon.
Why did you stop?
You want to save him,
and you plan
to let him go back
and tell everyone you're on my side?
I don't mind.
I can just change my location.
But your future
will be completely ruined.
You two...
Situ Hong,
you've actually joined him.
Why did you betray Master?
Situ Hong,
only by killing him
can you have a future.
I've never begged
anyone in my life.
He's still so young.
If we kill him,
how heartbroken
would his sister be?
Please,
can you give me
more time?
I will definitely persuade him.
I won't let him tell anyone.
Please.
You're so despicable.
No need to say anything.
I will never join you
in your wicked ways.
Kong Hao,
don't say it.
You're not even worthy
of being Changfeng's disciple.
Kong Hao,
do you really think
I can't bear to kill you?
I've done so much.
Isn't it just because I hope
to become stronger
and not be looked down upon by others?
What's wrong with that?
After coming to Changfeng Academy,
the teachers always
favor Dongbo Xueying.
You all believe in Xueying.
But I make it under my own steam.
Don't I
deserve
even a shred of care?
These things don't matter
at this moment.
If you want to go home,
if you want to see your sister,
keep quiet.
You...
What makes you think
you can compare to Xueying?
He has already become Transcendent.
He is the pride of Changfeng Academy.
He is my idol.
As for you,
you are
a complete loser.
No matter how skilled you become,
you will never be able to defeat him.
Kong Hao,
Kong Hao.
Very good.
Just a few days passed, and your skill
has improved a bit.
I killed him.
Yes,
you killed him.
You're getting stronger,
and you're getting more heartless.
Only in this way
will the things you want
get closer to you.
Don't be afraid.
I'll take you home.
Leave this body be.
I still need
it.
You just leave it to me.
Now,
the most important thing for you
is to focus on cultivation.
Only by becoming the strongest person
can you get everything you want.
Don't say I'm not helping you.
As long as you obey my words,
one day,
you'll stand above all.
(Fortune and auspiciousness)
Hao,
Hao.
(Blessing Pavilion)
Moyang Chen,
you killed Hao.
I'll fight you to the death.
You should be grateful
that I don't want to kill you right now.
You better behave.
Moyang Chen,
you beast.
Don't use such harsh words.
Your son isn't dead yet.
His bones
and muscles are just broken.
If I don't save him
with a special technique
within four hours,
you will see
your son die
of internal organ rupture.
No,
no.
I'll do whatever you want.
But
I...
I am just
an ordinary businessman.
Cooperate well,
and I will save your son,
and your family's weapon workshop
will still be the largest
and most prosperous
in the Dragon Mountain Empire.
Don't play tricks with me.
If you don't cooperate well,
then your son is going to die,
and it's your fault for not saving him.
Of course,
I can also go find your daughter.
No.
I hear
she's a talented businesswoman too.
No, no.
I...
I'm begging you.
I'll do whatever you want.
My daughter knows nothing.
She knows nothing.
I'm begging you.
Please spare my family.
Please.
Qingshi ordered
he wanted to eat roasted meat today.
You guys go to the ice cellar
to get more meat.
Yes.
You come with me to the ice cellar too
to see if there's anything else.
Let's go get some more ingredients
and bring them over here.
Yes.
You said you wanted to eat
roasted meat a few days ago,
so I specially asked the cooks
to make it for you.
Eat it.
Thank you, Rong.
What's wrong, brother?
We're waiting for you to start eating.
Everyone should at least
eat something.
I have no mood or appetite.
We've organized for so long.
But Ao Lan and the bronze coffin
seem to have vanished into thin air.
We've searched
the entire Xueying Territory
but found nothing.
Didn't Si An bring a message saying
although the exact location
of the bronze coffin hadn't been found,
it could be confirmed
that it was still
in the Xueying Territory?
It goes without saying.
Yeah, it's in the Xueying Territory,
and it is even
in the Dragon Mountain Empire.
(Ao Lan.)
(Where on earth is he hiding?)
The bronze coffin
is extremely important
to the Demon Clan.
According to common sense,
they should be
more anxious than us.
But the current situation...
Or
has Ao Lan already taken
the bronze coffin back
to the Demon God Association
unnoticed?
Impossible.
We have already activated
the Black White Moon.
It is the strongest artifact
in the Deity Mountain.
No matter how powerful Ao Lan is,
as long as he hasn't left
the Xueying Territory,
he can't possibly
slip out without triggering
the Black White Moon.
Then we'll continue to stay
in Master He's Black White Moon
to see who can outlast the other.
We won't go out,
and Ao Lan
won't be able to escape.
Everyone, eat the meal.
You need to be full to have the strength
for a protracted battle.
Master Tai Shu,
we will definitely avenge you.
Yes.
We must
find the bronze coffin
and the remains of the Demon God
and annihilate the Demon Clan.
Let's toast
Master Tai Shu.
(I'm sorry,)
(Master Tai Shu.)
(It was my fault.)
(If I hadn't helped the Demon Clan)
(break through the Demon Well)
(and start the war,)
(none of this would have happened.)
You guys eat.
I'll bring some food to Master He.
I'll go with you.
No need.
I can go by myself.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Master He,
how can you not eat?
The bronze coffin hasn't been found yet.
How can I eat?
That's all the more reason to eat.
Your practice consumes energy.
How can you manage without eating?
I got some food and wine
from Tong San.
Let's eat together.
Come on.
Today,
I'll accompany you for a drink.
Let's eat.
He's one of you too?
It doesn't matter who he is.
As long as we
can give each other
what we want,
isn't that enough?
(The Elders are all
in the Xueying Territory.)
(Even if we break through)
(the Black White Moon Barrier,)
(they'll chase us)
(and we still won't be able
to take the bronze coffin.)
(I need a foolproof plan)
(to transport the bronze coffin.)
(I'll first break the barrier)
(and have some people
distract the Elders)
(and then let Kong Hai, as usual,)
(transport the weapon,)
(taking the bronze coffin by land.)
(No one would suspect him.)
(What do they want me to do?)
(I killed my aunt, Borong)
(and Kong Hao.)
(I'm helping them open)
(the Black White Moon Barrier.)
(What have I become?)
(No.)
(It's not my fault.)
(They forced me.)
(I have no way out.)
(As long as I become the strongest one,)
(no one will care about my past.)
(No one will care about everything
that happened before.)
We arrived.
Is everything in place?
In a little while,
they might
discover that the barrier is broken.
As long as we can
take Master He out of commission,
there's a chance.
Black White Moon Barrier's ability
to obstruct people depends on how high
their martial arts cultivation level is.
Let's hurry.
We just need to carry
the coffin out.
Let's start right now.
Are you ready?
Black for opening.
White for closing.
Black for settling.
White for chasing.
(What's going on?)
(No.)
(It's hard)
(for others to notice)
(but so real.)
(Oh, no.)
(There must be a situation)
(with the Black White Moon Barrier
in the Xueying Territory.)
Oh, no.
There's a problem with the barrier.
Xi Yun,
He Yuan,
wake up.
What happened?
Come and help.
You guard here.
If someone breaks in,
kill without mercy.
Yes.
The so-called number one barrier
built by Master He
is nothing more than this.
Your skills have improved greatly.
It won't be long
before you surpass Xueying.
Keep your guard here.
When will I be able to leave
the Xueying Territory?
My father keeps sending letters
asking me to forgive him.
It was his birthday the other day,
but I couldn't go back.
He wouldn't spend money on himself
to buy something good.
The barrier is broken!
Hurry!
(Xueying Territory)
The barrier is broken!
Go and lead them away.
There's movement.
Go and check it out.
Stop!
Why is my father here?
Why is he with Uncle Tong San?
What are they up to?
Don't play tricks.
Your every move
can't escape me.
You're not Tong San.
Okay.
I...
I don't need to know
who you are.
Just tell me what to do
and I'll do it.
Father.
Yue.
Uncle Tong San,
you...
Yue,
why are you here?
You go back.
Hurry back.
I won't go back.
What are you up to?
Moyang Chen?
He's a wanted man
from the Demon Clan.
Father,
why are you hanging out
with him again?
Little girl,
you brought this upon yourself.
No, no.
No.
I'll send her back right away.
I'll send her back.
She knows nothing.
Yue, listen to me.
Go back now, okay?
Father,
I won't leave.
Don't be afraid of him.
Is he
blackmailing you
with something?
No.
Yue,
you...
You go back.
Please. I'm begging you.
Father,
are you seriously
in league
with them?
S-S-She doesn't know.
She knows nothing.
So it's you.
Father.
Killing you
is as easy as killing your son.
It's as easy
as crushing an ant.
Hao...
Hao was killed by them.
Hao.
Yue.
I...
I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect
you and Hao.
Father.
You go die with them.
Puyang Bo, let me go.
Youyue.
You can't go back.
Let me go back.
Youyue, Youyue,
you can't go back.
We can't go back.
We have no chance of winning
against Ao Lan and Moyang Chen.
I will kill them.
Youyue.
I will avenge my father.
Your father is already dead.
Youyue.
Alright.
Alright, Youyue.
It's okay now.
It's okay.
Puyang.
Youyue.
What's wrong with Miss Kong?
It's nothing.
The barrier
has been broken.
What?
Then
what about the bronze coffin?
The bronze coffin
has been taken away by them.
What on earth is going on?
Master He and Xi Yun
were drugged and fainted.
Xueying and Sikong Yang
are trying to cure them.
The Demon Clan
took advantage of it
and took away the coffin.
Don't try to take
the bronze coffin away.
(The demonic poison is acting up again.)
Forget them.
The coffin is more important.
Let's go.
Yes.
Rong.
Master, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you for saving me.
Rong,
go stop Ao Lan
and get back the bronze coffin.
Compared to those,
your life is the most important.
Master,
your hand...
Rong,
don't do this.
You will ruin yourself.
Master,
I am your disciple.
You're in trouble now.
How can I not save you?
Even if this demonic poison
enters my body,
I will still save you.
If it hadn't been for you,
I would have died long ago.
Rong,
remember this.
Some things
are not up to you to decide,
but don't lose yourself because of it.
Otherwise,
you will go further astray.
Master He.
The Black White Moon Barrier...
It has been broken.
The Demon Clan has already taken
the bronze coffin away.
What?
Xi Yun.
There was something wrong with the food.
It made us
completely pass out
without noticing it.
It was Tong San.
I asked him for food
for Master He,
never imagining
he would drug it.
That can't be true.
It was Ao Lan.
He disguised himself as Uncle Tong San.
Earlier
I saw Uncle Tong San
and Moyang Chen together,
and I couldn't believe it.
At that time, I thought
Uncle Tong San...
But
Ao Lan
suddenly revealed his true face.
He used my father.
It was he who took away
the bronze coffin,
and he killed my father!
Elders,
we must avenge
Youyue's father.
We will.
I can't believe
I didn't even recognize him
and let him
make a fool of me
right under my nose.
Where is Uncle Tong now?
Miss Ji Rong.
Ji Rong.
Tong San.
What's wrong with you, Tong San?
There.
Somebody!
Somebody, help!
Help!
Uncle Tong San.
Uncle Tong San, don't scare me.
Uncle Tong San,
don't scare me.
How could this happen?
Uncle Tong San,
please don't scare me.
There's no way.
We've tried every method
we could use.
Uncle Tong San.
Ready,
go.
Lord,
be careful.
Keep your back straight.
Put some strength into your hands.
Good.
Uncle Tong San.
Please.
(Tai Shu,)
(Tong San,)
(no matter what,)
(I'll fight to the death
to protect Xueying)
(and let him avenge you.)
(He will definitely inherit
the will of the Dragon Mountain.)
(He won't fail you.)
(How did everything go so horrible?)
Maybe Tong San
discovered the Demon Clan's breaking
of the Black White Moon Barrier,
so Ao Lan harmed him like this.
Ao Lan might have already taken action
against Tong San earlier.
We don't even know
when it happened.
He Yuan,
didn't you say
your Black White Moon
has strong power
and would never give the Demon Clan
an opportunity to take advantage?
You are implying
that my magic tool's not powerful enough
or that I let the Demon Clan in?
If it hadn't been
for the tainted meal,
would the barrier have been
broken today?
He Yuan,
I'm saying this for your own good.
The meal...
Stop it!
After so much hardship,
the bronze coffin
finally came from the abyss
to the human world.
Congratulations, Master.
Now the bronze coffin and Moyang Yu
have been brought back
to the Demon God Association.
The conditions for your reawakening
are all met.
This success
in bringing back the bronze coffin
was inseparable
from the cooperation between you two.
Next,
you two must continue to cooperate well.
With you two as my key aides,
the advent of the Demon God
is just around the corner.
Yes.
The next step
is to open the bronze coffin.
We must kill the six old geezers
who did the sealing back then.
Not one of them can escape.
Second Priest,
you can start the action now.
Don't worry, Master.
I will do my best.
High Priest,
I also need you
to continue to help in secret.
Yes.
Go ahead without worry.
I will provide strong support
behind the scenes.
(Let me see)
(how you will kill)
(your own clansmen.)
How did the Demon Clan break
Master He's magic tool?
The scope
of the Black White Moon Barrier
expands
with the increase in cultivation level.
As your strength improves in the future,
the scope
will become larger and larger.
I won't
let you down.
Moyang Chen.
It must be him.
How could you tell him
the incantation of Black White Moon?
I misjudged him.
I should not have let
him stay back then.
Renowned Master He,
in the past, you drove me out
of the Black White Deity Mountain.
Now I've broken
your Black White Moon,
and you can't stop me anymore.
Moyang Chen,
I will kill you with my own hands
to purge my sect
of your treachery.
In the great battle at the Demon Well,
Tai Shu sacrificed himself.
Now the barrier has been broken,
and the bronze coffin has been stolen.
Dangerous times
lie ahead of us now,
and we will soon be
in a more precarious position.
The coffin has already been
transported away.
The Demon Clan
will try every means to unseal it.
Unsealing it to let
the Great Demon God's body come out.
So all along they have been plotting
with constant resolve
for the Great Demon God's reemergence.
This is the aftermath
of that great battle years ago.
It's not so easy
to unseal the bronze coffin.
Back then,
the six of us
staked our very lives
to seal it.
Unless all six of us die.
Otherwise,
they have no way to deal with it.
The Demon Clan has come this far
with absolute confidence
in their inevitable success.
We
must unite and cooperate more than ever.
But now,
Ye Mei is not here.
Now the top priority
is to have Ye Mei
return to the council.
Back then,
you joined hands to seal it,
and this time only by working together
can you prevent
the bronze coffin from being unsealed.
The Demon Clan
must have taken the bronze coffin
back to the Demon God Association.
Make the Dragon Mountain Mansion
spare no effort and pay any price
to find out the exact location
of the Demon God Association.
Although the Demon God Association
has always been hidden in the dark,
however hard it is,
it must be better than just sitting here
and waiting for death.
Uncle Tong San, you're amazing.
You can do everything.
Ying, I'll give it to you.
I want one too.
If you catch up with me,
I'll give it to you.
I want one too.
Slow down.
Xueying.
As long as the Demon Clan
is not eliminated,
our homeland will never be at peace.
I know you're not feeling well,
but the Demon God Association's location
is hard to find.
We need to find a solution.
We can't think blindly.
The person
who took my mother
from the Leichao Sea Cliff
was the one
who freed Ao Lan.
You sure?
They had identical masks and figures.
It's him.
But didn't you say before
the masked man's box belonged
to the Xinhuo Palace?
Yes.
So I must go there
to find it out.
Youyue.
Moyang Chen and Ao Lan
killed my father.
And Hao...
Hao was killed by them too.
What should I do in the future?
Youyue,
count on us to take vengeance
for your father and brother.
From now on,
you can see us as your family.
It's not just your business
but our shared responsibility.
I'll go to Master later
and discuss the plan
with him.
Uncle Zong.
Shi.
Uncle Zong,
have you seen Ji Rong?
No.
She hasn't appeared
since the barrier incident.
How could this be?
A few days ago,
I saw Uncle Tong San
in her room.
No,
it's not her.
What?
You saw her
with Ao Lan disguised as Tong San?
No, no, Uncle Zong.
It was the real Uncle Tong San.
Back then,
we even talked.
Shi,
you have to make absolutely sure.
Ji Rong has been so good to me.
I believe her.
She would never
collude with the Demon Clan,
let alone harm Uncle Tong San.
I'm going to find her now.
Where are you going to find her?
I'll go to Master's residence
to find her.
Even if I can't find her,
I believe Master can find her.
Master.
Ji Rong,
you come to me.
I'm asking you.
Do you collude with the Demon Clan?
Did you kill Uncle Tong San?
Qingshi,
what nonsense are you talking about?
How can I collude with the Demon Clan?
Uncle Tong San is dead?
That day,
I saw the soldiers
of the Xueying Territory
going that way.
There seemed to be some movement,
so I hurriedly followed.
I saw Ao Lan and Moyang Chen
together.
They seemed to be carrying something.
I knew it must be
something important,
so I rushed to stop them.
But their demonic power was too strong,
and I just couldn't stop them.
Are you telling the truth?
You really aren't
in cahoots with the Demon Clan?
How could I be
Qingshi,
if you keep saying such things,
I'll get angry.
And I was even injured
by the Demon Clan.
Are you alright, Rong?
I...
Then...
Why didn't you go to someone for help?
Why didn't you go back
to the Xueying Territory
but come here instead?
Qingshi,
let me explain for her.
That day,
I felt there was something wrong
with the barrier,
so I rushed to the Xueying Territory.
On the way,
I saved Rong
and brought her back here.
She was alone
against the Demon Clan then.
It was a very dangerous situation.
If Master hadn't saved me,
I might have died
at the hands of the Demon Clan.
Qingshi,
I thought I'd never see you again.
I escaped death,
and you're even doubting me now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Rong.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
Fortunately, Master was there.
I know Uncle Tong San's death
is hard for you to accept.
I understand.
I won't blame you.
Because I've gotten used
to not being believed
and being wronged.
Rong,
I promise you
I will never
wrong you again.
From now on, whatever you say,
I will definitely believe you.
(Changfeng Academy)
Master.
Xueying.
♪Like an orchid
in isolation from the world♪
♪In the past, young men spoke joyfully♪
♪The past vanishes.
Still, the crane lingers in my mind♪
♪A game of chess,
a pot of wine, a lifelong journey♪
♪Boiling wine and tea,
at peace in leisure.♪
♪Asking myself, the grove deep,
clouds dense, can I find him♪
♪Boiling wine and tea in my dreams,
not seeing the distant hometown♪
♪The old city and years gone by
fill me with melancholy♪
♪I want to light
the candlelight with moonlight♪
♪Not masking the sharp-edged resolve,
sighing that the world is not in vain♪
♪The worldly love
is fickle and changeable♪
♪Walking leisurely,
hoping old friends are well♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
Wishing to enjoy it with you♪
♪I want to hide the starlight in time♪
♪Forgetting each other silently
at the ends of the earth♪
♪Worldly people love
indulging in joy and revelry♪
♪Gradually moving further away,
adding poetry to the wine cup♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
I wish to enjoy it with you♪
♪Together on this journey♪