♪Traversing the vast expanse of time♪
♪Smiling proudly
in the mortal world alone♪
♪Cold moonlight♪
♪Earth as paper, sky as brush♪
♪This life like ink splashed on paper♪
♪Indulging in ups and downs♪
♪Coldly confronting
the approaching edges, sword and blade♪
♪My heart is narrow,
only holding heaven and earth♪
♪Boundless sea,
countless surging waves in the dark♪
♪Aeons just like a fleeting moment,
using youth as color♪
♪A silver-white hue climbs up
the temples, undaunted by setbacks♪
♪In the eyes, an unquenchable light♪
♪A body of proud bones,
unbending in the face of wind and frost♪
♪Smiling at the thorny webs♪
♪Being a lone wolf,
born to be solitary and independent♪
♪My pride alters not a jot♪
♪Resounding loudly through the clouds♪
♪In the cold world,
a heart burning hot for you♪
=Snow Eagle Lord=
=Episode 1=
(I was born in the Snow Stone Fort.)
(Ever since I can remember,)
(my mother has told me many stories)
(about my ancestors.)
(My father said it is
because of the guardianship)
(of the ancestors
as depicted in those stories)
(that people of today's
Dragon Mountain Empire)
(are able to enjoy happiness and peace.)
(Next, I'll tell the story)
(of my father.)
(Young Dongbo Xueying)
Run! Go!
Run!
Go!
- Ying!
(Tong San)
(Zong Ling)
Uncle Zong, Uncle Tong San,
I'm here.
You scared us to death.
- Come down now.
- Come down.
How are you? Are you alright?
Uncle Tong San, Uncle Zong,
you almost
hurt that deer just now.
Deer?
It's all your fault, Tong San.
How was I supposed to know?
Ying,
now that the deer is saved by you,
we don't have deer meat to eat today.
Well, it's the Lucky Reunion Festival.
Let's go home and have dinner together.
Let's go.
Great, I'll have sweet buns to eat.
- Let's go have dinner.
- This kid.
(Dongbo Lie)
(Moyang Yu)
My lady,
you've been busy all afternoon.
You must be tired.
It is the Lucky Reunion Festival today.
Xueying and Qingshi
have been clamoring
to eat sweet buns.
With your help,
how could I feel tired?
When you came over just now,
I smelled the aroma.
Can I have one first?
Okay.
Give me.
Look.
You're skillful, my lady.
You made the figure
of yourself a bit chubby.
The one of Xueying looks so real.
Father, Mother.
Xueying, you're here.
Come to me.
If you had come any later,
I would have eaten the bun doll of you.
Mother, you can't play favorites
and give all the good food to my father.
You're unhappy about this?
Alright, you are our little treasure,
and I'll save all the good food
for you in the future.
Is that okay?
You're happy now.
Tong San, Zong Ling,
looks like you've returned empty-handed.
Actually, Tong San
could have brought back a wild deer.
But the little one
didn't want it dead and he let it go.
It seems
the future Lord of Xueying Territory
is benevolent.
Father, instead of being a lord,
I want my mother's
storage treasure more.
Okay.
When you cultivate Dou Qi,
I will give it to you.
Is that okay?
Okay.
No way.
Come to me.
Go to your father.
When you can pull
the Star Breaking Crossbow,
your mother
will reward you with her treasure.
Father, the Star Breaking Crossbow
(Xueying Territory)
is the most cherished treasure of our territory.
You can only pull the crossbow
with a tremendous force.
So it can shoot an arrow
with unmatched speed
and power.
Whether it's an iron wall
or a small snowflake,
it can be pierced through.
Father, Mother,
you just wait and see.
I will manage to pull
the Star Breaking Crossbow
and protect the Xueying Territory
in the future.
Little Stone, hurry up.
It's time for dinner.
Got it, brother.
It is the Lucky Reunion Festival today.
And it's been ten years
since we came to the Xueying Territory.
Let's raise our cups together,
wishing the territory peace and success.
Happiness.
Fortune in abundance.
And always together.
Cheers.
Come on.
The milk is so delicious.
Is it?
Then drink more.
Xueying,
here is your favorite sweet bun.
Thank you.
I think
I heard a wolf cub calling.
Father, it's this one.
I found it
in the snow today.
It looks so cute,
so I brought it back.
Can I keep it as a pet?
No way.
Father, I'm tired.
Father,
why do we have to send the wolf cub
back?
I haven't played enough with it.
If you were separated
from your own parents,
would you feel sad?
But it's not a person.
It's just an animal.
No matter if it's a human or an animal,
they are both living beings.
And they both long
for the warmth of a family.
It is the Lucky Reunion Festival today.
You are with your parents,
but you made the wolf cub
leave its parents.
Do you think what you're doing is right?
But if it lives with us
after I brought it back,
doesn't it mean it has a new home?
In the old days,
the Dragon Mountain Emperor
created the Dragon Mountain.
We, the Xia Clan,
do not thrive
through the slaughter
and pillaging of other races.
Great love comes from protection.
Only by protecting the weak
can one fulfill oneself
and gain more supporters.
You'll understand these
in the future.
Let's go.
The Silver Moon Wolf King!
It must be the wolf cub's family,
and it's coming for revenge.
Xueying, don't be afraid.
Give the wolf cub back.
That really scared me just now.
If the Silver Moon Wolf King
had really rushed up,
we'd have become
its Lucky Reunion Festival dinner.
Don't be afraid. I'm with you.
(Xueying Territory)
Little Stone,
you came up here too?
Brother, what are you looking at?
This book is called
"The Ten Transcendent Knights",
and it's about how those people
became Transcendent Knights
through practice.
Is it interesting?
Of course, it's interesting.
Through countless hours
of practice,
those ordinary lives
finally transformed
into Transcendent Heroes.
What does "Transcendent" mean?
It is an extremely high level
of cultivation.
First of all, you need to have Dou Qi
and practice to become a Mortal Knight.
But the Dou Qi of a Mortal Knight
cannot be condensed.
When the knight
reaches the Meteor Level,
his Dou Qi can transform
into a specific form.
First, Mortal Knights go
through the Human, Earth,
and Heaven Levels.
Later, they continue
to reach the Meteor,
Silver Moon, and Legend Levels
as the Star Knights.
The power of their Dou Qi
becomes stronger and stronger.
Once they step
into the Transcendent Realm,
that's a leap
in the entire level of life.
Aren't Transcendent Knights humans?
The knights with Transcendent Dou Qi
can harness the power
of heaven and earth
and integrate with the mysteries
of the universe.
(Transcendent)
People wielding ordinary weapons
can't hurt them at all.
(Transcendent)
So powerful.
But very few people in our entire empire
can enter the Transcendent Realm.
What about our father?
Our father is still at the Meteor Level.
With more practice,
he'll become a Silver Moon Knight.
Brother,
will you become
a Transcendent Knight in the future?
Of course.
After we
become Transcendent Heroes
with super powers,
we'll protect our parents
and our territory.
Light's out.
Brother,
I haven't heard enough of the stories.
That's just what happens
when your mother is a mage.
When it's time,
the lights will go out automatically.
Let's go back to the room to sleep.
I'll tell you more when I have time.
Lie.
Yu, don't be afraid.
I'm here.
I'll go check on the children.
(Thundering Gust)
Who's there?
(Ferocious Spearstrike)
Xueying.
Mother, what's up?
I have something for you.
Mother,
isn't this your storage treasure?
Why?
From today on,
it belongs to you.
Give me your hand.
Mother,
why are you
suddenly giving it to me?
Because then
you can keep
all your treasures
inside it.
You must keep it well.
When you meet someone in the future,
it may unleash
incredible power.
Mother, what's that sound?
Mother.
- Mother.
- Don't be afraid.
There, there, Qingshi.
Come to me.
- Mother.
- It's alright.
Good boys.
I'm here. Don't be afraid.
Wait here for me.
I'll be right back.
Mother! I want Mother!
Qingshi.
Mother.
Where is Moyang Yu?
(Moyang Chen)
Moyang Chen.
(Tong San,)
(take away Xueying
and Qingshi right now.)
(I entrust them to you.)
Well...
After all these years,
I've finally found you.
Moyang Chen,
what do you want to do?
Back then, you broke
the arranged marriage
and eloped with someone,
bringing huge shame on our family.
Bringing you back
is my responsibility as your brother.
I don't think
it's the family's request.
It's you who have ulterior motives.
You have to come with me today.
Don't blindly pursue
martial arts prowess
and lose your mind.
I really hate this kind
of didactic tone.
Are you going
to use your Ancient Bloodline
to deal with me?
I heard that great battle
almost exhausted
the strength
of your Ancient Bloodline.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have hidden here.
Let's see
who can help you today.
As long as I have a breath left,
no one can take her away.
Lie,
no need to talk to him.
Ying, where are you going?
- Let go of me.
- Where are you going?
It's dangerous outside. Stop it.
Little Stone
is still crying in the room.
Ying.
Mother.
Xueying.
(Thundering Strike)
Mother.
Xueying.
Did I kill that bad guy?
Xueying,
are you alright?
Let me take a look.
My silly child.
Mother, did I kill that bad guy?
You almost scared me to death.
This child
is your son, right?
The little guy
has the Ancient Bloodline too, right?
Father.
Xueying,
take good care of your mother.
Lie.
Lie, let go, Lie.
Lie, let go!
Father.
Lord.
Come with me.
No one can take my mother away.
If you don't,
the people
of the entire Xueying Territory
will be buried with you.
Let's start with your son.
(Moyang Chen is already
at the Silver Moon Level.)
(Destroying the territory would be
but a piece of cake for him.)
Don't hurt him.
I'll go with you.
Xueying, promise me
you'll take care of yourself
and your younger brother
when your father and I are not around.
Did you hear me? Tell me.
Yes, I did.
Mother, Mother.
Mother!
(Xueying Territory)
(Moyang Chen killed my father)
(and took my mother away.)
(Dragon Mountain Mansion)
(Please help me kill him.)
(Only those who possess
the Black Iron Order)
(can ask Dragon Mountain Mansion
to do something for them.)
(I'm afraid)
(you don't even have Dou Qi now, right?)
(You'd better go back.)
(Dragon Mountain Mansion)
(Ten years later)
(Dongbo Xueying)
(Blessings and Auspices)
(Dark Ice Spear Technique: Flying Snow)
Ying, eat first.
Stop practicing and take a break.
(Strong.)
(I need to become stronger.)
Good spear technique, Ying.
Nice.
It's been ten years,
but I haven't even cultivated Dou Qi.
Moyang Chen must be stronger than he was
ten years ago.
But I am not even
a Mortal Knight.
I'm really useless.
Ying,
you practice thousands of times a day.
You've managed to harness immense force
from the elementary technique,
Soul Spear.
It's no mean feat.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Given time,
you'll definitely surpass Moyang Chen.
Yeah, Ying.
I just hope
that day comes sooner.
Then I will rescue my mother.
Let's eat.
Alright, let's eat.
Smells good.
Eat more.
Ying.
Spit it out.
Ying,
eat slowly.
I haven't cultivated Dou Qi yet.
How do I increase
my strength without eating a lot?
How do I keep practicing
without enough strength?
Just don't stuff yourself too much.
It's okay.
I'll practice two thousand more times,
and it'll be fine.
Our lady has been missing
for so many years.
With only a few unconfirmed leads,
Ying wouldn't let any of them slip by.
Logically, the Dragon Mountain Mansion
is the only one
with any accurate information.
But they're unwilling to help.
We can only negotiate
with them on equal terms
once we have the Black Iron Order.
Snobbish.
That's the way this world is.
Whoever is powerful has the say
and can even
set the rules.
Uncle Tong San, Uncle Zong Ling,
come and practice with me.
Still practicing?
You go.
He's asking for you.
Go, go.
Look at him.
(Weapon Shop)
Lord Si An,
recently, the demons' attacks
have caused panic among the people.
What are your thoughts, Sir?
What about you?
Demons
are far from ordinary bandits
and are extremely ferocious.
Some say it's comparable
to a Transcendent Knight.
Transcendent?
They might be
underestimating a Transcendent Knight.
(The Water Daoist Temple)
(is the faction
with the most Transcendent Knights)
(Water Daoist Temple)
(in the entire Dragon Mountain Empire.)
(Master Sikong Yang)
(has formed Deity Heart.)
(Sikong Yang)
(He's considered a Demigod.)
(Not only does he have
superb martial arts,)
(he's also good at recognizing)
(and using talents.)
(The Black White Deity Mountain
is skilled in formation spells.)
(Master He was once recognized)
(Master He)
(as the number one martial artist in the world.)
(His Black White Moon alone)
(has made him famous all around.)
(The Temple of the Earth God)
(focuses on studying
divine mystic spells.)
(Master Xi Yun)
(is easygoing and never offends anyone.)
(Xi Yun)
(But he gives no quarter)
(when fighting others.)
(The sisters in the Fog City,)
(though gentle in nature,)
(have strong martial arts.)
(Bu Xiaoxi) (Bu Chunyuan)
(They wholeheartedly protect)
(the people of their city.)
(The Sea God Palace
is the farthest from here,)
(with the poorest resources
for cultivation.)
(No wonder the Master Tai Shu)
(has a bad temper.)
(However,)
(he's not reckless or aggressive.)
(Master Tai Shu)
(He merely wants to cultivate)
(Bloodshed Tavern)
(a few Transcendent Knights.)
(As for the Bloodshed Tavern,)
(Ye Mei has always been a loner.)
(She has long ceased getting involved)
(in the council's affairs.)
(Ye Mei)
(They are all powerful forces.)
Which organization do you think
is related to the demons?
Could it be the Demon God Association?
(Si An)
I have the same concern.
20 years ago,
during the great war
between the Xia Clan and the Demon Clan,
it took the power
of the entire Dragon Mountain Empire
to repel the Demon Clan.
However, the Great Demon God
was only sealed,
and the Demon Clan was not wiped out.
(You Tu)
Back then, the Six Great Elders sealed him together.
Even if the Demon God Association
has bad intentions,
what can
those low-level demons do?
We, the Dragon Mountain Mansion,
only care about intelligence.
As for the rest,
we'll wait and see.
Ying,
during this time,
you've broken so many spears.
Let's go to the town and buy a good one.
Hello?
Customers are here!
What would you two like to buy?
Good taste, Sir.
This is
a third-level alchemy weapon.
It can even handle
battles of Legend Levels.
Only 30,000 gold coins.
30,000 gold coins?
Sir,
we're serious about buying.
Could you give us a fair price?
Well...
20,000, and it can't go lower.
20,000 is still not low, Sir.
Sir, how much is this spear?
Well, it's just scrap metal,
and I was thinking of throwing it away.
If you want it, just give me
any amount of money you like.
Ying.
Actually, we don't lack money.
By saving a little each day,
Tong San and I
should be able to afford a spear.
Let's pick a better one.
No, I want this one.
It's a good one.
(I'll name you Flying Snow Spear.)
Only you would like
this lousy spear.
Ying,
look what junk you've got.
See, Tong San doesn't like it either.
Ying, how about tomorrow
I go with you to buy another one?
No, I want this one.
Well...
(Dongbo Qingshi)
I...
Brother.
Brother,
look at this.
Not bad, but keep working hard.
Brother,
you just bought this?
Well, brother.
Have you heard about the demon thing?
Yeah.
The demons' origin is unknown.
Don't go out at night.
Even a matter related to demons
can make you worry so much for me.
How can I save our mother then?
You don't need to worry
about that.
Focus on your training.
You have outstanding spiritual power.
You may be a promising mage.
Brother,
I will definitely train hard
and defeat Moyang Chen with you
in the future.
(Qingshi lost parents
when he was so young.)
(He has suffered enough.)
(Saving our mother is difficult.)
(I'll handle)
(the risks myself.)
Demons are attacking our territory!
(Hui An)
Stay here.
Ying, be careful.
Why do you stop me?
Let him have a try.
Shi, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Ying.
Ying,
it really is a good spear.
Brother, you're amazing.
I knew this would be a good spear.
Uncle Zong, Uncle Tong San,
you go back first and wait for me.
Wait for me.
You can't go.
Your skills are not strong enough.
These demons have
no independent thoughts.
They only know brute force.
He won't get hurt.
(This is the True Meaning of Space)
(that only Transcendent Knights
can use.)
(Chi Qiubai)
Are you okay?
May I ask your name, Sir?
I am Chi Qiubai.
Knight Changfeng.
You are Knight Changfeng.
You have no Dou Qi at all.
Why would you take the risk?
Demons are invading our territory.
I must investigate.
I have already passed on
some Dou Qi to you.
Perhaps it can stimulate
your own Dou Qi.
If you insist
on investigating the demons,
be careful.
(True Meaning of Space Split)
Knight Changfeng.
(Stimulating Dou Qi.)
Just now, in Yishui City,
I discovered traces of demons.
The demons' spirit and strength
are many times stronger
than an ordinary person's.
Knight Changfeng,
it's not a big deal.
Back then, we paid
such a high price
to seal Da Er Hao.
What do you mean now?
Do you think the demons are coming back?
I suggest
first to investigate
the Destruction Mountain Range.
The terrain there is complex,
and outsiders find it
hard to distinguish.
There are many desperate fugitives
and ferocious beasts hiding inside.
If we can find out the connection
between them and the demons,
maybe we can figure out
if it's related to the Demon Clan.
Now, the matter of the demons
is not only related
to the safety
of the people in Yishui City.
If it's related to the Demon Realm,
then the saying that the Demon Clan
is hiding among us
is not baseless.
Master Sikong,
you have many Transcendent disciples.
You might be in charge
of the investigation.
No way.
This is the matter
of the entire Dragon Mountain Empire.
It's a matter of the Xia Clan.
We all have a responsibility.
We, the Sea God Palace,
will definitely contribute.
Tai Shu, you are reckless by nature.
This time, we are in the light
while the demons hide in the shadows.
Our temple will get to the bottom
of it first
and make it clearer to you.
Or let Knight Changfeng investigate
and let the Dragon Mountain Mansion
issue a reward at the same time.
We'll do both.
Everyone must be reassured now.
Alright.
Yes.
(Blessings and Auspices)
Not bad.
You just went for a day,
and you have greatly improved
your skill with the spear.
Not bad.
I have to continue training
to save my mother as soon as possible.
Brother, I'm back.
(Notice)
The Dragon Mountain Mansion has issued a notice.
The demons
are hiding
in the Destruction Mountain Range.
Whoever can find out the truth
will be rewarded
with a Black Iron Order.
Really?
Absolutely.
That's great.
With the Black Iron Order,
I can find out where my mother is.
But the roads there are treacherous.
It's basically a one-way trip.
I'm not afraid.
Brother, I don't want you to go.
I have already lost my parents.
I can't afford to lose you.
I don't agree.
Is it worth taking such a risk
for a Black Iron Order?
Not just for the Black Iron Order.
If we don't figure out this matter,
and the demons come again,
we'll all be in danger.
Then I'll go with you.
Shi,
I'll accompany
your brother on this trip.
You and Tong guard the Xueying Territory
and wait for me to come back.
Zong Ling.
Alright, it's settled then.
Well...
High Priest,
it was because of Ge Bin's incompetence
that those demons escaped.
Useless.
Go back and tell Ge Bin.
If he can't handle this,
(High Priest of Demon Clan)
he and his entire Bent Blade Union
(Xiang Pangyun)
will disappear.
Yes.
It's time the empire changes hands.
Back in my prime,
I was making waves in the world,
but now I've fallen so much,
associating with the likes of you.
Get off.
Boss,
once we complete
this demon mission,
with the High Priest backing us up,
(Ge Bin)
you'll be able to do whatever you want
in the Dragon Mountain Empire.
You have quite the imagination.
They chose to create demons
in this place
because the Destruction Mountain Range
is a barren land.
If the demon mission fails,
our lives will be at stake.
Why don't we
take away
the Ocean Realm Stone
just in case something goes wrong?
We are just their tools
and ants they can crush at will.
If you touch that stone,
you may get yourself
turned into a demon.
So...
either way, it's death.
Get rid of everyone
who comes in,
and your head can stay
on your neck for a few more days.
Demons!
Uncle Zong, let's leave.
These demons seem
like ordinary people
with no attack power.
That flute player
must be the leader,
probably an insider.
Let's cut off the head of the snake.
Capture him and ask.
Ying, be careful.
Who gave you the guts
to come to my territory?
You are Ge Bin?
Ge Bin?
Well?
You must have heard
of my name, right?
The Bent Blade Union is notorious.
It seems this time the demons
are related to you guys.
Still stubborn when facing death.
Today I will send you...
To your death.
To your death!
B-B-Boss.
With just a little Dou Qi,
how dare you come here!
That's right.
(Cul-de-sac Attack)
This is the Meteor Level Dou Qi.
Die!
(Yu Jingqiu)
(She must be at least)
(at the Meteor Level.)
(Freezing Frost)
(It seems she is a mage)
(using spiritual power)
(like my mother.)
♪Like an orchid
in isolation from the world♪
♪In the past, young men spoke joyfully♪
♪The past vanishes.
Still, the crane lingers in my mind♪
♪A game of chess,
a pot of wine, a lifelong journey♪
♪Boiling wine and tea,
at peace in leisure.♪
♪Asking myself, the grove deep,
clouds dense, can I find him♪
♪Boiling wine and tea in my dreams,
not seeing the distant hometown♪
♪The old city and years gone by
fill me with melancholy♪
♪I want to light
the candlelight with moonlight♪
♪Not masking the sharp-edged resolve,
sighing that the world is not in vain♪
♪The worldly love
is fickle and changeable♪
♪Walking leisurely,
hoping old friends are well♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
Wishing to enjoy it with you♪
♪I want to hide the starlight in time♪
♪Forgetting each other silently
at the ends of the earth♪
♪Worldly people love
indulging in joy and revelry♪
♪Gradually moving further away,
adding poetry to the wine cup♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
I wish to enjoy it with you♪
♪Together on this journey♪