♪Traversing the vast expanse of time♪
♪Smiling proudly
in the mortal world alone♪
♪Cold moonlight♪
♪Earth as paper, sky as brush♪
♪This life like ink splashed on paper♪
♪Indulging in ups and downs♪
♪Coldly confronting
the approaching edges, sword and blade♪
♪My heart is narrow,
only holding heaven and earth♪
♪Boundless sea,
countless surging waves in the dark♪
♪Aeons just like a fleeting moment,
using youth as color♪
♪A silver-white hue climbs up
the temples, undaunted by setbacks♪
♪In the eyes, an unquenchable light♪
♪A body of proud bones,
unbending in the face of wind and frost♪
♪Smiling at the thorny webs♪
♪Being a lone wolf,
born to be solitary and independent♪
♪My pride alters not a jot♪
♪Resounding loudly through the clouds♪
♪In the cold world,
a heart burning hot for you♪
=Snow Eagle Lord=
=Episode 37=
The Demon Clan started to attack.
(Xueying,)
(you must be safe.)
Lan Sha, what are you doing?
Lan Sha!
Lan Sha.
Wu Cang, kill me now.
He was a disciple of Xinhuo Palace,
but why has he suddenly turned into
a demonized Black Armored Warrior?
As disciples of Xinhuo Palace
have extraordinary powers,
demonizing them
is not an easy task.
We still don't know
the reason for their demonization.
Yu Feng, be sober.
You are a disciple of Xinhuo Palace.
How can you become
a sacrifice for the Demon Clan?
How did he also become demonized?
Protect Lan Sha.
Yu Feng.
Yu Feng, Yu Feng.
Black Iron Order.
Oh no, my Bloodshed Tavern.
Look at that Black Iron Order.
It's the Black Iron Order
that has been demonized.
All those who hold
the Black Iron Orders
have been poisoned by demonic poison.
Xueying, what about yours?
Oh no, Qingshi.
(The Demon Clan
is surprisingly powerful.)
(Even the Black Iron Knights
of Xinhuo Palace)
(can be demonized.)
(Dragon Mountain)
(Ao Lan actually attacked
Dragon Mountain Mansion.)
(As I practiced demonic techniques,)
(I was not infected.)
(Luckily, I was not suspected by them.)
Let's go to
Dragon Mountain Mansion right away.
There must be
something wrong with Si An's.
Mother!
Don't be afraid.
There's something wrong
with the Black Iron Orders.
The Black Iron Orders have always been
under strict protection
by Dragon Mountain Mansion.
I don't know why
such a big mistake could happen.
It must have been Ji Rong
who tampered with the Black Iron Orders.
I'll go to Dragon Mountain Mansion.
You protect the civilians.
Lord Si An.
K-Kill me.
You Tu, kill me.
Lord,
I am poisoned by the demonic poison too.
With my current power,
I can't kill you.
What on earth is going on?
Why has everyone
turned into this?
The machine
that issues the Black Iron Orders
is poisoned by the demonic poison.
Everyone associated with
the Black Iron Orders
has been contaminated with
the demonic poison
and demonized.
Those who are poisoned by
the demonic poison
cannot kill each other.
They can only attack
those who are not poisoned.
Otherwise,
they will be choked
and their organs will be crushed.
Lord Si An!
I cannot become a puppet
and kill the innocent.
(Bloodshed Tavern)
(Dragon Mountain Mansion)
Xueying, Qingshi is inside.
Qingshi.
The demonized Heixuan Machine
is your doing.
Indeed.
Everyone who held the Black Iron Orders
has been demonized.
The Dragon Mountain Empire is in chaos.
Isn't it the best contribution
to the Demon Clan?
Hand over the antidote.
Who are you exactly?
You were trying to kill me
at Xueying Territory the other day.
But I saw you knew demonic techniques.
If you are one of us,
why are you doing this?
Hand over the antidote.
Or I'll kill you right now.
Since you don't consider me
one of your own,
then let's see who is the lucky one
to survive today.
At the last moment,
you can take this pill,
which can greatly increase your power
and help you fight against the enemy.
Second Priest actually lied to me.
I gave you a chance.
Senior.
She is my disciple.
Let me deal with her.
Master.
(If she tells others)
(about my demonic techniques,)
(my undercover investigation
in the Demon Clan)
(will be exposed.)
Go.
Go now.
If you still recognize me
as your senior brother,
let her go this time.
Consider it a favor.
Qiubai.
Senior,
why are you doing this?
I am her master.
You are also a master.
If it were you,
what would you do?
Senior.
The demonic poison has been in my body
for more than two decades now.
Sooner or later,
I will be demonized by it.
I've made many efforts
but all in vain.
I've gotten used to it.
Senior,
let me heal you.
No.
Once the demonic poison
invades your Dou Qi,
you will become demonized.
You must be careful.
Sikong Yang has already suffered.
I can't harm you anymore.
Qiubai,
the Dragon Mountain Emperor
established the Dragon Mountain Empire.
The will of Dragon Mountain
is still being passed down to this day.
It's for us to protect the homeland
and our people.
But it doesn't mean
we should exterminate other clans
at all costs.
Senior,
I understand.
I knew you would understand.
Back then, you were
the most outstanding disciple
of our Water Daoist Temple.
I didn't misjudge you.
Over these years,
you haven't disappointed me.
I'll leave Dragon Mountain Empire
to you all.
Farewell.
(Dragon Mountain Mansion)
Moyang Chen.
Dongbo Xueying!
Come out!
Qingshi.
Moyang Chen.
Do you still remember your master,
Master He?
He was killed by the Demon Clan.
Don't bring him up.
He was the one who drove me out
of the Black White Deity Mountain.
It was he who disowned me.
You only know
that he expelled you from the sect.
But you don't know
that if it weren't for him,
you wouldn't be alive today.
During the battle back then,
we paid a heavy price
to defeat the Demon Clan.
Now their remnants
are trying to establish
the Demon God Association
and corrupt and lure
our people of Dragon Mountain Empire.
I didn't expect
that person
has been hiding in your sect.
He just read
the secret manuals
left by the Demon Clan
after the war
and practiced it secretly.
He didn't know
it was a demonic technique.
He didn't join
the Demon God Association either.
I can guarantee this.
You.
You guarantee?
What can you guarantee?
He practiced the demonic techniques
under your nose
and you didn't even notice.
What makes you think
he didn't collude with
the Demon God Association?
Everyone saw that
he was obsessed with
practicing demonic techniques.
Now you want to vouch for
someone who practiced
demonic techniques?
You are a top practitioner of Xia Clan
and the head of
Black White Deity Mountain.
Don't tarnish your own
and your sect's reputation
for an unknown disciple.
An inattentive teacher is to blame.
It's my fault
for not supervising my disciple.
He Yuan,
what time is it?
And you're still
calling him your disciple?
He's already practiced
the demonic techniques,
which proves he can't sever ties
with the Demon Clan.
I will definitely
punish the rebellious disciple,
so he will
never dare to touch
demonic techniques again.
Save it.
In Dragon Mountain Empire,
anyone found
colluding with the Demon Clan
will be sentenced to death.
That's right.
Kill one to warn a hundred.
Everyone,
please give him one more chance.
He has a lot of potential.
I'll monitor him strictly in the future
and let him never dare to dabble in
demonic techniques again.
Once one practices demonic techniques,
demonic energy will enter the body.
How can you ensure
his energy is pure?
If he wants to practice
righteous martial arts again,
it will be hindered.
If he wants to make a breakthrough,
he needs to rely again on
the demonic technique
that has been suppressed in the body.
By then, the demonic technique
has already accumulated
in the body for a long time.
If you want to counter it,
it's by no means easy.
He was ten years old
when he joined
my Black White Deity Mountain.
He was smart and talented.
I had high hopes for him.
I didn't expect him to make a mistake
and it became a lifelong regret.
If we have to blame someone,
I can't pass the buck either.
I beg you
to spare his life.
I
will definitely sever his pulse.
So his martial arts
will never have a chance
to make progress again
and he absolutely can't
threaten the safety of all sects.
Master, you're so heartless.
Master!
Master,
you've already saved his life.
For him,
you even risked damaging
your own cultivation.
Is it really worth it?
Severing his pulse directly
is clean and neat.
But
for someone who has practiced
martial arts since childhood,
it's as if they're disabled,
which is equal to killing him.
Although I have severed
his pulse at four points,
the remaining pulse
is connected by cultivation.
But even so,
in this life,
he will never be able to
break through to Transcendent.
But he doesn't know
everything you've done for him.
He won't even
feel gratitude towards you.
I don't need his gratitude.
I just hope
he can live a decent life.
Forget the past
and start a new life.
Moyang Chen!
Master has been worried
about you all his life.
He just wanted you
to walk the right path.
But you went astray
and sank deeper and deeper,
eventually becoming
the accomplice who killed Master.
No, I didn't kill Master.
It was you, the accomplice.
Yes, it was me.
I killed Master.
Master, I'm sorry.
Shi.
Uncle Zong, hurry.
I'll detoxify him.
Take good care of Qingshi.
Master, I'm sorry.
Moyang Chen.
Puyang Bo.
Want to run?
Stop, Situ Hong.
You're actually
colluding with the Demon Clan.
Colluding with the Demon Clan
is not important.
What's important is
to have
a demonic technique
that can protect myself.
Then show me
your so-called
powerful demonic technique.
You
are not worth my effort.
Situ Hong,
if you dare, kill me.
Killing you is just
a piece of cake.
There's nothing
worth boasting about.
Only by killing Dongbo Xueying,
can I truly get excited.
Stop day-dreaming.
(The demonic poison is intensifying.)
(I)
(will never become like them.)
I've guarded this place for a lifetime.
Bloodshed Tavern.
If I kill them all,
there will be nothing left here.
Nothing at all.
Shan,
I'm on my way.
Moyang Chen must have used
a Vanishing Technique,
so they couldn't have gone far.
Follow me.
Uncle Zong Ling,
I don't have parents anymore.
No...
No one to protect me any longer.
What should I do?
With Uncle Zong Ling here,
no one will bully you.
I will protect you.
Shi,
I've told you
I will definitely protect you.
Uncle Zong, Uncle Zong.
Uncle Zong.
Uncle Zong,
you've taken my demonic poison.
Uncle Zong.
- Uncle Zong.
- Shi, don't cry.
You've already grown up.
You must learn to
protect yourself in the future.
Uncle Zong
can't protect you anymore.
No, don't!
Uncle Zong.
It's my fault.
I will not let you die in vain.
Master You Tu,
isn't there any other way
to prevent all of this?
Between Lord of Dragon Mountain Mansion
and Black Iron Orders,
there're contracts.
The contracts are passed down
from generation to generation.
Only Lord can terminate them.
But Lord is already unconscious.
Only by killing him,
can the contracts be ended.
Is there really no other way?
We'll leave Dragon Mountain Mansion
to you.
Master You Tu, Master You Tu.
Lord Si An.
Qingshi, what are you hesitating for?
Do it!
Lord Si An.
I'll entrust
Dragon Mountain Mansion to you.
I
will not fail you, Lord.
Take good care of
Dragon Mountain Mansion.
Take good care
of yourself.
- Master.
Let go of me, let go of me.
What on earth do you want to do?
Youyue.
Xueying.
Be careful. There must be a trap.
Puyang Bo!
Youyue.
Xueying.
Puyang Bo, figure it out now.
F-Figure it out.
Situ Hong,
as a descendant of the Si Family,
you bear the heavy responsibility
of the Xia Clan.
Yet you collude with the Demon Clan,
committing such despicable acts.
Situ Hong,
you conspired against Xueying.
I'll kill you.
Stop wasting your time.
This formation
is specifically designed for
Dongbo Xueying.
Except for the demonic techniques
of Demon Realm,
other martial arts
are of no use.
Dongbo Xueying,
you can only blame
the Ancient Blood within you.
I will not be at ease
until I kill you.
You're just like your deceased mother.
It's a pity to kill you,
but unbearable to let you live.
Let the Witch God Sword
drain out the Ancient Blood within you.
Then
leave the world forever.
- Xueying!
- Xueying.
Oh, no.
The Witch God formation
has been activated.
Xueying.
Master.
Master, please save Xueying. Master.
Master, hurry up.
I didn't expect Chi Qiubai
to be able to break
my Witch God Formation.
There you go.
Do take care of yourself.
Xueying,
I won't let you die.
Xueying.
Are you okay, Xueying?
Master,
did you use demonic technique?
(The Witch God Sword's
Witch Poison of Ghost Six Resentment)
(has seeped into your bloodstream.)
(Even if Witch God formation is broken,)
(there's no cure for your poison.)
(Dongbo Xueying,)
(your days are numbered.)
(Enjoy as your strength)
(dissipates gradually)
(and suffer slowly.)
Xueying.
Mrs. Xue,
I need to return to
Dragon Mountain Empire.
Right now.
Young Master,
I know you're worried about Xueying,
but that place
is not where you belong in the end.
And you just
got back to Moxue Empire.
Your divine veins
haven't fully recovered.
If you go down now,
you might not last three days.
Xueying
made efforts
to send me back here.
He didn't want me to be in any danger.
But now,
how can I just stand by
and watch him...
Watch him in danger.
I-I can't do it.
Even if you go back now,
it won't make a difference.
What do you mean by that?
Do you know
the Witch Poison Xueying was infected,
Witch Poison of Ghost Six Resentment,
was made by Witch God,
the brother of Great Demon God,
with his own energy core
before his death?
There's no cure at all.
What we can do now
is merely to use the medicine
to suppress the poison temporarily.
Eventually, his blood
will be consumed.
Even if you go back,
it won't change the outcome.
In that case,
I should return to the Empire even more.
If I can't even see Xueying
for the last time,
I will live in pain
forever
from now on.
With your current physical condition,
if you were to go down,
you wouldn't last a few days.
I don't care
how many days I can hold on.
Even if I could
see Xueying one more time,
I will definitely go back.
Is that person
that important to you?
Ever since I returned to Moxue Empire,
there hasn't been a day
that I haven't missed Xueying.
Every day, I reminisce
about every moment we spent together.
I really miss him.
Now that
he's afflicted with Witch Poison,
it must be the most painful
and vulnerable time for him.
Yet I can't stay by his side.
No. I must rush back.
If I don't go back now,
it'll be too late.
Young Master,
then you...
Stay with him.
Even if we come
to the end of life,
I'm willing.
Young Master,
are you sure about this?
Once it begins,
there's no turning back.
Mrs. Xue,
my mind is made up.
Let's begin.
If you truly wish to
stay in the human world,
I have a method.
What is it?
The Deboning Formation Spell.
It will eradicate the divine veins
within your body.
In this way,
I can live peacefully
in the Dragon Mountain Empire forever?
Then you will no longer
be a goddess,
but
an ordinary human.
As long as I can stay in
the Dragon Mountain Empire
and stay with Xueying,
whether I'm a goddess or not
doesn't matter anymore.
(Young Master,)
(the Deboning Formation Spell)
(only exists in ancient books.)
(No divine beings have ever)
(been willing to give up
their divine veins)
(and fall to the human world.)
So, the Deboning Formation Spell
might be more difficult than you think.
Even if you endure it,
there will be many
uncertainties.
For Xueying,
even if there's only
a one in ten thousand chance,
I will give it a try.
(I've sworn to Heaven)
(that I would protect and love her
for my entire life.)
(I am responsible
for protecting the world.)
(I am also responsible)
(for protecting my lover.)
(From now on, no matter where you are,)
(you are)
(the love of Dongbo Xueying)
(and the Lady of Xueying Territory.)
How is it?
His Dou Qi is continuously draining.
The Dou Qi you provided
probably won't last long.
It's my fault. Let's do it again.
Even if it drains all my Dou Qi,
I must save Xueying first.
I can't let my best friend die
of drained Dou Qi.
Puyang Bo, it's still not enough.
Xueying.
- Jingqiu.
You.
Jingqiu, your injury.
It's nothing.
This is Bitter Hundred Times,
which can temporarily suppress
the Witch Poison outbreak in his body
and slow down the spread.
Hurry, apply it on him.
The loss of Dou Qi
is finally under control.
Xueying.
Mother.
(When you needed me the most,)
(I wasn't by your side.)
(No matter what happens,)
(never give up hope.)
(You must live on.)
(Do you hear me, child?)
Master.
(My best friends)
(teamed up with my loved one)
(to deceive me.)
Jingqiu.
From today, I, Yu Jingqiu,
and Dongbo Xueying
are forever severed.
Xueying, I'm back.
Xueying,
I'm back.
♪Rain falls, kissing the flowers♪
♪The sound of a zither,
a beautiful figure♪
Why did you come back?
Am I dreaming?
It isn't a dream.
I'm here.
I'm back.
♪Brew the tale in moonlight♪
♪Drink it with the flavor of yearning♪
♪Half a life of sandstorms,
half a life of noise♪
I'm not leaving.
I'm staying here.
I will always be with you.
No.
You must go back.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I've found a way.
I can stay
at Dragon Mountain Empire for long.
Really? What is it?
♪Searching all corners of the world♪,
♪Crossing the wind and snow,
I will arrive♪
♪Regardless of the changes
brought by the passage of time♪
♪No matter if a lifetime
is like a moment♪
♪Like an orchid
in isolation from the world♪
♪In the past, young men spoke joyfully♪
♪The past vanishes.
Still, the crane lingers in my mind♪
♪A game of chess,
a pot of wine, a lifelong journey♪
♪Boiling wine and tea,
at peace in leisure.♪
♪Asking myself, the grove deep,
clouds dense, can I find him♪
♪Boiling wine and tea in my dreams,
not seeing the distant hometown♪
♪The old city and years gone by
fill me with melancholy♪
♪I want to light
the candlelight with moonlight♪
♪Not masking the sharp-edged resolve,
sighing that the world is not in vain♪
♪The worldly love
is fickle and changeable♪
♪Walking leisurely,
hoping old friends are well♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
Wishing to enjoy it with you♪
♪I want to hide the starlight in time♪
♪Forgetting each other silently
at the ends of the earth♪
♪Worldly people love
indulging in joy and revelry♪
♪Gradually moving further away,
adding poetry to the wine cup♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
I wish to enjoy it with you♪
♪Together on this journey♪