♪Traversing the vast expanse of time♪
♪Smiling proudly
in the mortal world alone♪
♪Cold moonlight♪
♪Earth as paper, sky as brush♪
♪This life like ink splashed on paper♪
♪Indulging in ups and downs♪
♪Coldly confronting
the approaching edges, sword and blade♪
♪My heart is narrow,
only holding heaven and earth♪
♪Boundless sea,
countless surging waves in the dark♪
♪Aeons just like a fleeting moment,
using youth as color♪
♪A silver-white hue climbs up
the temples, undaunted by setbacks♪
♪In the eyes, an unquenchable light♪
♪A body of proud bones,
unbending in the face of wind and frost♪
♪Smiling at the thorny webs♪
♪Being a lone wolf,
born to be solitary and independent♪
♪My pride alters not a jot♪
♪Resounding loudly through the clouds♪
♪In the cold world,
a heart burning hot for you♪
=Snow Eagle Lord=
=Episode 36=
Your Ancient Bloodline
is just awakened.
In the future, when you cultivate,
you must rest more.
If you need
anything,
feel free to find me.
Well,
I won't bother you anymore.
I need to discuss it with Xueying.
Xueying.
Situ Hong?
What do you want
from Xueying?
I'm parched.
Is there anything else?
If not,
we have something
to discuss with Xueying.
I think you should get lost.
If only I had listened to you.
The sun is too bright.
Xueying,
you saw the situation
with Hero Shan.
Master Bai Yuanzhi has been plagued
by the demonic poison for years.
Both Puyang Bo and I
are worried about his condition.
Yes.
What if he can't resist
the demonic poison
and ends up like Hero Shan?
I was planning
to discuss countermeasures
with Master Sikong and Bai Yuanzhi.
I-I have a stomachache.
Ate something bad?
No.
Youyue and I ate lunch together.
No, no, no, it's not that kind of pain.
Puyang Bo, are you alright?
Sit up.
Your breath is unstable.
Move to calm down.
I'm in too much pain to sit still
and you want me to move.
Are you feeling better?
Why is it suddenly so unstable?
I don't know.
Youyue and I
were planning to find you this morning.
I did what she did.
Ate what she ate.
She's fine.
How come my breath
is disordered?
No.
There's one thing we did differently.
You used it
but I didn't.
Tea.
Xueying,
it seems someone wanted to harm you
but Puyang Bo
accidentally took it.
Who is it?
I'll teach them a lesson.
No one
has touched my tea.
No one has been in my room.
Unless...
Situ Hong.
Nothing good happens when I meet him.
I'll find him now.
Situ Hong.
You're addicted to playing tricks,
aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Fine.
You don't understand. Then tell me
why you are standing here.
Are you checking
if you put
the right amount of poison in his tea
or if Xueying falls down or not?
Why do you
always talk about medicine?
I think you should take medicine.
I lost my jade pendant,
so I came to look for it.
What jade pendant?
You.
Puyang Bo.
This is Energy Gathering Pill.
It helps stabilize your inner breath.
Take it now.
Quick.
You just started practicing
the advanced moves of the Shadow Blade
and used a lot of Internal Energy
in a short time.
I guess that's why
your breath was suddenly chaotic.
You're talking nonsense.
Zhuo Yi,
it's Situ Hong's ill intention.
He put something in the tea
and Puyang Bo accidentally drank it.
That's why this happened.
Where is the tea?
I'll go get it.
It's here.
I'll give it to the Elder Council
to see what medicine
he put in it.
What are you doing?
Didn't you suspect
that there's a problem
with this cup of tea?
Look, I drank it
and there's no
breath instability.
It's not the tea's problem.
It's because the time was too short.
Look, almost 15 minutes
have passed.
And I am still fine.
It's not the tea's problem.
It's Puyang Bo's
unstable Internal Energy.
Then why
is Situ Hong still not leaving
and lurking outside the door?
First,
I didn't lurk.
Second,
I made it very clear just now
I came to find my jade pendant.
Your jade pendant.
Since it's all a misunderstanding,
everyone should go back.
As a boy,
you should
practice your breathing regularly.
Otherwise,
you'll often need medicine.
Situ Hong, you...
Youyue, Youyue.
Forget it. Forget it.
Ignore him.
Puyang Bo.
Xueying.
You just let him go like this?
I still think
there's something fishy about this.
This is clearly
Situ Hong's doing.
But we have no evidence,
so it's a waste of time to continue.
Don't forget
we have
more important things to do.
Right.
Youyue, simmer down.
Simmer down.
Next time,
we'll catch him red-handed,
so he has no way to argue,
alright?
Besides, we came to find Xueying
to discuss
Bai Yuanzhi and Sikong Yang's affairs, right?
We can't forget about the main issue.
Alright then.
Let's deal with the main issue first.
This time,
I'll put it
on my revenge memo.
You have such a memo?
Am I on it?
When will you stop
following me?
So you sealed off
your own breath.
That's how you managed to be unharmed.
I've practiced
the breath technique
of True Meaning of Taixu,
so I am most familiar
with adjusting the pulse.
I can retain
the superficial circulation of breath
while adjusting
the deep inner power on my own.
This technique is really good,
but
since you already know
my secret,
I...
Who sent you?
Why did you help me?
You are a capable person.
I'm willing to believe
you're not a bad person.
We are all
trying our best to survive.
Don't meddle in
other people's affairs in the future.
Otherwise,
I'll definitely kill you.
Do you really want to beat
Dongbo Xueying that much?
Someday,
Dongbo Xueying will be defeated
by me.
Look,
the moon tonight
is so round and bright.
It's been a long time
since I've seen such a beautiful moon.
Such a pity, though,
the moon has
its waxing and waning phases.
Senior, you're too sentimental,
making the kids
afraid to speak.
Do you have
any important matters?
Senior,
a few days ago we went to Qing River
and found out...
That the demon you saw
was the poisoned Hero Shan.
You both knew?
I knew what the outcome will be
after being poisoned
by the demonic poison.
So twenty years ago,
I wanted to end my life,
so as not to become
a demon that would harm the Xia Clan.
But
because of an unfinished task,
I couldn't leave so easily.
Yes.
In order to protect me,
Senior was accidentally
infected by the demonic poison.
If it weren't for my senior brother...
Alright, alright.
Talking about these things.
Who was to protect you?
Don't make us seem so intimate,
as if we were a couple.
But
as long as the Demon Clan exists,
they will be plotting
to continue their attack
on our Xia Clan.
As long as the Demon Clan exists,
our Xia Clan
will not have a single day of peace.
Senior and I will hold on
to the very last day we can
to protect the Xia Clan
and eradicate the Demon Clan.
It is our lifelong mission.
Xueying,
if one day,
we become like Hero Shan,
losing our minds
and turning
into uncontrollable demons,
you must be ruthless.
Master Bai,
Master,
"Fortune favors the virtuous."
You will be fine for sure.
You will definitely be alright.
Once we defeat Great Demon God,
we will get the antidote
for the demonic poison from them.
At that time,
you will be safe and sound.
Miss Youyue is right.
Both of you masters
shouldn't worry too much.
You will definitely be fine.
Alright, Senior,
don't go against the children's wishes.
Let's not talk about unhappy things.
Come, let's all enjoy the moon.
(Xueying,)
(what's on your mind?)
(Elder Ye is heartbroken)
(because of Hero Shan's incident.)
(Master Bai and Master Sikong)
(have also been infected
with the demonic poison.)
Now the Elder Council
has suffered heavy casualties.
The entire Dragon Mountain Empire
is in grave danger.
Is that all you wanted to say?
And the remnants of Demon God.
I really don't know where to find it.
The Demon Clan is invading,
one wave after another.
Suddenly, I feel
the road ahead is very dark
and I am very confused.
Xueying,
you practiced at the Changfeng Academy,
improving your martial arts
and elevating from a Mortal Knight
to Transcendent.
Since that day,
you are a qualified warrior
of the Xia Clan.
Not only do you shoulder
the mission to protect the Xia Clan,
but you also should have the ability
to withstand pressure and sadness.
But now I really don't know
how to hold on.
As long as you have faith,
you will be able to hold on.
You are so lost now,
not like a disciple
from Changfeng Academy.
Nor like a qualified disciple of mine,
Chi Qiubai's disciple.
Master.
Xueying,
why do you practice martial arts?
Without firm faith,
no matter how powerful you are,
you're just exercising.
How could you have become like this
when I valued you so much
in the beginning?
(I understand now.)
(I will find
the remnants of the Demon God)
(as soon as possible)
(and destroy him.)
(What you need is not)
(my encouragement and comfort.)
(What you need)
(is to eliminate
the distractions in your mind)
(and to stick to
your original intention.)
(You need to grow up soon.)
(Only by breaking through yourself)
(and relying on your own strength)
(to fight against
helplessness and loneliness,)
(can you have firm faith.)
At that time,
you will be a true powerhouse.
(Xueying,)
(if one day I am gone,)
(you become the only hope
for the Xia Clan.)
(For what I cannot do,)
(only you can make it in the future.)
(I will definitely become a qualified)
(Changfeng disciple.)
(To find Great Demon God's remnants.)
(But)
(where should I start?)
Rong,
whether you believe it or not,
since the day I took you as my disciple,
until now,
I have never thought about putting you
in a deadly situation.
I'd rather be killed now
than be like this.
It's not too late for everything.
You still have a chance.
The people of Xia Clan
will only suspect me,
doubt me,
and never trust me.
Have you ever thought
that the problem lies in yourself?
Rong,
if you are truly innocent,
they will trust you.
Who is it?
(I was truly tricked by them.)
Greetings, Second Priest.
I knew you
would definitely come to save me.
Ji Rong,
don't be too happy too soon.
You've been in trouble lately.
I don't understand what you mean,
Second Priest.
You should be very clear
you are just a half-demon.
The Demon Clan trusted you,
relied on you,
and gave you
the important tasks of Third Priest.
But your recent performance
has disappointed Great Demon God
and even made me
doubt your loyalty.
Second Priest,
Ji Rong is absolutely loyal
to the Demon Clan.
You misunderstood me.
A few days ago,
it was because my master
locked me up.
I lost my freedom,
so I couldn't
get in touch with Demon God Association.
This was not my intention.
Fine,
I will give you another chance
to atone for your sins.
Thank you, Second Priest.
I will definitely do my best.
Great Demon God has already gained
the Witch God Sword.
Use it to kill Xueying
and take his Ancient Bloodline's blood.
The Witch God Sword
is next to the Demon Well.
After you find it,
take it to Leichao Sea Cliff.
Can you do it?
I will definitely get it done.
(Xueying Territory)
Commander Zong.
Knight Changfeng.
Didn't Xueying return with you?
He just had awakened
his Ancient Bloodline
and his breath is unstable,
so he still needs to rest.
That's fine. It's good to rest well.
I came this time
to check the Demon Well.
Can you show me the way?
Sure.
Is there anything wrong
with the Demon Clan?
No. Don't worry.
Please.
Commander Zong.
Thank you all.
Standing guard may be boring,
but it's indispensable.
Without your protection,
there would be no peace in our homeland.
We still need to train and reorganize,
so we can maintain
a state of readiness
for battle at any time.
Guarding day after day
is not easy.
Today, since I'm here,
you could take a break.
You can go down the mountain to rest.
Commander Zong and I
will watch over here.
Commander Zong,
what do you think?
Of course, it's good.
You all go ahead.
Thank you, Commander Zong.
These little soldiers
are actually quite pitiful.
The youngest among them
was only 14 years old
when he became a soldier.
14 years old is the time for studying.
Yes, but most of them
had their parents killed by demons,
causing their families to be broken.
They became soldiers here.
One, they can be fed.
Two, they can kill the demons
and avenge their parents.
As long as
the Demon Clan is not eliminated,
such tragedies
will continue to happen.
The Demon Clan has caused
countless families to be separated,
and homes to be destroyed.
So many people
have lost their closest and dearest
because of the Demon Clan.
I remember when times were peaceful,
everyone loved to gather around me
and listen to stories.
At that time,
a good story
could be exchanged
for a pot of good wine.
Commander Zong.
It is not appropriate
since we are still guarding
and it's daytime.
Do you still have stories?
Good wine.
Ying and Shi
loved listening to my stories
when they were young.
Every time they said,
"Uncle Zong, have a drink."
I knew
they wanted to hear a story.
It's hard to imagine Xueying
clinging to you
and listening to your story.
Ying may look cold,
but he's actually warm-hearted.
Yet he likes
to keep things to himself
and not speak up.
Just like when Miss Yu left last time,
he was extremely reluctant,
but in order to
let Miss Yu leave with peace of mind,
he didn't say a word.
Actually, even if Xueying didn't say it,
I knew it.
Knowing or not knowing is one thing,
and saying or not saying
is another matter.
We
have to speak up.
Uncle Zong,
I'm sorry.
(Ao Lan said)
(the Witch God Sword)
(is meant to deal with Xueying.)
(It is a test from the Demon Clan.)
(What should I do?)
(I can't just let)
(the Demon Clan)
(kill Xueying.)
I must destroy you.
No.
You've been with me for so many years.
I can't destroy you.
Alright,
this time I'll listen to you.
Thank you, Senior.
(Chi Qiubai.)
(How could he be here?)
Chi Qiubai.
Why is the Witch God Sword in your hand?
Now there are two things
you need to do.
First,
fetch the Witch God Sword
from Xueying Territory.
Witch God Sword
was cast by the brother of Demon God,
Witch God, with his energy core
before dying.
The witch poison has no cure.
What do you want
the Witch God Sword for?
To kill your most beloved student,
Dongbo Xueying.
How did you promise me back then,
saying you would never harm Xueying?
Back then was back then.
Now things have changed.
His Ancient Bloodline
may threaten the safety
of Great Demon God at any time.
His blood
can also be refined
into Soul Condensing Pill.
The Witch God Sword
has the power to extract blood.
I want his blood
for the use of my Demon Clan.
What is the second thing?
Kill Ji Rong.
Ji Rong?
She is the third priest
of the Demon Clan,
but she is a half-demon.
Her stance has always been unclear
and she even
took a mortal as her master.
Time and time again,
she has refused
the orders of our Demon Clan.
I suspect she is not entirely loyal.
Kill her
and set an example.
But Ji Rong is close to Master Bai,
I'm afraid
it will be difficult to do it.
You just go and get the Witch God Sword
and Ji Rong will come to you.
Knight Changfeng,
once you complete these tasks,
you will be the third priest
of the Demon Clan.
You don't need to know.
(The Witch God Sword
is in his possession.)
(Could this be the intention
of the Demon Clan?)
Knight Changfeng.
Knight Changfeng.
Commander Zong,
you are awake.
Come on.
Is it my wine that's strong,
or is your alcohol tolerance weak?
Maybe I'm getting old.
I actually got drunk
on this little bit of wine.
I feel like I just had a nap.
Knight Changfeng, you...
I'm hungry.
Is there anything to eat?
Yes. Let's go.
I'll make you something delicious.
(She actually escaped)
(from Chi Qiubai.)
Did you get the item?
It's my incompetence.
The Witch God Sword
was taken by Chi Qiubai.
Chi Qiubai attacked you?
If it wasn't for
Zong Ling's interruption,
I would have been killed by him.
Chi Qiubai also used demonic technique.
Is he one of us?
You actually sent him to kill me.
I've been loyal
to the Demon Clan for so long
and I've done so much
for the Demon Clan.
Yet, you want to kill me.
Ji Rong,
you still don't understand
your own identity.
Your father and your master
are both human.
Now you have joined the Demon Clan,
but when will you
return to the embrace of humanity?
I won't.
Now it has come to
the most crucial moment
for our Demon Clan.
I can't tolerate
any uncertainty.
Chi Qiubai is also human,
so why do you trust him?
Foolish.
Value is more important than trust.
His identity within the Xia Clan
can help our Demon Clan
get things done more smoothly.
Besides,
I have something on him.
I am the same.
I can do
what he can.
You?
What value do you have left?
Today, I will consider
your past contributions
to the Demon Clan
and let you die a little faster.
Xueying.
Dongbo Xueying.
I know his younger brother,
Dongbo Qingshi, likes me.
I can use Qingshi
to lure Xueying.
I know Xueying is useful to you.
I can also use Qingshi
to restrain Xueying.
If you could really restrain Qingshi,
how could you have failed so many times?
Wait a minute.
Great Demon God.
I'll give you one last chance.
Do as you say
and lure Dongbo Xueying.
If you do well this time,
the position of the third priest
will still be yours.
Master.
Yes. Thank you, Great Demon God.
I will definitely
serve the Demon Clan to the death.
Ao Lan,
give her the item.
At the last moment,
you can take this pill.
It can greatly increase your strength
and fight a decisive battle
with the enemy.
Thank you, Great Demon God.
Thank you, Second Priest.
I will definitely succeed.
(Dragon Mountain Mansion)
Please show your pass.
I don't have a pass.
I'm here to find someone.
Without a pass
for Dragon Mountain Mansion,
nobody is allowed in.
Sir,
I'm here to find someone.
Let me in to find him
and then I'll naturally have a pass.
No.
Then,
can you send someone in to find him?
Just say
Dongbo Qingshi's sister
is looking for him.
Dongbo Qingshi's sister?
I've never heard
that Dongbo Qingshi has a sister.
You send someone in to find him
and you'll know after asking.
Since you're so unwilling,
then I'll leave.
It took me quite a while
to find this place.
If Qingshi asks later,
but you drove his sister away,
then...
Wait a moment.
Hold on, I'll report.
Ji Rong, it is Dragon Mountain Mansion.
That's not a place for you to come.
Qingshi,
I've been looking for you
for a long time
and finally found out you're here.
Why are you looking for me?
I'm sorry, Qingshi.
I know now,
in this world,
only you truly care about me
and truly love me.
Why are you suddenly saying such things?
Master and Sikong Yang
don't believe me at all.
They've been misunderstanding me
and have me under arrest.
I escaped with great difficulty.
Go, Ji Rong.
Go back to Master.
I won't go back.
If I go back, they will continue
to put me under house arrest.
Can I
stay with you for a while?
No.
Don't worry.
I will behave.
I absolutely won't cause you trouble.
It is Dragon Mountain Mansion.
It's not suitable
to keep you here.
Then I have no place
to go.
If you won't take me in,
then I...
You once said you'd give me a home,
no matter where this home is,
as long as it has you and me, it's home.
Have you forgotten all of this?
I just want to
be with you.
No matter where I go, I'm willing.
Alright.
I
can let you stay for now,
but the most important thing now is
to find the traces of Great Demon God.
Only after all this is over,
can I take you back to
Xueying Territory.
That's great, Qingshi.
I'm willing to go back with you
and kill the Demon Clan
to contribute to
the elimination of the Demon Clan.
Alright.
I believe in you.
Rong,
rest well.
I still have to be on guard.
One day when we
really occupy the Xia Clan,
they
not only will
be defeated by our Demon Clan
but also defeated by their confusion
and fear.
And only our Demon Clan,
such a loyal
and noble clan
with faith,
deserves to rule the world.
You are absolutely right, Master.
Why should we
curl up in this dark and cold
Dark Abyss?
Those inferior humans
don't deserve to live in
Dragon Mountain Empire
with abundant water, lush grass,
and blooming flowers.
In the future,
that place will definitely be ours.
Moyang Yu
ruined my plans again.
My remnants
need a new host,
which will take a long wait.
Otherwise,
Dragon Mountain Empire
would have been ours long ago.
Master, you can rest assured.
We will definitely think of
new methods.
They will never expect
the current Knight Changfeng
will become a future Demon Clan Knight.
Rong,
why are you here?
I was afraid
you'd be hungry when guarding,
so I made you some pastries.
Don't worry.
I was very careful on my way here.
No one discovered me.
You should stay
in the room.
Don't take any more risks coming out.
Alright, I got it.
You should eat now.
It doesn't taste good when it's cold.
I remember you mentioned
in Xueying Territory
that you loved
this osmanthus cake the most.
Fine,
I'll eat.
The Dragon Mountain Mansion is so big.
Are you the only one on guard duty?
Of course not.
The most valuable information
in Dragon Mountain Mansion
is all here.
Other places are just for archiving,
storing and placing some equipment.
There are mechanisms everywhere here.
It's hard for ordinary people to escape.
So Dragon Mountain Mansion
doesn't actually need too many guards.
I see.
What's this big stuff?
This is called Heixuan Machine.
The Black Iron Orders issued
by our Dragon Mountain Mansion
will spread to every corner
of Dragon Mountain Empire.
In order to be able
to assemble forces in an emergency,
this Heixuan Machine was set up.
It is used to control
all the Black Iron Orders
in our Dragon Mountain Empire.
Alright.
I will finish them.
You shall go back and rest well.
Come back quickly when you are done.
I'll be waiting for you in the room.
Xueying,
there's nothing in Leichao Sea Cliff.
Could there be something wrong
with Qingshi's intelligence?
Qingshi is at Dragon Mountain Mansion
studying intelligence investigation
with Si An.
His intelligence
is more accurate than before.
And
since he dares to
pass on this message,
he must be sure it's correct.
Actually, we had some gains.
Look,
I picked this up
near Leichao Sea Cliff.
It's a magic crystal
used to maintain
the Demon Clan's souls.
Maintaining Demon Clan's souls?
There must have been
Great Demon God lurking.
Only he would urgently need
this thing in large quantities.
We were one step late.
Or you could say
someone was one step
ahead of us.
Stop.
This is sand and gravel
found only by the sea.
Where have you gone?
You're not my wife.
Why do I have to report to you
where I went?
This unique scent from the seaside
smells like...
Sea God Palace.
It was I who asked Situ Hong
to take me
to Sea God Palace.
I have never been to
the sea area of Sea God Palace.
I have always yearned
for the scenery there,
so I asked Situ Hong
to take me for a tour nearby.
Don't believe it? My body
also contains the smell of the sea.
Even if both of you have
the same smell on your bodies,
it can only prove
you have been to the same place.
But it doesn't mean
where you went.
You mean
we teamed up to deceive you.
Kong Youyue,
I know you don't like me.
But before you have conclusive evidence,
get out of the way.
You...
Youyue.
If you want to go, just go.
Why all the nonsense?
I still feel something is wrong.
Last time,
it was also Zhuo Yi
who helped Situ Hong out.
Situ Hong's relationship
with the Demon Clan
must not be simple.
But the truth
will definitely come to light.
Qingshi.
I'm sorry, Qingshi.
This time I want to live for myself.
(Heixuan Machine that controls)
(all the Black Iron Orders
of Dragon Mountain Mansion)
(is about to be demonized.)
Come chaos.
The more chaotic, the better.
Let the whole Dragon Mountain Empire
be in chaos.
Always stubbornly saying to let go,
but the number of times
you come to the pavilion
is the most.
Princess,
it's so cold today.
Go back and sleep.
Alright.
I wonder how
Dragon Mountain Empire is doing.
Princess,
you and Lord Xueying are separated.
Forget
what you should.
Mrs. Xue,
let me take one more look, please.
The Demon Clan started to attack.
(Xueying.)
(You must be safe.)
♪Like an orchid
in isolation from the world♪
♪In the past, young men spoke joyfully♪
♪The past vanishes.
Still, the crane lingers in my mind♪
♪A game of chess,
a pot of wine, a lifelong journey♪
♪Boiling wine and tea,
at peace in leisure.♪
♪Asking myself, the grove deep,
clouds dense, can I find him♪
♪Boiling wine and tea in my dreams,
not seeing the distant hometown♪
♪The old city and years gone by
fill me with melancholy♪
♪I want to light
the candlelight with moonlight♪
♪Not masking the sharp-edged resolve,
sighing that the world is not in vain♪
♪The worldly love
is fickle and changeable♪
♪Walking leisurely,
hoping old friends are well♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
Wishing to enjoy it with you♪
♪I want to hide the starlight in time♪
♪Forgetting each other silently
at the ends of the earth♪
♪Worldly people love
indulging in joy and revelry♪
♪Gradually moving further away,
adding poetry to the wine cup♪
♪Depicting your gaze in my memory♪
♪Bathing in snow on a journey,
brushing sleeves covered in frost♪
♪Where the wind passes, peace follows.
I wish to enjoy it with you♪
♪Together on this journey♪