Sister.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
When I was young,
when I was young.
This is nothing.
Let me help you up.
Sister-in-law.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just fell down.
Is it Concubine Qiao again?
It has nothing to do with her.
I fell down in the shop.
How did you take care of her?
Shuang'er.
What does it have to do with Shuang'er?
As the manager,
I have to do my job myself.
Shuang'er.
Thank you.
Go back first.
Wang Lu.
I’m leaving too.
Does it hurt?
Be gentle.
Why are you so careless?
I told you
to do those things.
I'm the manager.
The pay is so expensive.
Of course I need to save money.
Be careful next time.
You haven't recovered yet. Why are you in such a hurry?
I finally won the championship.
but I got smashed again.
I hurt my foot again.
I need to get better soon.
and make money.
I'll do it myself.
You've been
throwing yourself into your arms lately?
That's because
You're handsome.
Sister, the decoction is ready.
It's all your fault.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
I didn't mean it.
I’m fine.
It’s my fault.
and bumped into Lady Daishuang.
Wang Lu,
Do you think this pair of girls gave me this handkerchief
for me too?
This handkerchief
is not from her, right?
Shuang'er.
Shuang’er’s handkerchief.
I washed it for you.
Here you are.
There's something wrong.
Shuang'er.
What do you think of our Second Prince?
Sister.
Mr. Bai is really
handsome and handsome.
You just came to open the shop in a hurry.
I thought it was a big business.
The God of Wealth helped me a lot.
With me here,
money will come.
Really?
Of course.
Of course you still need me.
The famous
and dashing husband.
Duke Zhou.
Help me.
Just a little.
It's worth it.
I'll give you
of your beauty store.
What do you think?
What did you call me?
Duke Zhou.
The first line.
Honey.
I don't want profit.
You are mine.
Yours is mine.
No way.
I can be yours.
But the money has to be mine.
Okay.
Tell me.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to bring me to the palace.
I want all the ladies in the palace
to use my cosmetics.
This can promote Qiao's beauty shop.
Okay.
It's nothing.
It's much white.
Your skin has indeed become tenderer.
Noble Consort,
are you satisfied?
Reward.
Great!
Qiao Qiao's cosmetics shop
will launch more new products in the future.
Please
Thank you.
Nine Provinces.
Nine counties.
Double white.
Half white.
Fortunately
[Sansan]
"Xiangshan."
Half white.
Qiao Zhou.
Virtuous Virtuous Virtuous Virtuous, half white.
King.
Xiangshan.
Nine counties.
First, Xiangshan.
Half white.
Nine counties.
Qiao Zhou.
[Concubine] Baek
Sangshan
Sangsan.
Maternal concubines are half white.
Mother and concubines are half white.
My grandmother gave birth to a concubine in charge, Wang Qiao Daimu.
Shang Shang Shan
Semi-king, Double-White Province.
Qiao, Zhou, Mu Zhou, Qiao.
Mother, Mother, concubine, cabinet, Virtuous Mother Half double white
Xiangshan.
My grandmother gave birth to my aunt, Wang Qiao Daimu.
Mother's concubine, Manager Virtuous, half white.
King Xiangshan.
My grandmother gave birth to my aunt, Wang Qiao Daimu.
Mother's concubine, Manager Virtuous, half white.
Semi-Wang, Double-White Province.
One.
King Xiangshan.
Huaquan Qu
"Cheng'er from both households of Hangsan Gan."
Mu Chow Qiao.
Semi-king, Double-White Province.
Qiao Chow Dynasty Mu Chow Qiao.
Factory, Factory, 17.
Shanshan.
Ten mouths of Hangshan.
One.
Xiangshan.
Prime minister, Double and White Provinces.
Ten times from Yuewang Restaurant.
Jiujiu, Wang Ban Wang, Double White Province.
Wang Qiao, Zhou, Mu Zhou Qiao.
Boshan Dazhuang.
Hashiyamaogua.
One, half, the whole county, nine.
Prince Xiangshan.
Xinchao.
Yu Xin Xin
Yu Xin Chao.
Xin Camp.
Falling Camp.
Yumori Fancamp.
Zantama Yu Xin Chao.
Feng, Yudian Camp.
Chen, Kai, Jue, Kai, Xin, Chao.
Fengyu Fan Camp.
Chen, Kai, Jue, roots, Xin, Chao.
Feng, Yudian Fan Camp.
Chen Xiu Kai, root jade, Xin Xin Chao.
Li Wenhan: Zhao Julin Yao, Ruan, Chen Lei, Huang Jiang, Wang.
Chen Xiu, Kai, Jade, Yu, Xinxin Chao.
Light.
Big.
Feng
Ali Yaoli Haicheng University.
Feng, Yudian Fan Camp
KAN Liqing, Glory.
Li Qing is brave.
[Yumori Fan Camp]
Bin Yaoli Yaoli Haicheng University.
Lin Yan Wan Xu Zhu Lu.
Ken Liqing.
Zhao Julin, Lin Yao, Chen Lei, Huang Jiang, Wang.
Chen Xiu, Kai, Kun, Yu, Xin Chao.
Chen, Kai, Yu, Yu. Xin. Chao.
Feng, Yudian Fan Camp.
Bin Yaoli Yaoli Haicheng University.
Kenli Qing
Zhao, Lin, Yao, Ruan, Chen, Lei, Yao. Huang, Jiang, Wang.
Feng, Yudian Fan Camp
Bin Ali Yaoli Yaoli Haicheng University.
Chen, Kai, Jue, roots, Xin, Chao.
Kenli Qing
Xu Lin Yan Wan Xu Zhu Lu.
Feng, Yudian Fan Camp.
Bin Yali Yaoli Haicheng University.
Neck.
Kenli Qing
Xu Lin Yan, Xu, Zhu Lu.
Li Zhenning: Zhao Zhenlin Yao, Ruan, Chen Lei, Huang Jiang, Wang.
Chen Xisu, Kai, Ken, Yu, Xin Chao.
Bin Ali Yaoli Yaoli Haicheng University.
Kenqing, Brave.
Xu Lin Yan Wan Xu Zhu Lu.
Chen Xiu Kai, Jade root, Yu Xin Chao.
Wu, Wu, Zhang, Sun, Huang, Li.
Sheep.
Group.
Chen, Zhang,
Yu...
Build Jin, Qinqing, Zhanqing, Wei.
Li Zhu, Li Fan, Chen, Zhang, Sun, Li.
Lan Jianjian, Qinqing, Zhanqing Camp,
Bin Yaoli Yaoli Haicheng University.
Camp, fight.
Xu Lin Yan Wan Xu Zhu Lu.
Huang You, you, Ding, Li, Zhu, Meng. Fan, Chen, Zhang, Sun, Huang, Li.
Yang, Youting, Luo, Li, Li, Li, Chen, Zhang, Sun, Huang, Li.
Mei Camp fights "Lan Jian, Jin Qinqing, Wei Wei, Wei, Wei, Wei, Wei, Wei."
At the beginning of the year,
Bao, Zhang, Sun,
Liang Da Xiao De Jie Xin Ke.
Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Yang, Huang Youting, Luo, Li, Li.
Fan Chen Zhang
Dijun, Jun, women, strong, plum camp, fight Lan, Jian, Jin, Qin, Qing, Jie. Wei Xin Camp.
Wang Yang.
Zhang Yixing: Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Ding, Ding, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li.
Dijun Kwan Kwan, Mei Camp, Da Lan, Jin Qinqing, the Imperial Guards.
Li, Fan, Chen, Wu, Zhang.
Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Yang, Huang Youting, Li, Li, Li, Chen, Zhang, Zhang, Li.
Dijun Kwan, Mei Camp, Lan Jian, Jin Qinqing, the best. Camp.
An, Yan, Xin, Youyou, Ding.
Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Ding, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li.
Dijun, Qiang Mei Camp. Lan Jianjian, Qinqing Group, Camp
Leblin Jiang Wen Wang
Dong, Zheng, Wei, Cong, Chao.
Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Yang, Huang Youting, Luo.
Li Zhu, Li Fan, Chen, Zhang, Sun, Li.
Dijun Kwan, Mei Camp, Da Lan, Jin Qinqing, and the Imperial Guards.
Sumire Lei Lin Jiang
Rain Dong Qing 1
Yan Xinyou Ding Little Water Wisdom Super Young-joon New Cream
Yao, Xu, Wang, Yang, Xin, Yo, Shi, Shi. Little water, Li, Chao, Yong, Zhang, Xin. Huang
Li Yao.
Dijun Kwan Meiqiang fights "Lan Jian, Jin Qinqing, the best warriors." Camp.
"Qu, Zhai, Dummy, Win, Bang, Fan, Housing Question"
Official Zhang Que, Wu Li Lilin's wife.
Li Yao, Xu San.
Jiang Zheng, Kun, Chen.
Wang Yang, Huang Youting, Luo, Li, Li, Chen, Zhang, Huang, Li.
Dijun Kwan Kwan, Mei Camp, Da Lan, Jin Qinqing Group, Wei Wei Camp.
Zhang Yixing: Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Ding, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Huang, Li.
Jiang Zheng, Kun, Chen, Chen.
Wai-wook
Dijun Qiang Mei Camp.
Wu Liulin, Jiang Wenwang.
Zeng.
Dijun Qiang Mei Camp. Lan Jian, Qinqing Group, Wei Xin Camp.
Fragrance, Zechen, Rain Dong, Wei, Wei, Sun.
A clear voice.
Zhou, Chen, Wei, De.
Zhang Yixing: Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Wang, Ding, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Huang, Li.
Zhang Zhai Wu Li Lin Jiang
Di Junqiang Mei Camp, Da Lan Jian, Jin Qinqing, the new camp.
Xiang, Jiang, Ze, Jiang, Ze, Jun, Dong.
Feng Lei.
Li Ronghao: Li Ronghao,
Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Wang, Yang, Huang Youting, Li, Li, Li, Chen, Zhang, Zhang, Huang Li.
Lin Jing.
Luo...
Dijun's Plum Camp is fighting. Lanjian Jin, Qinqing's army. Camp.
Jiang Zheng Kun Jie Chen.
Dijun Qiang Mei Camp, Da Lan, Jin Qinqing's army camp.
Boya, go.
Zhang Yao Xu, Yang Youting, Ding, Li Zhu, Li Fan, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Huang, Li.
Zhang, Zhou, Zhou, Zhou, Chen, Wei, Zhu, Wang.
Fang Ming Qi, Lei's private account.
Lin Jing Zhang Wu Lilin Jiang Wenwang
Xiang Li Zechen Yu Ziwei.
Lü Zhang, Zhou, Zhou, Zhou, Chen, Wei, Zeng.
SBA Chaochun Songshi just established Wei Xuli.
Ming Mingming Chaofeng Lei Songbo
Li Yao, Xu, Wang, Wang, Yang, Huang Youting, Li, Li, Li, Li, Chen, Zhang, Zhang, Huang, Li.
Lin, Zhang, Zheng, De, De.
Burning the robe, Zhang Zhai, exhausting Chu Xi.
Meng Fangming Feng Lei Bo Wei
Lin Xuan, Zhang Zhai, Wu Li, Lin Lin, Jiang Wendao.
Poison.
[Ming Mingming]
Mingming, Fenglei, Bo, Wei.
Liu, Yuan, Li, Jiang, Luo, Wang.
Lü Zhang, Zhou, Zhou, Zhou, Chen, Wei, Zeng, Zhu, Wang.
Meng, Bo, Feng, Song, Bo. Wei, one.
One.
When King Zhang, Zhou, Zhou, Wu, Chen, Wei, Zhu, Wang. Lin Jing, Zhang Wu Zhi, Lei,
"Ming Fangming, Feng Lei, Bo, Wei."
Zhang, Zhou, Wu, Chen, Zeng, Zhu.
Mingming, Feng Lei, Bo, Wei.
Ta.
A handsome man.
Look at him.
Bo Wangyang.
Mengfang Mengchao Feng Lei Bo
and handsome.
Zhou Xing Su.
Mingming, Feng Lei, Bo, Wei.
Congcong Chaobo Wangyang.
Weicong Chaoyang
Liu.
Mingming Chaofeng Lei Bowei.
Luo Wu.
The Book after the Empress of Yun.
King of Zhou, Zhou, Zhou, Chen, Wei, Duke Zhu.
Zhang, Zhou, Chao, Zhou, Zeng, De
A handsome man.
Northern Wai Cong Superwave Wangyang
Zhou Xing Susun.
Mingming, Fenglei Bowei.
Jun.
Bei Wei, Cong, Chao, Wang, Yang.
Ming, Feng Lei, Bo, Wei.
Dongjing Jun is handsome.
Liu Yuan, Li, Jiang, Luo Wu.
Beijing Weicong Superwave Wangyang
Hanlin Qiang.
Maomao
A handsome man.
Northern Wai Cong, super wave Wangyang.
Sun...Sun...Sun...
Hanlin Qiang.
Tan Maomao.
Beiwei Congcong Superwave Wangyang
Han Lin Qiang.
Jong Yoon Tiger
Deok.
Jun.
Beiwei Congcong Superwave Wangyang
De.
Hanlin Qiang.
Qin Juliang.
Cui Shao.
Flower.
Beiwei Congcong Superwave Wangyang
Dong Kyung Joon is handsome
Jianjian.
Guo Zhou Xing Susun.
Dongjing.
Zhou Xing, Su, Sun,
Sun...
Guo Zhou.
North.
Shao, Sun,
A handsome man.
Northern Wai Cong, super wave Wangyang.
Zhang, Shao, and Cui.
Zheng Jia, Jie Qing Jun.
Li.
Han Lin Qiang.
Yujian Xian Zheng Lei Jie Qing Jin
Guo, Zhou, Xing, Sun,
Li Duan, Shao, Wang, Sun, Cui.
Hanlin Qiang.
Maomao
Heungwoo Jian Xian Zheng Jie Qing Jin
Beijing Weicong Chaobo Wangyang
Cao, Li, Duan, Zhang, Wang, Sun, Cui Shao.
Hanlin Qiang.
Grass, Maomao.
Yuanxing.
Yuanxing, Yuanxing, Yuanxian, Jianxian, Jia, Jie, Qing, Qing, Qing.
Yuan...
Duan, Zhang.
Hengwoo Jian Xian Zheng Jie Qing Jin
Wang Cao, Li, Duan, Zhang, Wang, Sun, Cui Shao.
Zhou...
Do it.
Wuzhou.
Zhenshu Shitong.
Cao, Li, Duan, Shao, Wang, Sun, Cui Shao.
Niu, Li, Li, Zhou.
Yuanxing Wuxian Zhengjie Qingjun
Li Feng, Niu, Li Wuzhou.
Tengzhen Scholars, Guangzhou.
Meng Jian.
Yuanxing and Yunyin are the best.
The heir of Book of Deteng Zhenshu, Quchuan,
Royal Cao, Li, Duan, Zhang, Wang, Sun, Cui.
Yuanxing, Yuanxing, Wuxian, Zheng, Lei, Jie, Qing, Jin.
Zhou, Chen, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Jiaxing was the grandson of Jiaxi.
Poison.
Kun Seal Ji.
A long long and thick coin run to Ipo first.
The city of Yongwei
Tengzhen Scholar, Shi Tong.
Zhao, Xiong, Wei, Hou, Meng, Di, De. Zhen, Sheng, Shi, Tong, Yan.
Tian Yongwei's Home City, Fude Tengzhen, Scholar Shitong.
Li Wuzhou
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's city, Fude Tengzhen, the world of literature.
The tree has a clear conscience.
Hang, Xiao, Yongwei, Zizi, Home, City, Rich. "Virtuous Teng Zhen Zhen Shu Shi Tong."
Li Wuzhou
Yuan Zheng.
ZhuChong.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's City, Fude Tengzhen
Zhao Xiong, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Li.
Rain spring far away from Junshu.
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Try it.
Aeronautics Yongwei's Home City Fude Tengzhen
Anti Dizhen.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's city, FudeTeng.
Junshu, Yuan Zheng, Kun Kun Ji, Lun.
Open!
Aeronautics Yongwei Science City.
Hang Di Zhen.
Zhao Xiong, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Industrial competition Qihong.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's City FudeTeng
Meng Xu, Chen, Xiao, Wei, Xin.
Sun Meng, Xu, Chen Xiaoxian, Cheng.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi Home
Rain Spring, always the handsome tree.
"The Peace of the Pearl" and "Dizhen".
Xi, Zhao, Xiong, Zhen, Hou, Meng, Zhang, De. Teng Zhen Zhen Zhen Shu Shi Tong Yi Zhou
The fragrance is crystal.
Slide.
The young ladies of Qitan City run to Ivan first.
The fragrance is crystal and the jade is beautiful.
Xi, Zhao, Xiong, Fog, Chen, Chen, Chen, Hua. Win, book, world, luxury, Yi, Zhou
The fragrance is crystal
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's City Fude Tengzhen
Slide, Sun, Meng, De, Chen, Xiao, Xin, Ben.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's city, Fude Tengzhen, the world of literature.
Qihong of Zhijiang Championships.
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Slide.
Aeronautics Yongwei Zizi's City, Fude Tengzhen, Shi Tong.
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Slide, Sun, Meng, Xu, Chen, Xiao, Sen. Li...
Aeronautics Yongwei Zi Home City, Fude Tengzhen, Scholar Shitong
Famous.
Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Zhang, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Li, Zhou.
Slide.
"The Virtuous Mountains" and "Tizhen".
"The Peace of the Pearl" and "Tizhen".
Jiaoqiang.
Sexy.
Jang Oh!
Ren.
Hong Lei, Wen Yan, Ou Jing Ou, Jiaoqiang,
Zhijiang Preliminaries
Slide, Sun, Meng, Xu, Chen, Xiao, Jin. Li...
I owe Honglei Wenyan Ou Jing Ou Jiaoqiang
Slide, Sun, Meng, Xu, Chen, Xiao, Wang, Jin. Li
Jaws change into Yunya, Yongya is beautiful.
Wang Zou, Li Xiu, Xu, Zhang Wu!
Ou Honglei, Wenyan, Ou Jing, Ou Jiaoqiang.
Ou Honglei, Wen Yan, Ou Jing Ou, Jiaoqiang.
Ou Honglei, Wen Yan, Ou Jing.
Ou Honglei, Wenyan, Ou Jing Ou, Jiaoqiang.
King Xu, Zhang Wu, pass.
Nori.
Chen Qian.
Zhuo Qiu W Chen Qian
and broad-minded.
Ou Honglei, Wenyan, Ou Jing, Ou Jiaoqiang.
The master is broad and broad.
I, Xiang, Ding, no.
E Qihong is broad and broad.
E is in Wan.
W is higher than Han Tak Chow and Chen Qian
Ou Honglei, Wenyan, Ou Jing, Award Jiaoqiang.
But I am in the wild
Daxiu, Wang Zou, Li Xiu, Xu, Zhang Wu.
Mei Han
"Xiang Ding, no, ran, i" Nori.
Change.
Ou Honglei, Wen Yan, Ou Jing Ou, Qiang, i.
Daxiu will be Wang Zou, Li Xiu, Xu, Zhang Wu.
E Qihong is broad and broad.
W is higher than Han Tak Chow and Chen Qian
Name
Da, ba, Yi, Yang, Yun, water. Teeth Yan Jiao Yan
W is higher than Han Tak Chow and Chen Qian
The shoulders are broad and broad
W
E Xiang.
Hand.
Moon Ah Chen W Wang
Bailezhu Bridge Club.
E Qihong is broad and broad.
L bridge Club.
W is higher than Han Tak Chow
But Chen W
Spring and Bamboo E.
Yang Lei.
One, Sho.
Yi Yang Lei.
Nan, Han, Han, Hong, Autumn E.
Little Hu Ah Chen
W is higher than Han Tak Chow and Chen Qian
Sun E
"Social Yi Yang Lei."
"
Little Hu Ji
XiW is small.
is higher than Han Zhuo Qiu and Chen Qian.
E Qihong is broad and broad.
W is higher than Han Zhuo Qiu and Chen Qian.
E Qi-hong, Zhu Kuan-kuan is broad and Ming-e is in the world.
Zhi E
Yang Lei.
One Yanglei.
XiW, Little Wang, Hu, Chen, and WWang Xi.
The social EP Chow Chun Da E Bamboo
Chen
Hello.
XiW is small.
Talk.
Tao Tingdong.
Yao, Ma, Chen, De.
He, Gu, Xiang, Yao, Ma, Gao, Chen, Chen.
Jun.
[Xiao Qing] [Chen Xing Bridge's sexual committee]
Yu.
Fan, Mei, Xiao.
Dai, Xue, Sheng, Liang, He, Gu, Yao. Yao...
Chu Jiang Junhong
Shi Hui Jie Yu Yan Ting Dong Gong
Wealth, Xiao, Jian, Yue, Fan, Xiao, Chu, Jiang
Changzhu wandering around Ge Hong, Wu, Yang, Yang, Yan, Wu, Liang, Wu, Liang Wen, Gu, Zhu, Yaoyao.
"Plum Tong is a good match for German and Wai Jie Jia."
Yes, Ci, Xia, Jian.
Learn from Chu, Jiang Jun, Hong Congjun.
Mei Tong, Yu, Jie Lan.
Whale.
Yu Fei.
Wu Yang, Yan, Wu, Liang Wen, He, Zhu Yao, Ma Gao, Chen You.
Cixia Jian.
It's Lei, Xiaohai, Xiaoyue, Xiaoyue, Xiaoyue, Xiaochu, Xiaojun, Hong Congjun, Fang Yuyan, Mengmeng.
Ge Hong Dai Wu Yang Sheng De Liang, Wen, He, chef, chef Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen Kitchen
Chen Zhang Zhu
Yu Fei.
Wang Huang Wang Zhu Chen Zhang Zhu, Hu Yu, Ge Hong, Wu, Yang, Yan, Wu.
The screen starts first.
Worong and Wosang
I'll teach you a lesson!