♪The rift in time and space
is deftly manipulated♪
♪Dark clouds roil,
malice lurking and waiting♪
♪I roar, stirring a wild tempest
on the ground♪
♪No need for praise,
courage is my nature♪
♪Unable to endure
the deafening cries for help♪
♪Then don't look back.
I'll bring this battle to an end♪
♪I will not be a caged animal♪
♪Passive waiting is not my way♪
♪Awakened from slumber,
the sealed power ignites♪
♪With the Divine Warrior's Physique,
I preserve justice's fate♪
♪Don't be too alarmed.
I have made my entrance♪
♪Step aside willingly.
Watch as I address the chaos of battle♪
♪In youth, we're wild and free,
even venturing where dragons be♪
♪This battle's not in vain,
for the light that I maintain♪
[Hero Is Back]
[Adapted from Xu Chen's comic:
Rakshasa Street]
[Episode 4]
Wuxin?
[Tang Wuxin]
That's really moving, Cao Yanbing.
You are about to die,
yet someone come out to protect you.
Now that you're here,
prepare
to be destroyed.
Twelve Death-Bringer Blades.
Well, let's see.
Wuxin!
Fighting a former
Guardian Primordial Spirit like you
is indeed fun.
But still, you are down
and I'm standing.
Ethereal Fire Monarch.
Wuxin.
Fighting a fool like you
is more fun.
Yama's Cannon.
Bright Palm.
Demonic aura.
Is the seal broken?
No.
I screwed up.
I let out the Demonic aura
Patriarch sealed.
Patriarch will never forgive me.
Demonic Form.
He's taking on a Demonic Form.
No.
Don't...
It feels good to be free.
No.
I failed.
I'm back.
How did I let the Demonic aura out?
Patriarch...
Patriarch will never forgive me.
Little one,
long time no see.
Where are you, Patriarch?
Come and rescue me.
I... I don't want the beads.
I'll give you the beads back.
I beg you to go back.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
I know I was wrong.
Little one,
go see your Patriarch.
If you spot the escapee,
take him down at once.
- Yes, Sir.
Cao Yanbing?
He came out.
Is the Prison Guardian...?
Wuxin.
Do you remember we once
found a drug
named Celestial Revival?
It can activate
the maximum potential of the user,
granting him great strength,
but at the price
of using up
all his remaining life.
I wonder
where I put it.
You have it.
Give it to me.
Tang Wuxin,
just give it to me.
I won't use it
unless
I have no other choice.
For example,
when Cao Yanbing
is in grave danger
and I have no other way to save him.
If
I ever
had to drink poison,
I wouldn't hesitate.
Take him.
Yes.
Wuxin.
Wuxin,
wake up.
Wake up.
Wuxin.
[We are in the Human Realm now]
[Hall of Heroes won't]
[send anyone here]
I'm sorry, Wuxin.
It should have been me
bringing you out.
In the end,
I needed you to save me.
It's my fault.
[You've grown up]
[I am very happy]
[I saved you willingly]
[As long as you live,
there is hope for Master]
That's all right.
I'll take you back
to Rakshasa Street to heal.
Come on.
Don't worry.
Even if
your Primordial Spirit Power is gone,
there will be a way to fix it.
I won't let you stay here
and vanish.
I'm taking you back right now.
[Promise me]
[You will rescue your mother]
[She is at...]
Where is my mother?
Where is she?
Where?
[Luhua Ancient Tower]
Lu
Hua
Ancient
Tower.
Where is this Luhua Ancient Tower?
Wuxin?
Wuxin.
That means hello?
You learned this.
Now you can say hello to Wuxin.
When you learn a little more,
you can talk to him.
Why can't Tang Wuxin
speak?
Nothing special.
Once a Guardian Primordial Spirit
is formed,
he is no longer in our control.
Although Wuxin looks like
a bit aloof,
he is a good man.
I grew up
with him protecting me.
In a way,
he's even more reliable than a family.
More reliable than a family?
Why is that?
Because the relationship
between a Guardian Primordial Spirit
and his master
is very pure and noble.
Unless the master is dead
or there are other
very special reasons,
a Guardian Primordial Spirit
will always stand by
and protect the master.
Kid,
I can't
protect you forever.
If one day
I'm gone,
I hope
Wuxin can protect you.
Wuxin.
Rest assured.
I promise you.
Xia...
Xia Ling.
This is a work note.
[Hanxian Street]
Hanxian Street.
Dad was not only a Spirit-hosted Human,
but also a Spiritual Guardian.
Hanxian Street
was the one in his charge.
[Hanxian]
[Guardian]
What a special medal!
Can I have it?
No.
Then why did you take it out?
This necklace
can't be given to anyone.
But I can make
something else for you.
I promise you'll like it.
Fine.
Ling.
It's amazing.
It is so beautiful.
Dad, can you do magic tricks?
What I did was magic itself.
Because I'm
from the world of magic.
World of magic.
Did he mean Spiritual Crossroads?
General,
all the escaped prisoners
have been captured,
except...
Except what?
Except for the four in cell zero.
The former Hall of Heroes masters.
The other prisoners don't matter.
It's those four that matter.
I can't believe
this happened on my watch.
I should have
kept more men.
Now I wouldn't be so short in men
that this happened.
Forget it.
Cao Yanbing doesn't matter.
If I can't get those four back,
there will be consequences.
On my orders,
widen the search area.
I want everyone to look for them.
As for Cao Yanbing,
re-issue the arrest warrant.
Wait until Madam gets back first.
- Okay.
Chief.
Why are you in such a hurry?
It's Cao Yanbing.
He escaped from the Shadowbound Prison.
Are you sure?
Hall of Heroes
has issued his arrest warrant.
He did escape.
Not only did he escape,
but he also killed the Prison Guardian
and heavily damaged the defenders.
Cao Yanbing did not disappoint me.
He survived this,
which proves he deserves
to be part of my plan.
From now on,
he's a pawn
completely controlled
by your hand.
Kid.
Who is it?
Who am I?
That's a good question.
Let's talk about
who you are first.
Why do I need
to tell you my identity?
Looks like you not only
have the Divine Warrior's Physique,
but you also have a temper.
Fine.
I like it.
Who on earth are you?
How do you know
I have the Divine Warrior's Physique?
Of course, I know.
If it's not the case,
how could I have a form?
Why do you talk so much?
Come out if you can.
Let's have a good fight.
Let me out of here afterward.
I have to find
Luhua Ancient Tower.
You're going to Luhua Ancient Tower?
So what?
Do you know where it is?
Nice.
Very nice.
Perfect.
So noisy.
What's wrong with you?
Shut up.
Wake up, Cao Yanbing.
Cao Yanbing.
Xia Ling?
I remember your name now.
We'll meet again soon.
Sins bound to the nether realms,
enshrouded by the clouds of incense.
Upon the lotus of serenity and wisdom,
the divine spirit
ascends to eternal peace.
Sins bound to the nether realms,
enshrouded by the clouds of incense.
Upon the lotus of serenity and wisdom...
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
Xia Ling.
What happened to me?
I want to ask you the same thing.
I was at home
when I received
your update letter.
When we arrived,
you were lying in the alley alone.
What was going on?
I only remember
that someone
kept talking to me.
General Cao,
by the time we got there,
you were covered
with a thick black aura.
Your Primordial Spirit Power
was unsettled
and was attacking your viscera.
All look like
symptoms when your Primordial Spirit is
attacked by Demonic aura.
Thus,
just now I used
my master's
Sevenfold Soul-Resonance Bell
which has the power to ease the mind
and remove demons.
Now it seems the demonic nature
has been suppressed by the bell.
However,
it also proves your internal injuries
were caused by the demonic nature.
General Cao,
did you come into contact
with any demonic creatures recently?
Demonic aura?
I remember
back in the Shadowbound Prison,
the Prison Guardian attacked me.
Then I woke up.
[Luhua Ancient Tower]
Wuxin saved me.
Wuxin.
Li Xuanyuan,
come back first.
Can you tell me
what happened?
We're teammates.
I'm really worried about you.
I'm going back to Spiritual Crossroads
to find Luhua Ancient Tower.
Luhua Ancient Tower?
Is this what you mean?
Luhua Ancient Tower.
[Luhua Ancient Tower]
It actually exists.
Whose notebook is this?
It's complicated.
I need to sort things out
before I tell you.
My last three days
were quite complicated as well.
Shadowbound Prison.
Grave robbing.
Prison Guardian.
Hanxian Street.
Tang Wuxin.
Your father was a Spiritual Guardian.
Who would have thought
that an office worker
and a delivery guy
went through these things
in the last three days?
We are a miserable couple.
Fellows in distress?
Your father was a Spiritual Guardian.
My mother was also a Spiritual Guardian.
They all had something to do
with the Luhua Ancient Tower.
This can't be a coincidence.
By the way,
among your father's relics,
is there a General's Box?
What is a General's Box?
A General's Box
is a box that Spiritual Guardians use
to store information.
Only the General's Chain
can open it.
I suppose
your father
left key information
about Luhua Ancient Tower in it.
Is this what you're talking about?
Yes, that's it.
And the General's Chain?
I forgot to tell you.
When my dad's grave was robbed,
nothing went missing
except a necklace.
According to your words,
that must be the General's Chain.
Without the General's Chain,
we can't open the box.
But it was lost
before we knew it.
Where are we supposed to find it?
Not necessarily.
A General's Chain symbolizes
a Spiritual Guardian's
identity and qualification.
One street, one chain.
Whoever stole
your father's chain
must have something
to do with Hanxian Street.
Searching for it on Hanxian Street
is our best solution.
Xia Ling,
do you trust me?
Of course.
Then give me this box.
I will go to Hanxian Street
to search for the General's Chain.
No.
Because I'm coming, too.
Xia Ling,
hear me out.
This is not as simple as you think.
Whoever stole
the chain
must be a big deal
on Hanxian Street.
To take it back,
I probably need to risk my life.
Cao Yanbing.
It is my dad's box.
And it is
also my dad's chain.
And Hanxian Street
was the place where my dad died
trying to protect.
This time,
I must do it myself.
Besides,
aren't we partners?
If I were to risk my life,
would you rest assured
and wait for me in the Human Realm?
Of course, I wouldn't.
But...
No buts.
I know.
You think I've started a brand new life
with a new job
in the Human Realm,
and shouldn't get involved
in the fray of Spiritual Crossroads.
But have you ever thought
that it isn't the life
I truly desire?
Ever since I know
that I am a Spirit-hosted Human,
I feel like
my life isn't just about this.
It must have been blessed
with a mission.
And now,
I found out
that my father was a Spiritual Guardian.
Mysteries
are waiting for me to solve.
I have to go this time.
You and I together,
just like before.
Just like before.
But now what's crucial
is to find out
where the entrance
to Hanxian Street is.
That's not hard.
You told me once
that your father worked
at a bar in town.
Spiritual Guardians like us
who have a job
in the Human Realm
tend to work
near the entrance
to the street.
Then let's go there
and start searching.
That should do.
We'll leave early tomorrow morning.
Okay.
We'll leave first thing in the morning.
Go to bed early.
- Good night.
This hotel
only has
this one last room.
We'll be fine for this one night,
won't we?
It's not awkward, is it?
Yes, it is.
We are partners.
It won't be awkward.
Good night.
Uhh...
Gladly it's a standard room.
Two beds.
Just one for each.
It won't matter
even if there's just one bed.
One bed...
One bed might
be inappropriate.
Don't be so picky.
When I traveled with my classmates,
five of us shared one room.
Thank you,
Xia Ling.
♪Listen to the heartworm of desire♪
♪Gnawing away at thoughts♪
♪Behold the giant's world♪
♪Quaking and slowly tilting♪
♪We stride through thick smoke♪
♪Fearless in the face of stormy seas♪
♪Pressing on barefoot♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪
♪I'll never be alone♪
♪Life is like falling leaves♪
♪Having last words to recover♪
♪With my veiled eyes♪
♪To glimpse the hidden perils♪
♪On the edge of fate's blade♪
♪Facing the darkest abyss♪
♪Daring to leap forward♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I will never♪
♪My fire must blaze fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪