♪The rift in time and space
is deftly manipulated♪
♪Dark clouds roil,
malice lurking and waiting♪
♪I roar, stirring a wild tempest
on the ground♪
♪No need for praise,
courage is my nature♪
♪Unable to endure
the deafening cries for help♪
♪Then don't look back.
I'll bring this battle to an end♪
♪I will not be a caged animal♪
♪Passive waiting is not my way♪
♪Awakened from slumber,
the sealed power ignites♪
♪With the Divine Warrior's Physique,
I preserve justice's fate♪
♪Don't be too alarmed.
I have made my entrance♪
♪Step aside willingly.
Watch as I address the chaos of battle♪
♪In youth, we're wild and free,
even venturing where dragons be♪
♪This battle's not in vain,
for the light that I maintain♪
[Hero Is Back]
[Adapted from Xu Chen's comic:
Rakshasa Street]
[Episode 10]
[Lingfeng Street]
You've got to be joking.
The village we just saw
had a few hundred households,
yet this place has such a shabby
and worn-out gate.
How can the folks on Lingfeng Street
be living in such poverty?
It's not that they're poor.
It's that they're weak.
This place is on the outskirts
of Spiritual Crossroads,
surrounded by steep mountains,
making it very isolated.
Even the Hall of Heroes
and the Border Domain
can't be bothered with it,
so Malevolent Beings often show up here.
Plus, the people here
have weak Primordial Spirit Power,
making it hard for them
to fend off attacks,
which is why it looks so rundown.
Beiluo,
you seem to know a lot.
Cao Yanbing told me
that there was something
going on with you.
Is that really true?
Most people from Spiritual Crossroads
don't know much about Lingfeng Street.
If it weren't for the fact
that I came here years ago
looking for Shui,
I wouldn't be able to explain it either.
I don't think any of that matters.
What do you mean?
Haven't you noticed?
Looking around,
it's just the three of us here.
The gates are wide open
with no one guarding them,
and there's not a single person
in sight on the street.
Hello?
Is anyone here?
Anyone?
This is the central area
of Lingfeng Street.
It seems Lingfeng Street
is not so simple.
Yeah,
there's no one here at all.
There must be something suspicious
going on.
We can't just keep
looking around slowly.
Let's head straight
to the General's Mansion
and see their Spiritual Guardian.
[General's Mansion]
This is the place.
Let's go.
Is this the residence
of Lingfeng Street's Spiritual Guardian?
That's right.
I stayed here
when I visited before.
It's huge.
Miss.
Miss?
This melody sounds strange.
Members of the Wind-Treading Clan
are adept at using traps.
Please be cautious.
Beiluo,
look at this incense.
There's still quite a bit left.
Xia Ling.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What about you, Beiluo?
I'm all right.
Cao Yanbing, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Freeze!
You...
Who are you people?
I was about to ask the same question.
The soldiers' outfits suggest
they are members
of the Wind-Treading Clan.
Since you
are from the Wind-Treading Clan,
can you tell me
what this trap is for
and what the Spirit-Locking Platform
is all about?
Shut up.
What right do you have
to ask questions here?
Lingyu.
Do you know her?
General.
We've captured the wrong people.
These three
accidentally triggered the trap
we set for Fire-Eater King.
General?
General Yan,
I just arrived at Lingfeng Street today
with two friends,
but we accidentally fell into the trap.
Audacious intruders,
you ruined my trap
and disrupted my plans.
Beiluo,
what's going on?
Do you know her or not?
Lingyu,
don't you recognize me?
I'm Beiluo,
Beiluo Shimen.
Stop pretending to be close to me.
I've never met
any of you before.
Be honest and tell me
your true purpose
for coming to Lingfeng Street.
Forget it.
She doesn't want to admit
that she knows you.
No matter how much you argue,
it won't help.
However,
this means they don't know me either.
It seems the bounty notice
from the Hall of Heroes
hasn't reached Lingfeng Street yet,
which is a relief.
General,
we three have no ill intentions.
We came to Lingfeng Street
only to find
the legendary
Luhua Ancient Tower.
Lock them up!
Wait.
What's the meaning of this?
We haven't even had a chance
to talk properly,
and you've already put us in chains?
Stop whining.
We've seen plenty of people like you
who don't know their place
and try to break
into the Luhua Ancient Tower
in search of treasure.
Mother,
let's not worry
about these people for now.
The immediate priority
is to deal with the Fire-Eater King.
Lang Da,
quickly get the traps back in place.
Close it.
Yes, sir.
Who is this Fire-Eater King
they're talking about?
It should be a long-standing feud.
A long-standing feud?
It looks like we've been caught up
in the conflict
between the two clans.
That's possible.
They look terrified
at the mention of the guy,
so they probably can't defeat him.
Mother,
just restoring the traps
isn't enough.
If someone accidentally
triggers them again
like earlier,
it could cause trouble.
We need to send another person
to lure the Fire-Eater King over.
Lang Da,
fetch me the Blaze Jade.
Go get it now.
What is Blaze Jade?
Blaze Jade is a highly sought-after
and expensive elixir
on the black market these days.
That's right,
consuming it
can significantly boost
the Primordial Spirit Power
of Spirit-hosted Humans.
Mother.
General, here's the Blaze Jade
you requested.
Give it to me.
Young General.
Young General!
Yan Ruofu,
what are you doing?
If we're going
to take on the Fire-Eater King,
both of us can go.
Have you lost your mind?
Stop her from going.
Mother,
why can't you
face reality?
Your internal injuries have recurred,
and now I've consumed the Blaze Jade.
I have a better chance of winning
than you.
Your words don't make any difference.
Hurry and take her away.
I dare you to do that!
Listen up, everyone.
Today,
I must go
because I am the guide
the Fire-Eater King
is looking for.
I am currently the only guide
on Lingfeng Street.
Because I am the guide,
even if I can't defeat
the Fire-Eater King,
he won't kill me.
Once the Fire-Eater King has the guide,
he won't trouble us
on Lingfeng Street anymore.
Therefore,
it's enough for me
to go alone
for this battle.
How naive.
The Fire-Eater King has coveted
Lingfeng Street for years.
A mere guide
is just an excuse.
But Mother...
Hold on a moment.
General.
If you're going to fight,
I can help out.
You will help me?
Upon further thought,
your proposal
is also a feasible one.
I allow you to go and fight
the Fire-Eater King.
Guide him to the trap swiftly.
Just remember
not to be reckless.
Yes.
I'll go capture him now and show you.
Why are you leaving?
I meant it when I said
that I was willing to help.
Take these three away
and put them in the dungeon.
Didn't you hear
what I just said?
I said I could help you.
Do you understand Mandarin or not?
Get in.
Move!
What are you looking at?
Just
Beilu,
confess honestly.
Have you done anything
to offend that female general?
You are being overly suspicious,
It's all baseless.
That's impossible.
Apart from this,
I can't think of any reason
why my overtures
were rejected.
You're a stranger.
It's reasonable for her
to question your motives,
doubt your abilities,
and ignore you.
It's reasonable for her to ignore me.
Is it reasonable to ignore you though?
I am a stranger.
But you are not.
Enough.
You don't need to say anything.
Xia Ling.
Intuitive Judgment.
No.
There's no need
for intuitive judgment at all.
Beiluo's expression clearly displays
the term 'guilt-ridden.'
Even Xia Ling could see it.
Beiluo,
just admit it honestly.
Tell me.
Did you beat her up?
Beat her up?
Do you think you're a boxer?
This is clearly an unforgettable,
lingering,
and hard-to-move-on love story.
Is love
the only story
in the world?
Use a little imagination, will you?
It's not that I lack imagination.
It's that you're immune to love
and lack insight.
That's why I can draw my sword quickly
and fire accurately.
You actually think that's something
you could brag about?
You've been single all your life.
As if you
are not the same.
Beiluo.
Enough.
You two can stop guessing.
Actually, there's nothing
between her and me.
- That's impossible.
Fine,
since you're so curious,
I don't mind telling you.
But it's not as exciting
as you think.
It's just a simple, ordinary story.
Eight years ago,
I came near Lingfeng Street
looking for Shui
and met Yan Tianyue,
the Spiritual Guardian here,
and his sister Yan Lingyu.
Tianyue,
you're finally back.
[Yan Tianyue]
Where have you been?
Didn't you say
you were only going out for a few days
to buy supplies?
How did you end up being gone
for more than half a month?
I couldn't even get in touch with you
through the update letters.
Do you know how worried everyone was?
Yu, it's my fault.
I lost the update letters.
I'll apologize to you later.
Today, we have a guest at home.
A guest?
Come here, Beiluo.
Let me introduce you to each other.
This is my younger sister, Lingyu.
This is Beiluo Shimen,
a good friend I made
on this trip.
Tianyue,
is it because of this person
that you've delayed so long
out there?
Actually...
What is his background and identity?
Why is he near
our Lingfeng Street?
Are you aware of all this?
Does he have any ill intentions
or hidden agenda?
You can't just
casually bring someone back like this.
Tianyue,
she's right.
I shouldn't have just shown up
like this.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Don't.
Please wait.
Yu,
he came to look for his daughter.
Look for his daughter?
Raise your sword a bit higher.
Your movements need to be precise
and swift.
You must have
a surge of energy inside you.
Your thrusts should be effective
and your momentum consistent.
Don't be so limp, okay?
Try again.
Stop.
Squat lower.
What's the matter?
Why can't you
even hold the sword steady?
Didn't I tell you to practice
with more effort?
I practice every day
and put a lot of effort into it.
That means you're still
not putting in enough effort.
As a Spirit-hosted Human,
you still can't summon
your Guardian Primordial Spirit.
If you don't continue to work hard
and strengthen your abilities,
how will you survive
on Rakshasa Street in the future?
Not this again.
It's always the same line,
and it's so irritating.
I'm not going to practice anymore.
Come back.
Stop bothering me.
I know you're the guest
brought back by my uncle,
but I'm in a bad mood
right now.
I thought the Tanghulu
were meant for me.
Why are you eating it?
It was originally for you,
but I changed my mind.
I want to show you
something more interesting.
Is that okay?
What is it?
That's so impressive!
That was nothing.
I was able to do it
even before I had
the Guardian Primordial Spirit.
You could do that
without having
the Guardian Primordial Spirit?
In Spiritual Crossroads,
having
a powerful Guardian Primordial Spirit
is definitely advantageous.
However, the strength
of the Spirit-hosted Humans
is also important.
Only when you become stronger
will your Guardian Primordial Spirit
grow stronger.
Do you understand?
Then I must become stronger.
You can definitely do it.
Just like that,
I stayed on Lingfeng Street
for over a month,
and there was still no clue about Shui,
so I decided
to leave Lingfeng Street.
Who is it?
Lingyu.
Beiluo,
do you really intend
to leave tomorrow,
or could you extend your stay a bit?
Previously, I came to Lingfeng Street
with Tianyue
simply to find my daughter.
Since she's not here,
I think I should leave.
Actually,
there are some things
I've never told you.
The past cannot be held onto,
and those who have gone
cannot be pursued.
You should think more
about yourself
and not cling to the past.
Maybe
starting a new chapter
in life
would be better.
My daughter means everything to me.
I will never abandon her.
Since that day,
I haven't returned here
or seen Yan Lingyu.
I'm also unsure
how she became
the Spiritual Guardian
of Lingfeng Street.
Profound and reserved,
with a tacit understanding.
That's how adult relationships are.
Cao Yanbing, I told you.
This must be a love story.
Beiluo.
I originally wanted to learn more
about Beiluo's connection
with the Wind-Treading Clan,
but the story turned out to be so long.
If I don't leave now,
I'll miss out on important matters.
Where will the Young General go
to fight the Fire-Eater King?
The gates.
Aren't you supposed
to be in the dungeon?
How come you're here?
Young General, don't get me wrong.
It's me.
We've met each other
in the dungeon earlier.
I'm Cao Yanbing.
I'm not planning to flee.
I don't care who you are.
I'm warning you.
Don't try anything funny,
or I'll take your life.
Young General,
let's talk this over calmly.
Forget everything else.
I'll help you deal
with the Fire-Eater King
if you can be my guide.
How does that sound?
If I go fight the Fire-Eater King now,
Lingfeng Street will be just fine.
If I agree to help you,
how is it different from agreeing
to help the Fire-Eater King?
The difference is huge.
First of all,
I'm a hundred times better
than the Fire-Eater King
in terms of character,
I won't use Lingfeng Street
as leverage against you.
I'll discuss things with you properly.
If you have concerns, I'll address them.
If you have conditions, I'll meet them.
If all else fails, I'll beg you
until you agree.
Also,
I heard you'd drink something
called Blaze Jade,
which indicates you lack confidence
in your own strength.
But I'm different.
My 优酷剧集英语 setting is powerful,
and I have a much better chance
of winning than you.
I'm telling you this to help you.
Bah!
You can't even avoid
my Spirit-Locking Chain
and you say you want to help me?
You should first assess
your own capabilities.
Cao Yanbing
broke the door lock
without saying a word to us
and just ran off alone.
Isn't that too much?
Cao Yanbing is most likely
going to look for Yan Ruofu.
I never expected
that Yan Ruofu
would actually be the guide.
The Yan Ruofu you mentioned,
she's the Young General, right?
Since we don't have
much to do here,
why don't we go and help?
Sure.
Let's go.
What are you up to?
Thinking of escaping?
One of you is missing.
Where is he?
Has he already escaped?
General,
I can explain.
We came to Lingfeng Street
to find the guide
for entering the Luhua Ancient Tower.
My friend
learned that the Young General
is the guide,
so
he should be heading over
to protect her now.
You can rest assured.
General?
Young General?
From the way you speak,
it seems like you're blaming me
for not recognizing you earlier.
So you mean
you've recognized me now, General?
Otherwise,
why would I have come here alone,
Beiluo?
So you've already
recognized me earlier.
I thought you...
You thought
that even though I clearly
recognized you,
I pretended not to know you,
right?
Why would I think like that?
After all, we've been apart
for eight years.
It's normal for our appearances
to change a bit.
Not recognizing each other upon meeting
isn't strange.
All right,
since the misunderstanding
between us
is cleared up,
I feel
comfortable asking you
for help now.
The Fire-Eater King
will arrive soon,
and I know
Ruofu won't stand a chance
against him,
so
I'd like to ask you to help her.
Of course,
my friend
should already be on his way.
That won't do.
I don't know that friend of yours.
I don't trust him.
I only trust you.
Lingyu,
stay calm.
Tianyue and I go way back,
and Ruofu is the guide.
Even if you didn't ask,
there's no way
I'd let the Fire-Eater King
cause chaos
in Lingfeng Street.
But
there's something
I've been meaning to ask.
Why haven't I seen
Tianyue today?
And why is everyone
calling you General?
Could it be that something
has happened to him?
Don't overthink it.
My brother's situation is a long story.
Once the Fire-Eater King is dealt with,
I'll explain everything to you.
But for now,
we should focus on handling the enemy,
don't you think?
You're right.
There's no time to waste.
Quickly unlock the handcuffs
on me and Xia Ling,
and we'll go find Ruofu immediately.
No.
I can't release her.
You can't release her?
Why?
I can't release
all three of you.
I'll have to keep one person here
as a hostage.
Hostage?
Yes.
That's right.
Hostage.
Are you sure you are asking me for help?
You are clearly threatening me.
Beiluo,
please don't hold it against me.
This concerns
the safety of Lingfeng Street,
and I need to make sure
nothing goes wrong.
Since I've agreed to help you,
I'll give it my all.
You've chosen to trust me,
so why do something so unnecessary?
Unnecessary, you say?
I would like to think so too.
But the world is dangerous now,
and after eight years apart,
how can I be sure
our hearts
are still the same as before?
Lingyu,
I never thought
you would say something like this.
If I had known,
I would have preferred
that you didn't recognize me.
So you mean
you will no longer help me?
I can help you.
But not like this.
Hold on a moment.
I have an idea.
Considering the imminent threat,
we shouldn't let
our differing opinions on the solution
keep us from working together.
How about
you let me go
and keep Beiluo here
as a hostage instead?
How does that sound?
You?
My Guardian Primordial Spirit
is Li Xuanyuan.
I'm a great fighter.
[Lingfeng Street]
Where is everyone?
Did the entire Wind-Treading Clan
get wiped out?
Yan Lingyu,
your Wind-Treading Clan
hasn't changed a bit.
It's still so afraid of death.
Do you think hiding away
will help you avoid calamity?
Dream on!
What are you doing? Let go of me!
I know
some of you
are watching from somewhere.
So, open your eyes wide
and listen carefully.
Today,
if you don't hand over the guide,
I'll cut off his head.
Stay put.
And hang it on your village gate.
Don't kill me.
How come it's still locked?
Seriously?
I will only count to three.
One.
Don't kill me.
Two.
Stop!
Let Elder Mei go.
I'll fight with you.
I was wondering who it was.
Isn't this the Young General
in her twenties who still can't summon
a Guardian Primordial Spirit?
Are you fighting me
in a flirtatious way?
Cut the nonsense.
Let Elder Mei go,
and I'll leave your body intact.
Young General, you're very amusing.
The Fire-Eater Clan
and the Wind-Treading Clan
are basically neighbors.
I can help your mother
teach you a lesson.
We're family,
so no need to thank me.
Young General, please go back.
You can't defeat him.
Go back now!
You are no match for him.
Elder Mei!
Your hands are pretty soft,
and your legs are decent too.
I'm done with this.
With your half-baked skills,
you're just like the Wind-Treading Clan
who's only fit to be a timid coward.
You're just a bandit.
You have no standing
to judge our Wind-Treading Clan.
I'm a bandit?
Back when the Malevolent Beings
invaded Lingfeng Street,
it was our Fire-Eater Clan
that fought at the front.
You Wind-Treading Clan
only dared to hide
behind us and survive.
You've developed well over the years,
and I'm just reclaiming
what originally belonged to me.
Is that wrong?
It's mere sophistry.
It was clearly my mother
who defended Lingfeng Street to the end.
Sophistry?
I didn't even unsheathe my sword
before I knocked you down.
What right do you have to lecture me?
You're just
your mother's little princess,
and you don't understand the ways
of the Spiritual Crossroads at all.
♪Listen to the heartworm of desire♪
♪Gnawing away at thoughts♪
♪Behold the giant's world♪
♪Quaking and slowly tilting♪
♪We stride through thick smoke♪
♪Fearless in the face of stormy seas♪
♪Pressing on barefoot♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪
♪I'll never be alone♪
♪Life is like falling leaves♪
♪Having no last words to recover♪
♪With my veiled eyes♪
♪To glimpse the hidden perils♪
♪On the edge of fate's blade♪
♪Facing the darkest abyss♪
♪Daring to leap forward♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I will never♪
♪My fire must blaze fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪