♪The rift in time and space
is deftly manipulated♪
♪Dark clouds roil,
malice lurking and waiting♪
♪I roar, stirring a wild tempest
on the ground♪
♪No need for praise,
courage is my nature♪
♪Unable to endure
the deafening cries for help♪
♪Then don't look back.
I'll bring this battle to an end♪
♪I will not be a caged animal♪
♪Passive waiting is not my way♪
♪Awakened from slumber,
the sealed power ignites♪
♪With the Divine Warrior's Physique,
I preserve justice's fate♪
♪Don't be too alarmed.
I have made my entrance♪
♪Step aside willingly.
Watch as I address the chaos of battle♪
♪In youth, we're wild and free,
even venturing where dragons be♪
♪This battle's not in vain,
for the light that I maintain♪
[Hero Is Back]
[Adapted from Xu Chen's comic:
Rakshasa Street]
[Episode 8]
Come.
Dad,
I want that biggest doll.
No problem.
Beiluo.
Can you hear us?
Dad.
Dad,
shoot!
Okay.
Beiluo.
Wake up.
Dad.
You need to wake up, Beiluo.
[Mengquan Pavilion]
Cao Yanbing,
you're finally here.
Li Gucheng,
did you do this
to Beiluo?
You bunch
of sneaky rats,
this is how you've ended up.
What else do I need to do?
All I did was send you
an update letter.
You're indeed a stooge
of the Hall of Heroes.
Such underhanded tactics
are your specialty.
A fugitive who razed a street
and committed countless murders
doesn't deserve
to talk to me about morality.
You know the truth
deep down.
The truth?
Cao Yanbing,
you only escaped Shadowbound Prison
by sheer luck.
Instead of remaining hidden,
you dare to go to the Divine Realm,
Luhua Ancient Tower.
I suppose
you're trying to steal
the Devine Power.
I guess I am right.
I heard about your mother,
Tang Xiaoxiao,
a traitor of the Hall.
A traitor gave birth
to someone just as corrupt.
Your whole family's nothing
but a nest of vermin.
Li Gucheng.
You asked for this.
Yama's Cannon.
Beiluo.
Beiluo, wake up.
Wake up.
Beiluo.
Wake up!
Let me show you
real archery.
Li Guang.
[Li Guang]
Generals,
fight.
Beiluo.
Beiluo, wake up.
I wonder how long you can hold out.
Li Guang,
Starfall Arrow.
I'll help.
Don't hurt my master.
My master is stronger than this.
He won't fall here.
Hold it.
Wake up, Beiluo.
Beiluo.
Cao Yanbing,
what do I do?
Beiluo just won't wake up.
Hit harder.
Higher?
Shui,
is it beautiful here?
Yes.
It's called Bodhi Street.
I became
its Spiritual Guardian.
Now we
can live here
and never separate again.
You're incredible
for keeping your word.
I am thrilled.
Shui,
I've failed you.
That's why you are...
Dad,
why are you saying this suddenly?
Right.
Why am I saying that?
Never mind.
It is fine now.
I like it here very much.
I get to be with you all the time.
However,
I don't want
to just be protected by you.
I want to protect you as well.
No one treats me better than you,
so I'll try to protect you, too.
Shui?
Shui.
Shui!
Dad.
Shui.
- Shui.
- Dad.
Dad.
Look, I just picked these flowers.
It smells amazing. Take a sniff.
Dad.
Beiluo, I'm sorry.
You need to wake up.
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Dad.
It's not working.
I'm about to suffocate him to death.
Stab him.
Dad.
What's wrong? I'm so worried.
Beiluo, I'm sorry.
This is urgent.
I'm so sorry.
I am okay.
You are awake.
Xia Ling.
Cao Yanbing?
What's going on?
No time to explain.
You have to help.
Cao Yanbing,
where do I aim?
The front.
Move.
Let's go now.
Let's go.
Chief,
all is well.
Cao Yanbing has
escaped from the men
of the Hall of Heroes.
Nice.
I've always had faith in you.
Iron Pawn
will succeed as well.
If everything goes well,
his next step
will be heading for Lingfeng Street.
Then let's hope
he finds Lingfeng Street successfully,
and then safely enters
Luhua Ancient Tower.
After all, to obtain
the power in the tower,
it has to be him.
Chief,
if we plan
to get Cao Yanbing
to go to Luhua Ancient Tower,
why don't we
just let them know
where Lingfeng Street is?
I can arrange it now.
No.
Today
we've got his attention.
More actions
might backfire
and make him doubt us.
Besides,
people always value
what they've worked hard for,
whether it's truth or clues.
Let him do his work.
Okay.
Li Gucheng isn't after us, is he?
No.
I saw him trapped
by a sword qi.
I don't think he knows
where we were heading.
A sword qi?
And I felt an aura
of Divine Warrior's Form.
Do you mean
other Spirit-hosted Humans
were helping us?
Not necessarily helping us.
Hall of Heroes has so many enemies.
Maybe they were looking for revenge.
Beiluo.
How's your leg?
I'm sorry.
There was an emergency.
Don't blame me.
Our Commander Men is no ordinary human.
He has super Primordial Spirit Power.
That wound healed already.
You might as well
buy him a pair of pants.
Why do I have to buy him pants?
You told me to stab him.
And you just did what I said?
If I don't listen to you...
Since you and Xia Ling
are fine now,
I'll be on my way.
Beiluo,
we came to Leiquan Street
especially to see you.
To see me?
Why?
It's a long story.
How about we sit down
and talk it over?
That's about it.
We only know that Luhua Ancient Tower
is near Lingfeng Street.
But we don't know
how to get to Lingfeng Street
or where it is.
I see.
Do you have a pen and paper?
I'll draw you
where the entrance
to Lingfeng Street is.
I do.
It's an eyebrow pencil though.
Will this work?
Here.
Thank you, Beiluo.
I knew you were the right guy to go to.
Beiluo,
this Lingfeng Street
seems hard to find.
I need you to come with us.
Beiluo!
Anything else?
Can't I just chat with you
for no reason?
What is wrong with you?
When we parted
in Yulin Street,
you were all right.
It's only been a few months.
Why have you fallen so low?
I was a fool
to think I could reunite
Shui's Primordial Spirit.
Shui's Primordial Spirit?
So this is...
It is a treasure
that collects and saves
fragments of Primordial Spirit,
the Starspirit Bottle.
So it means
Shui can still be saved.
Even more reason to cheer up.
We'll help you save Shui.
I've tried every method said
to be able to gather Primordial Spirit.
They all didn't work.
What's worse,
these methods,
to varying degrees,
damage the Primordial Spirit.
I don't want to try again.
Otherwise,
Shui will be gone
forever.
Just let her stay in the bottle
safely and peacefully.
At least,
she can still be by my side.
My life is over.
Leiquan Street
is where I found
Shui's Primordial Spirit.
Let me just fend
for myself here.
Beiluo.
You're a Spiritual Guardian.
You can be sad.
But not so much
that you give up on yourself like this.
Spiritual Guardian.
On Bodhi Street,
thousands of Border Dwellers
and Shui.
They're all dead.
I'm the only one still alive,
shamelessly.
If I hadn't trusted Nan Yufu,
and allow him to invade,
they wouldn't have been killed.
Fine.
You don't have to go with us.
What's your next move?
Heading back to your temple,
seeking
another one,
or maybe go drink
that Mengquan water again?
I shouldn't have rescued you
if I knew you'd be
such a coward.
Yes.
You should never have rescued me.
Though I only have sheer strength,
I lack the acumen to discern character.
Again and again,
I harmed Shui.
And what did Shui do?
In order to save me,
her primordial spirit
was shot by an arrow.
But she was still smiling at me,
saying she wanted me to live,
and not to be sad.
I, Beiluo Shimen,
don't deserve to be her father.
How should I proceed with my life?
Do you think,
if I could
stop Shi Lingming
from trying to protect me,
I'd allow myself to be
standing here alive
In front of you?
Or if you guys
hadn't forced me to wake up,
how would I be standing here
and listening to your nonsense?
If you think
saving me was wrong,
take my life
right now.
I'll give you a proper thanks.
If you wouldn't kill,
then leave me alone.
I'm going to get some brew.
[Hongbin Restaurant]
Beiluo,
I'm sorry.
I was being too harsh on you.
I failed to think about your feelings.
I
will make amends with brew.
A pot for myself.
[Meng]
No need to apologize.
Leave Leiquan Street.
No one
can really get
what someone else is feeling.
I can't
fully understand your feelings.
But I know mine.
Pain and remorse.
Not for months,
but for ten years.
If I hadn't known
my mother was still alive
and trapped in the Luhua Ancient Tower,
I'm afraid, for my whole life,
I would think I killed her.
But I also remember
what my mom
used to say.
She said
your trust and kindness are right.
It was he who failed you.
Exactly because
I remembered this,
however I regret something after that,
I held back.
I didn't let the pain consume me.
I put all my energy
into becoming stronger.
Strong enough
to be able
to do what my mom said,
never letting it happen again.
My suffering is
nothing.
I have such a
loving mother.
I have to live a good life
to be worthy of her love.
Beiluo.
You said Shui saved you
with her Primordial Spirit shot.
Still, she was smiling at you
telling you not to be sad
and live a good life.
If I had
a daughter like her,
despite my
unbearable pain,
even if the world deemed me
unworthy of life,
I'd strive
to live well,
so Shui may find peace.
All right.
I've said everything I needed to.
Xia Ling and I are going to
look for Luhua Ancient Tower now.
What to do next
is up to you.
Beiluo,
Spiritual Crossroads are so big.
I believe there must be a way
to heal Shui's Primordial Spirit.
Don't ever give up.
Also don't forget
you have two partners.
You can always count on us.
Please wait, the two of you.
I think I heard you talking
about Luhua Ancient Tower.
Did you say Luhua Ancient Tower?
Yeah.
This place is always bustling
with people,
so I hear all kinds of news.
However,
if you want any specific news,
you need to...
How much?
One Border Coin?
One bar of gold.
Why don't you just rob me?
Don't get upset.
My prices are upfront
and fair to all customers.
By the way,
what you just said
about healing the Primordial Spirit,
there is a way
to do it in the tower.
He can sell twenty pieces
of fake information like that a day.
Don't be ridiculous.
My information
is from the Border King
when he was passing
through Leiquan Street.
That's real firsthand information.
Do you hear?
I'm buying this information.
Sir,
go on.
Here it is.
Why is the tower a Divine Realm?
First,
here dwell the ancient immortals.
Second,
there's a place
called Penglai
where the Divine Power is nurtured.
This power
can purify the evil
and rejuvenate all things.
If it can do that,
isn't healing Primordial Spirit
easy as pie?
So Shui can still be saved.
Li Gucheng
has also mentioned
the power in the Luhua Ancient Tower.
It must be true.
Beiluo.
You heard what the keeper said.
The power in Luhua Ancient Tower
might be able to save Shui.
No.
I will never believe in legends again.
You don't believe it,
or you don't want to believe it?
Beiluo Shimen,
are you really willing to accept this?
Don't you want
to try again for Shui?
Did Shui save you
only to see you
get so depraved?
Do you deserve
Shui's sacrifice?
If I had
a daughter like her,
despite my
unbearable pain,
even if the world deemed me
unworthy of life,
I'd strive
to live well,
so Shui may find peace.
Are you really willing to accept this?
Don't you want
to try again for Shui?
Coffee for two.
Thank you.
I know
seeing the way Beiluo is now,
you're a little disappointed.
Why should I be disappointed?
I have known
where Lingfeng Street is.
I'm beyond happy.
Just admit it.
I actually can
understand Beiluo.
As a man
of real goodness and integrity,
he found it hurt so much.
If he survives,
he'll carry the sorrow for the fallen.
If he doesn't,
he fears
letting down those who love him.
Don't you think
forcing him to cheer up
is a little harsh?
Harsh or not,
we'll find out tomorrow.
Let's set out
for Lingfeng Street.
[Beiluo Shimen]
♪You are a ray of light
illuminating the future♪
♪All directions are no longer confusing♪
♪Stand in the middle of the world♪
♪Follow your dreams♪
♪Build the highest wall with your hands♪
♪No compromise, no backing down♪
♪No loneliness, no regrets♪
♪It will all become the most fearless♪
♪And strongest faith♪
♪You are the light♪
♪My light♪
♪The power you give is burning hot♪
♪The pulse is beating and bouncing♪
♪Go find a light♪
♪Listen to the heartworm of desire♪
♪Gnawing away at thoughts♪
♪Behold the giant's world♪
♪Quaking and slowly tilting♪
♪We stride through thick smoke♪
♪Fearless in the face of stormy seas♪
♪Pressing on barefoot♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪
♪I'll never be alone♪
♪Life is like falling leaves♪
♪Having no last words to recover♪
♪With my veiled eyes♪
♪To glimpse the hidden perils♪
♪On the edge of fate's blade♪
♪Facing the darkest abyss♪
♪Daring to leap forward♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I will never♪
♪My fire must blaze fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪