♪The rift in time and space
is deftly manipulated♪
♪Dark clouds roil,
malice lurking and waiting♪
♪I roar, stirring a wild tempest
on the ground♪
♪No need for praise,
courage is my nature♪
♪Unable to endure
the deafening cries for help♪
♪Then don't look back.
I'll bring this battle to an end♪
♪I will not be a caged animal♪
♪Passive waiting is not my way♪
♪Awakened from slumber,
the sealed power ignites♪
♪With the Divine Warrior's Physique,
I preserve justice's fate♪
♪Don't be too alarmed.
I have made my entrance♪
♪Step aside willingly.
Watch as I address the chaos of battle♪
♪In youth, we're wild and free,
even venturing where dragons be♪
♪This battle's not in vain,
for the light that I maintain♪
[Hero Is Back]
[Adapted from Xu Chen's comic:
Rakshasa Street]
[Episode 9]
Just rent any car.
As long as it can take us
to the barrier's entrance,
it'll be fine.
Be careful what you say.
If the people inside
hear that
and think we're clueless,
they might try to pull a fast one on us.
What do we do then?
How about you handle it?
Listen,
anything with wheels
is my specialty.
Watch how it's done.
[Car Rental]
How many times do I have to say it?
We need to go to a big company
for car rentals.
How is this modest place
supposed to impress me?
Isn't my reputation worth something?
It's 400 yuan a day for a car here,
while 300 yuan for the ones outside.
Rent it or not, it's up to you.
280 yuan a day.
No.
She said no.
Let me handle it.
Hi there.
I see that the cars here
are a bit old and worn out.
Also, this spot
has some scratches.
The main issue is the colors.
All these colors
are quite dull, outdated,
and depressing.
I think sitting in one of these cars
would probably bring my mood down.
Wouldn't you agree?
Come, Miss.
This way, please.
Miss,
you really know your cars.
Everything you said makes perfect sense.
You're so much better
than that guy earlier.
The guys these days
are just not up to par.
This one looks great.
How much per day?
800 yuan per day.
800 yuan?
Let's rent it, please.
It's not that expensive.
Look at its style
and appearance.
Even if Beiluo sits in it,
he'd look ten years younger,
if not more.
After all, we earn money
for spending it, right?
Just rent it, please.
Rent my foot.
Beiluo,
please do something.
She's lost her mind.
Miss,
I noticed the insurance
on the SUV outside
is about to expire.
Also, it's the off-season,
so business is a bit tough.
Here's the deal:
800 yuan for a week.
Take it or leave it.
What do you say?
Beiluo,
you're the one we can count on.
This car offers the best value.
The two of us
would just be two fools
getting ripped off.
You can talk about yourself.
Why include me as well?
We're both the same in this regard.
Just admit it.
It's not a big deal.
I'm older than you,
so it's normal for me to know more.
Beiluo,
since you're here,
can you tell us about Lingfeng Street?
Are the folks there friendly?
I was just about to mention this.
We have an additional mission
on our visit to Lingfeng Street.
Mission?
What do you mean?
Weren't we supposed
to look for Luhua Ancient Tower?
It's not as simple as you think.
To find Luhua Ancient Tower,
you must get a guide
from the Wind-Treading Clan
on Lingfeng Street.
Guide?
What are you talking about?
The Wind-Treading Clan
is an ancient tribe
residing on Lingfeng Street.
Every member of their clan
is a Spirit-hosted Human,
and they have guarded
the Luhua Ancient Tower for generations.
Without one of their guides
to lead us,
none of us could ever locate
the precise spot
of Luhua Ancient Tower.
So, you mean
we need to find a guide?
But isn't that
pretty simple?
After all, there are so many people
in the Wind-Treading Clan.
But we need to pick
the most reliable one.
Don't interpret the role of this guide
purely by its literal meaning.
Then, how should we interpret it?
The location
where the Luhua Ancient Tower appears
is in a forest
near Lingfeng Street.
To safeguard the tower
from intruders,
the ancestors of the Wind-Treading Clan
cast an illusion spell
over the forest,
making the tower invisible to others.
This spell
is bound to the bloodline
of the Wind-Treading Clan,
and only a chosen one
can use a specific incantation
to lift the spell.
This chosen one
is called the guide.
You're not going to tell me this guide
is hard to find, are you?
It's not just hard.
It's incredibly tough.
Each generation
may have only one,
or at most two, guides.
Within the Wind-Treading Clan,
only the guide
and the clan leader
know the true identity
of the guide.
The clan leader
is usually the Spiritual Guardian
of Lingfeng Street.
There are just over ten days left
before the Luhua Ancient Tower appears.
Is that enough time
for us to find the guide?
In my opinion,
they won't easily hand over the guide
because they are committed
to protecting
the Luhua Ancient Tower.
I think
nothing is absolute in this world.
I'm confident
that we'll surely find
the guide.
Do you have a plan?
No.
How can you be so certain then?
Think about it.
The fact that your mother
was able to enter
the Luhua Ancient Tower back then
means
she had a guide.
The Wind-Treading Clan
was willing to guide her,
so it wouldn't make sense
that they are reluctant
to guide her son now.
In other words,
as long as we find
the guide from ten years ago,
we'll be able to enter the tower.
Let's go.
Head straight to Lingfeng Street.
Why the sudden rush?
You should have told us
if you were going to speed up.
Yes,
being in a rush won't help.
Before we go to Lingfeng Street,
we need to visit another place.
Another place?
Where?
Take a left turn ahead.
Sure.
This is the place.
Why are we here?
The barrier of Lingfeng Street
is on top of a mountain,
so we need to buy
some mountaineering gear
to climb up.
Climb up?
Any problems?
Not at all.
Welcome.
How may I help you?
Hi,
I'd like to buy
some mountaineering gear.
Okay.
This way, please.
What are you looking at?
This is a trendy item.
Recently, everyone has been using it
for camping photos.
Let's buy it too.
I want to post it as well.
Post on what?
Blue Note.
What is Blue Note?
You don't even know Blue Note?
You're so behind the times.
Xia's office wear?
What's your business with office wear
when you're unemployed?
I was just recently unemployed,
okay?
I'm just temporarily out
of the workforce.
I can still manage
my online persona.
You're deceiving people.
How is that deceiving people?
I'm just sharing
the outfits I like.
Plus, I spend hours editing
and choosing filters
for my photos.
Yes,
if you don't spend a few hours editing,
you won't achieve
such a transformative effect.
I'll show you
what's truly transformative.
One, two, three.
You look great.
Wait a second.
What is this?
Delete it.
You want me to delete it?
That can be arranged.
Buy me the lantern.
Xia Ling,
you know how to negotiate now,
huh?
That's right.
Don't make me do this.
Yama's Cannon.
I dodged it.
Sevenfold Soul-Resonance Bell!
I'm dodging it.
I dodged them all.
- Ethereal Fire Monarch!
- I dodged it!
Acala's Army-Crushing Seal.
I'm dodging it.
Great martial arts skills, Sir.
- I'm impressed.
- Here comes my ultimate move.
Dragon-Confining Fire Pillar.
Quit messing around.
I've bought everything.
Xia Ling,
here's the lantern you want.
You bought this lantern for me?
You truly are much better
than Cao Yanbing.
Beiluo,
I know you are rich,
but you can't spoil her
like this.
All right. It's getting late.
Let's find a place to stay.
Let's go.
♪Caught in the depths of a riddle,
there's no turning back♪
♪Becoming a misfit♪
Did you leave the AC on
while you slept last night?
♪Unable to feel the gravity pulls♪
You've only been driving
for half an hour,
and you're already dozing off.
♪Including hope in the mix♪
Thank you for the little lantern
you gave me.
Girls your age usually love
taking photos.
♪When tearing through
the last veil of darkness♪
All right, I'll be here and keep talking
with you.
Thank you so much, you kind soul.
What kind of girl do you like?
I like someone who is capable
and won't be a liability in a fight.
You are helpless.
What kind of man do you like?
I hope
he knows exactly what he's doing
and what he needs to do,
and is willing
to face any challenge.
Honestly,
I think you fit that description well,
but I don't mean anything else.
So please, don't read too much into it.
♪No loneliness, no regrets♪
♪It will all become the most fearless♪
Cao Yanbing!
♪And strongest faith♪
What's going on?
Good thing you had your seatbelt on.
Your dad used
to be a Spiritual Guardian.
Ever since I learned about this,
I've been imagining
how he must have hurried off
each time
to Hanxian Street
to protect the Border Dwellers.
So,
did you blame him for it?
Of course, I did.
It's merely
the moment he left though.
Because I knew
that from the very next moment,
I would start missing him,
really missing him,
until we met again.
[Tiangang Hall]
A few days have passed.
Where are Cao Yanbing
and the others now?
They're on their way to Lingfeng Street.
They're approaching the ancient tower.
That's great.
Chief,
I'm only worried about one thing.
What is it?
The guide.
With just over ten days
before the ancient tower appears,
if Cao Yanbing and the others
can't find a guide,
your plan might be...
The Spiritual Guardian
of Lingfeng Street
is named Yan Lingyu, right?
Yes.
Even though this person
is hard to approach,
everyone
has a weakness.
You mean...?
It's said that Lingfeng Street
is never truly peaceful,
and the Wind-Treading Clan
is frequently raided.
This is the doing
of a mountain bandit
named the Fire-Eater King.
The clan he belongs to,
the Fire-Eater Clan,
has a long-standing feud
with the Wind-Treading Clan
and often causes trouble
for Lingfeng Street.
The Guardian Primordial Spirit
of the Fire-Eater King
is a Demonic Warrior Form
called Salamander.
The Wind-Treading Clan has
inherently weak Primordial Spirit Power,
so the Fire-Eater King
is bound to be a major concern
for Yan Lingyu.
If you can provoke the Fire-Eater King
to attack Lingfeng Street,
Cao Yanbing and his group
will surely step in to help.
If Cao Yanbing helps Yan Lingyu
deal with this issue,
she will be extremely grateful
and any requests you have
will be easier to negotiate.
Understood.
I'll make sure
to use this pawn wisely.
[The outskirts of Lingfeng Street]
The Blaze Jade
we took on this trip
sold for a high price,
more than double
what it was worth last year.
When we return to Lingfeng Street,
the General will definitely...
Fire... Fire-Eater King.
What are you trying to do?
What am I trying to do?
I'm just here
[Fire-Eater King of Fire-Eater Clan]
to walk my dog.
Salamander!
You are awake.
I suppose you don't mind
being invited here
to be my guest.
You...
What did you do to the others?
Rest assured.
I can't even be bothered
to bring back those useless people.
Unlike you, who is very useful.
I heard there's a kind
of miraculous substance
called Blaze Jade on Lingfeng Street.
Taking it
can greatly increase
one's Primordial Spirit Power.
Is that true?
What Blaze Jade?
I...
I've never heard of it.
Think carefully
before you give me an answer.
Everyone knows
that you're the person
Yan Lingyu trusts most
on Lingfeng Street.
You must know
the method to make Blaze Jade.
Tell me!
I...
Even if you want to kill me,
I still won't tell you.
Blaze Jade can only belong
to the Wind-Treading Clan.
Why go through all this trouble
for what you want to do?
Who's outside?
Do you have a death wish?
Acting all mysterious.
Turns out you're a beauty.
Don't worry.
I will not
kill you so quickly.
Why are you wearing a mask?
Let me help you take it off.
What a shame.
The owner
of the Demonic Warrior Form Salamander
is utterly useless.
Who are you?
How do you know about the Salamander?
Who I am isn't important.
What matters
is why I've come to see you.
You have a Salamander,
but you lack the Primordial Spirit Power
to summon it.
Each time you try,
it vanishes in an instant.
Do you know
what's more shameful than lacking power?
It's being unworthy
of the power you have.
You!
You've gone to great lengths
to obtain Blaze Jade,
just to gain its power.
Yet, I can offer you a kind of power
that's even stronger
and more enduring
than what Blaze Jade
can provide.
This is...?
Xuanhuang Pill.
The legendary Xuanhuang Pill
that can enable Spirit-hosted Humans
to unlock and master the power
of their Guardian Primordial Spirit?
Are there other Xuanhuang Pills
in the world?
Before taking something from others,
you should first ask yourself
what you can do
for them.
What do you want me to do?
Tell me!
The guide?
You want to enter Luhua Ancient Tower?
It's best if you don't know
what I intend to do.
One Xuanhuang Pill
provides temporary effects,
while two offer permanence.
You can receive one now
and get the second one
after the task is done.
Deal.
It's highly likely that Elder Mei
has encountered problems this time.
He should have returned yesterday
according to the agreement,
but there's still no news today.
Elder Mei frequently takes this route,
so he's very familiar with it.
We'll have to wait
for the General to return
and see how she decides on this matter.
Only the General
can make the final decision.
Yes.
It's really hard to deal with.
[Yan Ruofu]
He's unlikely to come back unscathed.
Elders,
is there anything
you want to discuss today?
If Elder Mei doesn't return soon,
it will definitely affect
our business.
Elders,
do you have any matters
to discuss today?
I've just received the news,
and it's all true.
Yes. What should we do now?
The General has arrived!
- General.
[Yan Lingyu]
I trust you are all aware
that Elder Mei has been away
from the camp for over a month.
He was supposed to return
by yesterday at the latest,
but there has been no news.
Elder Mei is highly respected
and is my right-hand man.
This matter
should not be taken lightly.
Lang Da.
Yes, Ma'am.
Lead a search yourself.
We need to find
Elder Mei's whereabouts
by the end of today.
Yes, Ma'am.
Mother.
This is the Assembly Hall.
There's no place for a mother,
only for the General.
General.
What is it?
You may speak now.
I also want to go find Elder Mei.
Not allowed.
Why not?
If you go,
would you prefer Lang Da
to protect you
or Elder Mei?
General,
please trust me.
I will definitely find Elder Mei
and help ease your worries.
I already told you that you
are not allowed to go.
As the Young General of Lingfeng Street,
it is my duty to go
and I must go.
If I encounter any mishaps,
it will not be the fault of others.
I respectfully ask
for your permission, General.
Let me ask you this.
If
you fall into the enemy's hands,
what will you do?
I will fight to the death
to protect the honor
of the Wind-Treading Clan.
You can't even summon
your own Guardian Primordial Spirit.
How can you uphold the honor
of our Wind-Treading Clan?
If you need to cry,
do it somewhere else.
I have the freedom
to make my own choice,
and whether you allow it or not,
I will go search for Elder Mei.
You...
General!
General.
Bad news.
The Fire-Eater King is attacking us.
He's already entered Lingfeng Street.
This is bad.
The Fire-Eater King
is exceptionally ferocious
and formidable.
Yes,
the Fire-Eater King
has always been raiding
the surrounding areas.
How did he manage to get in?
What are we going to do now?
All right,
everyone be quiet.
How are the Border Dwellers outside?
They are too frightened
to leave their homes,
but we don't know if the Fire-Eater King
will actually hurt them.
Relay my command:
sound the drums at once
and prepare for battle.
- Yes!
[Assembly Hall]
The Fire-Eater King is here!
Run!
[Lingfeng Street]
Yan Lingyu,
it's been a while.
You've gathered
so many people to greet me.
How thoughtful of you.
Ji Long,
the feud between our clans
ended with the fall
of your Fire-Eater Clan.
I've put up
with your raids around Lingfeng Street
because you
are the last survivor
of the Fire-Eater Clan.
But today,
you dare to cause trouble
in Lingfeng Street?
You're digging your own grave.
I'm digging my own grave?
What nonsense!
The ones who should die are you
and your Wind-Treading Clan.
Why did my people have to perish
at the hands of the Malevolent Beings,
while you get to live?
It makes no sense.
Spiritual Crossroad
belongs to the strong,
and you
should have been dead long ago!
Your Salamander
couldn't even hold out for a moment,
and yet you still have the nerve
to challenge me?
Do you really think I'm afraid of you?
Yan Lingyu,
the only reason you're so arrogant
is because
of the Blaze Jade in your hand.
Just a friendly reminder.
Recently,
I happened to obtain
a Xuanhuang Pill.
After taking it,
I'm no longer the same as before.
My Salamander
now obeys my every command.
Crushing you
will be as easy as squashing an ant.
Fire-Eater King, I dare you to hurt him!
Kid,
go back and tell them
that your Elder Mei
is in my hands.
If they don't bring me
the guide
by tomorrow night,
I'll kill Elder Mei first
and then finish off
every one of them.
Got it?
Wind-Treading Clan.
General Yan.
Mother.
Pass on my order:
sound the alarm bell.
Bring it to me.
General.
- General!
Mother.
You didn't drink
the Blaze Jade again, did you?
Why has it taken so long?
How are the traps and mechanisms
coming along?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Elder Mei told me
that Blaze Jade with a darker color
is more potent
but also more poisonous.
The Blaze Jade our people usually take
is diluted
and considered a tonic,
but I know
that before it becomes a remedy,
it is first a poison.
You've been taking Blaze Jade for years.
You must have accumulated
a lot of toxins by now.
- How can you still...?
- That's enough.
Stop talking.
With such a formidable enemy
approaching,
anything that aids in resisting him
must be used,
even if it's poison.
Our Wind-Treading Clan
is inherently weak
in Primordial Spirit Power
and only managed
to resist Malevolent Beings
with the help of Blaze Jade.
And now,
we have no choice
but to rely on it again
to overcome this crisis.
Who says we have to rely on Blaze Jade?
I've already set up
the traps and mechanisms.
Once we capture
the Fire-Eater King tomorrow,
I'll personally defeat him and show you.
Defeat?
How can you defeat him?
You can't even summon
your own Guardian Primordial Spirit.
How do you plan to defeat him?
I practice rigorously each day,
and my body techniques
have greatly surpassed
those of most men in the clan.
You're overestimating
your own abilities.
At Spiritual Crossroads,
we rely on Primordial Spirit Power.
The Guardian Primordial Spirit
of Fire-Eater King,
Salamander,
is a rare Demonic Warrior Form.
Attempting to win
through hand-to-hand combat
is sheer fantasy.
I haven't had a chance to fight.
How can you be certain I can't win?
What if I'm capable?
Ridiculous!
You can't rely
on luck in battle.
You need
to get rid of that notion right away.
Don't even think about it.
I...
Mother.
[Human Realm]
Look,
the barrier of Lingfeng Mountain
is right at the top of the mountain.
Here's the plan.
I'll take the lead.
Xia Ling, you stay in the middle,
and Cao Yanbing covers the rear.
Cao Yanbing.
I said you'd be covering the rear later.
Any issues with that?
Not at all.
I got this.
But, you know,
the scenery around here
is quite nice.
How about we eat something here
before we continue?
I mean
before we head up.
I don't think it's necessary.
Being full and enjoying the view
probably won't cure a fear of heights.
Fear of heights?
Are you talking about me?
I could never be afraid of heights.
Every time I go out,
I find the highest spot
and stand on it.
Don't I?
Actually, this mountain
may appear high,
but it's not that difficult to climb.
In a moment, just follow me,
adjust your stride
and breathing,
and we'll reach the top soon.
Let's go and get our equipment.
Prepare to depart.
Hurry up.
Is this what you consider not high,
Beiluo?
It's obviously quite...
Cao Yanbing,
you're still not done being frightened?
Get your stuff packed up quickly.
Beiluo,
where's this barrier
you mentioned?
How come I don't see it anywhere?
It's right here.
Just go past that rock,
and you'll reach Lingfeng Street.
Let's go then.
Hold on.
I haven't finished my instructions.
That rock
only allows one person
to pass each time.
Only one person can pass at a time?
What a strange rule.
You know
about such an odd rule,
so it seems you must have
a deep connection
with Lingfeng Street.
It's nothing special.
I just have a friend there.
How special is it then?
What kind of relationship?
Is it a man or a woman?
He avoids answering the question
and runs away,
he must be hiding something.
All right,
stop gossiping.
Let's go.
Coming out of the mountain
still feels like being within it.
This place is different
from the Spiritual Crossroads
we visited before.
This mountain
is named Lingfeng Mountain.
We are now in the domain
of Lingfeng Street.
Look.
As cracks are heard in the waters,
long fish emerge.
As we look up,
Lingfeng's mighty hawks fly high.
[Lingfeng Street]
Lingfeng Street?
That's right.
This is Lingfeng Street.
♪Listen to the heartworm of deSire♪
♪Gnawing away at thoughts♪
♪Behold the giant's world♪
♪Quaking and slowly tilting♪
♪We stride through thick smoke♪
♪Fearless in the face of stormy seas♪
♪Pressing on barefoot♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪
♪I'll never be alone♪
♪Life is like falling leaves♪
♪Having no last words to recover♪
♪With my veiled eyes♪
♪To glimpse the hidden perils♪
♪On the edge of fate's blade♪
♪Facing the darkest abyss♪
♪Daring to leap forward♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I will never♪
♪My fire must blaze fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪