♪The rift in time and space
is deftly manipulated♪
♪Dark clouds roil,
malice lurking and waiting♪
♪I roar, stirring a wild tempest
on the ground♪
♪No need for praise,
courage is my nature♪
♪Unable to endure
the deafening cries for help♪
♪Then don't look back.
I'll bring this battle to an end♪
♪I will not be a caged animal♪
♪Passive waiting is not my way♪
♪Awakened from slumber,
the sealed power ignites♪
♪With the Divine Warrior's Physique,
I preserve justice's fate♪
♪Don't be too alarmed.
I have made my entrance♪
♪Step aside willingly.
Watch as I address the chaos of battle♪
♪In youth, we're wild and free,
even venturing where dragons be♪
♪This battle's not in vain,
for the light that I maintain♪
[Hero Is Back]
[Adapted from Xu Chen's comic:
Rakshasa Street]
[Episode 3]
About the main work
you undertook on the last project,
could you please
be more specific?
I was mainly responsible
for perfecting the design
and completing the presentation.
Completing the presentation.
Okay, I see.
[Endless Creativity]
Miss Xia,
that's all for today.
As for the interview results,
we'll inform you through text messages.
That's it?
Next one, please.
Wait.
Here is the thing.
I have something to say.
Even though I don't have
much work experience,
when I graduated from the college,
I was the valedictorian.
And I got A in every class.
I have faith in my learning ability
and adaptability.
I hope you can
give me a chance.
It seems that you have fair skin.
What does that mean?
What does getting a job
have to do with that?
I assume you can't stay up late.
In this circle, we do overtime
and stay up late.
It's all very normal.
I see how thin you are.
Can you work on the construction site?
With the intense heat of summer
and the biting cold of winter,
are you up for such weather?
You can't always ask a male colleague
to take care of you, can you?
You mean
you only hire male candidates, right?
That's not what I meant.
Hello?
The cemetery?
[Here rests Xia Qifeng.
In loving memory, Xia Ling.]
What happened here?
What happened to my dad's grave?
We found it
this morning.
We called you
to check in with you.
If
this was done
by one of your families?
How could my family have done this?
Who would destroy
the grave of their own family?
It's not impossible.
I just checked.
The other day, one of your families
asked to open the grave
and redirect the cremains
for Feng Shui considerations.
Isn't this crazy?
Redirect the cremains?
One of my families?
I remember Dad had a necklace.
Why is it gone now?
[Guardian]
[Hanxian]
What a special medal!
Can I have it?
No.
This necklace
can't be given to anyone.
But
I can
make something else for you.
It can't be given to anyone.
Is it
something important?
So important
that robbing a grave is worth it?
Water.
Thank you.
How long have I been unconscious for?
Two days.
Oh no.
Only one day left.
Xu Chu. Dianwei.
Lost your Guardian Primordial Spirit?
It's useless.
You can't defeat him.
Who is that guy?
He is called
the Prison Guardian.
Shadowbound Prison, vast as it is,
is under his command.
With an acute awareness
of the Primordial Spirit Power,
he possesses the power
to claim the Guardian Primordial Spirits.
Within three days.
Just three days.
Once the black beads turn white,
they will remain so permanently.
The Prison Guardian was
just a little monster at first.
In the war,
he was saved by the Patriarch.
Then
he was asked to guard this place.
The Patriarch promised him
to pick him up in five hundred years
and take him as a disciple.
But it's been eight hundred years.
The Patriarch still
hasn't come to pick him up.
Thus,
he was left in this tragic state,
neither fully human
nor wholly a spirit.
I don't care
if he's a human or a spirit.
[Four]
[One]
Give me some water.
I beg of you.
The heat is unbearable.
Out. Let me out.
Be quiet when I'm on patrol.
Wait.
Why are you still here?
Other Meal Deliverers
left long ago.
So you're going there.
Keep an eye out.
The new guy
may get out of jail any minute.
If you see him out,
report it to me.
If you dare to hide it...
the consequences will be severe.
Leave.
He's weird.
I didn't smell human.
Master,
still no clue?
Actually,
I didn't know my dad very well.
Why do you say that?
When I was a kid,
my dad was always busy.
I remember him travel a lot.
He only came back to see me
every ten days or half a month.
Sir,
please pick the sweetest one.
Okay.
Is this all right?
Fine.
Five yuan.
Come often.
Thank you.
Be careful. It's hot.
Okay.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Dad,
this time,
how long will you stay?
I'll leave tomorrow afternoon.
Ling.
I am
not always there for you.
Do you blame me?
No.
Because every time you come back,
you would take me out to have fun.
I am very happy.
Not like Mom.
She only wants me to study.
Your mother wants you to study
for your own good.
And then,
my mom and dad got divorced.
I saw him even less.
He did come back to see me,
but it was always in a hurry.
He wouldn't stay long.
Then,
how did he die?
I heard it from my mom.
When at sea,
he caught a typhoon.
The boat capsized.
He was swept away by the waves.
We never found his body.
Later we heard from a friend
about his death.
Several relics were found
and we managed to build a grave.
So,
could there be any clue?
The notebook is blank.
The box couldn't be opened.
Nothing at all.
Don't you think it's weird?
In this notebook,
there is nothing,
but it feels like
it's been flipped over many times.
Before I say thank you,
I want to know
who you really are
and why you help me.
You have no trace of humanity.
You must be a Border Dweller.
All the Meal Deliverers here
in the Shadowbound Prison
seem to be Border Dwellers.
But you're no ordinary Border Dweller.
You can even
hide my aura.
Who exactly are you?
What do you mean?
I knew the cell zero isn't easy to find.
But there're too many cells.
Where do I start looking?
Aren't you coming with me?
The top floor?
Is that where you want me to go?
Do you know who I'm looking for?
I'm looking for
someone named Tang Xiaoxiao.
All right.
Regardless of your motive
for making me go there
or your purpose
in helping me,
thanks
anyway.
Did the Meal Deliverer
want me to see this?
Who is it
to end up in a place like this?
Who is at the door?
I asked you a question.
Why don't you answer?
Excuse me.
I am a common prisoner
who just got arrested.
I came here
looking for someone.
Looking for someone?
You came to the Shadowbound Prison
to look for someone.
I have never heard
of anything sillier.
I have no choice
but to come.
I came to find someone
named Tang Xiaoxiao.
Do you know
where she is being held?
Judged by your voice,
you are still quite young.
But you made it
to the Shadowbound Prison,
which means you're quite resourceful.
Sir,
don't you think
talking through the door
is inconvenient?
Now it's time to unlock the ones on you.
As far as I know,
there's only one person
who can unlock this
with such speed
in this world.
Kid,
who are you?
Why are you so eager to know
who I am?
Because only after you tell me,
can I decide
whether to help you or not.
Sir, you mean
you can help me find her?
Okay.
Then I can tell you.
My name is Cao Yanbing.
Tang Xiaoxiao who I was
telling you about
is my mother.
So you are Xiaoxiao's son.
No wonder.
Looks like you totally inherited
the lock-picking skills
of the Tang Family.
You know my mother?
We go way back.
To tell you the truth,
I'm the former Chief of Staff
of the Hall of Heroes,
one of The Four Eminent Warriors,
Li Gubai.
[Li Gubai, former Chief of Staff
of the Hall of Heroes]
Your mother was
also a member of the Hall of Heroes.
My mom was
a member of the Hall of Heroes?
How is that possible?
Though
she served
the Hall of Heroes with us,
we were in the front
in charge of the fights.
She was in the dark
in charge of assassinations
and other secret missions.
Her identity was a secret.
She only served the chief,
Huangfu Longdou.
Huangfu Longdou?
The wanted man?
Mom used to work for him?
Okay Sir, let's put that aside.
Could you please tell me
where my mom is being held?
I need to save her
and then we can leave
together.
Don't bother, kid.
Your mother is not even
here.
Not here?
How is it possible?
I heard
she was held
in the Shadowbound Prison.
I can share with you
an image of her.
Because of this image,
I'm sure
she's not here now.
Then please show it to me, Sir.
But
how do you show it to me?
Though I am blind,
I can share with you
via the eyes
of the Guardian Primordial Spirit.
Then the image
can be transmitted to your mind.
This will be traumatising
to your spirit.
You need to think it over.
Master,
I found that on every page
of this notebook,
there are traces
of weak Primordial Spirit Power.
If I'm not wrong,
it's not like there's nothing there.
Someone did something to it.
Only using Primordial Spirit Power on it
can you see what's in it.
No need to think it over.
I can take it.
Do you mean
my dad was a Spirit-hosted Human?
But you have to promise me.
No matter what you see,
keep control of your feelings.
I promise you.
Just transmit the image.
Did you say
I needed to use
Primordial Spirit Power on it?
Yes.
Master, you might as well give it a try.
Come here.
[Huangfu Longdou. Divine Power.
Luhua Ancient Tower]
Celestial Eye.
Open.
You want to kill me?
Not that easy.
Jing Shisan.
Shisan!
Shisan.
General Zhao,
Hall of Heroes shall claim your life.
You band of murderous shadows,
cowering from the light.
I simply didn't
obey orders.
You put a charge on me
and try to kill me secretly.
Hall of Heroes is
nothing but a stooge
to the Border Realm.
You've lost your soul
and serve as the henchman
of malevolence.
Your vile actions
will cast a long shadow
over your offspring.
Xiaoxiao,
don't listen to him.
Just kill him.
So we can complete our mission.
Forget it.
Having lost
his Guardian Primordial Spirit,
he's already a dead man.
Let's throw him
out of the Spiritual Crossroads
and leave him to his own devices.
Xiaoxiao,
the orders we got were
to execute him on the spot.
If you let him go,
how do we explain this to the hall?
About this,
I will explain this to Chief Huangfu.
You little rascal,
why do you keep staring at your brother?
He is small,
and soft.
I worry I'll break him if I touch him.
When will he grow up?
You're a big brother now.
Now,
you must take good care of your brother.
Take care of him?
Just like dad
takes care of Rakshasa Street?
There are many Border Dwellers
in Rakshasa Street.
To keep them from falling into darkness
and becoming evil,
Spiritual Guardians are needed
to keep this place safe
and peaceful.
This is the responsibility
of the Spiritual Guardians.
Responsibility?
What is responsibility?
We are a family.
So you love us.
You love our home
and Rakshasa Street.
What we're protecting is love.
That is our responsibility.
Love is our responsibility.
Yanbing.
A Border Dweller became evil.
I need to take care of it.
Take care of the house and Liang.
Wait for me.
Sirs,
you came
to Rakshasa Street so late at night.
What can I do for you?
[Su, the Right Envoy.
Qi, the Left Envoy]
You know us?
When I visited Chief Huangfu,
I met you.
Since you know who we are,
we won't play around with you.
Tang Xiaoxiao,
I need you to come with us.
Where to?
What for?
Later,
you will know.
What if I say no?
You should know.
With our strength,
destroying this street is
easy as pie.
Even if you don't think for yourself,
you must think for your kids.
That's right.
Mom, where are you?
Mom?
Mom!
Mom's body was fake.
Kid, stop it now.
Unleashing your Primordial Spirit Power
like this,
your body will fail.
Stop it!
Cao Yanbing,
get out of here.
I know you're here.
It seems
I was too kind to you.
Here he comes.
He sensed your Primordial Spirit Power.
Impossible.
That's not true.
Sir,
please tell me.
What you just showed me,
is it reliable?
That was your mother's
Guardian Primordial Spirit.
Her Guardian Primordial Spirit?
You mean Tang Wuxin?
Why do you have his memory?
Have you seen him anywhere?
And where is that place
you just showed me?
Get out of here.
I'm running out of patience.
It's no use hiding.
I smell you.
It's too late.
Even if you find Tang Wuxin
and the place in the image,
you won't
be able to escape Shadowbound Prison.
For hundreds of years,
no one has ever defeated
the Prison Guardian.
No.
There is a first time for everything.
No one has made it in hundreds of years.
It doesn't mean I can't either.
There has to be some way.
Kid.
There has to be.
Cao Yanbing,
this time I want you dead.
The Patriarch asked me
to eliminate evils here.
I have eliminated so many already.
Instead of behaving yourselves,
you became more and more audacious.
The Patriarch promised
to pick me up in five hundred years.
But it has been
eight hundred and thirty-nine years.
Once I eliminate one evil,
ten more are born.
The more I eliminate,
the more there are.
Because of the existence
of evil beings like you,
this hell
will never be empty.
How pathetic.
What did you say?
It's been eight hundred years.
Your Patriarch
has abandoned you.
Cao Yanbing,
if you were
trying to provoke me,
good job.
The Meal Deliverer.
You are no ordinary Border Dweller.
Who are you?
Wuxin?
[Tang Wuxin]
♪Listen to the heartworm of desire♪
♪Gnawing away at thoughts♪
♪Behold the giant's world♪
♪Quaking and slowly tilting♪
♪We stride through thick smoke♪
♪Fearless in the face of stormy seas♪
♪Pressing on barefoot♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪
♪I'll never be alone♪
♪Life is like falling leaves♪
♪Having last words to recover♪
♪With my veiled eyes♪
♪To glimpse the hidden perils♪
♪On the edge of fate's blade♪
♪Facing the darkest abyss♪
♪Daring to leap forward♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪The fire blazes fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never surrender♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I will never♪
♪My fire must blaze fiercely♪
♪Let nightmares
and dark nights be erased♪
♪I will never♪
♪Crimson blooms with fervent grace♪
♪For a fresh and radiant tomorrow♪
♪I'll never fail♪