Ae-ra.
If I tell you not to do it...
Ae-ra!
What's wrong?
Dong-man... what's wrong?
What's wrong? What is it?
Why? Why?
Why are you talking like that?
What?
Why aren't you making any sound?
Why is nothing making any sound?
Why? Why?
Why is everything quiet? Why?
Why? Why!
The storm has passed
and the world shut down.
EPISODE 15
I wasn't expecting you.
Lie down.
Sorry?
I said to lie down.
Shouldn't we talk first?
You can't treat your own back.
Why did you do it?
Why...
Why did you...
You're being ridiculous right now.
It's okay with me...
if you date Chan-ho.
What?
I'll wait.
I wish you wouldn't go out with him,
but if you do...
I'll wait.
You can hurt me.
You can hurt me all you want,
and I'll still wait for you.
Do I have to go out with Chan-ho
just to hurt you?
I will...
wait for you until I turn 50.
Do as you wish.
I'm not the old Baek Sul-hee anymore.
I won't fall for your lame tricks.
Sul-hee, why do you talk like Ae-ra?
Back in Joseon era,
they branded people for cheating.
You stubbed your toe while moving
Ye-jin's packages,
and you burned your back
on the coal today.
You're being punished.
So I don't feel bad at all.
I'm just putting ointment on you.
Lie down.
What?
What happened?
Is he okay?
He has a concussion, which is why
he couldn't hear temporarily.
Based on the scans,
the damage isn't severe,
so he'll be fine soon.
Thank you.
The problem is...
there's a hairline fracture
in his temporal region...
To be honest,
I cried a little.
Just a little?
No, I cried a lot.
That flip phone is the only way
to show...
how the real Hwang Bok-hee's like was,
rather than the clown Hwang Bok-hee.
Keep it safe for now.
I thought...
you were a warrior who wasn't
fazed by anything, but...
But it turns out I'm a crybaby?
Not at all, you seem even cooler.
When I was young,
I was an assistant at Rose Photo Studio.
I just really liked being
in front of the camera.
I see.
When I met my husband,
I decided to give up.
But the fire within me wouldn't go out.
I wanted to be in front of the camera
and be an actress.
So that's why you auditioned
for that movie.
I heard the competition was fierce.
In order to win, I had to hide.
Back then,
no one wanted an actress with a child.
That's when my life started to tangle up.
Come on, it wasn't completely tangled.
You were the fairy in the posters
in my room.
The path I chose...
was a thorny one.
Dong-man, it's time to eat.
Wake up.
Dong-man slept for days.
Eat up, your first lady, Choi.
Wearing a red hat
I'm a clown that always smiles
Behind the blue smile
Are the tears that no one sees
Am I really going to be on TV?
It's a MMA show,
so the audience pool is small.
But it's a famous show among fans.
But why am I...
We've always had male hosts,
and they all seem the same after all.
Above all,
I recommended you because I thought
you'd show some innovation.
The production director saw your video,
and approved you right away.
It's a bit pricey...
to sell on a home shopping show,
so we could throw in sauces
to make it a package.
Mr. Kim, would you like the claws
and guts separately?
Yes.
Anyhow, we should give customers
more options to make a strategic approach.
What strategy?
Mr. Kim, are you okay?
Are you crying?
It's my first pay.
I wanted to treat you something nice,
so I looked all over Cheongdam-dong.
-Joo-man.
-What should we get?
Cheese, chili?
I heard from somewhere that...
steamed cockroaches
taste the same as lobsters.
What?
You know...
It's kind of gross that I can't eat it.
Let's go some place else.
You're worried about the price, right?
I mean...
Isn't 57,000 won too much?
It's just an insect from the sea.
Sul-hee, can't we just enjoy our time?
Please?
Sure, go ahead and order.
Here.
Why are you giving me the whole thing?
-Are you going to eat fries only?
-What?
Whenever you do this,
I get kind of emotional.
Joo-man, what's wrong?
Why is your nose flaring again?
Why are you making me look like a bad guy?
Don't do that. It's upsetting me.
Fine, I'll eat the tail.
Forget it, just...
Stop this.
You should stop now.
Sul-hee, I cried at work today
and made myself a fool.
I know, everyone at the office knows.
Chan-ho knows we used to date now.
-That's a good thing...
-What?
We dated for six years and we only had
two bad months. The rest was really good.
Can you forget all of that?
I miss the six years we dated,
but because of the last two months...
I don't want to go back.
Seeing you change...
I can't do it again.
You changed, too.
Why are you acting as if you didn't?
How did I change?
You were never worried about anything
and you were naive.
You were just a pure white puppy.
Why are you talking about a puppy?
After you met me, you matured,
started becoming conscious of yourself.
Whenever you did that, I blamed myself,
and it was painful for me, too.
Sure, I changed and you did, too.
-So...
-I don't want to.
-I can't break up with you.
-What?
You said you don't have regrets
because you tried your best.
I'm going to try everything I can, too,
so I won't regret.
I'm going to cling on.
So take this.
I love you so much,
and I won't marry anybody else.
And I need to put some ointment today too,
so come up right away.
If I get infected, I'll die.
Hello.
Thank you.
Before we start the broadcast,
we'll conduct a short interview first.
Okay.
Here's the first question.
I heard your shoulder injury
is pretty serious.
Aren't you afraid to go back in the ring?
I'm lucky my injury is not too bad.
Lucky?
If I think about Sam Vasquez
and Gary Goodridge,
it can get scary.
What happened to them?
I'm putting porridge in the fridge,
so eat when you get up.
Don't lie around and not eat anything--
Hey.
Why are you yelling at me?
Can you hear me?
-Can you hear everything now?
-Yes, I can.
I heard you being noisy since you came in.
You're such a pain!
I was really scared.
I really was.
Excuse me, what brings you here?
Excuse me?
You can't come in here.
How have you been?
You look well.
I tried looking for you everywhere.
Do you know how scary it is to not be
able to hear for merely five minutes?
It's like the world has been turned off.
It feels like you're
at the bottom of the ocean.
I couldn't even breathe.
You can hear me no problem, right?
-There's no ringing, right?
-I'm good.
Have some.
It's good. Why aren't you eating?
Why are you so calm?
Dong-man.
You can really hear me well, right?
Yes, I told you.
Then, you don't need
a complete rest, right?
What?
Then...
listen to me carefully.
What is it?
You have...
a fracture somewhere in your skull.
The problem is...
the hairline fracture
in his temporal region.
A fracture?
With fractures in temporal region,
they heal without any treatment.
However...
the fracture is near the ear cochlea.
If he receives more impact
in the same region...
So if you receive more impact,
you might not be able to hear forever.
You'll get trapped in that ocean forever.
What nonsense is this?
I can hear just fine now.
So the conclusion is...
you can't fight anymore.
I won't let you.
Okay.
I'll meet the doctor first
and hear from him--
MMA fighter Sam Vasquez died of severe
brain injury within six weeks.
Gary Goodridge got Chronic Traumatic
Encephalopathy in his 40s.
Those are the extreme cases.
During a fight, injuries occur often.
They occur often?
Why do I have to watch you get injured
so often?
Ae-ra.
If I was going to quit this fast,
I wouldn't have started again
after ten years.
Fine, do as you like.
If you decide you fight again,
that's the end for us.
It's been over 20 years.
I still can't...
forgive you.
You kneeling down...
won't bring back the years
I spent in silence.
But still...
stay like that a while longer.
I'd like to...
watch a bit longer.
Director.
We already aired the preview. It's done.
We can't pull off a show.
You should know better than this.
You're making me feel uncomfortable.
Director.
-Stop it.
-Help me out.
This show can't go on TV.
Stop, stop.
Look for Dong-man on VCR 3.
Hang on.
Are you sure...
-we can air this?
-Yes.
Is this for show?
I guess you can find out
by returning to the ring.
You can't threaten me with this,
just because I love you.
I can't choose one.
I'll protect you even if it means
playing unfair.
Fight again and we're over.
We can't even be friends.
We'll never meet again forever.
Yes, Dad.
On TV?
I'm on TV?
What preview?
Show her the footage first.
The show airs in an hour.
There's no time for another inspection.
Who is she?
Producer Jung Kyung-koo.
Did the person you filmed
agree to this broadcast?
Excuse me?
From what I heard,
you and Ko Dong-man once met
as a suspect and victim.
Are you allowed to use a program
to get a revenge?
It was all in the past.
Who are you anyway?
Me? I represent Ko Dong-man.
What?
It's quite cheap.
MACKEREL
EFFECT OF MACKEREL.
Where did he go?
Did he go to the gym?
She must be upstairs.
What is she dragging around?
Is she hanging herself?
Oh, no.
She can't kill herself in the flat
above mine.
You can't barge in like this.
You barge into my place and Dong-man's.
Can't I...
What's that chair for?
Why is it over there?
Die 60 years later quietly
at some other place.
-Why in the flat above...
-Why would I die?
What's that then?
I was changing the bathroom light bulb.
The light bulb?
UNPAID BILLS
Do you think you won?
Gossips say you got a fortune in alimony.
Why would I take their money?
Like people say, I'm a spoiled brat.
Do you think I'd leave with a fortune?
I told them clearly
that I didn't want a cent,
and walked out with my own feet.
Is that why you're renting a place
for 300,000 won a month?
I asked if you think you've won.
No one knows better than you
what I mean to Dong-man.
He will take me back.
I won't lose him to you.
Knowing each other for so long...
is only good for friendship and loyalty.
To her, this was...
Don't think that you won.
...the only way to preserve her pride.
What are you doing?
You've been struggling with this
for a week now.
What's this noise?
What? Come and hold the chair.
Don't air the show.
I refused to interview.
It'll air soon.
-Pull it.
-No.
Ae-ra's right.
People never do change.
I told Ae-ra something, too.
I told her I'm not the old Jang Kyung-koo.
That I'm not as lame and sloppy.
What are you doing outside my place?
What's in there?
You mentioned in your messenger profile...
that you wanted strawberries.
Do you think I asked you to buy me?
You confessed to me a day after
dumping Chan-sook,
got me pulled from the pungmul band,
and you're constantly texted me.
You're telling people we're dating.
That's what I want.
Does that even make sense?
Why should I become an outcast
because of you?
If no one likes you,
maybe you'll date me.
What kind of stupid logic is that?
Don't come here again.
Why are you here?
I'm out on my 100-day holiday.
I have 546 more days to serve.
If you bother her again, I might desert.
Then, I'll bring a K2 rifle with me.
I'm warning you.
Don't bother Ae-ra again, okay?
Did you want to get back at me that badly?
Or do you still want Ae-ra back?
Just watch the show. It'll air soon.
I bet you made up a story to paint me
like a fool.
Without a story,
will anyone care for an unknown fighter?
What?
The story and malicious editing
was strategical.
I caught the deliberate headbutt.
-What?
-I tried my best to make you look good.
Watch it yourself.
From my point of view,
it was an intentional outburst.
It looks like he purposely induced
a no contest.
This is such a malicious editing!
The director...
was determined to create
fiction with fact.
He replayed the headbutt in slow motion
and inserted an expert's interview.
It's a total mess.
Our people are unable to deal
with the media backlash.
Didn't you know they were
filming Dong-man?
Tak-su, you shouldn't get all agitated.
Even if it's a light concussion,
you need to relax and keep calm.
Let me make this clear.
I won't fight
against that monster again, okay?
Get the media to stop talking.
Makes sure talks about rematches
don't start.
WE ROOT FOR DONG-MAN,
THE RISING STAR
What is this?
Why... Why is it so...
Good?
Are you touched?
Did you cry?
No, is my face...
Did you photoshop my face?
What did you do?
What have you done?
Why are you slapping your husband's back?
If you knew he would get hurt like that,
you should've stopped him.
Why did you support him?
-That is a sport.
-My goodness.
He's in a cage.
How can I watch him bleed?
Dad.
Yes?
Dong-hee, do you want something?
-I want to go see Dong-man.
-What?
I have something to give to him.
This is our newest menu.
-Then we'll have that.
-Okay.
My wife used to be an idol trainee.
She's really beautiful.
Our daughter is prettier
since she takes after her.
-People say she's like a fairy.
-A fairy?
See? You got it all wrong.
Why did you have to come and find Ae-ra
and chase her around?
My daughter is really cute, right?
But, not too long ago...
she got bullied at school.
One boy called Choi Ji-ho started it.
It turns out...
he thought if no one liked my daughter,
she'd only play with him.
If no one likes you, maybe you'll date me.
That really woke me up.
It's karma. I realized what I did
is coming back to my daughter.
That's why I came looking for you guys.
To get rid of my karma.
Have you been going to church
or something?
You shouldn't make food
and deliver them to men.
Hello.
You don't look like the housewife type.
You're so nosy.
Are you having instant ramen again?
Why are you coming up?
To eat with you.
-You and me?
-Yes.
Why?
We both don't have anyone
to eat with right now.
It took me 20 years
and I couldn't fix him.
But I guess Sul-hee fixed his rhinitis.
Mother.
Hey.
Why aren't you at work?
I took a half day.
I had packages to mail out.
I see.
By the way,
why did you two break up?
Is it because of me?
Or was it because of his sisters?
No, it's not like that.
Then, what is it?
It just happened...
Sul-hee.
Don't lie to me and tell me the truth.
Did Joo-man cheat on you?
That scumbag.
You can't really say that he cheated.
Actually,
when Joo-man's dad was alive,
he had two more women aside from me.
I fell ill twice because of it.
You shouldn't live like me.
You don't deserve to suffer that way.
I didn't know.
A mother can be sly.
If your child is precious...
you should know other children are, too.
But, I can't help but think my son
deserves better.
He was always so protective of you.
I guess I was jealous.
I think I was lonely.
It was fine. I'm fine now.
Still,
if you two get back together,
I won't ever visit your house.
Pardon?
You don't have to come
to any family events.
I won't let his sisters
ever call you again.
I swear it on my name.
I'm sorry, Mother.
You're right. I'm a fool.
I didn't want to lose you.
I was being silly.
Mother.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry that we didn't last in the end.
Even if I don't see you again,
please take care, okay?
I'll visit your place to meet the idol
and the fairy one day.
Right, do you know Hwang Bok-hee?
-Who?
-Hwang Bok-hee.
That Hwang Bok-hee.
What's this?
It is a soup or a stew?
It's mackerel stew.
My parents own a fish stew restaurant.
Why would anyone make such stew...
My dad is really bad at fishing.
What?
He used to be a fisherman.
But he could never catch
the expensive fish.
He'd always get some Pacific saury
or mackerel.
We had a big family because we lived
with grandparents,
but there was only one mackerel.
So my mom got mad,
so she put it in water and boiled it.
But my dad...
liked it.
That's why we opened a restaurant,
but the business isn't good.
Unit 101,
are you normally that talkative
while eating?
Pardon?
I'm starting to get a headache.
What about you? Do you only eat?
-You should have conversations--
-I get indigestion if someone talks.
So just...
take your food and go to your room.
Gosh.
Then you can eat it by yourself.
I'll come back for the pot later.
Eat it.
No wonder you don't have anyone
to eat with.
-Hurry up.
-Rock, paper, scissors!
Blue sky, milky way...
Green light, red light.
Green light...
Do you call yourselves humans?
What brings you here?
How can you do this?
Why would you do this to the kids?
Am I an adult movie actress?
You killed me with a few lines you wrote,
and now you made it impossible
for me to be a mom.
Director, please.
The preview is already out.
We can't pull off the show.
You should know better than this.
Don't make me feel uncomfortable.
Director...
-Stop this.
-Please help me out.
This show...
can't air.
My baby understands everything now.
What did my child do wrong?
My Ae-ra... Please leave Ae-ra alone.
You can't tell a child
that her mom is an adult movie star.
That's too cruel.
If my parents find out you're here,
they'll freak out again.
Obba.
I couldn't even raise my baby...
for taking clothes off in a movie.
Bok-hee.
I'm going to Japan tomorrow.
Can't I sing to my baby just once?
Wearing a red hat
I'm a clown that always smiles
Behind the blue smiles
Are tears that no one sees
Dwarf Flower?
Dong-man.
You'll give this to me? When?
As always...
protect Ae-ra.
Protect her for me, okay?
Caramel.
The caramel lady.
Why do you keep going to my place?
-I wanted to eat with Ms. Hwang.
-Why?
-What?
-Why do you care so much about my mom?
Why are you pretending to be nice?
I'm not pretending to be nice.
I was just eating with her.
I tend to believe people are
inclined to be evil.
Whenever I see you, I want to test you...
to see if you're really nice,
and if you really are that naive.
Look.
People are all the same
when it comes down to it.
Everyone is weak and insecure.
Being so prickly...
It's like you're going through puberty.
Are you going through a puberty?
Why did you get a tattoo on your arm?
-Get it removed!
-What's wrong with you? Why hit me?
You're a brat, yet there's no one
to smack you.
That'd be the saddest thing in your life.
I won't let Kim Nam-il become
that pathetic.
Now, Kim Nam-il is Hwang Bok-hee's
kind and nice son.
If spankings are medicine, I'll hit you.
Got it?
Spankings are medicine for punks
like him.
So...
Why Nam-il?
She's a girl.
Are you that sad because of her?
Have you ever been that sad
because of me?
I'm tired right now.
When your business failed,
and when you cried alone and got cancer...
who was by your side?
Was Ae-ra there?
Nam-il.
Let's go to...
Japan together with me, Mom.
Why is Dong-hee suddenly coming?
-Hi.
-Sorry, we're late.
Dong-hee.
-Can I get this mailed out?
-Sure.
Please write down the recipient's address.
You're wearing the new sneakers.
Didn't you come to see me?
Why won't you look at me?
You still don't want to talk to me?
Do you want me to show you the gym?
Don't lose anymore.
Dong-hee.
You'll talk to me now?
Why did you make me feel bad
for ten years?
You were mean.
I told you, it wasn't because of you.
What's this?
I'm your...
fan girl.
It took me ten years to make
this scrapbook.
So don't lose anymore.
I hate seeing you unable to get up...
more than being unable to get up myself.
Don't ever lose again.
This is where athlete Ko Dong-man trains.
I don't get it. What's going on?
You have four interviews,
a magazine shoot,
a water park poster shoot...
-A water park?
-Yes.
But you need to take off your shirt.
You have an offer
for a TV commercial, too.
-A commercial?
-Yes.
The effect of going on TV is really huge.
Look. He's an assistant director at RFC.
The CEO told him to get you to confirm
a rematch with Kim Tak-su.
-Why?
-They want a fair fight.
But you know, I may not be able
to continue MMA fighting.
It's scary after an injury
like that, right?
They say skull fractures heal
on their own.
It's a common injury for fighters, too.
Once a baseball player gets
hit in the face,
it's hard for them to get back
in the batter's box.
Trauma's are tough.
It's not because of the trauma.
If I keep doing this,
I have to give up something huge.
Ma'am.
What brings you here at this hour?
I saw the article.
I see you made up your mind.
I was afraid.
It was the first time I couldn't hear.
I was terrified.
The trauma of the injury...
What scared me most
when I couldn't hear was...
that I may never...
stand in the ring again.
That scared me the most.
Then will you fight again?
Yes.
I request a rematch with Kim Tak-su.
That's one way of getting dumped.
Ae-ra.
Must we?
I...
can't let you go.
Dong-man.
When you couldn't hear,
I pulled all sorts of tricks.
I never went to church school,
but I went to an early prayer service.
If this wish was granted,
I swore I'll be good from now on.
I begged and pleaded.
-For me to get better?
-No.
I begged that you'd quit MMA fighting.
Whenever my dad went out to the sea,
my grandmother would pray
with her rosary all day and night.
Later on, she got dementia
and forgot his name,
but whenever it was windy,
she asked for her rosary.
Grandmother was trapped there
all her life.
She said whenever my dad goes
out to the sea...
she'd feel anxious and suffocated.
I don't think I can live like that.
I couldn't even survive that one week.
I'm scared, too.
I'm scared that I'll lose
my hearing again.
I'm scared of getting hit and injured.
But...
what frightens me more is...
going back.
If I'm told that this was all a dream,
and I need to go back
to exterminating ticks,
delivering packages,
and moving boxes, then I...
I won't...
I won't be able to survive a single day.
I don't want to be an extra again.
I don't want to live without a dream
like a fool.
To be honest...
I knew you couldn't stop.
This isn't...
just my dream anymore.
It's also my dad's, Dong-hee's
and Coach's dream.
Ae-ra.
-If you trust me...
-I guess this means...
we can't even be friends, right?
No.
I can't be.
I didn't hide myself,
beat around the bush,
nor plan to break up with you.
I can't be just friends with you again.
Okay.
I'll go.
Ae-ra.
Ae-ra...
Do you really have to do this?
Can't you just stay by my side?
I can't bear to watch.
It's too hard.
It's really hard.
I wish...
I really wish,
we had never started this.
What brings you here at this hour?
Ma'am.
Please protect Ae-ra...
from now on.
I don't think...
I can protect her anymore.
Dong-man.
I never told you,
but I'm...
very thankful to you.
There's no need.
Come to think of it,
it wasn't because of the caramel
you gave me.
I think it was always Ae-ra for me...
from the beginning.
Subtitle Translation by Minsoo Shim