I won't let you go again.
Let's stop making detours.
Stand strong.
We already kissed,
and I don't know anything about dating
or whatever.
If we kiss, it's day one.
Let's date.
I said let's date.
Since we're dating...
I want to do it again.
What?
They should ban those fireworks
nationwide.
Doing that kind of thing to impress girls,
and they end up burning the beach
and burning their hands.
Why would the beach burn?
Why are you always so extreme,
impulsive, vulgar...
and so masculine like that?
I didn't do it impulsively.
It's been a while
that I could only see your lips.
Then is today really day one?
Kissing between friends is illegal,
cheating and a jerk move.
So we're definitely dating.
So, don't think about seeing anyone else.
And even when you're riding the bus,
don't sit next to a man.
Even on the bus?
Don't think about any other man.
Especially that first love or whatever.
Don't think about that vaccine
or wrist again.
Think only of me.
The vaccine and the wrist were both you.
What did you say?
My first love...
that disgustingly dense first love...
the one that haunted me for 20 years...
It's you.
To me, you are like...
a pimple.
It would rise and fall by itself.
It hurt and then it doesn't.
If I leave it alone, it's fine.
But if I try to pop it,
it hurts like hell.
I did that for 20 years, looking at you.
That was me?
You seem like the type of person
who'd kidnap the person they like...
So...
Stop being my guy friend.
If you go back to being
a tricky guy friend after kissing me,
then I don't think I can live.
I really, really,
really like you.
Idiot.
You should've just kissed me.
I would've fallen for you right away.
Did you like it a lot?
Want to do it...
one more time?
Can you shoot those fireworks to someone?
I told you, right?
I got the feeling
it would be on this time.
People still give out rice cakes
when they move in?
This luggage doesn't seem
like it's meant for a one-room flat,
does it?
-I think it belongs to a girl.
-Do you think she'll be pretty?
Where are you going?
To throw out the trash.
Why are you going out like that?
What?
This is how I dress
to throw the trash out.
By any chance...
did something happen in Daecheon?
With Dong-man?
We didn't do it!
What?
What didn't you do?
Are your clothes drying?
Hey, why are you exposing your stomach?
Are you trying to let everyone see?
She said she normally dresses like that
just to throw out the trash.
Hurry up and go.
Aren't you going to leave for work?
You guys are going to stay together
all day, right?
Well, we're both unemployed,
so at least we won't be bored.
Let's open Seol Hee's plum wine
when come back from work.
Okay.
-Bye!
-Okay.
-But you guys...
-What?
Don't do it.
Do what?
Don't open it first. The plum wine.
Don't do it.
-Unit 101.
-Ah! That scared me, you scared me.
-You didn't get it, right?
-Pardon?
The lady gave everyone rice cakes
except you.
Just you. She only skipped you, Unit 101.
What the heck? Why just me?
Making me feel bad.
She's famous.
The moving man even got her autograph.
Is she a celebrity?
She's an extremely famous Korean...
announcer.
You!
Why did you move to the apartment
above Dong-man's?
I was allowed to live across from him,
but not above him?
I saw on the internet
that you got alimony in dollars.
So why move here?
It costs 300,000 won a month!
To see obba everyday, just like you.
We're dating, officially.
I know.
It's for the best.
Then you've lost that disgusting
female human friend.
So I'll fill in that spot.
I'll be your friend.
I'll make sure that unnie gets to know...
how annoying that friend is.
I'm both his girlfriend and his friend.
No, you're not. After you guys break up,
you'll be nothing.
You won't even be friends.
What do you know?
Now it's going to be all or nothing.
We can't go back anymore.
Didn't you know that?
What does she mean it's all or nothing?
Hey!
Ahem.
Get changed and come out.
I have the weigh-in today,
so you should come along.
Then let's go on a date
or whatever it's called.
Why aren't you been talking?
Why do I feel like you're acting
like a real woman now?
What are you saying?
You're not sexy or innocent.
And since you're keeping your mouth shut
and not saying anything...
what would my pleasure be in seeing you?
You are a character who should
constantly be funny...
Of course, on the cuteness side,
you are above average.
Ah, heart attack.
The Chun's said they won't do
a second broadcast.
But we sold out,
so could you please talk to her--
Talk to them about what?
The owner's feelings have completely
turned around.
Would they even want to give
a rice cake
to an assistant manager
who rejects her daughter?
Did you know Ye-jin took the day off?
But why do you keep standing there
and talking?
What?
Why are you talking here outside
instead of coming in, like a delivery man?
Well...
I don't think I can come in anymore.
Why?
Because we are young, vigorous,
impulsive...
and immature animals.
And accidents always happen fast.
This bastard is so uptight.
-What did you say?
-Nothing.
Anyway, I'll be waiting here,
so get changed and come out.
Oh, I think it will take about an hour
and a half though.
An hour and a half?
Why? Are you exfoliating your whole body?
What?
You just need to change that shirt
and come out.
Isn't it our first date?
Do you really know that little
about women?
How women feel?
-Bah.
-Bah?
I mean, why is she like this?
What, am I that pretty?
REAL WOMAN
Hey, Choi Ae-ra, come back! Back.
Hurry and change clothes.
Why? Is it weird?
Your legs!
Do my legs look fat?
Why are your legs so darn pretty?
-What?
-Your legs are those of a woman!
-Did you think I would really be a man?
-Hey.
I feel like I'd kick the guys who look
at your legs.
So put on pants and come back out.
Who are you to be...
How dare you, who used to carry
my bag around, defy me?
Whatever about your bag,
just go and change to pants.
How dare you...
Go change to pants and come back out.
Ah, really. Her legs...
Wow, seriously...
Those legs will cause trouble.
He hit the second baseman's face.
Choo Shin-soo, who added a base hit,
had two hits and four walks,
which brought his batting average
up to 0.275.
-Are you just going to watch baseball?
-What?
I mean, your girlfriend is sitting
right across from you.
Do you only want to watch
Choo Shin-soo playing baseball abroad?
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Aren't we going to talk?
Are we only supposed to eat
in a restaurant?
We've dated for six years.
How can we just sit and make eye contact?
You get duller.
It's duller?
Sul-hee, could you stop twisting
my words around?
I get tired of it, too.
Tired? Exactly what are you tired of?
You don't go on dates with me
or talk with me.
You don't even kiss me much,
and we don't do it either.
Hey.
What are you tired of
when you don't do anything with me?
What I am tired of is that...
when I am with you,
I always become the bad guy.
You don't get tired, you are kind,
and you're endlessly giving
and full of love,
so I always seem like the bad guy.
Only me.
Why are you like this again?
What do you mean "again"?
I mean, have I asked for much?
I don't want anything from you.
You know, I just want us to be
like before.
Is it that hard not to change?
How can someone stay the same
for six years?
I can.
I still blush when I see you.
I'm like you more now than then.
And I just want to do
everything together with you.
-I'm sorry.
-You're sighing again.
I'm always jumping up and down for you,
and you're always sighing.
Are we just in the seven-year itch,
or are we in the middle of breaking up?
What?
Lately, I feel more lonely
when I'm with you.
-Just a sec.
-What?
My hands are sweaty.
But are you going to tell them?
Ah, Joo-man is going to laugh
so much about us.
Let's keep it a secret for now.
Sul-hee would say something.
Why?
I don't know.
Sul-hee has always been like that.
She said not to end up dating
while fighting.
She said to get married,
instead of dating.
In that case...
are you proposing to me right now?
Would you like this to be a proposal?
I'll be doing an arm bar now,
what will you do?
I have to escape.
Hold on.
What did I tell you to do?
Hey, you punk! I told you not to tap me.
Why are you tapping me again?
Because it hurts!
What? Why are you such an honest bastard?
Who can bear the pain?
Other fighters don't flinch,
even if their bones break. How come--
That's just being an idiot.
Why wouldn't you tap when you're hurting?
Hey, if you're hurting, tap right away.
Right away!
Why would you pull someone's arm out?
You're seriously a weird person.
Hey, are you really going to let her
stick around?
I can't train with you, Coach.
When's Doo-ho coming?
-What? Can't you train without Doo-ho?
-Why are you yelling at him?
Kim Tak-su, that jerk!
Please face each other and pose.
Wow, this is totally a drama.
Han Doo-ho.
What is this?
An athlete can change teams,
to a team with better conditions
and vision.
I need to go somewhere like that and grow.
Did the coach know in advance?
At Tiger, I'm treated differently.
-Their system is so organized--
-I asked you if the coach knew?
They also promote you a ton...
The dog with the most fear
barks the loudest.
What?
So keep acting like a jerk.
That way, Dong-man will grit his teeth
even more.
I think you're the one talking more
right now.
Tak-su, now people know better.
Know what?
That the side that stinks is the side
that's crap.
Let's not talk to each other.
Don't go there too easily.
If you're too weak,
it'll be no fun to crush you.
Gosh.
Coach.
I'm so ashamed.
-Coach Choi.
-Yes.
Doo-ho has a three-year old kid,
and he's only 26-years-old.
So?
He's still a kid. A kid.
Don't use the kid who's trying to survive.
Raise him well.
Okay.
Gosh.
Seriously, I'm so embarrassed...
I would never have moved if I was alone.
But my daughter's eczema
is really severe, and she keeps bleeding.
We had to move,
but there was no other way.
Did I say anything?
A crying martial artist?
You'll get hit on the back by Coach Hwang.
I know he's trying to screw you
and have Coach close the gym...
but I leave Coach in your care.
Why are people who are supposed to fight
chit-chatting?
Hey, Han Doo-ho.
Just come eat sausages whenever you want.
Well, you two go eat alone.
There's a famous restaurant that was
featured in the Four Heavenly Kings.
I was going to buy you beef, but whatever.
Just go. Let's eat separately.
Are you sulking?
You said you're a martial artist!
-Who's sulking?
-You sound like you're sulking.
Ah, just forget it. You two just go
and have a delicious meal.
We're dating.
What?
I said we're dating.
-Why? I mean, why?
-What do you mean, "why"?
So, you should know
when to invite yourself.
It's our first date today after all.
Is there something you can't tell me?
Are you worried that I caused an accident?
No, nothing like that.
Do you have a big debt on her
or something?
I told you I really don't go well
with this old man.
Gosh.
Why do you keep clinging to me
like a puppy?
I'm hungry.
The food you used to make
seemed like dog food, but...
this feels like I got a gold ax...
instead of my iron ax from the pond.
Shut up and eat.
Hey, eat.
Is this dog food or what?
Eat what you're given.
Why are you on the floor?
There's space here.
Don't try to play tricks on me.
Hey, do you think I want to do something?
-Why are you telling me to lie on the bed?
-When did I?
I told you to sit down.
Won't sitting down lead to lying down?
That's the trick.
Are you someone that would fall for that?
You're almost like a girl Fedor.
I feel like if you tried to hurt me,
I would get a fatal injury.
And would I do something like that
when we just started dating yesterday?
Am I some kind of jerk?
I really didn't have any other intentions.
A jerk without any intentions.
What?
Even though we only dated today,
we've seen each other forever.
We've been sickly platonic
for over 20 years.
What?
Are you a human?
Does a person even need to be
this uptight?
I'm a little upset that...
you keep looking at me
like I'm Chewbacca or Fedor.
I also think we might need a turning point
in our relationship.
We really just went around and around
and had our first kiss in 23 years.
Don't you think we have to pick up
the pace, as slowly as we have gone?
Why are you so progressive...
Do I have to keep talking?
Don't you have any alcohol?
I told you to change your password.
Is this some community hall?
Hey, you two...
Want chili shrimp with Kaoliang liquor?
I could beat him up with Kaoliang liquor.
Oh wow, that feels good.
But can you all really skip work?
Hey, why should I keep working if I can't
take a day off for my BFF's debut fight?
I've basically raised you
since you were six-years-old.
-Of course I have to go.
-Thank you.
Should we go buy some tranquilizers?
-How can I take that before a match?
-No, for me, so I can take it.
Oh. Two, three...
Hello!
Are you all going somewhere?
Yes, I have something...
-Have a good day.
-Okay.
-Unit 102.
-Yes?
-Uh...
-Ah, the room rent...
Fighting!
What did she just say?
I think she cursed at you.
High kick?
My goodness.
After kicking him down,
you need to go in right away.
But you can't fall,
because you can't ground fight.
You have to knock him out
with your kick in the beginning.
Taekwondo-based fighters
usually can't ground fight.
Kick... But hey, why did you follow us
all the way here and act like this?
I used to be his original manager.
Can I have this t-shirt as well?
The "Hwang Jang Ho Gym" shirt?
Gosh, anyway, remember to kick.
Finish it with a blow.
I got it, I got it.
RFC match three, welterweight super fight.
I will be introducing both fighters.
Wow, let's sit down here.
Height 184 cm, weight 76 kg.
Why do guys like things like this?
I can't understand it.
The crazy fighter,
who's returned to the cage,
the wonder boy of strikes, Park Jung-sik!
Fighting against him in the red corner...
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
...record on pro MMA...
Where can you apply to do that?
-What do you mean?
-That.
Hong Su-hwan!
Please give it up for Park Jung-sik,
who's shown us a good fight.
Ko Dong-man!
Kooooooo!
What, what, what? What is it?
You startled me!
I guess you miss me
in places like this, too.
It's not like that.
What is she plotting
that she's acting like this?
Kooooooooo! That sounds familiar.
Why was he back there not making a sound?
How embarrassing!
I don't really like triangle kimbap.
It's just a concept.
It'll be very touching to show
that you're a hungry fighter.
I don't really want to be hungry,
and it feels like I'm trying to sell my--
Then just eat it.
Think of it as acting, acting.
If this gets broadcasted,
Mom and Dad would see it too...
Gosh, just try eating it.
I think I misunderstood the purpose
of this program. This is kind of...
Don't you want to become famous?
Don't you know what will make
your parents happy?
Ah, so you came to cheer Dong-man on, too.
Obba, I'm dating him.
Right... What?
Now, I officially got his back.
Oh, how can you so suddenly?
Anyway, congratulations for now.
Did you hear this warning sign?
The black dog doesn't bite,
but if someone bothers him,
the white dog bites.
If you bug him, I bite.
Don't film this.
But Ae-ra, this time around,
I have talked with Dong-man, and--
I told you clearly not to film this.
I'm leaving.
Why can't she hold herself back
instead of being so powerful
all the time?
RECRUITING CAGE ANNOUNCER
RECRUITING CAGE ANNOUNCER - RFC
Hey, do you really want to scream
and all that?
Rather than that, isn't it really cool
to hold a mic in the middle of the cage?
-That?
-My heart is already pounding.
But isn't that usually for men to do?
Do men and women hold a mic
any differently?
Even so, usually men do it.
-That's why I want to do it even more.
-What?
The first woman, the only woman,
the best woman.
Aren't these titles a killer?
Let's not go easy on that Tak-su jerk
and just understand Doo-ho.
I understand. It just feels iffy to win.
Are you sure you'll win?
Doo-ho is stronger than Byung-joo.
What? Are you some idiot from nowhere?
That's sick!
Whatever. They have three seconds.
I should at least be there
to cheer you up.
This is the way to cheer him up?
Why didn't you write sausages?
Focus. Knock him over with the kick.
And go in right away.
Yes, I'll go inside.
Ah, I'm getting really nervous.
This is his debut match on TV.
But internally, he's very well known.
Because he has become a hot athlete,
he got his debut match very quickly.
Sul-hee, I'm going to the toilet.
But the fight is about to begin.
My stomach suddenly started aching.
Okay!
Okay! Ready! Fight!
That was a great kick from Ko Dong-man!
That kick... Was Tak-su first or him?
Due to Han Doo-ho's cut,
we will have a doctor check it briefly.
Coach, I think he's badly hurt.
Why do you care?
You are in the middle of a fight!
Okay!
Ready! Fight!
Who is getting hit?
Now! Go now!
He seems to be missing his chance
right now.
He shouldn't be waiting like that.
Why isn't he hitting him?
Go in! Go in!
RFC match three, light class super fight.
We will be announcing the winner.
We had a unanimous vote of the referees
for this fight.
Blue corner, taekwon boy,
Ko Dong-man is the winner!
Win!
Are you okay?
Why did you go easy on me?
I'd rather you knock me out
than you go easy on me!
MEXX CHICKEN WORLD
What matters whether you win or not?
You made this kind of name for yourself.
Octagon Waiter?
They say you're really nice
because you wait if the opponent falls.
So embarrassing.
What kind of nickname is this?
Why would you fight in the ring
if you can't hit an opponent who fell?
What do you know?
It feels totally different from kicking
a protective gear for taekwondo.
It feels like I can feel
the person's bones and skin.
You're so weak-hearted you can't hit.
I totally understand, Dong-man.
In the ring, the strong fighter beats
the nice fighter.
If you're going to be like that,
just give up!
I won't! I'm going to continue!
I just need to do a K.O. then.
I won't go into a dog fight like today,
and just finish in the beginning.
You think you can get a knockout
just because you want to?
Is anyone good from the start?
Is life a movie?
Are fighters all Rocky?
That's what a fake character is!
-I just need to overcome my flaw.
-My flaw?
My flaw? I should just whack you.
Please give me water!
Why is a coach with such
an excellent stallion so anxious?
What? Stallion?
He was already a legend.
Who knew a Seosan novice
would make it to a national team?
Just sit still and watch.
And don't keep hitting his head.
You have to see if he's making money,
eating and living well.
If you're so worried,
why don't you give him a call?
What would I say on the phone?
What would I talk about?
Do a parent and child only call
to talk about specific things?
You should talk about your new job.
Oh, and your business trip.
You call him.
Like father, like son.
What about a phone call
before you sleep...
Why call when we live
right in front of each other?
Okay?
Then I'll come over
for breakfast tomorrow.
I should probably wash my hair
every morning.
You're supposed to do that, stupid.
Then I'll enter my passcode now.
Oh, me too.
Should I...
-just go to your house?
-What?
I mean, we can watch the television
and eat something.
Eat... what?
Something like ramen?
Ramen?
In addition to no cohabitation,
I'll add no late night ramen.
Why?
What?
Why are you prohibiting
eating ramen and living together?
That's an abuse of authority.
I gave you a discount on maintenance fees.
I even did pest control.
I never even raised your rents.
I agree that you've treated us well.
But--
And you can't even follow that rule?
Are you animals?
Why are you guys all dying to date?
The whole villa is...
love affairs.
I think she's jealous.
If you're unhappy,
you can move to a place where
you can sleep together for higher rent.
Stop making me walk on pins and needles.
I think she's hysterical.
Is it the neighborhood or the blood?
NATIONAL ATHLETE SAUSAGES
Aren't you going to hurry and open?
Are you living that well?
Can't do your business right?
How did you know I sell sausages here?
I didn't. I came out to buy soju
and I saw you here.
Ah, okay.
Give me one bottle of soju.
Excuse me?
You must have some hidden away.
I can't sell any alcohol here.
Don't take my money.
Then you're not selling it.
It's truly an honor.
Don't overreact.
I'm not overreacting.
My life really changed because of you.
You became my role model
after I met you,
living your life the way you want.
-Should I give you an autograph?
-No, I'd just throw it away...
I knew that you went to Japan
a while back,
but why did you come back?
After a near death experience,
I thought I must find him.
My Nam-il.
Nam-il?
Nam-il. My baby.
He'll release his fury...
Song Yong-jin...
Don't you think
the landlady is really strange?
Why does she care if we sleep--
I mean, eat ramen or not?
I wonder what Nam-il is doing,
not looking after his mom.
Nam-il is her son, so never mind him,
but what about her daughter-in-law?
Imagine if you had a mother-in-law
like her.
I would flip out.
So, you have a child.
How are you going to find him?
-I've already found him.
-What?
So, what exactly are you going to do now?
That bastard's all warmed up.
Tak-su, leave Dong-man to me.
You just worry about resting.
You've been working out so much lately,
you actually seem like an athlete.
What did you think I was?
Tak-su, just fight with Dong-man.
Excuse me?
Just fight Dong-man as soon as possible.
He doesn't protect his face or attack low.
Reminds you of someone?
Dong-man is exactly like you
when you first switched over
from taekwondo.
Come on. Aren't you going to grapple?
Will you only ever fight standing up?
I'm confident up here.
Ah, you jerk, how can you only do
what you want?
Will you negotiate with your opponent
during a match?
I just don't have to go low,
even if he tries to pull me down.
Then you'll never be
any more than half a fighter.
If you can't overcome it,
this is the end for you!
Let's just fight him.
He's someone you can't avoid anyway.
Let's fight him now.
Tak-su, what do you want to do?
I promise you.
Once Dong-man overcomes this,
no one can catch up to him.
Height 163.2 cm, weight, 50-- 45 kg...
The first female MMA announcer,
Choi Ae-ra!
Why are you knocking
on someone else's wall?
Are you a renter here?
Who are you?
I'm the owner's son.
Nam-il? That Nam-il?
Do you know me?
Why do you keep calling my name like that?
I'm sorry.
By the way, aren't the stairs a public,
common area?
Yes, they are.
Don't wear clothes
that make others feel uncomfortable.
Please don't harm other's enjoyment
of the common area
with your loud shouting.
No one would believe
you're 163.2 cm and 45 kg.
Neither are they curious to know.
He's so handsome, yet so rude.
Is she crazy or what?
Ye-jin, I asked you
to never call me again.
Why are you doing this to me, seriously?
What?
Take a picture. Here. That's right.
No, normally the car in the back
is always the one at fault!
You suddenly backed up
when the light changed.
Me? I backed up? Wow.
Wow, this girl is pretty hilarious.
Ye-jin.
Mr. Kim.
First, let's check the black box--
But my black box is broken right now...
It's the car at the back's fault!
Why do you keep arguing?
-You called the insurance, right?
-If your insurance goes up,
you'll lose more money.
Let's just deal with cash.
We'll call it even at two million won.
You two had samgyeopsal, right?
Thank you, Mr. Kim.
If it wasn't for you,
I would've given them two million won.
There's no way for two men
to eat samgyeopsal without soju.
It was shady. That's why
they wanted to deal with it in cash.
I must be getting punished.
I shouldn't always come to you.
I would really be a bad girl for doing so.
So stop it already.
Why did you come all the way here
and get into an accident?
Ye-jin.
I really hope you'll stop from now on.
I won't go there anymore.
I'll stop. Don't worry.
Go home safely.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Did you hurt yourself?
I think I was so shocked earlier
that I pressed the brake too hard.
Please come to work tomorrow.
If you don't come, I get uncomfortable
and a lot of people talk about it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes. Thank you for today.
What did you buy so much?
Together.
What? He got a new job?
How did Dad get a job
that I can't even get?
But does he have to... at my house...
Okay, I got it. Bye.
What is it? Your dad got a new job?
Yeah, but he's going to sleep at my house
for one night.
What's so serious about that?
Now that I think about it...
I don't think I ever slept alone
with my dad before.
He's your dad. You can just sleep.
Is that right?
You have an interview
the day after tomorrow, right?
Do you think you can do
that ring announcer...
and watch me fight?
If you're going to do it even if you die,
I have to watch it, even if I die.
To protect you.
You are such a tiny person,
who's been protecting me
since I was little.
I'm ready to jump in the cage
if I have to.
If you become a ring announcer...
would we become a couple
within the company?
A couple within the company?
I think it sounds pretty sexy.
Within the company.
You just do your job and make a living.
It's nothing sexy.
No, in the middle of work, secretly...
we can kiss each other.
What?
Kiss.
Are you deaf?
What?
Are you being shy right now?
I'm not shy.
You're a real woman now.
Your cheeks are super red right now.
What are you saying?
Why are you holding someone's hand
without any reason?
You're supposed to do that.
Why are you looking at me so much?
My makeup's all messed up...
Why are you tying my hands?
Why do I...
only see your lips?
What?
If we're dating...
can I keep doing it?
You crazy jerk, seriously!
Crazy jerk?
Why are you asking?
Do you like it?
Why do you keep asking?
I should've kissed you long ago.
Then you would've gotten a beating
from me.
Since I did it...
I really like it.
Choi Ae-ra, I really like you.
I think I'm going crazy.
I've always liked you, you jerk.
If it's all or nothing...
let's go with all.
What?
Do you want to...
sleepover at my apartment today?
Hey, is the chili shrimp good, dude?
Is it good?
Is it super delicious?
Why are you bugging someone
trying to concentrate?
You did something bad to me today.
Why? Did something happen to you?
Well, if I tell you, will you tease me?
What is it? I'll hear it first
then decide to tease you or not.
Is that so? Then... honestly, I...
A bow! Bow! It's a bow!
-Bow?
-Bow!
-Bow? Did you get a bow?
-A bow!
A bow? You got a bow?
Subtitle Translation by Minsoo Shim