♫ Grip the steering wheel
in the roars that soar into the sky ♫
♫ And burn out the dreams ♫
♫ Have a confrontation of speed
with the courage to win ♫
♫ And see the silver lining in desperation ♫
♫ Always return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ And never step down in the dream of racing ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
fill up your tank with courage as fuel ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
♫ Eventually return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ The wind echoes, whistling the answer ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
cut the corner and beat all obstacles ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
[We Go Fast on Trust]
[Episode 7]
[Thank you for respecting my every decision]
[The loved ones will see the sky
full of stars when they look up]
Mom,
you're awake.
The doctor said
the surgery was very successful.
After a period of observation,
you can be discharged from the hospital.
Mom,
after you're discharged,
how about we make dumplings together?
You want to eat dumplings?
I want the kind you used to make
for me and my brother
when I was a kid,
with crab roe filling.
I don't know if it's available this season.
Yes.
I know a place.
Good.
When you're discharged,
I'll go with you to buy some.
I'll be here with you.
You can rest.
How did you know I was here?
Hao Yang.
The spare you found
is somewhat useful.
You're a jerk.
I got quite the insight that day.
What do you mean?
Why did you suddenly turn
against what we had agreed upon before?
What Chen Mofei pursues is different from me.
I can't go back.
How is it different?
Aren't both pursuits for results?
I consider car racing my life,
but she treats car racing as a business.
Why would I go back?
You're a car racer.
She's a businesswoman.
Even if the matters of bribery are true,
what's wrong if everyone just
takes what they need?
You two really are similar.
Thanks for the compliment.
Alright,
then let me talk to you
from a friend's position.
If you don't go back to Ruifeng,
how will you run the Formula A?
We will find our own sponsors,
expand the team, and keep racing.
It's a good idea,
but reality might not let you be so optimistic.
Why?
Takano and Junda
have a joint venture relationship.
Once they get into Formula A,
even if no one explicit it,
they are Takano's satellite team.
They will receive a lot of technical support.
Many emerging teams have French teams
working for them.
The progress is rapid.
Those veteran teams are
all about German technology.
They consistently rank in the top group.
How are you going to stand out in the race
as an independent participant?
I know all the things you are talking about.
I understand that physical conditions
of the cars are indeed important.
But I believe
technology comes first.
Alright, let's talk about technology.
You've made a bold statement before.
Mitsui Taku, whom you said
you wanted to defeat,
has already gone to the Markus team
for secret training.
Do you really think you stand a chance?
Why wouldn't I?
Baibai, you should stop being stubborn.
If you really
treat racing as your life,
you should cherish it
and make the correct choice
as soon as possible.
You should know
that every second you're wasting now
could be added to your race time
to become every second that you fall behind.
I suggest that you should know more
about how the world-class teams operate.
Besides, you're running too slow.
Who are you calling slow?
[Markus Racing Team Training Base, Germany]
When does the special training start?
This is it.
What?
Let him drive my car and show me.
This is the special training?
I stopped training and took a flight
for more than ten hours.
Just to watch other people drive.
Mr. Mitsui,
what are you upset about?
Just watch.
This is impossible.
How could this car reach such a lap speed?
If you don't believe it,
check the lap speed on the car yourself.
When you see how much potential your car has,
you can have confidence
to achieve what you think is impossible.
That is why we are here.
Who is he?
In this year's Super Grand Prix,
the new official racer
who has garnered the most attention.
Markus' secret weapon.
Mr. Lin.
Hi, I'm Lin Shaoqian.
Honored to learn from you.
I wouldn't dare to teach you anything.
Mitsui has gone for secret special training.
[Wang Duobao tractor and coca company]
At this stage, if I want to improve,
I indeed lack hardware.
Mobai.
You're back.
How is Shen Xi's mom?
Surgery was successful, she's fine.
That's good.
The new sponsorship?
Just speaking of it gets on my nerves.
Junda really has no face.
They still have the nerve to send you…
[Racing Driver's Contract]
Send you this racing driver's contract.
They don't know what they did to us before?
Do they think we would really sign a contract?
So funny.
Alright, don't worry about it.
I'll go throw it away now.
I'll sign it.
Going to Junda might solve my problems.
Well.
No problems can be solved
by signing a contract with Junda.
Now Mitsui is already in special training
in Germany.
I don't want
to pressure Shen Xi
to be my engineer at this time.
You said if I wanted to advance to Formula A,
I needed support from a big company, right?
Jiang Yijun promised me before.
As long as I sign a contract with him,
he would provide me with the best conditions.
But Junda and Ruifeng are opponents.
If you really sign with Junda,
how do you want Mofei to save face?
Where did she put my face
when she bribed the drivers?
Make an appointment with Junda for a meeting.
Let's talk after seeing them.
Mr. Jiang.
Sir, everything is ready.
Just waiting for Chen Mobai to come and sign.
Mr. Liu.
I really want to know
how Chen Mofei is feeling now.
It's probably sourer
than eating five kilos of lemons.
Ruifeng's young master is coming
to drive for our Junda.
This news will attract lots of media.
We saved on advertising expenses.
Don't talk about him like he's something great.
This is not the key.
The key is Zhao Yingning of Weishi.
The reason why she chose
to continue to invest in Ruifeng
is for Chen Mobai's sake.
[You have a new message]
[Chen Mobai]
Giving you back your helmet.
Hoping it can comfort you
and give you the strongest support.
[Team Upgrade to Formula A Plan]
[Contents]
[Markus Racing Team Apartment, Germany]
Maria,
I've been invited
to a domestic racing conference.
Please book me a ticket home for next week.
Didn't I tell you not to…?
Morning.
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you
to take good care of your mom?
My mom's much better.
So I want to sort out your matters first.
What matters?
I've looked up the new information
on the Formula A.
[Formula B Record Table, Lu Yunhao, Junda Team]
I've formulated a promotion plan for the team.
Hope it can help you.
I mainly analyzed several aspects.
The first is cost.
It's much more than you budgeted.
Then technical support.
You need an entirely new engineering team
and a wind tunnel lab to build your car.
And sports injuries.
You have to have a professional fitness coach
to make a training plan.
You can check the other specific data later.
Overall,
joining a large car company like Ruifeng
is not the best choice,
but it's the only choice.
I accept your suggestion.
If I want to run Formula A,
large carmakers' support is indeed necessary.
So I'm considering joining Junda.
No way, you try to persuade him.
Anyway under no circumstances
should this be acceptable.
I'm not yet familiar with Junda's conditions.
But if they can offer
the same conditions as Ruifeng,
it's not ruled out.
Didn't you come for Mofei?
I can't just focus on my own task.
The important thing about choosing a team
is the driver's opinion.
Anyway, I'm strongly against this.
Alright.
Thanks for your proposal.
This matter
has been thoroughly resolved.
Your mission is over too.
Well,
let it be.
I'm off now.
Goodbye.
Chen Mobai wants to sign to Junda.
Should we try talking to him again?
There might be room for reversal.
He's done everything so ruthlessly.
He won't come back.
I know him.
He was like this before.
He's still the same now.
Am I a really terrible sister,
turning my own brother into an enemy?
No, he just has a lot of misunderstandings
about you.
Let's not talk about these things for now.
You haven't rested well for many days.
I'll take you home to sleep well.
I can't sleep at all.
I need to figure out how to face Zhao Yingning
and how to convince the directors.
Hello.
Miss Mofei, this is Duanmu Kuan.
Mr. Kuan, what's going on?
The multi-layered technology of the battery
has finally passed the electrochemical test
and achieved a stable structure.
That's great.
I shouldn't disturb you so late.
I just wanted to report to you.
Please come take a look tomorrow.
Okay, thank you for your hard work, Mr. Kuan.
Would you like to go over now and take a look?
I'll go prepare the car.
I know this is a big deal for you.
This one can do.
This one is not bad either. I like it.
Where's my necklace?
How many have you bought in the end?
Not many, not many.
Next time, I'll suggest auntie
to cancel your credit card.
I've tried it too.
I wanted to turn around and leave the mall.
But look at these clothes.
They are so beautiful.
They all have souls.
They seem to be softly calling out
"I need you."
By the way,
this outfit seems to suit you quite well.
After all, you now spend
your days with Chen Mobai.
Here's a small suggestion for you.
Nice clothes
can boost your love fortune.
Fortune is the Barnum effect.
It has no scientific basis.
It's merely a psychological hint
one gives oneself.
Besides, I'm not in a relationship.
I've stopped going to his place.
Why?
I was trying to persuade him
to go back to Ruifeng,
but it seems like he wants to go to Junda.
Junda?
Isn't that the mortal enemy of Ruifeng?
You didn't stop him?
This isn't like you.
Aren't you the one who never stops running
until the task is complete?
Robot, there's something wrong
with your programming.
For a driver,
hardware is indeed essential.
But so is the mental state.
If he finds it hard to go back to Ruifeng,
joining another team
might be a better choice.
You've been acting odd lately,
very odd indeed.
You've started caring about living things,
like this bean sprout,
like Chen Mobai's feelings.
And you claim you two aren't dating?
I don't care about his feelings.
As a competent engineer,
I should offer objective advice and analysis.
You just said you were an engineer?
I…
Great!
I'm glad to see
you're back to your normal state.
But I have to add,
every time Junda makes the trending news,
it's never for good reasons.
If Chen Mobai really intends
to go to that company,
I think you should warn him to be careful.
I see.
However, that's not the main point for tonight.
Tonight's main point is
I have sorted these clothes out for you.
Now I'm going to take them to your bedroom.
Please remember to wear them.
These are what I saved up and bought for you.
Don't let my intentions go in vain.
[Junda Automobile Group Limited]
Why are you here?
I still have some work to finish.
Don't you have anything else to do?
Your mission is complete. Please leave.
No way, I'm here to ensure your rights
are not violated.
You're not a lawyer. How can you ensure that?
Chen Mobai.
You've been following me to the same team.
You've run out of options?
Are you afraid that if I join your team,
your position isn't safe?
You've never grown up.
Still caring about this.
Don't tell me you really think
they see your potential.
You're just a gimmick.
Even being a gimmick
is better than not being worthy of even that.
You…
Mr. Mobai is here.
Yunhao,
you guys were from the same school.
Soon you'll become teammates.
You must be humble and get along well.
I have to be humble to Takano on the field.
Why should I be humble to him here?
Alright, come, this way please.
You've been dumped so soon.
Let's go.
Mr. Zhang, hello.
Mr. Mobai.
Didn't expect you to really come.
Bringing glory to Junda.
I'm honored.
Mr. Jiang, thank you for your invitation.
Don't call me Mr. Jiang. Call me Jun.
We are all buddies in the future.
I, Jiang Yijun, will definitely
not let my buddies down.
Okay, please come inside.
Excuse me, Miss.
This is our internal meeting at Junda.
Could you please step aside?
She is the friend
I brought intentionally today.
Isn't this the one
who helped you appeal last time?
She's from Ruifeng.
What's wrong with Ruifeng?
We, Junda, and Ruifeng are brother companies.
We are both fighting
for the cause of national cars.
No distinctions.
Come here.
[Driver's Contract]
I've read the contract. Everything else is fine.
There's only one thing I want to make clear.
Go ahead.
I'm all ears.
I see a clause in the contract,
saying that I must obey all team arrangements.
But I just want to drive.
I don't want to get involved with Ruifeng.
Don't worry, Mobai, what we value in our team
is your ability.
You don't have to worry about anything
unrelated to racing.
You just need to show
your strong ability on the track.
I have to be humble to Takano on the field.
Why should I be humble to him here?
I have a question.
Little girl,
what's your question?
It says in the contract
Chen Mobai needs to obey all team arrangements.
You have a deep cooperation with Takano.
So, will he need to cooperate tactically
with Takano
in future races?
Cooperation, what kind of cooperation?
That is,
is Chen Mobai,
as part of Takano's satellite team,
obligated to give way to Mitsui Taku to assist
for Junda's benefit during the race?
We are not a satellite team.
Our collaboration with Takano is comprehensive.
They make our cars run faster
and provide comprehensive cooperation…
Stop beating around the bush.
Answer her question directly.
Is there or isn't there?
Since it's a collaboration,
we'll analyze specific situations specifically.
Analyze what?
How to please Takano?
I, Chen Mobai, won't accept such clauses
which break the fairness of the race.
Racing isn't a tool for you
to do unfair trades.
Mobai, don't be angry.
If there is anything in the contract
that you are not satisfied with,
we can negotiate.
I really cherish talents.
Sorry, I can't join the Junda team.
Stop following me.
You can go back. Your work is over.
According to the plan I made for you before,
you are left with only the choice
to return to Ruifeng.
Let go.
Give me a moment.
Listen to me, okay?
First, let me go.
A girl holding a boy's hand on the street.
Is it something you should do?
I, I didn't mean that.
This is something a boy should do.
♫ The rose left fragrance ♫
♫ The sunset left glow ♫
♫ Your departure ♫
♫ Only left invisible wounds ♫
You said Shen Xi went with Mobai today?
Yes, it was Shen Xi who prevented Mobai
from going to Junda.
Wei, you relieve Mofei's worries.
I'll try to persuade him.
I know.
You really care about Mobai.
Jiang Wei, it's about time.
You have to tell me the truth.
On the day of the match,
did Mofei bribe the drivers?
Or is there a hidden story?
It's Mr. An.
Miss Mofei was afraid of making a fuss
without clarification.
Once it gets out that the seniors
at Ruifeng are fighting,
it will be more troublesome.
She didn't think
Mobai would believe her either.
I knew it.
Okay, leave the rest to me.
Mobai did not sign a contract with Junda.
It has always been a misunderstanding
between you siblings.
It's time
to explain to Mobai.
Those who understand
wouldn't need explanations.
Those who don't understand
wouldn't benefit from more explanations.
You and Mobai are exactly alike.
Stubborn.
It's Qingming Festival again.
Do you want to call him
to ask if he's coming back?
No need.
Just help me prepare the things.
I'm going back to work at Ruifeng tomorrow.
That's good.
Sorry about just now.
I think I ruined your contract signing.
How could it be?
If it weren't for your reminder,
I wouldn't have thought they'd go so low.
I absolutely won't cooperate with people
who don't respect fair competition.
Thank you for helping me make this judgment.
Did you decide not to sign with Junda today?
Nope.
I didn't really want to go back to Ruifeng.
If Junda is alright in all aspects,
why wouldn't I sign?
I don't know what plans you have next,
but you should hurry.
By the time you want
to enter the Super Grand Prix,
you may have missed your prime age.
Do you think I can enter the Super Grand Prix?
You won the Formula B championship.
As long as you can win the Formula A
championship for two consecutive years,
you will have enough points
and a chance to participate in the selection.
That's how my brother did it.
Your brother entered the Formula A
championship at the age of 19.
I'm still running in Formula B at 24.
Can that compare?
Age is important, but it's not absolute.
I don't think your skills are worse
than my brother's.
In some areas, you may be even better.
I didn't expect you to appreciate me so much.
That's why I urged you to return to Ruifeng.
I don't want to see you waste your talent.
But Chen Mofei is different from you.
Why do you say that?
In Chen Mofei's eyes,
everything has a clear price.
Keep what is valuable
and discard what is not.
She has always been like this.
She doesn't think
there's anything wrong with it.
I don't think Miss Mofei is like this.
Perhaps,
because of her position,
she's compelled to do certain things.
Since I joined Ruifeng,
the company has faced many difficulties.
But Miss Mofei is very persistent.
No matter how difficult,
she always delivers
the highest quality products.
People without dreams can't do this.
You're right.
Maybe it's a dream.
But after all, it's her dream.
She never took my dream into consideration.
She doesn't think I can drive well, either.
She doesn't think I have talent.
Even if she wants me to go back now,
it's only because she's forced to
by the circumstances.
Does Miss Mofei know
you think this way?
What difference does it make
whether she knows or not?
Nothing can change.
I don't care.
I don't think family members
should be like this.
If you have something to say,
you need to speak up in time.
When you have no opportunity,
you will regret it deeply.
Chen Mobai, did you hear what I said?
Before in the race,
the one who bribed others was not Mofei
but An Yunlong.
Why didn't she explain to me herself?
Chen Mobai, with your temper,
would you even listen if she explained?
I don't understand Mofei's issues.
I don't want to comment on the grudges
between you two, either.
But if you were misunderstood,
how would you feel
if Mofei unjustly scolded you in public?
This is the analysis Shen Xi
made for you before.
I don't think it's needed now. I'll discard it.
You dare?
[Team Upgrade to Formula A Plan]
I don't think your skills are worse
than my brother's.
There are even areas where you may be better.
That's why I urged you to return to Ruifeng.
I don't want to see you waste your talent.
Come in.
You're back. Come sit.
Still don't want to transfer?
I heard you were the one
who screwed up his thing with Junda.
He didn't really want to go to Junda.
Actually, if he doesn't join them,
he won't come back either.
What happened?
I wonder
what you were thinking
when you disbanded his racing team back then.
Have you heard
of the story of Icarus?
Yes, Greek mythology.
Icarus flew towards the sun
with wings made of wax.
Because the temperature was too high,
the wings melted.
In the end, he
fell down.
I've always thought
that for Chen Mobai, racing is like that sun.
He just has a pair of wax wings.
He's constantly chasing.
Maybe the previous races
gave him a lot of confidence.
Others also think he is very talented
and capable of flying high and far.
All I think is
one day he will lose those wings
and fall from a great height.
Have you ever thought
maybe
Chen Mobai is that sun?
There are times when problems are unsolvable.
We can change our approach to solving them.
Perhaps you can trust him more
and he can trust you more.
Understood.
If there's nothing else, you can leave first.
I'm working.
It was an accident.
Don't blame yourself too much
after all these years.
[Grave of Lu Xiaoye]
You can go back first.
I'm going to meet a friend.
It's evident
Mobai is much stronger than before.
It's been so many years.
Do you still plan to go on hiding it from him?
You've come to see my brother?
My mom is here too.
When I was nineteen,
Chen Mofei was driving
and had a car accident.
Doctor, how's my mom?
We've missed the best time for rescue.
If we could have arrived three minutes earlier,
there might have been a glimmer of hope.
[Linhai Go-Kart Speedway]
It must have been tough.
You asked me last time
what it was to leave no regrets.
I don't know how to make up
for the regrets of that day.
They say racing is a sport against time.
So every time
I will step on the accelerator regardless
to see
if I can regain those three minutes
or the results would be different.
Do you want me to drive you home?
I want to stay here a little longer.
Why haven't you left yet?
The car is broken.
Come to my place.
I'll give you a 20% discount.
I'll call a tow truck for you.
♫ The wind breathes quietly ♫
♫ The heart gradually silences ♫
♫ Your traces remain in my mind ♫
♫ I can't delete them ♫
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ Change the details bit by bit ♫
♫ Decide our fate
in every second of every minute ♫
♫ Just like the paradox of love ♫
♫ The synchronization of heartbeats ♫
♫ The surge of longing burns within ♫
♫ Waiting to find the answer at the end ♫
♫ Accelerating against the wind is your pride ♫
♫ And also my ultimate goal ♫