♫ Grip the steering wheel
in the roars that soar into the sky ♫
♫ And burn out the dreams ♫
♫ Have a confrontation of speed
with the courage to win ♫
♫ And see the silver lining in desperation ♫
♫ Always return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ And never step down in the dream of racing ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
fill up your tank with courage as fuel ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
♫ Eventually return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ The wind echoes, whistling the answer ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
cut the corner and beat all obstacles ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
[We Go Fast on Trust]
[Episode 11]
Miss Bi, what brings you here?
Well…
I need to come clean to Mr. Mobai about something.
It's about that…
I…
Before I…
You can tell me when you are ready.
I don't think Shen Xi caused that accident.
What do you mean?
I…
I previously helped to send data for her. I'm not sure if I left it behind.
Because of the car accident,
I only found it in my bag yesterday. No clue how it got there.
[Data]
Then, why are you only bringing this up now?
I was scared.
You're not scared now?
I am, but I can't just ignore my conscience.
I'm going to tell Miss Mofei in a moment and then resign.
Wait a minute.
Don't tell my sister about this yet.
[Game Record]
On the Test Day,
I'm going to use Shen Xi's data.
Are you sure? Your accident may be a misunderstanding.
But Shen Chuan did have an accident.
I don't want to doubt anyone, but you can't always rely on your gut feeling.
Should I go with the safe data from Mr. Liu and wait for defeat?
Then why didn't you tell Miss Mofei about this?
Her prejudice against Shen Xi is too deep,
so it's no use talking about it.
I'm not just going with my gut feeling here.
I've tested out Shen Xi's adjustments to the car,
and it's completely different from Mr. Liu's.
Achieve great success in one fell swoop.
Why don't I help her break all of her restraints?
She always gets stuck in her own traps.
This time, I'm going to tell her
that she's worth trusting,
not just for me, but for all of us.
I support Mobai and Xi.
I don't think there should be any problems with this data.
It seems that I can only use the famous racer Chen Mobai's motto from now on.
Your words have me
fired up!
Alright, what else is there to say?
- Let's do it.
- Let's go.
By the way, the issue of using Shen Xi's data
must be kept secret to the outside.
Ok.
[Even if the whole world doesn't believe you]
Mobai,
are there any issues?
You don't trust me?
It's not that, just in case…
What if it rains? What should we do then?
Why don't we reschedule it?
I've already notified everyone. Reporters are coming today.
Even if it rains acid, we have to do it.
Why don't we replace the rain tires in advance?
This way, although the speed is slower, it would be a lot safer.
When did you become such a fusspot?
The bystander is more concerned than the person concerned
Xu Gong, give me at the scene later.
Mobai, where are you going?
It's about to start.
What did I do wrong?
I can't watch Mr. Mobai test the car. I have to work overtime here.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Mobai,
are you free today?
Me?
Yes.
Would you mind finishing Shen Xi's record today?
Come with me.
Even though this is quite important,
does Chen Mobai have to call all the reporters?
It looks like Mr. Mobai is pretty confident.
To save his few people, he must have put in a lot of effort.
It sounds like Mr. An doesn't really want Chen Mobai to win.
On this point, I'm with Miss Zhao.
Professional matters should be left to professionals.
His rag-tag team should be replaced.
Are you worried about rain?
Murphy's Law.
This time, he's not just doing it for himself but for everyone.
So he will give it his all. Don't worry.
What?
Does Miss Mofei lack confidence today?
It depends. I believe in Chen Mobai's ability
but after all, but he's recently recovered from a big injury,
so I hope he takes care of himself
and does his best.
On the other hand, I think Miss Zhao
has a higher agenda for today's bet.
I am uncertain for a moment what Miss Mofei just said
was a compliment or a tease.
For a professional investor,
the value of perspective and business reputation
far outweighs that of money.
If Mobai loses this match,
you win the right to change people but lose the ability to judge people.
This is certainly not what you want.
So…
You hope to lose this bet more than I do,
so it can give Ruifeng a build-up.
If you put it that way, what I thought was a win-win situation for me
is now actually a win-win for you.
I'm in a lose-lose situation, right?
This is a win-win situation, Miss Zhao. Our goals
have always been the same from the beginning.
Why did you bring me here?
You just stand here and watch me test-drive.
You must watch my test-drive.
The data I'm using today is yours.
I will let everyone know who you are.
Mobai.
Mobai, hurry up and pack before it rains.
I have to go. You won't be discovered here.
Wait for me. Wait for me here.
Don't worry.
I have faith in the car you designed.
No. Chen Mobai.
Sorry, you can't get in.
We are clearing the area.
You can't get in now. The test-drive will start soon
Please wait outside.
Dear race fans,
we are reporting at the racer
Chen Mobai's preseason test.
We will provide you with the live stream
and commentary.
Now you can see Chen Mobai
gradually approaching the race car,
looking calm.
This is his first public racing event after being injured.
How he will perform today remains to be seen. Let's wait and see.
Mobai.
Let's go.
I want to tell everyone that
you are the engineer
who gives me the fastest speed.
♫ Soar into the sky ♫
♫ And burn out the dreams ♫
♫ Have a confrontation of speed ♫
♫ With the courage to win ♫
♫ And see the silver lining in desperation ♫
Chen Mobai has set off.
A beautiful acceleration state. Very good.
This preseason testing is very important
to him.
He is about to make his debut
on the Formula A stage.
After being injured before, it makes his style bolder.
We seem to have seen a great Race God with a determination to win.
His opponent Mitsui Taku's speed up
must have put a lot of pressure on him.
This also became his strong motivation.
Mobai,
one minute thirty-two seconds three-six-five.
The weather is getting gloomy.
Rain can put a lot of psychological pressure
on the racer,
but Chen Mobai's condition
has not been affected.
♫ Fight for a race of a lifetime ♫
One minute thirty-three seconds one-two-zero.
Again.
♫ And see the silver lining in desperation ♫
♫ Always return with glory ♫
♫ And the heat of life ♫
♫ And never step down ♫
♫ In the dream of racing ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance ♫
Thirty-one seconds.
One minute thirty-one seconds
seven-seven-eight.
Mobai, you got in thirty-one seconds.
That's good enough.
You are short by 0.1 second.
Let's do it again.
[Data Form]
♫ And go beyond the limit like a flash of light ♫
Hello, Mr. Liu.
Why are your data different from mine? What are you guys doing?
I'll explain to you later. We used other data this time.
What's going on?
Miss Mofei, the team's debugging data is different
from mine.
It seems to be another one.
I knew he wouldn't give up that easily.
Once it rains,
the racer must change to rain tires.
But Chen Mobai shows no signs of stopping.
Ask him to stop the car.
Ask him to stop the car now. It's raining.
He hung up.
Mobai, it's about to rain.
Mobai, you didn't change your rain tires.
You can't drive anymore.
Yeah, you can't drive in the rain, right?
Mobai, you better come back.
Even if the whole world doesn't believe you,
I believe you.
I'll prove the rest.
Only two timing points left.
I must break the record of Mitsui Taku.
Chen Mobai chose to continue.
The situation has become dangerous.
In the last hundred meters,
Chen Mobai started his final sprint.
What happened?
The car started to skid.
Chen Mobai ended the preseason test in an unexpected way.
One minute and thirty seconds nine-nine-seven.
Chen Mobai broke the record.
Let's congratulate him.
Mr. Mobai is really amazing.
Stop.
The data he used today is yours?
I'm sorry.
You've harmed your brother.
Don't mess with my brother anymore.
- Mobai is really something.
- Do you know how fast you were?
- Chubby, you tell him.
- One minute thirty seconds nine-nine-seven.
You broke Mitsui's record in an instant.
Bad news.
If there's anything else,
we'll talk about it later. Where's Shen Xi?
It's about Shen Xi and Miss Mofei.
What happened?
Miss Mofei slapped Shen Xi.
I'm afraid she might have an accident
because she doesn't seem alright.
- Where is she now?
- She's gone.
Don't think that just because I let you race, you can do whatever you want.
Go and get him back quickly.
Here.
Jiang Wei.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
[Duanmu Kuan]
Hello, Mr. Kuan.
Are you sure?
I'll be right at the lab.
Miss Zhao, I'm really sorry.
There were a few small mistakes
in our management.
We will definitely strengthen our management
in the future.
I only care about the numbers.
Today's result is even better than I expected.
I have nothing to say.
He didn't answer.
Yang, Mobai will be alright, right?
Don't talk nonsense.
Well, that's hard to say.
Beautiful women's town is the hero's tomb.
Tomb? What tomb? Shut your mouth.
Come with me to look for him.
You've harmed your brother.
Don't mess with my brother anymore.
Mr. Kuan.
Ruifeng Battery Lab
We've been working on the Maituo battery for long.
What if it still doesn't work this time?
Then I should resign.
Same.
What do you mean?
It means my choice is wrong.
I am not worthy to steer this ship
of Ruifeng anymore.
Miss Mofei.
What's going on, Miss Mofei?
Check why the alarm is going off.
This is a safety test warning.
The yellow light is classified as level C,
which indicates that all kinds of data have become unstable.
If the experiment continues to escalate,
all the systems of the batteries will exceed the safety value.
Then, there will be a level A warning.
The red light will be on.
Declaring this time's experiment a failure.
Mr. Kuan, about this yellow light…
[Data Monitoring]
Alright, Mr. Kuan.
Run the experiment results again.
Adjust the parameters.
This time, we can't have another yellow light.
[Data Monitoring]
[Loop Testing Completed]
We made it. It worked.
Miss Mofei, we made it.
Our lithium-ion battery is a success.
Mr. Kuan.
Mr. Kuan, thank you for your effort.
Thank you, Miss Mofei.
Everything today is due to your persistence.
Thank you, everyone.
Everyone has been working hard
for such a long time.
Have some hot tea to warm up.
Don't catch a cold.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
When Mobai heard that you left, he went to look for you.
I called him, but his phone was switched off.
Did he contact you?
No.
I… I want to apologize to you
on behalf of Miss Mofei.
No matter what, she should not have hit you.
I'm sorry.
But, she was so agitated
for a reason.
You probably don't know.
For so many years.
Mobai has never driven in the rain.
Even if there's a race, he would quit.
Because on the day his mother had a car accident,
it was raining.
Right now,
he should be looking for you in the heavy rain.
I'm not worth him doing this for me.
He thinks you're worth it.
Excuse me, I need to leave.
Shen Xi.
Have you ever heard, 'To help others is to help oneself'?
Helping is reciprocal.
Giving others a chance is also
giving yourself a chance.
Are you a snail?
Do you have to carry such heavy things
for yourself?
You just stand here and watch me test-drive.
You must watch my test-drive.
I will let everyone know who you are.
He thinks you're worth it.
Right now,
he should be looking for you in the heavy rain.
Today, this season's Formula B champion,
Chen Mobai,
set new records in all three timing stages on the Linhai practice track,
breaking the single-lap record previously set
by Mitsui Taku,
which greatly encouraged
the domestic racing community.
The last person to bring us such a surprise was
[Racer Chen Mobai]
Shen Chuan before him.
Chen Mobai and Mitsui Taku.
One newcomer. One veteran.
Who can win the upcoming Formula A championship?
It's indeed something to look forward to.
♫ The wind breathes quietly ♫
♫ The heart gradually silences ♫
♫ Your traces remain in my mind ♫
♫ I can't delete them ♫
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ I would like to help you race fast ♫
Stop. Stop the car. Are they there?
- Yes. Yes. It's him.
- It's him.
Where? Let me have a look.
All right. All right. Let's go. Hurry up.
If he finds us, we're so dead.
Let's go.
♫ The wind is howling at high speed
near my ear ♫
♫ The love in my heart is tormented
in memories ♫
♫ Accelerating against the wind ♫
♫ Is your pride ♫
♫ And also ♫
♫ My prayer for your safety ♫
Does it hurt?
♫ The rose leaves a fragrance ♫
♫ The setting sun radiates light ♫
♫ Your departure ♫
♫ Only left a transparent wound ♫
♫ I keep falling ♫
♫ Towards the direction you left ♫
♫ I'm embracing the fragments of memory ♫
I… It seems like it's
the first time I see you dress like this.
I just suddenly feel like wearing a dress.
♫ Come back, my love ♫
♫ In the sea of life, you are the only light ♫
You look very beautiful.
♫ Being scratched by the fragments of memory ♫
♫ Come back, my love ♫
♫ In the sea of life, you are the only light ♫
♫ Don't leave me in the endless night ♫
I caused you to get injured before.
Why did you still believe in me so much?
My trust in you has never once changed.
You know what?
The accident last time was due to an issue with the car parameters.
When you asked your coworker
to send the documents, she lost the data.
It's not your fault.
She also admitted her mistake to me,
but I feel like it's useless to
make a big fuss about it.
It's better to show everyone the results
directly.
You are the engineer who suits me the best.
I'm not a qualified engineer.
At that time, my brother--
You know
racing in itself is a contest between
control and losing control,
so no matter what happens,
any unexpected event, any accident,
it's nobody's fault.
Can you not put so much pressure on yourself?
If everything I do
can make you believe that you're worth it,
even just a little bit, even a bit is enough, Shen Xi.
I think you should
restore your timeline
to a normal life, like that of a sprout,
so that those who care about you won't feel sad.
Shen Xi, you can be upset with the world,
but I hope that you must believe
you deserve all the best.
Give me your hand.
I made it.
We made the lithium-ion battery.
There were countless times
that I dreamed about this moment.
I was crying, laughing,
screaming,
smashing your car,
but I really didn't think
I would feel like this now.
I'm happy for you.
Actually, I've never known if
what I have been insisting on is it right or wrong.
It's right.
Because you have courage.
You have the courage to do
what others dare not do,
so I know you will definitely succeed.
Your whole family is like this.
The chairman, Mobai,
and you.
It's hot.
Slow down.
Can't you eat something nutritious?
There are meat and vegetables.
There are all kinds of stuff.
How can it not be nutritious?
How is Chen Mobai?
Hao Yang just called and said he has found him.
You…
I know I shouldn't have hit her.
I wanted to ask
are you okay.
I know
you are protecting Mobai in your own way.
Maybe we are all protecting the ones
we want to protect in our own way.
I'll leave now.
Think more about the engineer thing.
I'll wait for your reply.
Don't forget to dry your hair
when you get home.
Don't catch a cold.
Okay. See you.
You're back.
Why are you here?
My dorm at school is lights-out,
but I haven't finished my homework yet,
so I came to cram at the last minute.
Wait a minute.
Where did you get this dress from?
Cute dress.
You finally realized it. Not bad.
What are you talking about?
I got wet from a sudden heavy rain,
so I just bought one randomly.
It sounds like a long story,
but I have time.
I can spare a bit to listen.
Go ahead and tell me.
If there was a person,
he was supposed to do something to you,
but he didn't.
Why?
Hold on. Wait a minute.
You've confused me.
Who was supposed to do what to you?
It's just
there was a person who was very close to me.
I thought
he was going to kiss me, but he didn't.
What an idiot.
What idiot?
Chen Mobai's brain isn't working.
That day, he bought you a lot of breakfast.
I thought he was good at it.
He must be a veteran in love.
Who knows he is such an idiot?
It seems like I need to reassess him.
What breakfast?
I didn't say it was Chen Mobai.
if it's not Chen Mobai,
then who else can it be?
At this point,
I really don't know what's going on
in Chen Mobai's brain.
What could be more important than love?
What love?
Love-love.
The romantic type.
He just wanted me to be his engineer.
We're not in that kind of relationship
Whether you're in that kind of relationship
right now is not important.
What's important is
what kind of relationship you want it to be.
We are just friends.
Friends?
Then let me ask you.
If you two were alone,
would you feel nervous?
Or if you two
had physical contact,
would you feel butterflies?
No, I wouldn't. I wouldn't be nervous.
My heart beats normally.
How come?
Don't lie to me. Tell the truth.
I'm telling the truth.
You better get back to your homework.
Don't lie to me.
If you don't explain things clearly to me,
how am I supposed to help you on this?
Does it hurt?
My trust in you has never changed.
I think you should restore your timeline
to a normal life,
like that of a sprout,
so that those who care about you
won't feel sad.
♫ The wind breathes quietly ♫
♫ The heart gradually silences ♫
♫ Your traces remain in my mind ♫
♫ I can't delete them ♫
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ Change the details bit by bit ♫
♫ Decide our fate
in every second of every minute ♫
♫ Just like the paradox of love ♫
♫ The synchronization of heartbeats ♫
♫ The surge of longing burns within ♫
♫ Waiting to find the answer at the end ♫
♫ Accelerating against the wind is your pride ♫
♫ And also my ultimate goal ♫