♫ Grip the steering wheel
in the roars that soar into the sky ♫
♫ And burn out the dreams ♫
♫ Have a confrontation of speed
with the courage to win ♫
♫ And see the silver lining in desperation ♫
♫ Always return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ And never step down in the dream of racing ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
fill up your tank with courage as fuel ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
♫ Eventually return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ The wind echoes, whistling the answer ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
cut the corner and beat all obstacles ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
[We Go Fast on Trust]
[Episode 18]
Yesterday,
did I confess my feelings?
Did she say yes?
I don't think so. But she didn't say no.
Where's Yang?
Wasn't he drinking with us last night?
Do you feel like something was missing
when you woke up this morning?
Something does seem to be missing.
Mobai?
And Xi?
I was wondering
where they were last night.
Could they have snuck out
to celebrate on their own?
Not likely.
When I was half-asleep last night,
I saw Xi leaving by herself.
She left by herself?
But it might have been my mistake
since I drank too much.
Leaving by herself…
Yang.
You're all here.
What's up?
Playing games.
Yang, weren't you supposed
to drop off Miss Zhao last night?
Why are you just getting back?
Well…
It's not your business.
Don't you three start slacking off
just because you won the game.
Have you completed the task
that Dr. Shen assigned to you?
Speaking of whom,
did you see Mobai and Xi last night?
I didn't, why?
They've been missing since last night.
Just give them a call.
[Chen Mobai]
Try Xi then.
[Shen Xi]
Wait, why aren't they picking up the phone?
Hello.
Okay, got it. I see.
I know where he is now. Wait for me.
Yang…
[Wish You A Safe Journey]
How do you think I should react right now?
Wishing you a safe journey
or begging you to stay?
Wish me a safe journey.
I wish you a safe journey.
I bought you some ice cream.
I remember back in Markus,
every time you had ice cream,
it made you happy.
At that time, Chuan would say it has
no nutrients and wouldn't let you have it.
So the two of us
would sneak out for it.
Do you want me to call Chen Mobai?
No, thanks.
I'm fine.
So, what are your plans now?
I know it's not quite the right timing,
and you've said no once.
But would you like to reconsider coming back
to Markus with me?
Think of it as a short leave from here.
It'll be good for you and him.
Have some water.
Did you say he's been like this since morning?
Yep. Luckily, I'm familiar with the staff here.
They noticed he wasn't training properly
and got worried.
So they immediately called me here.
What about Shen Xi?
I've been calling her all day,
and she hardly answered.
Then she told me she was going back to Markus,
leaving the day after tomorrow.
Why so sudden?
I don't know.
They are the same. They won't say anything.
Chen Mobai, when will you stop running?
Just tell us what happened.
Take a rest.
If you don't want Shen Xi to leave,
you should stop her.
Why are you torturing yourself here?
Yes, if there's any misunderstanding,
you should explain it to her properly.
What if she leaves and never comes back?
She won't.
This is not the time to be stubborn.
Aren't you the demon king that can't stop
once you enter the field?
What happened? Don't you even
dare to stop or chase after her?
I won't.
I respect her choice.
She's leaving on an early flight
the day after tomorrow.
Don't blame me for not telling you.
♫ The wind breathes quietly ♫
♫ The heart gradually silences ♫
♫ Your traces remain in my mind ♫
♫ I can't delete them ♫
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ I would like to help you race fast ♫
[You can speed up your life once in a while]
♫ And hope that all is well with you ♫
♫ Love is a paradox ♫
♫ The synchronization of heartbeats ♫
♫ The wind is howling at high speed
near my ear ♫
♫ The love in my heart is tormented
in memories ♫
♫ Accelerating against the wind ♫
♫ Is your pride ♫
♫ And also ♫
♫ My prayer for your safety ♫
With the recent sudden halt
of the promotional campaign
in various Junda stores,
this price war unilaterally started
by Junda company has ended.
Next, let's focus on the overseas information.
Our promotion plan was very successful.
According to the Marketing Dept.,
sales of all products have increased,
and the pre-sales performance
of Maituo is especially good.
After all these years,
your hard work finally paid off.
Help me keep an eye on the workshop.
We must be extra cautious at this time.
Not a single mistake is allowed.
The Race Team made a great contribution.
One more thing.
I don't know if you've heard.
What?
Shen Xi decided to leave Ruifeng
and return to Markus.
Would Chen Mobai agree?
I heard that Mobai did not object.
Do we need to intervene?
Everyone has the right to make choices.
If one wants to leave,
and the other does not stop her.
What can we do?
Has she handed over all her work?
Shen Xi has handed over all her work files
to Engineer Liu.
Well, help me keep an eye on Chen Mobai then.
That's all we can do.
Are you ready?
Xi.
Little master, are you really leaving?
Without you, I have no confidence.
Remember what I told you
about improving assembly precision.
and don't forget the theoretical knowledge.
You'll be fine. You can do it.
But without you, I…
Shen Xi, we all hate to see you go,
but we're all happy
that you can return to Markus, right?
Don't worry. We will work harder in the future.
Your future achievements
will be better and better.
Xi,
if you miss us, come back to visit us.
The Skyfall Team is always your home.
Sis, if you get bullied outside,
come back and we will stand up for you.
Alright, enough with the mushy comments.
It's used.
We should get going.
Okay.
Allow me, Xi.
Thank you.
Where is Mobai?
I don't have much to say.
Have a safe journey.
See you when fate allows.
See you.
We really need to get going.
I'll come back to visit you when I have time.
Do you want to wait for him?
No, let's go.
[Markus Asian Special Task Force, Shanghai]
[Shanghai Special Task Force]
Hi, Nick.
Dr. Shen.
Welcome back, it's been a long time.
Good to see you.
Shaoqian, good to see you.
Nick. It's good to see you too.
Please, follow me.
You two and Shen Chuan have been
waiting for this day for too long.
So as an apology from Markus,
things will get back on track
as soon as possible.
This is our special racing training program.
We made it to select the best racers.
[Markus Shanghai Special Training Camp Program]
The best car deserves the best racer.
Right?
Wings of Wind?
Yes, Wings of Wind.
That's our gift for your return with Markus.
We have decided to rebuild the car
with the highest standards.
And your revolutionary Air kit designs
will be integrated.
This time,
Wings of Wind, I believe, will become
a legendary car in the history of Markus.
And of course,
its complex new features
will put high pressure on the driver's ability.
That is why we have created
this special training program
to find, together, the most suitable person
to drive Wings of Wind.
Thank you, Nick.
Don't thank me.
It's your persistence
that has been my motivation.
Please take this as the solemn apology
of Markus and of myself
to Shen Chuan, may he rest in peace,
and to you, Shen Xi.
Thank you, Nick.
Please, dear Mr. Chen.
Why are you still practicing here
in the middle of the night?
I'm not tired. I'll practice a little more.
You can go to sleep first.
The next stop is in a few days.
You need to get your head in the game.
My head is in the game.
Anyway, don't be too hard on yourself.
Good night,
[Gift from Wang Duobao]
Congratulations to Chen Mobai
of Ruifeng Race Team
for winning the championship
of the substation race again.
Well, this should be
his sixth championship after Linhai stop.
[Chen Mobai won three consecutive championships]
Let us sincerely congratulate him.
Good, you're getting more accurate.
His recent performance is so good,
achieving three consecutive championships.
But why is Mobai frowning all day long?
I got up to pee last night.
And I saw Mobai go out at midnight
and didn't come back until morning.
How did he become this way recently?
You're having fun with Engineer Liu every day.
How would you understand
the pain of us who are longing for someone?
Mobai trains during the day
and doesn't sleep at night.
Can his body hold up?
I don't know where he goes every day.
Chen Mobai.
Thank you.
So you would stay with me
until the Super Grand Prix?
Xi.
I knew you were up.
This is the list of the Special Training Camp.
Thank you.
Their resumes and rankings
for this season are attached in the back.
Thank you.
[Resume of Chen Mobai]
His recent performance is very good.
And he's also been stable.
He has also earned back many
of the points he lost before.
Do you think he will come?
[Lu Yunhao's Resume]
If he meets the criteria,
we will send him an invitation.
Whether he comes is up to him.
- Xi, actually…
- Don't worry.
Now that I'm back at Markus,
I will do my job well.
Okay.
Good night, then.
Good night.
- See you tomorrow
- See you tomorrow.
Yang, Mobai.
What's got you all excited?
Markus! It's an invitation from Markus.
Markus?
Mobai.
I really didn't expect
such a good thing to happen.
Markus's invitation.
This is a rocket.
Direct access to the Super Grand Prix
and driving Wings of Wind.
Okay, you go up first.
I need to talk to Mobai.
Go on.
[Invitation Letter for Chen Mobai]
Are you going?
I don't know.
You've been training
day and night like crazy recently.
Isn't it to get into the Super Grand Prix?
Shen Xi is in this training camp,
and you're afraid to face her, right?
I don't know what happened between you two,
but if you're both doing the best
for each other,
you should be more rational
and do what's right.
Yang, Engineer Liu is coming soon.
Didn't you just say that you wanted
to hold a summary meeting?
Okay, I got it, get ready first.
Think it over before you make a choice.
Think hard.
It's time to unwrap the gift.
Ready?
Let's go.
It looks the same as before.
This is your gift to the racing world.
How is the registration of the contestants?
Basically, everyone who has received
an invitation has registered,
except for Chen Mobai.
Do I need to call him and find out?
No.
There's not much we can do
if he doesn't want to come.
If he doesn't come,
wouldn't you feel pitiful?
No matter what, we choose our own paths.
Just let it be.
A great man once said,
the road is tortuous, but the future is bright.
The first half of the season is over,
and our results were very satisfying.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, cheers.
Come on.
Here,
we need especially thank someone.
[Mid-Season Summary]
A hero who took up the challenge without fear
and saved us from a predicament.
We'll have Mobai thank her in person.
There's no suspense. It's Engineer Liu.
It's normal. It's what I should do.
Let's not get emotional.
Don't be modest.
Your data is so beautifully done.
Not only was it quick,
but it was also very suitable for Mobai.
It matches the international standard,
accurate and ruthless.
I can be sure
you're not just seeing an engineer
through the eyes of a lover.
She really has achieved…
- Don't mess with me.
- Dr. Shen's standard.
If Engineer Liu wasn't here,
I would think that this data is just
from Dr. Shen.
Engineer Liu, why are you sweating
while drinking Cola?
I'm not. No.
We're all so familiar now, right?
Hearing compliments like this
makes me self-conscious.
We are all family. Just be casual.
Not only should there be compliments,
but there should also be rewards.
Engineer Liu, tell me what you want.
I will pay for it personally.
That's not what I meant.
If anything, you should buy it for Shen Xi.
What I mean is that…
Shen Xi has built a great foundation
in the early stages.
Yes, exactly, a round of applause.
Good. Impressive.
Very good.
This meeting is so good.
I have to go. There's a thing.
Who bought this? It's amazing.
Off I go now.
Qianqian, are you leaving so soon?
Engineer Liu.
[SKYFALL Auto Parts]
Why are you leaving so soon?
Hao Yang grew two watermelons
on the rooftop. Take them with you.
Ah…
You haven't eaten, have you?
How about we have a meal together? Let's go.
No, no.
I must hurry back home.
No, I have to treat you to a meal.
You've put in so much effort for me.
I have to reward you properly.
You can't get something for nothing.
I see.
Watermelons and meals are too cheap.
How about we go and buy a gold necklace?
No, what are you doing?
Can you just let me go?
Fine.
I can let you go.
Tell me the truth.
What did you want to say
about Shen Xi just now?
It's okay.
If you don't want to say it, I won't force you.
I'll pretend that I don't know.
In the future,
these guys and I
will treat you as our goddess
every day like today.
It doesn't matter. You are our only goddess.
No.
Why would you two drag me into your quarrel?
One won't let me talk no matter what,
and the other will torture me to death
if I don't speak.
I'm very innocent, sir.
Just tell me what's going on.
You can see for yourself.
[Shen Xi]
Engineer Liu, this is the latest modified data. Thanks.
So,
all this data was sent to you by Shen Xi.
After she left,
she asked me to come over here as an engineer.
But she was worried that I wouldn't
be able to adapt to your style,
so after I finished the data each time,
she would take it
and modify it carefully again.
Look at her.
She's really hard-working.
Busy with the camp during the day,
and she has to worry
about these things for you at night.
Every time I receive her call at midnight,
she always sounds exhausted.
It's quite sad.
Good luck and see ya.
Looking for me?
Chen Mobai, why have you become so long-winded?
No, I haven't.
Why are you looking for me?
Do you think I want to?
If it wasn't for Hao Yang
constantly nagging me,
saying that Mobai is in a bad mood,
Mobai is not in good condition,
Mobai wants someone to chat with him,
I couldn't be bothered to deal with you.
Boss, is my skewer ready?
It's ready. Here it comes.
What's the point of drinking alone?
Let me join you.
Engineer Liu told me today…
that the data for these few stops
was all from Shen Xi.
Can you guess how I felt when I heard that?
What else could you feel? Happy, right?
It means she's still thinking of you.
I was very confused.
Very confused.
I don't know what to make of her help.
I also felt very guilty
because I just watched her
worrying about me every day
and staying up late for me.
I don't want that.
You just can't get over your pride.
If you're in pain, go find her.
You know I won't do that.
If you want to see her, go see her.
Solve the problem if there is any.
Easy for you to say. I think you
called me here this time
just to deliberately sprinkle
chili powder on my wound.
This is what I call
fighting poison with poison.
Prick you a few times and let you bleed,
maybe then you'll be okay.
Do you think it's because
I don't want to see her?
It's that I can't.
I hate it when people do that.
You can't even bear to get
a little mud on your legs,
and yet you talk about running
toward each other.
I just want to remind you,
that if one solution doesn't work,
don't be stubborn about it.
Find another way to go around it.
Like?
Like me, I wanted to be with you.
I tried, I went for it,
but it didn't work, so I gave up.
I am now formally notifying you,
that I, Zhao Yingning,
am giving up on you, Chen Mobai.
It's just like investing.
Knowing when to cut loss
is much wiser than indefinitely investing.
That's you.
Yes, it's me.
But we can only be ourselves,
and when we encounter problems, we can only use
our own ways to solve them.
Don't get stuck in the other person's logic.
Besides, love is not
about you becoming me and me becoming you.
You're still you, and I'm still me,
but together, we become "us".
My own way…
But there's only one standard.
When making choices,
make the one you won't regret.
How's the progress on Maituo recently?
You guys talk. I'll go get the medicine.
Okay.
Dad, in terms of the production line,
the parts suppliers are all caught up.
They're working overtime for production.
The number of pre-sale orders
has far surpassed expectations.
We must remind the factory
the more tense the situation, the more
attention must be paid to production safety.
I have reminded them many times.
For so many years,
thanks to your persistence,
Maituo caused a phenomenal stir
as soon as it was launched.
Well, it's also thanks to Mobai.
His Formula A performance was very good,
attracting more attention to Ruifeng.
It seems that your relationship
has improved a lot.
Mobai has grown up
and become more mature.
Right?
Everything is getting better.
Come on.
[Markus Asian Special Task Force, Shanghai]
Welcome to Markus's Special Training Camp.
I am your examiner, Shen Xi.
All of you are very outstanding drivers
of this Formula A season.
In the next few days,
we will have stricter demands
for your physical and racing skills.
Good luck, everyone.
- Excuse me.
- I am also an invited driver.
We don't allow entry here.
This is a private territory.
Your entry is not allowed here.
This is a closed training camp.
- Unrelated personnel are not allowed to enter.
- What unrelated personnel?
I am not unrelated personnel.
- Please understand.
- I must come to this training camp. If not,
- how will you select the best driver?
- Sir.
It's not my loss. It's Markus's loss.
- Do you understand?
- Sir.
- Don't stop me.
- You can't go any further.
- Reporting. I'm here.
♫ The wind breathes quietly ♫
♫ The heart gradually silences ♫
♫ Your traces remain in my mind ♫
♫ I can't delete them ♫
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ Change the details bit by bit ♫
♫ Decide our fate
in every second of every minute ♫
♫ Just like the paradox of love ♫
♫ The synchronization of heartbeats ♫
♫ The surge of longing burns within ♫
♫ Waiting to find the answer at the end ♫
♫ Accelerating against the wind is your pride ♫
♫ And also my ultimate goal ♫