♫ Grip the steering wheel
in the roars that soar into the sky ♫
♫ And burn out the dreams ♫
♫ Have a confrontation of speed
with the courage to win ♫
♫ And see the silver lining in desperation ♫
♫ Always return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ And never step down in the dream of racing ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
fill up your tank with courage as fuel ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
♫ Eventually return with glory
and the heat of life ♫
♫ The wind echoes, whistling the answer ♫
♫ In a triumphant stance,
cut the corner and beat all obstacles ♫
♫ And go beyond the limit
like a flash of light ♫
[We Go Fast on Trust]
[Episode 12]
Does it hurt?
Never has my trust in you changed,
not even once.
I feel like you should be
like that green bean sprout.
Revert your timeline
back into a normal living routine
so that those of us who care about you
won't be upset.
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ I would like to help you race fast ♫
[Please, Engineer]
♫ And hope that all is well with you ♫
♫ Love is a paradox ♫
♫ The synchronization of heartbeats ♫
♫ The wind is howling at high speed
near my ear ♫
♫ The love in my heart is tormented
in memories ♫
Are you sick?
You're haunted.
You're the haunted one.
Go ahead, speak.
What's going on with you and Shen Xi?
What's going on with us?
Aren't we looking for an engineer?
Why did you kiss her?
You were stalking me.
That's because I care about you.
I went to find you, then…
You, you're talking nonsense. I didn't.
I didn't do anything.
What?
Why? Don't you like her?
All of that was to get her to be our engineer.
Then prepare for Formula A together.
Stop.
Chen Mobai, let me ask you.
With all that you've done,
is it because of her,
Dr. Shen, who is suitable to be your engineer?
Or is it because of Shen Xi,
the person you like?
Of course, it should be Dr. Shen.
Is that true or false?
Only certain people would know.
Go to sleep.
Sleep early.
Don't.
Fine, you later pass these
data you've sort out on. Go ahead.
Want to know the answer? Isn't that easy?
Just call.
What do you know?
You can't disturb her at this time.
You should let her think clearly.
Are you afraid to call?
Who said I was afraid?
Answer it, what are you waiting for?
You are the team manager, you answer it.
Even the Demon King is scared sometimes.
Hello.
OK, got it.
What's wrong?
Now you really don't have to think about it.
What?
Qiao Na notified us something.
Shen Xi was dismissed
by the admin department today.
It was decided by Mofei.
She has also arranged a new engineer for you.
He is in the outside.
Don't be in a rush, take it easy.
What's going on?
On what grounds does Chen Mofei dismiss people?
I haven't even settled the score
for hitting people with her.
Now she's dismissing an employee.
All decisions were made by me.
Let her come to me by herself.
Miss Mofei was impulsive.
She has already apologized to Shen Xi.
Is the apology useful?
Mobai, just calm down.
Let's meet the new engineer
who just joined the team.
I don't need to know him.
Tell the new engineer
I have a bad temper. He will leave
sooner or later if he comes.
Let him leave early now.
Or let's meet first.
I don't need to see him.
I won't see him if I say no.
Then don't regret it.
I won't regret it.
Miss Shen,
let's go.
No, wait, wait, who did you say?
You said you wouldn't regret it.
I just don't want anyone to use my data
behind my back.
Starting from today,
Dr. Shen leaves the admin department
and joins the team as an engineer.
Pleased to work together.
Please,
Miss Shen.
Very sorry.
You had to make a trip here.
No, this is important.
I heard the new car Maituo of Ruifeng
that will be listed
used Thrustion battery.
This is
epoch-making technology.
Ruifeng takes the lead in this field.
That's an unprecedented crisis for us.
Seems like we can't stop Ruifeng.
No, there is a way.
What method?
It's Ruifeng's first time participating
in the Formula A tournament
starting next month.
It gives us
a chance to hit them head on.
We need to break their momentum
and delay their development.
But I heard that in Ruifeng Race Team's
pre-season testing a few days ago,
their driver, Chen Mobai,
beat Mitsui's record on that track.
Our two teams were friends.
We can teach them a lesson on the racetrack.
Mr. Hideo, don't worry.
We will fully cooperate with Mitsui.
I heard that Lin Shaoqian of Markus
was also in Linhai.
If we can invite him to train us
as a special guide for our two teams,
Mitsui
will not let everyone down.
Come on, cheers.
[Chen Mobai's Work Plan]
[Team Member's Work Plan]
[Shen Xi]
Shaoqian, there's something I should tell you.
I have agreed to be the engineer
of the Ruifeng Race Team.
[XXXXX]
[Lin Shaoqian]
That's great, I'm happy for you.
Hurry up, stand up straight, stand up straight.
Three, two, one.
Miss Shen, good morning!
Good morning, everyone.
This is the new work schedule I have set up.
We will strictly follow it from now on.
[Xu Gong's Work Plan]
[Hou Jian's Work Plan]
You deserve to be Dr. Shen.
What about mine?
This one is yours.
[30-day Training Schedule
for the Formula A Championship]
Do I still need a baseline evaluation?
Don't you need it?
Do I need it?
What baseline can you evaluate from me?
Are you dressed like this to jog with me?
Our goal today is fifteen kilometers.
If you feel too tired,
we can reduce the distance.
Tired?
Let me tell you.
As long as you're running with me,
I can go around the earth without panting.
Do you know how many kilometers
it is to go around the earth?
A lot of kilometers.
It's 40076 kilometers.
If it's a Super Grand Prix race,
it's 70 laps of 350 kilometers.
It's equivalent to 8,000 laps.
My engineer is really
a living encyclopedia.
Fifteen kilometers is indeed too short for you.
So run the extra miles of the earth first.
76 kilometers, okay?
Okay, as long as you can catch up with me,
you can add as much as you want.
Is that what you said?
That's what I said.
I've caught up with you.
I'll add another five kilometers.
You really say to add and just add, huh?
I want to see where your endurance
limit lies.
Speed up,
or I'll add two more sandbags.
Are we also practicing swimming here?
The pool is too small.
This is not a practice. It's for you to relax.
Do you want to undress?
No, no, not really.
It's not appropriate during the day, is it?
Whatever, you go ahead and get in.
Okay.
It's too cold.
Wait a moment, please.
Yeah, yeah, add some hot water.
It's too cold.
Pour it in.
Ice? What for?
Bathing in icy water after exercise
can constrict capillaries
and repair damaged muscles.
So you won't ache tomorrow
and you can continue training.
It's just too cold.
How does it feel?
Like basking in spring breeze
or bathing in spring rain.
Doesn't it imply a bit of a romantic feeling?
Well, you're adding insult to injury.
I will settle this with you sooner or later.
How could I? I'm pretty envious of you.
Really?
Why don't you get in too?
We're here.
Thank you.
I'll head back now.
Get some rest early.
Come pick me up tomorrow.
That way we can get to the team earlier
and improve efficiency.
You're not willing?
I, I am willing.
Okay, okay.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
We were looking forward
to the new official taking office with a bang.
As a result, everyone was carried away
without caution.
I don't understand professional issues.
But
from the perspective of uniting the team,
Shen Xi's method truly works.
I just want to know
if they really kissed or not.
They say they didn't.
But he was definitely thoughtful about it.
Look, I told you I wouldn't tell you,
but you had to ask.
After asking, you behave like this.
Why can't I ask?
He is my chosen marriage partner.
I can't just let someone else take him away,
can I?
Listen to me.
You are purely wasting time on Chen Mobai.
What's wrong? Do you think I,
Zhao Yingning, can't make it?
How am I worse than her?
Not a bit worse.
But
in this world,
all efforts
must be mutual to make sense.
If the two of you are not on the same path,
you will just diverge
and drift further and further apart.
How do you know
that they two are on the same path?
I don't think necessarily.
Here, I peeled these for you, you eat these.
I just don't like things
that are easily attained.
Mobai.
Mobai, I've been waiting
for you guys for a while.
What's wrong now?
Why does it seem like something major
happened every day?
Something big indeed happened.
Go, go, go. Let's go quickly.
Quick, quick.
How come you're here?
You broke the single lap record of Formula A.
It's fine to be a little proud.
But when doing something bad,
you should at least try to hide it.
What did I do?
The two of you seem to be progressing smoothly.
Miss Zhao, did you misunderstand something?
Hao Yang, did you speak nonsense?
Let me… I can explain.
What are you explaining? Can you explain now?
I suddenly remember
everyone gets a pass
if you break the record of Mitsui Taku.
Didn't your team include her last time?
The team fleet has parachuted a new engineer.
I, as an investor, want to try
where her abilities lie.
No problem, right?
Aren't you masking your personal grudge?
I suggest you,
if it can't be changed,
you'd better learn to accept it
like when you were a kid.
It's fair like this, isn't it, Miss Shen?
Very fair.
I'm ready.
You have some courage.
I have one condition,
Chen Mobai can't participate.
No problem.
I will prove to you that I can do it.
Okay, then let's begin.
Well,
won't you ask for my opinion?
- You caused this, right?
- What?
You caused all this fuss!
You just watch the excitement.
This is a test I specially brought in.
A question to test the team's technical level.
The track is not a garage.
It needs multiple tasks
to be accurately and correctly completed
in a short time.
Whether or not it can be done
is a basic standard to test
whether a team is excellent or not.
The first task,
assemble the engine parts.
The second task,
assemble these mixed suspension parts
into four suspensions.
The third task,
on the software level, complete the inspection
and debugging
of the program of the ECU.
Miss Zhao, we have done these tasks regularly.
How much time is there?
The standard is an hour and a half.
But I don't want to be too bullying.
It can be relaxed for thirty minutes.
With this process,
it usually takes at least three or four hours.
Miss Zhao, you…
If you are testing Xi,
why did you have to
bring us three weights with her?
Isn't this bullying Xi?
An engineer is the brain of a racing team
and the brain should be responsible
for the whole body.
If you want to surrender now,
it's not too late.
One hour.
I've calculated it. We only need one hour.
Two hours is too much.
One hour? Well…
Confidence is a good thing,
but let me be the bad guy here.
If you can't finish, you have to leave.
Not even Chen Mobai can stop it.
No problem.
Let's get started.
Just do your best.
Chubby eats so much normally.
He's completely useless
when it comes to real work.
Why has Xu Gong gone to this state?
Probably nervous.
When is it not okay to be nervous?
You see Zhao Yingning and you're not nervous?
That's true.
Xu Gong,
first clean, then categorize.
And finally assemble.
He who wants to do good work
must first sharpen his tools.
We'll win by taking our time.
Chubby, although there are a lot of components,
the suspension structure itself
is quite simple.
If you remember the torque of every screw,
you can save a lot of time.
Different intake and exhaust settings
will affect the amount of fuel injection
and ignition angle.
You might as well download
the most commonly used settings as a reference.
Xu Gong, the screws in the corresponding parts
need to use the appropriate force
according to the overall torque and rigidity.
Chubby,
remember to balance the aerodynamics.
Monkey, don't forget about safety
when optimizing parameters.
Control the air-fuel ratio
through engine calibration maps
and the oxygen concentration
sensor closed-loop.
Shall we go down?
Let's keep observing for a while.
If we go down now,
it would be like adding fuel to the fire.
- Done.
Done.
59 minutes and 55 seconds.
Amazing!
Looks like it was a false alarm.
Xi is awesome.
I declare, starting from today,
Xi is my little master now.
Miss Zhao,
that's not bad, right?
You did perform well today.
But whether you can take on the job,
I will keep observing.
I grew up with Chen Mobai.
He is not so easy to tame.
Wait a minute, I am a driver, not an animal.
Why do you need to tame me?
Drivers don't need to be tamed by engineers.
What's needed is cooperation
and the cultivation of tacit understanding.
Wait and see.
But you should know
it's not so easy for me to give up what I want.
This time is no exception.
This woman is calm on the surface.
There is danger lurking beneath.
Everyone did well today.
What do you want to eat tonight? My treat.
Listen to Xi. Thanks to her to pass today.
This must be decided by my little master.
Today is all your credit.
Your technical foundation is fine
and you are very talented.
You must believe in yourself more.
Little Master, what do you want to eat tonight?
You decide.
Sour fish soup it is.
What's going on?
The sun is rising in the west.
Chubby is reading a book.
Zhao Yingning's challenge was pretty good.
Isn't this better than team building?
You don't look at who the engineer is?
That's right.
Alright, having good taste doesn't mean
you should always stare at her.
Chubby, stop reading. Stop reading.
Well, I can't be a drag on the team.
Let me tell you,
since we have a way
to break Mitsui Taku's record,
regardless of which track we use in the future,
breaking his record will be easy.
It's not only one lap in the formal race.
You have to win several dozens of laps.
I'm good with that.
Alright, just let them practice.
After all, they also want to be like someone.
Improved their grades
and got the beauty.
You brat.
Stop it, stop it, be gentle, be gentle.
Ouch, ouch, you've spilled it all over me.
Chen Mobai,
come with me.
Me, me?
Alone?
Go, go.
Special training, special training.
Be a bit more serious.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What are you looking at?
What do you think about the relationship
between Xi and Mobai now?
I bet fifty cents.
If they want to break through
this paper screen between them,
I'm afraid it will take them a week.
You are seriously underestimating your Mobai.
I bet.
Seven days.
Isn't it the same thing?
Did I miss something just now?
Chubby, well, I bet three packs of ramen.
Well, what's wrong with them?
Come on, call out your most frequently used
racetrack map.
Just use the simulator?
I normally also play this simulator.
Are you afraid
I'm tired and suffering normally?
It's okay. Just say
what you want to train me on.
I won't argue.
The most frequently used track.
And then?
There is no "and then". Just practice this.
Practice until you can drive it
with your eyes closed.
Let me tell you.
I have run this circuit map,
if not 100,000 times,
at least 10,000 times.
Give me a day and I guarantee
to complete the task.
What do I practice after finishing this?
Nothing new. Just practice this.
What?
[SKYFALL Auto Parts]
Why have you stopped?
No, I…
I, I just stopped to stretch my legs.
Where's Hao Yang and the others?
They are growing organic vegetables
on the rooftop.
Organic vegetables.
Oh no. Do they need help?
Want to give up?
No, no, I don't want to give up.
I just want to change the circuit map.
Let me tell you, this seems like,
the sour fish soup is delicious,
but you can't always eat it.
When you eat to the last,
there is a fishy smell.
Let me tell you about this racetrack.
I've driven it countless times.
Now I can complete it even if I close my eyes.
You said that.
Well, really driving with eyes closed?
Come on.
Okay, Dr. Shen.
Wait a minute.
Okay, there should be no light leakage now.
My brother once said
the instinct of a top-notch driver
was actually like mechanical precision
of muscle memory.
Even with eyes closed
and rehearsing in the mind,
he can achieve the same precision
as in reality.
This is also the level I hope he can achieve.
No peeking.
I…
I didn't peek.
I,
I just want to have a sip of water.
Well,
after you finish drinking water,
remember to continue practicing.
I have something else to do, I'll leave first.
Okay.
[Auto Parts]
If you two were alone,
would you feel nervous?
Or if there were any physical contact
between the two of you,
would your heart be pounding?
Chubby, late-night snack.
Take it away quickly.
Yang,
why would you like planting
at such a young age?
You don't understand.
Mobai is plowing ahead.
I'm happily planting behind.
That's called striving
for a moderately prosperous life with family.
Forget it, I don't understand you.
I will just plant my lemon tree.
Xi, are you leaving?
You won't have dinner?
I have something else to do, I'll leave first.
What could be so important
that you skip dinner?
- She left that fast?
- She left.
Yang, do you think your bugs are really edible?
Give it a try.
I won't try.
The plowman is here.
Mobai, have you finished practicing driving?
What do you want to eat tonight, Mobai?
I will pick and cook it for you on the spot.
Absolutely natural and organic.
Strange, why did she suddenly leave?
What strange things are you muttering here?
You don't understand. Grow your veggies.
Shut up.
I don't like beans, Yang.
Red bean rice.
A cure for lovesickness.
Then I will eat it.
Nonsense. I'll weed your vegetables.
[Pumpkin]
[Red Bean]
[Massive Gratification]
Good morning.
Morning.
Today,
could it still be practicing on a simulator?
There's no simulator practice today.
Although you have made a lot of progress,
it still does not meet the standard.
Practice something else today.
So…
There's a new training task.
What kind of training is it?
You will know when you get there.
Miss Xi, are you sure you want to do this?
I'm a bit worried.
What are you worried about?
I'm afraid his manly pride can't take it.
He can only become
a truly qualified Formula A driver
if he gets over this.
Chen Mobai, no rule-breaking.
The speed cannot exceed 20 mph.
Uncle, are you a tortoise?
Who are you calling a tortoise? Come back.
What's going on?
Uncle, Uncle, can you do it?
If you can't do it, don't block the road.
I…
So slow.
You are so slow.
Such a naughty kid.
I think you want
to taste the bitterness of society.
Are you alright?
Don't cry, don't cry.
Don't be angry, okay?
Miss Xi, it's okay. I'll take care of it.
Come on, come on.
Slow down, okay?
Stop crying, stop crying.
Chen Mobai, you broke the rules.
Why did you irritate him?
I just wanted to show him
what a proper overtaking looked like.
But, then I lost a bit of control.
Fifteen mph.
♫ The wind breathes quietly ♫
♫ The heart gradually silences ♫
♫ Your traces remain in my mind ♫
♫ I can't delete them ♫
♫ Time drips away bit by bit ♫
♫ Memories are scattered everywhere ♫
♫ The passing trees cast shadows like you ♫
♫ Fading away ♫
♫ Change the details bit by bit ♫
♫ Decide our fate
in every second of every minute ♫
♫ Just like the paradox of love ♫
♫ The synchronization of heartbeats ♫
♫ The surge of longing burns within ♫
♫ Waiting to find the answer at the end ♫
♫ Accelerating against the wind is your pride ♫
♫ And also my ultimate goal ♫