Pearl,
Yes.
We've sold a few dresses.
My Lady,
didn't you ask just now?
I haven't sold one yet.
How many days has it been?
Why aren't there any guests?
It shouldn't be.
Welcome.
Just you.
Stop,
Can you stop looking at me like that?
I'm sorry,
because seeing my benefactor again,
So I'm a little happy.
I, Wu Yue,
escaped from the palace and went to Xiadu,
I can't let Father's men find out.
I'd better use an alias.
You came to Xiadu to find a relative?
But my family is no longer alive.
The coil was stolen again.
When I was hungry,
it was the benefactor's baked wheat cake.
He saved my life.
I can't repay you,
but I've been studying for a few years,
I also managed the account for my family for a few years.
You want to stay and be the accountant for your benefactor?
No wages.
As long as you have food and shelter.
I pick you (I announce you),
I pick you (I announce you)
This time, Su Jinxia went to the villa to cultivate herself,
which is a great plan to solve her problem.
I understand.
Fake
Where is Su Jinxia?
I don't know.
I know nothing.
Please forgive me.
Since you don't know anything,
you can leave now.
Master,
there's news from the courtyard,
Assassins broke in.
Looks like
they can't take it anymore.
How is the hunting going?
It's going as planned.
That's great.
By the way,
how is the empress?
After Her Highness settled down,
she opened a large-size women's clothing store in the city.
Large size women's clothing store,
it seems to sell some strange clothes.
Interesting.
She is not afraid that others will find out her identity as the empress.
I'm looking forward to it more and more.
I met the empress.
Wipe it well now.
Here we go again,
Shopkeeper Chen.
What can I do for you?
I don't think there's anyone in your shop
who can make you more popular.
It has to be people who can make it more popular.
Hey,
Shopkeeper Su's mouth is so open,
Awesome,
But,
It's not enough to open a shop
with only one mouth.
Hey,
Why don't you
give me this plate.
You won't lose all your money.
You got it.
Shopkeeper Chen,
let's make a bet.
Let's find a model,
wear their own ready-made clothes and compete in this street.
Let's see who has the highest rate of return.
What rate?
It attracts a lot of people.
What if you lose?
Then I'll give this shop to you.
He barks like a dog,
but,
If you lose,
please take a detour when you see me again.
Don't dirty my eyes.
Okay,
It's a deal.
The match will be held in five days.