You're full now, right?
Let's play a game.
The last pair standing
gets to pick who does the dishes.
Kim, can I ask you something?
- Please don't tell anyone about this.
- Of course.
That includes Nubdao, too.
He didn't sleep well last night.
Kim usually sleeps like a log.
Can I stay for dinner?
But after eating, you need
to go home and get some rest.
Maybe I should just sleep here.
Sure. Uncle Pu's room has some space.
Kim, help me.
Nubdao, I have an urgent matter.
I need to go.
Mr. Wee…
Why does my heart always beat so fast
when I'm near him?
Her physical injuries
suggest two possibilities.
Either she was assaulted
or she harmed herself.
No way. She wouldn't hurt herself.
Come on, sis. I came home late
because I was visiting you here.
That's just an excuse.
But if you're worried about the kids,
just visit them. Stay over sometimes.
Tell me.
In what capacity do you expect me
to return to my kids?
I've never even been
a good mother to them.
I wish I could say I love them,
hug them, or kiss them. But I can't, Pu.
Today, I was so happy.
I've never been this close
to my children before.
Me too, sis.
I've been waiting
for this moment for so long.
The day you'd finally get to see them,
even if just for a short while.
Hey, how about this?
Next time you get a day off, let me know.
Let me know in advance.
I'll find a way to sneak you in again.
Thanks, Pu.
Are you sure you'll make it smooth?
Of course. I'm the master.
Nubdao.
Do you remember anything about Mom?
Tell me about her.
When Mom passed away, I was only two.
Dad used to say
I wouldn't sleep
unless she rocked me to bed.
He also said I was a crybaby.
I'd only stop crying if she carried me.
What about me? Was I a crybaby too?
No, not really.
I wish I had some memories of her,
but I guess that's impossible now.
Hey!
Crybaby confirmed!
You still haven't grown out of it?
Who's a crybaby?
Your eyes are all red.
Where's Kim?
He's not coming today.
I think he got home late last night.
I didn't see his car at home
when I got back either.
He probably overslept this morning.
Then, let me drive you today.
Thank you so much.
Namfah should be ready soon.
She'll be out in a bit.
Looks like she already left.
I must've just missed her.
Hello?
Yeah.
I already left.
Sorry for not waiting for you.
But I'm still waiting for you.
You were up late
because of a birthday party, right?
I didn't go. My friend
had a fight with her boyfriend.
And what about you?
Are you mad at me for something?
I'm not mad!
Definitely.
Nubdao, let's go together today.
You should sit in the front
with Mr. Pathawee.
I'm too sleepy. I'll sit in the back.
Namfah, sit properly.
Here's a blanket.
Thank you.
Namfah, do you have
a problem with Mr. Pathawee?
No.
Why did you sit in the back?
I told you, I'm sleepy.
That's the only reason?
Of course.
Stay here for now.
You'll be safe from your stepfather.
Okay.
Here are my clothes.
I think you can wear them.
You're letting me stay here.
Won't Nubdao misunderstand?
I'll explain it to her myself.
"It's been two weeks
since we became a couple.
Let's go on a date tonight."
DID YOU RECEIVE MY GIFT?
SEE YOU TONIGHT
Talking to Nubdao?
Yeah.
I'm taking her out for dinner tonight.
Special occasion?
Our two-week anniversary as a couple.
That's romantic.
Enjoy your dinner. I'll be fine alone.
Who said I'll leave you alone?
I hired a nurse to take care of you.
Hello, ma'am.
Please take care of her.
Call me if there's anything.
Yes, sir.
Where's your secretary?
On sick leave.
And what wind brought you here?
The wind of love.
How much love?
A lot of love, dear brother.
Wait, don't tell me…
Your little sister is my girlfriend now.
Seriously?
Yup. Yesterday, I even
went with her to the hospital.
And?
And she let me carry her gift basket.
Plus, she took me along
to visit her friend.
That's it?
That's why you think
she's your girlfriend now?
When two people are in love,
they don't need words. They just know.
Oh, and I saw your brother
at the hospital too.
Kim?
Was he dropping off Promtawan?
No, I think he was visiting someone else.
Wow! You look stunning, Nubdao.
Are you sure you're not an angel instead?
Nubdao,
if Mr. Kim proposes tonight,
don't play hard to get, okay?
Look, your Prince Charming is here!
So beautiful.
I'm talking about you…
not the dress.
I bet I'm the only one who remembered.
This is my first relationship,
so I didn't know
which dates I had to remember.
I never remembered with anyone else.
After dinner, let's go watch a movie.
Sure.
What genre do you like?
Horror.
I can't handle that. I get scared easily.
With me, you don't have to be afraid.
Hello?
Okay. I'll be right there.
The nurse said my friend disappeared
and hasn't been found yet.
- Do you want me to come with you?
- No.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me?
When did you last see her?
After she finished eating,
she fell asleep,
so I went to use the restroom.
When I came out, she was gone.
Did she take her phone?
No, she didn't.
Mr. Kimhan!
Yada…
No one understands me.
I do.
You know I do.
I've been through this too.
I'm so tired.
I have no one left.
You still have me.
You have me, Yada.
Nubdao, how was the dinner?
Was the food good?
Where's Mr. Kim?
Nubdao,
are you okay?
I brought Pad Thai for you guys.
Mr. Wee!
This one is very good.
Now is not the time
to be excited about food.
Who would have the appetite
for food right now?
I'll eat it. Thank you.
Okay.
Mr. Kim took her on a date,
but something happened.
I heard he went to find his friend
in the middle of their date.
Mr. Kimhan said he found his friend.
Everything's okay now.
That day, Talay told me
he saw Kim at the hospital.
He must have visited this same friend.
I wonder if it's a male or female friend.
Mr. Wee,
do you think an ex
can still be called a friend?
Not sure. I've never had a girlfriend.
What about you?
I…
I've never had a boyfriend either.
There, there.
Heal quickly.
And from now on,
don't think about the painful past,
little wound.
In a relationship,
what is the most important thing?
I think trust.
If you don't trust each other,
how can you move forward?
Like us, right?
What do you mean?
Because…
I love you, and I trust you.
I trust you too, Namfah,
and I love you the most.
It's late now, dear brother.
And where are you off to?
Picking up a package.
What's this?
Some clothes and essentials for you.
Thank you. I was just telling the nurse
I needed to go out and buy some things.
Wearing your clothes downstairs
gets me weird looks.
I think you should rest more first.
Don't go out just yet.
Okay.
Here's your medicine.
Kim?
What are you doing here?
Dropping something off for a friend.
What about you? Why are you here?
I had a few too many drinks last night,
so I stayed over with my friend.
Do you stay over here often?
Not really.
Kim.
You can go down first.
I forgot something in my friend's room.
Is every week often though?
Hey, what's the matter?
Tomorrow?
No, I can't. I have to be
with my patient at the penthouse.
New office, same coffee, right on time.
Where did you find your friend last night?
The rooftop.
You're lucky you found them in time.
Was this a university friend?
A friend from university.
Just don't forget
to take care of yourself too, okay?
Thank you.
Alright.
Mr. Kong, I need you to find a house
that's ready to move into immediately.
I need a ready-to-move-in one.
No, not for me. It's for a friend.
Please handle it.
This is urgent.
Just give me a little more time, Nubdao.
Are you catching a cold?
Did you take any medicine?
Not yet.
Why don't you take medicine
and rest in the infirmary for a while?
It's alright.
Go rest. I'll handle things here.
Thank you.
Welcome to Oriental Paradise,
ma'am.
I have a reservation.
- May I have your name, please?
- Mew.
It's nice going home together for once.
Nubdao, you feel feverish. Are you okay?
I think I caught Waree's cold.
Let's stop by the pharmacy
before heading home.
Nubdao!
I made it in time to take you home, right?
Hurry. Nubdao's not feeling well.
You're burning up.
I'll take you to see a doctor.
Mr. Kim…
I can walk.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Mr. Kim!
Hey, put me down!
I don't know if Nubdao is actually sick,
but Mr. Kim is definitely burning up.
Namfah, do you have medicine at home?
No.
I'll stop by a pharmacy.
Are you cold?
I'm fine now.
NURSE
Oh, it's a nurse calling.
What should we do, Nubdao?
NURSE
Hello?
Hello. Mr. Kimhan
isn't available right now.
Is there something urgent?
I just wanted to update him
that Ms. Yada has a fever.
Who again?
Ms. Yada, ma'am.
I see. I'll let him know.
Thank you.
Nubdao,
if you're not feeling well,
don't push yourself.
If your fever gets worse tonight,
call me, okay?
I'll head out now.
Mr. Kim.
Your friend has a fever.
I see.
When you were buying medicine,
the nurse called.
I answered for you.
Are you sure it was Yada?
I heard it clearly.
Ms. Yada has a fever.
You really didn't know?
I know.
She took sick leave.
But I just found out now that
she's the friend Kim is taking care of.
You just found out? Are you sure?
Yes.
I saw your brother at the hospital too.
Kim?
Was he dropping off Promtawan?
No, I think he was visiting someone else.
Kim, what are you doing here?
Dropping something off for a friend.
How is Nubdao now?
She seems okay on the outside.
But inside, I really don't know.
She always said
trust is the most important thing
in a relationship.
Actually,
if Mr. Kim had just told her that it was
Ms. Yada, this wouldn't be an issue.
Why did he keep it a secret?
Right?
Yeah.
Call Mr. Kim again. Why isn't he here yet?
I've called him multiple times, ma'am.
Did you tell him I have a fever?
A woman answered the phone,
but I passed the message along.
Who?
I didn't ask for her name.
Hello, Mr. Pathawee.
How are you feeling, Yada?
Are you getting better?
I feel much better now.
Did the doctor say
how long you need to stay in the hospital?
I'm back home already.
Oh, you're home?
Yes.
I sleep much better at home.
Okay, then. I won't bother you.
Alright.
Home?
Why is she still awake?
Which hospital is closest?
Kim.
Namfah told me your friend is really sick.
What happened to your friend?
She was abused by her stepfather.
She's in bad shape,
both physically and emotionally.
I don't want any woman
to go through what she did.
Mom…
No woman
should suffer like you did.
Do you think Nubdao will understand me?
YADA PHAKAMAS
Are you at home right now, Yada?
Yes, I am.
I'll drop by to see you then.
You don't need to come.
I feel much better now.
Nurse, can you come with me?
Where are you going, ma'am?
I need to pick up something from home.
- Hello, Mr. Pathawee.
- Hello.
- Please come in.
- Thank you.
This way, please.
You really didn't have to go through
the trouble of visiting me at home.
You're my secretary.
Of course, I had to come check on you.
Thank you.
Of course.
You have a nurse at home?
Yes, since I live alone,
I hired a nurse to help me recover.
I see.
Ms. Yada, you look pale.
Are you feeling unwell?
Yes.
You should rest at the infirmary.
It's alright.
I'll just go to the hospital later.
My friend is seriously ill.
This friend has no one.
I had to take them to the hospital.
How's your friend now?
Still bad.
Was this a university friend?
A friend from university.
The nurse said my friend disappeared
and hasn't been found yet.
- Do you want me to come with you?
- No.
I just wanted to update him
that Ms. Yada has a fever.
In a relationship,
what is the most important thing?
I think trust.
If you don't trust each other,
how can you move forward?
MR. KIMHAN
Yes, Mr. Kimhan?
How are you feeling?
I'm getting better.
You need to take all your medicine
and get plenty of rest.
If your fever comes back,
call me right away, okay?
Okay.
I won't bother you then.
Wait, Mr. Kim.
Did you order yet?
If not, I can order for you.
Do I know the friend
you've been taking care of?
No, you don't.
I guess I've never met this friend either.
Never.
Then, it's not Ms. Yada?
Kim, can I ask you something?
Please don't tell anyone about this.
It's embarrassing.
That includes Nubdao, too.
If I wanted to visit your friend,
would I be able to?
Right now, my friend
doesn't want to see anyone.
So, your friend…
She's getting better now, right?
NURSE
Pick it up.
She might have gone missing again.
Or maybe…
Ms. Yada's fever came back.
Life is just like this carousel.
It has its ups and downs,
happiness and sadness,
spinning in cycles.
The more hardships we endure,
the closer we are to happiness.
Why do you want to explain
yourself to me so badly?
How did you know I'd be back?
I saw your car key over there.
I left it there intentionally.
You're up early today.
Not too early or too late, right?
For me to pick up my girlfriend
for work every morning.
I feel sorry for your friend.
Being all alone like that.
So, I have to take care of them.
I haven't had much time for you lately.
Alright.
But even if I have less time,
I still love you just the same.
Aran always told me he would marry me.
So, why did he leave me?
And your child?
He left me with nothing but this.
This is all I have. I have no other proof.
What's this?
A key to a rental home.
A gift for you and your mother.
I guess I'm not Mr. Kim's trust anymore.
Why do you think that?
Because I was never worth trusting.
You're the one who needs to stop.
I'm giving back all your time.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon