Do you have any proof
that Mr. Aran truly took his own life
and wasn't murdered?
Here it is. This is Mr. Aran's will,
written before he died.
Congratulations. You've successfully
put yourself in the spotlight.
Nubdao doesn't seek the spotlight.
But if her success overshadows someone,
that's not her fault.
Today is the day. I have to meet him.
Fah!
Oh, Dad, be careful, though.
Once you're no longer useful,
they might turn on you like stray dogs,
biting the hand that once fed them.
The real problem
is people who pick fights
with everyone without thinking.
Wee!
When the sun sets,
it's time for the stars to shine,
isn't it?
Tell the messenger to wait there.
I'll be out soon.
It's not even urgent.
I could've signed it tomorrow.
Are you okay?
Yes, but what about you?
I'm fine.
Mr. Kimhan, are you sure you're okay?
You should see a doctor.
It's nothing serious.
I'm so sorry. This is my fault.
Nubdao.
Yes?
I'm glad it was me.
If it had been you,
I'd feel even worse for bringing you here.
When I was little,
every time I got hurt,
my mom would blow on my wound
and say,
"Heal quickly."
Alright.
Heal quickly.
And from now on,
forget about the painful past,
little wound.
We just posted
this announcement for a day,
and it's already gone viral.
What made you decide to bring it back?
Did your dad finally approve?
Dad doesn't know yet.
I misunderstood him. I thought
he was stopping me from running the page.
Wait.
Then what did you think
he was stopping you from doing?
He thought I was dating you.
He assumed we were more than friends.
Damn, your dad's got good instincts.
Should we just make it official?
Enough of that.
You look happier than ever
doing this again.
This page is my whole world.
It's where I can be myself,
do what I love,
without anyone stopping me.
And what if your dad finds out?
My only happiness
will be gone.
Am I not your happiness?
Come on.
The Mystery Chef has to stay a mystery.
- You ready?
- Ready.
Five, four, three, two… Record.
Wait. What about you?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine,
but Mr. Kim…
Are you okay?
Yes, but what about you?
I'm fine.
What a hero. Risking his life like that.
Nubdao.
Have you started falling for him?
Falling for what?
Come on. Mr. Kim is serious about you.
If he keeps up surprises like this,
Mr. Pathawee
is so getting left in the dust.
Stop overthinking things. Go to sleep.
So, Mr. Pathawee
still has a chance, right?
When I was little,
if I fell,
my mom would blow on my wounds
and say,
"Heal quickly."
Alright.
Heal quickly.
And from now on,
stop thinking about the painful past,
little wound.
When will the sun and the stars
finally be together?
Thank you.
Your coffee, sir.
Your shoulder is still in pain?
It still hurts.
Can you help me?
Of course. What do you need me to do?
Feed me my coffee.
What?
I can't lift it.
It's too hot.
Is there anything on my mouth?
I thought you said your shoulder hurt.
Well…
It just got better. Like, right now.
You tricked me?
Nubdao…
Nubdao, I wasn't tricking you.
I wasn't trying to trick you.
I was just teasing.
Do you think
that's something to joke about?
I just wanted to know
if you care about me.
And now I know you do.
You're overthinking.
I was just following orders.
That's all.
The chairman wants to speak with you.
How much trouble are you planning
to bring to Mr. Kimhan?
Sit down.
Explain this.
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
When will you stop being so reckless?
Look at Pathawee.
He never steps out of line.
He listens to me
and follows orders.
Remember,
you have no right
to tarnish my hotel's reputation.
If you do,
be prepared to step down
from your vice president position.
Nubdao.
Are you okay?
What are you going to do now?
I bet whoever leaked this photo wanted
the higher-ups to put you under scrutiny.
Nubdao.
I hate people who don't know their place.
I can explain, Ms. Sanguansri.
You're putting Nubdao in danger,
all because of that one photo.
And how is that any of your business?
This is between me and Nubdao.
Just the two of us.
I must thank you, Nubdao.
Thanks to you, every employee now knows
that our management team
is brave enough to protect their people.
Don't worry, Ms. Sanguansri.
I ordered all employees
to delete the photo.
Alright, sir.
I also instructed them
not to share it further.
Of course.
I also already handled that myself.
Mr. Kimhan, do you realize
that every single employee
is now incredibly proud of you?
Right now, you're practically their hero.
Now, let's see. Which shoulder was it?
The one that got injured
while bravely saving her
with your brave heart?
Left or right?
Oh no!
If it's the right shoulder,
you must have trouble signing checks.
But don't worry, I'll find you a…
A quill pen. Yes. Something light.
Quill… quill… quill… quill… quill…
Here's some Khao Chae for you, ma'am.
That fragrant candle-smoked aroma.
Smells delicious.
Tasty.
Ever since you started working here,
my appetite has improved tremendously.
Same here. Everything you cook is amazing.
You could be a Michelin-starred chef.
Thank you.
When I was younger,
I dreamed of becoming a chef,
but it never happened.
It's okay.
I dreamed of being a good daughter,
but I'm not.
Enjoy your meal.
So, you wanted to be a chef?
I can get you to work at the hotel.
That's alright.
I have something else I want to do more.
What is it? Maybe Grandma and I can help.
To repay the people
who made me who I am today.
Good.
Never forget those who have helped you.
I hope you succeed
in whatever it is you're planning.
Thank you.
Good afternoon, Ms. Sasi.
Since I started working here,
I haven't had the chance
to introduce myself yet.
Alright. If you ever need anything,
don't hesitate to ask me.
Thank you.
You seem to like white orchids a lot.
I once heard that white orchids
symbolize unconditional love.
Unconditional love…
Yes.
That reminds me of…
What are you doing here?
Nothing, dear.
Go and do whatever you have to.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
If you're going to work here,
you better know who to listen to.
Don't think for a second that
your so-called master can protect you.
Yes, sir. I will remember that.
Nubdao.
Yes?
There's something
I want to warn you about,
but I'm not sure if I should say it.
Go ahead.
Kim has never been serious about anyone.
That's his personal matter.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm just worried
that you might get too invested
and end up getting hurt.
Thank you for your concern,
but I know my place.
Good. Then stop causing trouble for Kim.
The one who should stop causing trouble…
is you,
Yada.
Instead of being "concerned",
maybe you should be congratulating us.
That'd be the right thing.
Excuse me.
You took that photo
and leaked it, didn't you?
Aren't you jumping to conclusions
a little too quickly?
Ms. Sanguansri sent a messenger
to deliver documents to me.
They were from your department.
And then, Nubdao nearly got injured.
Followed by the leaked photo.
Quite a coincidence, don't you think?
It's almost like you're determined
to cast me as the villain in your story.
And why would I even do such a thing?
For the thrill.
Creating drama
is something you're quite skilled at.
The amusement park
sent this formal letter of apology
regarding last night's accident.
If you still have doubts, I can connect
you directly with their management team.
Welcome back!
Eat With Me is officially returning,
and we've got something exciting for you!
Got a dish you'd love
to see our mystery chef cook?
Drop your menu suggestions in the comments
and use the hashtag EatWithMe!
The first ten lucky winners will receive
an imported, limited-edition
French wooden cutting board,
personally signed by our chef!
Oh my gosh. It's so cute!
I want it!
I need to comment now.
What should I say?
Ravioli.
Hey?
Come on. Send already.
There's no signal.
You want this, don't you?
The French cutting board with
the chef's signature. How did you get it?
I have my ways.
But they just announced it on the page.
Can I have it? Pretty please?
- Please.
- Sure.
Thank you! You're the best!
If you want this,
you need to help me with something first.
Help you with what?
- I want--
- What do you want?
- I want to invite--
- Invite what?
- Invite--
Invite Nubdao to have lunch with me.
Okay!
Then the cutting board here…
Will be yours immediately.
Yes, Mr. Kimhan?
Are you home yet, Nubdao?
Almost there.
Tomorrow is your day off, right?
Yes.
I'd like to treat you to a meal.
Why do you want to treat me to a meal?
I want to apologize
for that leaked photo today.
I'm not available.
Why not?
On my day off, I have to do laundry
and finish translating documents.
Can't you do them another day?
No.
I'm home now, Mr. Kim. I have to go.
Nubdao. Nubdao.
- Nubdao.
- Namfah.
You dragged Mr. Pathawee
to drive you home again, didn't you?
That's not it.
It's not that. Really, it's not.
Tomorrow's your day off, right?
I'm off tomorrow too.
And so is Mr. Pathawee, right?
Yes.
So, that means you're free tomorrow.
- No, I'm not.
- Why not?
I have laundry to do. And ironing.
It's okay. I'll do it for you.
I also have
a lot of translations to finish.
Give it to me. I'll do it for you.
Nubdao.
Yes?
The weather here is nice, isn't it?
Yes.
If we go for…
I'd like to invite you to lunch…
with my mom.
Lunch with Ms. Sasi?
Yes.
Nubdao, why did you pinch me?
I told you not to bother
Mr. Pathawee again, didn't I?
I wasn't bothering him.
He wanted to drive me home.
Don't lie to me.
I'm not lying, really.
Then, do you know why he invited me
to lunch with his mother?
- Nope.
- Are you sure?
I really don't know why
he brought up his mother as an excuse--
I mean, I don't know.
Namfah, get up right now.
Don't pretend to snore.
I don't care what you say.
You're coming with me tomorrow.
I made some
Krathon Loy Kaew for you to try.
Let's go inside.
Here's some Krathon Loy Kaew. Try it.
A little tangy.
Just the right sweetness.
I haven't had this exact taste
in over 20 years.
You should teach me
how to make it, Ratree.
Of course, so you could
make some for Mr. Taychit.
Mother.
Excuse me.
Alright.
Yes?
Please, Mother.
Come have lunch with me.
Why don't you just go with her alone?
Why do you need me there?
Because I don't have
the courage to go alone. So, I…
Used me as an excuse.
Yes.
It wasn't easy
getting her to agree to this.
I won't.
Mother…
Please come with me? Just this once?
I won't refuse.
Thank you, Mother.
Come on.
Thank you.
Here are some fruits, Madam Jitree.
If Jitsuda were still alive,
she would be doing this too.
Wait.
Yes?
Sasi didn't cause you
any trouble, did she?
No, ma'am.
Maybe she sees that I work for you,
so she doesn't dare.
Good. As long as she knows
whose side you're on.
I don't want you
to serve people like them.
Yes, ma'am.
But Mr. Taychit told me
that if I wanted to stay here,
I had to listen to him alone.
I was the one who brought you in.
You listen to me, not him.
Yes, ma'am.
I trust you.
You won't disappoint me, will you?
No, ma'am.
There they are.
Nubdao.
Good afternoon, Ms. Sasi.
‪Good afternoon.
Please, have a seat.
Such a lovely young lady. Is this the one?
What's your name, dear?
Mom,
this is Namfah, Nubdao's younger sister.
She's just here as company.
Make yourselves comfortable, dears.
- Thank you.
Kim, I have a surprise for you.
I'm really happy
to have this lunch with you today.
It's an honor for me, Ms. Sasi.
If I knew you knew each other,
I would've invited you
to lunch a long time ago.
Well, it's not too late now.
That's true.
Mr. Pathawee mentioned you had something
you wanted to talk to me about?
I just wanted to thank you
for what you did the other day.
If it weren't for you,
the hotel's reputation
would have been at risk.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Alright, what's your surprise?
Why don't you take a look inside?
Well? Surprise, isn't it?
You have to try this dish.
The "Two-Hearted Sea Bass".
Mr. Wee, my sister doesn't eat spicy food.
Oh, right.
Thank you.
Here, Mom.
They all seem to be having
such a great time together.
Aren't you going to go say hello?
Not necessary.
Bringing Nubdao to meet Ms. Sasi…
That means Mr. Pathawee
must be really serious about her.
Who Nubdao eats with,
or who introduces her to whom,
that's her personal business.
Wow, you're really open-minded, Kim.
It's not about being open-minded.
I just trust Nubdao.
Mother, what do you think of Nubdao?
She's lovely and well-mannered.
So, that means
you won't object if I pursue her?
Of course.
And what if Kim likes her too?
Kimhan likes Nubdao too?
Yes.
If it were anything else,
I might let it go. But not this.
Or…
Are you saying
I should step aside for Kim?
I want you to search your heart carefully.
If you truly like Nubdao,
then fight for her.
I will, Mother.
Nubdao.
How was it?
The food?
Totally worth the reviews.
No, I mean Mr. Wee.
Nothing special. It was just lunch.
Really?
You didn't feel anything at all?
- Oh, I feel something.
- Really?
What did you feel?
I feel like you like him.
No way! Not at all!
He's not my type at all.
Are you sure?
My heart belongs to the Mystery Chef.
But weren't you the one who kept
saying how perfect Mr. Wee is?
Handsome, cool, and gentle.
When did I ever say that?
He's the perfect man.
He's handsome and such a gentleman.
So cool!
I'm so sleepy.
My stomach's full. Time for a nap.
Don't try to play dumb with me.
And don't change the topic.
So, what is it? Mr. Pathawee?
I think I'll go sleep inside.
You can't just run away.
MR. KIMHAN
Yes, Mr. Kim.
How much have you translated today?
Still a lot left to do.
Were you busy with housework?
Yes.
Have you eaten yet?
I have.
Was it good?
It was nice.
That restaurant has a great atmosphere,
and the food's pretty good too,
especially the "Twin-Hearted Seabass".
If you didn't want to eat with me
because you had plans with someone else,
you could've just told me directly.
So good.
I've never thought Taychit would make
his friend's lover his wife.
Sis, it takes two to tango.
The woman must've been into him too.
But it seems like
Ms. Sasi still loves Mr. Aran.
How do you know?
She remembers everything about him.
So?
If I get close to Ms. Sasi,
I might be able to find proof
about Mr. Aran's death.
You think they'd leave evidence
lying around for you to find that easily?
Well, good luck finding it.
Just be careful.
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, by the way, sis.
If you find out
where he keeps his money, just tell me.
Enough.
- I wasn't done eating.
- All you think about is money.
Well, I…
And about eating.
I…
- I'm thinking about you too…
- That's not true.
Finally!
The signed cutting board is mine!
If you can get Nubdao to go
on a one-on-one date with me,
you can ask for anything you want
from Eat With Me.
Really? Anything at all?
Then I want…
- What do you want?
- I want…
A candlelit dinner with the Mystery Chef.
Deal-- Wait!
- You can't.
- You just said I could ask for anything.
The chef probably
doesn't want to reveal his identity.
But I want to meet him. You get it, right?
I get it.
Then it's settled.
You pick the restaurant.
Next week, I'll finally meet him.
- Next week?
- Yes.
Welcome to Oriental Paradise.
Would you like a single or double bed?
- A double bed, please.
- Sure.
Alright.
Please fill out this form.
Sure.
Thank you. I'll handle the rest for you.
Your coffee, Mr. Kimhan.
Thank you.
- About yesterday--
- Please, you go first.
- You first.
I just wanted to say that
yesterday, I…
You forgot to sign
one more document yesterday.
Here you go.
The meeting is about to start.
Okay.
I'll be back for my coffee.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
See you in the afternoon.
Alright. Goodbye.
Everyone's ready for the meeting.
Let me help you.
You should go help Pathawee.
I doubt Mr. Pathawee
wants my help right now.
Let me double-check the guest list.
Of course.
Nubdao.
What time do you finish work today?
Five p.m. Why?
Nothing. I'm heading home first.
See you at home.
I've arranged it. See you this evening.
This evening?
Yes. As soon as she finishes work,
come straight to my house.
- It can be another day.
- Nope. It has to be today.
And don't forget our deal.
Namfah, wait.
Namfah.
Finally, my dream will come true!
Mr. Kimhan.
Are you waiting for me?
Yes. I don't want you to misunderstand
what happened yesterday.
About what?
That I turned down the meal with you
but went with Mr. Pathawee.
So?
Ms. Sasi just wanted to treat me to lunch
as a thank-you for the press conference.
That's all.
That's all, I swear.
I wasn't hiding anything from you.
Why do you want to explain
yourself to me so badly?
How did you know I'd be back?
I saw your car key over there.
I left it there intentionally.
Do you think he'd like
a girl like me, Mr. Wee?
Of course.
You decorated the house so nicely.
Something special happening?
A special someone
is coming over for dinner with Nubdao.
Namfah invited Mr. Pathawee over
for dinner tonight.
Then go ahead and have dinner
with them. I won't intrude.
You'll lead the team
and come up with
a new signature dish within two weeks.
Two weeks?
You won't let me down, will you?
Can I break our contract?
Of course.
Why don't you raise
your children yourself?
I'm not ready.
Don't wait until you are.
By then, you might not
have the chance anymore.
Namfah is one of my employees.
I told you about her before.
- I've met her.
- Excuse me?
Why are you grinning
at your phone like that?
And why are you smiling
at the clock like that?
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon