You might not get to have dinner
with the Mystery Chef, just with me.
You decorated this place so nicely.
What's the special occasion?
A special guest is coming
to have dinner with Nubdao.
You don't eat spicy food either.
I've eaten it for him, Namfah.
You knew that?
And I also know
why you ate it instead of me.
I respect Nubdao's decision.
I don't want to put her
in a difficult position.
- Can I cancel our deal?
- Of course.
So, you'll be the project leader.
Come up with a special dish
within two weeks.
All of my time belongs to you alone.
No matter if it's good times or bad times,
the sunlight will always be near you.
I hope you're doing well.
Nubdao.
Lungo coffee, your favorite.
Aren't you going to have a sip?
I made this for you myself.
It's the same coffee,
but brewed by a different person, Yada.
Even if the barista changes,
the rich aroma
and intensity
might make you reconsider and come back
to the coffee you used to love.
Thanks for the effort for this old friend.
But I won't go back
to drinking the same coffee again.
You come early every day
just to flirt with Kim over coffee?
Were you talking to me?
Is there anyone else here?
If the coffee is good, you don't need
to flirt. He'll drink it anyway.
Aren't you Mr. Pathawee's secretary?
Then why aren't you bringing
that cup to your own boss?
Did Ms. Yada bring you coffee?
She did,
but I didn't drink it.
Aren't you going to ask why?
Even without drinking it, I'd still
get in trouble with someone. If I had,
I'd be dead by now.
This… This is my favorite cup.
We've reached a consensus.
- We've decided on…
- Tom Yum Goong!
Why this dish?
Because Tom Yum Goong
is a globally recognized dish.
It's practically
a signature of Thai cuisine,
with a rich and distinctive taste.
It won't be overshadowed
when fused with other culinary traditions.
It has its own characteristics.
Anyone who tastes it will
immediately understand and appreciate it.
And what is your Tom Yum soup
preparation technique?
We start by roasting the prawn heads
and shells until it's completely dry.
Then we add tomato paste
and cook until well combined.
Adds chopped onions, celery,
lemongrass, galangal,
and kaffir lime leaves, then fry them.
Then add water.
Bring the broth to a boil
and let it simmer for about 20 minutes.
Blend until smooth,
then strain to get a clear broth.
Let it reduce by a third
to concentrate the flavors.
Add a bit of finely ground chili paste
to enhance the Tom Yum flavor,
then stir until fully dissolved.
Add a bit of cooking cream
to balance out the strong flavors
from the prawn heads and shells.
Enhance the aroma with lemon zest.
Balance the flavors with halved lemons,
salt, and a touch of sugar.
Bring to a boil,
then turn off the heat. Remove the lemons
before straining the broth one final time.
If the consistency is too thin,
add a tiny amount of cornstarch slurry
to stabilize it.
Finally, we finish
with a knob of chilled butter
to add richness
and a silky mouthfeel before serving.
Now we have
a concentrated French-style Tom Yum broth.
But these techniques
come with their own challenges.
Like what?
KEY CHALLENGES
Here are the key challenges.
One, we need to control the roasting
of the prawn heads and shells precisely.
You put oil in it.
If undercooked, the broth will be fishy.
If overcooked, it'll turn bitter.
BALANCING FLAVOR
Two, we have to be careful
not to make the broth too Thai,
since it will overpower
the French influence.
Lastly…
This is very important.
If we want to put butter in it,
it's a Western way of cooking,
we have to incorporate it
gradually into the hot broth,
stirring in rhythm.
Otherwise, the butter
will separate and float on top.
Understood.
- Got it.
Too fishy. The prawn shells
weren't roasted enough. Start over.
- Got it!
Abracadabra! I hope we pass this time!
It smells good.
It's bitter. Over-roasted.
The heat was too high.
Start over.
- Yes.
Are you sure you'll finish in time?
Yes.
If you can't make it, let me know.
I can assign someone else.
I have plenty of other easy tasks
for you to prove yourself.
It's alright. I can do it.
I know you won't disappoint me.
The Chairman himself came
to personally encourage his favorite son?
Why? Afraid he might fail
and disappoint you?
Pathawee already promised me.
He'll never disappoint me.
Then I'll be sure
to cheer him on from the sidelines.
If he succeeds,
it will not only be
a triumph for our hotel,
but also prove to the Board
that he has a talent
that you clearly lack.
And the Board will see just how obviously
you favor one vice president
over the other, right?
Exactly.
- Smells as good as ever.
- Agreed.
If you can't make it, let me know.
I can assign someone else.
I have plenty of other easy tasks
for you to prove yourself.
I know you won't disappoint me.
Why is it still bitter?
Why does it keep turning out like this?
Right? I swear
I managed the flames properly.
My hand is cramping
from stirring so precisely,
and it's still bitter?
Maybe we should start from the beginning?
Go home.
- But we're--
- I said go home!
Yes, sir.
I've never seen
Mr. Pathawee like this before.
Yeah.
He's usually calm, but that was scary.
Because you didn't watch
the heat properly.
- It's because you didn't roast it well.
- Me?
Yes, you.
- It's you.
- Stop!
Could it be…
What was that about?
Maybe…
it wasn't you and me?
- Enough.
- What are you talking about?
Mr. Wee.
- Why are you still here?
- Because I just realized something.
I asked why.
What if the bitterness
isn't from burnt shells?
Then what is it from?
Is it possible that it's bitter
because we over-boiled the broth?
Yes, that's right.
Thank you, Namfah.
How long have we been boiling it?
Twenty minutes.
Set the timer for 18 minutes.
Turn it off now.
Still bitter.
- Reduce the time.
- Got it.
It's still bitter. Reduce the time again.
Got it.
Mr. Wee!
Smile. It's almost time.
No bitterness!
Yes!
- No more bitterness!
- Be careful.
No bitterness!
It's not bitter anymore!
So, we passed the first challenge, right?
Yes. I forgot
that if prawn shells are boiled
too long, they release ammonia,
which makes the broth taste bitter.
You were too stressed.
It happens when you pressure
yourself too much.
That's why the Mystery Chef says
we have to enjoy cooking.
Otherwise, the food won't turn out right.
Right.
So, in the next steps,
don't be stressed
and don't pressure yourself.
Alright.
Let's go, then. I'll drive you home.
Okay.
- Here's your water.
- Thanks.
You can leave first if you want.
I'd rather stay…
and keep you company.
Where's the clock I gave you?
It's over there.
Where? I don't see it.
Right there.
You pretended not to see it?
Oh, Namfah, you're here already?
Nope. Still on my way.
Hello, Mr. Kimhan.
I'm glad…
you brought her home.
I'm heading out first.
Okay.
It smells good.
My favorite cup of coffee.
What are you doing here?
Visiting my girlfriend.
Can't I?
What if someone sees us?
It's still early. No one's here yet.
How was your morning?
Traffic wasn't too bad today.
Same here!
The highway was pretty empty too.
But it's good we're here early.
Now we can enjoy coffee and do our makeup.
True, but the lighting here isn't great.
You're right.
Let's go to the restroom first.
We'll grab coffee later.
Coffee?
- Let's go.
They want coffee?
Wait! Someone else might come.
Let me check first.
What are you doing down there?
Uh… Fixing a pipe leak.
How bad? I can help.
Uh, no, it's fine! It's fixed already!
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
You fixed it yourself?
Yes.
Wow, a woman
as pretty as you fixing pipes?
Lucky will be the guy who dates you.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Oh.
You're single. I'm single. We're single.
Can I get your LINE?
Oh, my boss is calling.
Why didn't you tell him
you have a boyfriend?
I think we nailed the first challenge.
I'm pretty sure we got the second one too.
Yeah.
Let me try.
Here, go ahead.
Be careful. It's hot.
It tastes way too Thai.
Still not there?
The Thai flavors are overpowering.
There's no French influence.
Namfah, let me see your notes.
Here it is.
Yes, Mom?
What do you want me to do?
I'm still at work.
Namfah.
The aroma is there.
We've brought back the French influence.
- Really?
- Yes!
Namfah, try it.
Does that mean
we passed the second challenge?
Yes.
Yeah!
Woo!
Can I taste it?
Let me try too.
Wow, it's good.
Let me try.
Wow.
You spent days perfecting just the soup.
Are you sure you'll finish in time?
Yes, I'm sure.
Good.
Ah, the embassy is calling.
I'll confirm the presentation date now.
Alright.
Are you worried about something?
It's the presentation. I'm not good at it.
Just explain it step by step.
I know you can do it.
I'll try.
I'm so lucky
to have a great team.
The kitchen work is tough,
but even someone as small as Namfah
is handling it with determination.
She never complains.
And she lifts everyone's spirits.
That sounds like fun.
It's so fun, and I'm so happy, Mom.
Mr. Wee is incredible.
How?
Whenever there's a problem,
he fixes it right away.
I never expected someone like him
to be this skilled.
You should see him cook.
It's so cool!
If he's that good. It sounds like
he'll take the Mystery Chef's place.
No way!
The Mystery Chef is always my number one.
No one can top him.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
Everyone's busy with the banquet
in the main kitchen,
so I'm the only assistant today.
Got it.
So, we're at the final step
of making the soup?
Yes. For this step,
you have to be very patient.
Make sure the butter doesn't float.
Fah.
Don't rush.
I have to add it one piece at a time?
Yes, we need to blend it in fully
before adding more.
This is another
French technique, isn't it,
Mystery Chef?
Yes.
You have to stir in sync,
or else the butter will float.
It smells amazing, Mystery Chef.
Yes, it does.
Namfah.
Yes, Mystery Chef?
Namfah, stop stirring.
Add the next piece of butter.
Got it.
Slowly.
What are you working on?
Presentation notes,
but they're still a mess.
Are you the one presenting?
No, I'm just helping Mr. Wee research.
With good notes and preparation,
it should be fine for him.
But he told me
he's not confident in presentations.
It'd be great if someone good
at presenting could help him.
I won't be able to go home
with you this evening.
Why? Where are you going?
I'll take you there.
Hey.
I'm going to check in
on Mr. Pathawee and Namfah.
Do you want to come along?
I'd better not.
Wee wouldn't want me near him.
I think he'd actually be happy
if his brother came to support him.
You did well yesterday.
That was a good start.
I just wanted to make you happy,
that's all.
And it made you happy too, didn't it?
Try it.
Let's try it.
- Rich and creamy.
- The sourness is just right.
- Perfect balance of saltiness.
- And a light aroma of pepper.
Great.
Need any help?
Nubdao, help try this.
Sure. What is it?
A key ingredient for the dish.
Give it a taste.
Sure.
Nubdao.
Did you invite him?
Very smooth.
I can really taste the kaffir lime.
Why don't you let Mr. Kimhan try?
- Alright.
- No need.
Nubdao, get it for me.
Sure.
How is it?
Very smooth.
Do you need more help?
Yes, a lot.
Excuse me.
Come here. There's a lot to do.
A lot?
I'll go help over there.
Nope.
We're not done yet.
Wrap it properly, or it will smell.
Excuse me, Mr. Kimhan.
I'll wait outside.
Okay.
Nubdao, what's Mr. Kimhan doing?
Shape the dough properly.
Got it.
I'd like to introduce our Thai River Prawn
Tom Yum Bisque.
We first sauté the prawn heads and shells
with brandy until dry,
then add onions,
celery, Japanese scallions,
galangal, lemongrass,
and kaffir lime leaves.
We sauté them,
then blend and strain the mixture,
then reduce the broth to one-third.
Everyone, please enjoy.
Please, go ahead.
Feels like it's missing something, right?
I'd like you to try adding
a touch of this sour cream
and tasting the soup again.
The Thai Tom Yum essence remains strong,
yet there's a refined,
smooth texture, like a French bisque.
That's thanks
to the French cooking technique.
We blend chilled butter into the hot broth
for extra aroma and a smooth texture.
So, the more sour cream you add,
the deeper the Tom Yum flavor becomes?
Exactly.
Very innovative.
It's a beautifully balanced
Thai-French Tom Yum bisque.
And absolutely delicious.
To make this dish even more exceptional,
I recommend pairing it with this.
Why don't you pair it with rice?
I believe that if we try
pairing the bisque with bread,
it might create a fresh,
unexpected experience.
I chose three-colored bread
to incorporate elements
from Thailand's four regions
into this dish.
That sounds interesting.
Can you elaborate a little more?
Sure. I chose the Ayutthaya river prawn,
which symbolizes the abundance
of Thailand's central rivers.
That's the key ingredient of the dish.
For the three-colored bread
that I serve with the soup,
I've made it
with three regional rice varieties.
The first layer is made from
"Forget Husband" rice from the North.
The second layer comes from
sticky green rice from the Northeast,
while the third
uses Sangyod rice from the South.
That's an excellent idea.
Pairing it with the soup
will enhance the flavors even more.
This is an outstanding dish.
It seamlessly blends the uniqueness
of Thailand's four regions
with the elegance of French cuisine.
I'm confident our VIP guests
will be highly impressed.
We're delighted to collaborate with you.
Thank you very much.
We greatly appreciate this opportunity.
- Sure.
- The pleasure is ours.
Thank you so much.
You did an excellent job.
Thank you, Father.
Hooray!
- I was on edge the whole time, Mr. Wee.
- You nailed that presentation.
You were amazing, Mr. Wee!
Teach us some of those
presentation tricks, please.
It's all about the three S's. First,
spark interest.
Second, stimulate engagement
Third, surpass expectations.
That three-colored bread
really went beyond expectations,
not just for them but for us too!
That was Namfah's idea.
Namfah, you're incredible!
Tonight, let's celebrate our success.
Come in.
Thank you, Kim.
3S'S PRESENTATION TECHNIQUE
FIRST, SPARK INTEREST
If you hadn't given me those tips,
I wouldn't have passed the presentation.
Selling a dish is one thing,
but if the food isn't good,
it wouldn't have passed.
So, did I pass in your book?
Thank you, really. Thank you.
Why don't you eat at the restaurant?
We have to clean.
Stop complaining, Uncle Pu.
You never helped me and Numdao clean.
Isn't what I'm doing right now helping?
Yes, it is.
You little troublemaker.
- Hurry up.
- I'm on it.
I know.
Anything I can do to help?
Mr. Pathawee. No, no.
Just sit back and enjoy the BBQ.
Here, let me pour you some water.
Come, come, sit down and enjoy.
The grill's ready.
- Here we go!
- Here's your drink.
What about mine, Uncle Pu?
Yours is soda.
I know you too well.
Oh no, I'm so thirsty!
I'm hurrying.
Thank you for helping Pathawee.
I wasn't helping him.
I was helping the hotel.
Yeah.
Either way, you did a great job.
So, did Mr. Pathawee invite you
to the celebration party?
- Yeah.
- Are you going?
The host went out of his way
to invite you. Don't turn him down.
Come with me.
Fine, I'll go…
for your peace of mind.
Thank you.
Let's celebrate!
Cheers!
We made it just in time, right?
Your house is so cozy.
Do you live here with just your sister?
And my uncle too.
It's just touching, you know?
We don't get special guests here often.
Next time, let us know in advance,
so we can prepare properly.
Kim must really like your coffee.
He finished the whole cup.
He had trouble sleeping last night.
He usually sleeps like a log.
Thank you for staying with me all night.
I haven't had much time for you lately.
But even if I have less time,
I still love you just the same.
Are you tired?
A little. But hearing your voice
makes it all better.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon