[English subtitles are available]
[Love's Rebellion]
[Episode 31]
I collected spiritual aura from the North Region.
Now I have two spirit pearls.
It's enough for you to enter Bone-Deep Mirror.
Promise me
that from now on,
no matter what you do,
you can't abandon me again.
♫Through the storms and cold♫
♫Just to wait for you♫
♫I break through the curse of fate♫
♫And pierce through the dark clouds♫
I got it.
♫May heaven and earth last forever♫
♫May our love be eternal♫
♫The impermanent years have never stopped♫
♫We spend this lifetime hand in hand♫
♫Billions of light beams converge into a galaxy♫
♫But they still can't compare to the moment you look back♫
♫The past is mottled with old memories♫
♫As long as you're by my side♫
♫Over the hills, seeing through the world♫
♫I'll hold your hand till we grow old♫
The barrier has been disrupted.
If we close it by force,
our disciples will be hurt.
We have no time.
I can only weaken my cultivation
and force my way through
to fight the Reincarnated Sen Luo.
I'll go with you
to bring them out.
No need.
Stay here
to receive them.
Alright.
Be careful, Dragon Lord.
Yan.
Tell me
about Lunar Sect.
Big Brother
is a scholar.
The Fox is a troublemaker.
I thought
you were a pure soul.
I didn't expect
you'd become
vicious when we fell out.
After I knew you were the monarch,
I wanted to kick you out of my home.
But who know
you'd refused to leave.
You even threatened
to kill me.
After that,
you finally took your medicine
and had your meals.
But I didn't expect...
you'd be hurt
by a demonic cultivator.
I'm willing to sacrifice everything
in exchange for you.
But I know
you won't return.
Ji Yang.
After being separated for three years,
we've finally reunited.
Don't leave me again.
She
wants to kill you herself.
So I need you to gather the five prisons
and become the Reincarnated Sen Luo.
Yan.
I was too greedy.
I just wanted to
be by your side day after day.
But now,
I can’t do it.
My Lord!
Dragon Lord is here.
Dragon Lord.
I underestimated you, Dragon Lord.
You chose to weaken your cultivation
to fight against me.
But the realm of the Bone-Deep Mirror
belongs to me.
What are you talking about?
Someone is absorbing his spiritual power.
Did you arrange for an accomplice?
Have they all been
killed by you?
I misunderstood you, Dragon Lord.
Dragon Lord.
Stay here to recuperate.
My Lord!
Something happened in Shanhai's main hall.
Let's go.
Ji Yang!
Ji Yang.
Yun Nian!
I can't hold on anymore!
[Ten Percepts Mountain]
Open up the path.
[Ten Percepts Mountain; Shanhai's Forbidden Tournament Ground]
[Ten Percepts Mountain]
[Shanhai's main hall; Shanhai's Forbidden Tournament Ground]
It's you?
So you are the masked man.
I finally get to see you today.
Sorry it took me so long.
Even if you're the Reincarnated Sen Luo,
you can't
ruin my plan today.
Pot calling the kettle black.
Rao?
Rao.
Silly Meng.
Rao?
Han is here too.
Where have you been all these years?
Why are you yelling at me?
Watch it,
or I'll tell Dragon Lord
you stole the Thunder Dragon Pestle
from his treasury
to use in fights in the Central State.
You...
What's going on?
So Sword Master
sacrified countless disciples
in the barrier
not to capture the prison
but to revive Chief Nan.
It's the forbidden resurrection technique.
Meng Xiaolou!
Are you crazy?
You've killed so many people.
If you don't stop,
the children here
will all be killed by you!
You're going against the right path!
Against the right path?
Rao cultivated into a god
but died from her heart being ripped out.
Do you think
there's still a right path in this world?
If this is
the so-called right path,
I must go against it!
Compared to Nan Rao,
those people are not important at all.
Meng Xiaolou.
I didn't expect
that you're so
secretly devoted to Rao.
You cultivated into a god,
but you went against the right path.
You'll plunge into the depths of the demonic path!
Demonic path?
Even if it's the depths of purgatory,
I'll still have Rao by my side.
What are you doing?
Rao.
Do you remember
promising to go to Tianqiao Peak with me
to see the frosted fireflies in the early winter?
Is it still valid?
Buddy Meng.
What's up?
I'm returning this.
I slept so deeply that the sun is setting.
Were you just standing here foolishly?
I heard you've always been romantic.
No.
I mean elegant.
It's frustrating to be bothered when in a drunken sleep.
So I didn't dare make a sound.
Romantic...
While some see it
as being amorous and vulgar,
naturally, there are those
who see it as pure and natural.
You and I can be good friends.
Thank you.
Anything else?
I've thought about it for a long time.
If you have time,
can you accompany me
to watch the frosted fireflies at Tianqiao Peak?
What do you think?
Just inviting me?
I...
like you.
I don't know how long you've prepared
for this statement,
but I
already have someone in my heart.
It's Mu Guanghan.
Frosted fireflies...
Sure, I can join you to catch them
for fun.
Just think of
your last statement as a dream.
Rao.
Promise me.
I'll take you away.
You're joking again.
Just pretend this
is all just a dream.
Rao.
Rao!
Chief, so you're here.
Is Mu Guanghan's birthday banquet over?
Why didn't you go celebrate?
Han likes such
nonsensical stuff.
I can't be bothered with them.
I'm really tired.
Then you should go back to rest.
Why are you here?
I was waiting for you.
What?
Aren't you here
to punish me?
Punish you?
I thought you'd remember it.
This smell...
It's Lunar Epiphyllum?
Is it familiar now?
You didn't attend any of Venerable Lord's lectures
last month.
So you went
to my yard then.
That's right.
I took all the Lunar Epiphyllums
in your yard.
Since I promised to gift you good wine,
it mustn't be shoddy.
After some consideration,
I realized your yard's Lunar Epiphyllum
is the best ingredient for wine making.
You actually used them to make wine?
This wine is called Clear Dew Sorrow.
Clear Dew Sorrow?
It's brewed by the dew
I gathered from cicadas' legs.
Try it.
Don't worry.
Your Lunar Epiphyllum isn't suitable for brewing wine.
It was hard to figure out the proportions.
But I've given Mu Guanghan
the wine that were brewed badly.
The good stuff is here.
Try it.
How is it?
It's refreshing
but strong.
One should drink
wine that suits them.
The moon is bright in the Central State.
One's heart is hard to fathom.
Rao.
Rao!
Impossible.
I did everything he said.
How could this happen?
Going against fate is impossible since ancient times.
Even if you conjured
Nan Rao's human form,
it's just
an illusion.
No way.
It's due to a lack of spiritual power.
Meng Xiaolou.
Are you going to kill everyone?
I told you.
I don't care!
Meng Xiaolou!
When did you
restore the Divine Realm?
Mu Guanghan!
With one-tenth
of the spiritual powers of Shanhai
and the Bone-Deep Mirror each,
I can kill you.
Leave me alone!
Dragon Lord.
Let me tell you.
Meng Xiaolou
has a deep inner demon.
He absorbed too much spiritual power.
Both of us are no match for him.
Just now, I've planted
the fate-sharing talisman in him and myself.
Help me
perish with him.
This is for the benefit of the five states.
You must...
You must obey it.
Do it.
Do it!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Rao...
Brat.
You're quite something.
You're really not the Reincarnated Sen Luo.
Dragon Lord.
From now on,
please take care...
of Zhanting and Yan for me.
Dragon Lord.
Hang in there for Mu Zhanting.
I can't.
Tell him...
From now on...
he can write poems whenever he wants
and marry whomever he wants.
I'll relay it to him.
Also,
if Yan
falls in love,
prepare her dowry for me.
Give the Phoenix Crowing Sky Skirt
to her for me too.
When she wears it,
she'd look as pretty
as Nan Rao.
Dragon Lord.
Ying Zewei.
I was wondering why
I couldn't find you.
I asked you to drink at the banquet,
but you refused.
You sneaked all the way
here to find Rao!
Han.
Don't make fun of him.
Look at him.
He's scared speechless.
You two are
even drinking secretly.
Rao.
Why is your wine
different from
the wine
you gave me?
The wine I drank
was much more sour than this.
How is it different?
They were all made by me.
If it's sour, spicy, or bitter,
it must be your tastebuds' problem.
Give it back.
Impossible.
Try it. Try it.
This wine is really good.
It's much better than the wine she gave us...
No, no, no.
Have a sip.
Look at you.
You're drunk.
I spilled it on you.
Take a sip.
-Have a taste.
-No, thanks.
Try it.
What are you doing? You're drunk.
The gods have fallen.
Father!
Father.
How could this happen?
You were fine yesterday.
Father.
-Master.
Master.
Master, what's wrong?
Master!
It can't be. It can't be.
My father wouldn't die!
Why?
Ji Yang.
Ji Yang!
Mu Zhanting!
-Mu Zhanting!
-Big Brother!
-Ji Yang!
Calm down!
Mu Zhanting!
Kids, calm down.
Let go of me!
Kids, don't be impulsive.
Mu Zhanting!
Let go of me!
You can't get in.
Then I'll smash it!
This thing...
Doesn't this thing
let you go back to the past?
I want to go back.
I want to go back
to bring my father back.
You...
Fate can be reversed theoretically,
but it's determined.
If you change it for no reason,
you will be punished.
I'm not afraid of punishment!
You...
As hot-tempered as Dragon Lord.
Big Brother!
Mu Zhanting!
Big Brother.
Master.
How did you get in?
The barrier of Shanhai
has been on the verge of collapse.
My disciple,
keep an eye on him.
[Great Path Sect]
Great Path Sect?
What are you doing?
I forgot the way to Great Path Sect.
Are you new here?
He was scolded by Master,
so he's hiding here.
Premier's enthronement banquet is today.
Don't run around.
Yes.
The 42th year of Qingxu?
No wonder Zhu Sui can't recognize me now.
Great Path's main hall
is empty,
so I guessed you were here.
We've been
waiting for your sister
for half a day,
but she hasn't come out.
I composed a new song
called "Silent Night".
I want to co-compose it with Zewei
to celebrate this auspicious occasion.
Take the lead
and I'll play along.
What's wrong with you?
What took you so long?
One of you
is a musical genius,
while the other is gentle and elegant.
Virtuous and musically talented.
Wonderful.
Sister, the auspicious hour is here.
Let's go.
I've been lazy lately.
I won't go.
You guys go ahead.
Have a good rest.
Let's go.
Come in.
I won't bite.