[English subtitles are available]
[Love's Rebellion]
[Episode 10]
Yan, take a rest.
Leave these to me.
Do this one.
Nan Yan.
Nan Yan!
People from the Great Path sect are here again.
They said they received
an anonymous report letter
insisting that
Lord Shao Cang is in the Lunar Sect.
Why are you all looking at me?
It won't do me any good
if the Great Path Sect comes here.
I don't want to be locked
in the Spirit-Sealing Formation.
I'll make some noise down the mountain
and lure them away.
Don't go.
The Great Path Sect has a clear goal this time.
I think
they won't
retreat easily.
I'm familiar with the Lunar Sect.
Next,
listen to my arrangement.
Don't act on your own.
I have an idea.
I agree.
Brother.
Take this with you.
For self-defense.
Okay.
Come with me.
What about me?
You...
Find a place to hide.
Just don't let them skin you.
It's so noisy.
Whose dog is so arrogant?
Disturbing my sleep.
Oh, it's just you, Zhu.
We're here at the premier's order
to capture the rebel Shao Cang.
Please do us a favor
and let us search thoroughly.
What if
I refuse?
If this delays the Great Path's plan
and receives the Premier's blame,
your father won't be able to help you.
Elder Zhu.
At a time like this,
you should worry about yourself.
Your trip this time
not only disturbed the civilians
but also provoked the established sects.
Aren't you afraid of ruining
Great Path's reputation?
What if Premier fires you
in a fit of rage?
Don’t worry about that.
I have a clear conscience.
Premier will understand.
Right.
Anyway, Great Path
has no reputation to begin with.
Seems like we can only
settle this by force.
Let's see who dares to come forward.
Go in and have a look.
Search carefully.
[Five-Poison Heart Pill]
[Ji Yang]
It's Shao Cang's handwriting.
Let’s report it to the Elder.
Junior Mo.
If Shao Cang wrote this,
he might be nearby.
Go report to the Elder.
I'll lead the team and continue to search around.
Mr. Mu, you keep trying to keep us at bay.
Could there really be
something suspicious in the closet?
Since you know it,
why are you forcing me?
Let me tell you the truth.
It's not that I don't want to open it for you.
I'm just afraid that after I open it,
you'll see something you shouldn't see
and hurt our peace.
[Premier of Great Path Sect, Ying Zewei]
How dare you disrespect
Premier this way?
My goodness.
My confidant!
Elder Zhu,
this painting is my treasure.
I've shown it to many people.
[Premier of Great Path Sect, Ying Zewei]
Only you
can recognize at a glance
that this is Ying Zewei.
It seems that you not only know painting,
but also me
and your master.
His name is written on it.
Do you think I'm blind?
[Premier of Great Path Sect, Ying Zewei]
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
I forgot.
No.
I wrote it there because most people
couldn't recognize him.
Mr. Mu.
[Premier of Great Path Sect, Ying Zewei]
Don't go too far.
This is not the East Sea.
Yes.
Elder Zhu.
Calm down.
Since you
have such discerning eyes,
why don't you guess
who this is?
Look.
Your father?
Elder Zhu.
You are really my confidant!
I’ve been studying
this kind of beast style recently.
It emphasizes simplicity.
A few strokes
can draw out the essence of the character.
Elder Zhu,
if you are interested,
I can draw one for you.
It's very fast.
It won't take long.
No need!
Mr. Mu, you'd better save your talent
for your father's portraits.
[Premier of Great Path Sect, Ying Zewei]
Elder Zhu!
Think about it!
I'm fast!
Elder Zhu.
This man humiliated Premier.
Should we just let it go?
Let's not argue with those below us.
The Great Path is better than that.
Yes.
I'll take care of them.
You go first.
No.
I was the one who kept you.
This happened all because of me.
If the entire sect is implicated
because of this,
then Mu Zhanting, Yin Ya,
Chief, and even Meng Ying
will all be killed.
Once Great Path's people
find you,
the Lunar Sect
will also be guilty
of hiding a fugitive.
Don't worry.
I will clarify everything.
The reason I'm here at Lunar Sect
is because I forced you
to hide me here.
Lunar Sect was unaware.
This matter
has nothing to do with the Lunar Sect.
You don't have to take responsibility for me.
In their eyes,
you are a treacherous and
untrustworthy person.
If you suddenly cut us
off like this,
can't they tell that
you want to protect us instead?
If you really care about us
and don't want me to take the blame for you,
just stay here and
don't go anywhere.
You just said that
the Great Path Sect is hard to fool.
Since they are here,
they won't leave easily.
If anything happens to you,
I'll let them die with you.
If you really kill
Zhu Sui and the rest today,
you'll fall right into their hands.
You'd really be found guilty
of slaughtering your fellow disciples.
By then,
the entire cultivation realm will be your enemy.
There are so many people,
can you kill them all?
No matter what happens,
you must not show up.
This belongs to your mother.
You can't give it to outsiders.
You are not an outsider.
Miss,
why are you
in this forest alone?
I'm catching some venomous insects
to make medicine.
Did you plant those Vermilion flower
at the foot of the mountain?
You know poison too?
A fellow of the same craft.
I know a little.
May I ask
who lives in that room with you?
I've been studying poison.
I'm always alone.
Who would live with me?
Young Master.
It seems that you know poison too.
Why don't you stay
and make medicine with me?
What do you think?
I am Mo Xingzheng, a disciple of the Great Path.
I was ordered to search for a fugitive here.
If you
see any suspicious person,
please inform me.
A suspicious person?
I think you are suspicious.
You sneaked into the yard
while the master of the house was absent.
That's akin to a robber.
You asked a stranger woman
about her private life.
That's akin to a hooligan.
You broke into our sect
and wandered around as you like.
That's akin to a bandit.
You misunderstood.
Misunderstood?
If I remember correctly,
a few days ago,
you already searched the place, right?
In just a few days,
you intrude on our sect twice.
What?
Do you want to
ransack our sect while you're at it?
Unfortunately,
I'm so poor that
I only have these precious insects.
Have you thought it through?
Do you want them?
No need.
I shall take my leave.
How was it?
Don't worry.
That’s good.
Where is Elder Zhu?
Don't mention it.
Zhu
was so mad that he almost fainted.
All disciples of the Lunar Sect,
gather at the square immediately.
I have something to ask.
Who does he think he is?
He acts like he's such a big deal all the time.
I'll roast him with the Sun Fire.
Calm down.
He is not a good person.
The chief is not here now.
If we confront him head-on, there will only be trouble.
How about
playing it by ear?
We'll talk about it when Chief comes back.
This lucky bastard.
Let's go and have a look.
Ji Yang.
Where are you?
[Ji Yang]
This handwriting
is the same as Great Path's fugitive,
Shao Cang's handwriting.
[Ji Yang]
If my guess is right,
Ji Yang
is Shao Cang.
[Ji Yang]
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
The rebel Shao Cang
is evil and ruthless.
He won't even spare the people of the same clan,
let alone your lot
who have nothing to do with him.
The ignorant is innocent.
Today,
whoever reveals Shao Cang’s whereabouts,
will not only be spared,
but also heavily rewarded.
If you conceal the truth on purpose,
the entire Lunar Sect
will be buried together.
Who is playing tricks?
Show yourself if you dare...
Was it not the fox spirit that day,
but Lord Shao Cang?
Senior!
Where is Ji Yang?
I don't know.
Wait!
Senior!
Are you alright?
Elder Zhu.
The person you are looking for
is here.
Mr. Mu.
It's you again.
Are you kidding me again?
How can I joke with you, Elder Zhu?
You are the one
joking here.
Elder Zhu, look.
Here.
Great Path's Lord Shao Cang
is nowhere to be seen.
To be honest,
I wrote
these words.
[Ji Yang]
How is that possible?
Thank you for your compliment.
It seems that
my imitation of Shao Cang's handwriting
has reached the level
of being mistaken for the real deal.
Mr. Mu.
Why did you imitate Shao Cang's handwriting?
This must be new information for you.
Shao Cang’s calligraphy
is stylish and powerful.
The strokes are lively
and absolutely striking.
Wait.
What's wrong with imitating it?
Did I use your brush
or dipped your ink?
Seriously.
Mr. Mu is eloquent.
I admire that.
However,
who is Ji Yang?
Isn't he...
Well...
Who?
Who? He...
I came here to study
because the Lunar Sect
has Master Boyang's
Eternity Inner Canon.
Recorded inside
is a unique healing method that fights poison with poison.
It can cure my mother's old illness.
So,
I found a patient
with a similar illness
to my mother's.
This medicine tester
is called Ji Yang.
We checked her room.
It is indeed filled
with venomous insects and poisonous plants.
If it's a patient,
why doesn't anyone in the
sect know about it?
The Lunar Sect has strict rules.
We can't hide outsiders.
So this person
never showed up.
Where is he today?
He's not in the sect today.
Maybe he went down the mountain.
Have you
met this person?
This person?
No.
No?
Really?
No matter how many times you ask,
the answer is the same.
Of course not.
Fine.
But
you have no evidence.
If you have a clear conscience,
why don't you try my
Celestial Lightning of Truth?
No way!
The Celestial Lightning of Truth?
You're the Elder of Great Path.
How could you do this?
Are you trying to force an answer out of her?
Mu Zhanting!
I've had enough of you!
Me too!
I'm not afraid of you!
The Dragon Roar of the Ninth Heaven!
Array!
Why isn't Father back yet?
Come on.
Here we go.
It's coming...
Coming!
Chief Meng.
I found that when
Nan Rao isn't here,
you become really
lucky.
Of course.
I didn't read the The Sparrow's Nine Verses
Yingying gave me for naught.
I told you.
Rao and I don't get along at the game table,
but you didn't believe me.
This is just an analysis, but,
were you losing to her
on purpose?
Don't tell me...
Are you in love with her?
You...
My card!
You can insult me,
but not my sportsmanship.
Yes.
I saw you went to the back mountain,
so I followed you.
Yan
went after the people from
Great Path, right?
Did she do it to lure them away?
Yan is in danger
because of you.
Why don't we help her?
If we work together,
I'm sure we can
defeat them somehow.
W-what's wrong?
You wrote that
anonymous letter, right?
Don't...
Don't kill me.
Nan Yan treats you as his friend.
Is this how you treat her?
Kid,
you should stop trying to show off
with your mediocre skills
in the future.
Let go of me!
You're shameless!
Let...
Don't hurt him.
Come at me if you dare.
You're quite loyal.
Fine.
As long as you tell me where Shao Cang is,
I promise
I will release
all of you.
I've never seen him.
Why would I know where he is?
Nan Yan!
Let go of me.
And let you die?
How will I answer to Chief then?
Senior Fu...
You are really united.
Okay.
I’ll give you another chance.
You've really never seen Shao Cang before?
Elder Zhu,
are you deaf?
How many times have I told you?
No.
Fine.
Since you are so stubborn,
I will grant your wish
and let you experience the
Celestial Lightning of Truth.
Senior.
What should we do?
Don't move.
Dispelling evil and warding off misfortune.
Invoking lightning for righteous punishments.
Let me ask you again.
Have you ever seen Shao Cang?
Never.
Fine.
Senior.
Senior, tell him to stop.
She will die.
The Celestial Lightning of Truth.
Nan Yan.
If I lie to you,
let me be struck by lightning.
This isn't good.
Meng Zhiguang!
How can a sect leader like you
just run away after winning?
How is it?
It doesn't feel good, does it?
Tell me the truth now,
and I can spare your life.
If you're inclined to be stubborn,
the Celestial Lightning strikes without mercy.
I have no idea
which bolt of lightning
will make even your soul disappear
when it hits you.
I'll tell you.
Speak.
Even if you kill me here,
I've still never seen him!
The Celestial Lightning of Truth
pierces the bones and devours your soul.
I'll ask you one last time.
Have you ever seen Shao Cang?
Bear with it.
Everything will be fine
after this time.
Fine.
Since you ask for death
just for a traitor who has
no relations with you,
I'll grant your wish.
♫Gazing at the distant sky♫
♫The clouds roll in as the wind rises♫
♫The faces we passed by♫
♫Met each other in fate♫
♫Like the vast starry sky♫
♫Falling into my eyes♫
♫Thousands of mountains apart♫
Ji Yang.
♫I hug you amongst a sea of people♫
♫At the Riverbank of Forgetfulness♫
♫I am willing to be a lone boat♫
♫Through the storms and cold♫
♫Just to wait for you♫
♫I break through the curse of fate♫
♫And pierce through the dark clouds♫
♫May heaven and earth last forever♫
♫May our love be eternal♫
♫The impermanent years have never stopped♫
♫We spend this lifetime hand in hand♫
♫Billions of light beams converge into a galaxy♫
♫But still can't compare to the moment you look back♫
♫The past is mottled with old memories♫
♫I am lucky to have you by my side♫
♫From now on we'll let time pass♫
♫And spend the rest of our lives travelling hand in hand♫
♫Through the night and day♫
Shao Cang!
Shao Cang, I know it's you!
Come out if you dare!
Be a man!
Ji Yang.
Don't come out.
Come out if you dare to!
Shao Cang!
Fine.
You forced my hand.
Nan Yan!
It's you.
Meng Zhiguang!
How dare you hurt the judicial elder
of the Great Path Sect?
Name the punishments you deserve!
Elder Zhu,
you're really quite thick skinned.
You broke into my sect looking for a fugitive,
but instead you attacked my disciples
while I was away
just because you couldn't find him.
I've already given the one at your sect
enough respect by not killing you
with a bolt of lightning!
It’s the Lunar Sect who
hid the fugitive first.
You deserved it!
What proof do you have?
Proof?
The proof is Ji Yang
hiding from us.
So Elder Zhu
did indeed find something suspicious.
I won't hide it then.
Wayward disciple Ji Yang, show yourself!
You're a spirit!
Wayward disciple!
Hurry up and
greet Elder Zhu.
Don't blame me for hijacking you here.
Help our sect get through this,
and I'll ensure your safety.
I, Ji Yang,
greet Elder Zhu.
Meng Zhiguang.
How dare you hide
a spirit in your sect
and fraternize with him
as the chief of your sect?
This fox spirit has always been a sick man
and has never done anything to harm anyone.
Because his illness is similar to her mother's,
Nan Yan hid him in her quarters
to test treatments on him.
I saw that he was inherently good at heart,
and that he had ideal physique for cultivation,
so I instructed him
a few times secretly.
Firstly,
he's not in our sect's register.
Secondly,
he has never had a disciple initiation ceremony.
I don’t believe this counts as fraternizing.
Like I'll believe you.
If you don't believe me,
you can search him.
I left him a note
I wrote personally
to prohibit anyone in the sect
to hurt him.
Someone!
Take the spirit back to our sect!
Hold on.
Elder Zhu need not concern himself
with our sect's internal affairs.
Step away!
If I have to report
even such a small thing as
keeping a spirit pet to the Great Path Sect,
will there be anyone who dares
to raise chickens and livestock in the Five States?
Moreover,
the spirits have been imprisoned for hundreds of years.
They are no longer a threat.
A little spirit like him is
as trivial as an ant.
I am merely
giving him a way out.
The Great Path has always lead with virtue.
Are you planning to eliminate all of them?
If there is nothing else,
please leave.
Fu Lang, see them out.
Elder Zhu.
After you.
Just you wait.
Don't let me catch hold of
any evidence against the Lunar Sect.
You two
take Nan Yan back to her room.
I'll be there soon.
Father.
Chief,
you were so impressive just now.
You beat
that Elder Zhu so coolly.
That's right, father.
This is the first time
I've realized that
you are so cool.
Who asked you to stand out just now?
Do you want to die?
I'm your daughter.
How can I stand down
at such a critical moment?
No, you should.
Don't try to act brave anymore.
You scared me to death.
Father!
Chief!
Make me a pot of soothing tea.
Let me calm myself down.
Be careful.
Be careful, Chief.
Don't worry.
She will be fine.
But it's strange.
By right Nan Yan
shouldn't even have learnt
how to start cultivating,
but when I checked her spiritual chamber
I found that she has almost cultivated a core.
Maybe that's why the Celestial Lightning of Truth
did not hurt her foundation.
She'll be fine after taking some pills
and resting a few days.
Thank you
for helping me today.
I will never forget
your protection.
Please stop.
I do not dare to accept a bow from you.
If you really want to kill all of them,
are you also going to see Nan Yan
getting hunted by the Great Path Sect
for the rest of her life and never get peace?
No matter who comes to attack,
I have to protect her.
Even if you can protect her now,
can you
be by her side forever?
If anything happens to her,
can you
take the responsibility?
Shao Cang,
is that you?
You'd better show yourself.
Otherwise,
don't blame me for what I'll do.
If you show up now,
Nan Yan will have suffered for nothing.
If you trust me,
stay here.
I will have a way.
Nan Yan.
Nan Yan has suffered because of me
and nearly died.
Thank you for helping her in my stead.
Lord Shao Cang is welcome.
I'm just someone with very little influence.
I'm satisfied
if I can just play mahjong all day
and win a few more times.
But if,
someone dares to hurt my disciples,
I'll risk my life
rather than do nothing.
Don't worry, Chief Meng.
I will leave immediately
and never step foot into Lunar Sect again.
Lord Shao Cang understands where I come from.
That’s great.
Everything started because of me.
Nan Yan suffered too much for me,
so let me be the one to end it.
♫When you appeared behind me♫
♫The stars in the sky stopped twinkling too♫
♫The universe has fallen♫
♫When I stand by your side♫
♫Everything in the world turns into nothing♫
♫Only your eyes remain♫
♫Every minute and second that I'm with you is engraved in my mind♫
♫Our story falls into your eyes like smoke and willows♫
♫Can you hold my hands tightly?♫
♫No matter if it's a fair or gloomy day♫
♫From the beginning♫
♫Till the end, oh♫
♫Let me keep going forward with you♫
♫Let all the bright fireworks stop for you, oh♫
♫When the wind blows♫
♫From your brows♫
♫To my heart♫
♫It seems calm but it's actually turbulent♫
♫I was once ignorant♫
♫But am now deeply in love♫
♫All I can say is that I will never leave you♫
♫Let me keep going forward with you♫
♫Let all the bright fireworks stop for you, oh♫
♫When the wind blows♫
[I wish you a lifetime of peace, free from worry and hardship]
You haven't left.
How can I be at ease
with someone like you near her?
I suddenly realized
when the Great Path Elder
came to search for the fugitive that
maybe that person
really is Lord Shao Cang?
You think too much.
What if it's really him?
Chief,
should we conduct a thorough search again?
Why do you have so many what ifs?
This thing is over.
Don't mention it again.
I'll take my leave then.
Hold on.
I haven't finished asking you questions.
You said that someone hidden hurt you.
What's the matter?
I think it's most probably because
you ruined Nan Yan's climbing fig
and was taught a lesson
by the fox spirit, wasn't it?
It's not like that.
At that time I—
Do you really think that
I see nothing
just because I usually
turn a blind eye?
Do you know what this is called?
You deserve it.
From tomorrow onwards,
you'll be confined for three days.
Reflect on yourself!
Yes.
I'll take my leave.
Get lost!
[The Sparrow's Nine Verses]
Something's not right.
The Great Path Sect made
such a big ruckus today.
Chief Nan would've came out
to settle the score just as it started.
I didn't see her in today's game either.
Did something
happen to her?
[Ji Ming Temple]
Lord Shao Cang,
what do you mean by this?
You lured the Great Path Sect here
to force me
to leave Lunar Sect.
Do you think with me gone
no one will stop you from stealing the silver mermaid pearl?
So,
how could I
leave such trouble like you by her side?