[English subtitles are available]
[Love's Rebellion]
[Episode 16]
Open the door
and get out of here.
Be with him
and fulfill your wish.
Ji Yang.
Ji Yang...
No joy, no worries.
No anger, no hatred.
No fear, no desire.
I know
you lured me
to this place
to tell me that
because of me,
he was impaled by the Yin Zhus.
Because of me,
he was doomed.
his remains are gone.
You want me to forget him,
and forget
all the hardships.
Otherwise,
I'll fall into
the endless abyss forever.
When you forget all your emotions, you'll feel relieved.
Only then can you accept your fate
and control the power of the
Seven Sins Manual.
If you are willing,
I can help you.
But I'm unwilling.
So my inner demon
isn't Ji Yang,
but myself.
He's dead.
Why won't you forget him?
Because it takes love
to differentiate good from evil.
It takes love
to see the world's cruelty.
to see the suffering in the world.
Shouldering the seven emotions to cleanse the demons of the world
is the hardest path in the world.
Is it worth it?
I only hope that
no one else suffers like me.
Then everything
will be worth it.
Let me remind you.
After entering the Nine Calamities Pagoda,
your trial will only just begin.
Dragon Lord.
Let me out!
What's he yelling about
in there this time?
Hearing that his friend passed away,
he has been drunk inside for 3 days.
Let me out!
Get my Dad here!
Dad.
Let me out.
I want to find the Demon Clan.
I want to avenge Ji yang.
You want to find the Demon Clan?
How many lives do you have?
Li Chi killed my brother.
As long as he's alive,
Yin Ya and Nan Yan
will be targeted sooner or later.
As their big brother,
I can't just sit and watch.
You are
loyal but incompetent.
You can't even take three hits
from Zhu Sui.
If you meet Li Chi,
can you still survive?
Are you going to depend on your
lame poems?
Zhu Sui is nothing!
Aren't I fine right now?
Come.
Get up.
I want to avenge my friend!
Today, I'll fight your full power
with 10% of my power.
If you can escape
from me,
you can do whatever you want.
I won't stop you anymore!
Okay.
A gentleman never
goes back on his word.
Come!
Zhu Sui was right.
I really have a good-for-nothing son.
Again!
I don't believe this.
You can't even protect yourself
with 90% brute strength and 10% luck.
Yet you want to protect others?
Again!
Tomorrow at noon,
see you at Longting Square.
Young Fox.
This is where you'll cultivate.
Old man,
am I
in your Zijin bowl?
Yes.
The elixir on the stone table
is a treasure with a purifying effect.
It's also your fate.
There is only one fast way
to break the Spirit-Sealing Formation.
Eat it.
Who would believe you?
Who knows if you will harm me?
Given Master's level of cultivation,
he can harm you without doing all of these.
Who are you?
I am Zhen Fang.
You should call me your senior.
That old man is good at naming people.
Your name is Zhen Fang,
Nan Yan is called Zhen Yuan.
If you want it,
you have to get through me.
You're just a kid.
I'll be bullying you if I use any magic.
Old man.
Why are you here?
Master?
You brat.
Don't force me to get serious.
Dad, pardon me.
I will get you
another cup next time.
Zhan,
Your Sun Fire today
was excellent.
Tell me what reward
you would like.
Then...
Can I leave now?
Shut up.
You haven't recovered yet.
No, but I'm already...
Yu Quan.
Get some spirit stones from the storage
and bring out Young Lord's treasured
poem selection.
Print a thousand copies
and distribute them among the 49 whaleboats.
Yes.
No, Dad.
When can I
leave?
S-small master,
can anyone really get through this?
The last person to get through this
was Yin Ruochen from the Nightmare Fox clan.
Who are you lying to?
He's the ancestor of our Fox Clan.
Master told me.
It is said that he took half a year
to get the elixir.
Why don't you
ask Master?
I don't want to ask him now.
Let's...
Try again.
You're on.
I don't feel anything.
Does this elixir take some time
to take effect?
Actually,
this elixir
is just an ordinary pill.
How dare you lie to me?
Old man?
Young friend,
don't you think
your power has improved
after all that training?
So during this period,
you were the one practicing with me?
It's just a clone.
You old liar.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
Where's Nan Yan?
Junior Zhen Yuan
went down the mountain a month ago.
There were demons nearby terrorizing the civilians.
She
killed the head of the demons
within half a month.
They called her
Bloody-handed Asura.
Bloody-handed Asura?
She sent word that she was
investigating the case of Evil Path kidnapping children
in Pingfeng Mountain in the North.
She told you to find her
after you get out.
Little Boy.
Just listen to half of the old man's words.
Don't believe it all.
I'm leaving.
See you never.
Master.
Why did he say
not to believe you?
That's because he's not smart.
Master,
you're just going to let him go?
What can I do?
His cultivation improved rapidly.
We can't trap him here anymore.
I see.
The old man said
Pingfeng Mountain right?
Why is no one here?
Come out.
They're all dead.
Now a fox is here.
You'll help with my cultivation.
It's rare to see a fox
with Core Formation cultivation.
I made a breakthrough?
That old man tricked me again!
Can you check me out again?
Are you crazy?
Dream on!
A cultivator can only attain true joy
by not speaking of taking lives.
You completed your training?
That demonic cultivator just now...
You could have just killed him.
Wasn't shattering him a bit too much?
Everything has a soul.
If the soul is shattered,
the plants can absorb it better.
Listen to yourself.
How can you say that?
Those demonic cultivators hunted on children.
They were sinful.
They deserved it.
What is your cultivation level now?
Yuanying.
This...
That old man
is too biased.
Did you get promoted?
He found an excuse
to imprison me for three years.
He even lied that I was about to be promoted.
You're still a six-tail?
It doesn't matter
as long as you can return to your fox form.
It's so cute.
If I can pet you,
I won't mind how many tails you have.
When I saw you killing without mercy,
I thought you had
become a whole different person.
But you can still joke around,
so I'm relieved.
I just detached myself from worldly desires,
I didn't lose my memories.
Well...
What about him?
Everything has passed.
Now,
I just want to follow the Holy Master's path
to slay the demons and save the world.
The rest
is not important.
You are really determined.
You let it go like you said you would.
What about you?
What's your plan now that you're out?
The Spirit-Sealing Formation cannot be broken
and even the Seven Sins Manual
can't break it.
I plan to
listen to that old man
and focus on cultivating
before finding a way to break the formation.
At worst, I'll bet on my life
and force a way out.
In that case,
come with me.
Where are we going?
To Lunar Sect.
It's been three years.
It's time to visit Meng.
I do miss him.
[Huangquan Prison]
Where is this?
A human spirit in a demonic body.
How wonderful.
You're indeed
a rare talent.
A forbidden spell was cast on you,
but you came back from the dead.
Who are you?
You locked me in your body,
now you pretend you don't remember me?
Have you forgotten?
My Lord, have you forgotten
who you are?
My Lord?
What sect's
lord am I?
Demon Lord Sen Luo.
That is you.
A thousand years ago,
you absorbed the ancient evil,
Yin Zhu, into your body,
and dominated the five states.
Unfortunately,
you were ambushed by Ji Ming
and your body was destroyed.
Only a fragment of your soul was left.
It was imprisoned here.
If I'm Sen Luo,
who are you?
I'm your loyal servant, who has been
waiting for you for a thousand years.
You just said you were my prisoner.
You changed your mind quickly.
Although you sealed me,
I have always
been obedient to you,
waiting for this day to come
and help you achieve your great cause.
What great cause?
That old man Ji Ming
sealed the Yin Zhus around you
in the five prisons.
Huangquan Prison is one of them.
It's also the only prison
that holds your soul.
If you can gather
all the Yin Zhus in the five prisons,
you can control life and death in the world.
The world will be yours to rule.
So,
I still have something important to do.
Why don't I
kill you first?
Please think twice.
My mind is blank,
so you think I have lost my memories
and said that nonsense to me.
That means you're either crazy,
or a liar.
If you don't believe me,
you can summon the Yin Zhu in your body.
You'll know after a try.
Ancient evil beings are quite interesting.
However,
I've lost all my memories.
I'm not interested in becoming
the Demon Lord anymore.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You've been sleeping for a long time.
How about
awakening this prison first?
If you want to make a mark in the future,
I will do my best
to help you seize all the five prisons
and rule the netherworld!
What's the fun of being a lonely ruler?
I'm no longer the man I used to be.
Instead of having fun alone,
I prefer
to drag the whole world
down with me.
Greetings,
Master of Huangquan Prison.
What are you laughing at?
As a Demon Lord,
you gave me the Huangquan Prison just like that.
Yet you still have the mood to laugh?
You...
What?
You're the one who
tried to trick a junior like me.
Didn't you say all that nonsense
just to incite me
to collect the Five Prisons for you?
Junior,
as long as my soul is still here,
you must obey me
and collect the Yin Zhus in the world for me.
When you are in charge of life and death...
Take charge of life and death?
I'm not interested.
You...
It's boring to stay here.
How about
going out for a tour?
Boss lady,
when is your stall opening?
We're all waiting
to be fed.
Yes.
You have to open for business.
Stop arguing.
We need to eat.
My stall is open every day.
I'm afraid the lost ghost
wouldn't dare to drink my wine.
Sir,
please enjoy.
Young sir, you are so handsome.
Waiter.
Serve him well.
Okay.
Our wine
is the best in the North.
After this village,
you won't find a stall as good as this again.
The best in the North?
This wine is the best in the North?
It's no different from water.
Young sir, you must be joking.
This wine is the strongest wine
in the North.
Have another pot.
If it's still tasteless,
I won't charge you for the drinks.
I told you it's tasteless.
Take it away.
What happened?
I gave him
three times the dose.
Even a spirit would faint by now.
What's going on?
The body of a Yin Zhu has no blood or tears.
You don't know agony
and pain.
You cannot taste
anything either.
It's so hard to be a monster.
I can't even savor good wine anymore.
Why worry?
After you destroy the Five Prisons
and collect the Yin Zhus,
if you want to laugh,
all beings will dance in the fire to entertain you.
If you want to cry,
all seas will echo with wails of grief.
The mortal's mere sense of taste
is not worth mentioning.
But now, I only want a scoop of wine.
What's wrong, young sir?
Are you leaving?
Aren't you going to pay for the drinks?
Didn't you say
you wouldn't charge if the wine is tasteless?
I won't charge you for the wine.
But,
now that you're at my stall,
you have to pay for your life!
Get him!
[Wine]
[Ji Ming Temple]
A thousand years ago,
you used the power of
the Yin Zhus
to dominate the five states.
[Ji Ming Temple]
Unfortunately,
you were ambushed by old man Ji Ming
[Ji Ming Temple]
and imprisoned here with hatred.
Enemies are bound to meet.
I'll show you your old friend today.
Ji Ming.
We meet again.
You killed me back then.
Now you're reduced to a piece of rotting wood.
Let's see what you can do to me now!
Don't stop me!
Shut up.
Shouldn't you reflect on yourself?
You're both of old age.
Why is he being worshipped
and praised for centuries,
while you were sealed
and hated for generations?
That old thing had a thousand years to reflect on himself,
and he's still so sensitive.
[Wine]
Why is this place so familiar?
Did I come here before?
This is...
Yin Zhu's aura?
Where is that?
The Lunar Sect.
The Lunar Sect?
They say loneliness is hard to tolerate.
Rao.
Today, you might win
my cards.
[Lunar Sect]
Master.
Master?
Only the Demon Lord Sen Luo
can be called "master"
by the chief of Evil Path.
But Sen Luo died
1000 years ago.
There are indeed great masters in the North.
Few people can take a hit from me
in the cultivation realm.
Who are you?
The Blood Phoenix Hairpin is the treasure of the Chongming Bird Clan.
When the spirit queen passed away,
she gave it to her
only daughter.
This item is extremely precious.
You have no right to keep it.
Give it to me.
I might have no right.
But you don't deserve to keep Chief Nan Fang's item either.
Master.
I'm afraid this person
is stalling you
to lure you away from what's important.
Senior!
What a lovely couple.
How dare you demonic cultivators
break into Lunar Mountain?
Let her go!
Give me the Blood Phoenix Hairpin
and I'll spare your lives.
Stop dawdling.
Do you want to be a couple in the Netherworld?
Wait.
I'll hand it over.
Let her go first.
Yingying.
Brother.
Since we have it,
let's go.
Mian.
Since I have it,
we have to silence him.
The magic of the Seven Sins Manual.
Bloody-handed Asura is here.
Retreat!
What's going on?
Master ordered Yingying and me
to send a hairpin to Tianqiao Peak.
Yingying, Fu Lang.
Remember,
You must deliver this
to Tianqiao Peak
and personally hand it to Sword Master
Meng Xiaolou.
The faster, the better.
Make no mistake.
We never expected
the Demon Clan to intercept
and snatch the hairpin away.
That demonic aura just now
doesn't belong to the ordinary demons.
Something must have happened to the Lunar Sect.
Let's go.
Aren't you bold?
Who are you?
Someone to send you on your way.
Ji Yang?