[English subtitles are available]
[Love's Rebellion]
[Episode 24]
Since you're willing to be the scapegoat,
I'll give you a ride.
Something's added to this candle.
Dawn herb
in powdered form.
It helps keep the fire burning.
So the annual sacrificial ritual
is all about these evil tricks.
Demonic cultivator!
Today, the sacrificial ritual begins.
The demonic cultivator won't give up easily.
Since Heaven has given us a bait,
let them fight for it.
The bride
will be decided by Evil Lord.
If the candle goes out,
you must leave the cave immediately.
Don't fight
and hurt each other.
Go in.
Don't worry.
I'll be out soon.
Jiao Niang.
Welcome, Chief Nan.
Congratulations, Chief Nan.
Chief Nan, I heard you're engaged
and will marry your beloved soon.
Recently, mermaid spirits
have been causing trouble nearby and hurting people.
The court has ordered for a mermaid hunt
and finally caught one.
The mermaid spirit's plight
can be considered compensation for her sins.
The mermaid spirit deserves to die.
If we take its silver mermaid pearl alive,
we'll get a ray of precious light
that's priceless.
Let's kill her now.
But the heaven and earth are watching.
I'm willing to use my humble skill
to let it die without pain.
I hope everyone
doesn't seize her elixir alive.
Young Lord Nan, you're famous for your qin skills.
You specially made a trip here.
I dare not disobey.
It's also part of the mermaid spirit's fate
that she gets to
die happily to this magical tune.
Yes.
We can take the elixir now.
Hurry up.
We can finally take the elixir.
Get the elixir!
Hurry up! Get it!
That's right.
As expected, it's not mortal.
Back then, for my own selfish reasons,
I hurt Jiao Niang
and caused big trouble.
That's why things ended up like this.
It's a serious crime to release
a spirit privately.
Haven't you thought of the consequences?
Sir.
Have you ever regretted it?
After seeing you today,
I know you
can tell right from wrong.
You must've had your reasons
for the matter
in Linglong Capital.
To save her clansmen,
Yin Ya did what she did despite knowing it's impossible.
I know all the righteous sects
hate spirits.
But they are my flesh and blood.
How can I watch
innocent spirits get hurt
and do nothing?
Even if I let you into the formation,
you'll have to pay a huge price
to force the Spirit-Subduing Tablet open.
Even if I'm obliterated,
I won't regret it.
I'm joining you!
You have a big family and business.
Why are you joining me?
It's none of your business.
I said I'm joining you and that's that.
Wait...
Enough, enough.
Young and foolish.
Fine.
If the fox spirits live in seclusion
and vow never to do evil,
I...
am willing to help.
But I can only
sustain it for 30 minutes.
I've never entered this formation before.
I can't guide you.
You've to rely on your wits.
-They're out.
Evil Lord didn't take a fancy to me.
It's Heaven's will.
Maybe your mother
doesn’t want you to get married.
Chief.
It seems
you have so much love
for your clansmen.
I have no other wish in my life.
As long as the fort
is in peace,
I'd have lived up to my ancestors' wishes.
In that case,
why do you send people to die every year?
This is the rule.
Rules are created by people.
They can be flexibly changed.
Every year today,
it must be agonizing for you too.
So what?
If Evil Lord is provoked,
Chidi Fort will really be destroyed.
Foolish.
What does
a foreigner know?
Stop there.
How dare you!
You tampered with my wife's
candle.
Aren't you afraid I'll kill your whole clan?
What are you talking about?
The so-called Evil Lord's choice
is just to choose a red candle
and set up a secret spell.
The chosen one
is destined
to die.
You...
You tampered with the candle
you gave Nan Yan.
You want to protect your clansmen
with Nan Yan's life, right?
Don't forget
you willingly chose
to participate in this.
Count yourself lucky this time.
Your attempt to outwit us
is exactly what I want.
What do you want?
After today,
there will be no Evil Lord in Chidi Fort.
The Queen is coming out.
Welcome, Queen.
Why is it Su?
I really didn't expect
it to be her.
Su is an orphan.
She's really becoming the queen?
When did she
become so capable?
Ba Jiao.
Help your sister.
Evil Lord has bad taste.
Looks like I have to spend an eternity
with my wife.
I'm not meant to be the queen.
I'll just have to admit defeat.
Queen, please enter the formation.
Yan.
Why is your candle
burning so intensely?
What she's holding
is no ordinary candle.
Who are you?
The bride of Evil Lord.
We still don't know
who will win.
She's not Su.
Su can't talk.
Give it to me.
It's just the title of Queen.
If you want it,
I'll give it to you.
Don't you want it?
I'm already married to someone else.
How can I marry Evil Lord?
I was just curious today,
so I got Huo Wuji
to let me in to have a tour.
Here.
Are you okay, Huixiang?
When we go out,
don't say anything.
I will protect you.
Trust me.
Let's go.
Password.
This formation was created by the Great Path.
Is this password
about
flattering the Great Path?
Wrong password.
Two more chances left.
It seems we shouldn't say
the word "password".
Wrong password.
One more chance left.
Get it wrong again
and the formation will be sealed
and annihilated instantly.
This won't do.
We lost two chances.
There's only one chance left.
Do you think we can just break into it?
We can’t use
our spiritual power here.
If a fight broke out,
we'd be doomed.
Plus, these guards
don't look like
they have keys on their waists.
If the formation is sealed,
our efforts will be in vain.
I have an idea.
I used this
to exorcise Nan Yan.
It didn't work then,
but it might this time.
Watch me.
Oh Heaven, Oh Earth.
I'm the best at exorcism.
I'm the best! I'm the best!
Hurry up.
Oh Heaven, Oh Earth.
I'm the best at exorcism.
I'm the best! I'm the best!
Oh Heaven, Oh Earth.
I'm the best at exorcism.
Go on!
Stop!
Have a taste of
the dragons' ultimate move!
That's it?
That's right.
I'm the ultimate move.
It's time.
Enter the bridal chamber.
Demonic cultivator.
You came after all.
Chief.
The fort's people have all been captured.
I'll go
meet your Evil Lord.
If you don't want to die,
behave yourself.
If you offend Evil Lord,
you will be punished.
Punished?
Test me, and I'll kill each
and every one of you
to feed Yin Zhu inside.
Don't bother.
Your Blood Phoenix Hairpin is fake.
Evil Path Chief.
We've been waiting for you.
There's demonic aura.
It's her?
The Seven Sins Manual in my body
can detect demonic cultivators within 100 meters.
The fox's tail has been exposed.
For our next moves,
I'll listen to you, my lady.
She's poorly cultivated,
so she won’t cause any trouble
by infiltrating the fort.
Why don't we play
the long game?
The mastermind will show up
when the formation opens tomorrow.
Who are you?
Chief.
It's them.
Three years ago, at Filth Valley,
they fought for the Seven Sins Manual with us.
So it is
you two babies.
I didn’t kill you then.
Isn’t it good to be alive?
Why have you come to die today?
I've been thinking
about you too, Chief Li.
You're finally here today.
How could I not meet you?
I didn't expose you,
as I was waiting for you to walk into the trap
to annihilate you once and for all.
You're lucky to have survived
till today.
But Ji Yang must be avenged
with your blood.
Who do you think you are, kid?
Bloody-handed Asura?
Move!
Chief, be careful!
Brother!
Yin Zhu?
Take the people outside the cave away.
How can you control Yin Zhu?
Well done.
I'll kill them
for you now.
Get lost!
This and that; perceptions and thoughts.
Sacrifice my soul and blood to that body.
Soul Transference Technique?
He asked for it.
He can't bear
this body of mine.
Sen Luo...
Grandmaster...
I really didn't know it was you.
I was...
I was wrong.
Please spare my life.
L-Let me go.
This is the day I've been waiting for.
My dear disciple.
Give his body to me.
I've been waiting for this day.
We can
finally put an end to this today.
This and that; perceptions and thoughts.
Sacrifice my soul and blood to that body.
Nan Yan.
Ji Yang.
I'm fine.
Brother!
Brother.
Tell me.
Who asked you to seize the prison?
Kill me if you want.
Please!
No!
What do you know?
Shut... up!
He was wearing a mask from the beginning
and never showed his face.
-You wretch!
-I don’t know...
Get lost!
-Brother.
-Get lost!
Brother!
Get lost!
I beg you, Brother.
Tell them what you know.
Get lost!
You failed today.
Do you think he will let you go?
Tell me the truth,
and I can keep her safe.
He committed suicide.
Brother!
Brother.
Why didn't you tell them
who he was?
Why did you kill yourself?
Why did you abandon me?
I'm now alone in this world!
Li Chi deserved to die for his sins.
No.
My brother was not a bad person.
He became demonic
to protect me.
It's all my fault.
For you?
He became demonic
to protect me.
Are you okay?
Here, Mian.
Mian.
Brother, run!
If Evil Path members catch up,
we'll both die.
No, I will protect you.
Get up now.
Get up.
Brother!
Mian!
I’ve done it.
I’ve done it!
I've become a demonic cultivator!
Brother.
Sister. Sister.
Brother, how could you become demonic?
If our parents knew about this,
they...
they wouldn't want to see you being bullied.
Demonic cultivators attack every day.
If I don't become demonic,
who will protect you?
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
He killed Evil Path's chief
and replaced him.
Later,
he started to practice Soul Transference Technique.
Sometimes he was sober
and sometimes possessed.
Once he became bloodthirsty,
he couldn't stop.
I don't ask you to forgive me.
My brother's sins
can't be redeemed.
But
as his sister,
I want to bear
all of his karma and sins
for him.
I want
one more person in this world...
to remember he was a good person.
I don't want to hear this.
Leave now!
It's okay now.
Brother.
I'll take you away.
Thank you, our benefactors.
You saved every one of us
in the fort.
Thank you, our benefactors.
If you really want to thank me,
abolish the rule of the sacrificial ritual
forever.
What?
Evil Lord
will blame us!
Yes!
We've always been like this.
There is no Evil Lord in the cave.
It was just an evil thing
left behind from a century ago.
-Evil thing?
Yes.
It was just an evil thing?
We've been like this for so many years.
How could there be an evil thing?
How is that possible?
What about the Creeping Bloodthorn?
Over the past hundred years,
Creeping Bloodthorn had been infected by that evil thing,
and its bloodthirsty nature intensified.
So,
every year,
the girl you sacrificed
just quenched its thirst.
Then didn't the girls of our fort
all die in vain?
Daughter.
If I had known this,
I wouldn't have sent you
into this fire pit.
It’s all my fault...
The chief was eager to protect the fort's people.
I think
he didn't do it on purpose.
Creeping Bloodthorn
will regenerate even if it's burnt.
We're here
to get the thing out of the cave.
With the evil thing gone,
Creeping Bloodthorn could be eradicated.
Only then would Chidi Fort
avoid future troubles.
This is great.
We're finally
rid of the plague of our fort.
Great!
Thank you.
You don't have to do this.
Get up.
Get up, everyone.
Yan.
I misunderstood you.
Huixiang.
Don’t be upset.
Chief.
You gave me the candle
that doesn't go out.
I guess you didn't want
to see Huixiang die.
So from now on...
I understand
what you mean.
Don't worry.
Leave Huixiang and Ba Jiao
to me.
I also promise
to treat
everyone
in the fort well.
Don't worry.
As long as we have a bite of rice,
they'll have theirs.
Right.
Right?
Thank you, sir and madam.
Ba Jiao.
When you grow up,
take good care of your sister.
Be good.
Nan Yan.
Let's go.
[Youquan Prison]
Come on!