[English subtitles are available]
[Love's Rebellion]
[Episode 11]
So,
how could I let you,
a liability, stay by her side?
You're not killing me?
I'll spare your life.
I have use for you.
May you be safe
and happy.
Nan Yan?
You should
stay in bed.
Well,
hasn't Shao Cang come back yet?
He's left.
When the wind rises, the leaves rustle.
When the wind is gone, it leaves nothing behind.
He didn't want to implicate you
or Lunar Sect,
so he chose to leave alone.
Such a righteous man.
I respect him even more!
Now that
he's gone,
I wonder when we can see him again.
Maybe
when I go to Filth Valley
to look for the Snow Branch,
I can meet him again.
You'll go to Filth Valley too?
Take me with you.
To be honest,
I attract treasures.
It's a gift I was born with.
With me by your side,
you can definitely find…
find…
find that…
Show Branch.
It's the Snow Branch.
Whatever.
No matter what branch it is,
after we find it
and make the Five-Poison Heart Pill,
Shao Cang's heart disease can be cured.
By then,
let me take
some credit.
Don't think too much.
August 15th is coming.
Today,
let's have a good meal.
Well,
tomorrow is August 15th.
I need to go down the mountain to visit my mom.
Why don't you
go with me?
You're all alone.
You might as well celebrate
the festival with me.
Can I?
Okay.
My pleasure.
By the way,
where's that annoying fox?
I haven't seen him since I woke up.
He's so unreliable.
We agreed he'd look after you
when I was away getting you food.
He actually ran away and left you alone.
Ji Yang has always
hated Little Fox.
They've both disappeared.
Could it be that…
It can't be.
Then, when we go into Filth Valley
to collect the fox's body,
should we bring a pot
or a coffin?
A coffin.
Fox meat
is gamy.
Well,
I'll prepare some food for you.
Meng Ying?
What's the matter?
Well...
Actually, Ji Yang
is not the fox spirit, right?
I knew it.
My dad just took
that fox spirit in.
How could it be that
he has your mom's heart disease too?
And that fox spirit
doesn't look like a sick man.
Meng Ying.
I can explain.
Alright.
You don't need to explain anything.
I swear
I'll never tell anyone,
not even my dad.
But I still think
my dad has seen through it.
That's why he used that fox spirit as a cover.
As for Ji Yang,
whether he is
Lord Shao Cang or not
is none of my business.
I just hope
you can stay safe.
Thank you.
By the way,
this is for you.
I made some mooncakes.
Happy early Mid-Autumn Festival.
Have a good rest.
I'll get going.
Thank you.
By the way,
I almost forgot to tell you.
You nailed it today.
Do you want a bite?
I already apologized.
Don't be so petty.
Shut up.
Smell it.
It smells so good.
I'm not hungry.
Take it away.
Stop pretending.
If you lose weight
or get sick,
Yan will think
I mistreated you.
She'll try to take my Internal Elixir
to make medicine for you again.
Don't worry.
You will never see her again.
Fine.
I won't see her again.
How about you?
You won't see her again either?
My Lord,
you're so cruel.
Yan was struck by lightning
for you.
But you
left without saying goodbye.
Also,
tomorrow is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
People celebrate reunions on this day.
But now,
you and she are worlds apart.
God sent you to me,
but after just a few days,
he took you back.
♫The sound of rain♫
♫I hold my breath♫
♫Our promise under the umbrella♫
My Lord.
It seems
♫When I'm with you♫
you're not very good at woodwork.
♫It becomes clear♫
Master didn't teach me it.
♫I'll hold up for you♫
I taught myself.
♫Even if it rains heavily♫
Thank you.
♫The blurry world is now clear♫
It's a bit ugly,
but…
I like it very much.
♫I won't give up♫
♫I'll protect you♫
I know you didn't want
to drag me in,
so you left quietly.
But you
are so heartless.
If you had told me,
I would understand you.
Why did you leave without saying goodbye?
Did you come back for me
because you like me?
Say yes.
♫The sound of rain♫
♫I hold my breath♫
Do you like me or not?
♫Our promise under the umbrella♫
Say yes.
♫When I'm with you♫
♫It becomes clear♫
♫I'll hold up for you♫
♫Even if it rains heavily♫
Yes.
♫The blurry world is now clear♫
♫I won't give up♫
♫I'll protect you♫
♫I'll hold up for you♫
♫Even if it rains heavily♫
♫The blurry world is now clear♫
♫I won't give up♫
♫I'll protect you♫
What a surprise
that you're waiting for me.
Why is it tea?
Wine is poison.
Tea is the antidote.
I've used poison my whole life.
Today,
I can finally cure the pain
in my heart.
Can't you just wait a little longer
for your daughter?
She's studied in Lunar Sect
for two years.
It's for you.
If all her efforts are in vain,
what can I say to comfort her?
At Yan's age,
she should be traveling around the Five States
to see this beautiful world.
But because of me,
she's stuck here.
After I pass away,
I don't want her
to become
as powerful as me.
I just wish she could find the one for her
and live a carefree
and peaceful life.
That's all I want for her.
Are you sure
you can entrust Yan
to that boy?
It's their fate.
I can't decide anything.
I just let nature take its course.
Fate is ruthless.
If one chooses not to feel,
life will become a prison.
If one chooses to feel,
they'll have to fight fate.
I only hope
they can protect
and look out for each other.
They can't be
a normal couple.
But I wish
they could love each other
till the end of their days.
Nan Yan.
What's all that?
We're just going down the mountain to celebrate the festival.
Why are you carrying so many things?
It's my first time meeting my godmother.
How can I go empty-handed?
That's improper.
Look at these things.
And this.
These are all gifts
for my godmother.
Look.
What do you think?
Is this gift good enough
for the Queen of Mahjong in the North?
When did my mom
become your godmother?
As the saying goes,
you're fatherless and I'm motherless,
so your mother will be my godmother.
Whatever.
Shao Cang
is like my brother.
He'll propose sooner or later.
With your mom being my godmother,
we'll all become family.
What's wrong?
He'll marry you sooner or later.
I'm helping my buddy
curry favor with your mom.
What's wrong with that?
Let me make it clear.
Don't cozy up to my mom.
She'll ask you to drink
and play dice with her
and win all your money.
Gosh.
It doesn't matter.
I don't mind losing money to my godmother.
Wait for me.
Osmanthus blooms around August 15th.
Why are peach trees blooming?
Could it be the magic of some immortal?
There are no immortals here.
Only
daydreams.
Have you never thought about ascension
after joining Lunar Sect?
I joined Lunar Sect
to cure my mom's disease.
When my mom recovers one day,
I'll take her
to travel around the Five States
and live a carefree life.
100 years is enough.
If one
lives for 500 years
or thousands of years
but doesn't have family and friends around
and is always alone,
what's the point of that?
You're wise.
We share the same view.
Beautiful flowers under the full moon.
[Mooncake]
My godmother
will be very happy.
[Mooncake]
Let's go.
My mom must be waiting.
Mom.
Isn't she home?
She should be.
Mom, I'm back.
This is not right.
I haven't been back for so many days.
The house
should be a mess.
Has she
gone on a trip?
Mom.
Chief.
N-Nan Yan.
Why aren't you
r-resting
in the sect?
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I came back to see my mom.
I'm old.
I actually forgot about the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Well,
your mom didn't come to play mahjong with me yesterday.
It's said she's gone traveling.
So I came
to check it out.
She's really not home.
She's gone traveling?
Impossible.
We agreed on it.
After I cure her heart disease,
I'll go traveling with her.
You know her temper best.
She's spontaneous.
No one can stop her.
How about this?
Your mom is not home anyway.
Why don't you guys
celebrate the festival
with Yingying and me?
Okay.
Let's go.
Chief.
Are you
going to visit someone's grave?
Who else could it be?
Yingying's mother.
No way.
People visit graves on Tomb-Sweeping Day
or during the Ghost Festival,
not during the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I just miss my wife.
There's no need to pick a day.
Chief.
Who told you
my mom went traveling?
Someone I play mahjong with.
Where did she go?
I didn't ask.
Chief.
My mom doesn't have many friends
in Lunar Town.
You're her only friend.
It's my honor.
All these years,
you've helped her a lot for me.
If she was going on a trip,
why would she
not tell you
when she was leaving
and where she was going?
Chief.
Where on earth
is my mom?
Your mom…
Chief.
Did something happen to her?
Your mom…
passed away.
Godmother.
Nan Yan and I
came to see you.
Although we've never met,
I've heard a lot about you from Nan Yan.
I picked these gifts
especially for you.
I hope, in the afterlife,
you can still be the winner
at every mahjong table.
I want to spend some time alone
with my mother.
Okay.
We'll wait for you at home.
It's getting dark.
Don't stay too late.
Why does your needle
look longer than before?
If you don't behave,
my needle
will become even longer.
Here we go.
Does it hurt?
I'm used to it.
Hang in there.
Yan.
Look at you.
All you think about every day
is poisons
and needles.
What if one day
a young man from Lunar Sect
wants to be close to you,
and you scare him away?
All I think about
is traveling around
the Five States with you
after you recover.
But I
can't stay with you forever.
Why not?
In the future,
you just need to enjoy your life.
I'll make sure you live a long life.
I'll buy you
your favorite steamed rice cake.
Wait for me here.
Come back soon.
I'm scared of being alone.
Okay.
Take it.
Wait for me here.
Mom.
You promised
to travel around the world
with me after you recovered.
Why did you break your promise?
Chief Nan Fang has passed away.
How could you leave me alone?
Peach trees are blossoming at the wrong season,
guiding seekers of truth
and marking the ends of the enlightened.
Just now,
I dreamed of my mom.
The dead can't come back to life.
I'm sorry.
You came to see me.
I don't want you to leave.
If you want to leave now,
it's not too late.
Cry it out.
In the past,
my mom kept telling me
she wanted to go traveling.
But I didn't allow her.
I was afraid she'd get too tired.
I always thought...
I always thought I still had time
to cure her.
Do you think…
Do you think she'd blame me?
No.
She would never blame you.
I wonder
what kind of person
my godmother was.
She was amazing.
How?
She drank when she could
and never lost at mahjong tables.
Footloose and fancy-free.
She had the world in her heart
and could see through everything.
She never cared about what other people said
and never showed any emotion.
She was like a god
who saw beyond the world.
It's hard to believe
someone like that existed.
It's a pity
I didn't get to meet her.
It's late.
Are you leaving?
I have to go to
Filth Valley.
Take this.
No.
Your mom left it for you.
I can't take it.
Filth Valley is dangerous.
This will come in handy.
At the street market,
I learned to hide my aura.
I can handle the Candlelight Beetles.
I can't take this.
I know
you may have a way to deal with the Candlelight Beetles.
But
Little Fox told me
there's an evil spirit
called Yin Zhu
in the depths of Filth Valley.
It sucks people's souls.
♫Can you hold my hands tightly?♫
If you meet it,
you'll die.
The silver mermaid pearl
♫No matter if it's a fair or gloomy day♫
can hide your aura and breath
and help you get past it.
♫From the beginning♫
Here.
♫Till the end, oh♫
♫Let me keep going forward with you♫
♫Let all the bright fireworks stop for you♫
Remember.
You need to return it to me.
You must come back alive.
♫When the wind blows♫
Okay.
I promise you.
♫When the wind blows♫
[Li Chi, Chief of the Evil Path Sect]
Chief.
Sorry for not receiving you.
You're injured.
Just a minor injury.
Don't worry, Chief.
You were hurt by the monarch of the Great Path.
It can't be just a minor injury.
Don't worry, Chief.
I recovered a few days ago.
I'm fine now.
It won't…
It won't affect
me serving the Evil Path.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
There's something
I need you to do.
[Li Mian, the Evil Path Sect]
She's the only person
who saw Yin Zhu
and lived to tell about it.
She has Yin Zhu's aura on her.
Making her into a demonic pill
can help us hide from Yin Zhu
when we go deep into Filth Valley.
It's the best way
she can serve the Demon Clan.
Chief, you're wise.
[Zhan Xian, an elder of the Evil Path Sect]
I heard that
Yin Zhu eats people's souls
in the depths of Filth Valley.
Do we have to take this risk?
Of course!
Thousands of years ago,
when Sen Luo, the Demon Lord, was close to success,
Holy Master killed him with the Seven Sins Manual,
a kind of demon subduing magic.
From then on, the Demon Clan has been in decline!
If we don't ruin the Seven Sins Manual,
the Demon Clan can never be revived!
I…
I'm just worried
about your safety.
You're worried about me?
You're just worried about
losing the cure
to the poison in you, right?
I dare not.
Zhan Xian, Deng Ba.
Yes.
Filth Valley will open tomorrow.
Seal your demonic aura.
These tokens
can make you appear as disciples of orthodox sects.
[Deng Ba, an elder of the Evil Path Sect]
Take these tokens
and go with me.
Brother.
There are many great cultivators in the valley.
The monarch of the Great Path
may be among them.
He killed Elder Yu Yong.
Elder Die Wan
was seriously injured by him.
Should we…
What?
Even if we run into him,
what's there to be afraid of?
Even if we meet
the premier of the Great Path,
we'll still kill him
if he tries to stop us
from ruining the Seven Sins Manual.
You're wise, Chief.
Nan Yan.
You're back.
Chief Meng told me a lot
about your mom's achievements.
I can only say
the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Go pack up.
Go back to Lunar Sect with me
for the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Chief.
I have to stay
to sit vigil for my mom.
Fine.
You can go back tomorrow.
Yingying and I
will celebrate the festival for you then.
I'm going into Filth Valley tomorrow
to look for the Snow Branch.
But your mom already…
Ji Yang's heart disease hasn't been cured.
I still need to make
the Five-Poison Heart Pill.
Filth Valley
is not a good place.
Don't go there
unless necessary.
My mom has passed away.
I don't want to have more regrets.
Okay.
You must be careful.
Don't act tough.
Don't worry, Chief.
I'll protect Nan Yan.
Are you going with her?
Of course.
Have you forgotten?
I planned to go to Filth Valley
to look for Shao Cang.
Now that he needs the pill
to treat his heart disease,
I'll do my best
to help Nan Yan.
You young people
have so many ideas.
Never mind.
I can't stop you.
Keep this in mind.
Don't go deep into Filth Valley.
Once you find the Snow Branch,
come out immediately.
Don't delay any longer.
Understand?
Yes.
I'm leaving.
I need to go back now,
or Yingying will complain.
Young Lord,
don't forget to give the thing to her.
Okay.
What thing?
Your mom left this for you.
Chief found it
when he went through your mom's stuff.