[English subtitles are available]
[Love's Rebellion]
[Episode 23]
My wife has squandered all of our fortune.
It looks like
we will be cold and hungry from now on.
Tell me.
How's the intel coming along?
I've been dealing with it for a long time.
I'm a little thirsty.
Here.
Have some tea.
There's no one else here.
What have you found out?
It looks like the people here
know nothing about Youquan Prison.
Even Huo Wuji doesn't seem to
know much about it.
It must be Holy Master
who sealed Yin Zhu here.
That's what caused
the Creeping Bloodthorn to mutate.
Creeping Bloodthorn is nothing to be afraid of.
It might just scare
the people in the village.
It's just...
I don't know if there are any
hidden motives in this ceremony.
Even Huo Wuji keeping silent.
There's definitely something going on.
Could the Jiluo Festival
be related to the ceremony?
Why don't I immediately
drag Huo Wuji to the battlefield
and give him a good scare?
That'll get him to activate the formation in advance.
There's no need to alert him.
Why don't we wait for the formation to be activated tomorrow?
We'll take the opportunity to go in then.
You're right.
We'll do whatever you say.
My lady.
Would you be willing to
see the lantern display with me tonight?
[Spirit-Sealing Formation]
We're here?
It's right here.
Where's the formation?
I don't know either.
The Spirit-Sealing Formation is complicated and confusing.
There's all sorts of tricks in there.
It's not something that
ordinary people like us can just figure out.
So did we just come here to try our luck
without knowing what's going on?
Wait.
This is no ordinary fog.
I can't tell what's different.
It's an illusion.
Now that you mentioned it.
I am feeling giddy.
Sister!
By the order of the Premier of Great Path Sect,
we will take everyone from the Nightmare Fox clan
and seal them in the Spirit-Sealing Formation.
[Mu Zhanting's Poetry Book Signing]
Young Lord, you're now famous across the five states.
Mr. Shanyang.
Don't talk nonsense.
I am...
just a talented and brilliant
poet.
Right, here.
Next.
Sir.
My Lady
has no appetite,
because she has been holding onto this book of poems
and refuses to part with it.
Nian.
I-I was previously wrong about you.
I hope
I'll get to share a drink and recite poems with you
on a beautiful day soon.
Okay.
Here.
Is it my turn?
Next.
Hu.
Master.
Is that you?
What is true could also be fake.
Whether it's true or false
all depends on your state of mind.
Hu.
When you were practicing in the alms bowl,
I secretly planted a strand of
divine energy within you to protect you.
This is all an illusion?
If not for Master,
I'd have almost fell into its trap.
Just drinking and reading poems.
What else could we ask for in life?
That's all I need.
Since no one is asleep even in the middle of the night,
let's all gather and exchange ideas as poets.
In the future, if I...
become an eminent scholar,
no one will have to attend court in the morning.
Big Brother.
This is...
Turns out, it was a dream.
It wasn't a dream.
It's a illusion of the Spirit-Sealing Formation.
Little Fox,
what did you see in the illusion?
Qingqiu.
When I used to be in Qingqiu,
I always wanted to get out.
Now when I want to go back, but I can't.
Mother has nothing better to do all day.
All she knows is to ponder over
which vixen is the prettiest,
and then drag me onto blind dates.
That's because
you've been asking to go out,
and that made her worried.
She will only rest her heart when she gets her grandchildren.
I won't have children.
I will never have children.
I am never ever having children.
Sister,
why don't you become the fox queen?
You could guide Fox Clan to build Qingqiu.
As for me,
I want to travel around the world
and live a carefree life.
What do you think?
Fine.
I'll tell Mother tomorrow
to let you off the hook.
If I knew the Fox Clan
would end up like this,
I wouldn't be
so willful back then.
How about...
You make the illusionary fog
appear again?
Let's take a few more breaths
and go back to our old dreams.
Do you want to die?
One day in the illusion
is a few decades in the mortal world.
Many people were like you
and chose to immerse themselves in the illusion.
Before they know it,
they are already dead.
If it weren't for
the blood of the Nightmare Fox Clan,
there was no way we could break free from the formation.
Both of us could have been
dead just now.
No, that won't do.
Right, we've got work to do.
Let's go.
The biggest lantern stall
in our village is up ahead.
Boss.
Huixiang.
Take a look.
I'll take this one.
Huixiang.
Have you made your preparations
for the ceremony tomorrow?
Well, I'm here to count on your blessings.
Your shop is the most efficacious
when it comes to making wishes.
These two are the guests
at my house.
They're newlyweds,
and I'm really envious.
Could you also please
pick a lantern for them?
My lady,
which one do you like?
I...
I see you two have a lot of love for each other.
How about this lantern?
Flowers fall with love,
and the river flows with affection.
May both of you
be in everlasting bliss.
It's a pair of mandarin ducks on the lantern.
The lantern
is really beautiful.
Of course.
Any couple
who wishes upon this lantern
will definitely stay together.
Fine.
I'll decide for my wife.
We'll take this one.
Okay.
Hold tight.
This lantern is so beautiful.
Yan, both of you should come with us.
Okay.
♫I weave through the crowd♫
♫Rain passes by, leaving traces♫
♫How lucky I am to meet you♫
♫There is endless scenery to be seen♫
♫There are too many topics to talk about♫
What did you wish for?
♫I'll be with you until it's sunny♫
May all beings
enjoy this spectacle peacefully every year.
That's all?
Nothing else?
One day,
when the dust is settled,
come back to the Sorrow Mountain Brahma Sea with me.
Sounds good.
But the Sorrow Mountain Brahma Sea
is a really quite place.
I'm just a commoner.
I just want to
do all the mundane things with you.
Don't say that.
Just for this moment,
can you forget about the world
and just focus on us?
♫The sound of rain♫
♫I hold my breath♫
♫Our promise under the umbrella♫
What about you?
What did you wish for?
♫When I'm with you♫
♫It becomes clear♫
I wished for
♫I'll hold it up for you♫
for your wishes to come true.
♫Even if it rains heavily♫
♫The blurry world is now clear♫
♫I won't give up♫
♫I'll protect you♫
♫I weave through the crowd♫
♫Rain passes by, leaving traces♫
♫How lucky I am to meet you♫
I really envy you two.
If only I could fall in love
and marry someone
just as good.
That's not easy.
You'll need to learn from Yan.
I'm afraid I won't get the chance.
What's wrong?
I've already made my wish.
I'll try my best to be a bride
and sacrifice myself to Evil Lord
at the ceremony tomorrow.
Sacrifice yourself to Evil Lord?
This is the Spirit-Sealing Formation
set by Great Path Sect.
Let's go.
What's the hurry?
I came well-prepared.
Isn't this the Drunken Qin
which you stole from the shop
before we alighted the whaleobat?
Well, don't say that.
Boss.
Get me the Drunken Qin.
This Drunken Qin
is our shop's treasure.
If you are looking to play qin as you write poems,
why don't you consider
the top-class Wuya Qin?
I promise it will
live up to your expecations.
His poems...
probably go better with a suona.
Don't you say anything.
Don't be a nag.
I want only want the Drunken Qin.
Besides, yours is not the legitimate item.
Why do you feel upset parting with it?
Although it's not legitimate,
it's still a top-notch counterfeit
in the cultivation realm.
Forget it.
Yu Quan told me everything.
You've got ten
of this counterfeit qin.
Fine.
I'll get it for you.
What other tricks
do you have up your sleeve?
Little Fox.
Do you see this score?
[Silent Night]
Silent Night?
Yes.
These past three years,
I asked around
and finally got something useful
from Yu Quan's mouth.
It is said that
the formation guard here
is a qin master.
Silent Night is his musical piece.
You mean
you want to lure him out with the sound of the qin?
Yes.
But Silent Night
also has some tricks to it.
It seems that it can only be played
by the real Drunken Qin.
But the real Drunken Qin
has been destroyed.
So,
I asked around some more.
Yu Quan told you more things?
That's right.
Yu Quan said
the best fake
is on the whaleboat.
That's why
I stole—
I bought it for you.
Big Brother,
you really got smarter.
Look.
You are the Mighty Dragon's brother.
How can I watch you
risk your life?
Right?
Come.
It's very fun
to meet with the qin.
Little Fox,
do you need me to burn incense and fan for you?
Hey.
Do you know how to play or not?
Silent Night can't be
learned so easily.
Why don't you do it?
Forget it.
I only know how to play with words.
I know nothing about playing music.
Play it yourself.
Wait a minute.
Here.
Take it yourself.
Wait a minute.
Okay, go ahead.
[Silent Night]
Who is messing around?
This is sacrilegious.
[Nan Yi, Young Lord of Yao Palace]
Silent Night.
These are the women
who married the Evil Lord over the years.
Is the so-called sacrifice
to send these girls
into the formation?
That's the Evil Lord's mansion.
A hundred years ago, the Evil Lord suddenly appeared
and countless Creeping Bloodthorns
extended from his mansion.
They almost killed the whole village.
Our ancestors tried all sorts of solutions.
In the end, they chose a bride
and sent her to the mansion.
Indeed, the Creeping Bloodthorns
no longer spread that year.
The rule of doing this
once per year
continued after that.
Then why do you want to be the bride?
Those who marry the Evil Lord
are given the title of Queen
and given a candle here.
Not only can they be respected by the whole village,
but their families are also treated well.
So,
you did this for Ba Jiao?
I don't want him to suffer
with me anymore.
But to get from the formation's entrance
to the Evil Lord's mansion, I still have to pass a test.
I heard the test is hard.
I don't know if I can do it.
But have you ever thought
that maybe there is
no Evil Lord at all?
Maybe you'll just die
if you go in.
Who cares what's inside?
It’s a good thing
to protect the entire village by myself.
With money and a good reputation,
Ba Jiao can start a family and his career.
He can live proudly in the village too.
That’s enough.
The celebration is about to begin.
I'll go take a look.
To put it bluntly,
the custom of this place
is human sacrifice.
Many girls have been killed.
Talks about the Evil Lord
are ridiculous.
But they strongly believe
in this matter.
If we insist on breaking into the formation tomorrow,
even if we can
deal with Huo Wuji by himself,
I’m afraid it’ll hard to deal with
the entire village.
We will hurt the innocent too.
Are you thinking...
I'll be
the Queen this year.
No.
It's dangerous if we don't know the situation.
Didn't you say
that my reputation
as the Bloody-handed Asura is well-known?
What?
You don't trust me now?
It's not that I don't trust you.
Is there another way
to see Youquan Prison faster?
This is the only way
to help you overcome the demon
and find who murdered Chief Meng.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
Since you want to be the Queen,
then
I can only be Evil Lord.
Chief.
The competition is about to begin.
Coming.
There's no hurry.
Let's talk.
You?
I have something
to discuss with you.
You two?
No discussion.
You lied to me.
Didn't you say you have
no cultivation at all?
I'm a little curious.
I want to know
what your Evil Lord looks like.
Please do me a favor
and allow me to participate
in the Queen's selection tomorrow.
Are you crazy?
My wife is so polite.
How dare you call her crazy?
You must want to die.
Threats are what I fear
the least.
Even killing me will do no good.
I won’t allow outsiders
to meddle in our village's affairs.
Still being stubborn?
Yes or no?
Absolutely not.
My lady,
attack.
Wait!
Do you have any last words?
If you win
today's competition,
I'll let you go. How about it?
Deal.
You're done?
Why is there no response?
This can't be it.
If the qin master knew
someone played his piece so badly,
he should jump out to hit you.
Who is playing the Silent Night?
Sir.
The one playing was I,
Yin Ya.
The Silent Night was composed together by Ying Zewei
of the Great Path.
It has never been disclosed.
Where
did you learn it from?
I got the sheet music
from Dragon Court Treasury.
And who are you?
I am Mu Zhanting, the Young Dragon Lord.
Young Dragon Lord?
I was an old friend of Dragon Lord.
A century has passed.
I didn't know he's started a family.
This is a forbidden place of the cultivation realm.
What brings you two juniors
here?
I want to open the formation
to save my clan.
Ridiculous!
The Spirit-Sealing Formation has sealed the many spirits
for 100 years.
It's impossible
to open it.
The hundred years are up.
The spirits are still being tormented inside
the Spirit-Sealing Formation
You broke the contract first
and you didn't give us an explanation.
I want to save my clansmen.
What's wrong with that?
I'm just guarding the formation.
As for the matter of the spirits,
the Great Path is in charge.
Please leave.
I'll pretend you never came.
If you insist on stopping me,
I will risk my life to fight you.
Let's show him what we've got!
The silver mermaid pearl?
Why is this pearl
with you?
Yan.
Huixiang.
Are you here for the game too?
Yes.
How do we play this game?
See that
flower ball over there?
When the drumming starts,
the ball will be passed around.
Once the drumming stops,
whoever has the flower ball is out of the game.
That's it?
The last one standing
without the flower ball
will be the winner.
Okay. Let’s go have a look.
Chief.
Keep your promise.
You should let me join the selection tomorrow.
What?
You want to join the selection too?
Trust us.
You...
Are so despicable.
Don't be a sore loser.
[Jiao Niang]
After I return to the Yao Palace
and report our matter
to my mother and sister,
I will marry you.
What does marry mean?
It means we will
sleep together when we're alive
and be buried together when we're dead.
Will it be like now
till the day we die?
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
By the way,
I heard spirits have been spotted in the vicinity lately.
You're a mortal.
You have no cultivation.
While I'm away,
you must be wary of danger.
Don't worry.
But do you know that
without the silver mermaid pearl
concealing my aura,
I'm also the danger you speak of?
Is this pearl really his?
The silver mermaid pearl suddenly recognizes its owner
and he acted so anxiously.
If it weren't for
the appearance of the mermaid's divine energy
stopping him just now,
we would have been dead.
The silver mermaid pearl
was really given to you
by a lady surnamed Nan?
Absolutely.
I swear on my dad's life.
This pearl is my sister
Nan Yan's heirloom.
Her uncle left it to her mother
and her mother left it to her.
What's her mother's name?
I don't know.
Chief Nan Fang of Yao Palace,
Nan Rao.
It's her, then.
My sister.
Are you
Chief Nan Fang's brother,
Nan Yi?
Oh my!
Uncle!
Uncle.
What do you mean?
Uncle, you are...
I...
Who is your uncle?
Don't talk nonsense.
Uncle.
Fine.
You...
Listen to me.
Uncle,
you don't know.
Actually, Little Fox, Nan Yan, and I
have already bowed to heaven and earth.
We're just sworn siblings, don't talk like we're married.
Whose side are you on?
Don't sworn siblings have to
bow to heaven and earth too?
No.
It's not important.
Anyway,
we were like a family
back in the Lunar Sect.
We even went to Filth Valley together.
We lived and died together.
Our relationship,
oh man,
is closer than a real family!
No wonder she gave you
the silver mermaid pearl.
She acted so freely.
It's very like her mother.
Uncle,
since we are family,
please help us
and let us in.
Uncle.
Great Path's people
are on their way.
If we miss this opportunity,
we don't know
how much longer the fox clan will be locked inside.
As I said,
the Premier has his own reason
to strengthen the Spirit-Sealing Formation.
If the spirits return to the world,
it'll inevitably cause more trouble.
Great Path must uphold the greater good.
If your innocent family and loved ones
were subjected to slaughter
by the righteous groups
purely because they are spirits,
sir,
what would you do?
What did you say?
Don't upset him.
Now that I know
your name,
I understand
why you were exiled here
for a hundred years.
Sir,
you were once the son of the Red Emperor,
Young Lord of the Yao Palace.
But for a mere mermaid,
you committed the Linglong Capital massacre.
Shut up!
What do you think?
Do I look the part?
The Evil Lord's bride
is indeed the most beautiful.
Sit.
No one would expect that
the bride is wearing
the real Blood Phoenix Hairpin.
Why are you doing this?
What's in it for you to be the Queen?
Huixiang,
if I persuade you
to give up on this selection,
will you listen to me?
You helped me a lot.
But I will never
give up on this matter.
Ba Jiao's future life
depends on me.
In that case,
no matter what happens today,
I will protect you.
We'll depend on our own skills.
I may not lose to you.
Sister Nan Yan,
you look like a fairy
in this outfit.
You look prettier than my sister.
This brat.
He's sweeter than me.
Ba Jiao, come here.
Why do these two foreigners
insist on joining
our ritual?
They're even a couple.
And now he's giving his wife to the Evil Lord just like that.
What kind of man is he?
My lady.
I'm starting to regret it.
Don't worry.
Everyone is here.
The ritual begins.
As usual,
each of you
will take a red candle
and enter the Luanfeng Cave.
Whoever comes out of the cave
with her candle still lit
will be the Queen of this year.
Luanfeng Cave
is no more than a hundred feet in and out.
But there is wind everywhere in the cave.
It's not that easy
to protect the candle's flame.
Don't worry.
It's easy.
Since you're willing to be the scapegoat,
I'll send you off.