It's his ears.
He lost his hearing because of this.
Suppurative otitis media due
to a generalized infection.
As the infection is already underway,
a definite diagnosis
and treatment is crucial.
We can't run a diagnostic test here.
We must hurry before it
develops into sepsis.
We don't have much time.
We have another suspected
Nipah virus patient reported.
The patient is a 68-year old man,
and the hospital is running
the diagnostic test.
The KCDC stated the results
will be out by midnight,
with many eyes watching.
Yes.
Are the results out?
- Honey!
- Are you okay?
My baby!
Father.
Yes, it's Kang Mi Rae.
After the examination and
treatment, you'll get well.
- Please take good care of him.
- Yes, we will.
Let's go.
Good job, everyone.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Great job, Dr. Cha.
You did great.
Dr. Kang Mi Rae.
You played the biggest role today.
My role was...
merely an acquaintance
to the priest.
At times, rather than us who observe
the patient through equipment,
a friend who observes a patient's life...
is a better doctor.
But...
do you think Sunbae will be okay?
♫ Until she calls you ♫
Whether a discipline or a lawsuit,
I'll gladly accept it.
And...
most importantly,
your phantom limb pain...
I'll take responsibility and
do my best to cure it.
Can it be cured?
Miss.
You see the holes, right?
Put both of your arms in them.
Let's open the box now.
♫ Look at these hearts ♫
♫ Burning up ♫
♫ Defeats by the fire fight ♫
You said your amputated right arm
feels paralyzed, correct?
Yes.
As if I'm clenching my fist.
We'll try unclenching that fist now.
First,
clench your left hand into a fist.
Look in the mirror then
unclench your fist.
♫ The traces you find ♫
♫ One way street that
leads back to you ♫
It's open.
How can this be?
I opened the hand that isn't there.
Now, fold your fingers one by one.
Yes.
Good job.
- Melioidosis?
- Yes.
Further delays would've
resulted in sepsis,
and might have resulted in death.
If Dr. Cha hadn't gone in...
what would've happened?
- Director?
- So...
Dr. Cha diagnosed solely on
observation without equipment...
Is that it?
Yes.
Pardon?
Right now?
I understand.
We have reporters at the
Dept. of Pain Medicine.
They're inquiring what was diagnosed
since it wasn't the Nipah virus.
Prepare the briefing again
and call Dr. Cha.
Pardon?
A doctor entered a quarantined
center risking his life.
He discovered bacteria which
was dormant for over 40 years.
How can we pass up such an
amazing and rare medical story?
What are you doing?
- I have a patient...
- Be quiet and just follow me.
[ Treatment Room ]
Have a seat.
I said, have a seat.
♫ I can't see no matter how I try ♫
♫ Like a dream which
has ended for me ♫
No fever.
Now your blood pressure.
I'll do it.
I'll do it. Lift your arm.
♫ You're still lingering behind me ♫
♫ Even though I'm not able to
♫ Erase away your pain ♫
♫ It's our destiny and
I can't get away ♫
♫ A day full of sorrow and pain ♫
♫ I'm here now ♫
It's normal.
♫ Right by your side ♫
I'll check your pulse.
I'll do it after I see my patient.
I'll do it, just let it be.
♫ I always trust in you ♫
♫ Right by your side ♫
What's the problem?
There was nothing I could do.
You were next to
an infected patient.
I was worried sick,
but what's even worse
is that you looked happy
while I was scared.
I know.
That you'll never change.
You'll keep thinking of
only your patients until
you're black and blue.
So I plan to change.
♫ I'll comfort your heart ♫
I'll try to understand you, Dr. Cha.
You said I'll never understand.
No.
I can.
♫ Are you listening to me ♫
What is this about?
You brought him?
You look well.
What a relief.
Right?
Keep looking.
So what will you do?
About what?
I'm sure you didn't bring
him just to show me.
He still has a cast,
you shouldn't bring him...
He'll stay with me until
the cast comes off.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
Why? You don't believe me?
I didn't see you as the type
to take care of stray cats.
Geez...
So when did you start
doing volunteer work?
From my med school days.
- I used to follow Chief around.
- I see.
Chief does volunteer work, too?
She's been to Africa several times.
Wow...
I did have her pegged right.
What do you mean?
A female warrior.
She's charismatic and capable.
Plus, she's a humanitarian. Wow...
You're teasing me, right?
Teasing you?
No one really likes the Chief.
But why? I thought she's
a very rare and special lady.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
How?
Like you, Dr. Cha.
You don't understand pain...
but you understand
a patient's suffering.
I'll be like that, too.
As you do, I'll...
try to understand you.
Why are you laughing?
Sorry.
I wasn't laughing at you.
I...
don't understand
a patient's suffering.
I just...
study and analyze like crazy.
I put my imagination into overdrive...
and picture everything.
You'll do the same.
But...
there's a difference...
between knowing and understanding.
I monitor myself on CCTV,
and check my body
with these things.
The pain of having to repeat
this every single day...
You can't understand it.
Why attempt such a hard feat?
It's impossible, so why?
You can't, anyway.
Don't do that.
You'll only exhaust yourself.
I'll get going.
See you tomorrow.
Dr. Cha has recently
made headlines by diagnosing
Joo Hyung Woo's Myasthenia gravis.
And for the first time in history,
he diagnosed a CIPA
patient's central sensitization.
And today,
against everyone's dissuasion,
[ A doctor sentenced three years for murder ]
he entered...
a quarantined area
without any equipment,
and diagnosed the
melioidosis which was
dormant for 44 years.
Can you please explain
what melioidosis is?
We're curious as to how
it's contracted and treated.
We've asked Dr. Cha Yo Han to join us.
He'll inform you of the details.
He can't make it? Why not?
- He went to the ICU.
- But why?
To see a patient.
The melioidosis patient.
Right now?
Is he out of his mind?
Where are his priorities?
Hurry up and bring him!
Dr. Cha needs a little more time.
Please give us a minute.
Yes, go ahead.
Is Dr. Cha Yo Han...
the anesthesiologist who was
sentenced for euthanizing a patient
three years ago?
I thought it was someone
with the same name,
but the specialties are the same.
I'm curious if he's the one.
Dr. Cha.
How are you feeling?
It's quiet now.
My head which used to
pound all day long...
is quiet as well.
My heart was troubled
for over 40 years...
but it's at peace now.
You did well.
You'll be well now.
God...
has indeed given all of us life.
And he also punishes us as well.
But...
you are right, Dr. Cha.
He doesn't cast us in suffering...
and look the other way.
Yes.
He is that Dr. Cha Yo Han.
From that incident three years ago.
Wasn't his license revoked?
Was he penalized?
Did you grant him special favors?
How was he hired
at the Hansae Hospital?
There weren't any issues
with Dr. Cha's appointment.
Hansae Hospital appointed him
based on his superior skills.
We had no prejudices or any bias...
I guess Cha Yo Han is not coming.
- Everyone, say hello first.
- Yes, hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Good seeing you.
Sir, this is the friend I mentioned.
Oh, I see. Yes, yes.
Please go in first.
I think she's here.
Hello, welcome.
We were waiting for you.
- Thank you for coming.
- Glad you're here.
[ A Conversation About Death ]
Hello.
It's good seeing you all.
We'll introduce ourselves first.
Hello.
My ID is Oasis74.
I have stage four breast cancer.
I'm a mom of two children.
It spread to my bones,
and it's unlikely I'll recover.
I lost my hair after
36 rounds of chemo.
So I'm wearing a wig.
Hello.
My ID is Scissorhands.
I have stage three colon cancer.
I just found out...
that it's spread to my liver.
I threw my cell phone in anger...
and this is what happened.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello. I'm...
here at this meeting for the first time.
- I don't have an ID yet.
- It's all right.
What ailment are you suffering from?
I have stage three stomach cancer.
From Hansae Hospital this afternoon.
Right?
Welcome.
One of our guests made
a difficult trip out to see us.
Please say hello.
Hello.
I have...
a tumor called olfactory
neuroblastoma.
It's malignant, and
I'm a terminal patient.
Two months...
or...
in a month, I'll be gone.
I heard that...
we're to talk about death here...
to overcome our fear.
But honestly...
I'm not afraid of dying.
Then...
is there anything else that
we may assist you with?
I heard one of your attendees...
went to Switzerland not too long ago.
And he underwent
an assisted suicide over there.
I wanted to hear about him.
That's why I'm here today...
Just a moment.
That's a sensitive topic.
Where and...
how did you hear of...
Miss!
Oh, no! Aigoo!
Please call 911!
I'll call them.
Call the ambulance!
[ Nurse in Charge: Chae Eun Jung ]
I increased the painkillers.
You'll sleep well tonight.
Thank you as always.
Don't mention it.
Get some rest.
Did you watch the news?
Yes.
Dr. Cha delivers again.
We must put a stop
to him, Prosecutor.
Have you forgotten?
Even God had abandoned
Yoon Sung Gyu...
but Cha Yo Han, a mere
human saved him.
Whether a clinical trial or whatnot,
Yoon Sun Gyu should've
suffered more and
died a painful death!
Prosecutor, you have no idea.
How I got him to
sign that agreement.
I...
needed to hear something
from Yoon Sung Gyu.
Why...
he did such an unspeakable thing...
to my Jung In and Seung Yoo.
Those kids hadn't
done anything wrong.
Do you remember asking me
to demand a death penalty...
for Yoon Sung Gyu?
"I could demand a death penalty,
or stab him with my
own hands, but I didn't...
because murder is wrong...
and there can't be any exceptions."
That remains the same.
I'm doing this because
it's the right thing...
not because of personal grudges.
You're a parent first
then a prosecutor.
Principles come first to
a criminal who killed children,
and you have no personal grudge...
against Cha Yo Han
who gave him a mercy killing?
Stabbing Yoon Sung Gyu and
revoking Cha Yo Han's license
won't change the world.
The law that stops them...
The law that punishes them...
Only the law changes the world.
Cha Yo Han...
will put a stop to himself.
We just need to wait.
When Cha Yo Han meets a patient...
facing only death and pain.
I'll...
try to understand you.
You don't understand pain...
but you understand
a patient's suffering.
As you do, I'll...
try to understand you.
You'll do the same.
You'll study and analyze my illness.
But...
there's a difference...
between knowing
and understanding.
Mommy!
Honey, are you okay?
- Does it hurt?
- It hurts a lot...
What's wrong?
Mom, what's the matter?
What's wrong? Are you
uncomfortable, Mom?
- I'm okay.
- Should I call the nurse?
You can't understand it.
Why attempt such a hard feat?
It's impossible, so why?
You can't, anyway.
Even a parent can't suffer
in their children's place,
and a husband can't suffer
on his wife's behalf.
A child can't take his
parents' suffering, either.
Even if he fervently prays
for that to be.
You're not the only one, Dr. Cha.
No human being can feel
another's pain as their own.
We can only try to understand it.
To understand someone's pain...
is to understand that person.
I'm not trying to understand
your illness, Dr. Cha.
I'm trying to understand
this Cha Yo Han...
who has suffered from it.
♫ You warm my heart ♫
♫ We must never try to stop ♫
♫ I can't erase you from
deep inside my heart ♫
Dr. Cha.
♫ So many questions are
floating in my mind ♫
♫ I lost my way today as well ♫
♫ Your eyes that show so much pain ♫
♫ I'm drawn ever slowly to you ♫
♫ I'm sure everything will get better ♫
Don't worry too much.
- Bye.
- See you.
♫ The more I get to know you ♫
♫ The more I can't get you
out of my mind ♫
We all need someone.
Even if someone can't suffer for me...
at least someone who understands
and share my burden.
Dr. Cha, you were that
person to your patients.
However, you...
have endured it alone.
So?
Do you feel sorry for me?
- No.
- Then...
since you're overly empathetic
with your patients,
do you feel responsible as a doctor?
Because you know
of a patient's illness?
No.
Then why?
If it's not sympathy...
nor a sense of
responsibility, then why?
I have feelings for you.
I have...
feelings for you, Dr. Cha.
Let's go.
Oh, Dr. Cha.
Everyone,
this is Dr. Cha Yo Han from
Dept. of Pain Medicine.
♫ Sometimes I try to
find a way to go back ♫
♫ Cuz it's unforgettable time  ♫
♫ It's all still in my mind ♫
♫ Closer, a little bit closer  ♫
[ Doctor John ]
For the time being,
I'll keep an eye on both
- Cha Yo Han and Kang Shi Young.
- Okay.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Regarding yesterday.
Is it time now?
We'll discuss the
CEO's life prolongation.
You're working late, Dr. Cha.
♫ A way to go back ♫
♫ Cuz it's beautiful time ♫
♫ Just a little bit of breeze
colored my life  ♫