[ Seoul Hansae Hospital ]
A breaking news.
The first confirmed carrier
of the Nipah virus
has been discovered in our country.
It's an airborne disease
which can infect
both animals and humans.
In India, of the 13 confirmed
patients last month,
10 of them are reported to have died.
The Dept. of Health and Welfare will
carry out a large scale epidemiological
investigation due to the Nipah virus...
The Nipah virus symptoms are fevers
over 38 degrees, headaches,
and also vomiting.
Infection may occur through the
patient's secretions and bodily fluids.
The KCDC is investigating those
who were in contact with the infected.
If you show symptoms within
two weeks after visiting India,
please report immediately
to your nearest clinic.
Onto our next news.
[ Seoul Hansae Hospital ]
We're at Hansae Hospital.
What's this?
"Nipah Virus Infection Warning?"
Hello!
Please have some snacks.
Oh, my...
Thank you!
Gosh, an avocado sandwich!
Avocados aren't fatty, right?
Of course not.
Avocados won't gain any weight.
But you'll gain the
weight, Nurse Hong.
It's okay. Just eat it.
What's this? The Nipah virus?
Wait, did you see this?
There's an announcement.
No, not yet.
What's this?
The first case of the Nipah
virus in our country?
Dr. Lee.
They just finished the surgery.
Aigoo, must've gone well.
He just woke up from
the anesthesia.
May I go there real quick?
I'll be back before the
outpatient clinic.
Fine, however...
this will be your last trip to the vet.
- I'll visit him until the discharge.
- But why?
You have allergies and
shouldn't be visiting the vet.
Don't even think about it.
Don't get any ideas
either. No thanks.
Who, me?
Then why are you blushing?
Wait, don't tell anyone I let you out.
- Fighting!
- Cool.
Let me take a look.
Sure.
[ Lee Da Hae, 8/02/2019,
Pain in the right arm ]
[ Diagnosis and Treatment
Request Form: Lee Da Hae ]
[ Pain in the right arm after surgery ]
No way...
Wow...
We're loaded with patients,
but we're understaffed.
Let's conduct preliminary
exams before Dr. Cha arrives.
Dr. Kim and Dr. Kang,
please get started.
Dr. Heo, you come with me to...
Dr. Heo.
Prepare the treatment room.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Lee Da Hae!
Ms. Lee Ji Young.
Please come in.
Hello.
- You're Lee Da Hae, correct?
- Yes.
Where are you
experiencing discomfort?
I had surgery on my right arm
last year at this hospital.
The surgery went well...
and the tests state
everything is fine.
I know this may sound
strange, but...
even though there's nothing
here, my arm hurts a lot.
How does it hurt?
It's as if I'm clenching
my right fist
and it froze that way.
It hurts as though
I'm experiencing spasms.
If I could unclench my
right hand, it wouldn't hurt.
But I can't because
I don't have a hand.
No way, could it be then...
[ Department of Pain Medicine ]
Do you want something to eat?
Mommy will go get some food.
Stay here.
Wait, my purse.
Soo Jin, stay right here.
Mr. Yoo Deok Gyu, please come in!
Mr. Yoo Deok Gyu!
Yes.
Hello.
How can I help you?
Starting about a year ago...
my head hurts a lot.
How does it hurt?
Mostly...
I have a splitting
headache all day long.
Some days,
it feels like someone is nailing
my head with a hammer.
I hear ringing.
And some days,
it feels as if my head is being drilled.
- Aigoo...
- You must be getting poor sleep.
Yes, that's the case.
At this point...
[ Brain CT, Brain MRI ]
if I sense pain coming my way...
it really scares me.
[ No abnormalities in brain parenchyma,
ventricle, clvarium, scalp ]
[ No abnormalities shown
after contrast injection ]
Your brain MRI and CT scans
show no abnormalities.
I see you've been to
several hospitals.
Yes.
Eight places.
But wherever I go...
they can't find the cause...
for my headaches.
When did the coughing start?
It's been a few days.
Every time I cough...
Right here.
It hurts so much here.
Let's take your temperature.
I feel this hot air...
coming from my mouth.
[ 39.5 Celsius degree ]
It's 39.5 degrees, Doctor.
Me, too.
I feel so feverish.
Let's check.
It's 38.6 degrees.
I sat next to him on the
shuttle bus to here.
Then my fever...
Aside from what you told me,
any other symptoms?
Two or three days ago...
I started vomiting.
By chance, were you
overseas recently?
No, I wasn't.
I haven't been on a plane...
for over 40 years.
Wait a minute, last week,
I dined with someone
who was back from...
an overseas business trip.
- Where was the business trip?
- It was India.
Excuse me for a sec.
Dr. Kang, see me for a second.
High fever, headache, vomiting.
Could it be...
No way.
There's a confirmed case
of the Nipah virus.
Doctor.
This child's mom left
her unattended,
and she's running a fever.
Oh, no! She's burning up.
That girl...
was also on the shuttle bus earlier.
- Has it spread already?
- That's nonsense.
The incubation period is
five days. This is too fast.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Dr. Kang.
All right, the center
must be shut down.
Shut down?
We'll follow the hospital's
protocol for now.
First, quarantine the suspected
patients to the treatment room.
Okay.
I'll call Chief and ask
for the hazmat suits.
And the man whom the
patient met last week...
Since he's back from
India business trip,
we must identify the symptoms.
Hurry up and ask the KCDC for help.
Dr. Cha is on his way.
Shouldn't we ask first before
we shutdown the center?
Dr. Cha?
Let's get going. Hurry, let's move.
No.
Dr. Cha can't come in here.
[ Dr. Kang Shi Young ]
Whoa, no, no, no, no!
What are you doing? I have to leave!
Why are you locking it?
- What's going on?
- Please wait, please wait.
- Dr. Cha, you can't come in.
- What?
- What's going on?
- Why are you doing this?
Starting now...
no one can leave this room.
What? Why not?
- I have to leave!
- What did he say?
Kim Won Hee.
What's going on?
I said, what's going on?
[ Isolated Ward - Do Not Enter ]
We're closing this area off.
Thank you for your understanding.
What's going on?
Please don't worry.
Please go inside.
- Is everything okay?
- What's happening?
We apologize!
That way, please.
Thank you.
That way, that way.
There are 19 patients in the
Dept. of Pain Medicine.
Plus a fellow, two residents,
and two nurses.
Five in total.
We sent protective masks and
equipment to the Dept. of Pain Medicine.
The KCDC will send
over an investigator.
What about the diagnosis?
We'll conduct blood tests
and throat exams.
The results will be out in six hours.
It takes that long?
This won't do.
Dr. Kwon, please go to the center.
What?
Why should I?
There's only a fellow and residents.
The suspected patient
is in bad shape.
What if an emergency arises?
Why are you telling me this?
If you're so worried, then
you should go in yourself.
No one is allowed in the center.
There's no cure for the Nipah virus...
plus it's highly contagious and lethal.
Until the result is negative
and quarantine is called off,
no one is allowed in the
Department of Pain Medicine...
and no one is allowed out.
- What's going on?
- Why are the doors locked?
How is the suspected patient?
He's quarantined in the
treatment room for now.
Dr. Kang, are you okay?
- Yes.
- Dr. Kang?
Which Dr. Kang is it...
Did something happen to
Kang Shi Young?
She was splattered with the
patient's blood just now.
What's going on?
Dr. Cha, is something wrong?
A suspected Nipah virus
patient is inside.
The center has been shut down.
[ Freedom from Diseases:
Korea Center for Disease Control ]
[ KCDC ]
[ Korea Center for Disease
Control - Investigation ]
[ High risk ]
[ Radiation area ]
[ Korea Center for Disease
Control - Do Not Enter ]
The Nipah virus?
The symptoms are similar
to the flu and enteritis.
We must make a diagnosis.
I'll draw some blood and
samples from your throat.
[ Dr. Cha Yo Han ]
- Dr. Cha.
- Are you with the patient right now?
Yes. Where are you?
You're not inside the center, right?
I'm right outside.
You can't come in here.
Don't even be right
outside the center.
Stay away as far as you can.
How are you feeling?
- Pardon?
- You were splattered with blood.
I'm fine.
The hazmat suit...
- Are you wearing one?
- Yes.
I'm wearing one.
What about the patient?
The patient has stabilized
but having trouble breathing.
And Dr. Cha...
A few other patients in the center
are running high fevers and vomiting.
They were on the same
shuttle bus with this patient.
Can it spread rapidly like this?
If that's the case,
- the rest of the patients...
- Kang Shi Young.
Yes.
There's a suspected patient
right next to you.
The rest of the patients have
weakened immune system
and at high risk.
The worst-case scenario is
that this patient gets diagnosed,
then spreads the virus to the rest.
But we don't know yet.
Not until we have the results.
Until then, don't think of the
worst-case scenario.
Instead, think of better scenarios.
A better case scenario?
For example, this patient has
Nipah virus symptoms.
However, maybe it's another
non-contagious disease.
Is that a possibility?
Do you remember the
0.00001% chance patient?
Yes.
Let's do it like that time.
We can do it.
You and I. Together.
Yes, sir.
Okay, Dr. Cha.
Good, let's start again.
Why did the patient
come to the hospital?
He's had chronic headaches, fatigue,
and no appetite for over a year.
After meeting a friend
who's back from India,
his coughing, vomiting,
and fever started.
Headache, coughing,
vomiting, and fever,
are Nipah virus symptoms,
but not loss of appetite.
Plus, if his headaches and
fatigue persisted for a year,
then it could be another cause.
Let's examine him for now.
Okay.
I'll ask KCDC to run a PCR test,
and run basic tests, including CBC.
[ Dr. Cha Yo Han ]
We finished running the tests.
Good. Did you check his breathing?
Yes. It didn't sound too good.
- Take a chest X-ray.
- Okay.
Sir.
Dr. Cha, his pulse went up to 200.
- Inject Brevibloc.
- Okay.
How is he?
It's dropping.
Sir. What's the matter?
My chest.
My chest...
I feel like it's being crushed.
Dr. Cha, the patient feels
pressure on his chest.
I'll take the X-rays.
Sir.
Can you get up slowly?
I'll take your chest X-rays.
Please lower yourself slowly.
- Sir.
- What's wrong?
Dr. Cha, something's
wrong with the patient.
Why?
He's lost his sense of direction.
Look him over asap.
What other symptoms are there?
Sir, please sit this way.
Any paralysis?
How do your arms feel?
Do you feel everything?
Are you able to feel this?
No paralysis.
He's suffering disorientation.
Then by any chance...
Sir!
Sir...
What was that sound?
Kang Shi Young.
What is it, Dr. Cha?
Kang Shi Young?
Kang Shi Young.
Answer me, Kang Shi Young.
Call Dr. Lee Yoo Joon.
My apologies.
I'm Dr. Cha Yo Han from the
Dept. of Pain Medicine.
The treatment room in the
center that's shut down.
I'd like to see it on the monitor.
Dr. Kang!
What happened?
What's going on?
Dr. Kang Shi Young is in the
treatment room with a patient.
But the call dropped all of a sudden.
What?
Dr. Kang.
Dr. Kang!
- Dr. Kang Mi Rae.
- Yes.
Dr. Kang Shi Young is unconscious.
Dr. Kang!
[ Dr. Kang Mi Rae ]
Sir.
Sir!
[ Dr. Cha Yo Han ]
Dr. Cha!
Sir!
Inject 10cc of thiopental.
What?
I'm at the security office.
I'm watching you on CCTV.
Inject it now.
Done.
How is he?
He's stabilizing.
Okay.
How is Dr. Kang Shi Young?
Dr. Kang.
Dr. Kang!
She's still unconscious!
Okay.
Dr. Cha...
Dr. Cha?
Thank you.
Dr. Kang!
Dr. Kang.
♫ Like a dream which
has ended for me ♫
♫ Deep in the dark shadows ♫
♫ You're still lingering behind me ♫
♫ Even though I'm not able
to erase away your pain♫
How is the patient?
His seizures stopped.
Check the patient's condition.
♫ A day full of sorrow ♫
Kang Shi Young.
Are you awake?
Dr. Cha...
♫ Even through every
fading moment ♫
♫ I always trust in you ♫
♫ Right by your side ♫
[ Doctor John ]
Dr. Cha entering the center,
regardless of the results...
He must face the consequences.
What we must do now is
to diagnose him before
his condition gets worse.
Is the patient's name
Yoo Deok Gyu?
- Do you know him?
- I...
have killed someone.
My arm hurts so much...
You're a parent first
then a prosecutor.
You hold no personal grudge
against Cha Yo Han?
What's the problem here?
There was nothing I could do.
You were next to an infected patient.
I was going crazy with worry...
♫ I'll comfort your heart ♫