[ Son Seok Ki / Age 38 ]
Please don't yawn or swallow.
[ Patient: Son Seok Ki,
Hemato Oncology ]
Are you being discharged?
Yes.
The side effects are the
worst after the first round.
Swelling, vomiting, and fatigue.
Your stomach pain may
worsen as well.
If it gets too hard,
- please come to the ER.
- Okay.
Are you done?
Yes.
You waited a while, huh?
That's what a guardian does.
Waiting.
You did well.
Let's go.
Isn't that bag heavy?
No.
Give me the bag.
It's all right.
It's too crowded here.
[ Doctor John ]
[ Episode 12: Schrodinger's Cat ]
[ Gyeongseo University Hospital ]
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Prosecutor, sorry to bother
you on your vacation.
What's the matter?
I'll be right there.
Don't walk near the road.
There's somewhere
I want to take you.
Where?
Don't expect too much.
It's just someone
you'd be happy to see.
Someone I'd be happy to see?
Here's the hand-drip
coffee you ordered.
Please enjoy.
Hyung!
Hello, 5353.
Dr. Cha...
Geez, Hyung.
What on earth?
When did you get here?
Hyung.
Park Jung Bo, how have you been?
Oh, hello.
Man, Hyung!
How long has it been? Huh?
Have you been well?
Wow, you're looking good.
Really? Do I look better?
Here is your hand-drip coffee.
And your iced mocha.
Thank you.
Wow, the water is
precisely 75 degrees.
How did you know that, Hyung?
75 degrees water doesn't
give off steam, but...
If you do this...
Then it steams.
Hey, I should come
here more often.
I have a barista who nails
the water temperature.
This is why...
I've been telling you to
come by for a while.
I said I was sorry.
No need to be sorry.
I saw everything on the news.
You've been quite busy.
You're so cool, indeed.
How is your health?
You're still going to the hospital, right?
Yes, Dr. Kang. I have my
regular check-ups.
I go with my older brother.
I've gotten so much
better thanks to you.
Thank you.
What a relief.
That's so great.
- You look wonderful.
- I do?
The two of you, too.
You guys look great together.
Thank you.
Please come again.
You must, you must!
Don't worry, I'll come by often.
- You have customers. Go on in.
- Okay, Hyung.
- Thank you.
- Get home safely, Dr. Kang.
Thank you.
[ Coffee Da ]
What is it?
Are you dizzy?
Give me a minute.
I'm okay now.
Take it.
You may get dizzy again.
♫ Something that disappears
without a trace ♫
Let's go.
We have a lot to do.
♫ I can't stand that
I keep thinking about it ♫
♫ Unbelievable days of the past ♫
♫ Do what you want ♫
Boosts the immune system
and is high in antioxidants...
Broccoli.
♫ The more I get to know you,
you warm my heart ♫
Bell peppers.
And...
♫ We must never try to stop ♫
What are you looking for?
There it is.
♫ I can't erase you from
deep inside my heart ♫
[ Doctor Capsule ]
Probiotics for your stomach.
With steroid treatments,
I worry your immune
system will weaken.
You must take these diligently.
Okay?
Answer me.
Yes, ma'am.
- She's missing?
- Yes.
There's a missing persons report on
a "Conversation about death" member.
Try this place.
It'll be worthwhile.
From Hansae Hospital
this afternoon. Right?
But her husband received...
a message this morning.
Wait.
It may be quite shocking.
Honey.
They told me that...
I have two or three months left.
More than death itself,
the pain I must face beforehand...
scared me more.
Since I can put an end
to that fear now,
I'm at peace.
For over 10 years...
you've suffered a lot...
taking care of me.
Please find...
peace for yourself as well.
This...
was not forced upon me.
This is my choice.
I'm ready now.
To paraphrase "pain,"
I think it's our bodies talking to us.
Even when he gets injured,
he doesn't feel pain.
He gets injured often.
If our body is in danger
or something is not right,
it talks to us.
[ Reporter Ahn Seung Hyun ]
- Hello?
- Let's meet up tomorrow.
I need to tell you something
about Cha Yo Han.
On this week's "SBC Famous Healers,"
we'll be airing the "Cha Yo Han Episode"
of Seoul Hansae Hospital's
Anesthesiology and Pain
Medicine Department.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[ Kerubim ]
[ Her brain waves started from beta
and transitioned to theta. ]
[ Then it finally flatlined, and Ms. Park Hyun Sook
passed away peacefully. ]
[ "Kerubim" promises an end without pain ]
Kerubim...
What are Dr. Cha's thoughts?
Do you think...
he'll be joining our project?
When Dr. Cha was released,
I went to pick him up.
There is a hospital
I'd like to refer you to.
What do you say?
Do you want to start right away?
No point in being idle.
If someone takes me, I'll be grateful.
If in the case
you come across another
patient like Yoon Sung Gyu...
what do you think you'll do?
If you had the protection of the law,
then without fearing punishment...
couldn't you send off
patients like Yoon Sung Gyu?
Protection of the law?
Giving doctors the license
to commit legitimate murder?
Just thinking about it is scary.
He's skeptical.
Yes.
I don't know what
he'll think of Kerubim.
So I haven't mentioned it
until it was perfected.
I'm positive.
That when Dr. Cha
administers to his patients...
Kerubim will be of an asset to him.
The video clip was sent...
from a burner phone.
[ "Kerubim" promises an end without pain ]
Prosecutor?
Are you okay?
"A conversation about death,"
their sponsoring foundation,
and Zinmu Rijund,
the pharmaceutical company.
Yes, Zinmu Rijund.
Their stock price soared
nearly 20% recently.
Yes, a pharmaceutical stock rises
due to an anticipated new drug.
Prosecutor.
That drug from earlier.
Can it be released?
If euthanasia becomes legal.
Then you can even sell it exclusively.
Any connections to former
Minister Lee Won Gil? Not yet?
As you know, he's such a big figure...
You had asked me to look into this.
In the Hebrew language,
it means "Cherubim."
There's a definite connection,
but no decisive evidence.
I know.
Please look into it further.
Something will come out for sure.
Okay, will do.
But...
the one who administered
the shot in the video...
- Could it be...
- No.
We don't know anything yet.
Yes, sir.
[ "Kerubim" promises an end without pain ]
Officer.
Yes?
Have the National Forensic
Service analyze this clip.
Yes, sir. Will do.
[ Zinmou Rijund expands its business ]
[ Recommended to Hansae
Hospital: Reasons unclear ]
Apples, blueberries.
Eat them every morning.
Mushrooms.
You're trying to fatten me up, huh?
Weight gain would be good too.
Broccoli.
Broccoli, bell peppers...
They're packed with Vitamin C...
and potatoes.
What?
Is something wrong?
No, you sounded far away.
But it's fine now.
This won't do. Please lie down.
I'll take your temperature.
No fever.
Let's take your pulse.
Why is your pulse so fast?
Do you have dizziness?
No.
I'm fine.
Hang on a sec.
It's strange, that's why.
What is?
My heart...
is beating like crazy.
Aside from myself,
I've never imagined
anyone else being here.
I've dreamt about it though.
About this place being found out.
By whom?
The patients.
"You're a patient, too?"
"You can't feel pain?"
"Then why act like you know?"
"You don't even know
what pain is like."
"My ailment...
Did you make the right diagnosis?"
Even though you're not
able to feel pain,
you have a disease yourself.
The suffering,
the sadness...
and loneliness.
You know better than anyone.
The patients want you to know that.
"Where does it hurt?"
Instead of that...
"You must be hurting so much."
That's what they want to hear.
Are you expecting someone?
No.
Will you be okay?
Yes, I'll be fine.
I'll stay here and show myself out.
Hurry and go outside.
Maybe he's not in?
- Dr. Cha!
- What brings you by?
Are you okay?
We're here because we were worried.
But whoa, how nice.
We couldn't come empty-handed,
so we brought these. We did good, right?
Dr. Cha, what is this
disciplinary action? Huh?
What have you done wrong here?
This is definitely...
- A conspiracy.
- It's a conspiracy!
Why is your house so clean?
It's daebak, wow...
How can the Department of
Pain Medicine be without you?
You can't forfeit your position.
Hang on a second.
Just come anyway.
It's only for a week, okay?
I get to rest, so it's all good.
Dr. Cha does need to rest.
But the hospital is
being so unreasonable...
Moreover, what about all the
patients if you're not there?
They have you, Dr. Lee.
Me...
Who, me?
I'll give you my treatment
protocol book. Just give it a go.
Take this opportunity to
conduct more procedures.
- Whoa!
- That's good.
Why do you have so much?
This is no joke.
Can I have some, Dr. Cha?
Sure, go ahead. Eat.
Let's go out.
- Pardon?
- What?
Let's go out! Okay?
Daebak, okay, let's go!
But I like it here, too!
All right!
It's better than my house.
I'm not sure.
Is something on your mind?
It just...
seems a bit difficult.
"But I'm sure someday, I'll be able to...
correct your misdiagnosis."
Didn't you say that?
I said that to you?
Mr. 6238.
So I could beat you.
Someday I'll be able to
correct your misdiagnosis.
Well, that was then.
You're doing great.
You really are.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Dr. Cha, did you see this?
It's an exclusive app for doctors.
After you joined us...
We placed first in the rankings!
[ 1st Place: Seoul Hansae Hospital ]
All right! Should we do it once?
Wishing for our
Dr. Cha's speedy return.
Geez, AnesthPain, AnesthPain.
Okay, okay, here, here,
let's go, let's go.
One, two, three!
AnesthPain, AnesthPain, fighting!
We went down last time.
You went up last time.
- We changed it because of you, Dr. Cha.
- That's right.
You guys, go on home.
But why?
Why keep telling us to leave?
I'll sleep over.
Can I sleep over? It'll be fun.
♫ I can't see no matter how I try ♫
I was saddened.
At the thought of you being
alone here every day.
It frightened me.
That you must do this
every day to survive.
♫ You're still lingering behind me ♫
♫ Even though I'm not able to
♫ Erase away your pain ♫
♫ It's our destiny and
I can't get away ♫
Nevertheless, thank you.
For being alive.
♫ I'm here now ♫
For staying by my side...
♫ Right by your side ♫
♫ Even through every
fading moment ♫
♫ I always trust in you ♫
♫ I trust in you ♫
♫ Are you listening to me ♫
[ Dr. Cha Yo Han ]
Thank you.
♫ Look at your scars ♫
♫ Revealing but you're still
watching the day go by ♫
[ Doctor Capsule ]
♫ Steering your car ♫
♫ Spinning out ♫
♫ Your thoughts, they just
crash in a line ♫
♫ It won't be wrong ♫
♫ To fall in love again ♫
♫ And time... ♫
♫ Loses itself again ♫
♫ The traces you find ♫
♫ One way street that
leads back to you ♫
♫ You ♫
♫ You... ♫
[ Shi Young ]
[ Message ]
Dad, the full moon is out tonight.
[ This is your lovely Shi Young. Stir-fried squid!
My cooking got better. Looks delicious, right? ]
[ I saw this after work. The sunset is
so pretty so I took a pic. Isn't it beautiful? ]
[ Ta-da! Today's lunch is chicken soup.
Thank you for the meal. ]
Dad says he loves you.
Tell Dad that I love him too.
We love you, Dad.
Both Unni...
and I.
We love you so much, Dad.