Get him!
Great! Get him!
Come on!
Hyung Woo! Hyung Woo!
Medic!
I can't see.
- I can't see.
- What?
I can't see!
The match is over.
Draw the blood.
You'd go blind otherwise.
Who are you? Are you a doctor?
I'm not an eye doctor.
You're a doctor, right?
Draw the blood.
Do it right now if you can.
What are you saying?
You don't even know him.
The match is...
not over yet!
Prepare disinfectant,
betadine, forceps...
lidocaine, and the
surgical instrument set.
Yes.
You said you're not an eye doctor.
I'm not.
- Are you a surgeon?
- No.
What will you do then...
I was in jail until recently.
Whatever you can imagine,
I had it worse.
The kinds of treatment
I provided there.
Shall I put you under anesthesia?
[ Doctor John ]
[ Episode 3: Champion ]
♫ Look at your scars ♫
♫ Revealing but you're still
watching the day go by ♫
♫ Steering your car, spinning out ♫
♫ Your thoughts, they just
crash in a line ♫
♫ It won't be long ♫
It's my first day at work.
I'm sorry for coming back so late.
I'll visit you when I get stronger...
mentally and physically.
Please watch me.
- One hot Americano, but not so hot.
- Pardon?
- I'll just take it as is.
- Okay.
♫ For you to love again ♫
[ Basic Information ]
This is not right!
He's a murderer!
This is a university hospital
where residents get trained.
Can we let someone like
him train the residents?
His license was revoked,
as I understand.
It was reinstated.
- He got his license back?
- Yes, he did.
Even the doctors who sexually harassed
patients or committed malpractice
get reinstated quickly.
This is nothing like sexual
harassment or medical malpractice.
This was a murder. Murder!
He's not a doctor, in my opinion.
He is a doctor.
He killed someone!
In Korea, a doctor is...
someone who passed the state exam
and acquired an official license.
Does anyone...
disagree with that?
This man is a doctor.
A very proficient one at that.
Did you all forget?
Before that incident three years ago,
he proved himself as the best
doctor in pain medicine.
He used to be famous.
He was on TV, too.
Everyone used to talk
about him at conferences.
He had a nickname, too.
Doctor 10 seconds.
Doctor 10 seconds?
What does that mean?
He can scan a patient
completely in 10 seconds.
[ Herpes zoster: Shingles, a viral
disease with painful skin rash ]
He can tell what's
causing the pain and
what the problem is right away
in 10 seconds.
I'm not questioning his
ability right now!
This might be a more
convincing reason.
The reason he was hired as a doctor
at the Pain Medicine Center.
That's what I'm asking right now.
Why did you hire someone like this?
- He was recommended.
- Recommended?
By whom?
He was recommended by the
former Minister Lee Won Gil from...
the Ministry of Health and Welfare.
So we couldn't oppose him during
the recruitment meeting.
He was Chief Min's teacher, right?
He wasn't just her teacher.
He was like a god.
To her, he's like a god.
He's very close with my
brother-in-law as well.
Why did the Minister
recommend someone...
like him anyway?
That's what I'd like to know, too.
He'd obviously be a problem.
But we can't reject someone
recommended by the minister.
I know.
By the way, sir...
If this recruitment ends
up being a problem,
wouldn't it jeopardize
Chief Min's career?
So? We should just enjoy the show?
Excuse me, everyone.
Isn't that Joo Hyung Woo?
He fell down the stairs.
His ankle hurts.
We'll take an x-ray.
Anything else?
- What do you think?
- My eye.
Does your eye hurt?
Could you take the sunglasses off...
Call an ophthalmologist.
And an anesthesiologist, too.
An anesthesiologist?
The anesthesiologist...
Cha Yo Han.
♫ Sometimes I try to
find a way to go back ♫
[ Cha Yo Han ]
♫ Cuz it's unforgettable time  ♫
♫ It's all still in my mind ♫
♫ Just a little bit of your
heart makes my life  ♫
♫ I see a hope in sunrise ♫
♫ The light shines all my loneliness ♫
♫ How do I deal with desire ♫
♫ I don't know how I can
fly like you to the sky ♫
♫ Closer, a little bit closer  ♫
♫ What if I walk to you  ♫
♫ Can you hold my hand  ♫
[ Cha Yo Han, Doctor in Pain Medicine ]
[ Kang Shi Young, Anesthesiology ]
Will you be a doctor in our department?
Yes.
I guess you're in the
anesthesiology department here.
Yes.
So we meet again.
You're Dr. Cha Yo Han, right?
Yes.
I'm Kim Jung Ho, a third-year
resident in Ophthalmology.
- Ophthalmology?
- Yes.
A doctor in my department
would like to see you.
Right now?
Where's the anesthesiologist anyway?
- Call them again.
- Yes.
Geez.
Are you Dr. Cha Yo Han?
Yes, that's me.
Excuse me for a second.
Can you not see well?
Since this morning, I had a
hard time opening my eyes.
Things looked out of focus,
and I felt dizzy, too.
And I fell.
How could you cut it open like that?
As an anesthesiologist.
How was the test result?
His intraocular pressure, consensual
pupillary reaction, and VEP were normal?
Yes, but...
It was all normal, but he
still has a blurry vision?
He's eating all this?
That's why he does mukbang.
[ A doctor receives a 3-year sentence
for euthanizing a patient... ]
[ Dr. Cha, an anesthesiologist at
Seoul Myeongwon University Hospital... ]
Hey, hey, hey.
It's him, right?
Cha Yo Han.
- It's him.
- Geez.
A murder convict is our
professor starting today?
Geez, what a shame.
I guess I'm the only
one who worries.
You guys have nothing
to worry about.
You're Chief's daughter...
and your parents own a building.
- I'm in your care.
- Me, too.
Dr. Lee.
It was you. I wasn't sure at first.
Your hair.
I didn't know you applied
to this hospital, too.
I did and I got accepted.
That's why I'm here.
You said "too."
Did you already run into him?
No. 6238.
Did you know?
I have two people to
introduce today.
One of them is running late.
Let's start with you,
Dr. Lee Yoo Joon.
He's got broad shoulders.
What did you say?
His broad shoulders.
My goodness.
How did someone so
handsome end up here?
I'm Lee Yoo Joon,
a second-year fellow.
Thank you in advance.
Welcome!
Am I the only one welcoming him?
A 38-year-old male.
He had canthotomy...
two days ago due to an emergency.
I held the tendon in lateral
canthus with forceps,
cut the outer issue with scissors,
and removed the hematoma...
that was pressuring the optic nerve.
The patient is currently...
suffering from sudden
dizziness, diplopia,
and he has a droopy eyelid.
But all the test results
came out normal.
Is that patient
Joo Hyung Woo by chance?
Joo Hyung Woo? The MMA fighter?
Joo Hyung Woo?
Daebak, wow.
Well...
What I wanted to say is...
The canthotomy was successful.
But he's suddenly suffering
from dizziness and diplopia.
So there must be something else
going on other than his eye.
- Is that what you're saying?
- Yes, that's correct.
The patient had a slight fever,
similar to a flu symptom.
He also has diabetes in addition,
but he had slight numbness
on his extremities.
No problem with his vision.
What's the reason
you're bringing this up now?
You're not suggesting to
find the cause together.
I am.
Why?
He's not even our patient.
We didn't treat someone
else's patient...
and caused a problem
in the first place.
Who's it?
Excuse me.
This is Cha Yo Han.
Got it.
Apparently...
his vision just came back.
That's great.
- There's no problem then.
- No.
There is a problem.
We successfully stopped the bleeding
that was pressuring the optic nerve.
But he couldn't open his eye.
He had blurry vision and was dizzy.
And he fainted.
He suddenly developed...
dizziness and diplopia.
And he just recovered naturally.
Is this normal?
Can you think of anything?
By chance...
does he have a neurological disorder...
that has nothing to do
with this accident?
If so, Neurology should
treat him instead.
That's none of our concern.
Isn't it our job to treat patients
regardless of departments?
So what?
What are you suggesting?
It can be any of you.
An attending, a fellow, or a resident.
If any of you have an opinion,
feel free to call me.
Right.
I'll be...
in charge of Pain Surgery
starting today.
I'm Cha Yo Han.
"Isn't it our job to treat patients
regardless of departments?"
He thinks he's Schweitzer
or something.
He freaked out when the
patient deteriorated.
He's all talk!
The patient is doing fine.
What is the problem?
He's determined to be responsible
for the patient he treated.
A strong sense of duty
and responsibility.
He's irresponsible!
He operated on someone
when it's not his specialty!
Why is he yelling at me?
Gosh.
Shi Young.
This is your first day.
Good luck!
Yes, Auntie.
Do you have 10 licenses
or something?
Or are you planning
to get a new one...
whenever it's revoked?
Fine, that's up to you.
But keep this in mind.
You might get your license back,
but this is your only chance
to work at Hansae Hospital.
Who's the one...
who gave me that chance?
Is that the only reason you hired me?
You said this about what
happened three years ago.
"I didn't sin. I broke the law."
I agree with that.
You got punished for
breaking the law.
You're going back to work
since you've been punished.
Work harder than anyone...
and try to be discreet about it.
I'll go first.
I'm a fellow, and you're
a second-year resident.
Okay?
Yes.
It's me.
No. 6238.
Who are you...
I'm Lee Yoo Joon.
I worked at the hospital
nearby where you were...
Oh, right!
The fellow who
misdiagnosed frequently.
Not frequently.
It was just twice.
Are we meant to be, or is it
just a coincidence?
It's destiny.
I applied here so I could beat you.
Were you beaten by me?
When I was at that hospital...
I was in a much better
position than you were.
I could see and examine
patients myself.
All you did was eavesdropping in jail.
But you were always right.
How do you think I felt?
I wouldn't know.
I've never felt that way before.
You're now an attending,
and I'm a fellow.
It might sound ridiculous that
a fellow is challenging an attending,
but I'm sure someday,
I'll be able to...
correct your misdiagnosis.
I'm not sure about that.
Before that, Doctor...
- Dr. who?
- Lee Yoo Joon.
Dr. Lee Yoo Joon should
learn this first.
First, diagnosis isn't a competition.
Second, getting a new look won't
make you a better doctor.
What's this?
Is this supposed to be fashionable?
Diagnosis isn't a competition.
Why is he so cool?
I didn't get to say hello
properly earlier.
[ Kim Shi Young ]
Are you allowed to talk
to me like this?
Pardon?
Do people need to know about
our prison connection?
What's wrong with that...
Of course, if you feel uncomfortable...
Aren't you back from a long break?
- Yes.
- A lot of people are
probably watching you right now.
- Yes.
- Don't stick out.
That's what Chief Min told me.
I'm happy to see you again.
It was just that one day, but...
someone near death
was revived that day.
It was the day I decided
to stop running
and have a fresh start.
I hope to learn a lot from you.
I'll study hard.
- You haven't changed.
- Pardon?
Your shoelaces are undone.
Dr. Kim Young Mi, please come
to the emergency room.
[ Management Center ]
[ Pain ]
Yes!
[ Pain Management ]
Why did you put me in the basement?
Are you in the position to choose?
Be thankful that you got hired.
The legal team is on the 12th floor.
Do you want to have lunch
together later?
Well, I plan on being very busy today.
Let's talk later.
You're Dr. Cha Yo Han, right?
Yes.
I'm Hong Yeon Jin.
Not Engine, but Yeon Jin.
I'm Nurse Na Kyung Ah.
Nice to meet you.
Where are the residents by the way?
In the conference room.
Nurse Na Kyung Ah.
- And Nurse Hong Yeon Jin.
- Hong.
I'm so upset!
Why is this happening
in my final term?
- You dislike him that much?
- Honestly, I hate him.
Have you read an article about the
incident three years ago?
He didn't just remove
the respirator or
stop giving medicine
to a hopeless patient.
He gave him a lethal
dose of anesthetic.
He wasn't an old man or
anything. He was only 20!
He was a young patient.
He had terminal cancer.
Cancer would've spread faster
and been more painful.
He would've died soon anyway
if he had terminal cancer.
I looked into that case, too.
He had too much time
to just wait and die.
It was terminal cancer.
He didn't have a lot of time.
Since he was only 20...
- years old.
- Right.
Since his heart was young and healthy,
instead of dying...
he had excruciating pain.
But that patient was a kidnapper.
You're right.
He killed two children, right?
It was an infamous case.
What was that culprit's name?
- Yoon Sung Gyu.
- Yes, Yoon Sung Gyu.
But that's not important right now.
Why does my teaching physician
have to be an ex-con?
Why?
Hello, Doctor.
Hello.
Who has an opinion
about Joo Hyung Woo?
- Can I ask a question?
- Shoot.
Will you keep monitoring
Joo Hyung Woo?
Why shouldn't I?
Because this is Pain Medicine,
not Ophthalmology nor Neurology.
I don't think there's
anything we can do.
Give me your hand.
Ouch! It hurts!
The patient is in pain, too.
And he doesn't even know
why he's in pain.
Doesn't that give us enough
reason to be interested in him?
[ Prescribed med for discharge ]
Doctor.
According to the chart,
he's about to get discharged.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself.
I'll be cheering for you.
Thank you, Doctor.
You must be busy.
We'll let you go now.
He can't leave.
We're done examining him.
Everything's normal.
Why don't you stay a few days
longer and get tested?
I have an important match next week.
I'll get going.
You can't fight the next match like this.
Come on now.
We said he's fine. What's with you?
I know.
Actually, since my eye was
acting up this morning,
I thought you messed up
the other day.
But apparently not.
Isn't that enough?
What more do I need?
Are you sure you're
not disappointed?
You came to the hospital
this morning
because something was
wrong with your eye.
If I did do something wrong,
you wanted these
ophthalmologists to treat you.
Of course, you didn't forget about
suing me or demand responsibility.
But...
I did a perfect job performing
canthotomy operation.
performing canthotomy operation.
That means it's not that
I made a mistake,
but your eye is acting up because
there's something else going on.
What would other patients
do in this situation?
They'd receive checkups
instead of going home.
What are you trying to say?
You knew something is wrong
with your body, didn't you?
You just hoped it wasn't true.
If something is wrong with my body,
that means I don't have
much time to fight.
Since I'm running out of time,
I'll get going.
Wow, Joo Hyung Woo is a big guy.
Yes, kick! Counterattack!
Yes!
He's fighting well.
What does he think is
wrong with him anyway?
Since we have no patients,
we'll continue to monitor
Joo Hyung Woo.
- Didn't he get discharged?
- In the process.
- But he'll come back soon.
- Why?
He left his watch.
Suddenly feeling eye
discomfort and dizziness.
If his recovery is connected
to the nerves system,
he'd experience other symptoms, too.
That's why he'd come back.
That's why he'd be back.
Can anyone guess what the
first symptom would be?
Go ahead, Heo Joon.
Live up to your name.
If our department
figures out the illness...
If so?
Wouldn't the other departments hate us?
Like Ophthalmology or Neurology.
Of course, I'm a huge fan
of Joo Hyung Woo,
but I'm worried about you as well...
Anyone else? No other
opinions? Go ahead.
Do you go see Joo Hyung Woo's
matches often?
- Your name is?
- First-year resident, Kim Won Hee.
Continue.
Why do people watch violence
when they're against it?
I'm curious.
Well?
Do you think it's just to
watch violent fights?
What else do you see at those fights?
Pretty grid girls?
- More importantly, there are fighters.
- And?
That'd be your homework.
Second-year resident.
- Yes.
- Didn't you have an opinion?
Well, yes.
Joo Hyung Woo went to South America
to film a TV show recently.
If he was vaccinated,
the antigens could've
damaged the nerve cells...
It could've caused Guillain-Barre syndrome
or acute demyelinating encephalomyelitis?
Guillain-Barre syndrome could've
caused the eye problem,
but it doesn't explain how
he recovered naturally.
I suspect a stroke,
neuromyelitis optica,
or other neurological issues
such as multiple sclerosis.
But since he's not showing
any neurological symptoms...
The numbness he felt
on his hands and feet.
It could easily be mistaken
as diabetes, but...
It's also the symptom
of multiple sclerosis...
or neuromyelitis optica.
Should I call the patient
to receive checkups?
Tell him it might be
his brain, not his eye.
Tell him to receive
a checkup at Neurology.
Okay!
I'll get going.
Doctor, what if he was
already discharged?
I said he'd be back for his watch.
I'm Kang Shi Young,
a resident at Anesthesiology.
I'm Heo Joon, a resident.
I'm enjoying your fights.
Dr. Cha said it's not your eye,
but it could be your brain.
He says to receive a checkup.
Receive a checkup at Neurology
and let them diagnose you.
Let Dr. Cha explain to you and...
Doctor.
You know what the DNR
(Do Not Resuscitate) order is right?
Yes.
I signed one recently.
If I get sent here for an emergency,
don't do anything to prolong my life.
Please tell him that.
Please.
Why would you say that?
You haven't even been diagnosed yet.
I'll get going for now.
Well...
You're afraid, aren't you?
You're afraid you'd get diagnosed
with an incurable disease.
That's what you're afraid of, right?
Most people like us...
get scared if we notice something
wrong with our bodies.
But you're an athlete.
Your body is everything to you.
I think that's why you're
probably more afraid.
But your condition might
get worse if you wait.
- It's not too late...
- Thank you, Doctor.
I am afraid.
Knowing someone understands that...
comforts me.
- Wait!
- Hey, Kang Shi Young!
This is so upsetting.
Sir.
Sir!
You can't leave.
If you see here, there's
a fracture on your left leg.
The CT scan and everything is normal,
but according to the spinal MRI,
we see a herniated disc that's
pressing down your left nerve.
I'll transfer you to Orthopedics.
We'll be treating you from now on.
Neurology, not Orthopedics.
Have you experienced weird or
burning sensations on your limbs?
Why do you ask?
It might be a neurological disease.
Please receive a checkup.
Neurological diseases need
to get diagnosed ASAP.
A herniated disc doesn't explain
the dizziness and blurry vision.
- Transfer to Neurology and...
- No, that's okay.
Please treat my leg ASAP.
Don't you have a guardian?
How about family?
Does your family know
about any of this?
- You have no one to visit you?
- I have no one!