Officer lady
You're tonight's biggest highlight!
Welcome to my world
The signal appeared.
Thanks for the gifts, guys.
Lin Xue.
Who would've thought?
Our show just keeps getting more exciting.
We've even got real cops joining in.
Watch your mouth.
He's using a masked signal.
I'm filtering it out.
Speed up the trace.
The real show
is about to begin.
The location's in Lianhai District.
Find out which village ASAP.
How about it,
officer lady?
I'm not easy to catch.
Wait.
Play back that footage.
Okay.
Zoom in on Lin Xue's hand.
What does this gesture mean?
C.
Caowu Village.
Hello.
Jiang Han.
Get to Caowu Village immediately.
Got it, Captain Wang.
How far to Caowu Village?
Three kilometers.
Full speed. Go!
Roger that.
This is just our appetizer.
I figure
you'd want to know
where you stand with your boss, right?
What do you say?
I'll give you ten seconds.
Tell those cops on the other side
to stop attacking my site.
Otherwise,
she'll be saying goodbye to this world.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Stop the trace.
Three.
Two.
That's more like it.
Nothing here. Nothing.
Come on, check over here.
Hold on.
Remember this from now on.
When you're at a scene with him,
medical gloves
are a must.
This is Lin Xue's glove.
The suspect must be inside.
Shunzi.
You two, watch the main gate.
Yang, let's look around.
See if there's a way in.
Go.
Move.
Do you want this character
carved on your belly,
or carved on your chest?
Don't move!
Xing Mingliang!
Drop the knife!
Got him.
So what?
Come on!
Shoot me!
I want to know what a bullet feels like too.
Xing Mingliang!
You're assaulting an officer.
That's another charge, you get it?
You think I give a damn?
They're all bitches.
Filthy bitches!
They all deserve to die!
Come on!
Shoot!
Shoot me!
You don't have the guts, do you?
Come on!
Everyone, listen up!
If the suspect resists again,
you are
authorized to shoot to kill.
Authorized to shoot to kill.
Xing Mingliang!
This is your final warning.
Drop the knife!
Or I will shoot!
Go ahead and shoot!
We'll just die together, no big deal!
Mingliang, just stop.
Don't go any further down this path.
Shut up!
This is all because of you, you bitch!
I'll kill this damn cop,
and then I'll kill you!
Don't move!
This garage is reserved for President Su's car.
He rarely drives this car.
The keys.
I don't have them.
Hey, you can't smash it!
I'll take responsibility. Move aside.
I'll keep it brief.
While I was away at the provincial meeting,
something major happened at the bureau.
A big case has broken in Fengdu.
The situation regarding Comrade Li Kaiyang,
I'm sure you've all heard about it.
Let me make my position clear.
Until the truth comes to light,
no one is allowed to smear his name.
Xing.
Go ahead and speak.
Chief Gao,
this is my failure.
I bear full responsibility.
With a case this significant,
as head of the Criminal Investigation Division,
you should be held accountable.
But as Xing Mingliang's immediate family,
you must recuse yourself.
Yonglin,
from this moment on,
you'll lead all the comrades on the team,
to work around the clock.
Even without food or rest,
you must crack this case.
Yes, sir.
Comrades,
I expect everyone to give 120 percent
and win this tough battle.
Because this concerns not only
the reputation of the Fengdu police,
but also
the safety of Fengdu's citizens.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Please, sit down.
What are you doing?
What are YOU doing?
I'm investigating.
So am I.
Aren't you interrogating Xing Mingliang?
He admitted to kidnapping women and filming it.
But he flatly denies framing Captain Li.
That's exactly why we have to keep at it.
Why are you following me?
Captain Li isn't just your boss.
He's also family to me at Major Crimes.
I want the truth even more than you do.
To clear his name.
Parking in such a remote spot,
He must be hiding something
Let's go
Chief Xing
Someone's upstairs.
Did you bring your gun?
Chief Xing is still breathing.
Call an ambulance, now!
Come here.
Weren't you supposed to be dead?
Why are you here?
The killer's still around.
Wait, am I the one who's dead?
Why are you pinching me?
Are you out of your mind?
The guy's got a crossbow.
And you charge in bare-handed?
You think you're Astro Boy or something?
Weren't you supposed to be dead?
What the hell is going on?
It's a long story.
Let's catch him first.
Okay?
Go.
Move!
Let's split up.
You be careful.
Boss
What the hell is going on?
Weren't you dead?
How are you alive again?
And why did Chief Xing fall?
Say something!
You didn't actually commit a crime, did you?
We'll talk about that later.
How's Chief Xing?
Li Kaiyang.
Why don't you ask how I'm doing?
Do you know that ever since you died,
how devastated the team has been?
Do you know that since I became an adult,
I've never cried.
But because of you...
I'll explain everything.
Trust me.
How am I supposed to trust you?
You're a fugitive now.
I'm a cop.
What am I supposed to do?
I'll go back to the unit with you.
Comrade Li Kaiyang
You've been through a lot.
Everyone, have a seat.
Kaiyang
You sit too.
Yeah.
Jiang Han
Sit down.
Kaiyang
Let's hear the answer.
You're quite good at posing riddles.
And you're quite good at solving them.
A carp.
What?
That mission we were on,
I caught a carp this big too.
Once, the two of us were on a mission,
right here.
You disguised yourself as a fisherman.
The suspect never showed up,
but you reeled in a five-pound carp.
I remember that.
Back then you told me,
"This is amazing.
I can brag about this to my grandson forever."
Lucky for me,
it's a granddaughter.
That mouth of yours,
is a classic case of harming others for no gain.
But you've got some nerve, kid.
With everything going on,
you still dared to stay at a hotel?
If I didn't leave you a clue,
how would you find me?
Were you that certain
I wouldn't arrest you?
If you hadn't gone easy on me,
even with wings I couldn't escape the Criminal Investigation Unit.
Provincial Criminal Police Marksmanship Award,
you've won it three times.
It was just an easy favor.
Chief Xing
bringing a gun into the interrogation room
meant he intended to let you go.
You know,
you may seem rough around the edges,
but you're more meticulous than anyone.
Telling Chief Xing I wasn't cuffed was a double entendre, right?
Both a warning,
and a test.
Hey,
When did you start suspecting Chief Xing?
After Su Zhuang's death,
I secretly pulled the hospital surveillance.
The only ones who entered Su Zhuang's room alone
were you and Chief Xing.
Then why did you rule me out?
Because of Xing Mingliang.
I had a feeling that everything bad Xing Mingliang did,
Chief Xing knew about.
And he'd been to Xu Wenwen's club.
Jiang Han's father, Chief Jiang,
got photos of it.
Not bad, kid.
You even pulled Chief Jiang into this.
But up to now,
our suspicions about Xu Wenwen
are all based on inference and guesswork.
We have no solid evidence.
Then let's follow the chain of profit,
and dig deep.
Think about it.
Xu Wenwen took such huge risks
to commit these crimes,
all for the money, right?
Shen Qing's death,
Su Zhuang's death,
are both tied to money.
What does that tell us?
It tells us there's a full profit chain behind them.
Xu Wenwen is at the top,
Shen Qing and Su Zhuang are in the middle.
So who's at the bottom?