♪Don't be afraid of the long journey♪
♪Love will comfort your missing♪
♪All the wounds will scab over♪
♪And turn into the blossoms of time♪
♪Someone will wipe them away for you♪
♪Don't feel lonely, moving on♪
♪Share your story with time♪
♪It will respond
with a gentle beam of light♪
♪Wishing you find her in the crowd♪
♪And rest content with a simple life♪
♪Even though life is full of regrets♪
♪May you always maintain enthusiasm♪
♪For every winter and summer♪
[Love Is Panacea]
[Episode 27]
[The show is the Major Project
for Supporting Literature and Art]
[in Sichuan Province in 2022]
[Based on the novel "Healer"
by Ningmeng Yuyan]
Only the person on site
exposed three cases
of aneurysmal ruptures.
Yet Prof. Wen Yuliang in charge of R&D
failed to convince at the conference.
Mr. Du,
is this intentional covering up
or poor management?
Let me answer that for you.
Hello, board members.
My name is Wen Ran.
I'm now in charge
of project HDQ39.
The Prof. Wen Yuliang you mentioned
is my father.
I know his research
better than anyone.
From what I understand,
these three patients with ruptures
had already signed
voluntary withdrawal forms
before the ruptures.
In clinical trials,
these should be counted
as natural dropouts.
Clearly, it's used
by someone with an agenda
to smear our company
and HDQ39.
This just goes to show
the project's huge potential.
We've stepped on some toes.
Regardless,
we'll soon present
a crisis management plan.
Don't think a crisis management plan
will help you muddle through.
I suspect
there are serious flaws
in HDQ39's development,
and they have caught someone's eye.
If similar adverse events happen again,
this drug
will surely be halted
by the Ethics Committee.
All the billions invested
will go down the drain.
That's just speculation.
There's no evidence
linking HDQ39 to the ruptures.
Even with risks,
our job is
to exhaust our ability
to ensure the project's success
and its smooth market launch.
It's an "orphan drug".
Even if it hits the market,
how big can it get?
With such a negative impact now,
I suggest
cutting our losses.
Listen, everyone.
Authoritative data shows
China's orphan drug market
will exceed ten billion dollars
in the next five to ten years.
It has great promise.
Our company, Jiehui,
is among the first in China
to plan and strategize it.
HDQ39 will be the vanguard
in orphan drug research.
And the eager acquisition interest
from the Maiteng
proves this point.
When I started this project,
you all resisted, just like now.
You want me to cut losses now?
Should we deduct it...
Mr. Wang,
from your bonus?
You...
Mr. Wang, stop it.
Everyone,
if HDQ39 launches smoothly,
it's good for all.
If it doesn't,
someone must pay
for this stubborn decision.
That's it.
Yuncheng,
those older men on the board
just talked nonsense.
Don't take it to heart.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best
to produce results
and shut them up.
Lots notice problems,
but few solve them.
The latter is who we need.
Are you referring to me?
Ran, step out, please.
Alright.
Senior.
Wei'an, why are you here?
My aunt's sanatorium,
why did you arrange it?
Did you know she has depression?
She can be a heavy burden on your mom.
Not just house chores
like washing and cooking
but caring for her mood.
Caring for the sick can be exhausting.
That sanatorium must be pricey.
I'll transfer you the money.
Let's not talk cash between us.
I told your mom not to tell you.
You're too proud.
If you knew this,
you'd have wanted to settle accounts
or felt embarrassed.
But please tell me,
why was the video of my aunt
in Prof. Wen's report
and taken at the sanatorium?
About the video...
Hold on.
Assistant Lin, come in, please.
Mr. Du.
About the video
taken at the sanatorium
for Wei'an's aunt,
do you know that?
Here's the thing.
Before Prof. Wen's
neurology annual conference,
he needed supporting materials
to show clinical trial results.
I thought a video would be convincing,
so I got Ms. Su Yuan's consent
and sent a video of her to Prof. Wen.
For privacy protection,
I pixelated her face.
About Wei'an's aunt's matter,
why didn't you consult me first?
I thought
with the face blurred,
it'd be unrecognizable.
So I...
Sorry, Mr. Du.
I didn't think it through.
Such a thing can never happen again.
Got it.
Sorry, Wei'an,
for my poor management.
I'll personally apologize
to your aunt another day.
No need, senior.
Thanks for the care.
But we shouldn't trouble you.
I'll find another sanatorium
and move my aunt out soon.
Wei'an, I really wanted
to help you out.
We appreciate it.
There's something
I must tell you.
The result of the experiment
Gu Yunzheng and I made indicates that
HDQ39
may be linked to aneurysms.
Tomorrow, I'll talk to Prof. Wen.
I know
you're under pressure for the project.
But I remember you said
if there's any adverse event
with the drug,
you'd end it yourself.
Sorry, senior.
I wish more than you
for the drug to work.
But now,
I have to make that choice.
Yuncheng,
what's she doing at Jiehui?
She wants me
to halt project HDQ39 myself.
What?
What is she up to?
I've left Huaren Hospital.
Why won't she leave us alone?
They've found
preliminary evidence
linking HDQ39 to aneurysms.
She'll see Prof. Wen soon.
Yes.
With my dad's integrity,
he'll surely be convinced by her
and halt the trial.
That'll make his years
of hard work wasted.
No, Yuncheng, think of some way.
The state has policies
favoring orphan drug research.
I can get expedited approval.
After the drug's launch,
I'll collect further data
on its efficacy and safety
for evaluation.
Ran,
I need your help.
what's going on?
I spilled orange juice
all over my laptop.
You're so clumsy.
Dad, can I use your laptop?
Mine won't start.
Alright.
But be careful.
All my work stuff is on there.
Don't damage it.
I know.
[HDQ39-related files]
[HDQ39 clinical trial report]
[To: Du Yuncheng]
[Outpatient Zhang He Hospital]
Prof. Wen.
Next Tuesday at 2 PM,
please come to the lecture hall.
[Invitation: HDQ39 Clinical Trial
Termination Press Conference]
Prof. Wen,
you've got your answer?
Let's see
your trial results.
[HDQ39-Mouse Aneurysm Association Study]
In hypertensive models,
over 4% of mice with Huntington's gene
show a positive for aneurysm.
You've won.
Prof. Wen,
our goal in the trial
was never to win
or to negate HDQ39.
Instead,
during the trials,
we saw HDQ39's great potential.
We hope you
continue to refine it.
Rest assured,
HDQ39 is like my child.
I'll give the public
a satisfactory response.
And Su,
I had a prejudice against you.
I apologize.
Now I solemnly apologize to you.
No, please don't.
I should apologize to you
for my impulsive action
when seeing my aunt's video
at the conference.
Sorry, Prof. Wen.
I didn't mean to offend you.
It's fine.
Rigorous science
must withstand questioning.
Mr. Du of Jiehui sent me the video
to include in my report
to corroborate HDQ39's effects.
At that time, I hesitated
whether to include it,
wondering if it was inappropriate.
But in the end, to draw the audience,
I added it.
You say Mr. Du of Jiehui
gave it to you?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
[Du Yuncheng Auto-reply:]
Wen Ran!
Wen Ran, come here!
Dad.
Didn't I tell you not to work at Jiehui?
You're taking my words lightly,
aren't you?
If not at Jiehui, where can I work?
Huaren's sanction
means I can't work in hospitals anymore.
Only Jiehui would offer me
a project manager position right away.
Ran,
why can't you see?
Du Yuncheng is using you.
Dad,
why can't you trust
your daughter's abilities?
Wherever I go,
I'm outstanding enough.
But in your eyes,
everything I do is wrong.
You always interfere.
Fine, then I'll ask you,
did you touch my laptop?
What did you send to Du Yuncheng
with my email?
I...
Dad,
Yuncheng is also for your good.
You've researched HDQ39 for many years.
You can't let everyone's efforts
go to waste
over less than 1% side effects.
Are you willing?
You've let Du Yuncheng
brainwash you into this!
Haven't you thought?
Letting you join Jiehui now,
he has an agenda,
and it's not simple.
I worry
he'll do anything to achieve his goal.
Yuncheng has his difficulties.
He needs profits.
Without advancing the new drug
to market,
he'll lose control of Jiehui.
I've seen how the old board
schemes against him.
He's really struggling.
Dad,
please just trust me once.
With Yuncheng's abilities,
He surely has a way
to get HDQ39 to market.
I tell you,
I won't let HDQ39 hit the market.
It's a matter of principle,
no room for discussion.
I will halt the trial.
Dad...
Let everyone know,
move the press conference to tomorrow.
Notify Gu and Su from Huaren Hospital.
Dad,
you've been my idol since childhood.
How can you lose
to someone like Su Wei'an?
How can you do this?
Ran, research isn't child's play.
Winning or losing,
and Du Yuncheng's profits,
all can't outweigh patients' safety
and health.
You say I'm your idol,
but would I teach you
to act like this?
Yuncheng, bad news.
My dad's calling a press conference.
He's halting the trial tomorrow.
Dad,
pretty please,
don't hold the press conference.
When you announce the halt,
It's all over for Yuncheng.
Now all you think about is Du Yuncheng.
I don't know what bewitched you,
making you cast aside
research ethics and personal principles.
Yes, it's all my fault.
Just don't end the trial.
I'll leave Jiehui
and break up with Yuncheng.
I'll listen to you.
Ran,
you really disappoint me.
What should I do?
Senior.
Make it short.
I'm pressed for time.
This might take up some
of your time, Mr. Du.
We have many questions for you.
Why were those three aneurysm patients'
voluntary dropout forms
all signed
just before they fell ill?
Even if they fell ill
after dropping out,
you should still report
to the Ethics Committee.
Months have passed,
but we haven't seen
any report from the Ethics Committee.
I wonder why.
That's for the research team.
Jiehui just funds it.
You can ask Prof. Wen about it.
I've already spoken to Prof. Wen.
I've hoped
he'd report the adverse events,
but Yang Wenbin has been obstructing.
And before the neurology conference,
Prof. Wen knew nothing
of the three patients
with aneurysms.
Someone's covering it up.
Senior,
did you bribe Yang Wenbin?
Wei'an,
don't make accusations
without evidence.
Senior, please stop lying.
I learned from Prof. Wen.
You sent that video
of my aunt to him.
How many patients like my aunt
are confined
in your so-called sanatoriums,
under surveillance, at your mercy?
Also,
how did you persuade my mom
and my aunt
to sign the voluntary dropout forms?
Wei'an, it's not what you think.
I'll explain everything to you later.
But now,
I have urgent business.
Senior.
Du Yuncheng.
If you don't explain everything today,
don't think about leaving.
Get out of my way!
Senior!
Du Yuncheng!
No matter if Prof. Wen
holds a press conference today,
we'll report our findings
to the Ethics Committee.
HDQ39 won't hit the market.
Senior!
- Gu Yunzheng!
- Senior!
Why do you oppose me on everything?
Is it because of Su Wei'an?
Don't you know
HDQ39 is her only hope
of survival?
What did you say?
How do you know?
I know. I've known for a long time.
I know everything.
Ever since you left school,
I've known it all.
You carry the gene
for Huntington's Disease.
You're
a third-generation paternal carrier.
In a few years,
you're going to get sick.
Without a specific drug,
you're likely to die.
Do you think I wanted
to abandon being a doctor
to take over Grandpa's medicine company?
I've been under so much pressure
from the board
to invest in HDQ39.
Because it's the only mature project
on Huntington's
in our country.
If Wen Ran weren't Prof. Wen's daughter,
I wouldn't have given her a second look.
I've done all this for you!
A drug that could cause
aneurysmal ruptures
and even cause death.
You say it's for Wei'an?
Yes.
I've analyzed
the impact of hypertension
on medication.
Gu Yunzheng,
do you think you're the only clever one?
As long as Wei'an
doesn't have high blood pressure,
the drug is effective.
Don't talk about the incidence
of adverse events
being four percent.
Even if it was forty percent,
I would overcome all difficulties
to make it to market.
You can say I'm after money,
say I want to win.
No matter how you see me,
as long as I can save Wei'an,
I'll do whatever it takes.
But I don't need it, senior.
I need even less
for you to sacrifice others to save me.
Yes,
it's all wishful thinking on my part.
You rejected me before.
I thought it was because
of Huntington's.
I thought that if I developed a cure,
you would give me another chance
and consider me again.
I thought we would
be carefree and happy like before.
But
I was wrong.
You only have Gu Yunzheng
in your heart, like them.
No matter how hard I try, it's in vain.
No matter my achievements,
I'm worthless in your eyes.
Remember the Hippocratic Oath
we swore before we enrolled?
Why can you only see
the one percent of aneurysmal ruptures
but not the ninety-nine percent
of patients
whose symptoms are delayed?
For that one percent,
after ten years
of attack of Huntington's,
they may end in dementia
and death by choking
and become a burden on their families.
They'd better die on the operating table
and gain a clean end.
Du Yuncheng,
you've completely lost your mind.
Yes, I've lost it.
You guys are driving me crazy.
Are you still the senior I knew?
[HDQ39 Phase III Clinical Trial]
As we recheck it,
[Termination Press Conference]
Among the 300 subjects
in the HDQ39 Phase III clinical trial,
three suffered aneurysmal ruptures,
and one of them...
died.
After an internal assessment,
it's a significant adverse event.
It has been submitted
for Ethics Committee review.
Therefore,
I offer sincere apologies
to the patients and families
who suffered adverse reactions,
and deep condolences
to the deceased patient
of HDQ39.
I announce
that the HDQ39 drug trial
for Huntington's Disease
is completely suspended.
Until the drug mechanism
that caused the adverse event
is completely revised,
HDQ39
will not go to market.
[Family of Patient]
You won.
You've destroyed my father's work
for so many years.
You're happy, right?
I wanted HDQ39 to market more than you.
Right.
I almost forgot.
You also carry the gene
for Huntington's.
Wen Ran.
Dr. Gu,
your last show
of protecting your girlfriend
was well played.
Research is rigorous,
not a stage for personal grudges.
Dr. Gu,
you're not my higher-up anymore.
So I'll speak it frankly
and stop being prudish before me.
Assigning your girlfriend
an assistant in your team,
is that your rigor?
Enough.
Su Wei'an,
your so-called love for research,
and returning to the lab,
these are just for your survival, right?
Yes, what's wrong with it?
I want to find a chance to survive
for thirty thousand patients
with Huntington's
in my lifetime.
Is there anything wrong with it?
I'm telling you,
HDQ39 is your only chance to survive.
And today, you destroyed it
with your own hand.
When you fall ill with no cure,
you'll get what you deserve.
Wei'an.
Wen Ran,
you truly don't deserve
to be Prof. Wen's daughter.
[HDQ39-Mouse Aneurysm]
You've already known
[Association Study Report]
HDQ39 could lead to aneurysms.
Why didn't you report it
to the Medical Ethics Committee?
This research report,
he gave it to you, right?
You think you've done
nothing wrong, right?
Yunzheng gave me this report
to frame you up.
Do you mean that?
Prof. Wen has been rigorous
during his whole life.
He couldn't have made
such a stupid mistake.
If it's not his problem,
then it must be yours.
Dad,
if it wasn't me standing here today,
but Yunzheng,
would you believe him,
or would you believe Prof. Wen?
Jiehui was founded by me.
You've taken over it
just for three years
but caused such a scandal.
From now on,
don't come to this old house anymore.
Is coming to this old house
some great honor?
Do you think I want to come?
Grandpa,
since I was young,
you've only cared for Yunzheng.
You said I'm inferior
to him in every way
and you told me to give way to him.
He lost his mother,
but you gave him all the best things
in the world.
You favoured him and praised him.
Even though I was the one by your side,
you still wished to see him.
Clearly, I'm the eldest son
and grandson of this family.
Clearly, he has changed
his surname to Gu.
But in your heart,
I could never equal Gu Yunzheng.
And my mom,
she prepared so many gifts for you.
Have you ever appreciated them?
Have you ever cared about her feelings?
Today I just want
to ask you one question.
What did we do wrong?
Is our dignity worth nothing to you?
Shut up!
How can you speak
to your grandpa like this?
Grandpa,
dad,
I won't come
to this old house again.
Du Yuncheng!
We want the medicine!
Give us the medicine!
Call your president out!
Let him explain to us!
Why was the HDQ39 trial suspended?
Why can't it be marketed?
- We want the medicine!
- Give us the medicine!
Give us an explanation!
Quiet, quiet!
Listen to me.
We will surely give you an explanation.
But Mr. Du isn't here today,
please go back home for now, okay?
I'll give you an explanation.
Yes.
You want to know
who's stopping you
from getting your medicine?
I'll tell you now.
How could they let my son
stop his medication?
She's here.
- Quickly, quickly!
- It's them!
- It's your fault!
- What are you doing?
It's all because of you!
Miss, please,
announce that you were mistaken.
If this drug goes to market,
my wife can have a chance to survive!
Right!
Your aunt's aneurysm was her bad luck.
But you're stopping us from medication.
That's your fault!
Yes, give us the medicine!
Enough.
Give us the medicine!
Calm down.
Everyone disperse,
or we'll call the police.
Calm down!
Haven't you slept yet?
I was thinking
that although HDQ39 has side effects,
it's also the hope
of every person with Huntington's.
I destroyed that hope with my own hands,
but where is the next hope?
We are able
to create that hope together.
Since we met in Lacaya,
you seem to always be unlucky,
with endless trouble
and a series of misfortunes.
Maybe,
to meet you,
I've used up all my luck.
Come on, let's see
who received the NSFDYS
this time.
Of course, it's my Boss.
[Ji Lanjuan, Luo Qun'an,
Qi Changyong, Zhao Yanxin]
[Xu Zhiqi, Shen Jiaming, Xu Ting]
How come he's not there?
Director Wang said,
my Boss's project on glioma
had a great chance to get the NSFDYS.
Fan,
your Boss,
has changed the direction
of his research
from glioma to Huntington's.
Really? Why don't I know that?
Boss!
Director Wang.
What happened?
Why the rush?
Nothing.
Well, teacher,
I'm going to change clothes first,
and let's meet
at our usual place tonight.
Teacher,
here,
your favorite Spicy Rabbit Kidneys.
Try it.
I have no appetite.
Tell me,
why did you suddenly decide
to apply for a Huntington's project?
Our entire Neurosurgery Department
has no foundation in this area.
Even if you collaborate
with internal medicine
or collaborate with international teams
to apply for the project,
it'll be starting from scratch.
Are you aware of that?
Right.
You know it's a tough task,
so I have to move faster.
What about your glioma project?
Are you going
to abandon it halfway?
The glioma project
has concluded,
so it's not abandoned halfway.
What about the work
of your glioma research team?
Well,
I trust Director Wang,
you'll find the right person
to take over it.
Stop kidding around.
If you really took me, your director,
your teacher, seriously,
why wouldn't you discuss it with me
before making such a big decision?
Teacher,
One day a teacher, a lifetime a father.
You're even closer to me
than my own father.
Here,
try this also.
Try it.
You have limited funds and staff,
and it's hard to produce results.
Have you thought
about these difficulties?
Huntington's Disease
is a global challenge.
It might take
the rest of your life on this.
Have you considered that?
Teacher,
I didn't discuss it with you this time
because there was no room
for discussion.
I've made my decision.
I'm not being impulsive
or being emotional.
Every step I'm taking now
has been thought through.
I've even designed
a tentative cure mechanism.
My task now
is to wage a long battle
against this disease.
Look at you...
I think
it's because you fell in love
with Su Wei'an.
Just for her,
you changed your research direction,
didn't you?
Teacher,
do you remember
why you chose
to research glioma originally?
You told me your son's story.
He was fourteen
when he had stage III glioma.
Now,
it's been nearly ten years
since he left you.
I believe you would understand the most
the pain and despair
of being unable to do anything
for your loved ones
when they are sick.
Yes,
I'm dating Su Wei'an.
But it's also because of her
that I've understood better
patients with Huntington's
and their families.
And I understood their helplessness
and despair
in the face of illness.
It's for this reason
that I have the courage
to fight this disease
to the bitter end.
Maybe in our lifetime,
we'll never achieve anything.
But isn't it better
than doing nothing?
I knew before coming here
that talking to you would be pointless,
like casting pearls before swine.
Here, teacher,
have some of this.
In the future,
I will still need a lot
of support from you.
Understood.
What's wrong?
Anything goes down in the hospital?
It's not the hospital, it's Yunzheng.
Yunzheng?
What's wrong with him?
He was doing fine with glioma research,
but suddenly he wanted
to switch to Huntington's.
I don't know what he's up to.
Huntington's?
I've never even heard of it.
What's
in Yunzheng's mind?
Du, don't be anxious.
Yunzheng might just be on a whim.
He might switch back
in a couple of days.
Switch what?
Do you think this is a game?
Academic research requires
wholehearted dedication.
Don't get angry with me.
In my opinion,
Yunzheng is an excellent child,
but you can't let him be all the time.
You still need to oversee things.
However,
whether he listens to you
is another question.
After all, Yunzheng is not Yuncheng.
He has had his own mind since childhood.
Speaking of Yuncheng,
I have been unable
to contact him recently.
- Enough.
- Now Jiehui...
Let's not bring up Yuncheng.
On Yunzheng,
I have my judgment.
Let's eat.
[Using Novel Small-Molecule Compounds]
[To Selectively Degrade HD-Associated
Pathogenic HTT Protein]
Boss,
I didn't finish
what I wanted to say last time.
I heard you're switching
to Huntington's,
and I want to join you.
Fang Mingfan,
You don't need to switch with me.
The follow-up work for my former project
will be well managed
by Director Wang Huanzhong.
I just have one question for you:
Do you still need people
on your project team?
Then why do you hesitate?
I just want to follow you.
Moreover,
I don't have a specific research project
or the ambition
to achieve specific results.
You have to think it through.
What's in front of me now
is very likely a dead end,
or every path could be a dead end.
Even if ending up
with a disastrous defeat,
that could be possible.
Even so, do you still want to join?
I'm not afraid.
Even if there's a dead end ahead,
we can always find another way.
Let me tell you,
my current research team
only has me and Su Wei'an.
We're in need of staff,
in desperate need.
Yunzheng.
When will you bring
your favourite pupil home
to meet your grandpa?
Who has bewitched my grandson?
I just want to see the person.
Fang Mingfan,
there's only one condition
to join my team:
don't spy for my grandpa.
No, I didn't.
If it's not you, then who...
Don't distress Fang Mingfan.
I heard it from Wang.
Now, in the whole country,
probably only my grandpa
and no one else would dare
to call Director Wang Huanzhong
Wang.
Exactly!
Director Wang used
to be grandpa's subordinate.
It must have been him who did it.
Boss, I'm going to leave now.
Hello, director.
Why do you want
to change your research direction
to study a rare disease?
Though fewer patients
have rare diseases,
their lives are equally valuable,
and they also need to be seen.
But why is it specifically Huntington's?
♪The night moves the hands of the clock♪
♪The noise replaces the silence♪
♪We act out a script of an encounter♪
♪The rainbow insetting the night♪
♪And the wind blowing over the desert♪
♪Were all once our witnesses♪
♪Who isn't lost in the vastness♪
♪Seeking a slim chance?♪
♪Trapped in this city called fate♪
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
♪Your lonely soul keeps warm with wine♪
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
♪You shine bright as a star♪
♪Twinkling in the loneliest times♪
♪The night moves the hands of the clock♪
♪The noise replaces the silence♪
♪We act out a script of an encounter♪
♪The rainbow insetting the night♪
♪And the wind blowing over the desert♪
♪Were all once our witnesses♪
♪Who isn't lost in the vastness♪
♪Seeking a slim chance?♪
♪Trapped in this city called fate♪
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
♪Your lonely soul keeps warm with wine♪
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
♪You shine bright as a star♪
♪Twinkling in the loneliest times♪