♪Don't be afraid of the long journey♪
♪Love will comfort your missing♪
♪All the wounds will scab over♪
♪And turn into the blossoms of time♪
♪Someone will wipe them away for you♪
♪Don't feel lonely, moving on♪
♪Share your story with time♪
♪It will respond
with a gentle beam of light♪
♪Wishing you find her in the crowd♪
♪And rest content with a simple life♪
♪Even though life is full of regrets♪
♪May you always maintain enthusiasm♪
♪For every winter and summer♪
[Love Is Panacea]
[Episode 14]
[The show is the Major Project
for Supporting Literature and Art]
[in Sichuan Province in 2022]
[Based on the novel "Healer"
by Ningmeng Yuyan]
Huaren Hospital
International Department.
Not in the same building.
So I'm unlikely
to run into Gu Yunzheng, right?
If I could just catch a glimpse of him
from afar.
[Outpatient]
Hi.
I'd like to register
with a psychiatrist.
Dr. Li Wantong, please.
Sure, please wait a moment.
Sorry ma'am,
I've looked it up for you.
Dr. Li is fully booked for today.
Could I make an appointment for you
on Friday morning?
Okay, thank you.
You are welcome.
I've made the appointment for you.
Next.
Hello.
Gu Yunzheng.
Dr. Li,
this is where we work.
I hope you will behave yourself.
I get it.
Dr. Gu,
from now on,
I'll do my job in the hospital
and pursue you after work.
Did I not make myself clear?
Dr. Li.
I don't know you at all,
and I'm not sure of your intentions.
But the sure thing is,
we are not suitable for each other.
My purpose is very clear.
Your IQ is 145,
and mine is 140,
which means we can make
a perfect couple.
I don't have any
family history of diseases.
So our next generation
will definitely have terrific genes,
born with a winning hand.
What could be luckier than that?
According to your theory,
I think you should go to a gene bank
to find your other half.
By that time,
you will find
that there are a lot of genes better
than mine.
If I have to,
that could be a solution.
But for now,
fate has brought us together.
I won't waste this opportunity.
Don't you think the combination
of our good genes
is a contribution to human evolution?
I think discussing genetics here
is a complete waste of time.
Gu Yunzheng,
I'll give you some time
to think it over.
You have no reason to reject me.
(And our next generation)
(will definitely have terrific genes,)
(born with a winning hand.)
(What could be luckier than that? )
(It's already difficult to be alive.)
(What right do I have
to talk about love?)
What are you thinking about?
Look at that girl.
Do you think she is pretty?
Which one?
The one in leather.
Yes, she is pretty.
Even though I'm a female,
I'd like to have her WeChat.
What's the matter?
Do you think that if a Harvard M. D.
looks like that,
there would be no man
who doesn't like her?
Such a beautiful woman
wouldn't be refused by anyone,
even if she is not a Harvard Ph.D.
When standing together,
they're indeed a perfect match.
Wei'an, you've had so much lemon water.
don't you feel sour?
Let's dance.
I don't want to dance.
Come on.
I'm not going. I can't dance.
Let's dance.
Just treat them
as if they were nonexistent.
Keep dancing, and you'll learn.
Okay, fine.
I'm not unhappy.
Go find your Fang Mingfan.
It's fine. No need to worry about him.
Right now,
I have him wrapped around my finger.
He comes and goes at my command.
He's a normal person
with his worries and dignity.
What do you mean?
Has Fang Mingfan fallen
for someone else?
How is that possible?
He's close to wearing a sign
around his neck
that says I am in love.
Look at this.
[Fang Mingfan:
Do you also find life difficult?]
Why haven't I seen this post before?
Look at mine.
[Fang Mingfan's Moments]
It really is.
I can't believe he blocked me.
Even the sun
can have its cloudy days.
You should spend more time with him.
[Kai: Ying, do you want
to watch a movie together tomorrow night?]
[There's a great blockbuster
with amazing special effects lately.]
He's inviting me to watch a movie.
Is he trying to pursue me,
or is he trying
to pursue me,
or is he trying to pursue me?
No. I already have a boyfriend.
Right. I should make it clear to him.
[Jiang Muying:
Kai, I actually have a boyfriend.]
Would this be too much?
It's just watching a movie.
It's nothing.
Maybe that's because he just returned
from abroad and doesn't have many friends.
[Jiang Muying: OK]
[Send]
[Fang Mingfan]
[Jiang Muying]
What is my Dr. Fang doing?
Do you miss me?
Provence tomahawk steak
and garlic-flavored shrimp
are your favorites.
Not to forget your little quirks.
Everything has to be drizzled
with pumpkin soup, right?
How am I doing?
Aren't I considerate?
A surprise.
This is Dr. Fang's
exclusive on-duty gift package.
The most crucial liver supplement.
Steam eye mask.
You really need sleep spray
and vitamins.
Jiang.
What's going on with you today?
Why are you so nice to me?
Usually, you just order the dishes
you like,
and it is me who give you gifts.
Have I done something wrong?
Tell me if I did something wrong.
You don't need to do this.
Why, don't you like it?
Isn't it only natural
for a girlfriend to be kind
to her boyfriend?
You don't like it?
Then I'll be nice to someone else.
I like it. I like it very much.
I just want to know what happened.
You're acting
like a completely different person today.
Okay.
Then let me ask you.
Why did you block me
when you posted to Moments?
When?
I saw it.
It's about a lonely little bear
or something,
with a caption saying life is difficult.
Why did you do that?
Who did you send it to?
Which girl do you want
to care about you?
I didn't mean that at all, Jiang.
I was just passing by a cafe that day,
seeing a little bear.
And I felt a bit sad
at that moment. That's all.
Then why did you block me?
Besides,
when you're in trouble,
shouldn't I be the first to know?
No. Jiang, I...
I just didn't want you to feel sad.
I was afraid you'd worry about me.
I didn't want my emotions to affect you.
And there was the thing that happened
in the hospital operating room that day.
It's hard to say in a few words.
It's hard to say in a few words?
Then just say a few more words.
Jiang, let's drop it.
Can't we be happy
and have a nice meal together?
Let's eat.
I know I'm dumb and useless.
I don't know
any of those medical terms
that you are familiar with.
I know you just don't want
to talk to me.
Because you think talking to me
is like talking to a wall.
Is that it?
Jiang, why do you misunderstand me?
I really didn't have that thought
at that time.
I blocked you back then
just because I didn't want you
to worry about me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't consider your feelings.
But I really don't mean
to think less of you.
Then tell me now.
What kind of trouble are you in?
I don't deserve to know it,
is that it?
Fang Mingfan,
you don't have
to tell me anything anymore.
I don't want to hear it either.
From now on, your joys or sorrows
have nothing to do with me
as long as you are happy.
Jiang.
Sir, you haven't paid yet.
Ying.
Kai.
You don't look so good.
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
No.
Maybe I didn't sleep well last night.
I'm a bit tired.
How about we reschedule for another day?
Don't worry. I am fine.
We're already here.
Just let me know
If you feel uncomfortable.
Let's go.
Wait a moment.
I need to tell my mom.
Mom,
I'm going to the movies with Ying,
and I cannot go shopping with you.
You can only shop by yourselves.
Let's take a picture.
Smile.
Alright, let's go.
Dr. Gu,
there are no more surgeries today.
You can go home and get some rest.
Okay, got it. Thank you.
No need to work overtime today.
Why don't you go on a date
with your girlfriend?
I almost
don't have a girlfriend anymore.
What happened? Did you have a fight?
To be precise,
I made her angry.
She just wanted to comfort me,
but I...
She was right.
I was just feeling sorry for myself.
Look at this.
I've made so many calls,
but she didn't answer.
First, she didn't answer the phone.
Then she blocked me on WeChat.
And finally,
she disappeared without a word
and went without a trace.
I know this all too well.
Patrãozinho,
she didn't block me.
It's just you
who didn't make it through.
Just kidding.
She only blocked you
and didn't delete you,
which means there's still hope for you.
Is there a difference
between block and delete?
Of course there is.
If she deletes you,
it is to erase all of your memories,
like the chat history,
the pictures,
and the videos you sent are all gone.
But If she blocks you,
you are just not chatting temporarily.
That makes sense.
In terms of love skills,
I do have a little
more experience than you.
My Jiang Muying
is probably
just temporarily ignoring me.
You look like
you're going to live alone forever.
I'm going to live alone forever
because of you.
What did I do wrong again?
Last time, I was actually going
to clear things up with Su Wei'an
but was called back for surgery by you.
I'm sorry, patrãozinho.
I really didn't know at the time.
Fang Mingfan,
I can give you a chance to make amends.
I want to meet Su Wei'an.
Su Wei'an?
Where can I find Su Wei'an?
I don't have her contact information.
Su Wei'an is in China right now.
Your girlfriend
meets her frequently.
I don't care what tricks you use.
If I can't meet the person
I want to see,
then you'll never get to see the person
you want to see.
Okay.
Understood.
I'll go make up with Jiang Muying now
and then bring Su Wei'an
in front of you.
Then why don't you go right away?
[ONE WAY LIVE HOUSE Bar]
Wei'an,
I'm your most loyal fan.
Don't let my passion intimidate you.
You've done a great job
with the atmosphere here.
You can ask the boss
for your salary later.
Today, I'll show you
what it means to be a one-person team.
Where's Fang Mingfan?
Doing surgery?
Don't mention him.
We haven't contacted
for quite a few days.
Let it be.
Reconciliation is just one step
from the fight.
It depends on who takes that step first.
Then why should I be the one
to take the step?
Can't he take that step first?
Of course he can,
but it could have different outcomes.
It's like if he misses a step,
it might be just a scrape.
But if he rolls down the stairs,
then it's all over.
[Your hustle and bustle
has nothing to do with me.]
[I just want
to be a quiet, beautiful woman!]
[Loading data...]
[Jiang: Your hustle and bustle
has nothing to do with me.]
[I just want
to be a quiet, beautiful woman!]
Wei'an, you're here.
I'd like to introduce
to you a mystery guest.
Who?
Wei'an.
Yuncheng?
What are you doing here?
Alright,
today's performance is up to you.
You guys have a good chat.
Yuncheng, do you remember me?
Jiang Muying,
Wei'an's best friend.
I remember everyone
related to Wei'an.
Yuncheng, you know this place well.
Do you come here often?
This is a secret between me and Hui.
Excuse me, I have to go to the bathroom.
Something to drink?
Waiter.
[ONE WAY LIVE HOUSE Bar]
[Jiang Muying: Your hustle and bustle
has nothing to do with me.]
[I just want
to be a quiet, beautiful woman!]
[Jinhai City, ONE WAY Bar]
She posted to Moments plus location.
Fang Mingfan, can't you understand this?
No wonder you don't have a girlfriend.
Su Wei'an?
She found a new love so quickly.
It's a pity
that patrãozinho was still waiting.
I didn't expect her to be such a woman.
[Fang Mingfan]
(He finally left.)
[Du Yuncheng]
(Hello,)
(the number you've dialed is busy.)
[Wen Ran: Why don't you answer the phone?
Where are you? I'm coming to find you.]
Alright,
then you pay more attention
to this patient.
(Hello, the number you've dialed
is busy.)
(Please dial later.)
He's not answering my calls.
[We have been in love for 745 days.]
[Couple's Map]
[ONE WAY Happy]
It's ONE WAY Bar again.
Yuncheng.
What kind of secret
could you and Hui have?
You're making it seem so mysterious.
Next, a perfect combination,
the soul drummer and her guitar prince
will put on the melody of love.
Old partner,
let's relive the glory
of the Huaren Band.
Go ahead.
♪The night moves the hands of the clock♪
♪The noise replaces the silence♪
♪We act out a script of an encounter♪
You are terrific.
♪And the wind blowing over the desert♪
♪Were all once our witnesses♪
♪Who isn't lost in the vastness♪
♪Seeking a slim chance?♪
♪Trapped in this city called fate♪
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
Wei'an!
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
Thank god,
finally I made it.
Please don't go, okay?
(Your life)
(means a lot)
to the person who loves you.
(Can you fix)
(all broken things?)
(Sure.)
(I can fix anything.)
(Can you fix me then?)
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
♪Your lonely soul keeps warm with wine♪
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
[ONE WAY LIVE HOUSE BAR ]
♪You shine bright as a star♪
♪Twinkling in the loneliest times♪
♪Who isn't lost in the vastness♪
♪Seeking a slim chance?♪
♪Trapped in this city called fate♪
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
♪Your lonely soul keeps warm with wine♪
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
♪You shine bright as a star♪
♪Twinkling in the loneliest times♪
Is the hospital not busy today, Dr. Gu?
You even have time to relax in a bar.
Aren't you the same?
Mr. Du, who has a packed schedule,
turns out to be an artist
playing the guitar to charm the ladies.
You're good at it.
I learned it for Wei'an
and practiced for a long time
to match her drumbeats.
If you can't match it, just give up.
Love cannot be forced.
[Kai: You are an angel.]
[Jiang replied to Yan Kai: Thank you, Kai.]
Kai.
You call him so affectionately.
What's the matter?
Is it not okay?
I thought you were mad at me
these past few days,
so I'm afraid to disturb you.
But it turns out you're flirting
with someone named Kai.
What are you talking about?
He's my childhood friend,
why wouldn't I call him Kai?
Really?
Believe it or not.
How did you know I was here?
You posted on Moments
with location sharing.
Were you worried
that I couldn't find you?
How could it be?
Did I post it?
I didn't notice.
If I hadn't arrived in time,
you would have run off with that Kai.
Are you jealous?
No man can stand it.
Calling you an angel
with a heart emoji.
Ugh,
a slick guy.
You even called him Kai.
You have never called me like that.
Mingfan.
Dear Mingfan.
Okay.
You'd better call me by my full name.
Jiang.
I reflected on it that day.
I shouldn't have hidden it from you.
Patrãozinho asked me to perform surgery,
but I couldn't
overcome my mental barrier.
I was afraid I'd mess it up.
It was my fault that day.
I spoke too harshly
and was too mean to you.
I was afraid you'd think I was useless
and couldn't do anything right.
I was more afraid
that I was not even qualified
to be your listener.
How is that possible?
I was afraid...
I was afraid that after I told you,
you'd think I was useless.
Compared to patrãozinho,
who can do anything,
I'm useless.
How could it be?
You are already much stronger than me.
Although you've faced setbacks
and difficulties,
you never gave up.
Because you have dreams.
In my eyes,
you've always shone brightly.
Really?
Alone?
What are you doing?
My boyfriend is right over there.
Don't mess around.
It's not fun.
Do you want to know
where single girls are?
Where?
Right over there.
The girl who was playing the drums.
I know her.
She's never had a boyfriend
and is eager to fall in love.
I wonder
if you're the man of her dreams.
She's really lovely.
There's no girl I can't flirt with.
Really?
You will see.
You can do it.
Su Wei'an.
You asked for it.
Hi, babe.
I've been watching you for a while.
The way
you were playing the drums just now
was really cool.
I love it.
Don't leave just yet.
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk. Come on.
Waiter,
please give him a glass of honey water.
That's great.
You're going to feed me, aren't you?
Come on.
Let's have a drink together.
If you continue like this,
I'll call security.
You little girl,
stop pretending to be aloof with me.
Come on.
Let go of me.
You've got a temper, don't you?
Let me see how tough you are.
Who are you? Mind your own business.
I'm really sorry, dude.
I haven't practiced Ju-Jitsu
for a long time.
Seeing the sitting ducks like you,
I just couldn't help it.
I'll tell you what.
Even though you stink
and you're ugly,
you are suitable as the sitting ducks.
I'm really sorry, dude.
You?
Where did you come from?
Let me tell you.
You'd better get out of here quickly
before I get angry.
Or I'll give you a good kick.
I'm leaving.
Don't move.
Are you okay?
Call the boss.
Listen,
I've already called the police.
Don't play tricks.
What kind of jerk
who dares to bully her?
Boss,
could you please
check the pub's security cameras for me?
I want to know
if there are any details we don't know.
Don't worry.
Wei'an's business is my business.
Boss,
come over here immediately.
So
when I'm done here,
I'll take you
to check the security cameras.
Okay.
You're not hurt, are you?
That's good.
Gu Yunzheng,
I know you have me in mind.
If you hadn't been there just now,
I might have got hurt.
Dr. Gu,
won't you introduce your friend to us?
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Li Wantong.
I'm Dr. Gu's
colleague.
Just colleague.
It's a bit strange.
It's a feeling I can't describe.
Who is this lady?
You know her?
She's a Harvard Ph.D.
in the Psychological Department
at Huaren Hospital.
She is Boss's pursuer.
She's a Harvard woman with a PhD?
Impressive.
I remember now.
Wei'an mentioned her last time.
Since we're all gathered here,
how about having a drink
and getting to know each other?
Yeah, that's right.
Why is everyone still standing here?
Let's drink and talk. Let's go.
I won't be joining you.
I have to perform.
Wei'an,
you don't have to perform today.
Just have a good drink
and chat with your friends.
Don't worry. You'll still get paid.
I'll cover
all the expenses today.
Let me arrange it.
I'm here if you need anything.
Su Wei'an,
your boss told you to stay.
Are you still going to run away?
Why would I run away?
So,
why don't we sit together,
chat and have fun?
I don't have time.
I'm busy.
Is there any kind of painful past
between Miss Su and Dr. Gu?
Otherwise, why would it trigger
such a strong
psychological defense in Miss Su?
You're overthinking it.
There was nothing special between us
in the past.
I just don't want to talk.
So,
let's all sit together and chat.
I've been waiting for you
for a long time.
Wei'an,
let's sit for a while.
It's not fun to chat at a pub.
Let's play games.
These games are all too complicated.
[Chess]
Let's play something simple.
[Truth or Dare]
Truth or Dare.
Mr. Gu, Truth or Dare is outdated.
Let's play
The Werewolves of Miller's Hollow.
[The Werewolves of Miller's Hollow]
It's a fun game.
The music is so loud here.
Are you sure you want to play it?
Yes, Jiang.
I can't even hear what you're saying.
Everyone,
let's just play
Truth or Dare.
This game can help us
get to know each other faster.
I'll take the lead, Dr. Gu.
[Truth or Dare]
I choose Truth.
[Is there someone of the opposite sex
in this gathering whom you like? ]
Is there someone of the opposite sex
in this gathering whom you like?
Yes.
Who?
This is the next question.
Dr. Li, it's your turn.
Okay.
[What is your ideal type? ]
What is your ideal type?
My ideal type is someone like Dr. Gu.
He is handsome, intelligent,
emotionally stable and healthy.
It's my turn now.
I choose Truth.
[What would you say
to the one you love? ]
Say something to the one you love.
What would you say?
I'll tell her that
the sights are still there.
Where have you been when you
were supposed to see the sights with me?
Dr. Gu, you are so romantic.
You have increased my admiration
for you.
Fang Mingfan, it's your turn.
I'll do it.
I choose
Truth.
Okay.
[Share a secret
about the previous player. ]
Share a secret
about the previous player.
Boss has so many secrets.
I don't know which one to tell.
I choose to drink.
Drank it all.
How come none of you choose Dare?
Dare is more fun.
I'll choose Dare.
[Share the first contact you called]
Share the first contact
[Say I love you to the one]
you recently called.
Say I love you to the one.
What?
[Kai]
I choose to drink too.
What are you drinking for?
Who is the first contact
you recently called?
It's the courier.
You know that.
I order so much stuff every day.
If I call him and say "I love you".
How weird that would be.
And the courier knows my address.
It's not safe.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'll drink it for you.
You will have the chance
to drink it later.
Wei'an, it's your turn.
Truth or Dare?
I'll choose Truth.
What's great about this game is
that you can hear things
you don't usually hear.
But I like to play Dare.
Yes, Wei'an likes adventures.
Look at the person directly
across from you for 30 seconds.
Su Wei'an,
what's the matter?
You don't even have the guts
to look me in the eyes?
Come over.
Su Wei'an,
look me in the eyes.
I'll time it.
Ready, go.
[Is there someone of the opposite sex
in this gathering whom you like? ]
Boring.
Is this boring to you?
I think it's quite fun.
At least it gives me a chance
to ask you
why you disappeared without a word.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Miss Jiang Muying
just dedicated a song to all of you.
Let's shake our hands.
Dr. Gu,
the most important thing for adults
in a relationship
is to be responsible for themselves.
The past is the past,
even if it's beautiful.
Wei'an has moved on now.
Why are you stuck in the past?
You're making everyone unhappy.
Did I make her unhappy?
Yes.
Life is not easy for Wei'an.
I beg you, Dr. Gu.
Please stay away from her
and stop putting so much pressure
on her.
Wei'an, are you okay?
Is there a story
between you and Gu Yunzheng?
Seeing you two were. . .
It's all right.
When we were in Lacaya,
he was a doctor
and I was an interpreter.
We were just
work partners.
Maybe I left too abruptly
and didn't explain things
to him clearly.
So there might be some misunderstanding.
Besides that,
there's nothing else.
Actually, I really like being with you.
I can take off the mask
and stay away from competition.
It's nice to live life to the fullest.
Wei'an, actually,
you can be like this too.
You can tell me
what's bothering you.
But compared to an exciting life,
what I want more
is a peaceful and lasting one.
You know, you don't have to
push yourself too hard.
Just relax and be yourself.
But I don't have time anymore.
Why?
I
♪The night moves the hands of the clock♪
♪The noise replaces the silence♪
♪We act out a script of an encounter♪
♪The rainbow insetting the night♪
♪And the wind blowing over the desert♪
♪Were all once our witnesses♪
♪Who isn't lost in the vastness♪
♪Seeking a slim chance?♪
♪Trapped in this city called fate♪
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
♪Your lonely soul keeps warm with wine♪
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
♪You shine bright as a star♪
♪Twinkling in the loneliest times♪
♪The night moves the hands of the clock♪
♪The noise replaces the silence♪
♪We act out a script of an encounter♪
♪The rainbow insetting the night♪
♪And the wind blowing over the desert♪
♪Were all once our witnesses♪
♪Who isn't lost in the vastness♪
♪Seeking a slim chance?♪
♪Trapped in this city called fate♪
♪Yet still chasing the stars♪
♪Don't worry, my lost loved one♪
♪Your lonely soul keeps warm with wine♪
♪Let me embrace your wounds♪
♪You shine bright as a star♪
♪Twinkling in the loneliest times♪