=Save it for the Honeymoon=
=Episode 7=
You
can't avoid me anymore.
Mr. Zhou,
you must be hungry.
To thank you,
I'm taking you to my secret base.
All right.
Let's go.
(Gangyuan Restaurant
Mei's Canteen)
Aunt Mei!
Lin, there you go again.
You...
Why haven't you been here in years?
Aunt Mei,
I've been abroad for the past few years,
and have returned recently.
You're a regular here, too?
Sit here. Come on.
The little goal you talked about
last time, you made it?
How did you know that?
I think it's great.
You're a perfect match.
Aunt Mei, this one is my little goal.
I don't have a name yet,
but I'm going
to call it Xuenong Spirit.
What do you think?
You guys can have a good talk.
Okay!
I'll get to work.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Here are your dishes.
All your favorite ones.
Thanks, Aunt Mei.
Go ahead, please.
♪In the pink universe♪
♪I have pure love♪
So you come here a lot?
That's right. Good quality
and low price here.
And Aunt Mei is nice.
I'll come over as soon as I have time.
Thank you
for patronizing Aunt Mei's canteen.
♪I'm going with a group of people♪
♪In your eyes♪
♪There is a hidden universe♪
I'm exhausted.
What are you doing?
Making a PPT. Just give me
a minute. You eat first.
Okay.
Hey,
Mr. Zhou fired you yesterday
and put you back to work the next day.
What is he up to?
Playing hard to get?
He cherishes talents.
I'm also talented
but why doesn't he come to me every day?
Well, I see
you're going to fall in love with him.
No, no no.
I'm as normal
as fried eggs and tomatoes,
not like abalone or seafood.
He's only interested in me
for a few days.
I won't fall for it.
Good for you, Nong.
You're wise.
But he is Zhou Heng.
When a man like him
throws his pride down to pursue you,
you're not moved?
Listen to yourself.
Even if he gets down on his knees,
I can't be attracted to him.
(She must explain herself tomorrow.)
(But we have no relationship.)
(Why should she explain?)
(People say women)
(are emotionally unstable
a few days a month.)
(I've always wondered)
(if men, like women,)
(have a few days a month.)
Here is the document.
Don't make me wait for you next time.
You're the one who forgot the document.
Lin Xuenong.
Do you know you
have a meeting with Ice today?
Look at what you're wearing.
We represent the face
of the company on the outside.
You don't need
to attend today's meeting.
(You jerk! I'll be there!)
(Ice, Internet celebrity,
and livestreaming sales king)
Ice, the helicopter is in position.
The band is in position.
Wei.
Today is the 1314th day
we've known each other.
I want to make this day memorable
and make you
the most happiest woman in the world.
Wei, please open the door.
Jerk!
Who are you? What do you want?
I'm so sorry!
Hello? Wei, where are you?
I...
But...
No, you haven't seen it!
I'm serious.
Hello? Hello?
What kind of paparazzi wrecks my plan?
Ice's always presented himself
in public as single.
My man said
he was meeting
his girlfriend here secretly.
Get a clear shot.
He's just
a livestreaming sales influencer.
Why are you filming him?
God, use your mind!
He claims to be in charge
of the nation's women's wallets.
He makes more money
through live commerce than many stars.
But when does he come?
His agent is not there anymore.
He'll be here soon.
I've seen your spirits.
To be frank,
The Chinese Baijiu is old-fashioned,
which isn't for Ice's soul.
We're not interested.
Hope it'll be successful.
(Gu Yu, looks like the endorsement
isn't going to work out.)
Hey! Still filming?
What are you doing?
Honey,
we'll talk about it at home.
Don't be mad.
We're fine. Let's go home.
What are you talking about?
We'll talk about it at home.
Let go of me!
What happened?
Isn't that our son's classmate,
Lin Xuenong?
Let's go home,
Dad.
Shame on her dad.
(Dandan noodles.)
Let's go home.
We'll talk about it at home.
What are you doing?
(I think my crowd phobia
seems to have acted up again.)
Are you okay?
You did great just now.
But I still need you
to pretend to be my girlfriend.
Name your price.
You think you can
buy everything with money?
Who do you think you are?
If you agree to endorse Xuenong Spirit,
I'll do as you request.