ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
NO CHILDREN OR ANIMALS WERE HARMED
IN THE MAKING OF THIS DRAMA
The truth is, Je-na knew the right answer.
Stop.
From now on, for every wrong answer,
one of you will hit the other's palms.
She simply chose to get hit
rather than hit Je-i.
I can't live like this anymore. I won't!
I told you divorce isn't an option.
You need treatment.
- Je-na.
- Don't treat me like a patient.
Please, let's separate.
What about the kids?
I'll take Je-i.
That won't do.
Je-i is the future of the hospital.
I'll let you have Je-na.
AWARD FOR SURGICAL SKILL
Je-na.
Your foot is bleeding.
Je-i, let's get ready for kindergarten.
Okay.
That little girl bent over backwards
so her parents wouldn't abandon her.
Eat up.
She must've believed
she had to excel
to keep her family together.
Here.
It's the so-called Big Sister Syndrome.
Je-i, wait for me.
Je-i, let's go to school together.
Once Je-na came to the realization
that her sister didn't need her anymore,
she began to pray to God
for something else.
God is our refuge and strength,
an ever-present help in trouble.
Therefore, we will not fear…
She prayed to God
to give her an incurable illness.
She asked for help
to make her parents and sister
feel pity for her.
Je-na.
What is the cause?
There's no specific cause for narcolepsy.
Are you sure it's narcolepsy?
It's hard to be sure.
Let's give her medication
and see if she improves.
Thanks.
You must be busy with your studies,
but you even brought Je-yun.
It'd be a problem
if you collapsed in the street again,
so take Je-yun with you.
I don't want to.
Don't you know how dangerous cataplexy is?
Instead of Je-yun,
you can stay with me, Je-i.
I have to go to the cram school.
Forget it.
Give Je-yun back.
Come on, Je-yun. Let's go.
How are you feeling?
I'm much less drowsy,
and my mind is more clear.
I can feel the improvement.
I'm glad the medication is working.
You must've had a hard time
dealing with unwanted sleep.
I had no idea.
I'd be so disappointed
to see you doze off while studying.
Both as a father and a doctor,
I've failed you, haven't I?
I sincerely apologize.
It's okay, Dad.
You don't have to apologize.
Don't blame yourself.
Now that we know the cause,
you'll be able to study
even better than before.
If you improve your math scores,
I believe you can be
the top student in your year.
You can be on top, too, like Je-i.
Je-na didn't expect this turn of events.
As your father,
I'll give you my full support.
In our last class,
we learned about graphs and values
of exponential functions.
Now, we're going to move them around.
What are some ways to move these figures?
There are shifts and reflections, right?
Now, let's transform this function…
The actual meaning of "full support"
was that he would be keeping
a much closer eye on her.
So, the basics of exponential functions…
CHAEHWA GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
JUNIOR MATH
Je-na,
you can leave early
if you're still not feeling well.
Or do you want to rest
in the nurse's office?
Mr. Woo.
Yes?
This Hankuk University key chain…
Can I have it?
If I have this,
I feel like
I can get a perfect score in math
and be the top student of the school.
HANKUK UNIVERSITY
PRESS ROOM
CHAEHWA GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
JUNIOR KOREAN
JUNIOR
CHAEHWA GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
JUNIOR MATH
Je-na, what are you…
Yu Je-na!
JUNIOR
Please…
You didn't call my dad, did you?
No, not yet.
Are you feeling okay?
What are you going to do?
I'm still thinking.
If you let this slide, then I can live.
If not, I'll just die right here.
- Is that a threat?
- No.
I'm just stating the facts.
I'll wait for your decision.
Let me ask one thing.
Was it your first time doing this?
Yes.
The Je-na that I know
is quite smart, kind, and beautiful.
You're also honorable.
So, can I ask
why you went to such lengths?
Please don't give up on me.
What did you say?
Don't…
Don't give up on me.
Okay.
I'll never give up on you, Je-na.
So, don't--
That was a promise, okay?
Je-na?
Je-i, what are you doing here?
Me? What about you--
So, you know it, too.
That Dad killed Mr. Woo.
What?
That's Mr. Woo's phone, right?
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
Are you kidding me?
Yu Je-na!
Who is that over there?
Are you a Hoegyeong High School student?
What are you doing here?
Hey.
Seul-gi!
Gosh, what do we do?
Oh, dear.
Call 911!
Do it quickly.
This is an announcement.
The festival is now over.
Students, return to your classrooms now.
Parents and other attendees,
proceed to the auditorium
and await further instructions.
Again, this is an announcement.
The festival is now over.
- Stay calm.
- Let us out.
Everyone on school grounds
must follow our instructions.
Students, please remain calm
and return to your classrooms now.
- Wait.
- Please.
What is it?
What happened?
Seul-gi got hurt.
Seul-gi?
How bad is it?
Where is she now?
- Your dad took her--
- Damn it.
Need a hand?
Where the fuck are the bandages?
In here.
Turn on the lights.
Sit down for a second.
Kim Beom-su, get it together.
Answer my questions properly.
Have you been drinking?
Then, are you on drugs?
Contact Beom-su's parents
and tell our legal team to come in.
- Quickly.
- Yes, ma'am.
- We're assessing the situation.
- Don't worry, ma'am.
- It's not our school.
- One moment.
Of course, it's not.
It's not our school.
Stop!
No one answers the phone.
People from Seoul are so damn…
- Oh, hello.
- A student from my school came in, right?
What is their name?
Where's my dad?
Are you just going to stand there?
Do you want to try?
Once you're given the chance
to see how it feels,
your commitment to medical school
will become even stronger.
In the first year of pre-med,
you practice suturing on pig skin.
But it's too thick
and inconsistent in quality.
It's frustrating.
It doesn't feel like your expectations.
Then, in the second year,
you use donated cadavers
and try it for the first time
on real human skin.
When you pull the thread,
the feeling is so smooth and elastic.
That night,
my hands kept tingling,
so I couldn't sleep.
But this friend of yours,
who grew up in an orphanage,
has a skin with thin fat layers.
There's no elasticity.
Malnutrition during your growth phase
can cause this.
But since she's your friend,
I'll take extra care
so it won't leave a scar.
Can you bring me those forceps?
SANITARY PADS
Damn it.
Not just marijuana is banned.
No vapes, either, Gu Chae-ryeong.
Got it?
Ms. Kim, that's digestive medicine.
Don't carry it personally.
Get it from the nurse's office.
Vice President.
Open up all the lockers.
What about the students who aren't here?
Should I break the locks?
Leave them for now.
WOO SEUL-GI, YU JE-I
KIM BEOM-SU
You still have a habit of operating
without the guardian's consent.
Were you only going to call
after something went wrong again?
First, my husband,
and now, my stepdaughter.
And you call yourself a doctor?
I want her transferred.
If you find a hospital to take her
at this late hour, go ahead.
However, since we
just finished stitching her up,
there is a risk of infection.
So, you'll need to sign a waiver first.
Escort Woo Seul-gi to the VIP ward.
CHAEHWA GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
YEAR 2023 JUNIORS
RANK 1: YU JE-I, RANK 2: CHOI GYUNG
RANK 20: KIM BEOM-SU
She is severely ill.
YEAR 2024 SENIORS
RANK 1: WOO SEUL-GI, RANK 1: YU JE-I
RANK 1: WOO SEUL-GI
TEST RESULTS PENDING
J MEDICAL CENTER DIRECTOR, YU TAE-JUN
Hello, Principal.
REPORT CARD
ACADEMIC YEAR 2021, SEMESTER 1
YU JE-NA
RANKING IN MATH
What do we do?
About what?
Where on earth are you?
Did you read my texts?
Things are worse than we thought.
Why the fuss? Did you stab Seul-gi?
No, Beom-su did.
She stabbed Seul-gi while high on drugs.
What if they find out we sold them?
"We"?
I told you not to do any deals in person.
You're the one who went
and sold to Beom-su directly.
What do you mean, "we"?
- Watch your mouth.
- Regardless,
I was just the seller.
You're the one who supplied the drugs.
Think carefully.
The only person
who knows I supplied the pills
is you.
But there are plenty of kids
who got your paper cranes
and bought pills directly from you, right?
Don't worry or get ahead of yourself.
Just do as I say and keep your mouth shut.
This will all be over soon.
There's one more.
Woo Seul-gi.
Didn't you sell directly to Woo Seul-gi?
Can you trust her?
If she talks,
both of us are fucked.
SEUL-GI'S LOCATION: J MEDICAL CENTER
You've never ranked first,
so I knew you weren't the smartest.
But, Choi Gyung, were you this stupid?
Why are you bringing that up now?
Jeez, can you stop?
You saw how the school responded.
They're trying to cover up a stabbing
when the evidence is clear.
The police should know.
Don't breathe a word of this to anyone.
- Mom.
- Under no circumstances
will I let you
jeopardize your college admissions.
Do as I say.
Got it?
Aren't you ashamed
as someone who works in law?
I'm doing this
because I know the law too well.
Get out.
NOTICE OF SEIZURE
VIDEO OF STABBING AT CHAEHWA
Seul-gi!
IS IT YOU IN THE VIDEO?
YOU HAD IT COMING, JU YE-RI
TIP-OFF ABOUT STABBING AT CHAEHWA
Why do you all look down on me?
You always leave me out.
Why do you keep lying to me?
CHAEHWA GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL STABBING
NO CALLER ID
Why do you keep lying to me?
You always leave me out.
Seul-gi!
Why do you keep lying to me?
You always leave me out.
SHE GOT DOXXED
I'D BE TOO SCARED TO GO TO SCHOOL
I WONDER WHO WAS BEHIND IT
NO ONE'S BEHIND IT
SHE HAD SELF-HARM PHOTOS
I BET SOMEONE WAS BEHIND IT
Seul-gi, are you okay?
Isn't it painful?
The sutures were done well.
It'll heal quickly.
It's stuffy in here.
Do you want to go outside
for a bit with Je-yun?
Hey, what is it?
Sometimes, I imagine Je-yun dying.
What?
I'm afraid I'll be too sad
when Je-yun really dies,
so I imagine it in advance
to prepare myself.
Lately, I've been imagining
your death a lot, too.
By the way, have you seen my phone?
What?
Not this one.
Technically, it's my dad's phone.
I lost it.
How did that happen?
I haven't even figured out the PIN yet.
Come to think of it,
you must've known my dad, too.
I never took his class.
But…
I don't think he was a good person.
Why not?
There were rumors
that he slept with students.
No way.
I'll pretend I never heard that.
Why?
Isn't it better this way?
You'd feel even more upset
if he had been a great person.
What?
You're really pathetic.
Not everyone lives like you, Yu Je-i.
REFRIGERATED TRUCK
Are you still alive?
Taking pills and ranking first
with the hospital director's daughter.
Is the hospital treating you well?
The Internet is blowing up with the secret
behind Chaehwa's high success rates.
I have a great business plan.
Do you want to hear it?
As you already know,
I'm in the hospital right now.
That's why I called you in a rush.
Start collecting some painkillers, okay?
Anyway, can't you really get
in touch with Choi Su-jin?
Damn it, where the fuck is she?
Why doesn't anyone know where she is?
Hey, Woo Seul-gi.
Are you listening?
Subtitle translation by: Eunice Kim