ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
NO CHILDREN OR ANIMALS WERE HARMED
IN THE MAKING OF THIS DRAMA
- Good luck on the exam!
- Good luck!
Good luck!
- Good luck.
- Do your best.
- You've got this.
- Good luck.
- Good luck!
- I wish you luck.
- Good luck.
- Je-na.
Hey, Ye-ri.
You know you're our hope, don't you?
You'll ace the CSAT.
We're rooting for you. Good luck.
Oh, thanks.
DON'T THINK OF RETAKING THE CSAT!
Hey.
Dear Je-i.
You've always scared me.
- Good luck, Je-na.
- Good luck.
HANKUK UNIVERSITY
Especially your dark pupils.
MATH
You looked at me mockingly
as if you knew everything.
I thought I'd lose my mind.
This is all your fault, Yu Je-i.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT, YU JE-I
It sucks not to be
as good as your younger sibling.
Nobody would understand.
I simply wanted to beat you
and make Dad love me again.
When Dad found out about me and Mr. Woo,
he praised me.
Very warmly, at that.
It was the kind of compliment
I'd never had before.
I heard you lost a daughter
thirteen years ago.
- Let's stop this.
- Why?
What got into you now?
We agreed to keep looking
for one more year.
Why do you do this?
Why do you want to find my daughter?
If we find her, you might agree
to have a child with me, too.
We won't have a child
whether we find Seul-gi or not.
You should give up.
"Woo Seul-gi"?
MISSING CHILD
NAME: WOO SEUL-GI
DEAR JE-I
YOU'VE ALWAYS SCARED ME…
No, thank you.
I'm not asking for a favor for free.
I'll compensate for it.
I don't need it.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
I'll find your daughter.
And then, father to father,
we can both do our very best.
Je-na knew Mr. Woo had a missing daughter
and used it to her advantage?
SUNDAY, DECEMBER 3, 2023
DEAR JE-I…
I swear I did not tell anyone.
Hello?
IS IT TRUE CHAEHWA HIGH'S KIM SEON-YEONG
IS A QUESTION-SETTER FOR THIS YEAR?
Hello?
Mr. Woo.
Ms. Kim was fired as a CSAT
question-setter for breach of secrecy.
Our omniscient and omnipotent father.
I found your daughter.
WOO SEUL-GI
GYUNGSUN HIGH SCHOOL
99.98 PERCENT MATCH
CONSTRUCTION SITE
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
You don't want this video
to end up in the hands
of the daughter you found
after 13 years, don't you think?
Sir, you must hand in your phone.
POWER OFF
MATH (MATHEMATICS)
CONFERENCE ROOM
LET X EQUALS T
BE A VERTICAL LINE THAT INTERSECTS…
LET X EQUALS T…
1 DAY BEFORE THE CSAT
The plan was simple.
He was to swallow a capsule
with the killer math problem
and sneak out of confinement.
EMERGENCY SERVICES
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Dear Heavenly Father,
ruler of the living and the dead,
we gathered here today to mourn
the life and death of Yu Je-na,
who suffered for a long time
with a brain tumor
before leaving this world to be with you.
We were forged from dust
and will return to dust.
We believe that you gave us life
and that you take it from us…
The whole family's here.
She'll be in the coffin soon.
Our beloved sister Yu Je-na's body
may have disappeared from our sight,
but on the glorious day
you promised us that would come,
we know we will meet again
in a different body
that has overcome death.
Today, we part for a brief while.
It is a short farewell…
Yu Je-i.
You don't think so, either.
- What do you mean?
- This body.
It's not Je-na's.
Look. There's a burn mark.
Did your sister have a scar like this?
Your father
has quite an interesting hobby.
He collects unidentified corpses
and practices his skills on them.
She's from my orphanage.
Choi Su-jin.
No one claimed her body after she died,
so the morgue fees kept piling up.
The local government sends such corpses
to your dad's hospital.
Also, Choi Su-jin
stayed right next door to your sister.
Is that a coincidence?
I get it now.
He's a doctor, and he's family.
There would've been no hitch
pronouncing her dead or identifying her.
Not to mention a letter, too.
It's just perfect.
What are you doing?
Will you turn her into your sister?
Yes.
Then Je-na will no longer exist.
If Dad's plan is to make it
look like she's dead,
won't it be in our favor
to let him to commit more crimes?
If we put a stop to Je-na's funeral,
my dad will just come up with a new plan.
Because he never gives up.
For now, Dad can't know
that we know about this.
Let's get out of here.
Go on your own.
I can't leave like this.
You see,
I read your sister's journal.
How my dad ended up dead.
It was all there.
I have to find evidence.
You'll get caught
before you find anything.
Come with me.
I'll buy you some time. Hurry.
Miss Yu?
Mom doesn't want footage of the VIP guests
remaining on the server
when it's a sad event we'd rather forget.
She told me to turn off
the security cameras
until the coffin gets taken away.
I must confirm with the director--
It's my mom's request, not the director's.
That's why she sent me.
Where were you during the service?
Then where the hell were you
while Je-na got this bad?
Smile.
It's what you're good at.
Oh, no.
Should you rather cry today?
You're a doctor
but couldn't even treat your child?
Who would want to be your patient now?
That's enough.
It's better for the parents
if a weak kid gets out of the way sooner.
You have grown up, Je-i.
I hear you excel in school.
Too bad it happened in your senior year.
You should be using
every available moment to study.
That only applies to students
who cram before exams.
A short break from studying
won't hurt someone like me, Uncle.
My gosh.
You have a child just like yourself.
Thanks for the compliment.
WEDNESDAY, NOVEMBER 15, 2023
DEAR JE-I…
Dear Je-i.
Dad sees everything.
Who is naughty…
and who is nice.
What?
Are you stuck?
Shall I do it for you?
Did you come here to show off?
You have no time to sit and stare.
I don't need your help. Get out.
Get out!
Get out of here!
Get lost!
You should never cry.
Dad doesn't give presents
to a child who cries.
This is a reference to a Christmas carol.
What's the "present"?
Was there something that Je-na wanted?
I'm not sure.
But Je-na was obsessed
with birthdays, Christmas,
and anniversaries, just like Dad.
The day before last year's CSAT,
November 15th.
No, Seul-gi.
Ma'am.
Yu Je-na.
It's women's intuition.
I wanted to ignore it.
THE KEY CHAIN IS MY GUARDIAN, MR. WOO.
FROM JE-NA
But I couldn't.
That girl
kept hovering around us.
I'LL BRING YOUR HUSBAND'S PHONE
All the suspicious incidents
that happened after Do-hyeok died…
At first,
I thought it was the girl's doing.
YU JE-NA IS DEAD
Could it be that Je-na
was trying to tell us something?
Make way, please.
J MEDICAL CENTER
FUNERAL HALL
I am fully aware that they framed you
for stealing drugs to force me to settle.
So, did you settle with them?
No.
When I said I would not,
they asked if it was
because I was a stepmom.
Do you agree with that?
No, you did the right thing.
Where are you going?
Hold onto this, please.
And keep the lawyer here.
- Seul--
- Does she mean me?
Shit, you startled me.
What do you want?
Don't you know everything?
About what?
Don't lie to me.
I know you paid off
Su-jin's rent and unpaid tabs.
What about it?
Aren't you here
because it's Su-jin's funeral?
If no one had done anything,
she would have been kept
in a freezer all alone, unable to rot.
It's nice that she got a send-off
she didn't deserve.
Take it positively.
Do you really think so?
If you're human,
shouldn't you feel some guilt
that she ended up like this?
But then,
if you were human, you wouldn't have
gotten us hooked on meds.
Hey, get out.
You're not doing this
just for Su-jin, either.
This X-ray can't be used as evidence.
Why not? Why is that?
Even if this is
a CSAT math problem, as you claim,
being cut open to remove it
won't simply kill you.
Of course, not informing the family
of the patient's exact condition
can be considered malpractice.
But it's not easy to prove causality
with the cause of death.
And to go further
and say he intended to kill?
That's far-fetched.
He had hundreds of these records.
He killed…
He killed people
while listening to the music.
He could've listened to it
while saving people.
Did you listen to this record?
Yes.
It was a Lucid Fall song.
Je-na was a fan.
That's insane.
It's as she wrote in her journal.
Je-na was called to the operating room.
Since we don't have the security footage
from the operating room,
we need Je-na to take the witness stand.
If we can't do that,
we need something to prove
this is her handwriting.
But now, our only witness isn't with us.
What are these?
I received these after my husband died.
The person who sent them
knew about their relationship
from the start.
Could this person be another witness?
It could be a third person
that was in the OR,
or a CSAT question-setter.
It could be someone at their school.
If they knew something crucial,
wouldn't they have written it down?
There must be a reason
these were sent anonymously.
But even if you find out the sender,
it's never easy to persuade them
to take the stand.
When is the next hearing?
Why do you ask?
I understand you want to have hope,
but as I said before,
it's impossible to prove murder
with this evidence.
Unless you bring someone back
from the dead.
Quit playing detective.
Focus on studying for the CSAT.
If I were a lawyer,
I'd have so many questions for me,
a very important witness.
I guess you don't.
But you've never cared
about such low-value cases.
You pretend to care about your client
- and act like a great lawyer--
- Choi Gyung.
That's how you act around me.
You pretend to be a good mom
and a parent with a conscience.
You're a hypocrite.
Aren't you curious how I found out
about Mr. Woo and Je-na's relationship?
No.
I'm not curious at all.
You wouldn't know,
but I love to masturbate.
I went to school that day to masturbate.
Masturbating in the classroom
the day before an exam relieves stress.
And I happened to see Je-na with Mr. Woo.
I wanted to tell people,
but they would ask me back
why I was at school at that time.
I didn't think I could explain,
so I couldn't tell anyone.
I wished hell upon Je-i.
If only she were to disappear,
I would be ranked first.
I was so annoyed
that I was always in her shadow.
When I saw Je-na at the school festival…
I talked to her.
"I know everything.
If you don't tell the truth,
I will expose you."
But now, she's dead.
I'm scared to death
because I think it's my fault,
but my own mom just bullies me
and tells me to study.
You had nothing to do
with Yu Je-na's death.
The same goes for Mr. Woo's death.
You will never take
the witness stand in court.
So, don't ever repeat what you just said.
Do you understand, Gyung?
That's my advice as your mom and a lawyer.
BUSINESS CLUB
Hello, ma'am.
Can you get me Zolpidin?
Sleeping pills?
I'll see what I can do.
Don't sell to anyone else.
Supply me with everything.
I'll pay you well.
Okay.
Get me some cigarettes.
You can keep the change.
Thank you.
Hello.
Why? What is it?
You and Seul-gi.
You're birds of a feather.
Why would you compare me to her?
I'm way prettier.
I can't stop thinking
I'm losing out on this deal.
You kept all the Consotine from the club.
And you didn't tell me
you saw Je-na at Gangnam Station.
What business partners
have so little trust in each other?
I should do this alone.
I'm more persuasive as a dealer
than a young girl.
Can you also get me stuff like Zolpidin?
If we take over J Medical Center,
we can get more than Zolpidin.
Sit tight and wait.
By the way, what does
a rich, smart kid like Je-i
get from selling pills to kids?
Don't try to understand.
They're wired differently than us.
Why are you dragging me down
to your level by saying "us"?
Ma'am, how much do we owe you?
Can I have some blood sausage?
It'll be 5,000 won altogether.
Thank you.
Anyway, look out.
That man is scarier than you think.
He even killed Seul-gi's dad.
Be sure to keep your side of the deal.
I'll be in touch.
Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim