♪From our first sight
to your fading face♪
♪Fleeting fate,
like a dream we can't embrace♪
♪Who squandered
that heart-fluttering chase?♪
♪Only a silhouette is left♪
♪The ripples of time, interwoven♪
♪Flowing through my palm♪
♪Leaving deep wounds behind♪
♪I gaze out, through mist and rain♪
♪But cannot attain your horizon♪
♪Worldly charm fades in comparison♪
♪To your sweetest words♪
♪Wind on my cheek♪
♪Stirs up tangled thoughts♪
♪I can't let go♪
=Money is Coming=
=Episode 13=
(The one lying here is
the only daughter of Prince Ning,)
(and the benefactor who took an arrow
for the Crown Prince.)
(Last time, she was poisoned
and called His Highness a doll.)
(They must have a close relationship.)
(Luckily,)
(though she's seriously injured,
it was only a scare.)
(If something had happened,
I wouldn't have the face...)
(I wouldn't dare face the Crown Prince.)
What is Her Grace holding?
Could you show it to me?
(This is...)
This is a rare medicinal herb.
Since Her Grace obtained it,
it naturally belongs to her.
But this herb
needs to be processed quickly
to preserve its medicinal properties.
May I take the herb back first
and return it after processing?
Speak.
The arrow from Her Grace's
left chest has been removed.
Fortunately, it was slightly off
and missed the vital area.
Plus, Her Grace's always been healthy,
so her life is not in danger.
Is there anything else wrong with her?
Will there be any aftereffects?
Her Grace might have a fever tonight.
But as long as the fever
subsides by morning,
there will be no major issues.
Just take care of her
during the recovery
and there will be no aftereffects.
Your Highness, please return.
Have the physician
check your injuries as well.
Thank you for saving me today,
Prince Ning.
I shall take my leave for now.
I will visit her again tomorrow.
I noticed
the arrow that hit Her Grace
was not poisoned
but it was coated
with a compound medicine juice.
Medicine juice?
Yes, it is made
by grinding various herbs.
It's harmless to ordinary people,
but it can trigger the toxicity
of "Dream Drunkenness".
The enemy was obviously prepared.
Even if the assassination fails,
as long as you're slightly wounded
by this arrow,
you would succumb to the toxicity
of "Dream Drunkenness"
and meet an untimely death.
Your Highness,
before Princess Yuexi fell unconscious,
she unintentionally pulled
a wildflower by its roots
from the forest floor.
I confirmed multiple times
and discovered
it is the Hidden Face Flower
we've been seeking.
Most importantly,
this is the last ingredient needed
to eliminate the Dream Drunkenness
toxin in you.
However, the remaining toxin
is particularly stubborn.
I have a way,
but I'm missing one herb.
What rare treasure could it be
that even you couldn't find it?
The Hidden Face Flower is not only rare
but also hard to locate.
This herb is not particular
about its growing environment,
but it looks far too ordinary.
When not blooming,
it looks just like roadside weeds.
It can be identified when blooming,
but resembles wildflowers too much.
Most importantly,
the Hidden Face Flower
blooms irregularly.
It must be picked when blooming
to retain its potency.
I see.
I will send people to look out for it.
As for whether it can be found,
as you said,
it depends on fate.
The destined person?
Master,
His Majesty summons you.
Prince Ning, I'm quite curious.
No one else knew about
the Crown Prince's assassination.
How did you come to know about it?
And you brought so many guards
to save him. Could it be
this was a coincidence?
To be honest, Your Majesty,
this was no coincidence
I received Chuxi's signal,
one that's unique to our family.
I thought she was in trouble,
so I brought people to rescue her.
Unexpectedly,
I also saved the Crown Prince.
She shielded the Crown Prince
from an arrow.
Me and the Crown Prince
will always remember her devotion.
Not at all.
The Crown Prince is the heir
and is essential
to the foundation of our nation.
Chuxi simply did what every citizen
of Great Li should do.
Princess Yuexi and you
have made great contributions.
But you're already at the highest rank.
I don't know how to reward you.
I don't need any reward, Your Majesty,
but I wish to ask for a favor for Chuxi.
If Chuxi wakes up
and has any wishes,
she'll request this favor from you.
I grant it.
(A promise from the Emperor
is more practical than any title.)
Greetings, Father.
You're injured.
Spare the formalities.
Thank you, Father.
How is your injury?
Is it serious?
Thank you for your concern, Father.
Thanks to Prince Ning's assistance,
I'm not seriously hurt.
This time, Prince Ning arrived in time
to save your life.
His contribution is immense.
You flatter me.
This assassination attempt
is of great significance.
Are there any clues about the assassin?
The men in black I captured
all committed suicide by poisoning.
No survivors are left.
But...
Speak.
I found this
(Token)
from their leader.
This is the Third Prince's token.
Father, I'm innocent.
Let the Third Prince see it.
(Someone is trying
to kill two birds with one stone.)
Father, this token
does indeed belong to me.
But I've always
respected my elder brother.
I would never commit
such an act of assassination.
Someone must be framing me.
Crown Prince, what do you think?
I believe Xu has been wronged.
The assassin not only tried to kill me,
but also wanted to sow discord
between us brothers
and disrupt the court.
Father, please
investigate this thoroughly.
Your Majesty,
these assassins
carried no information
that could identify them
and all poisoned themselves
upon capture,
yet this token was left behind.
It is indeed suspicious.
I hope you can discern the truth.
The Crown Prince's assassination case
will be jointly investigated by
the Highest Judiciary and the Censorate.
The assassin must be apprehended
to set the record straight.
Thank you, Father.
You may all leave.
The Crown Prince stays.
I take my leave.
Good day, Your Majesty.
Now it's just you and me.
Tell me honestly,
did you do this on your own?
Father, do you not trust me?
Princess Yuexi is still unconscious.
If she didn't risk her life to save me,
I would be the one lying there now.
I have indeed envied Xiao Xu,
but I'd never risk my life to frame him
and implicate Princess Yuexi.
Should I have died in the foreign land
and never returned?
So I wouldn't have stirred up
so much trouble.
Nonsense.
I was just asking casually.
How could I not trust you?
You've suffered from this.
I will uphold justice for you.
Thank you, Father.
I trust you, Father.
But I have one more humble request.
Speak.
Princess Yuexi saved my life,
but she is still in danger.
If anything happens to her,
I wish to marry Princess Yuexi
to repay her kindness.
I beg for your permission.
This matter shall be discussed later.
Yes.
♪Just a glance, and the world♪
♪Becomes no longer bright♪
♪Unknowingly, we're bound♪
♪By a thread of red♪
♪Let's face the world's perils together♪
♪Before petals fall, fall in love again♪
(When I first met her,)
(I felt her presence
brought me calmness.)
♪And the crowds♪
(Her every expression brought me joy.)
♪After all the world's splendor
I've seen♪
(When I was with her,)
(I finally felt at ease)
(like an ordinary person.)
♪Whether forever or just a moment♪
♪What remains is called longing♪
♪Wishing to be by your side,
for eternity♪
♪Let's face the world's perils together♪
♪Before petals fall, fall in love again♪
I've been abandoned my whole life
by my father, my mother,
and the Duke of State.
I have long been used to being
discarded as a pawn.
♪Your face is what I love the most♪
♪All the memories♪
♪Are flashing back♪
♪Whether forever or just a moment♪
♪What remains is called longing♪
(It turns out I can also
not be abandoned.)
(I can be firmly chosen by someone.)
(If I knew getting shot
was this painful,)
(I wouldn't have rushed forward.)
Miss, you're finally awake!
Your fever has subsided.
I'm fine, the Crown Prince...
Great, I'll go inform Mr. Ning now.
Mei.
Her Grace's temperature
is back to normal
and her wounds haven't become inflamed.
She is now out of danger.
As long as she recuperates well,
once the wound heals,
there will be no further issues.
You brat, you've grown bold,
haven't you?
You even shielded others from arrows.
Do you not care about your life anymore?
Old man, I won't dare do it next time.
You dare have a next time?
Do you like Xiao Xingheng so much
that you'd risk your life for him?
(Is it that obvious?)
You've already
shielded him from an arrow
and he's not yet yours.
What?
My daughter isn't like other girls,
who only know to make sacrifices.
If you like him, just go for it
and win him over!
I don't think this is what
we were just talking about.
What are you talking about, old man?
He's the Crown Prince.
Winning over the Crown Prince
sounds somehow terrifying.
What's wrong with the Crown Prince?
You're not worthy of the Crown Prince?
Exactly.
(That actually makes some sense.)
Well,
take good care of your injuries.
Leave this matter for me to handle.
Winning over the Crown Prince is easy,
but convincing His Majesty is not.
I will
have to think this through.
Old man...
Mei,
how's the Crown Prince doing?
After you were attacked,
His Majesty summoned the ministers,
but found...
That's roughly how things went.
The assassins
all committed suicide by poison,
but Prince Ning still
found the Third Prince's token
on one of them.
It seems this assassination
is very complicated.
By the way,
the Crown Prince
bypassed the guards last night
and stayed by your side
the entire night.
I didn't take this arrow in vain.
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)