♪From our first sight
to your fading face♪
♪Fleeting fate,
like a dream we can't embrace♪
♪Who squandered
that heart-fluttering chase?♪
♪Only a silhouette is left♪
♪The ripples of time, interwoven♪
♪Flowing through my palm♪
♪Leaving deep wounds behind♪
♪I gaze out, through mist and rain♪
♪But cannot attain your horizon♪
♪Worldly charm fades in comparison♪
♪To your sweetest words♪
♪Wind on my cheek♪
♪Stirs up tangled thoughts♪
♪I can't let go♪
=Money is Coming=
=Episode 6=
I've sent the eunuch in charge
to report back to Hanzhang Palace
that you happened to see
Princess Yuexi faint,
and placed her in an outer hall
near your residence.
The physician said
it's just a cold and not serious,
so Noble Consort Sun
doesn't need to worry.
Alright.
Hanzhang Palace has been quite restless.
It's time to give them a lesson.
(Dedication and Wisdom)
Miss, do you still remember
what happened yesterday?
Yesterday?
We're taking off!
I want to fly higher.
Shall we sleep?
Yesterday...
It's over, it's over.
I took the drug that a female lead
normally takes.
I'm so embarrassing.
You've remembered now?
Let this world be destroyed.
Let the male and female leads
hurry up and kill me.
It's all Xiao Yue'er's fault.
She gave me
such an embarrassing drug.
Miss, Miss, where are you going?
You're not dressed yet, Miss.
(Dedication and Wisdom)
Old man.
Old man, your daughter's been bullied.
Just say what you're going to do.
Who dares to bully you?
I haven't asked you.
How did you leave standing
but return lying down?
If it weren't for
the guards and the physician
repeatedly assuring
that you only have a cold,
I thought you were going to die.
What cold? The Fourth Princess
gave me something to drink.
And then this happened.
They've gone too far!
Exactly.
But old man, you can't
take a sword
and cut down the Hanzhang Palace.
Be careful, or you'll ruin your health.
Although we can't cut down
the Hanzhang Palace,
I can still manage
to make those two restless.
Good.
Let them be restless.
I have a report to make.
Speak.
The Fourth Princess held
a banquet at Wei Garden
and cost a great deal.
(Emperor Shaoyuan)
And ten days ago,
she took the descendants
of the Sun family on an outing.
For the convenience of enjoyment,
she ignored the desperate pleas
of the farmers
and trampled over more than
50 acres of farmland on a horse.
I also have a matter to report.
Sun Wei, sold offices and titles,
making a profit of ten thousand.
This is the account list I obtained.
He's just a sixth-rank official.
By selling offices
and evaluations of appointments,
he's made ten thousand liang.
This could rival the annual
tax revenue of some small counties.
How bold!
Is Sun Wei
from your Sun family?
(Minister Sun)
He is a distant relative of my family.
Although he is a distant relative,
anyone with eyes can see
these branches of the Sun family
all rely on Noble Consort Sun
and Minister Sun
to secure some positions and titles.
Sun Wei sold offices and titles.
He will be stripped of his office
and exiled to Yaozhou.
Also, those who engage in bribery
will be investigated.
Originally,
the Fourth Princess's matter
wasn't that serious.
Who would have thought that
Sun Wei would be exposed?
Now, His Majesty is troubled by this
and Noble Consort Sun
is also caught in the scandal.
Truly, Heaven has opened its eyes.
It's like a timely rain has fallen.
The Sun family
has been too reckless lately
and annoyed so many people.
Father, you're a man of your word.
Noble Consort Sun
and the Fourth Princess
are going to have a rough time.
By the way,
did you go thank the Crown Prince?
Although the Crown Prince
has no real power,
he is still the heir to the throne.
And he helped you.
The proper etiquette
should be observed.
What help did he give me?
Old man, I didn't do anything.
Why are you so anxious?
The Crown Prince
saw that you were drugged
and kindly took you back.
Yes, yes, yes, I should
definitely thank him for this.
Then what are you waiting for? Go!
Now?
Of course. We always
return the favors immediately.
Hurry up, and come back early.
(Dedication and Wisdom)
You're going like this?
I'm really sorry about last time.
Which matter are you referring to?
(Why he has to bring this up?)
Is it that you held on to me
or that you took advantage of me
under the influence of the drug?
Don't humiliate me like this.
Are you doing this on purpose?
It was the effect of the drug,
you don't need to mind that.
But I still need to thank you
for helping me out.
Your Grace, why don't you
move here?
Isn't that be a bit too obvious?
Going to your residence every day
is like announcing to the world
that we have a relationship.
What relationship?
It's just like
we have underhand secret dealings.
No.
We can have Huailiu drive
the carriage to the back courtyard
then switch to another carriage.
There's a passage
straight to the inner hall.
It won't attract attention.
The inner hall is full of my people,
you need not worry.
It won't be too troublesome, will it?
- Greetings, Your Highness.
These two are chefs
I brought from Jiangnan.
The best chefs in the capital
have all learned from them.
The daily necessities in the inner hall
are definitely more exquisite
than those in the back courtyard.
The back courtyard is just
a temporary resting place, also...
No need to say more, I agree.
It takes more than a few days to heal.
No matter how comfortable
I make it, it's still just a room.
I worry that you might
feel bored staying there.
You're very thoughtful.
I just need some good food and drink.
But does this count as moving in?
Sort of, but not exactly.
We're here anyway.
Your Highness, would you like
to lie down for a while?
Now? Lie down?
Don't worry, treatment is free today.
Is this bed comfortable?
Then let's talk about something serious.
It will be the Longevity Festival
in just a few days.
What? Is there some trouble again?
I got a tip-off
that Xiao Xu has been frequently
corresponding with the post station.
I don't know which envoy
he's in contact with.
No matter which country it is,
we'll know when he pulls this trick.
However, this is confidential.
Why are you telling me this?
I thought we were allies.
That's right.
Don't expect me
to come up with plans for you
or do anything personally.
At most, I'll use my father's power
to give you a little help
in critical moments.
I don't want you to do anything for me.
I'm just sharing
my intelligence with you.
Oh.
Go to sleep now.
I'll have to go home for dinner
in four hours.
The old man is watching me closely.
Everyone, come quickly!
- Let me go.
- Everyone come and judge.
This foreign man has been
attempting improper actions
toward me in broad daylight.
Everyone, come quickly!
Don't leave.
It's him.
He was attempting
improper actions toward me.
Everyone, come quickly!
Let's go see.
Go, go, go.
- Don't leave.
- Let go.
Everyone, come quickly.
Let go, I didn't do it.
Please come and help me.
This foreign man is going too far.
Please help me say something.
You're lying. I didn't touch you.
I went out today to shop.
Who would have thought
this foreign man
would be attracted to me
and tried to do
improper things to me?
You're talking nonsense.
Please, help me.
Why not report this to officials?
I'm not the chief magistrate.
I can't have this man arrested.
He's a foreigner.
The authorities may not
dare to deal with him.
But luckily, I'm fine now.
I just want him to compensate me
with money.
If you're trying to use me as a pawn,
that's unlikely to work.
No, you misunderstand.
I'm not.
Smells so good.
If you don't tell the truth now,
I'll send someone
to the Imperial Office of Music
to check your household registration.
Mei, go to the Imperial Office of Music.
Yes.
No.
He didn't assault me.
I saw he was a foreigner,
so I came up with this idea
to make money.
I won't do it again, please show mercy.
She's falsely accusing you.
Whether to report it to the authorities
is up to you.
I won't argue with such women.
Thank you, sir.
You are kind, thank you.
Let's go.
- What a waste of time.
- Let's go.
Miss, I am He Louche.
Thank you for helping me out.
May I have your name
to go thank you properly in person?
Isn't "He"
a royal surname in Beiqiong?
It was just a small favor,
no need to mention it.
I wonder how you knew
that woman was falsely accusing me.
No decent woman,
after being assaulted,
would instinctively
leave her shoulder exposed
instead of clutching
her clothes tightly,
fearing that others might not notice.
And the perfume she's wearing
is distributed and prepared
by the Imperial Office of Music.
The women in brothels
all use that perfume.
That's impressive.
Then, may I ask
how do you know about this perfume?
Our young lady
has visited all the brothels in Yizhou,
so of course...
I've just smelled it.
But still, thank you.
Although you are reluctant
to tell me your name,
if you ever need
anything from me,
just send someone
to the post station to inform me.
I will do my best.
No need to worry about
such small matters.
See you.
Master.
Master, don't worry.
I won' let such lowly people
to enter Jiqing Workshop again.
From today on,
you will personally escort
Princess Yuexi home.
Don't let her
get off the carriage easily.
Yes.
♪Just a glance, and the world♪
♪Becomes no longer bright♪
♪Unknowingly, we're bound♪
♪By a thread of red♪
♪Let's face the world's perils together♪
♪Before petals fall, fall in love again♪
♪Like the wind entwining with you♪
♪Crossed through the vast lands♪
♪And the crowds♪
♪In this life, deep feelings
can't fit in a short letter♪
♪After all the world's splendor
I've seen♪
♪Your face is what I love the most♪
♪All the memories♪
♪Are flashing back♪
♪Whether forever or just a moment♪
♪What remains is called longing♪
♪Wishing to be by your side,
for eternity♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)