(Year 2017)
(Episode 1)
Goodness.
- Hey. - Oh, hello.
- Hi, Gyu Yeong. - Hello.
Hye Mi.
Oh, hey.
(Asung High School)
First of all, I'd like to apologize to all the parents and students...
who made time to come all the way here.
I'm sure the recent article came to everyone as a shock.
According to the article, our school is full of special favours.
Special favours.
These days, it's called an opportunity.
An opportunity given to someone thanks to his or her parents,
grandparents, or school principals.
And it's true.
Our students are doing well thanks to those opportunities.
That's a fact.
Entrance examinations have a very long history.
(Asung High School)
A long time ago, during the Qing Dynasty,
one scholar consecutively failed to pass the civil service exam.
As he was about to hang himself, he suddenly thought it was unfair.
So he decided to ask Jade Emperor before he died.
"I tried so hard to study for that test."
"But why can't I ever pass?"
"Those who passed are less competent and didn't even try as hard."
"How is it that they pass the test?"
To answer his question, the Jade Emperor called two deities.
(Asung High School)
The deity of endeavour and the deity of fate.
He made the two deities have a drinking battle.
How do you think that ended?
The deity of fate drank seven glasses...
while the deity of endeavour only drank three.
That's the story behind the saying,
"Luck plays a bigger role than skill."
No matter how hard you try, you can't beat luck.
- That's gibberish. - Our students were born with luck,
but people say they're being favoured.
But what would they say if I ask them this?
"If you could choose between working hard and being lucky,"
"which one would you choose?"
We live in a world where luck outperforms hard work.
That's nonsense.
The world is ruled by those who were born lucky.
You're talking garbage.
- My goodness. - What's with her?
I can't believe she came here.
Don't fabricate the story, Ms. Noh.
The deity of endeavour wasn't the one who drank with the deity of fate.
What is she saying?
It was the deity of justice,
which means the true meaning behind the story is this.
"Although people can get lucky,"
"justice still exists."
"Therefore, luck isn't everything."
If the teachers and parents choose to ignore this,
there's nothing I can do about it.
But...
I hope...
the students will at least...
remember what I just said.
I've heard many people say that,
but they're just losers who were born with no luck...
and have no courage to practice justice.
Aren't you supposed to get investigated by the police today?
Goodbye, Ms. Ji.
- Take her outside. - Let's go.
Goodness.
Let's get moving. Come on.
(Asung High School)
Ms. Ji!
Stop him.
I'll prove it.
I will prove it.
Take her.
(Police)
- She was a good teacher. - A good teacher?
Then why did this happen?
Many things in this world do not become a problem...
if they're kept well hidden.
But she failed to keep it hidden.
Ms. Ji, I mean.
- How could you? - You're a teacher?
Say something!
- My gosh. - Aren't you ashamed?
- Gosh. - She won't say a thing.
Seung Yoo's mom?
Her exceptional affection and special feelings for him.
Her overflowing emotions.
That's why this happened.
Ms. Ji Yoon Su.
Did you do it?
Did you do the deed with the student?
Asung High School sophomore.
Baek Seung Yoo.
(4 months ago, Cheongju Station)
(Parking Lot)
Oh, no!
My gosh.
A woman's on the ground!
I'm outside Cheongju Station. It's a hit-and-run.
A guy on a motorcycle just hit a lady and drove off.
The license plate?
(Chungbuk Cheongju CHA2418)
(Vroom Courier)
Did anyone see the plate?
Chungbuk Cheongju CHA2418.
The bike's license plate.
010-891-0276.
There was a phone number on the storage box.
That's not how it's done. Let me try.
Give it to me.
I think this is how to do it.
You're even worse than me.
You can't solve it either.
Don't spin it that way. This has to go here.
- Guys! - Mom's here.
Hurry.
- Do you have everything? - My Rubik's cube!
- Darn it. - You should've packed it.
What happened? Why is it solved?
- Hey. - Hello.
Hi there.
See you.
- Welcome. - What a fuss.
Take care of it. Don't mix it up with theirs.
Sure thing.
Hee Seung.
- Stand up. - What for?
This seat is taken.
By whom?
- Hye Mi. - Hi.
Hye Mi.
Oh, you're Seung Yoo's mom. It's been a while.
It has been, Ye Rin's mom.
- Did she say "Ye Rin's mom"? - What?
You don't seem to know because you haven't been around for a while.
The seats are assigned.
They are? I don't see any name tags.
We don't decide where we sit.
- Then who does? - The kids do.
To be more exact,
where we sit depends on our child's academic ranking.
I think your son put you...
Yes, somewhere over there.
Stay if you want.
If you're not smart, you should at least be quick-witted.
Hye Mi, sit over here.
- Come on. - Okay.
Thank you.
That's your seat.
- What? - Hi.
- Are you there yet? - I'm inside.
Don't hang up. Let me listen.
Okay.
(Husband)
There she is.
She's here.
- Hello. - Hello.
What are you all doing here?
Did the moms get together?
- We're here for lobster. - We're here for lobster.
Ji Na's so pretty.
Everyone.
Moms of Asung High's students...
got together for dinner,
but it just so happens that today...
is the birthday of Ms. Noh, our Director of School Affairs.
Shall we all raise our glasses?
- Yes. - Yes.
Ms. Noh, happy birthday.
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday. - Long live Ms. Noh!
Why don't you say a few words?
First of all, thank you for your well-wishes.
The second semester starts soon,
and as Asung High's Director of School Affairs,
I would like to say something.
Educational policies are continuously changing,
and I know you're concerned.
One sentence on the news and your hearts sink.
"We'll shut down autonomous private schools."
"We'll reduce early admissions."
"We'll standardize high schools."
The government is basically levelling us down.
But levelling down our Asung students...
won't make them ordinary.
Our children are special,
and we'll provide a distinct education accordingly.
Will it be okay to stray too far from the policies?
Of course not.
That's why, starting this semester,
we'll take part in the trial running of...
the government's new policy, the high school credit system.
- The credit system? - Yes.
However, we'll do it the Asung way. The special way.
(Dad)
Math.
To many students, it enlists fear and despair.
But it's the one subject that sets students apart...
in the entrance exam.
Our school will have a distinct...
upper-level math class.
And to teach that class, we hired a very special teacher.
Asung High School will hire...
a skilled teacher, many of whose students...
won Olympiads and other math competitions.
Name, Ji Yoon Su.
She's an Asung graduate.
Class of 2005.
Majored Math Education at Hankuk University.
She taught at Cheongju's Cheongan High School since 2012.
In the past few years, many of her students won Math Olympiads.
What's notable is none of those students...
had any private tutors.
Only by attending their regular math classes,
they prepared for the competitions and won.
Are you sure?
That makes no sense at all.
Kids from specialized schools for the gifted...
or science high schools usually win those things,
and you're saying kids from an ordinary school beat them.
That's right.
The secret is...
this.
I'm leaving now. See you soon.
Okay. Get here safe.
Sorry.
Oh no.
Excuse me.
How old?
- You're six? - Yes.
(Father)
Hello.
Hello, Hardy.
Hardy is giving the question today, right?
That's right. Okay, let's start.
Today, it's a fun question that doesn't require a formula.
A six-year-old girl who lives on Earth...
got on a train leaving from home heading south.
She went 1km and saw a bear and chased it 1km east.
Then she went 1km north...
and ended up at home where she started.
Here's the question.
What colour is the bear that the girl saw?
- The colour of the bear? - That's ridiculous.
She went south, east, then north.
And she went back to where she started?
Read the question carefully and you'll see it.
- I don't see it. - It's too hard.
White.
Correct.
(Correct)
Please hurry!
Sorry.
White? A polar bear?
Why is it a polar bear?
Will 3cut, who got the answer, please explain?
(Will 3cut, who got the answer, please explain?)
Since 3cut isn't responding,
I'll explain.
You need to think outside the box in order to solve this question.
You must wonder what if the land isn't flat?
That was why you specified that she lived on Earth.
Correct.
1km like this, another 1km, and then another 1km.
Since she lives on the North Pole, it was a white polar bear.
(You made math fun.)
(I'm going to be a math teacher just like you.)
(I'll study hard and follow in your footsteps! Hye Jin)
A train is approaching.
We've arrived at Seoul Station.
Please make sure you have your belongings.
That's right.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Hi. I just arrived.
Hi.
You must be tired.
Sorry I couldn't pick you up.
I was swamped with work. I just finished.
It's okay. It's nice taking the train.
- Me too. - What?
It's nice seeing you.
It won't let me hug you.
Let's go.
You didn't forget anything, did you?
No.
Careful. It's dark.
Stay here.
One, two, three.
Ta-Da.
Should I sing that song? Never mind.
So... I put your stuff here and there.
You had a bunch of stuff.
You need to throw out some things.
So, all the furniture is here.
Yes. Mother sent them.
We have a lot to do with just wedding planning.
Okay.
Why? You don't like it?
That's not it.
We have everything already from the start.
What do you mean?
Open the cupboard.
They're completely empty.
We have to fill them ourselves.
Okay. I'll do that.
Working at Asung will help your career.
It'll soon be a specialized school for math and arts.
A specialized school.
That sounds fancy.
- Oh no. - What now?
Did you lose something?
Thank you.
Was it 1729?
He's home.
Seung Yoo.
Where have you been?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I heard you skipped today's counselling session.
Answer me.
Where were you?
Cheongju.
- Cheongju? - Why were you in Cheongju?
It was the death anniversary.
Why did you go there?
Why are you still going there? That was years ago!
Sit here.
Seung Yoo.
Sit down for a minute.
We have something important to talk about.
Have a seat.
Honey, try not to yell.
You've been given an opportunity in eight years.
Let's start over again.
Really?
If anyone calls, can you please give that person my number?
Okay, thank you.
Did anyone leave it at the lost-and-found?
No, no one has called.
Gosh, I figured you might forget something.
Why do you always lose things so easily?
My laptop and teaching materials are all in that bag.
What am I going to do?
Why are you going through that?
I just want to see what's inside.
These photos are all so lame.
(21HO 1023)
(76SEO 2047)
- Wait. - What?
(30REO 8191)
These are Mersenne primes.
- What prime? - A Mersenne prime.
It's is a prime number that's one less than a power of two.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I have mathematics anxiety, so I'll be off now.
Is this person a mathematician?
Thank you.
I got your number...
from the lost-and-found center at Seoul Station.
Hello.
We took each other's bags, right?
Yes. When should we meet and exchange the bags?
I'm sorry.
I feel like I ended up causing you trouble.
Are you free tomorrow afternoon?
(That works...)
What time?
I bet you think I'm old-fashioned.
It's a hobby I picked up...
from my father, the chairman of Asung.
Drink up.
Thank you.
Will you be...
teaching calculus at our school as well?
I plan to.
I'd like you to teach these kids.
(Student Record)
They're the top students in our school.
I'd like to test them first.
Oh, you mean a placement test?
Of course. Go ahead. You should pick the best ones.
I'm sure you know...
that we're preparing to become a specialized high school.
I bet you also have high hopes for our students.
These days, convergence is a trend in education.
We wish to be creative with our education...
by integrating math with liberal arts, art, and so on.
Doesn't that also coincide with your curriculum?
It sounds like something I'd be interested in,
but it's far from the reality of the education in Korea.
We can't let kids continue to give up on studying math.
We have high expectations for you and the change...
you will be bringing to our school.
Thank you for the drink.
I'll be off now.
Why aren't you replying to my text?
I'm sorry. I just checked.
How does 5pm sound? Where do you live?
Hangok-dong.
Hangok-dong?
I live there too.
Then let's meet in front of Hangok Art Hall...
at 5pm.
Okay.
(Name: 1729)
(Name: Eco-bag)
(Eco-bag)
(Club membership application form)
I can't believe a math club is becoming a threat...
to our dance club.
But then again, I've enjoyed enough time dancing.
Then maybe it's time that I let the juniors...
have some fun on their own.
Okay.
- What do you say? - No.
I'm not going to waste my time solving math questions.
I'm going to stay in the dance club.
Join me.
(Club membership application form, Baek Seung Yoo)
(Calculus)
Hand in the forms once you're done.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Hey, watch it.
(Baek Seung Yoo)
(Calculus)
(Sung Ye Rin)
(2017 Math Club Test Question)
Here's the test question for the math club.
Help me solve it later during our private tutoring class.
Ye Rin.
- Hello. - Goodness, Ye Rin.
You not only study hard, but you're also the school president.
- It must be exhausting. - No, I'm fine.
By the way, you're not taking my class this semester.
Okay, go on.
All the smart kids are leaving me.
I'm only left with halfwits.
I couldn't take Advanced Math this semester,
so the least I can do is join the club.
Get lost.
If X, Y, Z are real numbers, prove that sides AB, BC, and CA...
are perpendicular to each other when the three spatial vectors, ABC,
satisfy that the absolute value of XA plus YB plus ZC is...
greater than or equal to the sum of absolute value XA...
and absolute value YB.
(Lee Hyun Jae)
- What does this even mean? - Did you join a rap club?
- That verse was amazing. - It's calculus.
Stop talking about calculus. It's making me sick.
You can't even play soccer.
What is all that?
- Is this math? - Look.
- Hello. - Hello.
What's this, ma'am?
I wonder what these pictures mean.
What do they have to do with math?
Let's find out.
I'm Ji Yoon Su. It's nice to meet you.
And thank you...
for applying to take scary-sounding Advanced Math.
I solved all the math club problems. Can I submit it now?
Already?
Is he for real?
- What? - That's crazy.
- What is he? - I don't know.
(This problem is to select students for the math club "Calculus".)
Shall we begin?
- Yes. - Yes.
Turn to page six.
- Okay. - Okay.
You know of the convergence or divergence of numbers, right?
- What is that? - Yes.
Vector A and C, vector B and C, that makes zero.
The inner product of vector A and B is also zero.
So vector ABC is perpendicular.
That's the solution.
Did you get that?
- Yes. - Good.
Ask if you have any questions.
I will.
Don't mind them. They do it all the time.
You asked the School Operation Committee...
to set up an advanced math class?
Yes.
Why?
You know Ye Rin's poor at math.
It's to make sure Ye Rin's portfolio...
includes a presidential citation.
What? Say what? The President?
What do you mean? A presidential citation?
What are you on about?
Help me with this.
Okay.
Talk to me.
What's that about a presidential citation?
You just wait.
I'm an assemblyman...
and I'll make sure our daughter's portfolio...
includes a presidential citation.
A presidential citation?
(Aide Kim)
No, leave it.
What is it?
You're there?
I'll come right over.
Bye.
How's the Math Olympics coming along?
We're positive about opening it up to middle and high school students.
Co-hosted by the Math Society and Ministry of Education.
How do you like the new math teacher?
Do you think she'll cooperate?
I'm not sure but I doubt it.
Why?
You named her,
saying you needed her.
Get the competition lined up.
I'll take care of the next step.
Good shot.
(Math)
You all worked hard on the selection problem.
But...
none of you got it right.
I got it wrong too? That's impossible.
Not just you in Advanced Math,
but no sophomore got it right.
So I'm going to give you another chance.
You have until 8:30am tomorrow to submit your second attempt.
Any questions?
Could you give us a hint?
A hint?
Through any given point not on a line,
there passes exactly one line parallel to that line.
That is Euclid's parallel postulate.
For over 2,000 years, no mathematician doubted it.
But in the 19th century, a young man had a thought.
"Is this self-explanatory"?
The young man's father dissuaded his son from his fixation,
but he said this.
"Dad. I am starting from nothing..."
"to create a completely different world."
That young man was Janos Bolyai.
That's how non-Euclidean geometry was born.
(Geometry of space where Euclid's parallel postulate is invalid.)
Go back to square one...
and think about and with all available options.
That's the hint.
Shall we begin?
- Hey, look. - What's this?
- Take a look. - What is it?
It says it's valid.
- What? - What is this?
Ye Rin, look.
- Ms. Ji. - Yes?
Look at this.
Who left this here?
It wasn't me.
Me neither.
Hey. You were the first to leave the classroom.
It wasn't me. It was on the board when I left.
It's true.
Then who's pranking us?
(False premise. This margin is too narrow to contain the proof.)
It's not a prank.
Then is this...
Yes. This is the correct answer.
- What? - What?
The answer is "false premise"?
- Yes. - But I solved it.
If you solved it,
you misunderstood the premise.
Do you remember the hint I gave you?
Who did this?
Was it really none of you?
I think so.
No one saw who wrote this?
- No. - I didn't.
I don't know.
(Math)
What's going on?
- Hello. - Hello.
Sir, is this the correct answer?
What is it?
(False premise. This margin is too narrow to contain the proof.)
We don't have any footage of it.
Oh, I see.
Take a seat.
So... What's written here.
Is this the right answer?
Yes, it is.
The answer is "false premise"?
You fooled with the kids.
I fooled with them?
You twisted it because you didn't want to give an obvious question.
You don't know because you're new here,
but our kids are serious and naive.
Why would you pull a prank on them?
Is this even funny?
Or does this help their studies?
I will leave now.
You two can talk.
Try again.
This doesn't suit our school.
What exactly does that mean?
Saying the premise is false...
is denying the problem altogether.
Asung students won't give such an answer.
The students are already good at providing the correct answer.
I'd like to expose them to incorrect premises,
and problems that have no solution.
The fact that there are propositions that cannot be proven.
Do our students...
have to know that?
- Pardon? - Asung kids don't need to know,
and have no time for that.
Why that is...
You will soon find out.
Don't you want to know who got the right answer?
How do you know this was their answer?
They may have written it as a bluff.
- A bluff? - Think about it.
There's nothing there about what the error is.
Thank you.
I think I can find this student now.
Seung Yoo.
Was it you?
That question. The flawed premise. Was that you?
It was, wasn't it?
Why did you sign up for math club?
I don't know what you mean.
What about this?
You don't know about this either?
I think it was written for you.
(The person most likely is bluffing like Fermat...)
I'm bluffing?
What does this mean?
This is called...
Fermat's Last Theorem.
Fermat provided a theorem...
without proving it.
He left a famous note saying he'll skip demonstration
because this margin is too narrow to contain proof.
When the solution was finally found 350 years later,
most people said they believed Fermat did not, in fact,
know how to prove it.
(False premise. This margin is too narrow to contain the proof.)
Fermat's theorem was finally proved utilizing all of 20th century math.
Most say Fermat, a 17th-century mathematician, couldn't prove it.
Moreover, by citing Fermat,
the person most likely is bluffing like Fermat...
without knowing what the error in the problem is.
(Grand Prize Baek Min Jae, National Mathematics Association)
(International Grade School Mathematics Competition)
(Award of Excellence, Baek Min Jae)
(However)
- Have a nice day. - Have a nice day.
Have a nice day.
(Error)
Was it you?
You did great.
Yes. This is correct.
(Sung Ye Rin)
Your name is Ye Rin. Sung Ye Rin.
Why didn't you say it earlier that it was you?
Well...
I didn't think I should.
I didn't think I should say there was an error...
in the problem that you gave.
Sure, that's understandable.
But from now on, you can write answers like this freely.
I welcome it.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll go then.
I'm almost at Hangok Art Hall.
That's right.
You're wearing 1729 again.
It was a cap last time and today...
(Hangok Art Hall)
The smallest number which can be expressed...
as the sum of two different cubes in two different ways.
That was what Ramanujan said...
to Hardy when he said 1729 was an ordinary number.
(Hardy and Ramanujan: mathematicians)
If you look at numbers like that,
no number in the world is meaningless. Right?
Here you go.
I looked through the pictures in the camera...
to find a way to return it to you.
There were many fun pictures.
Do you like math?
No.
Thank you.
Did you see the badge that was here?
- It was this big. - No, I didn't.
I see.
Okay, then.
I must say, it's beautiful.
- Hello? - It rained earlier.
Did you get home okay?
What? Oh, yes.
Did you get your bag back?
Yes, we exchanged our bags.
- By the way... - Yes?
I think there's a Srinivasa Ramanujan in our school.
- Who? - You have arrived.
Yoon Su, I'm sorry. I've arrived at my destination.
I'll call you after I'm done.
Thanks to you, the Ministry of Education will be taking part...
in organizing the International Math Olympics in Korea.
The contest between middle school and high school students...
will be the main event of the Math Olympics.
Asung High School would've received a budget for being a model school...
for the high school credit system.
Well...
I thought Asung High School got picked...
because it passed the screening.
Am I wrong?
Pardon? Oh, right. Of course.
I work in the field of education,
so I don't want to do anything to embarrass myself.
Although this applies to everything else,
I really do try my best to be fair and transparent...
when it comes to my child's education.
You really are...
just like your late father.
He was known to be an extremely upright...
and righteous president.
He's here.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry for being late, Vice-minister and Assemblyman Sung.
(Error)
Sweetheart.
Have a snack.
I want a different math tutor.
What? Why?
She's not that good.
Really?
Goodness. Okay, I'll find you a new tutor.
By the way...
Gosh, your dad told me not to tell you anything.
You might get a presidential citation.
You know the Math World Cup?
The event that's taking place next month.
It's not the world cup. It's the Math Olympics.
Whatever. Same thing.
A presidential citation for what?
Did you ask for me?
Was it you?
Pardon?
Were you the one who wrote the answer...
for the math test?
Was it you?
Well...
It needs to be you.
Ms. Ji, the new math teacher,
is nothing like Mr. Han Myung Jin.
She won't give you special treatment...
or accommodate your needs.
So if you want to win her favour,
you need to do well.
I'll do my best.
Ye Rin.
You're pretty and smart.
But why do you always lack so much confidence?
Keep your chin up and look confident.
You don't want people to notice...
that you're not as good as they think you are.
You may go.
What do you want?
You managed to make a fool of everyone.
You told me...
that things will never go back to how they were.
Tell me. What are you thinking?
What's the fuss about?
Don't you get it?
I'm asking if I need to compete with you.
No.
Then why did you do it?
Why did you solve the question?
I don't know.
What?
Tell me.
How you solved the question.
Please.
(2017 Math Club Test Question)
What happened at MIT?
Your mind went blank after you came back to Korea.
Why did you pretend like you couldn't solve any questions?
What is it that you want to know? How to solve this question?
Or my story?
It must've been fun...
watching us compete with each other like crazy...
over math questions that you found extremely easy.
Did that make you feel superior?
How did you end up like this?
Don't you remember?
When I was young,
my parents always scolded me for not being better than you.
I always tried so hard to catch up to you,
but you were always ahead of me.
You have no idea how many times I wanted to give up.
Are you saying that's my fault?
Yes, it's your fault.
It's not that I wasn't good.
You were just extraordinary.
You're special.
You really are special.
You can't just leave.
Seung Yoo!
- Hi. - Hello.
First, let me talk to you about the math club.
As you all know,
we already got an answer for the first question.
"False premise."
I know you're not used to solving math questions...
with no definite answer.
But that's what makes it so similar to our lives.
We live in a world full of errors...
along with incomprehensible and insoluble questions.
Is the next question going to be something similar?
I haven't decided yet.
By the way, the person who solved the question is in this class.
- What? - What?
- Really? - Who is it?
- Who solved it? - Who was it?
Ye Rin.
Can you explain to your friends...
why that problem had an incorrect premise?
- My gosh. - Nice, Ye Rin.
- You're amazing. - Ye Rin.
- Great job. - Go on, Ye Rin.
- Unbelievable. - You're so smart.
Ye Rin.
You don't remember.
No.
I apologize. Having to solve it suddenly...
Take your seat.
I will explain it for you.
(Math)
What happened?
Ye Rin.
"You did great."
No one...
ever said that to me.
"Your answer is wrong" is what I heard the most...
since I started learning math.
I'm sorry I lied.
Then who are you?
Hey!
Okay. Eyes!
Double beat.
One.
Ms. Ji, right?
Ms. Ji.
- Hello. - Hello.
- We are Project... - D.
You appeared in our video,
so now you're a Project D member.
Congratulations.
Would you like to see the video?
Dance is more about feel than technique.
Feel. Please watch our expressions.
Okay.
Nice look.
We're preparing for a competition.
- We're always practicing. - Here's another one.
Oh, wait.
How long have you been filming?
- What do you do for free period? - Why?
I don't want our portfolios to overlap.
I'm not in Math Camp Prep.
Don't worry.
That solution. It wasn't you, was it?
You're hardly that good.
Who is it, then?
Press, up, press, up.
Press, up.
- You're really into this. - Do I look cool?
It's 1729 again.
Do you like math?
Ms. Ji, fill in a membership form.
Go way down and stretch.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Baek Seung Yoo)
Baek Seung Yoo.
I found you.
(False premise. This margin is too narrow to contain the proof.)
(Melancholia)
Baek Seung Yoo?
Can I see his file for the previous semester?
Still, you have to do well.
Or I will give up on you.
The International Olympic of Mathematicians...
will host a competition for middle and high school kids.
They spent the night together. Ms. Ji Yoon Su and that student.
No. I won't do it!
Fill this cabinet!
You can't do anything you want until this is full.
I know it and so do you.
The moment you don't feel anything.