(All characters, places, institutions, incidents,)
(and organizations portrayed in this drama are fictitious.)
Ji Na.
Mom.
The thing is...
Tell me exactly what happened.
Don't leave out a single thing.
(Art Room)
There are no security cameras in the art room.
Here are the footages from the security cameras nearby.
We'll give you a call after we take a look.
Okay.
Ms. Kim.
Mr. Paik.
- Did they find anything? - No.
The police just took the security footage.
How is Si An?
Did the surgery go well?
They're not done yet.
By any chance, did you happen to see her cell phone?
No, I haven't.
Her cell phone wasn't in the art room.
Why is her surgery taking so long?
I'm so worried.
This is driving me nuts.
What's wrong? Do you know something?
If you're suspicious of anything, I'd like to know.
Please.
(Episode 15)
Mom.
What if she dies?
What will happen to me then?
Shut your mouth.
Don't say a word.
Stop ruining my life.
From this moment on,
I won't forgive anyone who gets in my way.
Even if that's you.
Do you understand?
I'm off to a curriculum meeting.
I was on my way to a curriculum meeting.
Ji Na, where are you going?
I don't know how to explain this.
Why? What happened?
I'm going to teach Si An a lesson.
She's dead meat.
- Are you sure? - What are we going to do?
I don't know what to do.
Just because she said that doesn't necessarily mean...
that she was the one who hurt Si An.
So I didn't say anything to the police.
It felt like tattling.
I also got a little scared.
Thank you for telling me, at least.
Did you see Ji Na after that?
I actually looked for her,
but she was nowhere to be seen after the incident.
Okay. I'll call you later.
Did you look into the security footage from Asung Academy?
Yes, I did. Take a seat.
Hello?
Yes.
They finished the surgery and took her to the ICU.
Is she still unconscious?
Don't get shocked by what I'm about to say.
Go ahead. What is it?
I just saw the security footage.
I'm going to meet Principal Noh.
Si An's accident.
I need to check if Kim Ji Na's involved.
- Kim Ji Na? - Yes.
Ms. Kim Jin Hui told me something.
I'll go with you.
I need to see her. As Si An's guardian.
Passcode.
You have unlocked the safe. The door is open.
The door is closed.
Attorney Jang, are you on your way?
Please hurry up. Okay.
Bring me the files regarding Si An's accident,
the updates on the police investigation,
and all the footage from the school security cameras.
Attorney Jang, is that you?
Si An's guardian is here to see you.
Why are you here?
To ask for your cooperation with the investigation.
Where is Kim Ji Na right now?
- Why do you ask? - It's possible that...
she was Si An's attacker.
"Attacker"? What proof do you have?
How about you watch the security footage first?
This shows Kim Ji Na...
rushing from the art room direction right after the accident.
So what? Is this it?
This was from the camera closest to the art room...
right before the first witness discovered the scene.
How does this say my daughter was the attacker?
Someone heard what she said.
I will end Choi Si An.
I will kill her today.
Based on just that,
you say my daughter hurt Si An?
I would like to talk to her.
I want to hear...
what led her to say something like that.
You're here at last, Attorney Jang.
You called an attorney already.
Whenever there's an unfortunate incident,
as the principal,
isn't it natural for me to bring in a legal representative?
He's with the police.
She is Choi Si An's guardian,
and she's naming my daughter Ji Na as the attacker...
and demands to see her right away.
Without any clear proof, you identified a suspect?
We will not cooperate with such an investigation.
Follow the proper protocol.
We haven't concluded she's a suspect.
We'll send a request for an interview.
Please let her cooperate as a witness for now.
Very well.
Hello?
Are you Choi Si An's guardian?
- Yes, I am. - Can you come right now?
What? Right now?
I'll be there.
- Was that the hospital? - Yes. I need to go.
Let's go, then.
I'll come by tomorrow for your daughter's statement.
Please let me see Ji Na then.
I will.
You should pray Si An recovers.
You'd better pray even harder than we do.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
I told you...
the truth as it is.
In this kind of situation, what will happen to Ji Na?
She must insist it wasn't intentional.
If she says they fought and the plaster figure...
just happened to fall,
we can argue it was negligence resulting in an injury.
The issue will be the victim's condition.
What if it's bad?
In the worst-case scenario, what if she ends up dying?
It will be manslaughter.
Ji Na could be arrested.
Why not try to...
settle with the victim for ethical reasons?
The victim only has a guardian, not even a real parent.
Settle with them?
Do you think I can settle with the likes of...
Ji Yoon Su and Paik Seung Yoo?
They will use this incident to corner me.
They will never settle.
Not to mention that today,
I was made chairman of the Asung Foundation.
I will soon take it over from my father.
After all I did to get here...
I waited so long for this day.
We just have to hide this.
We can hide this.
Nothing will go wrong.
There will be no problems.
We thought she was waking up,
but then things turned worse.
How long must we just watch and wait for?
It's taking longer than I thought.
She could bleed into her brain again,
so we're watching her closely for now.
- Please do your best, doctor. - Sure.
Si An.
Do you hear me?
Stay strong. I hope you wake up and get to see me tomorrow.
Okay?
(Choi Si An: Let's talk.)
(Delete message)
(Select message)
(4 messages selected)
(Deleted)
Choi Si An.
Is it true you said you'd kill her yourself?
I didn't mean it literally. I was just angry...
Stop!
I don't care what you actually meant.
Tomorrow, to the police,
you will say you never said such a thing, okay?
Si An.
She won't die, will she?
You're worrying about her right now?
No one knows what she'll say if she wakes up.
What you did, what she knows.
She might spill everything.
What do you mean what I did?
I told you, Mom.
I really didn't do any...
I don't believe you.
You never got along with her.
I wouldn't find it strange if you did do something to her.
You're more than capable of it.
Don't make that face and listen to me.
You must never tell the police about...
the Global Talent Class or the special textbook.
Ji Yoon Su and Paik Seung Yoo...
don't seem to know about the textbook yet.
So don't mess up.
If you do, I will make you pay!
What? Are you afraid?
- This is nothing. - Mom.
Ji Na.
Why do you make me so angry?
I end up praying before I know it.
Are you really not going home?
You should take a nap.
I won't be able to sleep even if I go home.
Then...
The shower for families is over there,
so you should go if you want to wash up.
Drink this while it's still warm.
Thanks.
I'll go to the police station tomorrow...
and find out what time Ji Na is being interrogated.
Once she's done, I'll find out what she said...
and if there are any additional witnesses.
I plan to go to the school and talk to some of the kids too.
There may be more kids that know about the textbook.
I'll look for a way to see Ji Na.
You should rethink that.
Principal Noh won't let that happen so easily.
Ji Na may be afraid as well right now.
She may be too afraid to talk,
and even if she wants to,
she may not know to whom she can talk.
We'll find that out.
Once Si An wakes up,
let us find out everything...
that we wanted to know.
Okay. Let's do that.
- It's Assemblyman Sung Min Jun! - What?
Please tell us how you feel.
Did you really not know about this matter?
Yu Hye Mi, you admitted the charges right away. Why was that?
- Assemblyman Sung! - Is it true?
The first trial of Yu Hye Mi, who was arrested...
for the Asung High answer sheet leak...
is being held today at Seoul Central District Court.
We apologize...
for disappointing and causing concern...
to the people.
Whereas I knew nothing about my wife's deeds,
I sincerely apologize...
to the countless students and parents of students...
for causing them to feel a sense of deprivation and anger.
Whatever the result may be,
we will humbly accept the decision of the court.
Yu Hye Mi, do you have anything to say?
Please say something.
I've made a mistake a public figure must never make.
I'm a mom as well,
so I became greedy regarding my child's education...
and momentarily lacked discernment. I'm sorry.
They're discussing canceling your daughter's college admission.
Do you have anything to say regarding that?
I'm sorry, Ye Rin.
I've ruined your life.
(Yu Hye Mi's tearful remorse)
I'm so sorry.
Will your admission really be canceled?
Just go to school.
Ye Rin. At school yesterday...
Never mind.
(Assemblyman Sung Min Jun and wife, Yu Hye Mi, at the courthouse)
I'm sorry about your mother.
But your mother is more than willing to sacrifice herself for you.
You need to be protected.
Really? She's still unconscious?
Okay.
Look over Ji Na's statement...
before she goes in for her interrogation.
Thank you.
Tell Ji Na to come out.
She's not in her room. She must be washing up.
Tell her to hurry up.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am. Ji Na isn't home.
She's not?
Ji Na.
The person you have reached...
(Ji Na)
She's not coming today?
Kim Ji Na's mother just called.
She's sick.
Is there no way to question her?
It's most likely an excuse,
but we can't force her.
(Seoul Hangok Police Station)
It's me.
Really? Okay.
I stopped by at home to pick up some things.
I'll call you back.
(Please enter your password.)
(Accessing folder)
(Applicant's Profile, Kim Ji Na)
(Special talents: Tennis, cheerleading, composing)
Yoo Chan.
Aren't you going to school?
Where did he go?
(Mr. Paik Seung Yoo)
Hello? Seung Yoo?
Ji Na!
What are you doing?
Is Ji Na here?
Why would she come here this early in the morning?
- Is something wrong? - Is that what you want?
What's your problem?
Hey, you. Listen carefully.
What you want will never happen.
What's going on?
What do you want to ask?
I heard about the accident,
but he doesn't know anything.
Yoo Chan.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask.
How is...
Si An doing?
Thanks for asking.
Si An is still unconscious.
We're still waiting.
Have you seen this before?
No.
Si An said the Global Talent Class kids had it.
I know nothing about it. I mean it.
Did Ji Na tell you anything...
after the incident yesterday?
Yoo Chan.
Tell me anything you know.
I don't know anything.
Pick up, Ji Na.
- Pick up! - The person you have reached...
(Principal Noh Jung Ah)
If the Global Talent Class kids had it,
did Asung Academy make it?
I don't know.
Only that Si An was hurt because of it.
Because of this?
I think the person who either made this...
or had it was caught by Si An,
which was why that happened to her.
That's my guess.
Thanks for bringing Yoo Chan.
Are you going to dig into what Yoo Chan did wrong as well?
Do you think this was Yoo Chan's doing?
Even if we uncover what problems exist with the Global Talent Class,
Yoo Chan may still be a victim.
You were too, before.
You were led down the fast lane by the adults without knowing it.
These are the expected questions. Memorize everything.
According to Mr. Han,
the math test is going to be really hard this time.
Memorize everything, okay?
How did you end up doing volunteer work for IAIT?
Are you sure you prepared for the Olympics at school?
Seung Yoo.
Can you send me that photo of the textbook?
It's true that there was an unfortunate incident yesterday.
The police may ask the children to give statements.
- What? - Ji Hye gets scared easily.
We got a call already.
They said Jenny was caught on the security video.
Don't worry.
Don't agree to anything on your own no matter what the police request.
Please proceed only after consulting...
our foundation's lawyer.
Then everything will be fine.
- Okay. - Also...
We will put a hold on the consulting for the Global Talent Class.
You brought the textbooks, right?
- Yes. - Yes, of course.
(Oh Ji Hye)
(Ahn Jenny, Kyung Soo Young)
You're here.
- How is Si An? - Nothing's changed.
By the way, her friend came by just now.
- Her friend? - Yes.
Ji Na!
- Are you okay? - Ji Na.
Are you guys okay? Did you get hurt?
Ji Na, it's okay.
I know you came because you were worried about Si An.
Si An is fine.
She's going to be okay. You're both going to be okay.
Passcode.
The door is open.
The door is closed.
The phone is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail after the beep.
Please press the hash key to save your voicemail.
Ji Na.
This is your last warning.
Call me right now...
if you don't want both of us to die.
If you don't want to see me dead, call me right this instant!
Could she be...
thinking of hurting herself?
Or could she have gone to the police station?
Has she lost her mind?
Ji Na!
Where were you?
What are you doing?
Did you eat?
Your mom doesn't know you're here, does she?
No, she doesn't. Are you going to tell her?
If you don't want me to, I won't. Don't worry.
There's something I need to show you.
This file contains information about you.
Me?
There's that video clip of you...
at the meditation center and student profile.
I also have personal records about you.
Why do you have these?
I once wanted to use you to get back at your mother...
for how much she hurt me.
(Trash)
(Empty trash)
I feel embarrassed by this, and I'm also sorry.
I showed you everything and deleted the file.
Now, will you do the same for me?
Will you tell me what really happened?
Ji Na.
I was extremely surprised when I saw you earlier.
I had no idea you'd show up here.
You're very brave. I mean it.
Also, do you remember when I told you...
that if anything confused you, or if you had any questions,
you could feel free to open up to me?
- Yes, I remember. - I think now is that time.
He's right, Ji Na.
Muster up your courage a little bit more. Please.
Are you going to believe what I say...
no matter what I tell you?
Yes.
I heard there was an accident at school.
Yes, there was.
A disgraceful accident at that.
I can't believe the police came to my school...
and tried to investigate my daughter.
What did you do this time?
You're making kids get investigated as well?
Why is it that you kids don't know how to be grateful?
You're willing to take what I give when things are to your advantage,
but when things get tough, you're quick to blame it on me.
You know what this is, don't you?
What book is this?
Where did you get that?
Give me...
Give me that! Give it to me!
We need to hide it to keep things quiet!
Give it to me! Hey!
I didn't...
drop the plaster figure on her.
Okay.
Slowly tell us what happened.
You haven't made any textbooks for the clinic recently, have you?
No, I haven't. What's this?
It's a lot like what you made, isn't it?
I think it was made at your clinic.
The Global Talent Class kids had it.
And?
I think there's a problem with the textbook.
- What problem? - Choi Si An!
I'll call you back.
What is this?
- Why did you take a photo of this? - Be honest with me.
Where did you get that book?
The questions in that book were the same as the ones on the test.
Give it to me.
You, Yoo Chan, Jenny, and Soo Young.
Everyone in the Global Talent Class got a high score on the math test.
They had that book too, didn't they?
You know it's wrong.
You also know that it's a shameful thing to do.
I know you're scared.
But tell me what happened.
Okay, fine.
I'll explain everything. But first, delete that photo.
I'll tell you if you delete it.
No. This is evidence.
"Evidence"?
I'm going to tell Mr. Paik and Ms. Ji about this.
I'm going to report this to the Office of Education...
and the press.
What? You're going to report this?
Give that to me.
Give it to me.
Give me that.
- Stop it. - Give that to me.
Give it to me. Give me that.
I said, no.
Give me that.
Stop it.
- Give it to me. - No.
Get off me!
[VIU Ver] tvN E15 'Melancholia'
"Ji Na’s Guilt"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Si An.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I didn't know she'd end up getting hurt like that.
I swear.
Okay.
So it was an accident.
Do you...
believe me?
I do.
Do you really?
There's no reason you'd come here just to lie.
My mom...
didn't believe me.
I put so much work into this.
The poor thing.
You made it grow into the size, shape,
and direction you wanted,
but look at it now.
It shattered in an instant.
That's how weak they are.
Everything that you grow.
You ungrateful brat.
How dare you do this to me?
I'm warning you.
Don't think of ruining my brother.
It's already too late.
Don't you get it?
He can't stop now.
If he were to stop,
he wouldn't have come this far, don't you think?
You want to think it's too late.
I worked so hard on this plant.
There's a lot to turn back.
- It'll be hard work. - How ungrateful.
How can the darn things do this to me?
I once thought it wasn't your fault.
That it was on the adults who made you this way.
But you need to stop blaming others and take a look at yourself.
We can fix this.
If you decide to step up, I'll help you.
It's okay. Come and say hello.
Si An. Ji Na's here to see you.
She's worried about you.
Can I...
hold her hand?
Yes.
Si An.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I did.
Will you wake up?
Everything I grew is weak?
Don't be silly.
They'll come back, won't they?
When they realize that no place in the world...
can protect them as well as Asung did.
Where do they think they can go?
They're in the palm of my hand.
The punks.
Hello?
Ji Na, what happened to you?
She gave a full statement on Choi Si An's accident.
They got into an argument which turned physical,
and Choi Si An bumped into the shelf the sculpture was on,
and it fell on top of her head.
It was an accident.
That's what she said.
Is that it?
Why? Should there be something else?
- No, it's just that... - Can I read the statement?
Sure.
We can't close the case just based on her statement.
We'll wait until the victim regains consciousness.
We need her statement as well.
Please bring in your daughter for any additional questioning.
I'll do that.
Let's go, Ji Na.
(Hangok Police Station)
What were you up to?
You were missing the whole day,
and then came here alone?
I said I didn't hurt Si An on purpose.
You never believed me.
I just wanted to tell the truth.
How is that my fault?
Did you really say just that?
The textbook or Global Talent Class.
You didn't mention those things?
Tell me!
I didn't.
Well done, Ji Na.
Well done.
Do you know how worried I was for you all day?
I thought I would burn up inside.
Sorry, Mom.
Don't do this ever again.
Don't come to the police station on your own.
Ask me and discuss it with me first.
Okay?
Okay.
Good. Good girl.
You're a good girl.
Can you please not upset me?
Do you know...
what you put me through?
I won't, Mom.
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it again.
It makes me so upset.
Okay.
Ji Na said it was an accident with no malicious intent.
Keep a close eye on Choi Si An's condition.
Since it wasn't intentional,
try to make Ji Yoon Su and Paik Seung Yoo...
see we feel really bad about what happened.
Also, ask if they'd be willing...
to settle with us.
I understand.
I bet you were always anxious.
Mr. Paik. It's me.
About the math exam incident.
The mother and teacher who leaked the answer sheet...
are on trial.
Once they are punished as they deserve to be,
it will all be wrapped up.
Okay.
Well done. You did great.
You're bound to be attacked from all sides,
but seeing how well you dealt with it...
puts me greatly at ease.
Thank you for believing in me.
Now I can leave everything in your hands...
and fish to my heart's content.
Right?
Then...
the directors who favor Yeon Woo...
I will deal with them.
Yeon Woo seems to be very distraught.
She hasn't left her home in a while.
Really? Then is everything ready?
Yes, everything's ready.
Bye.
Nice to meet you. I'm Ryu Sung Jae.
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you.
(Board Meeting: Vote for Chairman)
You can all sit down.
He kept asking why Si An hasn't been coming...
and kept insisting that we call her.
He hasn't been eating at all...
and just looks at the chessboard.
Father.
We're here, professor.
Do you miss Si An?
That was a great match.
I'll see you again.
Where's Si An?
Hold on.
Hello?
Really? Today?
Okay.
We will begin...
the election of the next director of Asung Foundation.
Please make your nominations.
I nominate Noh Jung Ah.
I second.
Are there any other nominations?
(Asung Foundation)
The prosecutor took everything.
Even the stuff we set aside and kept from the auditors.
This was an inside job.
(Ministry of Education)
So? They took everything?
That's right.
(Education Minister Shin Seung Jae)
Fix this.
No one would attack me like this.
I'm sure you were the target,
- so you need to fix it. - Wait.
Why must I fix it?
You benefited the most from the museum.
Why must I take responsibility and fix it?
What? What did you say?
All I did was help increase the budget...
in order to get the museum in my district.
You manipulated the site selection...
and everything else along the way,
so you fix it yourself. Good day.
(Assemblyman Sung Min Jun)
Assemblyman Sung, you're trying to get out of this by yourself?
Get Professor Cha Seong Won from IAIT...
and Principal Noh Jung Ah from Asung.
Yes, sir.
Let's begin.
Okay. Got it.
("Exclusive: The Education Mafia")
("Exclusive: The Education Mafia and the Corrupt Private School")
(Assemblyman Sung Min Jun)
All who are in favor of Noh Jung Ah being the next director,
please raise your hand.
By unanimous vote,
Asung Foundation's new director is Noh Jung Ah.
(Asung Foundation)
This is terrible.
- What is it? - Look at this.
(Assemblyman Sung Min Jun)
("Exclusive: The Education Mafia and the Corrupt Private School")
(Police begin investigation based on auditors' report)
As Asung Foundation's next director,
I feel a great sense of responsibility.
Asung Foundation has been a trailblazer...
in creating global talent from Korea.
I will do my best to maintain our great reputation...
as the best...
- What is this? - My gosh.
What timing.
Gosh.
Ma'am.
Goodness.
How could they do that?
How despicable.
Father.
- What nerve. - What a disgrace.
(Asung Foundation)
(Minister of Education, assemblyman)
(College professor, private school principal's collusion)
The auditors have uncovered evidence that the Minister of Education,
an assemblyman, and the principal of a famous private school,
used the construction of a national math museum...
for their personal gain.
The auditors received a tip regarding corruption...
during selecting the site and construction company,
as well as the management of the federal funding...
for the construction of the museum. Upon investigating, they found...
criminal acts were committed by Minister Shin Seung Jae,
Assemblyman Sung Min Jun, and Noh Jung Ah,
the principal of Asung of Mathematics and Arts.
Thus, they reported them to Prosecution Services.
Hello?
I've sent the material to the press.
- The article should post soon. - Really? Today?
Okay.
(Asung High School)
This massive education mafia...
was uncovered once the anonymous tip was proved to be true.
According to the tip, whereas the construction of the museum...
started with the idea of Paik Seung Yoo,
the winner of the Lucifer Prize and a teacher at Asung.
However, Principal Noh Jung Ah was the one who turned it...
into a national project funded by the national government.
This way.
This way. That way. Search everything.
(Prosecution Services)
What do you think you're doing?
We have a search warrant...
to seize evidence regarding the suspicion of corruption.
Your cooperation is requested.
You have a search warrant? How dare you?
(Minister Kyung Woo Min)
We found a safe.
Bring it.
Open it.
We'll add on obstruction of justice if you refuse.
There's nothing in there.
Find the master key.
You should cooperate. You're only hurting yourself.
I found the master key.
Yes.
You're here?
Where?
What? There's nothing in here.
- There's nothing? - There's nothing inside.
The door is open.
I...
want to go to the police station and tell them the truth.
But I'm scared.
My mom won't forgive me.
Ji Na.
Even if you tell the truth,
the world might not believe you.
It might not be the answer that people want to hear.
I don't want you to get hurt in that process.
But...
I do want you to find a way to stop feeling guilty...
about what happened to Si An.
How do I do that?
You just need to free yourself.
Stop living the life that your mom forces you to live.
Find out what you want...
and what kind of life you want to live.
Decide that for yourself.
I know it wasn't easy to do this. Thank you, Ji Na.
- You're here. - Yes, Mr. Paik.
These books were in the safe. They belong to the other kids.
There's one more thing.
I found this.
Here. I've made my move.
What are you going to do?
The knight?
The knight... Goodness.
Here's my defense.
What's next?
(2021 Foundation funding from students' parents)
(Global Talent Class)
(First half of 2021)
(Second half of 2021)
(Kyung Soo Young, Kwon Sung Woo, Sung Yoo Chan, Ahn Jenny...)
See? There's nothing inside.
We already received the files regarding the irregularities...
of the museum establishment.
You need to get investigated as a suspect,
so you'll have to come with us.
I want to call my lawyer.
Go ahead.
Escort her.
Call Attorney Jung.
Now.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hurry up and search the rest of the place.
Mr. Paik, it's me.
Here are the documents regarding the midterm exam.
It has everything including the original copy of the math test,
answer sheet, and the minutes from the meeting that took place.
Thank you.
I won't reveal the source.
I think it's time that you do.
Everything I grew is weak?
Don't be silly. When they realize that no place in the world...
can protect them as well as Asung did.
Where do they think they can go?
They're in the palm of my hand. The punks.
I saw it.
Principal Noh is falling apart.
Also,
I'd like to apologize for everything that happened to the two of you.
I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
(2021 Second Semester Midterm Exam)
We just need to add the documents we received from Mr. Choi.
Are you going to head to the Office of Education?
Yes. Come with me.
You castled your king?
What a great idea.
Then I'll try moving the rook.
Check...
There. Let's see.
This room is a lot more lively now that Professor Ji is here.
Goodness.
Dad.
Si An.
(Melancholia)
I think we can do something with this.
How dare you treat me like a criminal who messed up her child?
What did I do wrong?
He said he wanted you to receive an apology.
He said he wanted to make you happy.
I could tell that he was sincere.
I never resented you.
You understood me.
Thank you.
I want to finish whatever it is that I started.
No matter how long it takes.
No matter the result.
Will you promise me something one more time?