[The Ferry Man: 10th Anniversary]
[Episode 23]
How did it go?
Did you find any other deities?
What's happening?
Doctor. Doctor!
No! No.
That's not it.
There's a disturbance in the energy field.
This isn't something
from our world.
It's a cyber bird.
It's crying.
It's crying tears of blood.
It must be trying to tell us
something important.
Maybe it's about Ya.
But we can't communicate with it at all.
Go get Xu
and his wife.
Do we need to create
a temporary dimensional space?
No need.
Extract its data,
and I'll create a projection
right here in the room.
Okay.
Analyze the code now.
Done.
Yan Yuzhen
killed my beloved.
Push hard! Don't give up!
It's almost out!
Ya!
Look, it's the crimson moon!
When the crimson moon rises to
the peak of all mountains,
the child of the divine shall be born!
Blood moon...
What?
Ya ended up in this state
because Yan Yuzhen poisoned her?
That's too vicious!
Why would she do that?
Because of your unborn child with Ya.
She wants to merge
the cyber world
and the real world
into a new world.
You once told me
Yan Yuzhen was just a wisp of
resentment that resided within a painting
and became a demon.
That's what Zhao Li said.
Such a demon should be very weak.
How did she become so powerful?
She's been working with
Situ Fei all along.
Could Situ Fei be helping her?
Impossible.
Situ Fei
doesn't have that much power.
Yes.
People within our company also know
that Situ Fei has always
had a collaborator
who is a very powerful female demon.
Her status is
higher than Situ Fei's.
Right.
She isn't even
a natural-born demon.
Then where does her power come from?
Are you talking about
the legendary
peerless beauty, Yan Yuzhen?
She has become a demon?
What?
I got it.
It's thought-based power.
The name "Yan Yuzhen"
has circulated through time,
recorded in history books
and unofficial chronicles,
and adapted into films, TV series,
novels, fan works,
and countless games.
Her story, spread in various forms,
means she is constantly mentioned.
Every time she is mentioned,
her power grows a little more.
But
from our perspective as demons,
that alone isn't enough.
Being mentioned
can only sustain her existence.
She still needs a source
for her demonic power.
Use Love Potion
and become more beautiful alongside me.
It's the Love Potion.
What is that?
It's the only product
Yan Yuzhen promoted
after becoming a top influencer.
Ya did a lot of work
helping her market it.
Every game character like me
who has entered the real world
has
monthly KPIs—
attract as many fans as possible
and give Love Potion to them
as gifts.
The more we give away,
the longer we can stay
in the real world.
So,
the very purpose of your existence
is to give the Love Potion
to as many humans as possible?
How is that used?
It's a bath product.
You pour it into the bathtub.
So that is
the source of Yan Yuzhen's demonic power.
Her fans get the Love Potion,
and while soaking in the bath,
they unknowingly transfer energy to her.
It's a very stealthy way
to steal human energy
and turn it into her demonic power.
The longer they soak,
the more energy she absorbs.
With so many people bathing...
the demonic power she accumulates
becomes truly terrifying.
His code is breaking down.
After Yan Yuzhen turned me into a bird,
both Wang Fang's code and mine
were prohibited from
appearing in the real world.
Doing so causes our code to collapse.
Has a virus been injected into the code?
Yes.
I can fix it,
but it will take time.
I don't think we have that kind of time.
It's okay.
My mission is already complete.
I was never
a real living being anyway.
Without Wang Fang...
I have no desire
to continue existing.
If we both become mere specks
in the vast universe,
that's another way of
being together forever.
He's crashing.
I hope you can save your wife
and bring her back.
If possible,
please avenge my beloved.
He will be a hero to all of humanity,
even if
he's only a game character.
Zhao Hengzhi,
let's go find Yan Yuzhen now
and stop her evil ambitions.
The fake Kunlun that Yan Yuzhen built
is a model
Situ Fei helped develop.
My wife can get you inside.
So the same logic
applies inside this model?
In theory, yes.
But it's hard to say for sure.
Last time, we used weapons
conjured through thought-based power.
Xu's computer
has your log from last time.
I'm rewriting the costume program now
and overlaying it with your code.
Then you can go straight in
with your equipment.
Great.
We'll crush her
and send her running.
But what about the poison in Ya?
She's in this state.
Yan Yuzhen is the one
who poisoned Ya.
In that case,
as long as we destroy
Yan Yuzhen's demon core
and kill her,
the demonic power in reality
will disappear,
and Ya will return to normal.
Done.
Extract their codes
and send them into the model directly.
Honey,
I will definitely bring you
and our child
back safely.
You two,
get ready.
What are you doing?
The moon has reached its zenith,
and the auspicious moment has arrived.
I must ensure your child
is born safely.
I'm going to perform a cesarean section.
No.
No!
Who's there?
Dongqing!
Honey,
we're here to save you!
Don't believe
that demon's nonsense!
She's up to no good!
Ya!
Your wife
and the child in her belly
are mine.
You...
Where did you take
my wife?
She's just using a trick
to fool your eyes.
Ya is still there.
She's folded the space around her.
Defeat me,
and then you can
go home
with your wife and child.
But what do you think
your odds are of defeating me
in my world?
Dressed up so grandly—
what, are you auditioning
for an idol competition?
"Song of Rainbow Skirts and Feather Robes"
is Yan Yuzhen's first skill.
It deals 200 damage
with a slowing effect.
Let's check Dongqing's stats.
Let's check Mr. Zhao's as well.
Okay.
Let's take a look at Yan Yuzhen's again.
Her second skill is Flying Apsaras Dance,
with teleportation
and illusory explosions.
Once her energy bar is full,
she can unleash her ultimate move,
"Dance of the Rainbow Skirt
and Feathered Robe,"
which also regenerates health.
Her ultimate can even restore health?
Yan Yuzhen's starting HP
is 3,000 points.
Right.
Dongqing and Zhao Hengzhi
only have
1,000 HP each.
Can we do something?
I'll see
if I can transmit my voice
to Mr. Zhao.
Okay.
Mr. Zhao?
Mr. Zhao,
can you hear me?
We've established a connection
with you.
Wanping,
what do you want to say? Go ahead.
Yan Yuzhen's lotus throne
can restore health,
and every 10 seconds, it increases
her attack power by 10%.
Right.
Dongqing,
attack her lotus throne!
Dance of the Rainbow Skirt
and Feathered Robe!
Which one should we attack?
Which one is her real body?
None of them can get away!
Samadhi Fire—Heavens Incineration!
Yan Yuzhen, you lose!
Even if you have last words,
I have no interest in hearing them.
I'll finish you off right now.
What's happening?
A new skill button has
appeared in Yan Yuzhen's skill bar.
[Crimson Moon—Goddess Genesis]
When HP drops below 5%,
it triggers her hidden skill,
Crimson Moon—Goddess Genesis.
What on earth is that?