Ma'am,
this glass is broken.
See if it needs to be taken care of.
Oh, you mean that piece.
It's fine.
Even though it looks shattered inside,
as long as you don't touch it,
it'll be fine for a few weeks.
Weihao,
happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Li Weihao.
Excuse me, you dropped your student ID.
Is anyone there?
Help!
Your mother's and my lives
have been ruined by you.
Chao,
are you still busy?
Well,
the money,
I've already transferred it to your account.
In addition,
I added 500 yuan for you.
Eat and drink well.
Call me anytime if you need anything.
I don't want the extra money.
Be nicer to Qiong University students from now on.
Okay.
No problem.
When Qiong University students come in the future,
they all get a 20% discount.
Okay.
Then you carry on.
Don't worry.
Zhang Chao,
let's go.
How much longer do you think
it will take?
There's no time left.
What do you mean, no time left?
What's going on?
Chao.
What's wrong, Chao?
Li Weihao.
Did you put salt in my food again just now?
No, I didn't put anything in it.
You didn't? Why is it so salty then?
You put too much.
Sami.
Xiaoyu.
Li Weihao jumped off a building.
Jumped off a building.
That's good.
I'm still too busy right now.
Thank you.
Come on, thank you everyone.
Uncle, Auntie.
I'll go take a call first.
Excuse me.
Come on, let's have another toast.
Alright, cheers.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Li Weihao jumped off a building.
Are you crazy?
Really? You didn't know?
What?
Coward.
What did you say?
Nothing.
A student at school
took things too hard
and is gone.
What?
What do you mean, gone?
Stop talking nonsense!
My son had dinner at home tonight.
Let me tell you,
cursing someone will bring death to your whole family.
What's going on?
A scam call.
I'm so angry.
Do you know what he said?
He said our son...
I can't say it.
It's too unlucky.
Enough.
My heart is pounding.
It's going to jump out.
I was almost angered to death.
What's wrong?
This child.
It's this scam call again.
Is it that serious? It's just a scam call.
You're so scared. I'll answer it.
So infuriating.
Hello, who is it?
Give him a scolding.
What happened?
Let's go.
Where are we going?
The morgue.
Another round.
Alright, cheers.
Why are you staying here alone?
I'm not interested in this kind of event.
Me neither.
I have big news.
Do you want to hear it?
No.
Don't try to get close to me.
I'm not interested in you either.
Someone jumped off a building at Qiong University.
You should know him.
His name is Li Weihao.
What?
Xiaochao, you are my best friend.
Xiaohao, you too. Come and catch me.
You can't catch me.
I will catch you soon.
Come and catch me.
You can't catch me, Xiaohao.
Wait for me.
Li Weihao.
I'm sorry, Chao.
I didn't turn off my alarm.
Li Weihao is gone.
He's dead.
Chao.
Are you okay, Chao?
What's wrong, Chao?
Are you really okay, Chao?
Chao.
What's wrong with you, Chao?
Look at me, Chao.
Chao.
Let me help you up.
Let me take you to the infirmary.
I'm fine.
I'm going out for some fresh air. Slow down.
Who is it?
Who?
Stop right there.
Stop.
Come on.
Who is it?
Who?
Wu Yu.
Are you out of your mind?
Are you crazy?
Scaring people in the middle of the night.
I just came downstairs.
How did I scare you?
Stop pretending.
Step back a little.
Didn't you just go to the bathroom?
No.
I really didn't.
I came downstairs.
Why would I go to the bathroom?
Did you see a dark shadow just now?
Now that you mention it,
when I was coming downstairs just now,
I really saw a dark shadow
flash by over there.
Tell me,
could that shadow
be Weihao?
Stop talking nonsense.
Turn it off.
What are you doing?
I saw a shadow.
Where is it?
It was there just now.
Are you crazy?
No.
I just saw a shadow.
Is it Weihao?
Weihao is already dead.
No.
Boss.
Do you think Weihao's death
has anything to do with us?
Happy birthday to you.
No.
Happy birthday.
Why are you keeping these photos?
Keeping them to miss him?
No, no.
Delete it.
Why did we take so many pictures?
Can this car be driven?
No? Come on, let me drive.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
I'm going to the restroom.
Nobody is allowed to leave.
I'll be right back.
I'll go with you, boss.
Go back
and keep an eye on them.
Okay.
My boss said
nobody can leave.
Beat you to death!
Go to hell!
No offense, Weihao.
Have a good rest.
Brother Chao.
Do you feel
that this room is a bit chilly?
How about
we squeeze into one bed tonight?
Sure.
Welcome.
Great.
Go away.
Why are you in my bed?
Chao.
Last night,
didn't I ask if we could sleep together?
You agreed to it yourself.
Take your pillow and get out.
Chao.
Chao, listen to me.
You held my hand last night.
Why are you... Let go!
Let go.
Fine, I'll go.
You turn your back and deny everything.
This is my pillow.
Take it back.
Thank you.
Oh, my god.
Is that Li Weihao from the Design Department?
Poor thing.
He was so young.
Just passed away like this.
Excuse me,
hello.
What did you say about Li Weihao?
He jumped off the building last night. Right there.
I have good news for you.
We are getting married next month!
Really?
Come on, cheers!
My bad, my bad.
Why didn't you pour wine for everyone?
Here, I'll pour you a little more.
Let's make big money together.
I wish Mr. Chen happy every day!
The number you dialed is powered off.
Weihao,
I will go to Qiongzhou tomorrow
to see you.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Let us in.
We want to see the principal.
What are you doing? We want to see the principal.
Let us go.
Let us in. Don't stop us.
I have to go in. Let us in.
Stop.
Let me go.
Give my son back!
My son was fine when he arrived.
How did he become like this?
How does your school manage students?
I'm sorry.
It's our school's negligence
for this matter.
Is "sorry" useful?
Can it bring my son back to life?
What's wrong with you?
Give my son back! I can fully understand
your feelings.
If this punch
can relieve your anger,
I am willing to take a few more punches.
It's a bargain for you to take a few punches.
I'm telling you,
you must hand over the murderer to me today.
I want him to pay for my son's life.
Don't talk nonsense.
The police have ruled out the suspicion of homicide.
Your son...
What happened to my son?
It wasn't a homicide.
Did he jump down by himself?
Yes.
I think you still want to shirk your responsibility.
Give my son back!
What are you doing?
Let go. Let them go.
You think we have no backing, right?
I'm telling you,
ordinary people are not easy to bully.
Give my son back!
To be honest,
I am also very remorseful
and guilty.
Rest assured.
Give us some time
and trust.
We will definitely investigate this matter clearly.
Here,
on behalf of Qiongzhou University,
I sincerely apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Apologizing won't bring my son back.
There are still some of Li Weihao's belongings in his dorm room.
If you want to take them back,
I can take you there.
I'm sorry.
You should go back too.
Mr. Du,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's just that you haven't been back in so many years.
And now that you are,
you have to see a scene like this.
I'm really sorry.
Actually,
Weihao is my patient.
About seven years ago,
I registered a Tree Hole account on Weibo.
It was mainly used to share
psychological knowledge.
At that time,
Weihao
was the first person to leave me a message.
Over the past five years,
I have been recording what he told me,
and I initially concluded
that Weihao might have depression.
You mean
Li Weihao had depression?
He had a tendency towards depression,
but after years of psychological counseling,
he no longer had suicidal thoughts.
I also really want to know
why this happened.
If I had noticed something wrong with Weihao earlier,
maybe all of this
wouldn't have happened.
I will ask for two more days of leave from the hospital in Beijing
until this matter is cleared up.
No problem.
If you need anything,
we will fully cooperate.
If you are short-handed,
I will find you a partner.
It's probably a call about Weihao.
We are right in the thick of it now.
Do you want to avoid it?
No.
At this juncture,
our school absolutely cannot hide.
I'll take this call first.
Hello.
Go ahead.
Alright, Guixiang.
It's just a sticker.
Leave it.
It belongs to my son.
I want to take it home.
My condolences, Ma'am.
Xiaochao.
Can you tell me
what exactly happened?
You and Xiaohao
have been good friends since childhood.
You must know him well, right?
Can you tell me
what happened to him?
Why would he do such a thing?
Xiaochao, please tell me.
Tell me.
Say something.
You are his parents.
If you don't know,
how should I?
But...
Alright.
Let's go.
Chao.
Chao, are you okay?