Chao.
Come to my house for dinner, Chao.
Chao,
come to my house for dinner.
My mom made coconut chicken.
Sure.
Let's go.
Isn't this Shasha?
Her name is Yueyue.
Yueyue.
They look exactly alike.
Every time I see her,
I get scared.
It reminds me of that incident.
Alright, stop overthinking.
Shasha's death has nothing to do with us.
You think too simply.
The girl wants to make money.
We shouldn't stand in her way,
right?
What about the other one?
The other one
is very interesting.
The Bai family's
precious daughter,
Bai Qiu.
Bai Qiu?
Are you crazy?
Calm down first.
Don't you find it fishy?
A wealthy daughter of the Bai family,
just for that little money,
getting on this pirate ship with us?
I think there's
some trickery here.
She definitely has a motive for getting close to me.
Who knows?
Since she wants to get on board,
we should set up a ladder for her.
Has everything been going smoothly lately?
You must be extremely careful from now on.
If anything happens, be sure to tell me immediately.
Let's go.
Auntie.
Xiaorong.
Xiaorong is back!
I missed you so much, darling.
How are you all doing?
Are you in good health?
We're doing great.
Your grandpa
has been looking forward to your return since early morning.
Exactly.
He even wanted to get out of bed to welcome you himself.
Hurry up and step over it.
Okay!
He's been waiting here for ages.
We couldn't persuade him to go back inside.
How is your health?
I'm doing great.
Xiaorong is back.
Everything is fine.
Xiaorong.
Uncle.
Grandpa is waiting inside.
Long time no see.
Aunt.
Aunt is back.
Little Rongrong.
You're back.
Oh my, you've gotten even prettier.
Long time no see.
Grandpa is waiting for you.
Grandpa.
Is everything okay?
Come on, let's eat.
Let's start eating.
Look at all these dishes.
They are all Xiaorong's favorites.
Let me do it.
Okay.
Today is a great day for the Chen family.
Auntie.
Eat and drink more, Auntie.
Sister.
Slow down.
I cooked coconut milk chicken for Grandpa.
That's great.
Come here.
So good.
Come sit and eat with us.
I have something to do at home.
I'll be going now. Thank you.
Take some more food back with you.
Look at this child.
I brought you some food.
I'm not late, am I?
Not at all.
Adding another dish for you.
I thought I wouldn't make it in time.
Sister-in-law.
Sit down and eat with us.
No, thanks.
Grandpa just woke up,
and it's rare for Rong to come back.
You guys should have a family chat.
I won't bother you.
Let's eat together.
Take care on your way.
Okay, come on.
It's rare for us to gather together.
Cheers!
Let's have a drink.
Good.
Come.
So everyone is healthy.
These are all
local dishes from our hometown.
Nothing fancy.
You.
Don't mind it.
Make yourself at home.
Eat more.
Come.
Eat more. Have a taste.
Have a taste.
These mixed fish were just caught this morning.
They are super fresh.
Try a piece.
You have to try this chicken. Eat more.
Let me tell you.
This was raised by my second sister-in-law.
Authentic Wenchang chicken.
You've definitely never had it before.
Try it quickly.
Okay, eat more.
Come, taste it, eat more.
That's enough. Being a guest in Gechen Village,
you never get the chance to serve yourself.
Right.
Eat more.
Try it, eat up.
So good.
You are too far. Come.
Hurry up.
Enough.
Eat.
Does it taste good?
Is it good?
Good, right?
Old Chen's stuff is always good.
Yes.
Eat more.
Enough.
You have to eat well since you are here.
Eat more.
We are family once you're here.
His body is so strong.
Usually.
Grandpa,
want to take a photo?
Take a photo.
Okay.
Let's take a good one.
Let's take a family portrait.
Okay.
Come.
Let's take a family portrait. Give it to me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Come. Sorry for the trouble.
Taking a family portrait.
Taking a family portrait. Let's go.
Okay.
Come, take a family portrait.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
Let's take another one.
Grandpa,
smile.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
Good.
Let's continue eating after taking photos.
Okay.
Let's go eat.
What's wrong, Grandpa?
Are you calling Zhang Chao?
Come.
Sit down and eat. Everyone, please sit.
Chao.
Get me a stool.
Okay.
Have a seat.
Grandpa, you misunderstood.
He is my friend.
It's not the kind of relationship you think.
I have no plans to date right now.
Okay.
It's my fault.
I couldn't bring a partner back
to make you happy.
I've been too busy with work these past few years,
and I really haven't met the right person.
Got it.
Okay.
He is my student.
He ran into some trouble recently,
and is in a bad mood.
I was a bit worried about him,
so I brought him along.
Come.
Close.
Sad.
Pass.
Hard.
Okay.
Walk.
Have a candy.
I will remember that.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Guixiang.
I remember now.
I remember everything.
He doesn't like it.
He likes the one his grandmother made for him.
He doesn't like this latex pillow.
He doesn't like latex pillows.
He only likes the buckwheat pillow his grandmother gave him.
He doesn't like blue.
He likes pink.
He doesn't like Qiongzhou.
He likes going to Beijing.
Right. He likes Beijing, Guixiang.
Guixiang.
Calm down, Guixiang.
Pull yourself together. Don't be like this.
I remember everything.
Don't scare me, Guixiang.
Look at me. He doesn't like latex pillows.
Guixiang.
Snap out of it.
Weiguo.
I was too foolish before.
Now I remember everything.
I remember it all.
It was us.
We were the ones who lost Xiaohao.
It wasn't like this before.
When did we become like this?
Xiaohao must hate us so much.
Before he left,
he didn't leave a single word for us.
How much must he hate us?
All right, Guixiang.
How could we be wrong?
We couldn't be wrong.
Don't listen to their nonsense, okay?
I'm begging you.
If anyone's wrong, it's them.
It's all their fault.
He doesn't like latex pillows.
He likes the buckwheat pillow.
He doesn't like that latex pillow.
He likes that buckwheat pillow.
He doesn't like eating fish.
He likes coconut chicken.
I'm sorry.
I kept you busy all day.
You must be tired.
The food was delicious,
and the stars are beautiful.
As
your boyfriend,
I was taken good care of all night
and even got candy from Grandpa.
I should be the one thanking you.
You're quite aloof.
I didn't know you were so easily satisfied.
Is it easy?
My mother
passed away when I was young.
As for my dad,
he was never home all year round.
In my memory,
I was always alone.
A scene like today
is something I wouldn't even dare to dream of.
Actually, I'm quite like you.
When I was a kid,
I was always alone too.
It's just that
my parents had an accident
and could never come back.
I was ten that year,
like an angry bird.
I hated
everyone who pitied and cared for me.
I'd rather starve
than eat the food sent by my aunts.
With nothing to eat,
I learned to cook by myself.
I almost burned the house down.
And then?
Then,
it was Grandpa.
Grandpa pulled me out of the mire.
Are you unhappy?
Grandpa,
am I just bad at everything?
If you want to learn to cook,
why didn't you ask your aunts for help?
I don't want to trouble others.
Come, drink some tea.
Keep Grandpa company for a while.
Rong,
do you know
why our village is called Gechen Village?
A long, long time ago,
in this village of ours,
there was only a family with the surname Ge living here.
One year,
a family with the surname Chen fled famine and passed by here,
starving.
It was the Ge family
who brought them a bowl of rice soup
and saved their lives.
Later,
the Chen family
settled down here.
One year,
there was a flood,
and the Ge family's house
was destroyed by the flood.
It was the Chen family
who helped the Ge family
rebuild their house.
A few years later,
there was a huge typhoon,
and the Chen family's house
was blown down by the typhoon.
It was the Ge family
who helped them rebuild their house again.
And then?
Grandpa,
are you telling a tongue twister?
I'm so dizzy.
And then,
it became what you see today.
Everyone is together,
and happy.
Zhang Chao,
actually,
if you are willing to stop,
and turn your head,
you'll find that
you are never alone.
In this world,
there are still many people who care about you,
including me.
Have a taste.
Chao! Chao!
Come to my house for dinner, Chao.
Chao,
come to my house for dinner.
My mom made coconut milk chicken.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mom.
Chao is here.
Great.
You came just in time. Eat up.
Hello, Auntie.
Hello. Come and sit.
Dad. Hello, Uncle.
The coconut chicken is ready too.
When your parents are not at home in the future,
come eat with us.
You and Hao are good friends,
so you'll be good brothers in the future.
Eat up.
Quick.
Hurry up,
bring the new clothes,
and don't forget the shoes.
Quick.
Ms. Chen.
What's going on?
It's so lively.
Grandpa passed away.
What's wrong?
When I first came,
I saw how harmonious everyone was,
and I was quite envious.
I didn't expect you all to be so cold-blooded.
Such a good grandpa passed away.
If you don't cry, fine,
but you're actually laughing.
You misunderstood.
This is a happy funeral.
What do you mean?
Grandpa was 75 years old.
Although his health wasn't particularly good,
and he wasn't considered very old,
he had both virtue and longevity,
harmonious children,
and he passed away in his sleep
without illness or pain.
He was a blessed person.
When such an elderly person in the family passes away,
we shouldn't cry.
We should send him off with a smile,
celebrating the perfect end to his life.
It's just that
Grandpa looked pretty healthy to me.
I didn't expect him to go so soon.
Actually, when Grandpa woke up in the hospital
and returned home,
we all realized
that Grandpa's life was coming to an end.
It's just that Grandpa was lucky.
He borrowed a few more days from heaven
to say a proper goodbye to us.
Is this terminal lucidity?
You could say that.
Being able to clearly arrange one's own affairs
is indeed a fortunate thing.
Grandpa's photo.
He chose it himself.
The clothes
are also his favorite.
He divided the little money left in the bankbook,
had a meal with the family,
and drank the red rice wine brewed by his aunt.
We also took a big group photo together.
He repeatedly told us
that when he passed away,
the house should be decorated with lanterns inside and out,
and set off firecrackers.
He also said
that this day in the future
should not be treated as a death anniversary,
but as a festival
to celebrate for him.
Grandpa is really a free-spirited person.
Let Grandpa tell you,
a person's life
is like climbing a mountain.
Going up the mountain first, then coming down.
If you don't want to regret when coming down,
you must enjoy yourself to the fullest when going up.
How do you enjoy yourself to the fullest?
When you see a flower you like,
pick it.
If it rains,
just let it rain on you for a while.
How does the saying go?
Every obstacle is hard, but you overcome every one.
Every step is hard, but you take every step.
When you encounter a hurdle,
just step over it.
It's no big deal.
If you get lost,
don't be nervous.
Just keep walking and looking.
At worst,
Taking a little detour.
As long as you
keep moving forward
and don't look back,
then you will definitely
see the sun.
Understood.
Although physical death will destroy a person,
the concept of death
can save them.
And those spirits and virtues
will also save those left behind.
Loved ones won't turn into stars,
but their light
will stay in our hearts forever.
Difficult times,
are hard to pass.
But they
will pass.
It's hard.
Keep walking,
step by step.
Have a candy.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Thank you.
Here.
Take this to eat on the road.
These are for you and Xiaochao to take back.
Take good care of Xiaorong.
We'll be back for the New Year.
Xiaorong,
remember.
Even though Grandpa isn't here anymore,
this will always be your home.
Come back and visit often.
Come back often.
I'll miss you all.
We will.
We're leaving now.
Go.
Safe travels.
Bye-bye.
Have a safe trip.
Drive safely.
Let us know when you arrive.
Okay.
Xiaorong, be safe.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Come back often.
You seem reluctant to leave.
I feel like
Gechen Village is like my home.
Or maybe
it's the home I imagined.
I even feel that
there seems to be another me in this world
who once lived like this.
I don't know if
that's my imagination
or my memory.
You feel like there's another you
inside your body?
It's okay. You don't have to talk about it if you don't want to.
It's not that I don't want to talk about it.
It's just that
I don't know how to say it.
When I first came to Qiong University,
I saw Li Weihao again.
One part of me
was very happy.
Another part of me
was very resistant.
After he left,
one part of me
was heartbroken.
Another part of me
felt nothing.
I don't know why it's like this.
When did this start?
When Li Weihao
passed away.
No,
that's not right either.
Chang A·A
What's wrong?
Old problem.
It seems that whenever I think of Li Weihao,
I get a headache.
I know
the reason you keep looking for me
isn't because of Li Weihao,
it's because of me.
I'm sick, aren't I?
Yes.
Although I don't know what it is yet,
I'm willing to help you find the answer.
Okay.
I thought you'd refuse.
I was just
thinking about Grandpa.
He could even face death.
I shouldn't run away anymore.
Drink some water.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Chen Rong.
He Chuan.
I just went to the office to look for you.
Wait a moment.
Zhang Chao.
Take the local products back with you.
Don't forget what you said in the car.
I'll wait for you.
See you tomorrow.
Why did grandpa suddenly...
I should have gone back with you.
It's fine.
Grandpa had a happy funeral.
Everything went smoothly.
But,
why are you with Zhang Chao?
Did you go back to Gechen Village together?
I'm in a hurry.
Let's talk later.
Girls!
Cheers!
Over here!
Bottoms up!
Xiaoyu, is that a new watch?
It looks so good!
Sir.
What's wrong?
Miss, excuse me.
The room is over here.
It's limited edition.
Limited edition.
Let me tell you.
Xiaoyu.
Is that your friend,
Bai Qiu?
Hello, dear!
Let me introduce to you,
my good friend,
Bai Qiu.
Come on.
Hello.
I'll introduce a new friend to you today,
Yueyue.
Say hi.
Fang Yue,
our beautiful sales rep.
What do you think?
Isn't she pretty?
Which of your friends isn't?
I'm Bai Qiu.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm Fang Yue.
Just call me Yueyue.
Come on.
Please take care of me.
Don't just stand there awkwardly.
Sit down and talk.
Sit down and take your time.
Did you notice
who she looks like?
Who?
Now that you mention it,
I actually remember someone.
Who?
It seems to be
an actress from Hong Kong.
What's her name?
You flatter me too much.
Yueyue.
Amy,
give me your phone.
I mean Shasha.
Shasha?
Who is Shasha?
A good friend of yours.
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
I don't remember having a friend named Shasha.
But I've seen your pictures
on her Moments.
Love, Qiu.
Probably the same name.
My first name is just Qiu,
so it's not that special.
I think you're just forgetful, Miss Bai.
You have too many friends to remember.
Whether you have this friend or not,
just check your phone,
and you'll know.
Xiaochao, tell me.
Weihao...
Did he tell you anything?
You are good friends with him.
Does he hate me?
Tell me.
Let go. Let go. Let go.