On the night of Christmas Eve,
my father was murdered by someone.
The person arrested as the primary suspect
was Tomoya Endo.
Tomoya was the son of Rikiro Endo,
a man who received the death penalty
for murdering a family
22 years ago in Higashikayama.
However, my father left me a letter
that spoke of false accusations.
I trusted my father's letter
and sought to uncover the truth
alongside a lawyer named Matsukaze.
But then…
The one who forged Mr. Yamashita's letter…
is me.
Yes.
I received word from Someda just now
that the police had shown up at his place.
Someda will say that he forged the letter
under the orders of Tomoya Endo.
Yes, of course.
Someda is of no further use.
It's fine.
Nothing problematic has gotten out.
Is that so.
Someda should have known
better than anyone.
There are some things better left unknown.
Mr. Yamashita…
Why did it… turn out like this?
Hello!
-Mr. Someda!
-Huh?
-The person from the bank is here.
-Okay!
Mr. Someda, if your son
ever decides to inherit your business,
investing now will benefit him too.
SOMEDA TATAMI MAT STORE
DIRECTOR, SUSUMU SOMEDA
STAMP
I'm home!
Satoru!
How are you, Satoru?
Come here.
Up you go. Welcome home!
Back then,
I thought those happy times
would last forever.
More and more businesses are going
bankrupt due to failed investments.
Experts say they expect
the bubble's collapse to accelerate.
Sir, you have a call.
Yes?
That can't be…
I'm sorry for missing your payroll again.
I'm so sorry!
This is why we all objected to it.
-What are we supposed to do now?
-I'm sorry.
My father started that tatami mat store
and I caused it to go under.
PROPERTY FOR SALE
And on that day…
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
I'd like some flowers.
Today's our wedding anniversary.
Congratulations.
Thank you for your purchase.
I have to say it.
It's going to be tough from now,
but would you please stay with me?
Guess I should have the talk first.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
-Look, I--
-Don't you have something to say?
This came in from the court today.
You took out a loan
with our house as collateral?
You're always like this.
Why don't you ever tell me anything?
I had my mind made up, you know.
If the first thing you said
when you came home was about this,
I'd forgive you if you told me
everything of your own accord.
If you apologized and asked me to stay…
Wait.
-Hear me out.
-Hear what out?
Will it change anything if I do?
I just can't stay with you anymore.
The one who forged Mr. Yamashita's letter…
is me.
Mr. Yamashita…
I'm so…
Someda admitted to it
as soon as you came in, sir.
He must've sensed he couldn't fool you.
No, it's all thanks to you
for softening him up beforehand, Akisada.
Good job.
Thank you, sir.
Now, if only Tomoya Endo
would talk just as easily.
Yeah.
-Chief, you're drinking that water again?
-Yeah.
I'm told it's good for my body.
By your wife?
Pretty much.
TOMOYA ENDO
That'll do it.
Starting now,
I will take full responsibility
and represent you as your defense counsel.
If you ever need assistance,
don't hesitate to call me.
Also, I listened to it.
Listened?
-Listened to what?
-The recording.
He gave it to you?
The person you were talking to
was Mr. Haruo Yamashita, correct?
Can't you tell just by looking?
Just by looking?
I'm sorry. I deeply regret
what I've done to you, Tomoya.
I'm afraid I couldn't tell
from the voice alone.
Why'd he go and do that?
Do what?
There's a video.
He should have it.
A video of me and Haruo Yamashita talking.
Then,
what I heard was only
the audio from that recording?
Going off your reaction,
I guess that means…
you didn't see the most important thing.
-Chief.
-What?
That lawyer, Matsukaze, has officially
become Tomoya's defense attorney.
-Yes? Anan speaking.
-There's been a development.
We did another round
of questioning with Someda,
who owns the ramen stall
that Mr. Yamashita frequented.
He admitted to forging the letter
under the direction of Tomoya Endo.
I see.
Someda did?
Someda already talked.
It won't be long until Tomoya does.
Besides that,
there's another concerning matter.
What is it?
A lawyer came in contact with Someda.
His name is Yoshiteru Matsukaze.
He's the lawyer mentioned
in Mr. Yamashita's letter.
I think he might be involved
in this case somehow.
This Matsukaze guy is now
officially Tomoya's defense attorney.
I see.
Let's see how things play out for now.
Are you moving to rearrest
Tomoya Endo on a murder charge?
I should hope you are.
Yes.
We're trying to do exactly that.
Goodbye then.
Why'd you have to interfere?
Hello?
Um, I just wanted to know how it went.
I got Tomoya Endo to sign
the document assigning me as his counsel.
However…
However, what?
It's a bit complicated.
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Wait, now you've made me curious.
I'll come over there.
Don't. It'll be the same
whether I tell you today or tomorrow.
-Just wait until then.
-No.
Don't make this difficult.
What would you do in my position?
"It's complicated. Wait until tomorrow."
Would you wait?
Try to answer me using
your non-existent imagination.
I would… wait.
That's a lie. You're a liar. A dirty liar!
LIAR!
LIAT!
Jeez, calm down.
LIAR!
ARISA
MUGI, YOU ALRIGHT? DOING OKAY?
I'M DOING OKAY
CAN WE MEET?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
OPEN
Welcome.
Sorry for being late.
I took a bus, you see,
and it got stuck in some terrible traffic.
It's tough being poor.
Us poor reporters can't even take taxis.
-Why did you--
-Right.
If it's about me not sending
everything I had, that's my bad.
It's just, you know,
I'm a poor little reporter, after all.
If I showed all my cards,
I bet you wouldn't even give me
the time of day.
Hand over the recorded footage.
Can I order first?
-Welcome.
-A caffè latte, please.
Draw a rabbit with the foam, if you would.
Sorry?
Come on now. It's a joke.
Just trying to be funny.
I'm not here to make small talk.
Hand over the recorded footage!
-That's all for my order.
-Yes, sir.
Now that I'm his attorney,
I can't let him be prosecuted so easily.
Time is of the essence.
Do you have to look so scary?
Could be a poster for The Grudge.
Mr. Kamii, it seems to me
that you've gained Tomoya Endo's trust,
but you must know there's limits
to what a mere reporter can do.
You know, have you ever been told
that you're kind of a pompous ass?
What?
Oh my, you're not even self-aware?
That's a severe case!
A word of advice.
If you keep that up,
you'll never get anything out of anyone.
Me, I first build a firm foundation
with whoever I'm talking to.
I make sure to be sincere
with them. Real sincere.
And then,
I ever so smoothly get them to talk.
Does the way you treat Komugi
also count as being sincere?
-Of course--
-Absolutely not!
All you did was cause confusion.
It's still not clear
if that DNA test was even true.
It seems to me that you're
deliberately trying to confuse her,
perhaps for some other objective.
You claimed that the surviving child
of the Hayashikawa family
from 22 years ago is actually Komugi.
Komugi and Uta Hayashikawa
have different ages and birthdays.
She's already quite unsettled.
If you plan to keep confusing
her with baseless claims,
then I frankly don't care
about being called a pompous ass.
I will take action to protect her.
I know all that already.
About the birthdays and everything.
I said it all despite knowing.
Stop being so condescending,
you damn lawyer!
It really pisses me off.
That patronizing look.
Well, it's still true that I want
to get along with you two.
I'll show it to you,
as a way to make amends.
The video footage of Tomoya Endo
talking with Haruo Yamashita.
Here's your order.
So what did you want to talk about?
Yeah, about that.
The thing is,
the faculty of law makes
us do practical training,
so I attended some hearings in court.
And while I was there,
I met your dad at the court.
Mugi's dad?
You met Dad?
He was at the court?
But why?
I don't know that part.
But… I met him a few times.
What?
One of those times, he talked
to me about that one incident.
I'm really grateful to you, Arisa.
For when you two were in grade school.
Who did this?
What happened, Emi? Are you all right?
Someone cut up her scarf.
Did you do it, Komugi?
Komugi told me that you
stayed friends with her
after that scarf incident.
She'd probably have stopped
going to school if it wasn't for you.
She said so.
Mugi did?
I have to apologize to you.
I actually…
Komugi's so annoying,
always acting nice and obedient.
She sure is.
Hey, Emi.
Was it really okay to cut your own scarf?
It's fine.
Mom buys me new ones all the time.
What?
It was all orchestrated by Emi.
I found out the truth,
but Emi and her group threatened me.
I was too scared of them targeting me.
I told your dad about it.
And then he said…
I want to thank you…
for telling me.
It must've been tough.
I'm glad Komugi has such a good friend.
He said that to me.
Even after learning how I acted.
Mugi,
I'm really sorry.
What?
But why?
Because…
I was happy.
And also,
I finally found out that
the peacock really did dance.
The peacock danced?
Don't worry about it.
Arisa.
Thanks for telling me everything.
Wait, is this…
Yup, where we are right now.
I'm sorry.
I deeply regret
what I've done to you, Tomoya.
-I'm so sorry.
-What exactly are you apologizing for?
I'm asking you what the hell
you're apologizing for!
I've wronged both Rikiro
and Mr. Hayashikawa as well.
And what will you do about it?
I'll borrow Mr. Kamii's help,
and I'll disclose everything.
At the time,
I was a part of the investigation
for the Higashikayama case.
Your father ended up becoming a suspect,
and ultimately confessed to the crime.
But when Rikiro
received his death sentence…
I thought…
A certain thought began to plague my mind.
This is where it gets good.
Your father, Rikiro,
is not the person…
that's responsible…
for the murders.
See? Isn't that some good stuff?
If that's true,
then go announce that
in a press conference or whatever else.
Well, I would do that if I could.
Right now, I'm trying to gather proof.
-You're just gonna feign ignorance?!
-That's not it.
Mr. Kamii, please--
That's it?
I promised Haruo
I'd only film the apology.
-Is that actually true?
-It is! I swear.
Well, I hope you get the idea now.
Komugi is more than just
the daughter of a murder victim.
She's central to the Higashikayama case.
My guess is that Haruo
figured out who the true culprit was.
These are all the days
I met your dad at court.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Mugi, would you please stay
my friend from now on too?
Of course.
-Don't you have a seminar next?
-Oh, right.
-Later then, Mugi.
-Later.
Dad…
what were you doing in court?
So it growls even at a time like this.
Proof that I'm alive.
Right.
Too early, I guess.
That's not what we agreed to!
Please wait! I did what you asked!
Hello?!
Mr. Someda?
Mr. Someda.
Oh, Komugi.
Did something happen?
No, nothing at all.
Really?
Really.
Okay then.
That's good.
Mr. Someda?
Hey, Mr. Someda?
Komugi…
I've done something unthinkable.
What?
What happened?
I betrayed…
Mr. Yamashita.
I've wasted my life.
All of it.
My company went under,
and my wife and child left me.
I tried to kill myself.
IF TRAPPED PLEASE GET OUT
But… I couldn't do it.
When I was at rock bottom…
Are you all right, mister?
A young man I'd just met heard me out.
Thanks a lot.
I was ready to die just moments ago,
but I feel better now.
Don't try that again, okay?
Life just doesn't go the way you want.
Look, I have special something for you.
ROWAZO
Wait, is this…
Just hear me out.
If your life keeps refusing
to go your way, just try it out.
It will help you feel better.
Did you take it?
Once you get addicted,
it's over.
Nice work.
I had to pay for the drugs,
so I did as I was told,
creating counterfeit products
and forging signatures.
Satoru?
Satoru!
I'm from the police station.
You're Mr. Susumu Someda, correct?
You're under arrest for violating
the Unfair Competition Prevention Law.
You can leave.
I'll be handling your questioning.
I'm Yamashita.
Man, it sure is hot today.
Don't you think?
I'd love some hot ramen
on a day like this.
Doesn't it feel great to eat
some hot ramen on a hot day…
and just sweat away the heat?
That was how I met Mr. Yamashita.
I'll admit to everything.
I'm sorry.
I'll stop doing drugs.
I see.
But well,
looking at your state now,
I don't think that's gonna happen.
Huh?
I'll make a prediction.
You'll do the same thing again.
What would you know, fucking bastard?!
Get off your damn high horse!
Sit down.
Of course,
I have no way of knowing
what it's like to be in your shoes.
Then what gives you the right to preach?!
I may not be able to know,
but I want to see you
have some hope in your life.
I'd love to see that…
Mr. Someda.
It's strange, but those words,
they just stuck with me.
I got out of prison two years later.
His words stayed with me the entire time.
Somewhere deep inside me,
that hope Mr. Yamashita
talked about planted itself.
But you know,
having to fight
the cravings was like torture.
I want to see you
have some hope in your life.
A few years after that,
when I'd started a food stall…
Hello there.
Really?
Thank you!
Are you open?
Looking good.
DELICIOUSNESS GUARANTEED
RAMEN
That really hit the spot.
I'm surprised it's actually good.
Is that really a compliment?
-What's with the laugh?
-No, it's just…
I just felt kind of happy
after eating that delicious ramen.
I feel like I'm the younger brother
that has his act together,
and I'm watching
my elder brother trying his best.
That's awfully one-sided of you.
Wow, really? You have a child now?
-How old is she?
-How old are you?
I am five.
-Yeah, she's five.
-Five.
You like ramen?
I like ramen, but I like
curry and fish cakes more.
Right after curry and fish cakes, huh?
She eats a lot so she grows
faster than other children.
That's a good thing.
Mr. Yamashita showed me
the next stage of a family,
that I couldn't experience for myself.
And yet, I said
that I forged Mr. Yamashita's letter
under Tomoya Endo's orders.
I lied.
What?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Komugi.
Wait, but then…
Does that mean the letter…
really was written by Dad?
Why did you lie, Mr. Someda?
Did someone tell you to?
Report Mr. Yamashita's
words and actions to you?
Why would I do that?
This is all to protect Mr. Yamashita.
And not just him.
His daughter might be in danger too.
I'll come again, so let me know then
whether you're willing to cooperate.
No, I--
Hey, wait!
CASTELLA
10 MILLION YEN
Tell me, Mr. Someda!
I can't.
What?
If I do,
you'll be dragged into this.
I think I'll close shop.
Please, let's go to the police again.
I'll come with you!
We'll get Mr. Matsukaze to come too.
The police won't just ignore you
if you have a lawyer present.
Mr. Someda!
I want to…
keep coming here forever!
I want to keep eating your ramen!
I don't want to lose
anything else important to me.
Komugi…
Promise me, Mr. Someda.
Promise me you won't go anywhere.
Okay.
I promise.
Hello.
-Teru.
-Yeah?
-Big news.
-About your glasses again?
What? No.
It's about one of the names
in the letter, Tatsuo Mikita.
What about it?
He was a part of the defense counsel.
-For what?
-The Higashikayama case!
What?
Remember to stay cool!
The office is on the seventh floor here.
Komugi!
I'll wait here.
What?
I have to let the regulars know
the shop's closed today.
-I'll bring Mr. Matsukaze here then.
-Okay.
RIKIRO ENDO'S DEFENCE LAWYER
IN THE HIGASHIYAMA CASE
That's a shocker, isn't it?
Wouldn't have guessed
he defended Rikiro Endo.
What do we do? Take an appointment?
-Quick and cool, that's the rule.
-I'll ignore that, but yeah.
Roger.
-Mr. Matsukaze!
-There she is.
Would you please
come to the police with me?
He lied about forging the letter
at Tomoya Endo's command?
But he couldn't tell me why he did it.
Because it would drag me in.
Is there someone pulling the strings?
-Where's Mr. Someda?
-Down at the entrance.
Komugi, I should tell you
that Kamii gave me a video
of your father talking with Tomoya Endo.
What?
Your father made
a clear statement in the video.
That Rikiro Endo was not the culprit
behind the Higashikayama case.
My guess is that Haruo
knew the truth behind the case.
There's a saying that goes,
"Who saw the peacock dance in the jungle?"
SON OF DEATH ROW INMATE ARRESTED
Right now, our only lead
for getting to the jungle
is Mr. Someda.
Mr. Someda!
Mr. Someda?
-He's not here.
-What?
Wait…
Where did he go?
I'm sorry, Chief.
I followed them to the building
where Matsukaze's office is,
but I lost sight of Someda.
What the hell were you doing?
Go find him.
Find him right now!
Yes, sir!
Hey, wait! Jolly!
Jolly!
-Did you find him?
-No.
KOMUGI
I'm sorry, Komugi.
Urgent message from
Higashikayama North One to the MPD.
We discovered an unconscious elderly man
floating in the Edo River during patrol.
I repeat.
Higashikayama North One to…
-I'm gonna lower it.
-Lowering now.
Mr. Someda, can you hear us?
We're at the hospital.
You'll be fine. Entering now.
If only I had said it back then.
If your son ever decides
to inherit your business,
investing now will benefit him too.
I'll talk it over with my wife first.
If only I could have said it back then.
Listen, it's going to be
tough from now on,
but would you please stay with me?
If only I had said it…
-Look, Satoru.
-Wow, they're eating it. Look.
I'm the happiest man in the world.
What's gotten into you?
If only I could have let them know…
Maybe my life
would have turned out differently.
I'm sorry.
For being a pathetic
elder brother to the end.
Komugi.
I'm sorry.
For not telling you the truth.
I hope you can reach it.
Satoru…
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry…
Time of death, 6:55 p.m.
Mr. Someda…
Where are you?
Someda has died.
Is that so?
It's a shame I won't be able
to eat that ramen anymore.
Was it…
Surely not, right?
Of course not.
That's our only lead.
-Before that lawyer tricks you.
-Have some trust.
-Connected by secrets.
-I'm always watching.
Subtitle translation by: Saim Ul Hassan