Chef and owner of Ristorante, Haneda Ryujiro-san was found murdered in his home.
Police have arrested the delivery driver, Inaba Takahiko, aged 31, as prime suspect.
He is our first client.
Officials report that Inaba's DNA was found...
He has requested you to be his defense attorney.
Me?
We ought to turn him down. No one requesting my help is a decent client.
No, let's take on this case.
It'll do great publicity for us.
♫  Destiny is something  ♫
♫  That is so difficult to find  ♫
♫  But if you are my destiny,  ♫
♫  I call it a miracle  ♫
♫  Here's the love that I long for  ♫
A button left at the scene was found to have your DNA on it.
There's no use denying cold, hard facts.
I will have you prosecuted for theft and murder.
Exercising your right to stay silent?
You wouldn't believe my side of things, even if I spoke.
No one believes me.
Hello there. How have you been?
Horrible. And you, Attorney Miyashita?
I've been well.
Are you truly dating Haruto?
I am not obligated to answer.
I can't believe it's you, of all people.
The sentiment is mine.
I can't believe his ex is someone so attractive.
Please give me an answer.
We're in a relationship.
So you are lying.
I'm telling the truth.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
I'd forgotten to breathe.
How is that remotely possible?
You were upset and told me not to pretend to be your girlfriend before.
I can't have my coworker be a liar now, can I?
Oh my gosh, we'll be late.
We already are!
Why did you request that I become your attorney?
If you wanted to evade court, then–
Because you're the only one who can save me now.
I had often frequented Haneda-san's home as part of my job,
but that reason alone is why I've been suspected of murder.
That's why they've placed me here.
No one has taken my side.
And being here terrifies me.
But I thought you might believe my side of things.
That's why I've requested your help.
I did not kill him.
Tateishi-san, are you doubting me as well?
Tateishi-san. Only you can save me now.
I understand. I will accept your case.
Thank you.
When the incident occurred, I had been eating lunch at a cafe I frequent.
All together now. Happy birthday!
A couple was celebrating a birthday with friends behind me.
I saw they had a cake with candles in it as well.
Everyone, say cheese!
- Oops, it was a video!
- Seriously?
Dude, come on!
The folks around celebrated as well.
I recall everyone was in a jovial mood.
Afterward...
Let's not handle this case.
Why?
His alibi has no solid proof.
The cafe had no security cameras, and he paid in cash.
We can't prove he was ever in that store.
That was the same for my case as well.
Don't let your empathy sway you.
An attorney should be an ally to their client.
This is why I hate attorneys.
- But you're one yourself.
- That's your–
- He may be innocent.
- There's no proof.
If you think clients are innocent, our job is to believe them and do our best.
You already believe him, right?
Yes, I'm an attorney.
That's why I truly hate attorneys.
Our conversation is getting nowhere, no thanks to you.
Why won't you answer my calls?
Ren, are you ignoring me too?
What's up with you two?
Sorry.
I'm being immature.
I know it's my fault, but you share the blame, too, Ren.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
See you around.
If we ever cross paths again, it'll be a coincidence.
I'd like to ask about this individual. He was sitting in that seat, back there.
Was he?
I unfortunately don't recall anyone there.
- Excuse me.
- I'll be right with you.
My apologies.
I thought you might believe my side of things.
Thank you again.
Your son is turning 28 this year?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
You.
How dare you smile without a care?
Do you realize what day it is today?
If my son were alive...
I... I would be celebrating with him.
I would be grasping his hand.
And yet...
Don't smile in my presence ever again.
Sir, I am innocent.
Although I know you won't believe anything I say,
your threats won't change the fact I am innocent.
And your action just now counts as assault. A crime, punishable by law.
Unless a true culprit is found, you will always be guilty.
I will continue to pressure your firm, mark my words.
I've found proof of his alibi.
This couple celebrated a birthday on March 23rd, the day of the incident.
Just as he testified.
This isn't enough to solidify his alibi.
But it's enough to believe his statement.
Did something happen while you were out?
No, nothing at all.
Why won't you talk to me?
I don't wish to bring it up.
Are you all right?
Then I won't press.
It's unfortunate they wouldn't talk.
You were asking the wrong questions.
Not me, but you were, Tateishi-san.
No, you...
Yikes.
Let's run.
It doesn't look like it'll stop any time soon.
It sure doesn't.
Why do you look so happy?
Because it's a beautiful sight.
I hope we win.
Not hope. We will win.
Right.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, thank you.
In an effort to steal Haneda Ryujiro's valuables, the accused murdered him.
He was stabbed several times with a 12 cm long blade
and died instantly due to major blood loss.
The accused then stole three watches and several branded bags, totaling 10 million yen.
Accused, I will now ask about the charges the prosecution has made against you.
Do they speak the truth?
Are there any errors in their statement?
Defense, may we hear your opinion on this matter?
Judge, I believe our accused is innocent.
The accused has no motive to commit this offense.
A murder with theft as the reason needs no motive.
But for that reason to check out,
the theft must have happened.
Valuables have disappeared from the murder site.
There's no proof the accused was involved.
Because these items were not found in his home or his office.
Defense, are you suggesting the accused was not a thief?
Yes, Sir. Our conclusion now relies heavily on this "theft."
But if the accused committed no robbery,
then the reason for this murder falls through completely.
That is all from the Defense.
You played the part of an attorney to a tee.
Of course.
You okay?
I'm fine. I just became a bit dizzy.
Here, grab my arm.
Sorry.
I'm going to say something very immature.
I'm not one to fall ill,
so while this might not be the time, I am a bit jealous of her.
So am I.
I envy the fact he can offer help like that with ease.
Shall we?
Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- Thanks.
Please give us a moment.
- Thanks again.
- Sure.
Are you sure you don't need to see a doctor?
No, some medicine will pick me right back up.
You know that works for me, right?
Let's call it here.
Right.
Wait.
Stay with me a bit longer.
I'm sorry I hurt you back then.
I just wanted you to actually "see" me.
I know I'm in no position to say this.
But I want to stay with you, Haruto.
Maybe I'll clean up a bit.
The place is already spotless.
I'll clean out the fridge instead.
Also spotless.
You're...
no trouble.
Let me hire you.
I'm back.
I thought you weren't ever coming back.
I'm here now.
♫  I do things like listening to your favorite songs like you do  ♫
♫  Or tucking a bookmark into a novel that I don't usually read  ♫
I love you.
♫  The color of my hair and my fashion  ♫
I'm in love with you.
♫  I changed everything for you, to suit you  ♫
♫  The cheesy lines like a drama  ♫
♫  Don't suit me  ♫
♫  But don't laugh at me even if I try to act like a grown-up  ♫
Don't...
♫  Kiss your heart  ♫
Don't fall in love with me.
♫  But you seem close and yet far away  ♫
Why not?
I don't even get a reason?
I must ask you for a favor.
Please hug me, and I'll give you up.
I will return to the way I was, before I ever loved you.
Did something happen between you and Haruto?
Inaba has a criminal record.
You'll defend someone like him?
I only did what I needed to.
Is Miyashita-san currently in a relationship with anyone?
She's quite the wonderful individual.
I think I'll invite her to eat out sometime.
Will I come to regret this decision?
Just five minutes...
Could you stay by my side?