What are you about to do, Bong Hee?
Sentencing.
Let's...
break up.
When...
did you find out?
How about you, Mr. No?
When did you find out...
about my dad?
Recently.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Why did you suffer all alone?
Because it doesn't matter to me.
What doesn't matter to you?
Nothing matters to me.
To me, it's not important
what kind of person...
- your dad was.
- What if it's important to me?
I'm asking you a question.
What if it matters to me?
All right. Let's hear
it out then. Tell me.
I want to know
what matters to you...
and what difference
it's going to make.
It's painful.
What is?
Seeing you suffer because of me...
is hard for me.
Fine. I won't suffer then.
What else?
My dad isn't the kind of a man
you think he is,
but I can't even make that claim.
Okay. Let's think about that.
And what else?
I just don't like this whole
situation we are in.
Don't you get what I'm saying?
I want to break up with you.
Don't try to change
my mind, and just let me go.
I don't like it too.
I don't understand
what you are talking about now.
No matter what you tell me,
I won't ever let you go.
I don't want to.
It won't work even
if you try to stop me.
No matter how hard you try to
stop me, I'm going to leave.
I did well. I did the right thing.
What if I made...
No.
I did the right thing.
Where should I head to?
Who is it?
What's this?
What are you doing here?
Can I sleep over at your house?
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
How did you know where I live?
It's not difficult to find out
someone's home address.
Gosh, I did hear that you
recently moved.
Your place is great.
Let me stay here for a
couple of days.
What are you saying?
What's your problem?
This is breaking and entering.
I know that.
But because of a personal issue,
I don't really have a place to stay.
There's only one room at
my mom's place.
And I've already started to live
independently,
so I can't exactly move back into
her house.
I'm too old to do that, don't you
think?
Yes, you're right.
- No. But...
- See?
But why do you have to stay at
my place?
Hey, this is all I need.
You can sleep in your own bed.
Listen to me. The bed was mine
to begin with,
and this sofa's mine too.
My gosh, this is nice.
Hey.
You...
hate me, don't you?
Yes, I hate you a lot.
The same goes for me.
I really hate you.
Yes, I know that.
But why do you want to stay
at my house?
Go and stay with someone you like.
If I go to someone I like and ask
them if I can stay at their place,
that would be very ill-mannered.
Don't you think so?
I'm glad you know.
It's totally ill-mannered.
Then why do you think I chose to
stay at your place when I hate you?
What?
Hey, are you trying to get revenge?
This is my revenge and
your punishment.
You owe me a lot.
- Hey!
- Shall I list...
all the evil things you did to me?
No.
But you're really useful.
I was very miserable...
and distressed.
After I hurt him,
I was wondering all day...
if I had done the right thing
or not.
I couldn't tell if I was sane
or crazy.
I just really...
wanted to die.
But after seeing you,
I really want to start living again.
It's sort of like a will to fight.
"Even she's still alive, so I should
continue to live as well."
- Hey!
- Don't yell at me.
I'm really sad right now.
This is crazy.
Let's...
never break up, Bong Hee.
Even if I tell you to leave me,
don't leave.
(The Discovery of a Memory)
Hey.
My gosh, you startled me.
Can you put your hand on top of my
forehead and see if I have a fever?
You see, I rarely...
get sick.
But I think I have a fever.
Hang on.
Here.
By the way, Prosecutor Na.
Do you have a car?
Why?
Don't you need a personal driver?
I'm an expert at parking.
I drive really well.
I don't need a driver.
Hey, it says I'm 37째C.
Is this normal?
You're making such a big fuss.
That's pretty normal.
It's only a mild fever.
Really?
Are you sure?
I don't think so.
The meeting time has been
rescheduled to 10:30am.
He wants me to attend the meeting.
So?
He's telling me to come to work...
after all that fuss.
That's good news.
It makes no sense.
How can I go to work like this?
You're really bold...
for someone who has nothing.
- What?
- Don't you get it?
Do you think you'll be able to get
a job at any other companies...
other than that weird and
crazy law firm?
In your dreams.
Just forget about your pride
and go to work.
I don't care about your love life
nor am I interested,
but you'll need money to date anyone
in the first place.
Are you going to continue living
your life...
by relying on other people?
You're like a crazy bedbug. My gosh.
See you.
My gosh.
Follow me.
Did everyone else go somewhere?
Yes.
I came to give you this.
(Letter of Resignation)
To be honest, I was so torn...
about whether I should
submit it or not.
But...
But?
This is the conclusion
I've arrived at.
I apologize.
And thank you for everything.
Agonizing over it
was a total waste of your time.
This is your contract.
It clearly states that...
your contract term is two years.
If you want to leave, you can do so
after the end of your contract.
- But...
- I thought you'd at least know...
to separate personal feelings from
work. Was I expecting too much?
Mr. No.
Let's only talk about work today.
I'm not ready to talk
about what happened between us.
Ms. Eun, do you think this job
is like a joke?
No, not at all.
But the situation is...
I told you to draw the line between
work and personal feelings.
Don't...
give up work so easily.
Your desk over there.
Don't think it's easy
to get that spot.
Don't betray those whom you trust...
and those who have trusted you.
Work-wise,
I'm really sorry.
But it's not easy to go on
with work as if nothing happened...
in a situation like this.
It won't be easy for you either.
Every time you see me,
you'll think about your father.
And every time that happens, you'll
feel guilty toward him and me.
It'll cause you pain.
- So?
- So...
I'm telling you that is the reason
I'm quitting.
No, you're overstepping
your boundaries right now.
That's my problem, and I'll figure
out what to do. So you should...
only worry...
about your problem.
All right, let's do this.
I'll let you go on vacation.
Try to think rationally while
you're taking some time off.
I'll do some thinking too.
That's the most compromise
I can make.
What's your answer?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Get going, then.
(Letter of Resignation)
(Sunho District Prosecutor's Office)
I came to see you because
there's something I want to know...
about the arson case
that killed my parents.
I saw that you were the prosecutor
in charge of the case.
Yes, I was.
I wanted to figure it out on my own,
but it happened a long time ago.
And most of the records
have been lost as well,
so I thought I should
come and see you in person.
What is it that you want to ask me?
I'll be straightforward with you.
Why were my parents...
murdered?
I thought you'd know that much.
It was a revenge murder to retaliate
for getting prosecuted.
Right, but I really don't understand
that part.
At the time, the suspect,
Eun Man Soo,
was only involved
in a small assault case.
Logically, I cannot understand
why he had to get back...
at the prosecutor for being charged.
How would I know the reason?
What I know is the fact that he kept
complaining to the prosecution.
Then one day, he was found
as a dead body at the arson scene.
If that was the case,
how could you conclude
that he was the culprit?
Were there any additional
clues or pieces of evidence?
It was because of you.
Pardon me?
Can you recognize him?
This man is the one who...
killed your mom and dad. Okay?
You pegged him as the culprit.
You said yourself
that he started the fire...
and that he killed your parents.
I...
I said that?
Has your curiosity been answered?
It was because of you.
You pegged him as the culprit.
What on earth...
did I see?
Gosh, you scared me.
Hey!
Shall I watch it just once?
Why isn't it working?
Bong Hee, you're taking
a video right now.
Oh, really?
Look at that face. That was funny.
Why isn't it working?
Bong Hee, you're taking
a video right now.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Just once more.
Bong Hee, you're taking
a video right now.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Where are we with the divorce suit
of Kim Young Eun?
Well, we can't seem
to come to an agreement.
This week, we are going to ask for a
settlement and property division.
- Next...
- Did you two...
fight?
Did you guys break up?
Gosh, I'm not sure if he can
ever take a hint or not.
He probably can't.
I mean...
It's not likely...
that Ms. Lack of Evidence would
go on vacation by herself.
- Aren't I right?
- You are right.
So I'd like you to go
on vacation too.
Please use your vacation days.
It'd be better if your leave
of absence is long.
What do you think?
I'll stop talking.
I have no place to go.
We should use repeated assaults
in terms of the labor law.
That's right. I agree too.
What about Jung Hyun Soo?
Is he getting better?
I visited him yesterday,
but he's not getting any better.
The doctor didn't say much either.
- I see.
- You are not going to...
make up with Ms. Lack of Evidence?
How pathetic.
I raised you wrong.
Darn it.
I'll make sure he uses
his vacation days.
Please.
For his long leave of absence.
It's 37째C.
This falls in the normal range.
Hey, Bong Hee.
Are you going to sleep all day long?
Wake up. Or I'll kick you out.
Hey.
Hey, dummy.
What?
What's happening?
Was this broken?
Hey, Bong Hee.
Hey, hey. Wake up.
Hey.
Bong Hee.
Prosecutor Na.
Hey.
How's Ms. Eun?
Over there. Her temperature
hiked up as high as 40째C.
Bong Hee.
I wish this wasn't a dream.
No, it's not a dream.
Does it not suit your taste?
Well...
It's not bad, but...
The owner of this restaurant
is known to be a great cook.
Everyone has a different taste,
you know.
For goodness' sake.
How can your son
be nothing like you?
What are you talking about?
When he was a kid,
people used to tell me...
that he and I look exactly the same.
Whenever I went out with him,
more than a dozen people
said that to me.
Please only speak the truth.
You went too far with that one.
From his looks to his personality,
I don't know how you can have
a son like him.
Gosh, did you find him
on the streets somewhere or what?
No, I didn't.
I'm not his birth mom,
but I raised him with my heart.
Are we good now?
I'm really sorry.
I was just kidding.
My mouth got the best of me.
I sincerely apologize.
Gosh, I wish you didn't apologize.
I can't even get mad at you now.
Whether you're his birth mother
or not...
doesn't change anything.
Every mother cherishes her child...
equally.
Of course.
Do you drink soju?
I usually drink wine.
I'm trying my best
to become friends with her,
but we're so different.
I know, right?
But I do feel bad for her
at the same time.
She's actually tender-hearted.
As your future mother-in-law,
she's...
not too bad.
Goodness.
Mom, what are you talking about?
Don't you worry.
I'll be sure to train her,
so you should...
just keep your grip on Mr. No.
Mom, the thing is...
Actually...
What is it?
Just a second.
Hello?
Sorry? A police station?
She's an attorney.
Me?
Hello.
He said his taekwondo instructor
is an attorney. It was true.
Yes.
So to summarize it,
he witnessed a murder incident,
and he is...
the only witness.
That's what you're saying, right?
Show her the CCTV footage.
Yes, sir.
I'll have a look.
You saw the murderer's
whole face, didn't you?
But why won't you tell us?
It's all right. You can tell them.
He said he's pleading the Fifth.
Hey, you. Stop watching TV.
It's not that. I really don't
remember his face.
Ms. Eun.
Ms. Eun!
Hey, you!
You, Ms. Lack of Evidence.
Who told you that you can
take a leave of absence?
I'm sorry.
But who is the kid?
Is he a kid?
Come on. Everyone can
see he's a kid.
Whose kid is he?
Who are you?
Well, he is...
Mom.
"Mom"?
My dad passed away.
I live with an ugly aunt and uncle.
I'm a poor kid
just like Harry Potter.
Why don't you tell
them your name first?
My name is Kim Jae Hong.
Hi, Jae Hong.
She's my attorney.
Well, that's...
It sort of just happened.
He witnessed a murder?
This is what happened.
How dare you lie to us?
You're too young for that.
I don't like him.
But I can understand you.
Hey, you. Take your leave
of absence again. Go!
Mr. Byun, you should be the
one taking the leave of absence.
Jae Hong asked if there were snacks,
ice cream, or anything to eat.
He's just like someone I know.
It's been a while, right?
Has it been a while?
Have you been well?
Yes.
Are you really all right?
Of course.
It was nothing to me. You know
how healthy I am.
Right.
Thank you.
I see. Yes.
Then we will take care
of him for a while.
No, we will visit you.
Okay. Bye.
I told you so. My aunt doesn't
care about me.
Then he can stay with me
until we take care of his statement.
Oh, right.
You should just stay
at your aunt's house.
I'm living off someone for now. I do
not think I can take you. I'm sorry.
What about Mr. Byun or Mr. Ji?
Mr. Byun went golfing
and Mr. Ji has a trial.
Gosh.
I can't leave this little kid alone
since he's a witness.
I am not little.
Whom are you trying to fool?
Just have your snacks.
What should we do?
Let's do this.
Let's send him to either
Mr. Byun or Mr. Ji's house.
He's too little to...
Leave already.
Go.
Hey.
Listen carefully.
We are on the 1st floor, and the
floor above here is the 2nd floor.
You can't ever set foot
on the second floor.
Don't come upstairs or talk to me.
Don't ask me to do stuff
for you or walk around on your own.
Just don't do anything.
You should just think...
and stay by yourself.
Make your statement and
leave as fast as you can.
Okay?
Aren't you thankful that
I'm giving you a ride?
I'm thankful, and I like it.
Look at you. You look great now
that you're smiling and not sick.
I rarely get sick though.
You rarely get sick, yet your
temperature was as high as 40째C?
Oh, no. You are right.
How did you know that?
I was at the hospital.
Wait. I don't remember seeing you.
I guess you don't remember
as your temperature soared.
I see. You came to the hospital.
Hold on.
Did he...
Yes, I went there with Ji Wook.
No way.
No. What?
What is it?
Unbelievable.
Why?
I had a dream.
Wait a second. This was a dream.
This has to be a dream.
Oh, no! That wasn't a dream.
Ms. Eun, what's wrong? What is it?
After that...
It's been a while, right?
Has it been a while?
Have you been well?
Oh, dear. I can't believe it.
What? What is so unbelievable?
I'm really curious.
After I dumped him,
I did that to him.
I even told him that I hadn't seen
him for a while so brazenly.
No.
I should just die. I should.
Ms. Eun, Ms. Eun!
I'm sorry.
If you are truly sorry, stop it.
We might end up in an accident.
Okay.
Hey!
Didn't I tell you not to come
upstairs?
Go back down.
What? What are you doing?
Don't come near me.
Hey, back off. Go away.
What?
Hey.
What did you see? Tell me.
What was it that made you...
come upstairs and into my room?
It's because...
I had a nightmare.
You're just a little kid.
You shouldn't be having...
nightmares already.
If I don't testify,
will it be impossible to catch
the culprit?
And if the culprit doesn't get
caught because I don't testify,
will that be my fault?
It's all your fault.
You need to testify in order for us
to find the culprit.
If the culprit doesn't get caught,
it's all your fault.
You just need to tell me what
you saw.
You already know what you saw.
Right?
Mister?
Yes.
No.
You don't need to testify.
Just do what you want.
It doesn't matter whether you
testify or not.
Nothing will be your fault.
Okay?
Hey, Detective Park.
Jae Hong says he can't remember
anything,
so there's nothing much I can do.
Okay. I'll try talking to him.
But don't get your hopes up.
Okay. Okay, bye.
I told him to wait in front of the
school gate.
Hey, guys. Are you guys in
first grade?
Are you in the same class as
Jae Hong in class number three?
- No, we don't know him.
- We don't know him.
Okay, thanks.
Where is he?
What's wrong?
Is someone chasing after you?
Hey, Jae Hong!
I told you to wait for me in front
of the school gate. Where were you?
Come here. Did you get hurt?
Hello.
I just talked to Detective Park
just now.
Detective Park can be quite
stubborn.
Yes. Jae Hong can't remember
anything,
but he keeps forcing things,
which made me feel uneasy.
It's okay.
You don't need to testify
if it's too pressuring.
You know that, right?
I can't testify anyway because
I don't remember anything.
Are you okay?
By any chance,
are you...
and Ms. Eun...
Hey.
Don't laugh.
I said, don't laugh.
You little... Hey, what do you know?
Stop laughing.
Don't laugh.
I'm not kidding.
Are you going to keep laughing?
Why?
Did you have a nightmare again?
My gosh, it's okay.
It's okay.
It hurts.
Okay.
What if...
the culprit...
comes to kill me?
No, it won't happen.
That will never happen.
I don't know.
I don't know who the culprit is.
And I don't know if I should
testify...
or not.
I'll make sure...
you're safe regardless of whatever
choice you decide to make.
But there's one thing you need to
know.
If you just put a seal on this
problem without solving it,
these nightmares might...
continue to haunt you...
even when you grow old and
become an adult.
I'm going to testify.
Hello.
Hey, did you remember anything?
Are you here to testify?
Yes, apparently. What a good boy.
What a rude boy.
- At the supermarket...
- Yes?
Jae Hong, you're here to testify.
You can tell us what you saw.
It's okay.
It was him.
Me?
Why are you doing this to me?
Everyone knows my ringtone.
Stop joking around.
Those shoes.
There was blood on them.
I said, I didn't do it.
Why don't you believe me?
Hey, why are you doing this to me?
Let go. Gosh, I really didn't do it.
Now, we just have to organize
your statement.
You did well.
I'm not sure.
I don't remember who it was.
I don't know.
It was that man.
He's the culprit.
What are...
these two contrasting memories
that popped into my head?
Which one...
is the truth?
Well, Mr. Bang.
Something urgent has come up.
Please take care of the rest for me.
Sure, no problem.
Sorry. Don't be scared.
Mr. Bang is here with you.
Don't worry, okay?
- Please take good care of him.
- Okay.
Can you recognize him?
This man is the one who...
killed your mom and dad.
Okay?
This man is the one who
killed your mom and dad.
He killed your mom.
I don't remember who it was.
I don't know.
Yes, Mr. Bang.
Yes, he's still the same.
The doctor said there's been
no improvement.
Right.
Yes, okay.
All right.
(Love in Trouble)