I've experienced a painful end, numerous times now.
That was why I was terrified to start anything with you.
So when I realized my feelings for you...
I chose to run from them.
Don't... Don't fall in love with me.
But I was only making a futile effort.
Because I had already been drawn to you, long before I even knew.
Let me hire you.
The one thing I know now...
is that the inevitable has finally begun.
♫  Destiny is something  ♫
♫  That is so difficult to find  ♫
♫  But if you are my destiny,  ♫
♫  I call it a miracle  ♫
♫  Here's the love that I long for  ♫
I was about to knock.
And I was on my way to the living room.
I see.
Delicious.
I want to talk about what happened earlier.
I know it was an accident.
Don't worry; it doesn't bother me.
But... it bothers me.
I've already decided to move on from you, Tateishi-san.
I won't expect anything from this kind of accident.
It'd only hurt more if I did.
I'm perfectly happy with our current situation.
So I want to keep our relationship as it is.
Night.
Could I have a minute?
You had your time to monologue last night.
Now it's my turn.
Your turn?
I've come to realize my feelings far too late.
During that time, I had convinced you to move on,
and I'll respect your decision.
I won't ask you
to give me another chance.
But I want you to respect how I feel as well.
Don't take away my freedom
to think of you.
We can continue our life here together.
And if you ever have a change of heart, please give me that second chance.
Did you forget to breathe again?
I'll be waiting, so take all the time you need.
Then you'll be waiting your whole life.
I've already endured so much suffering.
You've lost your chance.
I'm sorry.
Just continue to wait.
Be prepared to wait for me until you die.
I got it.
Haruto, can you turn on the news now?
Earlier this morning, Momoi Yuma-san was found dead in Fujikita-cho.
He was found with a weapon police believe was used to murder Haneda Ryujiro-san.
But that's not all.
Momoi had a piece of paper with an address on him.
It was for the building next to Miyashita-san's old apartment.
Police found a body in the water tank there.
A body?
After some investigating,
the body is believed to be from March of 2023.
Which happens to be around the time Aoki Sota was killed.
I'll call again if anything new appears.
This is all too calculated.
Almost as if someone planned this all along.
But whom?
Sakura.
"Sakura"?
Could you stay within my sight, 24 hours a day?
What?
I meant nothing weird by it.
So bitter.
You're the one who bought it.
Oh, that tea.
It truly is bitter,
but I drink it every day.
How long have you suffered from insomnia?
Since I was a child.
It began when I lost my parents in a house fire.
I haven't had a good night's rest since.
I also lost my father when I was young.
You did?
But I'll save my story for another day.
Sure.
That is so bitter.
Sakura-san!
Sorry for rushing in like that...
- Are you all right?
- Yes, thank you.
What brings you here, Inaba-san?
Did anything break?
No, it's working just fine.
Well, see you.
Breathe and think carefully.
You're the only one who can save me now.
He bought my empathy and strategically got close to me.
He wanted to see if I would catch on.
If my hypothesis is true...
I declare the accused not guilty.
Then I've helped the culprit himself.
I made Tateishi-san stand up for a murderer.
I told you not to leave the house without me.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Sakura.
Could you already fall in love with me?
I know I promised to wait.
I'm sorry.
But I want you to fall for me right now.
Did something happen?
I'm just tired.
Is this about Inaba?
I heard that song playing from Inaba-san's phone.
Maybe, Inaba-san is...
He might be the true culprit.
Did you already notice?
I did.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I wasn't sure then.
Tateishi-san, I've caused you trouble again...
You don't need to worry about that.
- Still...
- I'll overcome this hardship together with you, Sakura.
Even if you choose to shove me aside.
I won't let that bastard get away with this.
In any case, the choice is yours, Sakura.
Do you want to overcome this together or on our own?
I want to overcome this hardship together with you.
The choice is yours, Sakura.
Do you want to overcome this together or on our own?
Tateishi-san.
I have something very important to tell you.
What is it?
From now on, I've decided to be true to myself and live as I wish.
So let's call this day one.
That's all.
Day one? What are you talking about?
Let's start dating from today. This will mark our first day together.
So that's what she meant.
Day one...
My girlfriend...
- Oranges?
- Yes, please.
♫  I do things like listening to your favorite songs like you do  ♫
♫  Or tucking a bookmark into a novel that I don't usually read  ♫
♫  The color of my hair and my fashion  ♫
♫  I changed everything for you, to suit you  ♫
That's all for day one.
♫  The cheesy lines like a drama  ♫
♫  Don't suit me  ♫
She's a worthy opponent.
♫  All I wanna do is kiss your heart  ♫
♫  I want you more  ♫
Did something good happen?
No.
- Something definitely happened.
- Nope.
- I'm right, aren't I?
- No.
Oh, right. We found a picture of Momoi from high school, Sir.
Momoi was Haneda Ryujiro's classmate and good friend.
Who are the other two?
Tabata Masashi and Shimano Daisuke.
Tabata has been radio silent for a while now.
- Hello?
- We've identified the body found in the water tank.
- The victim was Tabataー
- Masahi.
You knew?
I do now.
So when did he go missing?
Momoi went missing after he contacted us to share information.
And his senpai from high school, Tabata Masashi turned up as a dead body.
When did Tabata go radio silent?
The day Aoki Sota was found dead in Miyashita's apartment.
Are these two incidents tied to one another?
I'll look into this "Shimano."
Please do. I'll investigate more on Inaba's acquaintances.
I'll join you.
No, you won't. Messing with Inaba any further is too dangerous.
You stay here, Sakura.
Yes, Sir.
"Sakura"?
Hello?
Yes.
I see.
I'll try heading there right away.
The individual you have called is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
We've tracked down Shimano's location.
He returned from the United States earlier today.
We have to take action before Inaba finds him.
I'll send Shimano's address your way.
Thank you again.
Long time no see, Shimano.
Can you hear me, Yoneda-san?
Yoneda-san?
Yoneda-san, are you there?
Yoneda-san!
Yoneda-san! Yoneda-san!
For now, we prepare.
I'm about to say something crucial so listen well. I killed him.
Why are you doing this?
Could you please leave me alone already?
Haruto bought time for us.
Who's this?
I need to ask you for a favor.
You'll owe me one.
Why did you do something so rash?
Want to go on a date tomorrow?
A date?
It'll be our first date.