Some love begins...
without the owner of the heart
realizing that one's love has begun.
Just like the spring breeze
and moist rain drops,
our hearts slowly get soaked with
love whether we realize or not.
Love gets into our heart.
When I realized it, he took a corner
of my heart all of a sudden.
- Is this all true?
- Are you the murderer?
Do you admit the charge?
How do you feel now?
- Please give us a comment.
- Share a word.
- What was your motive?
- Please answer our questions.
Some say for one to fall in love,
0.2 second is more than enough.
The time I needed to fall in love...
It was only 0.2 second.
It's the love you fall in love
at first sight.
(Sunho District Prosecutor's Office)
This is why I'm going
to confess my love.
I'll confess that I love him.
You are the only present
I can move forward to,
my only love, and my destiny.
I think that we...
met by fate.
I also think you're my destiny...
An ill-fated encounter.
So...
let's never cross paths again.
Hey, Bong Hee.
I wanted to give you this.
What is this?
This tea is good for insomnia.
How did you know
that I have insomnia?
For about two months,
I used to work for you as...
your trainee prosecutor.
I was bound to find out.
Believe it or not,
I know you quite well.
I didn't delve into your private
life or pry on you. Don't worry.
By the way, considering how you
can't sleep, you don't look tired...
or have dark circles.
Did you know that?
At a glance, people might think
you sleep like a baby at night.
It makes me realize the importance
of skin once again,
and I'm rambling on, aren't I?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
You must be, but go on...
whether you want to ramble on
or have something to say.
This will be the last time anyway.
Last time...
There are so many things
I'm sorry about.
I mistook you for a pervert before.
Because of me,
you were fired from your position.
I'm sorry for everything.
Okay.
And I'd like to thank you too.
To me, you are a hero,
Prosecutor No.
I won't swap you for Iron Man.
Really?
Yes.
And...
I like you.
And?
And... What was it?
Oh, right. The real culprit.
I think I ran into the real culprit.
What?
But you don't have to worry
about that.
From now on, I won't be bother
or harm you in any way.
I will take care of this on my own.
You lost your job because of me.
It doesn't matter
if I lost my job or not.
You should've told me
if you saw the real culprit.
Well... I wasn't completely certain.
What are you not certain about?
Well...
We sort of met through a song.
A song?
The sound of the whistle I heard
on the night of Hee Jun's murder.
I also heard it in court.
I believe that
the real culprit came to my trial.
The whistle...
What kind of song was it?
Gosh.
Is this music from an unknown
world?
How should I put it?
This is quite unique.
Repeat it again.
Again?
Yes.
Gosh, this is bitter.
Gosh, this isn't good.
This is bitter and not tasty.
Hey, stop it. That's enough.
Stop with this odd melody.
What does he look like? Did you see
his face? How old does he look?
- Well...
- Yes?
I won't accept your help again.
- What?
- You went through a lot for me.
I will take care of this on my own.
You don't have to worry about that.
I wasn't worried about you.
I was just curious.
Goodness. Bong Hee,
you don't know anything.
Seriously, this is so bitter.
You eat, sleep, and breathe...
in a place where my son was
murdered. You are alive and well.
How dare you be alive?
I'm also heartbroken...
about what happened to your son.
I really mean it.
However,
I really didn't do it.
I know that you don't believe me,
but that doesn't mean...
I can admit something I didn't do.
I didn't find any evidence that
proves you didn't murder my son.
With all due respect,
there is no evidence
that I murdered him.
There is.
Only if No Ji Wook didn't
mess up the trial,
you would have been in prison
serving time for your crime.
That evidence...
was fabricated.
What?
Please forgive me...
for saying this.
However,
the prosecution has
to prove my guilt.
According to presumption
of innocence, I'm innocent.
If you believe that I'm guilty,
the prosecution ought
to prove that.
There is no responsibility
on my side...
to prove that I'm innocent,
but...
I'm going to prove my innocence.
I'll do it for myself,
Prosecutor No,
and my mom.
I will...
catch the real culprit for you
and Hee Jun. I'll make sure...
I don't know
how you won my son's heart...
with what kind of means
or abilities.
I was wondering how you put
No Ji Wook under your spell...
to get you out and regain
your freedom so brazenly.
I get it now.
Now I know that
you aren't a typical girl.
- District Attorney.
- However,
you are going to regret
acquiring your freedom again.
I'm going to catch you
by all means.
I'm definitely going
to punish you.
As long as you and I are alive,
I'm going to make you suffer,
and I won't forget to punish you.
(Late No Young Suk)
Dad.
I resigned.
(Late No Young Suk)
Before I could even solve
the last case as a prosecutor,
I quit.
What? You want to be like me?
Yes, when I grow up,
I'm going to be just like you.
My goodness, what an honor.
There is no greater honor than a son
wishing to be just like his father.
I'm sorry that...
I failed to become like you.
I'm sorry for...
not keeping my promise.
(Attorney No Ji Wook,
Attorney Ji Eun Hyuk)
Welcome, No Ji Wook!
My gosh.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm sincerely welcoming you
because I really like you.
Get lost.
No, wait.
What? Tell me anything you need.
I told someone that we have
an ill-fated relationship.
You did? To whom?
- Just listen.
- Okay, I will.
It's fine as long as
I'm not the one.
You're the worst one ever.
I already hate you.
My gosh.
Anyway, after I said we have
an ill-fated relationship,
I told that person to never show up
in front of me. But the thing is,
I need to ask that person something.
So if I contact that person first...
Come on. That'd be humiliating.
- Do you think so?
- Of course.
That'll make you seem very light.
But it'd be nice.
If it were me, I'd like it. I'd be
more touched and excited...
if someone called me after
saying that they won't.
That's how I felt when you
contacted me first.
The less you expect,
the bigger the surprise.
Get lost.
That's what I'm talking about.
You say that and then call me again.
It makes me have butterflies
in my stomach.
Hey.
Just because I act like
nothing happened,
don't get delusional and
actually think that way, Eun Hyuk.
Okay.
- Please disappear.
- But Ji Wook...
This is also my office.
This is your desk. That's my desk.
Where should I disappear to?
Bong Hee.
Do you want to eat lunch with us?
- Hey, stop it.
- Hey.
You can't ask her.
Let's go.
I decided to listen to all the music
in the world...
until I find the source of
that melody.
I even sent a message to
the culprit.
I let him know that
I was looking for him,
so he should come find me.
Hey, culprit.
Let's have a
head-to-head battle.
This is the only place the culprit
left a trace.
Where did the culprit go after that?
No way.
I heard culprits return to
the crime scene.
Bong Hee?
Mr. No?
You scared me. Why didn't you
tell me who you were?
You didn't ask me.
How could you not reveal yourself
at such a shady place like this?
Then am I supposed to
say my name out loud while I walk...
when nobody even asked me
who I am?
It's a shady place.
I mistook you as the culprit.
You're the one who came here
alone at this hour.
I was looking for criminal evidence.
Are you worrying about me?
No. Of course not.
Of course, you wouldn't.
My gosh.
Why did you come here, Mr. No?
The fact that a
competent prosecutor like me...
failed to solve his
last case felt...
How should I put it?
It hurt my pride and made
me feel uncomfortable.
I see.
I'll help you restore your pride by
finding the source of that melody...
Forget that. I'll give you the
CCTV footage of the court.
So check the culprit's face and...
I never saw his face.
You said you saw him.
I did, but I told you that...
I met him through a song.
He passed me by on a bicycle, and
in court, I only heard the melody.
What?
Don't ever say the
word "melody" again.
Why are you getting angry?
Okay, fine.
What did the bicycle look like?
What kind of bicycle was it?
What does it look like?
All bicycles look alike.
They have two wheels.
I didn't know that there was
a difference.
My goodness, I had no idea.
I thought you had a clue
or something.
I was so curious to know
what that was.
Because of that, my insomnia
got worse, and I couldn't work.
I even sacrificed my face
and came here.
My gosh, Bong Hee.
That's why I said
I'll solve this on my own.
How are you going to solve it?
Tell me how!
Coming here at this hour?
You're making me think that
you're worried about me.
You're right.
Does that mean you're not mad
at me anymore?
You told me to get lost and said
we have an ill-fated relationship.
So I thought I'd never get to
see you again.
That's true too.
Sorry?
As someone who was
your mentor and guardian...
for two months,
I did worry about you
quite a lot. But...
it ends here.
I'm not worried about you anymore.
So please don't cause trouble...
and live safely.
I'm really going to find a clue.
I'm going to find the culprit.
I might visit you after that.
That's okay, right?
I'm going to become successful,
and I'm going to repay you.
I'm going to change
our relationship...
from an ill-fated one to a good one.
(Interpretation of a Juristic Act)
I lived a diligent life.
And sometimes,
when I had a tough time...
I'm so happy.
Congratulations on getting
appointed. I'm so jealous.
Why are you jealous? I'm not
the only one who got appointed.
You all have been scouted
to a law firm too.
All of us did pretty well.
Except for someone.
From time to time when I felt
like life was suffocating me,
I took a little break...
by peeking at you.
Okay.
That way. Yes, good.
Pull it a bit more towards you.
Okay!
Let's secure it now.
Go ahead and secure it.
(Looking for a witness)
Okay, okay. I think it's good.
Thank you for your help.
I got it done easily thanks to you.
Are you the witness by any chance?
Are you going to call the police?
Thanks anyway.
(Please call this number.)
(Add to contacts)
(Restraining Order)
Goodness, this is...
Well...
I get that the injured party
isn't budging about settling,
but you can't threaten him
like that.
A sincere apology and
self-reflection should come first.
Of course, he won't accept your
apology, but that doesn't mean...
We're a victim in this too,
Attorney No.
Think about it. Why are they
turning it into such a big deal?
He just punched him a couple
of times.
Why are they treating him
like a brutal criminal?
Don't make it sound like
they just tussled. Look at this.
He's been instigating the bullying.
He's in for confinement and group
assault as well.
The victim was released
from the ICU only recently.
He deserved to get beaten up.
Be quiet.
He's saying that guy deserved it.
He should've behaved himself
to begin with.
Everyone loses it
when someone gets on their nerves.
Aren't I right?
We're not asking him to settle
for free.
I offered to pay his hospital bill
and all. He said, "It's not enough."
They obviously want more money.
I get that they're poor,
but how can they try to make money
off of their injured son?
Anyway, my son's future
is in your hands.
Please make sure he gets suspension
of prosecution or sentence.
Okay, let's say we can get out of
this. But what about the next time?
After his upcoming birthday, he'll
no longer be considered a minor.
What do you mean...
I'm a lot more experienced
than I seem.
I passed the exam very young.
I mean, I passed the bar exam
before I even graduated.
What a show-off.
Yes, I'm showing off.
Because I have a lot of experience
as a prosecutor, I've seen jerks...
I mean,
I've seen many boys like you.
Hey, isn't this your third case?
I see here that you almost raped
a girl and threatened her...
- with money to get out of it.
- That girl was a gold digger.
Right, of course. I'm sure
he's never done anything wrong.
- It must be everyone else's fault.
- Goodness.
You've been backing him up with your
money and connections all along,
and you'll continue to do so.
He's never had to reflect on
or think about what he's done wrong,
and it'll be the same in the future.
And your son will...
continue to commit bad deeds without
even realizing that they're crimes.
If he gets in huge trouble
that can't be sorted out,
you'll send him to a school abroad.
Then he'll get into drugs...
and won't even be able to graduate.
After that, he'll return to Korea...
and exercise violence against those
who are poorer and weaker than him.
Then he'll pay
his way out of it again.
Hey, everything will be okay. Your
mom will take care of everything.
Ma'am, you'll have to make sure you
live longer than your son does...
because you'll have to clean up
after his mess all your life.
For goodness' sake!
Money take cares of everything.
What an amazing world we live in.
Well, you know.
I'm just saying.
That's how the world is.
Shall we...
start over from the beginning...
with a refreshed mindset?
Let's start from "a sincere apology
and self-reflection".
Attorney No!
You're no longer a prosecutor.
You're an attorney now.
It's already been two years since
you gave up your prosecutor badge.
Why are you still
acting like a prosecutor?
Who are you to demand
self-reflection from your client?
Look at you. "I won't listen."
"You can talk all you want."
Is that what you're thinking now?
No, that's not really
what I'm thinking.
You should reflect on yourself.
Don't just demand it
from your client.
It looks like
you should do it first.
My life motto is,
"Don't ever regret."
But I'm starting to regret...
bringing you here.
Good grief.
(Sunho District Prosecutor's Office)
(Prosecutor No Ji Wook)
(Prosecutor Woo Myung Sik)
(Power saving)
Let's go for food.
I'm busy.
Let's eat. Come on.
(I'm busy.)
I think the food at Goyang Branch
of the District Court is the best.
Then you should eat there.
Why do you come here every day?
I can't go all the way to Ilsan
just to eat...
You have a lot of time on your hands
because you don't have much work.
Aren't I right, Prosecutor No?
I mean, Attorney No.
I heard you had a team dinner
two days ago.
Guys,
have you watched the move,
"The Devil's Advocate"?
In that movie,
an attorney...
sells his soul to a devil.
You see, it shows that some of us
are even willing...
to defend a devil
for wealth and fame.
How should I put this?
I think that movie...
captured the nature of attorneys
very precisely.
Anyway, I hate attorneys so much.
Even devils have the right
to be defended.
All of us here, including me,
are attorneys.
Mr. No. We rarely get to have
everyone gathered like this...
for a company dinner.
Ji Wook made the rare
company dinner even more special.
Hey, you're really...
Don't be ridiculous.
Let go, you punk.
Why are there so many
attorneys in this world?
You used to criticize prosecutors
so much when you were a prosecutor.
Now that you're an attorney, you
talk ill of attorneys all the time.
I bet there are countless ridiculous
stories you can share with me.
Prosecutor No. I mean, Attorney No.
Isn't this a bit too salty? I prefer
foods that are low in sodium.
Chameleons, lizards, and octopus.
Even those creatures change colors
to blend in with their surroundings.
You should at least be on par
with them if you can't surpass them.
For goodness' sake!
I'm really not cut out for it!
I like convicting criminals. I hate
having to defend people so much.
Gosh, I absolutely hate it.
When I was about 5 or 6 years old,
I realized, "I have to do things I
don't want to do at times in life."
That's when I learned it.
Goodness.
Don't worry so much, Mr. Bang.
You get hammered down
when you're prickly.
I'm trying to toughen him up.
Right?
But he'll never become rounded
no matter how much he gets beaten.
Don't you find his consistency
so charming?
I am very consistent.
I've been hating you
so much consistently.
Where are you going?
Isn't he so consistently mean?
Which one of you?
Gosh, you just hurt my feelings.
He's doing that a lot these days.
He's just lonely from
being an outcast for a long time.
He talks to the walls
because he has no one to talk to.
I never even run into the one
I miss so much,
but I keep bumping into my enemy
in this hallway.
What are you talking about?
You don't even get to come here
often because you have no work.
I'm saying I see you
every time I come here.
You have bad comprehension.
You're so...
You look so bad.
I get that you're broke, but you
should still try to be presentable.
You have horrible sense of fashion.
It's okay. My clothes are cheap,
but so what?
My soul and body are so classy.
They can make up for everything.
Your heels are about
to turn into flats.
I saw your heel dangling
when you were walking.
It's fixed.
Are we good now?
We sure are.
The CCTV footage from the scene
which the prosecution submitted...
as evidence can't be used to confirm
the identity of the defendant...
Also, seeing that no crucial
evidence such as...
fingerprints or footprints
were found at the crime scene...
The defendant is guilty.
He is guilty, Your Honor.
You're saying that he's guilty?
Did I say that?
You must be mistaken.
The defendant is not guilty.
He's innocent.
Next.
Case number 2017-G-66390.
I'm so embarrassed.
The defendant admits to his mistake.
He's sincerely regretting
what he did wrong.
He also did his best to
settle things with the victim,
and they succeeded in reaching
an agreement.
He has a family to take care of...
and no previous criminal records
of the same... Okay.
I'm sorry.
He has no...
He has no previous criminal records.
Please take that into notice,
Your Honor.
(Attorney, Defendant)
Mr. Ji?
It's been so long.
Have you been doing well, Ms. Eun?
Thanks to you, I'm still alive.
How have you been doing?
I'm also still alive, thanks to you.
You must've been peeking at Ji Wook.
Peeking?
- I was just looking.
- Hey.
Ji Wook's coming out now.
I'll be right back.
Hi, Ji Wook.
Gosh, you can at least say hello.
No.
I love you nonetheless.
I love you,
Ji Wook.
How pretty.
(Shoe repair shop)
Hello, I'm Attorney Eun Bong Hee
who's always ready to...
go and meet you wherever you are.
Yes.
In 30 minutes?
Okay.
Okay. I'll see you in 30 minutes.
Sir, can I have my shoes back?
I just started repairing them.
Here.
My goodness.
What should I do?
Should I wear these?
No, I can't do that.
Okay.
Hey, Ji Hye.
Hey.
Where did she suddenly come from?
Don't come near me.
What are you doing?
How pretty. Your feet must be 240mm.
So?
- What?
- Here. Wear these. There you go.
Just think of this as a small
payment...
for always being...
so mean to me.
My shoes are over there.
Sir, give her the repaired shoes.
- Who's going to pay?
- She'll pay.
Hey, you crazy wench!
I hope this client is
a normal person.
I really hope so.
Please be a normal person.
Up until now,
90 percent of all my clients...
were not normal.
(Attorney Eun Bong Hee)
I want to...
kill my husband.
But I don't know how.
I heard that you succeeded in...
killing your boyfriend.
There's so much evidence saying that
you're the one who committed murder.
How am I supposed to
prove that you're innocent?
I know you have your ways.
You know how to get away
with murder.
I'm not a professional killer.
I met these kinds of people.
My gosh.
My goodness.
Let's put these away.
It's good, right?
So please let this one be
a normal client.
(Eun Bong Hee Law Firm)
Yes, come in.
I am...
a so-called stalker.
There was a woman I loved.
We both liked each other very much.
The story he told me from then on...
was very similar to mine.
Just like how I did,
he also fell in love at first sight.
Let's talk, Na Eun.
Don't ever show up again.
- Na Eun.
- Just like me,
- he also had to disappear.
- Hey!
But again, just like me,
he kept wandering around her,
and in the end...
I received a restraining order.
After that, I haven't seen her
for a year and a half.
Then suddenly, yesterday...
It was really a coincidence.
We both pretended like we were
strangers, but it was so awkward.
So I thought it'd be okay to say
hello.
Na Eun.
No.
It can't be a coincidence.
I'm sure...
it wasn't.
I admit that running into him
could've been a coincidence.
I made sure that he didn't know
my place nor contact number.
But the fact that he got on the bus
cannot be a coincidental happening.
I'm sure of it.
I'm sure he was trying to
stalk me...
in order to find out where I live...
and where I work.
(Currently under trial)
Case number 2017-GD-22520.
Plaintiff, Jun Seong Ho.
Defendant, Lee Na Eun.
(Plaintiff, Defendant)
According to the medical report
that I've submitted,
Mr. Jun injured his wrist and needs
eight weeks of medical treatment.
He also injured his ankle which
requires four weeks of treatment.
He asks for a compensation
regarding his medical fees,
loss of earnings, and
psychological damage.
The plaintiff had received
a restraining order.
This happened in the process of his
disobeying of the given orders.
It means the plaintiff
was the cause of his own damage.
The defendant doesn't accept
the responsibility...
for the plaintiff's injury.
Ergo, I ask that you dismiss the
monetary demand of the plaintiff.
After the restraining order
was issued,
the plaintiff didn't stalk
the defendant even for a moment.
The incident happened on a bus
where they met coincidentally.
There is no evidence that
it was a coincidental encounter.
Even if they met out of a mere
chance, isn't approaching...
the defendant a violation
of the restraining order?
Even if the plaintiff approached
first, it doesn't change the fact...
that the defendant physically
harmed the plaintiff.
The defendant still doesn't have
the right to harm the plaintiff.
The defendant was
psychologically traumatized...
due to the constant stalking.
Your Honor, pushing the plaintiff...
can be seen as
a self-defense mechanism.
Your Honor, when the plaintiff
stalked the defendant,
there wasn't a single incident the
plaintiff caused any physical harm.
Physical harm isn't
the only type of abuse.
Stalking is the definition
of psychological and emotional...
stress and abuse.
The plaintiff only...
observed the defendant from afar.
Don't you think it's too much...
to condemn it as stalking?
Why is he looking at me?
Unwanted attention is also
a form of abuse.
When someone whom I don't like
observes and tails me from afar,
the feelings of fright, anxiety,
and unpleasantness can't be
understood...
by someone who hasn't had
the experience.
Is this meant for me?
Due to the stalking, the defendant
was forced to move constantly.
The defendant also had to cut off
all of her acquaintances.
She even had to give up her job
which she cared and loved the most.
Bingo. This is about me.
Everything was...
her desperate attempt to escape
from the plaintiff.
As I have mentioned before,
it was a coincidence...
I knew it.
You knew that I was stalking you,
didn't you?
Everything you say...
is aimed at me under the pretext
of a trial, isn't it?
Plaintiff's counsel.
I was asking you
if it would be possible...
for you to settle this incident.
It was the defendant
who refused to settle.
The plaintiff, Jun Seong Ho, is
willing to dismiss both criminal...
and civil cases if the defendant
makes a sincere apology.
The defendant has no intention to
face and apologize to the plaintiff.
With this opportunity,
the plaintiff might stalk...
You do not have to worry about that.
The plaintiff is currently preparing
to immigrate to another country.
If needed, I will submit additional
documents regarding this matter.
Good work.
Okay. Well, I will contact you
after I talk to my client.
All right. I'll get going.
The door is closing.
By the way, Prosecutor...
Hasn't it been so long
since we last met, Mr. No?
It hasn't been that long.
I saw you in court when you argued
that the defendant was guilty.
Oh, that. You saw that?
By the way, why are you being
so formal?
You used to call me by my name
and treat me causally.
You were my mentee at that time.
That only lasted 2 months,
and I haven't seen you for 2 years.
It'd be weirder if I treated you
casually due to those two months.
It's not weird. It feels distant.
Of course, you should feel distant.
We are meant to be distant.
Oh, I see.
The door is opening.
Bye.
That way.
Let me say this again.
After the settlement agreement,
you can't ever ask
Ms. Lee's contact...
or approach her.
Did you understand that?
Even after this settlement, the
restraining order and injunction...
are still valid.
Don't worry, I won't do anything
that Na Eun doesn't like.
But you stalked her.
I just know how she feels
when I look at her.
Her outfit, hair,
and the look on her face.
From the first day we met, I knew
everything by looking at those.
So you don't need to worry.
Okay.
With this, it is settled that the
plaintiff will drop the lawsuit...
and the defendant will not press
charges or file a lawsuit...
for the violation
of the restraining order.
Do both of you agree?
Yes.
Hey, I will call you later.
Are you going to be okay
on your own?
I will be. Thank you, Mr. No.
I'm sorry to leave first.
Don't be. Please go.
Thank you for your work.
Sure.
Bye.
He didn't even say goodbye.
Make a U-turn right now.
Mister, please hurry.
Thank you for your work.
How can he smile?
This is the last time
he will see a girl he loves.
Even if it ended amicably,
how can he smile?
Can that be possible?
The melody.
(Attorney Eun Bong Hee)
The number you have dialed
is not available at this moment.
Please.
If you tell me the address,
I can go by myself.
How can I...
I don't trust
the plaintiff's counsel.
Okay, then. Excuse me.
It's just a bad feeling I have.
It's highly likely to be nothing.
What is your bad feeling based on?
The look on Mr. Jun's face.
It wasn't a look someone would have
after letting his loved one go.
Also, small coincidences?
- Coincidences?
- For instance,
the melody before.
You are still obsessed
with the melody.
It's not that.
It's the ringtone of his cell phone.
It's still fresh in my mind.
The song that played on the very
first day I met Na Eun.
In my opinion, perhaps,
Mr. Jun Seong Ho
might be mistaken...
that Ms. Lee Na Eun wore
the same outfit for him...
and chose the ringtone.
He might be thinking that
these are her signals for him.
I think he might be deluded.
I hope you are right.
(Joongnam Apartment Building A)
I'll go in first.
What's the address?
Unit 308 in Building A.
Okay.
Hey, Bong Hee.
Do not get involved
even if anything happens. Got it?
Okay.
You just talked casually to me.
Hey, hey!
Na Eun.
I looked everywhere for you.
I missed you, Na Eun.
Na Eun, I know everything.
Come on out.
Na Eun, let's talk. Come out.
Open the door.
Na Eun.
Na Eun! Na Eun!
Lee Na Eun!
Na Eun.
Na Eun, open the door.
Come out, so that we can talk.
Na Eun!
Mr. Jun!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you out of your mind?
You're...
Don't come closer.
Don't interfere, please.
Please don't get in my way!
Hey, Bong Hee.
Hold on.
Don't come closer.
Don't come.
I said, don't come closer!
An attorney...
shouldn't beat up her client.
There he is.
- Is he the stalker?
- I guess so.
Please step back.
Move out of the way, please.
He looks completely normal.
Go on.
Hey.
Did everything get sorted out
on the scene?
Yes, almost.
How's Ms. Lee? Is she okay?
She's okay.
She's actually relieved
that things turned out like this.
I'm glad to hear that.
Here.
Thank you.
I...
I never even thought
about the possibility.
Mr. Jun...
I mean, that scum. I can't believe
he's a complete psycho.
I thought he looked normal.
Don't beat yourself up too much.
You see,
those scums usually look
completely normal.
Still,
I can't help beating myself up.
We could prevent a big mishap
thanks to you.
Thanks for saying that.
It's true.
Let's get up.
You need to give a statement
as a witness.
Right.
By the way, do you realize that you
keep talking casually to me?
No.
Because you grabbed the bat,
- Ms. Lee...
- I told you I never hit her.
Why would I hit the woman I love?
- You kept banging on her door...
- Gosh.
I'm telling you I never did
such things.
- Why did you pick up the bat...
- Did you see it? Did you?
That's the statement we got. How
dare you raise your voice at me...
Not being loved back by the one
you love is like torture.
But in a way,
being loved by someone
you don't want to be with...
and being forced to love
that person back...
could be a bigger torture.
How much of it can be called love?
Where does obsession begin?
And I...
- Why is the office in this area?
- At this moment,
whereabouts am I standing...
between love and obsession?
Physical harm isn't
the only type of abuse.
Stalking is the definition...
of psychological and emotional
stress and abuse.
Unwanted attention...
is also a form of abuse.
I would...
like to give myself
a restraining order.
Arrived at the destination.
Ending voice navigation.
This is the address according
to the navigation. Is this it?
Sorry? Oh...
Yes, this is it.
Thank you for the ride.
I just don't want you to worry.
Other than for work-related things
or bumping into you unexpectedly,
I'll stay at least 100m away
from you at all times.
What exactly do you mean by that?
I literally meant what I said.
And...
And?
I'm saying this
in case you got the wrong idea.
I don't like you.
I may have looked like I do because
I feel grateful and indebted to you,
but please don't worry
or get any wrong ideas.
I have no feelings for you
whatsoever.
Really. I'm serious.
Please believe me.
Drive safely.
Hey.
I couldn't even date him.
How many times do I have
these breakup-like situations?
(If you keep looking for me,
I'll find you first.)
"If you keep looking for me,
I'll find you first"?
(Looking for Witness)
(Please call this number.)
"If you keep looking for me,"
"I'll find you first."
(Love in Trouble)
Someone was here.
It's you, isn't it?
Are you worrying about me now?
I came because you kept asking, but
I'm not sure if we can do this...
No Ji Wook and Eun Bong Hee
were together?
I keep feeling that I should
protect Bong Hee. It's annoying me.
I'm going to go back
to my ex-boyfriend whom I betrayed.
Come back to me.
Come work with me,
Bong Hee.