I hesitated to start this because
I was afraid of it coming to an end.
The moment I realized
my feelings for you...
I ran away from you like a coward.
Don't fall for me.
And I failed...
because I started to have feelings
for you without realizing.
If you can open up to me again,
change your mind.
I'll be waiting.
You can take your time.
There must be a connection.
You know Jung Hyun Soo, right?
Can you please look into his past?
The guy who was going to make
a report didn't look like him?
- Ms. Eun.
- What a coincidence.
It was me who made Mr. No
defend a murderer.
I came here to tell you this.
Bong Hee, your ex-boyfriend...
I mean Jang Hee Jun. I'll be
reinvestigating his case.
I witnessed something without even
realizing that I saw it,
Bong Hee, stay here.
If I went through everything because
of this, I suffered so unfairly.
It'll be okay.
I took care of it perfectly.
Hey, Ji Wook. Our client's here.
I can see what's ahead of me.
I can see what's going to happen
in the future.
There's a probability that...
two people will soon die.
I...
changed my mind.
I suddenly felt pressured.
I started to feel a bit
uncomfortable.
Please respect my feelings...
and my decision.
Can you really foresee the future?
I get hunches.
It only happens
once in a while though.
You said two people at my firm
might die. Was that also true?
Yes, that's true too.
I should get going.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem. Bye.
Bye.
Gosh, no!
By the way, I'm not...
a swindler after all, right?
Don't cry so much, Mr. No.
Everything will be okay.
Yes, Mr. No.
Where am I now? I am...
(Emergency room)
Okay. Stay where you are.
All of us...
have lost someone.
Some lost a family member.
Some lost a friend.
Some lost a lover.
Whether the person was kind or evil,
there is no one...
who didn't lose someone...
in their course of life.
Therefore, life is cruel.
If that's true,
during this cruel,
limited period of time...
and in a way,
in this brief lifetime,
the only thing we can do is...
Bong Hee,
please...
Please like me back now.
I'm sorry I didn't...
keep my promise that
I was going to wait for you.
Bong Hee,
like me back right now, please.
What should I...
do now?
What's wrong?
I'm the one who should ask you
that question.
Why did you suddenly confess
your feelings...
in the middle of the street?
I felt pressured.
I just...
suddenly felt like...
I was wasting my time.
It's your turn, Bong Hee.
I know there's something going on.
What is it?
I'm just really exhausted.
Today was just...
one of those days where everything
annoys me and makes me want to cry.
That's when I ran into you.
That's why I cried,
which really wasn't like me.
Jung Hyun Soo.
Is it because of Jung Hyun Soo?
What do you know of him?
Long time no see, my friend.
What about you?
What do you know?
I know that Jung Hyun Soo...
might be...
the murderer.
He could be the one who murdered
Chef Yang.
And maybe...
This is just an over interpreted
guess.
I have no evidence to prove it.
It's just...
something I guessed based on my
instincts.
It's a nonscientific guess.
My gosh.
You're so mean.
Why didn't you tell me
when you knew everything?
You told me that you won't keep
secrets from me.
Okay, I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.
Then stop everything you're doing.
Stop expressing your feelings
for me.
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to.
- What do you mean?
- Why do we have to be like this...
because of a jerk like him?
Do you really not know why?
Yes.
I'm asking because I don't know.
- Try putting yourself in my shoes.
- I do.
I think a lot about how you might
feel.
I know you're blaming yourself.
"I lured the criminal."
"It's all because of me."
"I defended a criminal..."
"and set him free."
You're probably going through a hard
time. I know that already.
You're right. You know very well.
But I'm trying to tell you...
that you're mistaken.
No, you're wrong. It's the truth.
It's not the truth.
It's just an accident.
You got into an accident
with Jung Hyun Soo.
And I'm going to get through
this accident...
with you.
My decision won't change even if you
try to push me away.
I'm definitely...
going to catch Jung Hyun Soo.
So you need to make a decision.
Do you want us to...
go through this separately?
Or do you want to go through it
together?
I want us...
to do this together.
I asked you not to abandon me,
Yeon Woo.
Let's put an end to this.
We should just die together.
(Choi Yeon Woo)
Hey, Yeon Woo.
It's been such a long time...
What happened?
Where are you going this late?
Oh, well...
A friend of mine had a mishap.
A mishap?
Yes.
Yeon Woo. Yeon Woo...
Yeon Woo!
Hey, what happened?
Look at me. Let me have a look.
What happened?
I broke up with my ex-boyfriend,
and he said we should die together.
What?
Gosh, what a worthless piece
of trash.
Where's that jerk now?
He's in the holding cell.
But we couldn't find the weapon
you insisted he attacked you with.
He really tried to stab me
with a knife.
She has this cut that seems like
the knife brushed against.
It should be considered attempted
murder if he brandished a weapon.
However... Excuse me for a second.
The wound is too insignificant
to insist that was the case.
Plus, there's no evidence that
it was done by her ex-boyfriend.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling him the fact.
He can be detained
for up to 48 hours, right?
Yes, that's correct.
And we have to find
a suspect or the weapon...
in order to request a warrant.
We'll go through the CCTV footages
around the time of his arrest.
We'll do a thorough search.
Please find something.
You have to find something
within 48 hours.
I'll kill her.
Go on in.
- Thanks.
- Don't worry too much.
(48 Hours Later)
You two must be close friends.
I met her while preparing
for the bar exam.
I see. I guess you guys
used to study together.
No, her parents owned the restaurant
I used to go to often.
I see.
I'm really upset.
Why did she date a jerk like that?
I just...
suddenly felt like...
I was wasting my time.
Then stop everything you're doing.
Stop expressing your feelings
for me.
I'm sorry,
- but I don't want to.
- What do you mean?
Why do we have to be like this
because of a jerk like him?
So you need to make a decision.
Do you want us to
go through this separately? Or...
do you want to go through it
together?
I want us...
to do this together.
Hey, hey, hey! Goodness!
What do you think you're doing now?
What are you looking at?
I came to tell you something.
What is it?
I thought hard all night and have
decided to live with no shame.
Who cares, right? We should just
be selfish and live as we please.
What?
Let's start today.
Today is our first day. See you.
Hey, what does that mean?
What... What did you say?
Let's start a relationship.
What relationship...
Wait.
That relationship.
I have a girlfriend now.
My gosh.
I finally told him.
Does that mean today
is our first day together?
What's going on? What brought
such a drastic change in mood?
It's like night and day.
It's like going from a fall-winter
collection to a spring-summer one.
By the way, did the two of you not
get a good night's sleep or what?
I didn't get any sleep.
Same here.
Gosh, you two must've gotten
insomnia from Ji Wook.
What that crazy guy said...
keeps bothering me.
He said that two people from here
will die.
I think...
you and I will be those two people.
Why... Why are you dragging me
into it?
Oh, I guess none of you
have heard the news about...
What news?
It's nothing.
Don't cry so much, Mr. No.
Everything will be okay.
Anyhow, from now on...
No matter what happens,
no one can talk about anyone dying.
- Just don't talk about it, okay?
- By the way,
did I tell you that my doctor
wants to me to get tests done again?
Gosh, I must be terminally ill...
Mr. No just said that we can't
talk about things like that.
You always have to cut me off
like that, don't you?
With all due respect...
Don't even begin if you have any
respect.
Our meeting is going nowhere.
Why are you trying to blame me?
It's all your fault.
Today, it's your fault.
Be quiet! Go get me a glass of
water. I need to take my medication.
The older you get, the more you need
to move around to stay healthy.
Hey, Ms. Lack of Evidence!
- Yes?
- Goodness.
Young people these days...
I should try to be understanding.
What? What is it?
- What is it?
- Well...
You know...
I told you about my family,
didn't I?
Yes, you told me.
My parents' friends who raised me...
are now my legal guardians.
I told you...
about them too, right?
Yes, you did.
I really think they are like angels.
But I didn't tell you...
who they are.
No.
Who are they?
One of them is Mr. Byun.
I see. Mr. Byun?
Mister...
Mr. Byun?
Yes.
- It's him.
- I know you.
You are a murderer.
Ms. Lack of Evidence.
Ms. Lack of Evidence!
We have a secretary.
It's Ms. Lack of Evidence.
Ms. Lack of Evidence,
you lost my trial!
Hey! Look at you.
Are you all right?
We are doomed.
I do think we are doomed.
What are you up to?
Why are you smiling?
I'm not up to anything.
Don't smile.
It makes me feel sick.
I'm done.
I'm finished.
Yes?
What?
You found him?
Thank you for contacting me.
Okay. All right.
Nice!
Whom did they find?
By any chance, were you still
investigating Jung Hyun Soo?
To be more precise,
I found the identity
of the man in the photo.
I explicitly told you to stop
investigating him temporarily.
So you don't want me to brief you?
Well... I mean...
It'd be rude if I don't hear your
report since you investigated.
You don't need to be so formal
between us.
You don't need to hear it.
No, no.
I'd like to hear your report.
Please tell me.
- I met Ko Chan Ho's teacher.
- I will look into that.
Thank you.
Did he have any close friends?
- I went to the youth club...
- Well, I don't know.
he went during his high school days.
Finally,
I received a call.
He was in a senior class
in Ko Chan Ho's high school.
There was a reason why I couldn't
find him in the year book.
The years they graduated high
school were all different.
But what on earth...
happened between them?
Firstly,
I will meet with Kim Min Gu.
Since I found out who he is,
I'm sure I can find out
his address and contact quickly.
Hello?
It's me.
We just identified the body
in the water tank.
Luckily, he was in the database
of the missing person.
We found his identity quite fast.
No, we only identified one body,
not all of them.
- His name is Kim Min Gu.
- Kim Min Gu.
How did you know?
On what date was the missing
person report filed?
(Status of Ko
Chan Ho's disappearance)
Ko Chan Ho, the forensic officer,
said he wanted to give Bong Hee
information about the real killer.
After that, he's gone missing.
And this man.
This man was recently found
dead in the water tank...
on the roof top of the apartment.
When did he disappear?
The date of his disappearance is...
falls around the same time of
the murder of Jang Hee Jun.
Which means...
Everything is connected.
And this is the murder weapon
used in Jang Hee Jun's murder.
The size of the murder weapon
happens to match the size of the...
weapon used in Chef Yang's murder.
This implies the murderer
of these two cases is the same.
- That's right. He is...
- Jung Hyun Soo.
Jung Hyun Soo was listening
to the same song...
that I heard on the night
of Hee Jun's murder.
We don't have...
any physical evidence, do we?
No. None at all.
First, we should find that man.
But...
what if something bad happened
to that guy too?
Nothing might have happened to him.
We should have hope
and look for him.
No.
We are going to stop
everything here.
We are civilians
without any investigative right.
I am going to let the prosecution
take over.
Which means...
everyone in this room...
cannot make a rash move...
or do something.
I agree with Ji Wook on this.
I will notify Prosecutor Cha.
All right. That's all.
Are you feeling all right?
That's a relief.
Yes.
Don't look back.
I don't even want to see it.
Prosecutor Cha.
I'm glad I caught you.
I came here to see you.
Why? You said you wanted
to meet only coincidentally.
Why did you contact me?
- Then should I not?
- I didn't say that.
Well, it's nice...
if you want to get in touch with me.
Goodness, Yoo Jung.
Hello, Ms. Na.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Let go. I said let go.
- You need to let go first.
- Hold on. Wait!
- Darn it.
- All right. There you go.
Have a good day then.
I need to talk to you.
Okay.
What was that?
I think he just laughed at me.
No way. He couldn't have.
You are suspecting Jung Hyun Soo
to be the murderer?
Well, not exactly.
So far, we just think that he has
something to do with the murders.
To be honest,
something about him
didn't sit right with me.
I see.
So?
What do you really want to tell me?
We need the authority
to investigate.
There's nothing we can do.
Okay.
By the way,
why are you guys involved
in the case this deeply?
Is it about justice?
Or...
is it about Bong Hee?
Can't it be both?
I feel terrible.
I feel like I have
been just replaced.
Regardless of my wrongdoings,
I have lost you guys,
and now I have
to investigate for her.
What should I do? Should I look
for another prosecutor?
No.
I'll do it.
But...
don't be so harsh on me.
You know that you guys are
the only friends I have.
Please look into this case for us.
But...
you shouldn't personally handle it.
Jung Hyun Soo is dangerous.
You know there are strong
and experienced investigators.
Ask them to help you.
I'm also strong and experienced.
I can take care of myself
and protect others.
You know me.
Right, I know you.
I might have gone a bit far.
Be careful.
I'm serious.
Being careful won't cause any harm.
I'm going now.
Still nothing?
The weapon wasn't caught on any
of the CCTV cameras in the area...
around the time of the incident.
It happened at night,
and the angle wasn't ideal either.
We also searched the area, but
we couldn't find anything.
We'd like to know where he was
before he got arrested.
Could we get that information?
You don't have to tag along
like this.
I'll figure it out on my own
from here on.
What will you do now, then?
I need to find the weapon.
All by yourself?
That's nonsense. Even the police
haven't been able to find it.
If that jerk gets released from the
holding cell with no weapon found,
I know exactly what he's
going to do.
He'll go to see her
and do something crazy again.
You're right. That's highly likely.
- But still...
- We should still...
try our best with whatever it is
that we can do.
All right. Good luck with it.
Thanks.
Let's go and find that weapon.
Goodness.
Didn't it happen over there?
Yes.
It was right here.
Then...
They said he went in there, right?
Do you think he could've
left it in there?
If you go in there,
it could be seen as trespassing on
public property for sexual purposes.
Darn it. Goodness.
There's nothing.
Let's go.
It happened quite long ago.
I'm sure...
All the garbage from that time
must've been picked up already.
Are you really sure?
Let's go.
There's certainly a problem here.
Hey, you guys are back.
Gosh, what on earth happened?
What is this stink?
Right? They really stink.
I feel like throwing up.
Isn't it so bad?
I don't smell anything.
Anyway, that's not
important right now.
We couldn't find the weapon.
We have less than 24 hours now.
Oh, your friend's case, right?
What about the witness?
Not yet. I know which school
she goes to because of her uniform,
but I haven't been able to track
her down among all the students.
I see.
By the way, I'm getting...
a bad feeling about this case.
I feel like that jerk was determined
to harm her.
Don't cry so much,
Mr. No.
No, nothing will happen. Everything
will be fine. That can't be.
- Pardon?
- What?
What? Oh, I was just saying
you should go wash up.
We should wash up for everything
to be okay. What I mean is...
we won't get sick because we'll
get rid of all the germs. Let's go.
Don't you smell anything?
Thank goodness.
They'll wash up.
Thank goodness indeed.
Where's the air freshener?
Alibi...
I need an alibi.
No, I need to nail down
on the order first.
Who should go first?
If we can't find the weapon
or any witness,
it'll be considered
a simple assault case,
and he'll just get a fine.
Right.
That's why we have to find it.
Yes, we have to find it. We must.
By the way, why are you guys still
working at this late hour?
We have a lot of work, Ji Wook.
Unlike someone.
That's right.
Okay, fine.
Let's say that is the case.
But what I'm saying is,
you can work on it at home.
Why do you guys have to be working
here until this late today?
Today is the first day.
No, it's not.
It's the middle of the month.
My credit card payment
was taken out yesterday.
By "first day", do you mean...
- that kind of "first day"?
- What do you mean?
Hey, go find the witness.
You'll find a clue if you watch the
CCTV footage until your eyes hurt.
I told you that I'm busy.
All right. I'll help you like the
last time if you refuse to help us.
For goodness' sake.
I'll try to track her down
using social media.
You said she's in high school.
Using social media will be
the best bet.
How can we use it to find her?
Well, we can look up
the school's name as a hashtag...
and see if anything about the case
has been posted.
If that doesn't work, we can post...
a notice about looking for her
with the school's name as a hashtag.
You guys are not following, are you?
Don't you use social media?
Are you really not on things like
Instagram, Facebook, and Twitter?
Bong Hee, you don't use it either?
That's how people keep a record of
their daily experiences these days.
Oh, I keep a journal.
I handwrite it though.
- My goodness.
- Hey, and...
Alex Ferguson said that social media
is a waste of time.
That is true.
I see. All right.
Then I'll go waste my time
and use social media...
in order to track down that girl
all on my own.
Gosh, you guys are seriously...
Good grief.
You guys sure blow my mind.
They're such nerds.
Right, social media. That's it.
Goodness.
They should just go home.
Darn it.
Today must've been
stressful for you.
Don't worry about it.
But I must say,
going through the dumpster
was a bit much.
Which tea do you want?
Anything.
Anything? Okay.
Thanks for everything today.
Look at you.
Come here.
Come...
That's enough
to celebrate our first day.
She's pretty good at this.
That girl.
Don't work too hard.
You can drink this. Hey, drink it.
Gosh, this is bitter. What is it?
Is this drinkable?
What is this?
Tomorrow, I have to find the weapon,
a witness, or something...
and have a warrant issued.
Focus on. Look.
Take the photo and upload it.
- Is that it?
- Yes.
Come on. Try it.
I'm going to check.
Okay.
- Take the photo.
- Upload it.
- Gosh, it worked.
Goodness, it was uploaded.
(Hello)
(This is so interesting!)
Ta-da. I liked your photo.
So did I.
I also liked my own photo.
- This is new.
- I like this.
Eun Hyuk, I liked your photo too.
I have two likes.
Ms. Eun, you look
good in the photo.
(Dongbang High School)
- Look at him.
- Gosh, you are so handsome.
He's amazingly hot.
He's so good looking.
I see.
You guys are the ones who
wrote comments online, right?
What's up?
You are not that bad to look at.
Well, I have great looks actually.
What am I saying?
To you guys, I shouldn't act like
your peers. I'm an adult after all.
Anyhow,
there was someone
who witnessed...
an assault the night
before yesterday around here?
Yes, but she won't testify.
Leave that to me.
Where can I find her?
I'm glad I caught you, Ji Hye.
I needed to talk to you.
What is it?
Don't try to assault me again.
Just tell me.
When did I assault you?
What do you think about the crimes
committed after breakups...
that are on the rise nowadays?
Are you here to tell me you broke up
with Hee Jun because of me...
and physically abuse me again?
How did you become a prosecutor
with that head of yours?
I feel extremely uncomfortable...
to hear that from you. Are you aware
of that?
Obviously, I'm not.
You don't know the number of people
who reported their loved ones...
for abusive relationships for the
last 5 years is over 30,000, right?
I don't run the statistics.
How would I know that?
Average of seven women per month
are dead due to dating violence.
You ought to know this
as a prosecutor.
So what do you want from me?
Gather up all the related
previous cases...
and run an investigation for me.
Get some attention
to your investigation.
Inform the public of precautions.
I have a suitable case
to hand you over.
If you look into other cases, I'm
sure you'll find more cases.
Hey, this isn't easy.
I know that crimes committed
after breakups are problems.
There are no legal acts that can
prevent the crimes from happening.
Besides, they have to commit
crimes for me to arrest...
and punish them. What can I do
before the crimes even occur?
I knew it. You are not capable
of this. It was a waste of time.
- Hey!
- What?
There are only 2 hours left
until we reach the 48th hour.
(Attorney No Ji Wook)
Yes, Mr. Ji.
Yes. Should I go?
I see. Then I will go
see Yeon Woo then.
Yes. Okay, I got it.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Mr. Ji is doing his best
for this case.
I'm so touched.
He is.
He is indeed.
What about me?
What about me? I'm doing
my hardest too.
(Investigator Bang Eun Ho)
I told you to look into and save
all the text messages...
and letters Choi Yeon Woo
received, right?
Yes, I did those.
You did? Okay. Good job.
I'm going to meet Yeon Woo later.
My instincts tell me that I should
be with her today.
I'll come with you.
What? I'll be all right.
My instincts tell me...
that I should come with you.
What?
Yes, this is Bang Eun Ho speaking.
You found him?
Okay.
I see.
He recently came to Korea. I see.
His name is Lee Jae Ho?
Do you have his number and address?
Okay.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you so much. Goodbye.
We are civilians
without any investigative authority.
I'm going to let the prosecution
take over.
Which means
everyone in this room...
cannot make a rash move
or do something.
After your message, press the star
or the sharp button.
(Attorney No Ji Wook)
I'm on my way
to Lee Jae Ho, Mr. No.
You know the other man
in Ko Chan Ho's photo?
I found his whereabouts.
He has been abroad until recently
and just moved back to Korea.
I think that I should make a move
before Jung Hyun Soo gets to him.
I will leave you his number
and address just in case.
Bye.
Can he go there by himself?
I told him not to do this.
Goodness, Mr. Bang.
Should I call him?
He'll go even if we try to stop him.
It's not like we don't
know how he is.
Then go to Mr. Bang.
I will go to Yeon Woo.
Do you think you'll be okay alone?
Of course. Don't worry.
Goodness.
Okay. Let's do that.
Okay.
I'll call you, and you should
give me a call too, okay?
I will.
Bong Hee.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
- Hey, Yeon Woo.
- Bong Hee!
You didn't have to come.
Come on, that's nonsense.
An attorney must protect
her client.
Follow me. I'll protect you tonight.
- Let's go.
- Let's get going.
Are you done for the night?
(My friends are so pretty!)
Come on.
Shoot.
Yes, Detective.
I know that our 48 hours are up.
Please, give us a bit more time.
I want to hold him
for a longer time too,
but I can't hold him for more
than 48 hours.
I really believe that
I can meet up with the witness.
I don't even need that much time.
Please give me a bit more time.
She's here. I just met her.
Detective, please do me a favor.
Okay?
Hello.
Do you know how long I've waited
for you?
Me?
Who are you?
Anyway, thank you so much
for coming.
So can you spare me some time to
do a good deed?
They won't issue an arrest warrant,
so you'll be out in no time.
Don't worry. You just need to wait.
I'll trust that I'm in good hands.
Okay.
Excuse me, sir.
- Are you talking to me?
- What will happen to a guy like me?
Will I go straight to prison?
I don't defend people for free.
I heard that he's been locked up for
more than 48 hours.
Why are you still keeping him there?
- Well, it's because...
- You can't do this.
You can't do this to a civilian
without a warrant.
What you're doing is illegal.
Why can't you testify?
I was only there to witness that
because I skipped a class.
If my mom finds out about that
after I testify,
she'll kill me.
I'll make sure she never finds out.
My mom knows everything.
I see.
Okay.
Then I'll just tell her everything.
What?
You skipped class that day,
and you came out early today
to do the same thing.
I'm going to tell your mom
everything...
if you don't testify.
By the way,
is she okay?
She got stabbed with a knife.
You saw a knife?
Yes.
Then did you see what he did
with that knife?
Did you see where he threw it away?
Yes, I did.
He put it inside his cast.
Yes, this is Ji Eun Hyuk.
I already found the witness.
The weapon is in...
The suspect got released?
I'll walk you home tomorrow too.
How will you go home?
You don't need to worry about me.
Yeon Woo.
- Stay behind me.
- Oh, gosh.
Stay there.
Bong Hee. Bong Hee.
- Hey, are you okay?
- I told you to stay behind me.
(Ji Eun Hyuk)
Hey, what did the witness say?
I found...
the weapon.
Where?
He hid it inside his cast.
- What?
- But there's a problem.
It's been more than 48 hours,
so he got released.
- He's probably...
- You should've told me that first.
Okay, I got it.
My gosh.
Bong Hee. Bong Hee.
Bong Hee. I'm her guardian.
Get out of my way.
Bong Hee. Hey, Bong Hee.
Are you...
Mr. No.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. It just brushed against
my arm.
- Hey, you. Get over here.
- Stop, Mr. No.
I'm really okay.
I'm fine. I'm okay.
Are you sure you're okay?
Okay.
Gosh.
I'm relieved.
Hey, wait.
Where's Mr. Bang?
I was on my way there,
but I came here as soon as
I got a call from Eun Hyuk
Then you should go to him right now.
Okay.
Eun Hyuk will be here soon, so ask
him for help if anything happens.
- Okay?
- Okay. You should hurry up and go.
Please look after her.
I'll go now.
Why? What's wrong?
- It's okay.
- Okay.
You should go.
Okay.
Bye.
Please take good care of her.
The line is busy. Please leave
a message after the beep.
Why isn't he picking up?
The line is busy. Please leave
a message after the beep.
Is anyone here?
Mr. Lee Jae Ho?
(Mr. No)
Hello? Mr. Bang?
Hello?
Mr. Bang, can you hear me?
I used to be a detective
who knows how to fight well.
(Mr. Bang)
Hello? Mr. Bang.
Hello? Mr. Bang!
Hello?
What? What's going on?
My gosh.
Mr. Bang.
Mr. Bang, wake up. Mr. Bang.
Mr. Bang, please open your eyes.
Mr. Bang.
Open your eyes.
Eun Ho.
Eun Ho, please wake up. Eun Ho!
Eun Ho!
Eun Ho, open your eyes!
No!
Eun Ho...
Wake up, please...
No!
(Love in Trouble)