=Love Again=
=Episode 26=
Lina.
Mr. Shen.
Thank you
for everything.
It's not a problem at all, Xinghuo.
I'm sorry.
I'll throw it away.
It's all right.
It's good stuff.
Save it for Shen Qing.
Lina...
We'll take our leave now.
Ms. Lv Yuan!
You're a good friend.
You encouraged Lina,
encouraged Ding,
and brought so much energy
into my life.
Thank you.
Xinghuo and Taotao are good kids.
You all go back and live well together.
Taotao.
Grandpa Shen, this is for you.
I have no use for this.
Take it and your granny home.
Okay.
Granny.
Where did you get this?
Mr. French Fry gave it to me.
Is that so?
That's nice.
Granny.
I'm hungry.
Can you make dumplings for me?
Didn't you say
you were happy
when I wasn't home?
We were happy,
but I missed you.
You really missed me?
Really missed me?
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Bye-bye, Taotao.
- We're off.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye, Ms. Lv.
Goodbye, Lina.
Bye.
Take care, Lina.
Say bye-bye.
Bye-bye!
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Stretch your legs,
shake your arms, stand tall♪
♪Go, go, go♪
♪The path is right beneath your feet♪
♪For the sake of your health
and the ones who care about you♪
Please look here.
This time, I chose
a double-breasted design.
The bottom four buttons
are perfectly symmetrical.
♪Step by step,
we walk towards good health♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you taken in
the sunset views today?♪
♪Love the sunshine on sunny days,
love the rain on rainy ones♪
♪Whatever you want to do today,
it's up to you♪
♪It's all up to you♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you mastered
tomorrow's songs yet?♪
What a coincidence.
♪Whatever mood you're in,
come and join us♪
Didn't expect to run into you.
Eyes right!
59, 60,
61, 62.
Ms. Lv Yuan.
Mr. Shen.
Grandpa Shen.
Taotao.
Hello.
Mr. Shen.
Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?
We're working on it.
We all said we'd learn from you.
I already hit 20,000 steps today.
Learn from Ms. Lv Yuan!
Eyes right!
♪Life is all about moving your body♪
Lina.
I just came
from the school finance office.
The headmaster signed off
on the payment.
- You should be receiving it soon.
- That's great, Bai! You're amazing!
You have to let me buy you a meal.
Then I want something really good.
No worries.
No alcohol.
Of course.
Only the best food and drinks.
♪Have you taken in
the sunset views today?♪
(Zijin Rural Commercial Bank)
(Transaction Alert: 9 Sep 13:39, RMB285,000
credited from Zhang Hui)
♪Whatever you want to do today,
it's up to you♪
♪It's all up to you♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you mastered
tomorrow's songs yet?♪
Dear.
The payment came through.
I already transferred it
to your company.
♪Swing your arms
and let happiness lead the way♪
Lina.
Lina?
Zhuoran?
He's not here.
I'm just tidying up.
We brought your vacuum cleaner
over.
Didn't work well for us.
We weren't used to it.
- And it uses a lot of electricity.
- I could've just driven over to get it.
No need to come.
Do you know
how much gas costs these days?
Labor power.
Don't waste it if you've got it.
If we don't use you,
you'll go fishing again.
Fished all day for nothing
but small fry.
Not even enough to cover the gas money.
Thanks.
Lv Yuan didn't take her vacuum with her?
She and her daughter were crying
their eyes out
when they left.
Didn't have time to grab it.
I'll drop it off later.
They cried?
Now I understand
what Lv Xinghuo went through.
She's had it rough all these years.
Ms. Lv's great in every way, right?
Yes.
But she's really controlling.
She drove her ex-husband crazy
with all the nagging.
That's why he cheated,
and the divorce got so messy.
Really?
Why would I lie?
Even Ms. Lv admitted it in the end.
The more you try to control someone,
the more they run.
You've got to learn to let go.
So true.
Can't control people too much.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Dad's right.
Where there's oppression,
there's resistance.
You can't have people
controlling people.
No control?
If I let you loose,
you'll be off the rails!
There you go again, Mom.
Listen.
Even I've seen enough.
Dad doesn't have many hobbies.
He likes fishing.
And he does it at wild ponds.
It's free.
He needs a bit of social life
with his fishing buddies.
You could at least
give him a bit of cash.
Otherwise, people will laugh at him.
Like she would agree.
You make me sound like
I'm some stingy miser.
Fine. You want money?
I'll send it to you.
I'll do it.
I'll send it right now.
You...
1,000 yuan.
There!
Spend it however you like!
What can you even do
with 1,000 yuan, huh Dad?
She actually sent it!
She's being generous today.
Usually getting her
to send 100 is like pulling teeth.
Laugh it up. What's so funny?
You've got the money.
Do something useful.
Go check
if the vacuum's full of dust
and empty it.
On it.
You're right.
All this dirt.
I'll take care of this.
Be right back to take care of that!
I'll come back and tidy that!
You...
Mom, see? You let go a little
and Dad's all happy and motivated.
Being the one
who manages everything is hard work.
Look at this. Can I not step in?
There's a mess everywhere.
Yes.
Look at this!
Leave it there. I'll take care of it.
If he does anything,
I've got to follow behind and clean up.
- Stop. I'll do it.
- Seriously.
You're going to handle it?
I don't want to control everything.
It's exhausting.
Look at these.
It's been such a long time since then.
Your father-in-law's had
more romantic drama this year
than in his entire life.
Well, I think
Ms. Lian,
Ms. Nie,
Ms. Lv,
and Ms. Peng
are all brave women
going after their happiness.
They're admirable.
Yes.
Admirable, but way too much drama.
Maybe you can talk
to your father-in-law?
All this matchmaking
is wearing everyone out.
Sing some songs and dance a little.
Those are good activities
to pass the time,
aren't they?
(Bo'ai Building)
♪The night is so divine♪
♪My heart is full of joy and light♪
♪On this enchanting evening♪
Everyone.
The TV station will be here
to film us soon.
We must maintain this momentum.
Keep it up.
Our choir is going to be famous!
Wind and Rainbow Choir.
Calm and composed
in glory or shame.
Shen is our cultural ambassador.
When the station interviews us,
Shen will speak for us.
No, I can't...
Get him to do it!
Gou will represent us!
No, it has to be you!
No.
You have to be the one to do it!
They're here!
Ladies and gentlemen!
The TV station is here!
They even brought
a makeup artist for us!
This way, Director.
Good work, everyone.
Let's get right to it, then,
shall we? Let's start with makeup.
- Who goes first?
- All right.
Shen.
You go first.
You get your makeup done first.
- No...
- Shen, you have to go.
You'll be representing us
in the interview.
All right. Then I won't hold back.
Everyone else, rest where you are.
Take a short break.
Okay.
Sorry to trouble you.
Not at all.
Sorry to trouble you, Dear.
Here.
Try this on.
I fixed it.
Are we ready to begin?
Look in the mirror.
They look so much alike.
What are you looking at?
Jingmin.
Who?
Shen's late wife?
(The Past Gone with the Wind)
She looks so much like Mom.
That must be Grandma!
Definitely what Grandma looked like
before she got sick.
Now with AI, they can reconstruct
how you used to look.
Yes. It's uncanny. Look.
Let me say this one more time.
She is not your mom.
She's the makeup artist
the provincial TV station got
for our choir.
Her name is
Le Shuishan.
Dad.
Could she be Mom's long-lost sister?
Your grandma passed away not long
after your mom was born.
There's no way that's possible.
Grandpa,
I ran a facial comparison with software.
(Facial recognition: similarity 92%)
They look 92% alike!
She looks so much like her.
Dad.
What if Grandpa
had a secret affair
and this is his love child?
Like Xia Yuhe?
Nonsense!
Your grandpa was a very traditional man.
Shen Dai,
stop letting your imagination run wild.
I...
We shouldn't criticize Shen Dai.
Shen Dai is imaginative,
and she's a bit of a loner.
That's just who she is.
Grandpa, you're so biased.
It's not biased.
Her personality is why she's able
to do artistic work now? Right?
Dad, you've got taste.
You're so good to me.
I'm touched.
Sentiment received.
If you're touched,
then come visit Dad more often.
Don't just feel emotional
through the video call.
It's fine. I get it.
Ignore your brother.
I'm ignoring him.
He's lost his charm anyway.
(The Past Gone with the Wind)
(Forwarded
Link copied, ready to paste)
(Open in TikTok and send)
My goodness!
Debao!
What?
Look at this!
Look!
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
(The Past Gone with the Wind)
Gosh!
Unbelievable!
You're right.
It's like they're long-lost sisters.
They look exactly the same.
Right?
Yes.
Too much alike.
(The Past Gone with the Wind)
Their school was updating
its finance system,
so the payment was delayed.
I kept negotiating
with Headmaster Zhang.
In the end, he gave in and signed
the situation report.
I took it to the finance office
and had them process it
through the test system.
You're such a dependable friend.
If there's anything I can do for you,
let me know.
Lina.
Let's try not to get
into these situations again.
Oh, by the way,
your business loan was approved too.
You can borrow and repay as needed.
That's great!
With that backup fund,
we won't be caught off guard
when something urgent comes up.
That's right.
Here's your food.
Enjoy your meal.
Thanks.
You only ordered three dishes?
There's meat and fish. This is plenty.
This is going all out.
Bai.
Here's to you. Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Right.
When I was negotiating
the overdue payment,
I also brought up
the school uniform order.
He has a really good impression of you.
Said when the last batch arrived,
there wasn't even a loose thread.
Of course.
I hand-checked every piece.
So he's willing
to give you
the school uniform contract too.
Really?
3,000 pieces!
That's a huge order!
That said,
the school's trying
to keep costs low for the students,
so they're pressing the price way down.
But they still expect
high-quality results.
I'm worried you'll overexert yourself
and still end up not making a profit.
It's okay.
Uniforms are all about volume.
If I can land this deal,
the company will scale up.
No more a family workshop.
You've got the long-term vision.
Should we go see
Headmaster Zhang together?
Sure. Let's go tomorrow.
Sounds good.
Bai,
you really are my lucky star
on the road to success.
You're too kind.
Thank you.
That's
the situation.
Headmaster Zhang,
you want school uniforms
for all four seasons
to stay under 1,000 yuan in total,
with original designs,
and high-quality fabric.
It's not just not profitable.
We'd have to eat the cost.
She's right, Headmaster Zhang.
At least give us a bit of margin.
I'll guarantee quality,
delivery, and after-sales support.
Same as last time.
Not even a thread is out of place.
Ms. Liu.
I'll be honest with you.
Most of our students
come from modest families.
So as the headmaster,
I have to do everything I can
to save them money.
We've reached out
to some other manufacturers before
and they can do the job too.
But after working with you,
I feel like you are
more meticulous, and more thoughtful.
Also,
this price point was set
after careful research.
We really can't raise it any further.
But if it's difficult for you, Ms. Liu,
then perhaps we can find
another opportunity instead.
Let's go, Lina.
Headmaster Zhang.
I'll do it.
Starting a business
isn't just about making money,
right?
Then,
I thank you, Ms. Liu.
You're welcome.
Here's some info on Le Shuishan.
She's from Suzhou.
She's retired now,
but used to be a makeup artist.
She has a good reputation
and high EQ,
(Le Shuishan, Makeup Artist)
so she's invited to work events
and programs from time to time.
When she was younger,
she worked in the northwest.
Her husband was from Nanjing.
After he died in an accident,
she moved back to Nanjing
and took over her mother-in-law's job.
She first worked
in the broadcast group doing ad sales.
Then she taught herself makeup
and became a professional makeup artist.
She's had quite a journey.
Mr. Shen, why are you looking into her?
Because...
Le Shuishan
looks a bit
like my mom.
Seriously?
How similar are we talking?
I...
This is...
They're practically twins!
(Shen Dai)
Talk to me, Dai.
Qing, I'm transferring to Beijing.
About an hour till I land in Nanjing.
Come pick me up.
Are you out of your mind?
Why do you always act on impulse?
I have to go to the airport later.
My sister's coming back.
Hold on.
Is she back because of this woman?
Who knows?
This is an opera theater.
What are you...
- Come on!
- Do you want to watch opera?
Come on, Mom.
Take a few steps.
Are you sure about this?
You look stunning!
But my belly...
Look at how perfectly
this qipao fits you!
Walk a bit. Let me see!
You look fabulous.
Where would I even wear this?
Mom, listen.
Your figure hasn't changed a bit.
Turn around and let me take a look.
Such a waste of money.
Look at that waist!
The sleeves fit perfectly! Gorgeous!
Tastes just like I remembered!
Eat up, Qing!
I'm not that hungry.
What's on your mind?
I was thinking...
Mom also used to love wearing qipaos
and dressing up.
If I could go back in time,
I'd never have let her
take care of Duole.
Duole used
to spit up all over her.
For more than a year,
she didn't buy herself
a single new outfit.
When Duole got a little older,
Mom started fussing over me again.
She'd obsess over
whether I was wearing socks,
telling me,
"Cold enters through the feet!
You have to keep warm!"
It drove me crazy.
Thinking back,
she was probably
already having a relapse then.
Qing, there's something
I never told you.
You know what?
Now, when I sleep,
I always wear a pair of socks.
One night I woke up, and I was yelling
in my sleep.
"Mom! Mom, I wore socks!"
And then...
And then I remembered...
Mom isn't with us anymore.
Qing.
Why is it that we only listen
to our mothers
after they're gone?
You know what my biggest regret is?
What?
When Mom relapsed,
she wanted to go to Xinjiang.
I was afraid it'd be too hard
on her body,
so I told her to wait.
Wait till summer.
But she...
She didn't make it to summer.
In her final days,
lying in that hospital bed...
I...
I told her,
"Mom...
I'm sorry.
We probably won't get to Xinjiang."
She couldn't
talk anymore. She just...
She waved me over.
Smiled at me.
Ran her hand over my head,
and plucked out a white hair.
Even now...
Just thinking about that moment...
If something comes to mind,
do it.
If you miss the chance,
you might miss it forever.
That's why the moment
I saw that video of Le Shuishan,
I couldn't wait a second longer.
I just wanted to come back.
I just wanted to see her.
Qing...
I miss Mom...
(Chaihuo Wontons)
Where's my thanks, hm?
I carried this all the way back for you.
I really appreciate it, Aunt.
This thing is heavy!
"Welcome home" tangyuan for you.
I'll make you a feast tomorrow.
Thanks, Lina.
Slow down. Don't burn yourself.
All right.
Tell us.
Why did you suddenly come back?
Is something the matter?
Of course something's up, Dad.
Is missing home a big enough reason?
- Qing?
- Of course.
Is missing Mom a big enough reason?
Dad.
I took my brother
to see Le Shuishan today.
Her qipao team had a performance.
You...
You two...
You're something else.
There was a moment
when I truly felt like she was Mom.
I've always felt like
I owed her one last family meal.
She left with regrets.
And I'm living with mine.
So, my dear father,
can we please
invite Ms. Le over for dinner
this Mid-Autumn Festival?
I don't think that's appropriate.
Why wouldn't it be?
I just want her to sit there,
and for all of us to gather around her.
She doesn't need to do anything
but look at us.
But she's not Mom.
Doesn't matter if she is or isn't.
When I look at that face, she is.
Dad,
just this once, please let me have this?
I just want to use
Mom's favorite purple clay teacup
and
pour her favorite tea.
I'd just like her to sit there, smile,
and look at us.
To tell you the truth,
there are times
when I glance at her,
and think she really is your mom.
Right?
Then invite her.
I'll give it a shot.
You're the head of the house.
It's your call.
Give it a shot.
Okay.
How do you feel?
All that sweating really helps
relieve stress.
Right?
"Nature is an excellent sedative."
That's what Chekhov said.
Recently, we met someone
who looks just like my mom.
Our whole family was shocked.
How much does she look like her?
Facial recognition software
said 92% similarity
with no blood relation.
Wow, that's serious.
My sister
even flew back from overseas
just because of this.
And now she's insisting we invite
the woman to our house for dinner.
Feels a bit abrupt to me.
Well, meeting someone is fate.
Their being alike
makes it even more special.
You should meet her.
♪In the garden late at night,
all is hushed and still...♪
It came out great.
Not bad at all.
Excellent.
Good.
The Wind and Rainbow Choir
is well-known now.
We might want to consider expanding.
We should bring
Ms. Le Shuishan on board.
You know what?
Gou,
I think
that's a great idea.
I'm all for it.
Me too.
"Unbidden...
the memories come."
You've still got your wits, Ding.
I'll come pick you up later.
Bye.
(Welcome, Le Shuishan!)
This song has been around for a while.
She's here!
Ms. Le.
Come in.
Welcome!
Welcome, Ms. Le!
It's an honor
to have you with us.
Now that Ms. Le's here,
the visuals of our choir
just leveled up!
Zhou, better watch out.
Your wife keeps a tight leash.
Welcome!
I'm Le Shuishan,
the new member.
Please take care of me.
You're Mr. Shen?
Yes.
Mr. Shen Zhuoran?
That's me.
No wonder I thought you looked familiar
when I did your makeup the other day.
You were on the provincial channel's
reading program once.
Yes.
The Literary Beauty of Kun Opera.
That's right.
That's the event.
Yes.
I was there.
You said,
"In life,
there are no better or worse paths.
Just different ones."
That really stuck with me.
Talk about fate.
Ms. Le.
This must be fate.
Fate is up to the heavens.
Action is up to us.
What
do you mean?
Before Gou even called me,
I had already asked Dean Xu to help
recommend me to the choir.
Then, when Gou called to invite me,
I was over the moon!
Me and the Wind and Rainbow Choir
were meant to find each other.
Indeed!
Beautifully said!
Wonderful!
Mr. Shen.
Could I get your autograph?
You even brought the book?
How thoughtful.
I'll sign it right now.
Where should I sign?
Here, or...
Just right here. The first page.
All right.
Will that do?
(The Literary Beauty of Kun Opera
by Le Shuishan)
Haven't seen a man
use a fountain pen in a long time.
How sophisticated.
Ding.
Come here, Ding.
Your handwriting is beautiful.
Thank you.
Dad.
Le Shuishan joined your choir?
Yes.
Did you invite her to dinner
for Mid-Autumn yet?
Not yet.
Today was just our first rehearsal.
Inviting her now
would feel too abrupt.
That's true.
We'll have plenty of chances.
Oh,
and she even
brought one of my books today
and asked for an autograph.
Really?
Le Shuishan's a fan of yours, Dad?
- Of course.
- You never know.
Dad's got charm.
Oh right, Dad.
Try on this new shirt I brought you!
You've got to look your best
at choir practice from now on.
I don't like the color.
It's bright. It suits you.
Look at what Mr. Gou wears.
I can't compare to him.
And this thing
doesn't even have pockets.
Where am I supposed
to put my fountain pen?
Who still carries pens
in their shirts these days?
I do.
Maybe she likes that about him.
Here, you take it.
Dad.
I'll get you one with pockets
for your fountain pen.
Oh, good. You're here. Try this one on.
Your sister bought it.
I'll try it later.
I'm heading to Xuanwu Lake for a run.
It's not like you're catching a flight.
What's the rush?
And Xuanwu Lake?
Takes an hour round-trip
and parking is expensive.
Can't you just run near home?
You weren't happy when I had back pain.
And you still aren't happy
now that I'm running.
The running group at Xuanwu Lake
has great vibes.
Fine.
But try this on first.
You're looking sprightly these days.
This color fits you perfectly.
You'll be the most stylish one
in the group.
Are you sure this suits me?
No thanks.
Take it.
So hard to please.
Okay, not giving it to you then.
I'm off.
Most dedicated runner ever.
Let's eat. Try the fish head.
Eat more, little boy. Eat up.
Gentlemen. Everyone.
How are you finding the food?
This clay pot fish head
is pretty authentic.
Now this is someone who knows food.
Good taste.
What's your last name?
Liu.
Liu, allow me to give you a toast.
Let me tell you.
This clay pot fish head
is a local specialty.
I made it myself.
Liu.
You brought us to a great place.
My son-in-law recommended it.
If he says it's good, it must be good.
Another toast to Liu!
To Liu!
Cheers!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let me tell you.
I admire men who fish.
Why's that?
First,
they're patient.
Right.
Second,
it takes real skill.
Definitely.
And third,
those old fishing guys,
out there in wind and rain.
That's the real deal.
Ma'am!
The bill is on me!
Nobody fights me on this!
I'm paying!
Don't fight!
Don't bother fighting over it.
The bill's already been taken care of.
- Guess who paid?
- Who paid?
Was it you?
Guess!
Who paid?
Come on now.
Let's all
thank Liu together.
It's no big deal.
Thank you, Liu!
Cheers!
I have to admit,
this Western shirt's
pretty flashy.
Oh please.
You wear vibrant colors all the time,
and I can't show off
a little?
It's just fishing.
What's with this getup?
Who are you dressing up for?
Liu Debao.
Who is this Yu Meijiao?
Why did you transfer her
565 yuan?
The fishing group takes turns
buying dinners.
Yu Meijiao is the owner
of a farm stay.
Fishing group dinners? Farm stays?
Liu Debao,
you've got
a lot of funny ideas these days.
Funny ideas?
You only gave me 1,000.
Not 10,000!
What's that supposed to mean?
Not enough money for you?
You think wearing foreign clothes
makes you some overseas Chinese now?
All right.
Take the shirt off.
Wear it when you're out with guests.
Since the day we got married,
I've never even seen my bank card.
You finally give me 1,000,
and now you watch my every move!
What's wrong
with treating everyone to a meal?
It's not a crime.
Lina gave me this, and I can't wear it?
If not now, when?
After I'm dead?
That's...
Liu Debao!
How dare you talk to me like that!
Fine! Wear it!
Go ahead!
Wear it!
Take it!
Here's your bank card too!
I don't want it anymore!
It's right here!
New outfit and new hat!
Chasing a new woman,
and handing out cash!
Once you win the new one over,
just let me know!
I'll gladly make room for her!
The nerve of him!
Headmaster Zhang.
Pleasure working with you.
Likewise.
Ms. Liu.
Please get that clothing design sketch
to us as soon as possible.
No problem.
Looking forward to working together.
Thank you.
What?
28,000 yuan to design a school uniform?
I get
that they're professional designers,
but that's crazy.
Okay. I'll ask around.
What's wrong?
Regretting not
studying design back then.
Designers these days
charge ridiculous rates.
It's just a drawing, isn't it?
Don't sell someone's profession short.
Every industry has its own complexities.
I understand that,
but this project was already
a no-profit one for me.
If the design fee is that steep,
I'll be losing money big time.
They came to you
to save money, didn't they?
You should've thought
about that before taking it on.
You're barely home for meals already.
Can't you just be a bit supportive?
All you do is rain on my parade.
If the penalty for breaking
the contract isn't high,
just walk away from it. Let it go.
No way.
I want to do it.
I'll design it myself.
I'll figure it out.
There's always a way.
You just sounded just like
Ms. Lv Yuan.
And she's right.
Don't interrupt when I'm talking.
I promise.
This one, right here.
Yes?
Hello?
Le.
Mr. Shen.
Sorry to call so late.
Hope I'm not disturbing you?
No, not at all. Go ahead.
It's nothing major.
I just wanted to ask
if you're free for Mid-Autumn Festival.
Yes, I am.
What's up?
Well,
my daughter flew back from abroad
to celebrate.
While overseas, she followed your...
Channel.
Right.
She's a fan.
She asked if we could invite you over
for a casual dinner.
Just a little
Mid-Autumn celebration.
So I thought I'd ask.
I'd love to.
Are you sure I wouldn't be a bother?
Not at all.
We'd be honored
to have you celebrate with us.
Great. See you then.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Dad!
I'm so happy!
Ms. Le is coming!
I'll put the pastries in the fridge.
Save them for Ms. Le.
All right.
♪Yo, yo♪
♪Quiet now, let me sing♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Stretch your legs,
shake your arms, stand tall♪
♪Go, go, go, the path
is right beneath your feet♪
♪For the sake of your health♪
♪And the ones who care about you♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Afraid not,
it all begins with a single step♪
♪Exercise is the best medicine♪
♪Step by step,
we walk towards good health♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you taken in
the sunset views today?♪
♪Love the sunshine on sunny days,
love the rain on rainy ones♪
♪Whatever you want to do today,
it's up to you♪
♪It's all up to you♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you mastered
tomorrow's songs yet?♪
♪Whatever mood you're in,
come and join us♪
♪Swing your arms
and let happiness lead the way♪
♪La la la♪
♪Without small steps,
there's no journey of a thousand miles♪
♪A journey of a thousand miles
begins with a single step♪
♪Let's put down our phones♪
♪And swing our arms♪
♪Stride boldly into the spring♪
♪So many surprises
await in the distance♪
♪Stride boldly towards them♪
♪Start right now♪
♪This is the best time
to invest in your health♪
♪Life is all about moving your body♪
♪Energy never rests from dawn till dusk♪
♪Brilliance and vitality♪
♪Make the biggest secret
to a lasting bloom♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you taken in
the sunset views today?♪
♪Love the sunshine on sunny days,
love the rain on rainy ones♪
♪Whatever you want to do today,
it's up to you♪
♪It's all up to you♪
♪Have you walked
ten thousand steps today?♪
♪Have you mastered
tomorrow's songs yet?♪
♪Whatever mood you're in,
come and join us♪
♪Swing your arms
and let happiness lead the way♪
♪La la la♪