=Love Again=
=Episode 3=
Didn't you touch her hand?
Keep your voice down.
I told you to keep your voice down.
With my body and my age,
forget it.
You think about your age now?
You were 17 when you touched her hand.
Now that you let go,
you are 70 years old.
Don't be such a loser, will you?
Self-awareness is a valuable trait.
Besides, I think...
I think Shen Qing and Lina
aren't particularly supportive of it.
Shen.
Taking good care of yourself
is the best support
you can give your children.
Think about it.
If you take Ms. Lian home,
won't the whole family
welcome her with open arms?
I'm telling you.
Tomorrow is your last chance.
Confess to her.
Let the secret out.
Con...
Confess?
Isn't that too fast?
Look at you dawdling.
Do you want to be single forever?
Keep your voice down.
Don't be so mad. Come on.
Sit.
How...
How should I confess my feelings?
I think you should sing a song for her.
Sing a song?
I can't sing.
Reciting a poem is my forte.
Fine.
Shen, please don't recite a poem.
Have you forgotten
about the Mid-Autumn Festival party?
Didn't you land yourself in the hospital
with your recital?
Fine.
Enough of this.
Let's sing then.
Poems express intent,
while songs perpetuate words.
Let's sing...
What song should I sing?
Why don't you sing the song
when I confessed my love?
"Wildflowers".
Let me tell you.
As soon as I finished singing,
Tianzhen agreed immediately.
Is it that magical?
Wildflowers?
How do you sing it?
Give me a minute.
Let me show you.
♪For whom
do wildflowers on the mountain♪
♪Bloom and fade?♪
♪Waiting quietly to see
if someone will pick them♪
The lyrics are quite well written.
♪Just like that flower,
I wait for his arrival♪
Mom, I think Lian Yilian is quite good.
She's friendly.
She's even the head nurse.
A hospital remains unchanging,
but patients come and go frequently.
Right? There are many people
who are better and younger
than your father-in-law.
A head nurse?
Why is she still single?
I heard it was because
she had to take care of her son.
Son?
Her son wasn't in good health.
Her son.
A son with poor health is scarier
than one who lives off his parents.
Right? She...
- I'll leave.
- Go.
- Go play for a while.
- I'll leave.
Go play for a while.
I'm telling you.
She must have other intentions.
Mom, you're doing it again.
Is there now truth, goodness, and beauty
in the world?
Goodness and beauty.
I'm leaving then.
I'm telling you.
Let me know when your father-in-law
is discharged from the hospital.
We'll get prepared, handle it swiftly,
and cut off all possibilities.
Mom.
I left an exercise book at school.
I have to go back and get it.
Why didn't you stay at school?
I need to rush home to cook.
Didn't you take me away?
I'll take the subway and be back soon.
Be careful.
- Got it.
- Watch out for the cars!
Lian, bed two has finished the IV drip.
Okay.
Lian, have you read the apology letter
from the family member who made a scene?
We've gotten justice.
Yay.
Lin.
Well...
I have something to do on Tuesday.
Can I switch shifts with you?
Sure.
Thanks.
Professor Shen
is getting discharged on Tuesday.
Are you
not going to bid goodbye to him?
No need.
♪For whom do wildflowers on the mountain
bloom and fade♪
♪Waiting quietly to see
if someone will pick them♪
Grandpa.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see you, Grandpa.
Will you be discharged
the day after tomorrow?
Yes, sit down.
Grandpa.
Is Ms. Lian your girlfriend now?
No.
Don't talk nonsense.
You...
You haven't confessed?
No.
Grandpa.
Didn't you tell me
that courage is the greatest quality
of a human being?
You got to be brave.
I was going to give this
to someone else.
I'll let you use it first.
Take it.
Who is it for?
Don't ask.
I won't tell you even if you ask me.
Grandpa.
I'll tell you when you succeed.
You have secrets now.
Grandpa.
Grandma appeared in my dream.
She told me
she came into this world with nothing
and took a lot of love with her
when she left.
She's satisfied.
She wants to thank you,
but she's shy.
Because we Chinese always say
that family members
don't need to be formal with each other.
Yes.
But she still has to say it.
Otherwise,
how will you know
she gave you a five-star rating?
Really?
Of course.
Tell me
what else did Grandma say?
Grandma also asked you
to love the sunshine on sunny days
and love the rain on rainy days.
Grandpa.
Grandma wants you to be happy.
You're quite a smooth talker.
Lide Pharmaceutical has a patent
called NPI.
Dr. Qin suggested that we bring it in.
(Shen Dai)
Go on.
This is a tumor blood vessel disruptor.
It's effective
for our M701 and M703 targeted drugs.
If the introduction is successful,
it will greatly accelerate
our research and development.
It's almost time to start work.
I'll ask Jin to send an email
to inquire about the price.
Because there are many companies
eyeing this patent.
So we must hurry up.
If you have any specialized inquiries,
consult Dr. Qin.
If you have any questions, just ask me.
I'll go work on my experiment first.
Okay, thank you.
- Dr. Qin, thank you.
- It's okay.
I was embarrassed to say
when the scientist was here.
About the price...
Don't worry.
I'll ask the finance team
to calculate the cost-effectiveness.
It's a good thing
that I recruited you from the Big Four.
Otherwise, what would I do?
Stop making random confessions.
Alright, go home. It's getting late.
Go home?
My dad will be discharged.
I have a lot of work to do.
I'll go back to work.
Don't exhaust yourself.
You should hurry home.
I have plans tonight.
Take good care of yourself.
(Inpatient)
♪Pat me on the shoulder, and I'll...♪
♪Do whatever you say♪
♪Swaying flowers♪
♪She needs your comfort too♪
♪Don't let her...♪
♪Grow old and wither♪
It's time to get off work, Ms. Lian.
I got to go.
Okay.
For whom do wildflowers on the mountain
bloom and fade...
♪Waiting quietly to see
if someone will pick them♪
Yilian.
I'm old
and in poor health.
God arranged for me
to be hospitalized here
so that I could meet you.
I can't let God down.
I...
I wrote an acrostic poem for you.
Listen to the rain under the roof.
You're as beautiful
as tomorrow's flower.
Lone figure on a spring night.
I want to confess to you my secret.
I now change "My secret"
to "Until we grow old together".
I want to confess to you
until we grow old together.
I want to be with you.
Let's be together as long as we can.
Chocolates from my grandson.
There are even chocolates.
I'll apply some glue
on this handrail.
Your father can use it
when he comes home tomorrow.
Shen Qing.
Look.
Set an alarm on my phone.
The doctor said
your father has several medicines
that he has to take on time.
What time should I set?
Two are before dinner.
Two are after dinner.
Here?
Yes.
Is it my dad?
♪For whom do wildflowers on the mountain
bloom and fade...♪
How come you're back?
Weren't you going home on Tuesday?
That's right, Dad.
I'll get discharged when I recover.
What difference
does Monday or Tuesday make?
It's not a good place, right?
Shen Duole, what's going on?
What's that supposed to mean?
What gestures are those?
Fine.
I'll explain.
In-laws.
Ever since Jingmin died,
I've been depressed.
Today, I took the first step
to express my feelings to Ms. Lian.
Duole said it well.
Duole told me
to love the sunshine on sunny days
and love the rain on rainy days.
What was I like in the past?
I was afraid of the sun on sunny days
and scared of getting wet on rainy days.
I want to change
my attitude toward life.
I get it now.
If I live my life well,
it will be the greatest support
for my children.
And you,
Baoqin.
I remember the shoes.
You don't need Shen Qin to buy them now.
I know how to order online now.
Just wait for delivery.
By the way,
I would like to solemnly say this.
During my time in hospital,
you all have been busy running around
and worried.
You guys worked hard.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Dad, you...
Dad, well...
♪For whom do wildflowers on the mountain
bloom and fade♪
♪Waiting quietly to see
if someone will pick them♪
Shen Dai.
Lina.
Why does it sound like
the background music has changed?
Yes.
He switched to "Wildflowers".
No longer
listening to "Butterfly Lovers"?
Not bad.
Dad has cheered up.
I told you.
Hospitals
are good schools.
When a person gets hospitalized,
many things
naturally become clear to them.
Yeah, it's really
a good school.
Lina.
Why do I feel like
you mean something else?
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
Really.
Why close the door then?
Just say what you want to say.
You made me say it.
I just think
love is really nourishing.
Shen Dai, why don't you find a partner?
Liu Lina.
Do women like matchmaking
when they get older?
Shen Dai.
Alright, I'll stop talking.
I'm busy. Bye.
Shen Qing.
How can your sister
be so unappreciative?
What did she do?
I just asked her to find a partner,
and she got angry with me.
She even asked,
"Do women like matchmaking
when they get older?"
I sincerely thank your whole family.
Calling me old?
I got older
from doing chores for your family.
She's been hurt in relationships before.
You know that.
That scumbag
had her wrapped around his finger,
and she endured it in silence.
No need to bring up irrelevant history.
If I don't talk about it,
no one in your family will.
Shen Dai is still living abroad
at an old age.
She's all alone.
What should she do when she gets old?
Besides,
when are you going to tell your sister
about your dad and Ms. Lian?
Don't bother.
I'll find a chance to tell her.
(WeChat: Shen Dai)
She's complaining about me.
Qing, control your wife.
Can she have some sense of boundaries?
She keeps persuading me to get married.
Is her own marriage successful?
Don't I know what it's like
when you two argue?
What's that supposed to mean?
How would your sister know
when we argue?
How do I know how she knew?
You don't want this marriage anymore,
do you?
You even told your sister.
Don't over interpret it. Well...
Come on. Let's review it.
Why do we always argue?
Are you kidding me?
Reviewing
when we've been married for years?
This...
How could I have forgotten?
An Ruifeng asked me to go
to the company for a meeting today.
How could I forget?
You only have one day off every week.
Yet you still can't rest?
We're a startup company.
Just wait until we get listed.
Listed? Listed for what?
I'm leaving.
Will you be back for lunch?
I'll order takeout.
Don't bother.
I've already bought the ingredients.
Shen Duole.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the library
with my classmates
to study for excellence.
Yilian.
What are you doing?
I just bought some food.
I'm going back to work
after I finish eating.
Where are you?
I'm about to go to the library.
Look.
Behind me.
Did you see?
There are many lively elderly.
I still think you're the healthiest.
I still have to work hard.
I need to work hard.
Have you taken
your blood pressure medicine?
Not yet.
How worrying.
You have to take
antihypertensive drugs regularly.
Otherwise, it will harm your health.
I've taken my medicine.
I'm just kidding you.
But
I feel like I can't live
without you.
Alright, I'll stop talking.
I have to go back to work.
I'm entering the building now.
The signal is bad.
Let's talk later.
Okay.
Yilian.
Don't work too hard.
I'll be waiting for your call
at anytime and anywhere.
Alright.
Okay, it's lunchtime.
Hello, Ms. Lian.
(Ms. Yilian, I really need you.)
Dad.
Duole and Shen Qing aren't home,
so let's have rice with toppings.
Today...
Where did the food come from?
Coming.
All done.
Hello.
Ms. Lian.
Professor Shen happens to like
snails stuffed with meat.
I know how to make it.
It smells really good.
Yilian.
I'll ask my children
to call you Aunt Lian from now on.
Sure.
I think it's a good idea.
Aunt Lian? Will it make you sound old?
No, I think it's pretty good.
Just do whatever Professor Shen says.
Get her a set
- of bowl and chopsticks.
- Okay.
I'll get them myself.
Just sit down.
Just eat the ready-made food today.
Sit down.
Sure.
I'll eat this then.
Don't just eat the rice with toppings.
You can eat whatever you want.
Here.
Try Aunt Lian's cooking.
When eating shrimp,
you must remove
the black vein in the middle.
Although it's a bit troublesome,
it doesn't bother me.
Look.
Professor Shen,
you have such skillful hands.
Look.
It's out now.
It's true.
It doesn't bother me.
Why aren't you eating?
Here, dig in. Dip it in vinegar.
Come on.
Dig in.
Okay.
I'm going to eat this snail.
Dad, you guys eat.
I'll go home to put away the clothes.
I'll go back and eat.
Sure.
Let me add more food for you.
Okay, sure.
It's enough.
Let me give you some more.
No need.
You guys eat.
Lina.
Recently,
I keep forgetting to take my medicine.
It's dangerous if I don't take
the high blood pressure medicine.
I asked Aunt Lian to supervise me.
Tell Shen Qing
that Aunt Lian will move in next week.
Here.
This one.
Don't work so hard
that you end up not eating.
Okay.
Fragrance.
Shen Qing.
Your stepmother is coming.
Stepmother?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Ms. Lian is moving in.
They're moving in together.
It's going to rain,
and your dad is going to get married.
This isn't
a simple romantic relationship.
Shen Qing.
Your stepmother
is only a few years older than you.
How do you feel?
It's not even settled yet.
Don't talk nonsense.
"High blood pressure is dangerous,"
"so I've asked Aunt Lian
to supervise me."
Am I not a human being?
Can't I supervise him?
I've already set the alarm on my phone
to ring three times a day.
No, they're moving in together?
Isn't it too fast?
Shen Dai doesn't even know
about their relationship yet.
Now great.
She'll explode.
Don't tell Dai.
It's already chaotic enough.
She'll make a scene if she finds out.
Are we not going to say anything?
Are we keeping it a secret forever?
Now,
this new lung cancer-targeted drug,
M701,
has entered
the first phase of clinical trials.
Your company's patented NPI
will greatly advance
the research and development.
Once M701 is successfully launched,
the tumor remission rate
for terminal lung cancer
will reach 62.9%.
It's amazing.
What you have here is truly amazing.
My mother had primary lung cancer.
Five years later,
it metastasized to the breast
chest, and head.
In the end, her illness was beyond cure.
So M701 holds extraordinary significance
for me.
During business negotiation,
we shouldn't
talk about our private affairs,
but why did we bring it up?
It's because we want to express
that this matter is closely related
to all of us.
It's also to express our sincerity
in purchasing.
We also know that any patent's
research and development
is very difficult.
The effort and cost invested
can't be measured in money,
but
given our company's current strength,
the highest price
we can offer
is 6.8 million US dollars.
Mr. An, Mr. Shen.
We will be honored if we can contribute
to the Chinese pharmaceutical industry.
We also recognize
that China is a huge market.
So
we also hope to achieve
a deep and close cooperation
with your company.
We accept
this price.
Great.
Thank you.
Let me tell you, Peng Yulan.
There are many outstanding females,
but I highly recommend you.
Just rest for a while in the hospital.
Look at the old man.
It's been more than half a month
since he was discharged.
There's no movement at all.
The head nurse is young,
so she has a lot of options.
Right?
You should have confidence.
- You can't...
- I'll do it myself.
You have a chance.
No.
Let's go.
Why did you take that?
No problem.
Can you do it?
- Yes.
- Oh my God.
Oh no.
It's a big deal this time.
It's a big deal.
No, I'll stop talking.
I'll stop talking.
I'll hang up first.
- Shen Qing is back.
- This...
You came back just in time.
- This is...
- We're moving.
Hurry up.
No need to bother him.
Hurry. Here.
Don't just stand there.
- Move.
- Sorry.
Move it upstairs.
Why are there so many things?
What's going on?
Mom, you came.
No.
Let me introduce you.
This is...
Ms. Lian. My father's...
We've met.
Yes, they've met.
We've met in the hospital.
Shen Qing.
You can't move these things
with these clothes on.
Why are you moving items
wearing branded clothes?
- Well...
- Forget it...
I'm telling you, Ms. Lian.
Shen Qing has a successful career.
Yet you asked him to carry things.
Give me.
No, why let him carry so many things?
I raise my son for so long
but only use him for a moment.
What's wrong with that?
Go.
You're really careful
with how you use your son.
He still needs to make money.
Alright.
Let me formally introduce you.
Because I just got discharged,
I need Lian to take care of me.
So she moved here.
This is Lina's mother.
My in-law, Sun Baoqin.
Sun Baoqin.
Let's officially get to know each other.
- I'm Lian Yilian.
- Yes. You two should get to know each other.
Great.
Sorry to bother you, Ms. Lian.
The old cadre...
The old cadre's hospital ward
has been moved home.
We don't have to go to the hospital
when we're sick from now on.
We'll just find you.
Sure.
- No...
- Just tell me if you need anything.
Find me for these things.
I'll do these things.
No.
Let me tell you. When I was young...
You're not that young anymore.
It doesn't matter.
Back in our factory,
I carried the blower...
How could I let you help me?
No, give them to me.
You have a small physique.
You can do the injections
and give out medicine.
Let me do the work
of the laboring people.
Don't snatch it from me.
You two should stop arguing.
Press the elevator button for her.
Okay.
Let me take this.
Alright, go.
- I'll press...
- Press the button.
Go and press it.
Hurry. Don't worry about this.
You're back.
What happened?
Didn't you go to negotiate?
How come you're so tired?
What else can it be?
Downstairs.
My dad caught me
to help him move things.
Whose stuff are you moving?
Whose stuffs do you think they are?
Ms. Lian?
Is she already moving in?
By the way, your mom is downstairs too.
Let me see.
It's okay.
Are you tired?
- It's okay.
- Mom.
Put it down.
Let me get you some water.
It's quite heavy.
I'm born to work.
Look.
Thank you.
- It's okay.
- You're sweating.
Give her some water.
If it weren't for your mother,
who knows when this pile of stuff
will be moved up here.
Alright.
It's okay.
Don't move any more things.
Let me do it.
By the way,
Lina's mom,
I bought you the shoes.
Give it to your mom.
Thank you, Dad.
I'm telling you.
I spent a day searching online
to find this.
It suits your mom's temperament.
Is that so?
Try them on now.
Thank you, Zhuoran.
Thank you.
Do you like them?
Yes.
They suit me very well.
Good.
Very good. They look like
they suit me at first glance.
I don't need...
Alright, let's get to work.
What are you doing here?
Get to work.
Don't just stand there.
Let me do these.
Let me put it there.
Alright.
- I...
- Leave it here for now.
Ms. Lian.
Are your clothes
supposed to go
in that room?
Let me.
Don't bother.
Let me do it.
It's heavy.
It's okay.
It's not heavy.
Ms. Lian.
Are these
osmanthus?
Yes.
Lina.
I think we should move this easel
to Shen Dai's room.
Isn't it just fine to put it here?
Mom, don't be bossy.
Ms. Lian has many things.
You need to make room for her.
Alright.
Let's do it together.
I can do it alone.
How about...
Let me help...
I'll do it later.
No.
Don't worry about it.
Be careful.
Be careful. Don't break it. Be careful.
Well...
You even close the door?
What did I say?
What did you say?
Men
can't live without women,
no matter how old they are.
Look at your father-in-law.
He's so fast.
The spaceship has entered the house.
Mom, think positively.
Someone is taking care of Dad.
And she's a professional.
Anyway, it's done.
We can only let them be.
Right?
But
it's not bad that your father-in-law
found someone younger.
You don't need to serve him.
But
keep an eye
on your father-in-law's salary card
and property deed.
Those are for Duole.
You can't let down your guard.
How could I even see his salary card?
How could you be so useless?
Look, you have to be tough.
Do you know?
Other things aside,
let's just talk about Duole.
He's clever.
His athletic ability is well-developed.
Who shall we thank?
It's our family's genetics.
The Shen family
are all blockheads.
So you have to be tough.
Be confident.
Look.
The outsider has moved in.
Mom, do you think you're singing?
Soften your voice.
The outsider has moved in.
You need to improve...
Okay, I got it.
Stop talking and go out.
Okay.
Ms. Lian, there...
There are so many clothes.
Do you want to move all of them
into the room?
Put the shoes in first.
Gosh.
Mom, these shoes...
Put them in there.
These shoes are beautiful.
I think you should buy a pair like this.
They're pretty, but I can't wear
something with diamonds like this.
Ms. Lian can wear it.
Why can't you wear it? Right?
Women should shine
when they need to shine.
Ms. Lian, don't you think so?
Yes.
Leave them there.
I'll sort them out later.
Alright, stop sitting there.
Hurry up and work.
Don't worry about me. This is fine.
Let's go.
It's okay.
A four-piece set?
How elegant.
It's good.
What are you using them on?
I'll do it myself.
You two can do something else.
You have to wash them first.
You have to wash them.
I've washed them.
Okay.
Let's change all the sheets.
Ms. Lian, to tell the truth.
I really admire you.
You're really adaptable.
I can't do it. Really.
If I sleep in a new bed,
I won't be able to fall asleep.
We always work the night shift.
The bed doesn't bother us anymore.
We'll take a nap in the lounge
whenever we can.
My mother-in-law
loved this coarse bed sheet
before she passed away.
I have to keep it for her.
Sure.
Let's go.
Okay.
There's one more here.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Where are you going?
To help with moving.
No need.
My mom has moved everything upstairs.
No.
Mom isn't young.
What if she exhausts herself?
The Liu family
is committed to serving the Shen family.
But Ms. Lian also caused my mom
to exert herself.
I'll talk to Dad.
He can order me around,
but it's inappropriate
to order Mom around like this.
Don't go.
You'll get mad after you go.
What's wrong?
The female head of the household
is being replaced.
A big change is happening.
Even the bed sheet has been removed.
Love the sunshine on sunny days.
This is too fast.
This is too much.
My mom is right.
Once a man decides to move on,
he'll take action decisively.
These are Mom's favorite coarse cloth.
I took them back as a keepsake.
This is too fast.
Dear.
Let's treasure them.
What's wrong?
I'll take it away.
How did Jingmin's slippers
get here?
You...
Sleep here.
I'm afraid that it's chilly over there.
Do you think
I'm a bit too hasty
in moving here?
No.
You're not hasty at all.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Duole.
Stop studying. Go brush your teeth.
Dear, why are you washing it now?
Just let me do it.
I washed it while I was at it.
There's no sunshine.
Duole.
Where are you doing?
I want to ask Grandpa
about a Chinese language question.
You're not allowed to go.
You're not allowed to go tonight.
Grandpa is asleep.
Which color should I use?
Use green.
Green is refreshing and healthy.
How about this?
Use orange for these three
to make them more obvious.
Right?
Let's do whatever you say.
Dad.
Aunt Lian.
I washed the sheets.
I'll leave them in Shen Dai's room.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Right?
How about you write down
saffron
and goji berries?
How do I write
the Chinese character for "Saffron"?
I suddenly forgot.
That's because
you keep playing with your phone.
Here, get a piece of paper.
- I'll tell you how to write it.
- Okay.
Grass radical.
Write the stroke correctly,
and you'll be able to remember
the character easily.
Right?
You write it nicer.
Lina.
Dad.
What are you writing?
I... Well...
Ms. Lian made me
a clock-in form for taking medicine.
She said it'll be easier to remember.
I won't forget what I eat.
How professional.
It's clear at a glance.
Come on.
This will do.
Let's change to another color.
What color do you want to change to?
This yellow one then.
Look at this.
Which one do you think is better?
Okay.
My grandson sent me something.
What did he send?
I want to be
with you.
Let's be together as long as we can.
The combined age of these two people
goes back to the Qing Dynasty,
yet they're doing this.
(May Your Wish Come True)
What are you doing?
Didn't you ask me
to like everything you post?
You can't like this one.
Alright.
I'll delete it.
I'll repost.
I can't like it?
I'm telling you.
I'll delete this and repost it.
Don't like it.
I won't.
I want to be
with you.
Let's be together as long as we can.
Keep quiet.
Dai.
Dai's WeChat.
Hello?
Dai.
Hello.
Aunt.
Can you talk now?
I have something to ask you.
I can talk.
Go ahead.
Is my dad in a relationship?
Is your dad in a relationship?
Well...
Dai, why did you think of asking this?
Darn it.
You saw what I posted on Moments,
didn't you?
I forgot about it.
Aunt.
What happened?
Dai.
If I tell you,
don't tell anyone
I told you. Okay?
Look.
Shen Qing
doesn't want to tell you either, right?
Your dad...
Your dad is not only in a relationship,
but Ms. Lian has also moved in.
She even changed your mother's bedsheets
to hers.
What did you say?
♪This water♪
♪It watches the spring snow melt♪
♪It guards the home through all seasons♪
♪Drip drop, under the eaves♪
♪This water♪
♪It fills your cup with tea♪
♪It washes away the past♪
♪Every splash♪
♪Is a gesture of love to the world♪
♪Time is like water,
always carrying its sediment♪
♪Leaving memories behind for her,
far away♪
♪It will settle into clarity♪
♪It will stir up waves and ripples♪
♪Embracing change every step of the way♪
♪Memories ebb and flow like water♪
♪It adds to the journey,
it flows in the present♪
♪It answers life with a smile♪
♪It takes the weight of it all♪
♪And then gently lets it all down♪
♪This water♪
♪It watches the spring snow melt♪
♪It guards the home through all seasons♪
♪Drip drop, under the eaves♪
♪This water♪
♪It fills your cup with tea♪
♪It washes away the past♪
♪Every splash♪
♪Is a gesture of love to the world♪
♪Time is like water,
always carrying its sediment♪
♪Leaving memories behind for her,
far away♪
♪It will settle into clarity♪
♪It will stir up waves and ripples♪
♪Embracing change every step of the way♪
♪Memories ebb and flow like water♪
♪It adds to the journey,
it flows in the present♪
♪It answers life with a smile♪
♪It takes the weight of it all♪
♪And then gently lets it all down♪