[Translate By Machine]
[The sound of ripples]
(Eiji Eiji's M monologue) When I think about it, I started from that time.
Maybe everything was beginning to change
[Seabirds's cry and waves]
[Resonating footsteps]
(Naohiko Naohiko M) When I think about it, everything might have begun to change since then.
(Eiji) And then, some girls from other schools too
(Eiji) He's always chasing me
(Boy) Seriously? (Boy) What?
I was told by Eiji.
"I forgot about that wallet."
Oh ha ha ha...
No, it's a wallet!? Isn't it?
It's going to happen! [Boys panicking voice]
You're a transfer student to class 1, so I'm in the classroom, hurry up, you're like a girl!
[Eiji and the others' fuss]
(Eiji) Cho Naohiko!
- Let's go and see it! - picture?
[Students' fuss]
Let's go a little bit...
- What, which child, which child? - That girl is talking in the middle
(Women) Where did you come from? (Transfer student) Nishinaka
(Female) Wasn't that girl also from Nishinaka?
♪～
Eiji!
(Eiji) Izumi Izumi has returned!? (Izumi) Yes!
Eiji: It's safe because it's not changed
- Huh? You're getting more mature - huh? Where?
If you're going back, just contact me.
[Boys making noise]
No, that childhood friend
[Boys' fuss]
(Naohiko's M Monologue) Summer of the second year of junior high school
I'm at heart
I was jealous of him
(Eiji) Izumi
(Izumi) Huh?
- Izumi is here too - Yes
Oh, this guy is Bessho Naohiko
- I always wear some glasses... - It's not too dirty!
thank you
Yes, please look forward to it Naohiko-kun
Yeah
(Eiji) So let's go (Izumi/Naohiko) Yes
[Three talkers]
(Naohiko's M) Izumi is a so-called transfer family.
He was there until he was in fifth grade and apparently he was close to Eiji from that time onwards.
(3 people) Hello (children) Hello
(Izumi) So I'm here
Ah, why not go home with Naohiko?
- Huh? - No, it's the same direction, right?
I'm over there
Protect Izumi Naohiko from perverts!
(Izumi) What? (Eiji) Ah
(Naohiko) It's the other way around! (Eiji) Haha, right?
(Izumi Eiji) So (Naohiko) See you tomorrow
[Spring's Humor]
Eiji: It's really as usual
I've been a bit off for a long time
-Is that so-Yes
I like reading books but don't like studying
I know him well
Well, he's like a childhood friend
I see...
[Spring's Humor]
(Eiji) Yeeee!
[The three of them were excited]
♪～
(Naohiko's M) A bright spring at my own pace
It was fun to be with the three of us all the time...
(Eiji) Izumi is faster
(Izumi) Nao is late
(Eiji) Well then, babee (Izumi)
(Naohiko) See you tomorrow (Eiji) Tomorrow
(Naohiko's M) This moment when I was back together with Izumi
It was my most enjoyable
(Izumi) And today, Eiji is doing something strange again
(Naohiko's M) But it's autumn in the third year of junior high school...
Even after a year has passed, it will always be about Eiji.
Even though they're just two
I don't feel like we're two
This book
I thought I like it straight
If you like it
thank you
〔footsteps〕
(Eiji) What? That book...
Ah, Izumi lends me...
The one I lent a long time ago!
What...
(Eiji) Izumi I really like it
In the end, I bought it myself
No, it's nostalgic
What's up?
teeth? No no hmm...
Apparently he's going to move again
- Is that so? - This is the fifth time
Eiji is...
Don't you think about confessing to Izumi?
Huh?
Why at the spring? There's no way I think so
I see... That's right
Don't say anything weird
bad
(Naohiko's M) Something that Eiji doesn't have and that's in me...
What I can do...
[The sound of ripples]
[Seabird's Crying]
(Naohiko)
(Izumi) Huh?
I…
I like the fountain
[The sound of ripples]
(Eiji) Well then!
Good luck with Izumi Naohiko!
Thank you, see you later!
(Naohiko and Eiji) Again
(Eiji's M) Winter in the third year of junior high school...
I'm at heart
I was jealous of him
And with bitter memories
We are...
I've become a high school student
[♪~ Light Music Club Performance]
♪（It's time） to blow my fate away
♪（It's time） to confront who you are
♪I admit that I'm a hypocrite
to fear being hurt cowardly
♪（I know） I decided to live this way
♪（I know）
I can never take smartest ways
♪Grant me right to shout out my love
♪to blow my fate away
♪I'll let go of my pride
and confront you
♪Everything is by my side
to shout my love to you
♪Blow my fate away…
Ahh! Damn it!
(Guitar) Come on, Taichi Taichi~ (Taichi) Haha, sorry, sorry!
sorry! One more time! Sorry I did it once more!
(Taichi) Thank you! (Guitar) Last 1 OK It's fine!
(Eiji) Ahhhh, it's the second semester starting today...
Nothing, I've had lunch here with you, and every day just passes by
(Eiji) Haa... (Naohiko) Hehe
Don't sigh when you look at someone's face
a…
Apparently there are transfer students in group 1.
Wow
Transferring to high school is rare,
[Message reception sound]
spring?
Yeah
Are you doing well?
ah
Would you like to go see it? Transfer student
Let's go
(Eiji)Now What is it? (Naohiko) Umm, is it a quiz?
[Popping sound]
(Eiji) Huh?
(Taka) Chick: Why is there a ham cutlet bread?
(Koharu Koharu) Sorry...
I should have bought it but...
[Sound of scavenging inside the bag]
This is it...
Seriously...
(Taka) It's okay, Koharu, say goodbye
Can't use it... it doesn't mean her
(Koharu) Wait, I'll fix it with Taka-kun.
Don't say that...
(Taka) Come on!
It's heavy
(Eiji) Yes...
You go back!
What? Now? Now!? Yes...
Ah, um...
this…
Ah!
Ham cutlet bread...
Bad, that's falling over there...
I was dumped by Taka-kun
Huh? It's my fault!?
It's fine now
(Naohiko) What...
All of this for my boyfriend earlier?
Taka-kun, what you want to eat depends on your mood that day
I have to buy a lot...
Because it's my first boyfriend
I want to be so happy
But...
What is "heavy"?
Did I not go?
[Koharu's sob]
[Sound of scavenging my pocket]
[Koharu's cry]
(Naohiko) It's so heavy...
That's all I liked
(Eiji) No, it's cheating, it's cheating! (Naohiko) Why?
(Eiji) That kindness is no good for women other than Izumi
(Naohiko) You can't get into that kindness
(Eiji) I wonder what it is
Anyway, it's really troublesome
Every time I'm happy and sad
I don't need love after all
- Is that so? - Yeah
Aihara Aihara!
You skipped on duty again as a library committee member during your lunch break!
Ah, that's bad!
You must come after school and I'll get scolded!
yes…
Ahh
Cute and cute...
teeth? Taichi Are you really saying it?
Huh? Ikezawa is serious and cute
- Your hobby is crazy - I don't know that charm
Meow, you're not doing anything!
(Taichi) Wow, he's really cute...
[Message reception sound]
(Taichi) Ah, so cute, the back is cute too
Will you go and see it soon? Transfer student
[Women's talk]
♪～
I'm straight!
(Naohiko) Have you gotten used to it a little?
It's only day one? It's not possible
Hmm, is that so?
Can we go home together today?
Yeah!
It's been a while since Eiji was fine.
Ah, he's back
Yeah
Izumi said he wanted to surprise him, so it was hard to hide it.
Great success~ Hehehe
- Izumi- Huh?
Welcome home
Hehehe
(Eiji) It's so nostalgic (Izumi)
[Three laughter]
(Izumi) It's been a while since we went home together like this.
(Naohiko) Yes (Izumi) Ahhh
Okay, Seagrass Saga!
(Naohiko) I wonder if there is (Izumi) Eh
(Fountain) Was there any?
(Naohiko) What? No (Izumi) Ahaha
(Izumi) Eh, where?
(Naohiko) Ah, there it is! (Izumi) Huh?
[Sigh]
- Oh, what? Oh, amazing! - Ahahaha
(2 people) Yeeee!
(Taichi) Hey
Did you see a transfer student just now?
how was it?
(Eiji) No, why are you?
Don't ask anything you understand
It's because you and Ikezawa aren't alone together.
If you like it, why not contact us quickly?
If I could do that it wouldn't be a pain
I've decided
If he improves his guitar, he'll invite Ikezawa to a live show
So don't skip and go to practice early!
Hmm... damn it
If you put your hand on Ikezawa, don't let him go!
I understand, so go quickly!
You're serious, right?
You're serious?!
(Eiji) Go!
Hmm
(Mizuho Mizuho) Hey, what are you doing when the book is noisy?
If you're bored, help me!
No way!
Can you take that a bit?
yeah?
(Mizuho) That
- Ah!? - It's dangerous!
[The sound of a book falling]
[Sound of bumping] Ugh! I'll be there...
(Eiji) Tsu... Uh...
(Eiji) Are you okay? Ikezawa
Ikezawa?
picture?
Ah yes...
sorry
Is Aihara-kun okay?
ah
I'm fine, I'm strong enough
Hmm
ah…
That's amazing
Well, shall I pick it up?
I'm gonna...
Go on...
Ah...
Aihara-kun, right?
Five pairs
Ah, ham cutlet bread!
I have a request but...
There's a fireworks display soon, right?
So...
I want to go with Bessho Bessho-kun
I want you to cooperate
teeth?
Eh, Aihara-kun are friends, right?
Are you planning to switch to Naohiko?
It's awful to say you're switching!
- Because up until now, with my senior... - I know
It's too early to change my mind...
but…
It was my first time
I got it
I've always given it
So I'm thinking about trying my best to have a new love again
Don't give up, he has a girlfriend
I know
It's Shiosaki Shiosaki Izumi, a transfer student, right?
What? Do you know?
Yes, they're the same class and you'll know if you look at them
It's also wonderful to bear care about her
Don't get in the way
- picture? - Stop it
why?
Anyway, I won't let you get in if you get in the way!
If so...
[Greetings from students]
[The sound of running in]
good morning!
I'm Fujimura Koharu Koharu
We've become the same class, so let's become friends.
Yes, please!
-Yeah! Please, Izumi-chan! - Yeah!
[Eiji's Yawn] Ah, Aihara!
a?
I have a request from you!
fart?
(Taichi) Thank you, I can only ask you.
Please! Please! You can do it!
- You can do it! - Ah, I understand
thank you!
Well, Ikezawa...
Are you bored this Sunday?
picture?
I'm going to a fireworks display with my friends
If you like, could I go with Ikezawa too?
I don't go, I don't like crowds...
(Eiji) I see, that's right!
Sorry! Understood, then
picture?
teeth? a little bit…
[Sigh]
(Eiji) Ah, sorry, that was no good...
(Taichi) Ah...
Ah, but... Thanks
(Eiji) Yes...
(Izumi) There was
(Naohiko) Hey
Would you like to go to the next Sunday Fireworks Display?
(Eiji) Let's go together like that.
- I'm with Taichi... - Ah, I can't go!
Huh?!
Me...
Practice guitar...
That's right...
Either way, there's another one coming
Do you know Fujimura Koharu-chan, who is in the same class as me?
- Huh? - That ham cutlet bread baby
He invited me to become friends and go to the fireworks display with me.
He's such a crazy guy...
[Koharu's humming]
(Girl) And so, the hawk is crying like a puppy
(Taka) Stop, don't say that
- Hey that kid - What?
Who was it?
(Taka) I mean, where are you going today? karaoke?
(Naohiko) It's too late Eiji (Izumi) Hmm, right
(Koharu) Aihara-kun, you're late (Izumi) What are you doing?
(Koharu) What will I be wearing? (Izumi) Isn't it in casual clothes?
(Eiji) Sorry, please keep me waiting! (Naohiko/Izumi) Oh Eiji
(Eiji) Everyone suits you! (Izumi) Thank you
(Naohiko) Eiji Mona (Eiji) Hahaha
(Koharu) Hello Aihara-kun!
Ah... Hello
(The guy at the food stall) Come on!
(Koharu) Looks tasty! (Eiji) It's an apple
(Eiji) Izumi: Big go! (Izumi) Why?
(Izumi) Eiji is big so it's fine, but I guess I can eat (Eiji)...
Eh, which is better? Which do you like Bessho-kun better?
- Is it big? - Big?
I think I'm big too!
(Koharu) Eh, let's do that balloon together
(The guy at the food stall) Oh! Old men! How about this? This is a balloon split
If you break a balloon for three consecutive years, you'll get one prize!
Eh, what is that?!
(The guy at the food stall) That's fine, aim!
Ah!
- It's not good at all! - teeth? So do it!
I'm definitely better
(Izumi) Good luck Koharu-chan
(Koharu) Eeee! [Popping sound]
Wow, amazing!
(Koharu) Yeeee!
-Yeeee! - The guys are good friends!
- Couple? - What? No!
It's not, sorry, sorry, sorry
The whip
-Yeah! - I did it, I'm in!
- Ah, it's really cute - Isn't it cute?
(Eiji) Ahaha (Izumi) Oh!
- Will you do it? - What, I want to do it!
(Naohiko/Izumi) Oh (Eiji) What? I want to do it too, I want to do it!
good? I want to do it! please! It's my first time!
You'll need a mask~ The festival
Haha, what? Even if I remove it...?
(Everyone) Hahaha
(Koharu) Hey, Bessho-kun, which one would suit me?
- Isn't this? It's this, it suits you-- What is this
- Is this alive? - Ahaha
- Damn it! - Ahh!
No no!
- Okay! - Oh! Amazing!
- Yeeee! -Yeeee!
That's amazing! Yeeee! Don't do it, you!
You give me that duck, for me!
(Naohiko) What do you eat? (Izumi) What? What do you want to eat?
(Naohiko/Izumi) Hmm...
Whatever you do, it's useless
a! What cute Bessho-kun, why don't you do it together?
- You're shooting? - Let's get that together...
Let's do it with me Fujimura
- Why Aihara-kun... - No, I'm better than Naohiko
- What? Is that so? - That's right!
- Sorry, please for those two - Yes
- first time? - It's not my first time, it's delicious!
(Eiji) Are you going? (Everyone) Good luck
(Eiji) Let's go! (Shop owner) Yes
[Speech sound] (Everyone) Ahhhh!
[Crow's cry]
[Festival music]
- Why can't you get any? Damn it! - You too!
Haa, I'm feeling hungry
Ha!
Bessho-kun: There they sell candy apples over there, so why don't you go and buy them?
- Let's go with me Fujimura- Why?
I'll treat you to the apology for the shooting I just said, so come on, let's go!
Okay, later, Izumi Naohiko
- Yes - Oh
- Yes - Yes
You should just take it apart! You didn't get in the way, right?
Why does Aihara-kun have permission to my love?
The hard part later is Fujimura
I don't know
I want to work hard and do what I want to do for myself
[Sigh]
Fujimura's selfishness!
Don't destroy the relationship between the two of you!
Why do I have to hold back my feelings?
Is it not good to have someone you like?
I don't know about that...
If you don't know, please leave it alone and don't get in the way
♪～
[Spinning sound]
That's no good!
Fujimura...
Let's date me
Oh!? What are you talking about?
That's right...
No, that's right, but um...
Anyway, I want him to give up on Naohiko...
Why is that far? Aihara-kun has nothing to do with it
[The sound of fireworks and cheers]
(Izumi) Hey, look, Heart (Naohiko) Oh!
Hmm
That's what it is...
Understood
It's fine, let's date
fart?
Please, Aihara-kun
[The sound of fireworks]
Maybe Eiji was very concerned about it?
So that Nao and I can be alone together
Certainly something that someone might think
Yeah
For Eiji...
I wonder if there's any girl you like?
I don't really understand that...
He said he didn't need love or anything like that.
Is that so?
It seems like it's strangely hard to hear...
(Naohiko) That's weird... (Eiji) Hey
(Naohiko) It was late, where did you go?
(Eiji) Bad, I'm a bit lost
I have a report to Bessho-kun and Izumi-chan
We've been dating
- Huh? - What?
Really?!
Well, that's how it is...
To Eiji...
she?
Congratulations!
(Naohiko) Congratulations! (Izumi) Hehehehe
Anyway, when?!
(Izumi) Certainly
[Guitar practice sound]
Hmm... Ah, it's complicated!
Damn it...
(Naohiko) I felt relieved
(Eiji) Why?
(Naohiko) You said you don't need love or anything
I was wondering why
Well, Fujimura's yukata
It means that I fell in love at first sight!
I see
[Clashing sound]
Hey, can I have lunch with you too?
What!? Why?!
I'm Aihara-kun's girlfriend
Bessho-kun, should I exchange side dishes for my lunch box? I'm good at boiling food...
Haa... you come just a moment!
Huff, heuff
(Taichi) Hey
Who is the child now?
(Naohiko) Fujimura
It's Eiji's girlfriend
she!?
(Koharu) What?
What... Hey! a little bit!
Don't let me go!
Because...
Bessho-kun is dedicated to Izumi-chan
I thought it might be difficult to go straight to...
No, it's not possible
If you're nearby, you might change your mind!
Naohiko isn't that kind of person!
People's minds can easily change, right?
Taka-kun was like that...
unfortunately
There's a guy who's so persistent and devoted
Hmm
That's...
About Bessho-kun?
Or...
About yourself?
teeth? What are you talking about...
Aihara-kun is
You like Izumi-chan, right?
He told me to date
It's not for Bessho-kun, but for protecting Izumi-chan, right?
There's no way that's the case!
Don't be a good person, let's cooperate
If the two separate...
I'm with Bessho-kun
Aihara-kun is Izumi-chan
Maybe we can date you?
You're amazing
What? How can I live so selfishly?
Aihara-kun is the one
How can I hold my feelings so hard?
Isn't it painful?
(Koharu) Let's go back
[Whisper] (Taichi) Aihara~
Huh? Aihara?
Aihara
Aihara~ Aihara kun
Aihara?
Aihara
Aihara hmm? Aihara-kun
Aihara! Aihara! Aihara! Aihara...
(Mizuho) What's it for? (Taichi) Oh!?
(Taichi) Ah, Ikezawa...
Aihara Didn't you see it?
I'm not on duty today so I think I'm home already
Ah, is that so?
I was trying to question you damn
Something happened!?
no…
That guy...
Apparently she's got it
[Falling sound]
(Mizuho) Ah (Taichi) Ahhhh...
Ikezawa Maybe...
what?
[Izumi and the others laugh]
(Koharu) It's fun to go home with the four of us like this
It's like a double date
- Hehe, that's right- Yes!
Oh, come to think of it
How did Bessho-kun and Izumi-chan start dating?
When I was in the second year of junior high school, Izumi moved over here
Eiji introduced me to me, that's what I think it was.
Hmm, that's right
What about Eiji? What did you like about Koharu?
Where is...
- Well, it's all, it's all! -Huh
Eiji: That's changed, you're honest
It's not changed...
Even if it were Naohiko, I never thought there would be a day when I could hear such words from Eiji's mouth.
Well!
(Koharu) What? You can drink black coffee (Naohiko) Yes, you can drink it
Amazing I can't drink
- So I'm over here - So I'm over here too!
teeth?
(Koharu) See you tomorrow (Naohiko) Ah tomorrow
- See you tomorrow
(Eiji)
[The sound of pushing away] (Eiji) Hey!
What are you doing? Actually, if you want to cross your arms, say it first!
(Koharu) The reason the two of them got closer was Aihara-kun made it
If your rival is a best friend, you won't be able to move even more?
[Bike driving sound]
(Driver) Hey, it's dangerous!
[High breath]
Don't say anything you understand
(Izumi) Eiji and Koharu-chan
Are you really dating?
(Naohiko) Why?
(Izumi)
It's like a feeling of discomfort...
(Naohiko) Are you so curious? About Eiji...
(Izumi) What?
(Naohiko) No...
If you don't date
You don't understand the point of pretending you're dating, right?
(Izumi) That's right...
Yeah
[Running sound]
(Director) Okay, the upload is over, let's take a break
(Members) Yes! (Chairman) Hey, one year, come run three more laps!
(1 year) What? (Chief) Go!
(1 year) Yes! (1 year) Tight...
(Koharu) Haa...
[The sound of the wind]
(Mizuho) Aihara-kun's girlfriend...
Yes...
she…?
Ah, one pair here
(Koharu) Wow, that was the best
I'm glad I was able to watch Bessho-kun's morning practice!
It was super cool!
Yeah…
Next time, Aihara-kun will also invite us to go on a date with the four of us.
(Izumi) Oh, Koharu-chan...
Why did Koharu-chan date Eiji?
(Koharu) Haa...
what happened? Suddenly...
I wonder what kind of thing I fell in love with
Ah, Ikezawa-san!
Is Ikezawa a library committee member?
Yes, that's true but...
Next time, can you tell me about a book that Aihara-kun might like?
See, Aihara-kun, you see, but you love books, right?
That gap is nice
I understand, I'll think about it
thank you!
[Performance sounds and lively voice]
[Sound of air in]
Ah, I'm not tired somehow
We also liked the haunted house
What role does Izumi play?
A woman with a cleft mouth? Is Konaki old man?
- Why don't you go and see it later? - I hate it, it's scary
Who is Eiji going to play with today?
Hmm, I haven't decided anything else
Isn't it Fujimura?
Ah, yes! Yes That's right, That's right, Fujimura!
I'm definitely going to date Fujimura
(Naohiko) What role does Fujimura play in the haunted house?
(Eiji) Umm, what did you say...
(Naohiko) What? You don't know?
Are you on a date or something?
(Eiji) Yes you're doing it?
(Naohiko) So where did you go?
(Eiji) What is it suddenly?
Don't listen to something weird
(Naohiko) That's just normal, isn't it?
Oh, that's right, I'm gonna invite Fujimura.
(Eiji) That's amazing...
I'm not pretending to be with you a little longer...
Haa...
[A silly laughter] Wow!
Sorry...
Yes...
Wow, it feels soooo...
[Spirited sound effects]
Hey, is there anyone?
Wow!
Eiji!?
spring!?
- Don't threaten him... - No, what is Eiji doing?
picture? No, um...
Fujimura: That Fujimura search!
We're dating, so I thought maybe we can't get together
And so, yes...
(Izumi) I looked away
Isn't it a lie to be dating Koharu-chan?
What are you talking about, that's not possible!
How long do you think it's been a relationship?
I know Eiji's lie
It's not like Eiji
What's that kind of thing?
I've always been like this
It's the exact opposite of what you think
Eiji?
Ah, bad...
- Then I'll go- What? Wait, the story isn't over yet!
(Eiji, Izumi) Wow!
Go...
Are you okay?
Yeah…
♪～
[Sound of the shoji screen opens]
(Eiji) Fujimura...
I saw it
Are you cheating in a place like this?
You were kissing me now, right?
Tell Bessho-kun
Hey, wait, Fujimura!
Hey!
-Hey, wait, Fujimura! - what!?
Do you know what you did?
I told him not to destroy it, but I'll destroy it myself
but…
This was good
What about (Eiji)?
Because of that kiss...
Maybe Izumi-chan and Bessho-kun will break up?
Now finally
I can say I like you
Don't be kidding... you should just take it apart!
[Slap sound]
Which one is kidding me? I feel the same way as me
How long are you acting like a good person?
If so, don't kiss me!
Ah, I can't really invite you to Ikezawa.
That's good too, you too, Aihara too
Lovey-dovey with her!
That's not true...
picture?
(Izumi) Nao!
yeah?
what up?
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey he
You do it behind the scenes, behind the scenes! Come on, go see!
Tch!
- Flirt up! - A spring?
Sorry me...
Bad Naohiko!
I…
I kissed Izumi...
sorry…
(Eiji) Izumi Sorry!
why?
Why are you doing it?!
[Sniffing sound]
sorry…
- I asked why! - Direct!
Hey, stop, calm down! Calm down! Stop it!
(Eiji) Come on (Taichi) Hey!
(Boy) What's wrong?
(Taichi) Hey!
(Boy) What? A fight? Who?
(Izumi) Nao! Hey!
(Taichi) Aihara...
What's on now...
Is it true?
Don't do anything that makes you want to quit your friend
(Taichi) What are you looking at, it's disbanding! Disbanding!
Go!
(Izumi) Wait, I want to talk to Nao-chan!
(Naohiko) Haa... It's a school festival, so I'll do it later
(Izumi) Eh... But!
Have you passed away from the class?
You better go back
(Mizuho Mizuho) Aihara-kun?
[The sound of whistling]
(Taichi) Hey!
Everyone's gone home already
[Sound of placing it on the desk]
Let's drink
Come on, let's go!
(Mizuho) Is it okay?
It's better to cool it down
It looks so painful...
What hurts is...
It's not me...
What happened?
I hurt someone I didn't want to hurt...
Both of them are important...
So I'll hold it in forever...
I'll forget someday...
But in the end...
I broke it...
[The sound of opening the plug and bubbles]
Ah, that's a shame...
What are you thinking about Aihara's guy...
Ah but...
It seems that he fell like this and ended up slugging
Isn't that what it is?
I don't know but...
I wonder if a day like this will come someday
Maybe it was scary...
What about (Taichi)?
Izumi originally liked Eiji.
I thought I was just getting in the way...
What are you talking about?
More than me
Eiji spent a long time with Izumi.
What is suitable for a spring
Actually...
I wonder if it's Eiji
if…
If Eiji had always loved Izumi...
The two broke their relationship
It's me...
I'm entitled to punch him...
do not have…
Hmm, ah...
Well... well, alright, but alright? See
Let's drink it for now
Delicious! Come on, I opened it well, so come on a toast!
Okay, come on, cheers!
cheers! Let's get brighter!
What?
(Teacher) Yes, then don't forget your homework.
[Chime sound]
What do you do for lunch?
I'll eat with the track and field club
(Taichi)
Hmm, what do you do for lunch?
Let's eat while watching the sea, is it today? Let's take a look, see
Oh, which one should I do today?
(Izumi) Koharu-chan!
Haa...
what?
I didn't apologize properly for the other day
Why is Izumi apologizing?
The one who's wrong is Aihara-kun, and Izumi-chan is the victim, right?
But then...
He had a very hurtful face...
That shouldn't be... not
Because I...
I like Bessho-kun
picture?
Do you know why Aihara pretended to date me?
It's all for Izumi-chan
I like Bessho-kun and want to get closer
So I told Izumi-chan to become friends too.
Aihara-kun is
He tried to date me to keep me closer to Bessho-kun
But Izumi-chan
I don't know anything
You're able to apologize like you just now, because you're confident in yourself, right?
I can say this because I'm happy to be cared for by Bessho-kun!
Izumi-chan's thing
It's really frustrating...
I just don't want to be left awkward with Koharu-chan...
If so...
Please Bessho-kun
See
You can't do it
I don't want you to be too kind
(Taichi) Umm...
Bessho likes Shiosaki Shiosaki
I'm dating but
I doubt Aihara...
And Aihara seems to like Shiozaki
I'm dating Fujimura...
And me! I like Ikezawa though!
Ikezawa is Aihara...
Fujimura is dating Aihara but...
Who do you like?
no…
What is this tick
It's too complicated! Oh no...
[The sound of a notebook falling down]
A little...
(Taichi) Wow...
Ah, hey, wait! Don't watch!
Ah, that's that...
It's my own fantasy
that's why…
Don't worry!
What is love?
(Taichi) What?
When I saw Aihara-kun being hurt
Maybe...
I wonder if he's going to break up with Fujimura-san
a bit…
I was hoping for it
I can't believe this feeling is love...
I don't want to admit it
surely…
If I fall in love
Everyone is right
I just can't say it out loud
I'm
Ikezawa, who is so human, too
I think it's good
(Mizuho) What?
Me...
I'll support you
Ikezawa is
If you like Aihara
I want to become a power
[Running sound]
[Clashing sound]
(Naohiko) Ah!
sorry!
Fujimura?
(Koharu) What will you do now?
Izumi-chan...
With Aihara-kun
(Naohiko) Probably... nothing will change
Why? That terrible thing happened!
Well, each other...
I think you need time to sort it out
That's...
I don't like it
Even if you find someone you like
It's not always going well...
I just want to be happy like Izumi-chan
Are you happy...
That's right
My feelings for Izumi don't change, no matter what happened
of course
I understand how hard Fujimura is
But that's because Fujimura and his friends' problem.
If you can't believe Eiji, just tell him as it is.
And
It's better not to do this with anyone other than your boyfriend
Hehe
That's right, be careful
(Naohiko) You should talk to Eiji properly.
So me
I'm going back to club activities
[Spinning sound]
(Koharu) To Izumi-chan...
I talked about it all
So I'll stop now, pretend I'm dating
(Eiji) What about Naohiko?
give up
Bessho-kun and Izumi-chan
Surprisingly straight
I'm feeling embarrassed about this
I'm tired already...
Stop falling in love
It's not like Fujimura to hold back your own feelings
noisy! I don't want Aihara to say it!
If you continue like this, you're like me!
(Koharu) That's the one who told me not to get in the way!
Me...
Even if you get hurt, you'll bump into me. I thought you were amazing!
I…
Stop lying to yourself
I'll say it
Say it to Naohiko and Izumi
So you too...
Face the person you like!
No way...
I don't want to be hated any more
I'm here!
Even if the whole world hates you
Because I'm next to you
There's a story
I'll go later
Sorry this time
I was going to hide it properly
I wasn't even going to say it
But in the end I couldn't do it
Me...
I love the fountain
Why didn't you say it earlier?
I can't say it
You're a really good guy
Because I'm a friend
Can you say it?
that's why…
It's fun to be with you though
It was tough...
Me too...
There's something I couldn't tell you
In middle school
Izumi thought he liked Eiji.
that's why…
I confessed to her with the determination to be rejected
I thought I'd ruined the relationship between you and Izumi...
That's not true!
It's definitely different!
I'm in the end...
I was running away
Give me a reason
I was running away from being hurt
So you
Don't run away anymore
ah
Can I tell Izumi?
[The sound of waves]
It's nostalgic
This sea...
I'm really sorry!
Yeah
I've always been...
I liked Izumi
I really loved it
Eiji
It was conveyed properly
I've only been changing schools, but I've become as cheerful as I am now
Definitely thanks to Eiji
that's why…
I'm grateful
but…
This feeling
It's not love
Please share your feelings with me
You fell in love with me
thank you
ah!
[Eiji sniffs]
(Eiji) Hehehe
- Wow!? - What?
(Izumi) Nao!?
(Eiji) What is it!? (Naohiko) How long will he hold his hand?
Did you listen? Don't be fooled!
Hmm!
The location is also the sea, so don't create an atmosphere!
- Wow! - Barca!
No, that's about that good!
You're the one who eavesdrops and listens to them, right?
How scared you are, Barka!
- Oh! - Wow! Ha ha
Ha ha
Izumi!
What, what, what, what...!?
The fountain too! Don't make a gap when you're kissed!
(Eiji) What are you doing?
(Izumi) No!
♪～
(Eiji's M Monologue) The long first love
With tears...
Melted into the sea
[The sound of waves]
(Izumi) It made me feel anxious right
(Naohiko) Ugh
(Izumi) I guess so...
You have to tell it properly, right?
(Naohiko) Huh?
Just being with me makes me excited
Just because we can't see you for a while, I feel lonely and worried
That's what taught me about
Everything is straightforward
My first love
Definitely straight
The old and now...
I love it!
(Naohiko) Hehehe
(Izumi) Hehehehe
Me too
I love it!
from now on
thank you!
Hehe
(Izumi Naohiko) Hehehe
thank you
Hahaha
-Thank you very much- hahaha
(Girls) Hey, what will you do this Christmas?
(Boys) Let's go to a live show again this year (Women) Seriously? I want to show you a little bit!
(Koharu) Haa...
Koharu?
what up?
(Koharu) Taka-kun...
(Taka) Looks like he's not doing well
Morning
Oh good morning
Well, it's going to live on Christmas
If you like, please come and see it, right?
That... Aihara too!
yeah…
Something!
I'm going to forget all the annoying things like this
It's going to be the best live show!
What? Together with "Aihara"!
- Eiji... - Isn't it okay? please! Please!
- Wow, Eiji, I'm not sure... - Hey, let's go?
Because? Eiji
That's fun
Wow!?
(Eiji and Naohiko) Hahaha (Taichi) What?
What does that mean?
- Let's go, two of us! - I was worried
teeth? what? Have you made up?!
(3 people) Hahaha
(Taichi) That's good!
I'm really glad!
You guys, don't be kidding me!
It's you too! Don't be kidding me, seriously!
- That's right, what if I invite Izumi too? - That's right
Ah, sorry! So this is Shiozaki's part
I'm sure you'll come!
Ah Taichi!
Can you give me another one?
Ah, understand!
- Well then! - Yeah
(Taichi) Ikezawa!
If you like, please come and see it
Aihara is coming too
It's fine, about Aihara-kun
That's not good!
Ikezawa himself
I have to admit it properly...
That feeling of love
Poor thing
Wow, it might be my first time doing a live performance
I'm looking forward to it
Yeah
(Izumi) Eiji?
what happened?
Fujimura, what's up? I was thinking about when I was going to invite him,
I haven't been able to talk lately
What? Is that so?
- Yes- I see...
Then I'll look for a little
[Vibration sound from mobile phones]
Haa...
I've looked for it
(Taka) Haa...
Wow, where is it?
(Taka) Will we go back from us?
(Koharu) But Taka-kun says that it's too heavy for me...
(Taka) I'm the only guy who needs you, right?
Koharu likes me, doesn't he? What?
Are you okay! You like me...
(Eiji) Fujimura!
What are you doing?
- Aihara-kun - Let's go!
What about (Taka)?
Hey wait!
[The sound of the door closing with force]
[The sound of pulling the curtains]
Once you get this far it's fine
What do you intend?!
No, because he seemed to be in trouble...
I'm not particularly worried but
teeth?
It's not bad that it's needed...
No, you know, did you forget how that senior treated you?
Taka-kun is also kind to him...
There's none!
I'll contact you when I'm lonely
That's not just kindness or anything!
What's it like for a while now? It's nothing to do with Aihara-kun, right?
I'm worried about you!
I wonder if it hurts again...
(Taka) Koharu~
〔footsteps〕
Koharu?
(Female) Ah Taka What are you doing?
Oh no, Koharu is looking for a junior
Ah, that ex-girlfriend? Didn't you break up?
(Taka) He said he liked me, but...
Is it a feeling that my pet has run away because he's getting annoyed?
(Girls) Pet!? Oh no (Girls) Well, how many girlfriends are there now?
(Taka) Ah, it's fine if there are three (female)
(Taka) It was convenient, I was in charge of lunch.
(girl) Poor
(Taka) There's no way I'll really fall in love with someone like that
♪～
[The sound of the wind]
Haa... you've been weird again lately
What happened?
Is it going to hide it again like that?
Fujimura and...
I kissed...
teeth? Seriously?!
Seriously...
why?
I don't know that
So I'm having trouble...
That's weird...
[The sound of waves]
(Eiji) Well...
(Koharu) If that's what I mean, forget it
I was feeling anyway
(Eiji) Feeling?
That kind of thing feels like it, right?
I just did it because my face was close
that's why
Let's forget
What is that...
[The sound of ripples]
I…
What I like...
〔footsteps〕
Aihara-kun
yeah?
I looked unstoppable, but has something happened again?
Not particularly...
I'm curious
I'm listening because I'm curious!
I…
Because I like you
bad…
- I... - I know
I don't want any rewards
just
Face your feelings...
I wanted to tell you
This is a stolen
(Eiji) You have a bad taste!
I'm
Love isn't suitable...
Why?
Why do you think that way?
I thought I had finally broken the feelings I had been holding for so long
This time...
With people you thought you disliked
I don't know what it is anymore...
Aihara-kun
Do you understand the opposite of "love"?
You "hate" doesn't it?
Ugh
"there is nothing"
It means "I have no feelings."
"I hate"
Do you really have special feelings just for that person?
Aihara-kun is
He's a very easy-to-understand person
[Guitar practice sound]
Ikezawa...
I was dumped
I knew but...
sorry!
Why are you apologizing?
Because...
Even though they told me I would support you...
Don't hold it in!
Cry to your heart's content! You did your best!
〔cry〕
Fujimura-san
Is it a little okay?
About Aihara-kun...
Maybe me too?
I have something I want to talk to Koharu...
(Mizuho) I'm waiting in the library
(Koharu) What? Talk...
I…
I confessed to Aihara-kun...
Sorry it's Fujimura's boyfriend!
There's no need to worry about it, I wasn't dating
picture?
What... what does that mean?
I have someone else I like
To get closer to that person
He was just using Aihara-kun
Why that's what it is...
I'll say what it is to make you happy
I…
Because he's such a selfish person
[Sniffing sound]
Izumi-chan too
That's how I hurt
[Sobbing]
What to do
Can you be like the two of you?
Izumi-chan is...
Always straight and kind
Of course Bessho-kun will take good care of him.
Ikezawa-san too
Face your feelings properly
That's amazing
It's too amazing
I hate myself like this
I want to change...
sorry…
I'm really sorry
(Izumi) I...
I was happy that Koharu-chan told me to become friends.
Again, that's what happens...
Izumi-chan is all good!
I'm again...
I want to talk to Koharu and go home
me too…
I'm not the kind of person Fujimura said to me.
It took me a lot of time to get here
I once had jealous of Fujimura and had dirty feelings.
that's why…
It's not just you
Hey, can we not become friends?
It's impossible, that's...
why?
Because I'm a friend
Because we're friends, we get into fights and talk about them, right?
Ah, that's right!
Would you like to see this live together?
That's good!
Eiji is coming too
me too…
I want to change
Like two
Yeah
(Koharu/Izumi) Hehehe
[The sound of ripples]
[The students' excitement]
[Drum practice sound]
(Naohiko) Is Taichi nervous?
That's amazing
Hey, what about Koharu?
I haven't come yet
(Izumi) Does Eiji not know Koharu-chan?
here we go?
you…
Have you not been talking to Fujimura since then?
No, I don't even talk about it
- Come on a moment! - picture!?
- What!? - That's fine!
(Eiji) What?
what?
- What is it? - Find it about Fujimura
teeth? Why me?
Don't you know yet?
That's how you do the same thing!
What do you want to say?
Ah! You don't understand if you say that!?
[The sound of kissing]
Oh no, what are you doing?!
Izumi's kiss
I got it back
I really wanted it back soon after that!
No... So, should I do it for me now?
How about it? How do you feel now?
It's the worst!
Because this is a curse!
curse!?
This is the last time you kissed
It became me!
No, isn't it a serious curse?
Hmm
It's going to start soon?
ah…
- Later, I lifted the curse... - What? curse?
No, I don't want to do it with the girl I like too!
If so, go!
Shut up!
(Eiji's M Monologue) When I think about it, I started from that time.
Maybe everything was beginning to change
[Spinning sound]
[♪~ Light Music Club Performance]
♪（It's time） to blow my fate away
♪（It's time） to confront who you are
♪I admit that I'm a hypocrite
to fear being hurt cowardly
♪（I know） I decided to live this way
♪（I know）
I can never take smartest ways
♪Grant me right to shout out my love
♪to blow my fate away
♪I'll let go of my pride
and confront you
♪Everything is by my side
to shout my love to you
♪Blow my fate away…
[The sound of ripples]
[The sound of running in]
Was he here...
Haa haa...
what?
no…
No, um... that...
You are
Oh, again...
To that senior, um...
I was being chased and thought I might be in trouble
I haven't ordered it though!
You really have a bad personality!
What is that
But I can't leave it alone for some reason!
Me!
I love Fujimura!
I decided to be honest
It's unfair!
teeth?
Just express your feelings and feel refreshed
What about Fujimura?
What does Fujimura think?
…tree
picture?
like
I can't hear
like!
- Why are you crying again? - So loud, stupid!
Don't get mad!
I…
Isn't it annoying?
I know
I want you to take care of it
I told you
There are some who are so devoted that they are persistent
me too…
Take care
like
really like!
(Taichi) Uh, the next one...
It's the last song
everyone
Are you in love?
[Cheers]
I'm doing it
But I'm clumsy
I can't express my feelings like everyone else
But today
Just today...
When this live show is over
I'd like to ask someone I like about my thoughts
[Cheers]
So please listen
This is a song that conveys my feelings now
[Cheers]
[Stick count sound]
♪Hey, look at my eyes
♪What do you think?
♪I want to know but I'm timid
♪We don't know love
♪ It's true that I've run through this season
♪It's okay to cry
♪ I love you any
♪I pretended not to know love
♪I decided to pour my love on you
♪It doesn't have to arrive
♪Please let me scream for now
♪～
～♪
(Naohiko/Izumi) Hehehehe
♪I've learned about love
♪I decided to wish for your happiness
♪If I were to be in that happiness
♪Please let me scream for now
♪～
～♪
[♪~ Naniwa Danshi "Koisruhikari"]
♪I thought it was a common word, and with that one word
♪The familiar scenery looked completely different
♪I looked in the city and it must have been anywhere
♪The answer was always hidden in my heart
♪I want to tell you, I can't do it
♪The time passed I even "liked"
♪I fell in love, I missed, the shaking light
♪I reflected, crossed, illuminated you
♪It overlaps and passes by all of them
♪ It's been sparkling since that day, forever
♪If I spend my failures and regrets with you
♪A precious, precious, tears spilled
♪ Rainbow-colored memories drawn by Prism
♪Kimi ni Todoke Love Song
♪I hope that the heartbeat that resonates with each other whenever my eyes meet is not noticed
♪ Turn your back and say goodbye to yesterday, who lied
♪Even if you hurt, you hurt
♪If you "love" someone like this
♪Love is falling, love is lost, the missing heart
♪ It's not easy to fill up properly
♪ It's okay if it's not beautiful This feeling is right now
♪I want to convey it as it is
♪ Dreams that can't come true on your own
♪ I'm frustrated after chasing
♪Even every day, you're just there
♪ Everything was shining Oh
♪I fell in love, I missed, the shaking light
♪I reflected, crossed, illuminated you
♪We met by chance and everything
♪It must have been sparkling from the beginning
♪If I spend my failures and regrets with you
♪A precious, precious, tears spilled
♪ Rainbow-colored memories drawn by Prism
♪Just as I am, put it in this word
♪Kimi ni Todoke Love Song
♪～
～♪