(All characters, organizations,
places, entities, and events...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(Public Assembly)
In the previous episode,
I argued that
abortion is a crime.
But after finding out
about her pregnancy,
I recommended an abortion...
to my daughter who
wanted to keep the baby.
According to my logic,
I was asking her
to commit a crime.
I know that this is shameless,
and also that it doesn't
make much sense.
I was worried about my
young daughter's future,
and it was too much...
for me to handle as well.
Maybe that's why I asked
her to do such a thing.
But her words...
moved me.
She said she wanted
to protect her child...
just like her mom did for her.
When her mom had her,
her father was not there.
But right now,
she has the baby's
father by her side.
So she said she was confident
that she will not regret her choice.
So I decided to
respect her choice.
And using this opportunity,
I would like to say
something to my daughter.
I wasn't able to stay
by your mother's side.
But...
I will be there for you.
Dae Han socked it to me good.
I didn't fathom she would...
keep the baby.
We leaked it to the tabloids
and set it all up for him.
You gave Dae Han
some great publicity.
I'm sorry, sir.
That guy on my desk...
(Han Dong Nam)
Do you mean Wi Dae
Han's children's real dad?
Yes. Find him.
Yes, sir.
But why do you want...
I'm curious...
what will happen if
there are two dads.
Just wait a little while.
I'll show people
your true colors.
Get home safely.
- Thank you.
Do you think all these staff members
are here to air your personal show?
Why are you talking about
your personal life on live TV?
It took a lot for me to say it.
It was all for this show.
What does your admitting
your daughter is pregnant...
have to do with our show?
The viewers wouldn't
have heard a thing I said.
They would've only wondered
whether that jerk's daughter...
was really pregnant.
It's true his statement
wasn't on topic,
but it took a lot of
courage. Let's let it slide.
Sir. How could you
move us like this?
Thank you for being so kind.
I felt bad that I may
have hurt the show.
Hurt it?
The ratings hit seven percent.
We're sweeping the top
five most trending keywords.
- I'm glad.
- Right?
Let's go out for
dinner to celebrate.
It's on me. Let's
go to a buffet!
I'm sorry,
but I need to go home early.
The kids are waiting for me.
Yes, let's go out another time.
Do you have plans?
I can't make it either.
Then let's go ourselves.
My treat. Top-quality
Korean beef.
Let's go another time
when everyone can make it.
I'll get going then.
I thought you'd
deny it all the way.
What made you say
that on the show?
I decided...
to let Da Jung keep the baby.
I've been denying her
pregnancy all this time.
I should apologize
to the nation.
What made you suddenly
have a change of heart?
Da Jung sent me a
picture just before the show.
A picture?
The sonogram.
She said looking at
it gave her strength,
and that she wanted
to protect the baby,
and I couldn't get
myself to stop her.
They say no parent
can deny their child.
You're a real dad now.
Do you have a
baby in your belly?
Yes.
Then are we getting a
little brother or sister?
Stupid. Not a little brother
or sister. A niece or nephew.
Awesome. Do you know
what a niece and nephew are?
That's basic knowledge.
You'll be my brother-in-law now.
Song Yi, you are a genius.
Give me a break.
My good man. Your
words are quite harsh.
Please be careful going forward.
It's not good for the baby.
Sure. What a great
brother-in-law we have here.
Okay, let's go to sleep.
You too. It's late.
You should go.
I should say hi to Father first.
I want to thank him too.
Good work today. Goodnight.
Will you be okay?
About what?
Once Da Jung has a baby,
you'll be a grandpa.
Grand...
You're right.
That's right. I'll give it a
shot. National Grandpa.
I like how cool you are.
True. You said back then...
What?
That you have a superhero's
blood flowing through your veins.
You'll do great
as a grandpa too.
Have you ever seen a superhero
take down villains alone?
He needs a partner.
I was able to make this decision
because you were by my side.
- You'll help me, right?
- Forget it.
You must be tired. Go in.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
If you forgive me this once,
I will do my utmost to
carry out our agreement.
If you still refuse,
I'll have no choice but to
go public about our contract.
What?
(Quiet!)
(Episode 7: Secrets and Lies)
Welcome back.
Where is Da Jung?
She went to tuck
her siblings in.
Thank you for your approval.
Should I bow to you to show
how much I appreciate it?
No need.
What's the plan now?
I'll be more determined
to work harder.
I am going to earn money
by working part-time jobs.
Why are you running
part-time jobs?
What?
Thing is...
Jung Woo got kicked
out of the agency.
Father.
She deserves to know.
It's about her baby's father.
He is right.
Don't hide these things from me.
I didn't want you
to get worried.
Did you get kicked out
because of what happened to us?
If so, do we have
to pay a penalty?
There is some money
that I have to pay back.
I will try to take care of it.
You should come up with a
plan for your future instead.
Thank you for your approval.
And I am sorry...
that I sent that text
before the show.
I understand...
that you want to
protect your child.
But isn't it too much when you try
to threaten me with the contract?
Like I said,
I will do my utmost to
carry out our agreement.
And how are you
going to do that?
Anything.
If it helps you get re-elected
as an assemblyman.
Due to the choice I made today,
both you and I would have
to live very different lives.
And you don't need to threaten
me with that contract too.
What does that mean?
I openly said that you
will give birth to that child.
So?
People would be more
interested in how we live.
More than ever.
Now,
it's almost impossible for
us to cut our ties completely...
once our contract term is over.
I might as well have
tied you down too.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
I brought that on myself.
But I can't be
like your real dad.
I will continue to act
as your legal guardian.
That's enough for me.
I am sure you are tired.
I hope you rest well.
Mom...
Do you think I can do this?
(Da Jung)
Since we decided not to
feel sorry to each other,
I am not going to apologize.
I am going to be
grateful all my life.
Thank you for
protecting our baby...
even at the cost of your debut.
I am the one who
should be thankful.
But...
why am I so scared?
(Shut up and fry!)
Here you go. Eat.
- Dad.
- Huh?
Why are there fewer
customers than usual?
Usually, around this time,
I can't even find a seat.
You are right. Is there
something going on today?
It's weirdly empty.
Dad, did you see the show?
Of course, I did.
I have to say...
Wi Dae Han is quite a character.
Why?
Oh, come on.
What other people
may keep to themselves,
he just confesses on TV!
It's not easy, you know.
I mean, his name
has a good ring to it.
He is going to make a
name for himself, for sure.
Make a name for himself? No way.
He is going to get
into very big trouble.
Even if she wants the
baby, she is just a schoolgirl.
What is she going to do
after she has the baby?
You are right.
Doesn't she have young
siblings to take care of?
Now that I think about it...
Dae Han is quite rash.
Come on, Da Jung is not alone.
There's also the baby's father.
We don't need to worry now.
Come on.
Now...
it's been almost ten years
since Ji Hyun passed away.
Are you just going to
sit there and not work?
Go in and fry chicken.
Of course. I will do
that. I'm on my way.
(Kim Hye Jin)
Enjoy your meal.
Why did you want to
see me so late at night?
I have something to say,
but I thought talking about it
over the phone is not appropriate.
If you can't talk over the
phone, it's not about work.
You already know that
I like Mr. Kang, right?
So?
I was wondering
if you like him too.
This feels like
an interrogation.
Sorry. I am not good at
beating around the bush.
Then I will be
direct with you too.
You are correct. I'm
interested in Mr. Kang.
If this is why you
wanted to see me...
then I should get going.
This makes me feel
very uncomfortable.
Then what about Dae Han?
Weren't you two
close during college?
You two seem quite
close these days too.
Both physically and emotionally.
You are right. We are close.
We are neighbors, and
we also work together.
But that's it.
Is that so? Do you think
he feels the same way? You
should ask him. Why
are you asking me?
You have quite an imagination.
Trying to fix me up with someone
who is about to be a grandfather.
I need to go.
(Lawyer Kang)
Are we still on for night
fishing tomorrow night?
Of course. We promised.
Although it's my first time
fishing, so I am not very confident.
(Real-time keyword ranking,
Wi Dae Han, Debate, daughter)
The most searched
keyword is Wi Dae Han.
Followed by Wi
Dae Han's daughter.
Your popularity as National
Dad was starting to wane.
That baby is your lucky charm.
Low-birth rate is
a serious issue.
Having a child is
an act of patriotism.
People like me should be elected
as to the National Assembly.
I am going to have four children
and a grandchild before marriage.
Is that...
a baby on your back?
What? Who is this?
Who are you?
What? How did he get here?
- Do something. He's slipping.
- Do what?
Stop crying.
Oh no.
Why are you here?
How did you get...
What?
Am I really going
to be a grandfather?
Darn it.
Is he even inside?
There are tons of them!
Why are those people here?
Why do you think? It's thanks
to the great father and daughter
What are you going to do?
Everyone's going to know
who I am because of you.
Just wear a mask outside.
You can pretend that
you're a superstar.
Forget about them
and get ready for school.
I'll send them away.
He's coming.
When did she decide
to keep the baby?
How does it feel to
be a grandfather soon?
Did your daughter
drop out of school?
You must be having a
hard time working so early.
I'll be setting up a
press conference,
so please refrain from
coming to our house like this.
It doesn't matter for me,
but my kids are still young
and not public figures.
Please help protect
my children's privacy.
Could you at least answer this?
Is it true that the baby's
father is an idol trainee?
Gosh.
That would be great
for us, of course.
That's what I call
a win-win situation.
We get the publicity,
and Jung Woo won't
have to pay the penalty.
If I answer that question,
will you all go away?
Sure, we will do that.
He is an idol trainee.
See? I told you.
He was a member of a group
called "Chaos", set to debut soon.
- "Chaos"? Look that up.
- "Chaos"?
I settled the penalty problem,
so don't worry about it.
Okay. Thank you.
You should give up on school.
No. I'm going to keep attending.
I want to finish this
semester, at least.
The whole school will
know you're pregnant,
and the kids and their
parents won't leave you alone.
I'll have to deal with it.
I want to be a proud mother...
for my baby.
I don't want to
hide like a criminal.
I know how you feel, but...
I've been looking
it up all night,
and pregnant students
also have a right...
to education.
But what about the others' rights
being violated because of you?
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
You're going to have
to live a different life.
Give up school.
The principal will
say the same thing.
We have to let her
attend if she wants to.
The right to education...
is a basic human right
guaranteed by the constitution.
Yes. It is, sir.
I was touched...
by you and your daughter's
courage yesterday on the show.
Of course, there may
be some parents...
who oppose having a
pregnant student at school.
Yes, sir. That's what I mean.
As a parent,
I fully understand
how they feel.
But that's why the principal...
must resolve these conflicts.
I will try to persuade
the parents,
so don't worry.
Yes, sir.
Some of you may already know,
but the school has
been discussing it,
and Da Jung will keep
studying with you all.
I hope you can be
considerate towards Da Jung.
What? Wasn't she dropping out?
She wants to stay and
the principal agreed,
so she will be
finishing the semester.
Is she crazy?
What's wrong with our school?
It is a special case,
but she has the right to
education, just like the rest of you.
Sir, it's different.
What if she accidentally bumps
into someone and has a miscarriage?
Who is going to
take responsibility?
That's why you need
to be considerate.
Don't run around
in the classroom...
and talk quietly if you can.
Why do we have to be careful
at school because of her?
Being pregnant isn't
something to brag about, is it?
- That's right!
- Exactly!
Why do we have
to be the victims?
Sir.
It's all right with me, so please
treat me just like the others.
I'd feel better that way.
I'm sorry to be a bother
to you. I really am.
If you're sorry,
drop out of school.
Go Min Ji, that's enough.
Why do you keep picking on me?
She's the one who got
pregnant and is causing problems!
- That's right!
- Exactly!
You're a nation-wide star now.
You might even become
the president soon.
Gosh, why are you
complimenting me?
Did you see the debate regarding
the low-income apartments yesterday?
Contentwise, you lost.
Sure. I couldn't prepare
much because of Da Jung.
Who cares?
People only remember
the image and not the logic.
You may have lost the
combat, but you won the war.
How is the public opinion?
Before you came in, 70
percent was for the school...
and 30 percent was
for the apartments,
but we're up to 50-50 now.
We will have to win
the mothers' favor...
and go up to 70 percent.
You know that's the
hardest part, right?
Of course, I do.
But who is Wi Dae Han?
You're the National Dad.
Oh, what happened with
your daughter's school?
- Don't they suggest she quit?
- Of course.
That should be the
natural response,
but they're doing
the exact opposite.
The principal called, sir.
Is she going to keep
attending the school?
It seemed like Wi Dae
Han wanted her to quit,
but he was able to lead her
into attending as you instructed.
When they reveal her pregnancy
and say she will have the baby,
the people will like that.
But when their kids face a
disadvantage because of her,
it won't be the same.
Just you wait.
(Petition Against Pregnant
Students Attending School)
Teenage pregnancy
is nothing to brag about.
They won't stop
talking about it on TV...
and she's even going to
continue attending school.
I know! We can't
let that happen!
- Of course, not.
- No.
I'm worried my daughter
will get influenced.
Our kids are at a very
sensitive and important time.
If they are in the same
class as a pregnant girl,
how will they focus
on their studies?
- We can't let that happen.
- They won't be able to.
My gosh! Come and
take a look at this! Hurry!
He's so handsome!
- Is it him?
- Yes.
- He's my type.
- He's so handsome.
Too bad.
He would've been so
popular if he debuted.
Chaos made the
top keyword ranking.
He only helped
with their publicity.
I feel so bad for him.
Life is long.
He's only 20. He'll
get a better chance.
Yes, Dad?
Soo Hyun, we're in trouble.
We might have to close
down our restaurant.
What are you talking about?
Calm down and explain it to me.
Well, we suddenly had so
little customers yesterday...
and our regular customer...
wouldn't even look at
me when I greeted her.
It was so weird,
so I looked it up,
and there was a post on a
neighborhood mommy website...
that was talking ill
about our restaurant.
That's the only
reason I could find,
and I don't know what
I should do about it.
Why are you calling
everyone about it?
Hang up right now!
I was just mad and upset!
Then who am I
supposed to whine to?
- First, - Yes?
I'll find out what's going
on, so don't worry about it.
Okay.
- What's going on?
- What?
There's a post on a mommy website
slandering my dad's restaurant.
What?
Those kinds of websites have a huge
influence on the moms in that area.
I heard there are many restaurants
that closed down like that.
I'll have to find a way.
Hello. I see you're
all working hard.
What are you doing here today?
I was here for a
radio show today,
so I stopped by to
support you guys.
- I brought a snack.
- Thank you.
Soo Hyun.
What's with that look?
Dae Han. I'm glad you came. I
need to talk to you for a minute.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
Good luck.
Why aren't we
using the elevator?
I felt suffocated.
What? Do you
have claustrophobia?
It's good to get some exercise.
You need it too.
Fine.
(Love Inju)
(Our Neighborhood Talk)
(I've never seen a chicken
place like this before.)
I've never seen a chicken
place like this before.
The owner looks like a
thug and is incredibly rude.
The chicken is so old,
it's like chewing rubber.
They must reuse the oil.
The chicken smells old and
makes my stomach churn.
I even found a piece
of hair in the chicken.
There's a hair.
I couldn't stand it, so
I complained, and...
It's long. My hair is short.
No.
Honey, come here.
What?
Her joints just cracked.
But they got angry
and threw a fit.
You shouldn't run
a business like this.
A puppy dog like my dad
got angry and threw a fit?
She's determined to ruin them.
How could a place like
that still stay in business?
We should boycott
places like that.
They should know better.
Places that disrespect
customers should be shut down.
Where is this place?
The chicken place
in Inju Market.
Who is this woman? "Inju Mom"?
I'm going to find out who
she is and teach her a lesson.
What will that solve?
What if she insists
that happened?
You have a point.
The restaurant is going to go
bankrupt while we figure it out.
If you read through this, you can
tell she's angry at the restaurant.
What's this? Inju Mom?
Inju Mom is the one
who manages this site.
I think it would be better...
to patronize her rather
than get her angrier.
She's the manager.
I want to just...
Refrain yourself.
Don't stoop to her level.
Then what?
You're the head honcho
on this site, aren't you?
Hello, Mr. Kang.
When should I meet
you at the studio?
I'm so sorry,
but I have a family
matter to handle,
so I can't make it today.
Really?
Okay. I can't say I'm not
disappointed, but what can you do?
Okay.
Does he have
nothing better to do?
Chaos.
Okay. Nice.
So I don't owe you
a penalty, right?
That's right. This
is my problem.
I care about people too much.
Thank you.
Are the other
members practicing?
They don't even
have time to pee.
They left early this morning
to shoot a music video.
I wanted to say bye.
(Rules of the Studio)
(Sweat poured out together
is fragrant. By Jung Woo)
Okay. Let's go sweat.
(Jungnam Study Abroad Agency)
Hey, what are
you doing? Move it.
Okay. I will.
How...
Aren't you scared?
You punk. Why is this
scary? Money is what's scary.
I hired you because
you begged and begged.
Get over here.
Okay.
Money is scary,
but this is much scarier.
What? Someone who would
want to retaliate against us?
Yes. Looking at what she
wrote on the mommy site,
it couldn't have been
an average customer.
I'm sure she has a grudge
against the two of you.
That's right. Can't
you think of anyone?
I don't know.
As you know,
your dad would
let people hurt him,
but he would never hurt others.
I know that's how Dad
is, but you have a temper.
That's true.
What was that?
Whatever. Let's see how
well your business does.
I'll be sure to post about
your restaurant online.
It was that woman.
What? Who?
Who else?
Jae Hoon's mom.
You're right.
She's mad about the
low-income apartments.
That's right.
She wouldn't have posted that
just because of what happened.
No, no. That woman is
capable of much worse.
Who's Jae Hoon's mom?
She was a big supporter
of the international school.
This is trouble.
If it was her,
she won't take it down even
if I get on my knees and beg.
Why would we get on our
knees? What did we do wrong?
I'm going to
break her fingers...
Calm down.
- Ma'am.
- Calm down, will you?
You need to be
cool-headed in times like this.
Yes, she's right.
Please calm down.
I'm sure there's a way.
Why don't we show it to them?
Show what to whom?
You frying the chicken.
They'll probably believe
it if they see it themselves.
Let them see it themselves.
That sounds easy,
but how will we show it?
We can't bring everyone here.
You can film it and
post it on the website.
They'll think it was
filmed as a promotion.
I guess you're right.
Then our restaurant is ruined.
It's completely ruined.
You and your big mouth.
This is all your fault!
Why are you pinching me?
I'd do a livecast.
What?
A livecast?
That's it. A one-man broadcast.
If we post the URL on the
website, they'll check it themselves.
If we broadcast live
throughout business hours,
they can't insist it was
only during the filming.
That's right. And it'll help
promote the restaurant.
Why didn't I think of that?
Nice, Tak. Great idea.
Nice.
It's a great idea.
So...
- Oh my. Hello.
- Hello.
Mr. Kang.
What are you doing here?
I was craving chicken and beer.
It's so nice to see you. I didn't
think I'd get to see you today.
Why isn't Mr. Wi going with us?
He has work to do.
I hope Soo Hyun and
Mr. Wi get married.
Me too. Then she'll
become our mommy.
Why would she? She isn't stupid.
What about the night fishing?
I canceled it since
you couldn't make it.
It's no fun going alone.
What? Do you go night
fishing together and stuff?
Do you?
My gosh.
What about that matter?
Were you able to resolve it?
We're still in the process.
Dae Han, what
are you doing here?
Why? Are you curious?
I am fairly close
to her parents.
We are practically a family.
Right?
Mr. Kang.
Can I ask you
something straight up?
Do you like Soo Hyun?
Why would you ask that?
It's okay. It's not
a difficult question.
Yes, I do.
A lot, at that.
- Come on!
- Ouch!
Sorry. Don't mind us.
- Continue with your conversation.
- Go ahead.
Do you like him too?
It's rude to ask her
that kind of thing.
- What about you?
- What do you mean?
Do you have feelings for her?
That's enough. What are
you, high school students?
You two. Go home.
- Me too?
- But chicken...
- How...
- The chicken just came...
Why did you have to
come out of the blue?
The chicken just came out.
Go back home. Please.
Kang Joon Ho.
Why Soo Hyun?
What do you mean?
Why do you have to
like her of all people?
I have no reason...
to ask for your
permission on whom I like.
See you.
Are you going to
run for the election?
No.
I won't. I don't think politics
is the right field for me.
How many politicians would
actually think politics is right for them?
There are two
types of politicians.
They do it with a sense
of duty or for power.
If you are not interested,
it means you are not
interested in either duty or power.
Which one are you?
Is it duty or for power?
Of course, it's a sense of duty.
My duty to remove people like
Assemblyman Kang from office.
See you.
It's not true...
that I am not interested
in duty nor power.
Rather...
I just know very well...
what the family of a
politician must go through.
Are you dating that lawyer?
No, I am not.
Then what is it? Are
you not interested in him?
I don't know! I will take
care of my own business.
You focus on the restaurant.
What do you mean you don't know?
He says he likes you. A lot too!
There's no time to waste!
He seems like a great guy.
Just go for it!
- Dad.
- Huh?
You know he is the son of
Assemblyman Kang, right?
You said you didn't like
his father, remember?
Look at her.
When did I ever
say I didn't like him?
We may not agree
on political views,
but it's a completely different
story if he becomes our in-law.
- Am I right?
- Of course.
He is much better-looking
than Assemblyman Kang.
And he seems like a
nicer man than his father.
Why don't you date him
since he likes you already?
Stop getting ahead.
I'll go home.
Yes, I do.
A lot, at that.
I have no reason...
to ask for your
permission on whom I like.
("You Are My Sunshine")
What are you going to do?
Now our parents know.
I don't know.
You hesitate to be with him
because of Dae Han, right?
Not true at all.
It's just...
I am worried about Da Jung,
and I am not ready to like
someone so passionately.
I am not sure if I
am ready to date.
Why can't you like
him passionately?
Is it because of me?
(2005)
Hey.
Could you please return
this? Today is the last day.
Why should I? It's not mine.
Come on, it's for your sister.
Not today. I don't feel well.
And most importantly, it's
SHINHWA's comeback today.
You can stop by the
department store on your way out.
I am going to be
late if I drop by.
- Where are you going?
- I am going to see a movie.
With who?
Dae Han.
Really? A date?
I wouldn't call it a date.
He just offered to
show me a movie for...
working hard on that
student declaration.
That is a date!
Fine. I am sorry, SHINHWA.
Give me the bag.
- Here you go.
- Be on your best behavior.
Are you sure you can help me
and give up on your boy band?
What can I do? My only
sister is very bad at dating.
I, the generous sister,
should be the one to help.
- Don't cross the line.
- Then I won't go.
I am so sorry.
Why do you like Dae Han, anyway?
He is good-looking.
And I know you like him a lot.
I am so nervous!
(Theater entrance)
Dae Han.
- Hey.
- Sorry. Did you wait for long?
No. I just got here too.
- Good.
Shall we?
I love you for being alive.
Of course, my baby.
That's mine.
What are you doing?
- Sorry.
- What a weird guy.
I had so many
things I wanted to buy.
Let's see.
What is happening?
- I was so surprised!
- What is going on?
Honey, turn on your
phone light! Now!
Look for the emergency bell.
- Where is the emergency bell?
- Hello?
- What's going on?
- Is anyone there?
- Call someone!
- Hello?
- Isn't anyone picking up?
- What?
- What should we do?
- Hello?
(The phone is turned off...)
- Eun Mi!
- What are we going to do?
- It was really sad.
- Right?
I think I drank too much soda.
I need to use the restroom.
- Go ahead. I'll wait here.
- Okay.
(6 Missed Calls.
Ji Hyun 1, Dad 5)
What's going on?
Yes, Dad?
Soo Hyun.
What's wrong, Dad?
Ji Hyun...
went to the department store...
and the elevator crashed down...
Soo Hyun.
Soo Hyun?
Soo Hyun, open the door.
Open the door!
How are we supposed to
go on if you act like this too?
Soo Hyun, open the door!
What do we do?
Soo Hyun!
We need to go on
with our lives, don't we?
Soo Hyun, open the door!
(View Message)
(I got the refund! It's all thanks to
me if it works out with Dae Han.)
Sales are low at my dad's
restaurant, so I need to work.
I'll be taking
next semester off.
Is that why you didn't show
up for the student council?
Yes.
How bad is it?
I don't think I have
to explain that to you.
I came here because you
kept calling and texting me,
but I hope you won't
call me anymore.
Even if you do...
I won't be answering.
Soo Hyun.
Did I do something wrong?
It's not like that.
I hate it when people want to be by
my side when I'm having a hard time.
I have to go.
It still makes me sad.
I realized how influential
those mommy websites are.
That's why the store owners...
don't have a chance against
the people who run those sites.
I can't go around
meeting all those mothers.
I'll make full use of the sites to
boost support for the apartments.
Love Inju is the
biggest one, right?
I think so. The host, Inju Mom,
is Jae Hoon's mom, for sure.
I guess she used it to
control public opinion.
I guess so.
There might be better
websites if we look hard enough.
Why don't we win
them over to our side?
(Shut up and fry!)
What's this?
What's going on?
I put up a post to explain
the situation and it got deleted!
What?
Is she running it
however she wants to...
just because she's
the site manager?
If they're only going to
keep the posts they like,
why run a community website?
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll go and take that
woman's fingers...
Hey, wait. You
better hold it in, dear.
Please keep your
fists to yourself.
Darn it!
Sit down.
Wait a minute...
Wi D Han doesn't care
about students or parents...
and only looks out
for his daughter.
Why, that little...
- What is it?
- Why?
- What's going on?
What is it?
He says he cares
for the residents,
but he couldn't even
handle his own child...
and a teenager got pregnant.
Not only that, but she's
still going to attend school.
He doesn't care about the
stress our kids will be getting,
especially when they should
be focusing on their studies.
The dad and the daughter
are both so annoying!
Why, that little...
How could she say that?
Gosh!
(Lawyer Kang)
If you have time tonight,
will you accept my battle?
What are you trying to do?
Stop that!
(Da Jung)
Soo Hyun, are you free tonight?
Darn it!
(Lawyer Kang Joon Ho)
I'm sorry. I have
plans tonight as well.
I'll accept the
battle another time.
That's so cool.
You're amazing.
Why are you so good?
Go away.
I'm sorry.
Just watch if you want to.
Just don't get too close to me.
All right. I'll just
get close enough.
Hey, what does BLP mean?
What?
I heard Hwang Soo
Hyun calling you BLP.
What is that?
Our family receives
a basic living pension.
It's short for that.
Doesn't that even make you mad?
- Move over. Get out.
- Okay.
Hey, BLP. Did you make a friend?
You two look close.
Hey. I heard your
sister got pregnant.
Shut it.
You have a stranger for a dad...
and a pregnant teenage sister?
What a messed up family!
That's so messed up.
I said, shut it.
BLP and Messed Up Family.
You suit each other so well.
It's working!
Gosh!
You look so great on screen.
- Move your head back.
- Okay.
See?
Do you think this will work?
It won't hurt to try, Dad.
It could be a hit and promote
your restaurant as well.
It feels weird to have the
camera observing me, though.
- Right?
- Yes.
I get nervous in front
of the camera too.
Don't worry about it and act
naturally. Pretend it doesn't exist.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Good luck!
You have to keep
your head far away.
Oh, far away?
Hello.
Let me talk to you about
our fried chicken restaurant.
We received three stars...
which is the highest
hygiene rating in Inju City...
What are you doing?
Try to sound natural!
What are you doing? You
don't have your gloves...
on, sir. You must be so
nervous that you forgot.
Oh, yes.
I usually always put gloves on.
Are you doing some
kind of comedy act?
Try to act natural, will you?
Okay. Wait.
No, this could be their concept.
It's hilarious.
They're going to get
a ton of views like this.
You're right.
Just go on. It's great.
You're going to be a hit. Go on.
Okay.
After mixing it nicely...
Here.
Then...
(I'll tune in next time too)
We will fry the chicken.
You must be careful
not to fry your fingers.
Oh my.
Thus,
we will start
frying the chicken.
- Just fry them already.
- Okay.
That's right. Dae Han.
Yes?
Inju Mom posted
on the website...
about Da Jung staying in school.
She did?
Seriously. This woman is
determined to ruin me. Darn it.
What will you do?
What else? I'll have to give
her a taste of her own medicine.
Why that woman...
(Tak's teacher)
It's Tak's teacher.
Hello?
(Sunghan Hospital)
Don't make things
worse, and stay quiet.
I'll take care of it. Okay?
Hello, ma'am. You must
have been so scared.
I'm sorry.
I was so surprised when I
got the call from their teacher.
You must have been
incredibly shocked.
I'm terribly sorry.
Is Jae Hoon okay?
Do I look okay to you?
My gosh. Jae Hoon.
You poor thing.
Look at this cast.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Apologize to Jae Hoon
and his mom. Now!
You said to stay still.
What?
I meant don't say
anything stupid.
You should apologize.
Your friend got hurt.
Go on.
Sorry.
I'm speechless.
Hey. Do you expect us to
believe you're actually sorry?
What are you doing? Do it right.
Now.
Look at him, Mom. He looks like
he wants to stab me in this leg too.
Are you trying to kill someone?
A jerk like him belongs
in juvie, not at a school.
Ma'am.
What are you doing?
Ma'am, it's my fault.
I should've taught him
better as his father. I'm sorry.
I'll discipline him well so
this never happens again.
So, please. Please
forgive him just this once.
I'm sorry.
Hey, kid. What do
you think you're doing?
Your dad is on his knees.
I know I wasn't right,
but that jerk insulted my
family, called another kid BLP,
and made me lose my temper.
How dare you raise
your voice at me?
He was right.
Your family is messed up.
What's wrong with saying that?
And what? BLP?
That stands for basic
living pension, right?
You kids abbreviate just about
everything, so why not that?
- Look here, ma'am!
- Oh my gosh.
You can't even keep
your kid in check.
How dare you yell at me?
You're right, I can't
keep my kid in check.
But clearly, you're just as bad.
What was that?
Like father like son.
That's right.
Tak can't stand
injustice, just like me.
I guess Jae Hoon
takes after you...
and likes to divide people
and attack the weak.
- Are you done?
- No, far from it.
You're Inju Mom, aren't you?
The one who posted the nasty
post about the chicken restaurant.
- Why are you changing the topic?
- It's the same topic.
They're both about mom and
son slandering other people.
Fine.
Tak will take responsibility
for the assault.
But you will have to take
responsibility for posting lies.
I'm sorry.
I'm speechless.
Why didn't you
tell me that sooner?
Did you ask?
Anyway, whatever the
situation, you can't assault people.
Assault is the lowest
way of expressing rage.
You're not even my
dad. Stop lecturing me.
What was that?
If you want to act
like an old fogy,
have your own
kid and do it to him.
Tak. Hey, kid.
(Studio apartments)
This is where he
has been living?
Jung.
What happened?
What happened to your foot?
I hurt my foot while working.
It's nothing serious.
Anyway, what brings you here?
What...
Why didn't you tell me
you were living like this?
Jung. I'm really okay.
This place is
nicer than it looks.
It's so nice and cozy.
Keep it down!
See? I can't sleep
well by myself,
but I sleep really well here because
it's like they're sleeping with me.
Let's not do this here.
Let's go home and
have dinner together.
Darn it. Who is it?
Who is this?
How could we make someone
who's injured live there alone?
What other choice do we have?
It's already overcrowded with
the kids. There's no room for him.
No.
Don't mind me. I'm totally fine.
You always say you're fine.
- I want to live with Jung Woo.
- Me too.
No.
And Jung Woo isn't
the problem right now.
Then?
The school violence committee
is meeting today because of Tak.
He may be forced
to transfer out.
That punk.
Da Jung, you're in
no position to talk.
You're just as bad.
Here comes the man of the hour.
You haven't eaten
yet, right? Come eat.
Come in.
Is someone here?
- Daddy!
Hello, I'm Han Dong
Nam. I'm their dad.
(The Great Show)
You are Da Jung's
biological dad, right?
He's very suspicious.
That spoon and
chopsticks are Mr. Wi's.
It's all the same thing.
He's a total thief. All
he needs is a knife.
1,000 dollars?
I'm so glad you're with me.
What's going on here?
(Kim Hye Jin)
I want to be the best.
Tak stabbed his
friend in the leg.
It's better than being hit.
I'm regretting it deeply.
Can't you be our dad,
not just our guardian?