- Re-timing by YHANG -
[ Characters, locales, organizations, incidents,
and situations in this drama are fictitious ]
Huh?
What the.
Wait...
What is this?
I told you already.
That I'm on my way to meet my dad.
Huh?
Do you like your Christmas present?
What?
Look, it's fish. The fish!
This looks okay...
enough for five people to live in.
Wait, wait, wait. Look...
Can you please explain?
Why I'm your dad?
Huh?
You remember Kim Sun Mi, right?
Kim Sun Mi?
My first time hearing it.
I see.
You'll pretend you don't know, huh?
No, I...
If I remember, I'll say so.
Why lie about it?
Miss.
I guess...
your mom's name must
be Kim Sun Mi.
It's really my first time hearing it.
Okay?
You went to Ongdo in college, correct?
Where?
An island near Taehan.
Ongdo.
Ongdo?
Kim Sun Mi.
[ Ongdo Cruise ]
[ Year 2001 ]
So...
are you going to Ongdo?
Yes.
By yourself?
Yes, why?
I'm by myself as well.
This poem comes to mind...
seeing that island from here.
"There is an island between the people."
"I want to...
go to that island."
So pretty.
To be here...
the two of us...
Do you like to exercise?
Exercise, yes.
Aigoo, guys like doing pull-ups.
- Please be careful.
- No, I can do it.
Oh, are you okay?
Sit down and look around.
If you do, Ongdo...
- is prettier.
- Okay.
Like the movie "Before Sunrise,"
we only knew each
other's age and name
and became lovers for
a day on the island.
[ Episode 2: The weight
of the decision ]
Do you remember now?
No...
I mean...
You're saying...
That girl I had met there...
is your mother?
I look familiar, huh?
You know, I look just like my mom.
Okay, you know...
Yes, that did happen in college.
But getting pregnant...
I shouldn't say this to a student.
Say it.
You can say whatever you
want to your daughter.
Fine.
On that day, your mom and I...
did it only once.
Also, it was our first time
for both of us.
Wow, daebak.
You two must've had some
amazing chemistry.
Unni, what is "having
amazing chemistry?"
It means your hearts are
an amazing match.
What a nice thing to teach a kid.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait just a minute.
You're at the wrong house.
I don't know what you
heard from your mom,
but the probability I'm your dad...
Well, okay.
It's the same as winning
the lotto, okay?
Congratulations.
You've won the lotto.
Man...
Arguing won't get you anywhere.
To have a high school-aged
daughter at my age?
All righty.
Then let's do it.
Do what?
What do you think?
A DNA paternity test.
What?
If the results state otherwise,
then I'll apologize and go away.
But...
But, but?
If it's confirmed,
you must take all of us in.
What is this?
There's more? Huh?
Did you tell Soo Hyun?
That I'm your dad?
This unni?
I didn't tell her.
Not yet.
It's a bachelor's home,
why come over...
Bachelor, my foot.
Whoa, it's bigger than I thought.
It's a nice house.
- Is this the kitchen?
- Huh?
Hey, hey, Soo Hyun. You know...
Why did you come over at this hour?
Oh, I...
need to borrow a hammer.
A hammer this late at night?
But Sunbae, why are you shaking?
You think I'll strike you with it?
Geez, why make such a scary joke.
No, I need a hammer for my place.
I'm usually like this.
If something needs to get done,
I must do it right away.
So do you live here by yourself?
Huh?
Yeah, well...
Nope.
He'll live with us.
Noona, I have to go pee.
Aigoo, the hammer was
way over there.
Here.
Okay.
Goodnight and get home safely.
Thanks. Then get some rest.
You, too.
Hey.
Huh?
The girl from the afternoon.
Who, who?
Da Jung, the one who'd
lost her brother.
Oh, Da Jung.
From the market.
Yes, her name is Da Jung.
What about her?
Do you think she'll be okay?
About what?
Aigoo, I mean...
I was thinking it over...
and we don't know how
her biological dad will be.
The kids shouldn't see
him by themselves.
That's true. I see your point.
Sunbae.
How about we accompany
them and see him too?
No way! What are you saying?
Why should we meet him?
Why get angry?
Well, I was just joking.
Were you startled?
Yes, I understand your concern, but...
this is a very personal matter.
A third-party butting in is rude.
- You think?
- Yes.
- You can't hold it?
- No.
It's about to come out.
Hey.
Let's wait for now.
Don't be calling her first or anything.
I guess.
But I feel better after
talking to you, Sunbae.
- I'll get going.
- Okay.
Good luck with the hammer.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I'm about to suffocate.
Hey, hey, don't touch my stuff
without permission.
That's very important to me.
Give it.
There are cups in the kitchen...
What is this?
It's better you don't know.
Huh?
Come here.
Hey.
Did you meet your dad?
S***.
If you're so worried, just call her.
I don't want to be butting in.
Then get your mind off of it.
You're right. He wouldn't kick
his own daughter out.
Ah.
The test results will take one day.
You can sleep here tonight.
It's a waste of time.
My mom wouldn't make
stuff up like this.
Lies aren't only told
by the bad people.
Ahjussi, what is your blood type?
I'm an O.
You see, you see?
Mom is an O, I'm an O,
and you're an O.
You can't deny it.
It's not like an RH minus type.
There are many type O's in the world.
Anyway, my instincts are pretty good,
and it's obvious you're it, Ahjussi.
When I first saw you, I felt
affection and closeness...
This is why blood is
thicker than water.
I'm sorry, but...
I don't feel those emotions at all.
That's because
you're so worn down,
and your emotions are dried up.
Right, so...
You have no other close relatives?
I have no contact with my stepdad,
and I have one uncle
but he's in dire straits
so I can't ask him for help.
Honestly, I have my pride, too.
Why else would I have come to
you when we've never met?
Aigoo, really...
It's getting late. You must
be tired, get some sleep.
Okay.
Please get some rest.
Daddy.
Noona, are we going to live here?
Yeah.
If Ahjussi is your dad,
is he our dad, too?
I guess you can say that.
Then what about our real dad?
Well...
You'll have two dads.
Wow, how nice is that?
Most people have one,
but we have two.
But I don't think Ahjussi
likes us much.
No.
Ahjussi said you guys are very cute.
Liar.
I'm serious.
When did you ever see me lie?
Your entire life is a lie.
You want to die?
Unni, but...
what if Ahjussi kicks us out?
Song Yi, you don't know
what kind of person he is.
Ahjussi is a super great guy.
He was even an assemblyman.
An assemblyman?
What's that?
It's similar to a con-artist.
Man, that little punk...
Han Tak, stop being jaded.
Unni, then is Ahjussi a con-artist?
No.
Song Yi, you have
a class president, right?
Yes.
A kid who's nice and popular
gets voted the president, right?
Yes.
Assemblymen are similar
to class presidents.
My class president goes
around hitting everyone.
Assemblymen are like that.
They beat up everyone.
Seriously.
Like father, like daughter.
But after the test,
what if Ahjussi is not your dad?
Even if that's the test results,
there's no way Ahjussi
will kick us out.
How would she know
what I'm thinking?
Why not?
I told you.
Ahjussi is a super great guy.
So stop worrying and
get some sleep.
Where are you going?
To make money.
You said no designated
driving today.
How can I take a break?
Guys, Ahjussi is off to work.
Let's say bye.
Bye, see you later.
Okay.
If I submit the test myself,
people might talk.
Do me this favor.
Well, submitting this
test isn't difficult,
but what on earth?
You're not even married.
Shouldn't we hold
a shamanic ceremony?
That costs money.
I don't have any right now.
Right.
But...
what will you do if she is
your biological daughter?
What do you mean?
Let's say she is my
biological daughter.
Her siblings are completely
unrelated to me.
Well, that's true.
S***.
It's hard enough taking
care of myself.
Since she has an uncle,
I'll talk to him tomorrow.
What the hell.
Hey, hey, kiddo.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Don't jump on the sofa.
It's dangerous, come down.
It's not dangerous.
Ahjussi, I can do a forward roll.
What do you think? I'm good, huh?
You're up.
What are you doing?
Making bean paste casserole.
I'm a good cook like my mom.
- No!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Geez...
If you're going to poop,
you should close the door.
If I close the door, it's too
stuffy, and I can't go.
You shouldn't get startled then.
You're the one pooping with the
door open, so why get startled?
I'm the one who's startled.
Please don't say "poop" to a lady.
You have no manners.
You're the one who barged in,
and now you want manners.
I'm speechless.
Did I have this game
on my computer?
I downloaded it.
Man, you can't do that there.
This is a complete mess.
Why aren't you eating?
I have no appetite.
Please have some bean
paste casserole.
Then your appetite will come back.
What did you eat yesterday?
Ahjussi.
What?
Do you know how to say
"Don't fart" in English?
No, I don't.
It's "Don't pass gas."
(Sounds like Donkatsu.)
It's hilarious, isn't it?
Our Song Yi is a whiz
at a nonsense quiz.
If you live with her,
she'll crack you up. Yes.
I don't know yet if we'll
live together or not.
What do you mean by that?
Whether you're really
my biological daughter,
whether we'll live together or
go back to your old place.
Nothing has been decided.
We have nowhere to go back to.
What?
What are you talking about?
Our rent is backed up, so the
landlord told us to leave.
I'll meet with the landlord.
Living here will be
uncomfortable for everyone.
I'm not uncomfortable at all.
I'm uncomfortable here. Me!
Why are you yelling at the child?
I can't even yell in my own house?
You're in a stranger's house
doing whatever you want!
He's a tyrant, a tyrant.
Now I know why he lost
the assemblyman seat.
What?
What the heck? Give it back.
When talking to an adult, meet
their eyes and be courteous.
Ahjussi, who do you think you are?
This is my house.
My house, my rules.
If you don't like it, get out.
Understand?
Dad, please understand.
He's going through puberty.
You keep saying that
since yesterday...
Isn't it a bit premature
to call me "dad"?
Am I Hong Gil Dong or something?
That I can't even address
my own dad?
Goodness, and?
So what happened?
Did she meet her dad?
I don't know. She hasn't called me.
Geez, I'm so curious
about what will happen.
Isn't this perfect for
"Screening Humanity"?
No, it's weak sauce.
Don't you know Nam Bora?
She has 13 brothers and sisters.
I'm close to the writer of
"Screening Humanity."
Should I tell her their story?
Geez, don't.
We don't know what
will happen yet.
Her biological dad
may take them in.
I think that possibility is a zero.
Why?
One biological child is tough to
raise in our country, but four?
Plus three kids are not
blood-related to him.
Who would take them in?
But you never know.
The twins are adorable, too.
I have a feeling he'll take them in.
Da Jung's stepdad?
Don't even go there.
He used to be a detective
but is total trash.
In what ways?
He got into casinos and
blew everything they had.
He left home two years ago
and no one's heard from him.
It's better that he's not around.
So the only person the
kids could depend on...
is you, correct? You're her uncle.
Who, me?
Da Jung told me that her
uncle is a great guy.
If it were up to me,
I'd take all of them in.
I'm the only living blood
relative they have.
That's what I'm saying.
Even if Da Jung ends up
being my daughter,
I'm not familiar with her.
And Da Jung's siblings must
find me uncomfortable.
But...
I owe 60 million won in debt,
plus my study dorm rent
is two months behind.
Every single day is arduous for me.
After learning Da Jung's
biological dad is you,
honestly, I was envious of her.
Geez, no need to feel that...
Assemblyman, if you're
Da Jung's dad,
you'll be my brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law.
I'm in such dire straits...
could you please lend
me 500,000 won?
Pardon?
Brother-in-law.
- Please...
- Brother-in-law.
But...
Yes.
I submitted the test.
Did you meet the uncle? How is he?
Yeah, I just met with him.
Having any ties with
this family will kill me.
Please enjoy.
- Aigoo, hello.
- Yes.
Please enjoy your meal.
[ Assemblyman Kang Kyung Hoon: Sharing healthy, warm love ]
Aigoo, hello there.
You must've been starving.
You must eat to get
back on your feet.
- Yes.
- Please stay strong.
Yes, that's right. Hello there.
- Thank you.
- Please enjoy.
Yes.
Please stay strong.
Aigoo...
- Please eat a lot.
- Thank you.
Aigoo...
Geez.
Here.
Man...
Aigoo...
Since I'm getting older
and losing my strength,
I can't even do this anymore.
It's not due to your age.
It's probably your mind.
What do you mean?
You see it as political festivities,
not volunteer work.
Whether it's volunteer work
or political festivities.
I think it's time for me to call it quits.
We'll get going.
Okay.
What did you just mean...
by "time to call it quits"?
I won't run in the next
general election.
Why not?
Wasn't it your dream to
make it to the Blue House?
You go there instead of me.
I've already told you.
I have no plans to be a politician.
The conservative party is
under attack right now.
Yet you'll just flap
your mouth around?
That's why I do TV shows.
To defend the worth of
a healthy conservatism.
To establish that worth,
you must act, not just talk.
Stop making excuses
and come on in.
No one is owning the party.
So the timing isn't bad, either.
Are you seeing anyone?
I'm not dating anyone.
But someone has
caught my interest.
Politics is another form
of a family business.
When your family participates,
your chances go up.
If you like her, that's fine.
Have the wedding before
the general election.
This is why I don't
want to enter politics.
I don't want to put politics
before my family, as you have.
There are many different
types of people in the world.
Unni, I met my dad.
He's such a great guy.
Those who are kind...
Thank you for your efforts.
We'll invite you out
soon with the CEO.
Those who are corrupt.
Then there are lifetime rivals.
The most dangerous
type to a politician...
is the one clinging on for dear life.
If you can't severe ties with them...
you'll go down together.
Hey, Han Tak.
Did you have a good day?
I cleaned the place with my siblings.
I'm great at organizing like my mom.
Let's talk for a minute.
No need to be scared.
He's just acting like that.
Watch TV while I go talk to Ahjussi.
Okay.
He's such a f***er.
I knew this would happen.
Whatever happens, happens.
Did you eat?
Of course.
We ordered Chinese with
the credit card you gave me.
That's good.
I wanted to make rice,
but there was no rice.
The paternity test results
will be out tomorrow.
I told you it's a waste of time.
My mom wouldn't lie about...
Regardless of the test results,
I only have one choice.
And what's that?
Take a look.
[ Children are our future ]
What...
is this?
I went there myself today.
It's a clean building
and the director is a good person.
And?
You may think I'm grand
since I was an assemblyman.
But once an assemblyman
is done, he's nothing.
And becoming someone's guardian...
It's a heavy responsibility to bear.
I can't afford to take on
that responsibility right now.
Even if...
I am your daughter...
you'll...
[ Hari Orphanage ]
send us here?
Even if I am your biological dad,
I have no relations with
your siblings, right?
I'm not obligated nor have
the means to take them in.
And I can't tear you and
your siblings apart, right?
Until...
I graduate and start making money...
Is that too much?
Do you know what pops up
when you search my name?
What?
"Sinner."
As you did to your father.
You'll...
discard your daughter, too?
You're a quick one.
I think I came to the wrong person.
My apologies for troubling you.
Da Jung.
Where are you going
this late at night?
Then let's take my car.
I'll drop you off.
Come on, let's go.
If you won't take responsibility...
then don't mind us anymore.
Da Jung!
Soo Hyun.
Wait...
What's everyone doing over here?
Huh?
Well...
That's...
I mean...
We wanted to say bye
before we went back home.
- Yeah, they wanted to say bye.
- Yes.
But why?
Weren't you staying
at your dad's place?
Oh...
His place is too small,
so we can't stay there.
Where does your dad live?
Around here?
Let's go together.
I'll go myself and speak with him.
Hey, you're so intrusive.
Hey, Jung Soo Hyun.
Doing this will make things
harder on Da Jung.
What's wrong with you?
Then what are you
doing here, Sunbae?
I was going to take
the kids home.
I can't send them off alone.
What are you doing? Get in the car.
That car's over there,
what are you doing?
Okay, okay, let's go. Come on.
Come here.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Hurry, let's go.
All right, come on.
Let's get in.
Okay, please get in.
Here.
All right, put on your seat belts.
- Put on your seat belts.
- I'll go with you.
Get out, where are you going?
Man, this is nuts.
You said your dad is a great guy.
He is a great guy, but
he's having some difficulties,
and the house is too small.
My siblings were
uncomfortable, too.
No, I wasn't uncomfortable at all.
That place was a s***hole.
And the dad was an a**hole, too.
I mean, even though your
dad is having difficulties,
how could he ignore you like this?
No.
He looked into an orphanage.
Then he did all he could.
Rather than living
with a dad you just met,
wouldn't the orphanage
be a better choice?
We're not orphans.
We'll just live on our own.
Where is it?
Thank you.
Please give me the luggage.
Well then, get some rest.
Hey, we should get going.
Tae Poong, Song Yi,
you must be tired.
Let's go inside. Let's go in.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
All right.
Noona, I'm hungry.
Make me ramen.
Okay, just a second.
Ramen...
I'll boil you some eggs.
What side dishes do you like?
Meat. We like beef.
- And Song Yi?
- Egg crepes and sausages.
And Tak?
Shark's fin.
You're butting in too much.
Because I'm worried about them.
Can't you tell by
looking at Da Jung?
What do you mean?
It's obvious. Her dad
kicked them out.
I knew that man would do this.
At age 20,
with a girl he just met,
with no precaution...
Aigoo...
No way someone like that
would take them in.
Truthfully, if I did it my way,
I'd totally report him.
I mean...
This is something worth reporting?
Why not?
This is clearly child abandonment.
The more I think, he's not even
human. He's a f***ing trash.
Hey, trash...
That's too much.
And f***ing trash is...
Everyone has their situation.
Wow, you're taking the
man's side, huh?
No, it's just...
Yes, I feel bad for the
kids' situation,
but think of the biological
dad's side, too.
Da Jung is his blood,
so he could take her in.
What about the siblings?
Those kids and that guy
are complete strangers.
Aigoo...
Well, then what would you
do about the kids, Sunbae?
We can't just leave them like that.
I know.
They should stay at the orphanage.
That's the best for
Da Jung and the kids.
That's not the best,
he's running away.
I'm going crazy.
Thank you for the side dishes.
I know I made it, but I can't
guarantee it's good.
I'm not skilled with my hands.
It was pretty decent.
Please get home safely.
Sure, okay.
Call me if anything comes up.
I hope I won't ever have to call you.
Call me even if nothing comes up.
You got it?
Okay.
I'll get going.
It's nice to be back home, right?
Yup.
But since I'm home, I miss Mom.
Me, too.
Song Yi.
Any other nonsense quiz
you got up there?
What does a king say when he
doesn't want to go to his palace?
"I won't go!"
Wrong.
- "You go then."
- Wrong.
I have no idea.
The correct answer is,
"I hate the palace, I hate the palace."
(Sounds like "palace," but actually mumbling and complaining)
Wow, it's hilarious.
It's so funny I'm tearing up.
Soundproof mode.
So...
Ahjussi is not your dad, Unni?
Well...
I think Mom was mistaken.
What? What are you looking for?
Handkerchief.
Mommy's handkerchief disappeared.
Unni, what should I do?
I think I left it at Ahjussi's house.
Unni, let's go find the handkerchief.
Don't cry, Song Yi.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'll call Ahjussi and ask
him to send it back.
Unni, let's go.
Thank you.
Go in and get some rest.
Sunbae.
Yes?
I mean...
about sending the kids
to an orphanage...
Isn't there any other way but that?
No, there isn't.
Sunbae.
There isn't any other choice.
This is the best, okay?
I'm off.
- No!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[ Hari Orphanage ]
Even if I am your daughter...
you'll...
send us here?
[ Head of Household Girl ]
Yeah, I just got home
and was about to call...
Song Yi left a handkerchief
at your house.
A handkerchief?
Yes.
It's pink with flower prints.
Song Yi gets anxious without it.
Why?
That was our mom's handkerchief...
When she holds it,
she feels Mom next to her.
I know you're bothered,
but please send it to us if you find it.
I'll text you our address.
Okay then.
And...
Man, snap out of it.
You shouldn't worry
about someone else.
How many hours has it been?
You should act your age.
Just let me be.
If I don't even do this,
I may do something worse.
Do something worse?
Barge into Da Jung's
biological dad's house,
and deliver a cold, hard slap.
I know it's sad,
but aren't you overreacting?
How can I not overreact?
We dropped off the kids
alone in a shack.
Where could the handkerchief be?
Maybe she lost it somewhere else?
Oh, there it is.
It's here.
Hey, Bong Joo.
The paternity test results are out.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on a second.
What are the results?
There's good news and bad news.
They are not a match; therefore
it's not a father and daughter relation.
Yes!
Wow, what a close call.
You punk. What did I tell you?
There's no way she's my daughter.
But why would her mom
say you were the dad?
Huh?
It's obvious, isn't it?
To plant some fantasy
in her daughter's head.
If her real dad was an assemblyman,
how proud would she be?
She told a lie simply to create
a fantasy for her child?
If that's not it, then...
It's one or the other.
Her mom doesn't know
who the biological dad is...
Or?
The biological dad...
is someone whom
she can't tell the kids about.
Whatever, whatever.
It has nothing to do with me.
Woohoo!
But will you just leave
the kids like that?
Huh?
Well...
I know I'm not her dad,
but how could I ignore the
kids when they're left alone?
Shouldn't they stay in an orphanage?
That's true. As opposed
to living with you,
that would be better for the kids.
You were once my aide,
but you're a hater.
You really hate me.
Aigoo...
So what's the bad news?
- Huh?
- You know...
Assemblyman Kang's son,
Kang Joon Ho.
Your classmate.
What about him?
The news is all over Yeouido.
At the next general election,
Kang Joon Ho will be the candidate
from Assemblyman Kang's district.
What?
Unni.
Go to the hospital
- and get a brain MRI or something.
- Why?
You gobble up headache meds as if
they're vitamins. Aren't you worried?
A writer should have
an ailment to look cool.
What a thing to say.
Words to remember.
The door is open.
Go on up first.
Let's go up together.
You have a headache and all.
It hurts due to lack of exercise.
I'm going.
His place is too small,
so we can't stay there.
[ Former Assemblyman
Wie Dae Han's Lecture ]
Everyone.
How does a bird fly?
Yes, like this.
Yes.
It needs both wings
to balance and fly well.
Sames goes for politics.
"Progressivism" and "conservatism."
You need these two wings.
However,
just what is "progressivism"
and what is "conservatism"?
Does anyone know the answer?
It's all right, please relax.
Yes, I'm in a lecture.
What did you say?
An assemblyman is giving a lecture.
Which assemblyman?
I don't know him too well,
but he says he's an assemblyman.
Geez, I can't even comment.
Man, seriously.
Here.
Look at this article.
What is it?
[ Assemblyman Kang Kyung Hoon's volunteer
work with his son for the homeless ]
What's this?
When most politicians
do things like this,
most comments are negative.
But look at the comments
for this article.
Successful people are
successful for a reason.
Mr. Kang and his son, prosper!
Handsome guys hang
with handsome guys.
A handsome father
and a handsome son.
That is the truth.
Kang Kang family is the love...
(Sounds like "dirty")
The love of my heart.
They're all positive.
Why do you think?
Why is that?
Even if Kang Kyung Hoon
the politician is so-so,
his family looks wonderful.
So what's your point?
Being a politician with the
"Nation's Sinner" label.
It'll be impossible.
I'm saying this out of
consideration for you.
You should quit politics.
It's not over till it's over.
"Courage" and "bravado" are different.
Behaving this way is not
courage, it's bravado.
Quitting at the right time
takes real courage.
It's late, I'll get going.
Sunbae.
I'll prove it at the next
general election.
What you said to me today...
isn't advice, but meddling.
I'm leaving.
- Hello.
- Dad, look.
Bangtan Boys and BTS
are one and the same?
- Really?
- Of course!
How much gas?
- Please fill it up.
- Okay, will do.
Han Da Jung.
Hey.
Why aren't you at school...
I'm busy right now. Sorry.
You know her?
Yes, she's my school friend.
But Dad,
you really didn't know
they were the same?
No, why?
Am I Hong Gil Dong or something?
That I can't even address
my own dad?
Do you know what pops up
when you search my name?
"Sinner."
As you did to your father.
You'll...
discard your daughter, too?
You're a quick one.
I'm at work, what's up?
Forget work, come home
asap. We're in trouble.
- Noona.
- Unni.
Why are you guys doing that?
Hey, you should
educate your siblings.
They're so unruly.
Get up.
I said, get up!
Says who?
I heard you're here for Dad's debt.
If you want your money, talk to me.
Start talking. I have ears.
We haven't heard from
Dad in two years.
We'd like to know where he is, too.
Two years. He should be
missing his kids by now.
It's really hard to sever blood ties.
We'll have to stay here for now, okay?
Aigoo... Aigoo, so comfy.
Aigoo, this is nice.
Aigoo, how relaxing.
Hey, now.
Let's take a nap.
- Did you see that?
- Yeah, daebak.
Attorney Kang Joon Ho,
who's beautiful inside and out.
I'm always rooting for you.
There's an old saying you
can tell a lot by one's family.
Out of conservatives,
Kang Kyung Hoon seems the best.
What is Kang Kyung Hoon's former
opponent Wie Dae Han up to now?
Maybe getting free meals
from the homeless center?
Why, this punk...
Stop putting on a show and
focus on parliamentary politics.
Kang Kyung Hoon didn't propose any
legislation in the National Assembly.
I'm getting a call. Who is it?
Excuse me.
- Where is my name?
- You're in first place!
You're at the top!
[ 1: Wie Dae Han
2: Kang Joon Ho ]
- All right!
- You're number one!
- You did it!
- This is awesome!
- Of course.
- Yup.
Don't be discouraged.
Second place is amazing, too.
Wie Dae Han.
Hey, Kang Joon Ho.
Long time no see.
I know.
How have you been?
Huh?
I'm doing well, just taking
care of my district.
I guess you're still in politics.
Of course, people are
watching. How can I not?
You know.
Anyway, tell your father
to take a break now.
And leave politics to
young people like me.
If the water stands still, it'll go bad.
It's been still for too long.
Let's grab a beer
when you have time.
Well, that sounds good.
But I don't know when I'll have time.
Many are asking for me.
I came out tonight, too, since
they were begging me to come out.
Is that right?
Then we'll take our time.
Okay.
I'll see you next time.
- Okay, goodnight.
- All right.
Yes, I'm almost there...
You're the one who called
a designated driver?
What a funny situation.
I think you'll be uncomfortable.
I'll call another driver.
No, it's fine.
I don't pick and
choose my customers.
Is this it?
Give me your keys.
You waited a while, huh?
You know Assemblyman
Wie Dae Han, right?
We're high school alumni.
Of course, I do.
Assemblyman Wie Dae Han.
But what are you doing here,
Assemblyman Wie...
Give me your keys.
What's this?
I called for a designated driver...
and Wie Dae Han showed up.
How do you know Hye Jin...
Oh. We attend the same church.
Don't misunderstand.
She's like a sister to me.
Any rumors will scare
away her suitors.
I'm okay.
If my suitors go away,
I'll just marry you.
How is designated
driving? Isn't it rough?
It depends on who the customer is.
I hear you've done this over a year.
You've got guts.
My father says that
you need guts for politics.
For the record, Assemblyman Kang is
the reason I decided to get into politics.
Really?
Do you remember our bet
in high school for the grades?
Yes. Yes, I do remember.
When I placed the top of
the class, my mom's store...
almost got kicked out of the market.
Due to Assemblyman Kang's influence.
It's polite to let the
bygones be bygones.
Since he started it,
let's see it through.
And then?
I went to Assemblyman Kang
and begged.
That I won't take your spot, so please
let my mom's store remain at the market.
I studied mediocre to keep
my mom's store safe.
But that was more difficult...
than being the top of the class.
What does that have...
anything to do with
you going into politics?
I made a decision after that incident.
That I'll become an assemblyman.
I'll become an assemblyman
and chase out all the
bad assemblymen.
But then I got kicked out.
The bad assemblymen
were quite powerful.
If that's true,
I'll apologize on my father's behalf.
No need for an apology.
We should just bury the past.
However,
isn't it wrong to get into politics
over a personal vendetta?
What about the poor citizens?
Oh, oh, stop, stop,
the red light! Stop!
All right.
Man...
It's not going well.
All right, godori!
I'll bring it for now.
Oh, yeah!
Great, great!
I'm shaking them.
One go!
Wow, she's a master hwatu player.
Aren't you scared of us?
Not scared at all.
You guys coming over makes
me feel secure, uncles.
Won't you go now?
Hurry up and go.
S***.
Aigoo, not working.
Geez...
Okay.
Oh, yeah!
I got gwangbak there!
Okay, two go!
Man...
Are they starving or something?
I told you, two chickens
won't cut it.
Let's order one more then.
I'll buy this one.
I want fried.
Okay.
Hey, Da Jung. I was just
about to call you.
We ordered two seasoned
chickens earlier.
Please deliver one fried, too.
What are you talking about?
Is something the matter?
Your orders are backed up,
and it'll be a while?
Something's going on.
I understand. I'll be right there.
Okay, please come asap.
No one's playing Go-stop?
I don't see anyone playing. Hurry up.
Let's go.
Yes, yes.
It's right after the intersection.
Okay.
I was nervous because
you were talking and
not focusing on driving.
I have insurance.
They'll take care of
the body shop fees.
It's just a car.
Thank God, no one was hurt.
- You called a designated driver?
- Yes, this car.
Well, then.
Let me give you a piece
of advice as a friend.
Control your rage.
So you won't have accidents
in both driving and politics.
I'll get going.
Let me ask you one thing.
I hear you'll be running in the next
general election in your father's place.
Is it true?
I'm thinking it over.
Then let me give you
a piece of advice as a friend.
Don't get into politics.
It's a tough place for
timid boys like you.
Perhaps so.
However...
I know I can do better than you.
Politics.
See you later.
Hey, Soo Hyun.
Sunbae.
I think something's
happened to Da Jung.
What?
When is the chicken coming?
Unni.
The ahjussis are staying
here like that?
No, they'll leave soon.
Stop worrying and go to sleep.
You too, Tae Poong.
Maybe that noona is not coming?
No.
She'll come.
I said, when is the chicken coming?
I think our order got canceled.
I'll order it from another place.
Soo Hyun unni?
This is a chicken restaurant?
I guess you don't know.
It's a hot chicken spot these days.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Come out.
Come out!
Come out, s***!
Open the door!
Open it before we break it down!
You have your phone, right?
Let's call the police.
My battery is dead.
Her phone is off,
what should we do?
We shouldn't have
left them like that.
Please, please...
The news is all over Yeouido.
At the next general election,
Kang Joon Ho will be the candidate
from Assemblyman Kang's district.
I know I can do better than you.
Politics.
Being a politician with the
"Nation's Sinner" label.
It'll be impossible.
About sending the kids
to an orphanage.
Isn't there any other way but that?
If you won't take responsibility...
don't mind us anymore.
Once again...
I'm at a life-altering
decisive moment.
Korean cola
is delicious
If it's delicious,
then have it again
If you have it again,
you'll get a tummy ache
What are you doing?
Dr. Smarty Pants,
please take a guess
Ding, dong
Deng, dong...
How dare you barge in
and make this mess?
Who the heck are you?
Who are you to...
disrupt a legitimate
lender's business?
How on earth is this legitimate?
Don't you know that collection
is illegal after 9 p.m.?
Also, illegal lenders using
extortion and violence
will receive five years in jail
and 50 million won in fine.
If you want to serve time
that badly, just say the word.
I'll make sure you stay there.
Han Da Jung.
Bring your siblings and come out.
Why are you hiding like that?
Isn't this your home?
Hurry up and come out!
Han Da Jung!
Come here, hurry.
Okay, okay, like that.
Are you all right?
No need to be scared.
Those ahjussis are
ignorant about the law.
This will never happen again, okay?
Will you walk out or
be dragged out?
By any chance,
do you know their dad?
No, not at all.
Then what's your
relation to the kids?
My relation?
Here.
Song Yi.
Tae Poong.
Tak.
Da Jung.
Starting today,
I'll be their dad.
[ The Great Show ]
- Re-timing by YHANG -
You know this already.
Until I remove the "sinner" label,
I can't be back in politics.
I'm not doing this just for me.
The kids need a guardian.
You have money to raise them?
- But why not?
- No.
You're Assemblyman
Wie Dae Han, right?
Pick whatever you want!
It's an investment.
Shoulder riding is really dangerous.
You're Wie Dae Han, right?
You're the Nation's Dad!
It's worth being a dad.
Did you take them in to remove
your "sinner" label? Is that it?
Why? I can't do that?
- What?
- I can't find Tae Poong.
Tae Poong!