Chun Yu?
Uncle Lin.
Uncle Lin, you're back.
Your daughter came to see you, so I let her in.
- She…
- Quickly get that computer.
Young lady, let me tell you, your dad truly loves you.
He spent a lot of money
to buy an expensive laptop for you.
- Uncle Lin, hurry up.
- She is not…
Too embarrassed to do it yourself, are you? I'll do it for you.
She's your child. Don't be embarrassed.
Don't go through my things, you…
- Don't think I don't know. You just put it under this sheet.
- Don't go through my things.
All right, all right. Leave please.
Hello.
Hello, is this Chun Yu?
Yes.
Please come to the school gate.
It's your grandma. She…
- What's wrong with my grandma?
- Are you all right?
No, she's… she's in the guard room. Just come over here.
- Okay.
- What happened to your grandma?
I don't know. They said she's at the gate.
I'll come along.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Please sit down, please sit down.
Things are getting serious again.
Grandma.
Xiao Yu.
You are Chun Yu, right? You finally made it.
Your grandma insisted on entering to bring you food.
but we have a policy that no outsiders are allowed in now.
As you know, we've been practicing fire drills for two days.
I brought you some drunken shrimp.
Just let me in and I'll come right out.
I'll just put it there and leave right away.
- Why don't you let me in?  Why don't you let me in?
- Grandma.
We really do have a no entry policy.
Grandma, thanks for bringing me my favorite drunken shrimp,
but the school does have its policies.
I'll walk you back, and we'll eat it together, okay?
No.
You take it back and share it with your friends in the dorm.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm leaving.
- Bye, grandma.
Goodbye, Granny.
- What's wrong?
-  What's the matter?
- My back!
- Let's go to the hospital.
My back!
Can we go to the hospital? Come on, let's go to the hospital.
Are these chronic problems?
Then I'll take your grandma home with you.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Be careful.
- I'm going to call a taxi.
I'll call a taxi. Be careful.
Xiaoqin?
Did you choose this class too?
What about Yang Bawan?
I don't know. He's probably not taking this class.
Just stop thinking about those things.
Live in the moment. We'll get through it together.
Xiaoqin.
Wenya, could you move over there?
Sure.
Don't forget what I said this morning.
I understand. Time and space, right?
I'm sitting here. This space should be far enough, right?
Students, class has begun.
Come on, class has begun. Turn to page seven.
Be careful.
- Be careful.
Cushion, put on the cushion.
- Xiao Yu, go pour Uncle Lin a glass of water.
- Okay.
No need, I'm leaving.
Wait. Uncle Lin, take a seat.
You still need to drink some water.
All right.
Come on.
Look at you, you are so careless.
When will you change that?
- It's fine.
- I'm sorry.
- Look, it's all wet.
- It's okay.
It's just a little water.
It's okay.
He's so attached to this notebook.
What exactly is written inside?
This water is cold. Get some warm water.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Uncle Lin.
Take a look at this child.
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
Grandma, did you make dumplings?
The stuffing is already done,
but I haven't rolled the wrappers.
I thought you were coming back to eat.
Roll the wrappers? I don't know how.
Uncle Lin, why don't you teach me and have a meal with us?
Look at this girl.
He has to cook for the students.
Today I don't have a shift in the canteen.
Anyway, I'm free.
Chun Yu has been helping me all this time.
- This is my opportunity to thank her.
- Right, right.
Okay then. Where are the dumplings?
Grandma, just wait here.
Well, that's great.
Let me help you.
No need, you can just watch.
By the way, Xiao Yu, our rice cooker is broken.
Maybe you should find someone to fix it.
Okay.
I can take a look.
S-Sure.
This is the one. It may not be repairable.
I'll take a look.
There is no light in here.
Maybe there's a bad wire.
Do you have an electrician's toolkit at home?
Yes.
Nian Yongcheng refused my request for help.
I've been to the equipment management center,
but it requires a high-security access card.
Look for it in the Chief Engineer's office, room 202.
Do you know Chun Yiming?
Is he related to all this?
We'll be in touch after you get the pulse device.
Look for it in the Chief Engineer's office, room 202.
Hi, Engineer Gao, do you need help?
No, I'm going back. Thank you.
Uncle Lin, do you know how to repair it?
When I first came to the city, I worked as an electrician.
It's on. You are great.
Let's make more dumplings.
Okay, Grandma, just wait a minute.
Grandmother, why did you come here?
Sit over there and rest.
I'm here to supervise the work.
To supervise? We won't slack off.
You won't slack off, but I'm afraid you'll cut corners.
Look at this.
Look at this girl working.
She's making a mess everywhere.
She's afraid no one will know she's been working.
Mr. Lin,
today, our dumpling filling has no onions.
(Won't cause any tears.)
I miss my daughter.
I haven't seen her in a while.
Do you miss your daughter?
I have a good idea.
Put all of your yearning and missing into the filling,
give it a pinch,
and then eat it.
When I'm full, I'll have a sweet dream.
It'll be nice just to see her.
It is still nice to see her in a dream, is it not?
The water is boiling. Come on.
Time to drop the dumplings.
I'll also carry this plate over.
Let's cook the dumplings.
- The dumplings are here.
- They're here.
Uncle Lin, today let's treat each other as family
and have a good meal, shall we?
Please taste it.
Let's start eating.
Let's eat.
Come on, let's eat.
Thank you.
- Come on.
- Okay, thank you. I'll do it myself.
You did all these things.
You are too kind.
Chun Yu, are you interested in my notebook?
I…
Look. These are some of my daily notes.
It's a recipe book.
Our leader said students nowadays have more picky taste buds,
so he asked me to come up with a few new dishes.
That is why I spend all day studying it.
Professional.
Stop looking. Come on, let's eat.
- Okay.
- Come on.
The drunken shrimp is so delicious.
- Come on. Eat.
- Yes, I'll give it a try.
All right.
Uncle Lin could open it because he was an electrician.
There are rational explanations for the notebook and the recipe.
That means there is only Chun Yiming left,
whose identity is still suspicious.
If Chun Yiming is Mazzolini…
Then how is he related to Gao Xuan?
Where are you?
I'm heading out for an emergency. I'll come back to you later.
Zero, Four, One, Nine. .
You Brat! What are you doing?
You're as ruthless as your mom.
If you dare, then leave!
How dare you pour out my wine!
That is the day we met when we were children.
I'd like to know more about the self-developed equipment.
Well, the self-developed equipment section
is confidential.
I'm afraid I can't share that information with you.
Okay, I understand.
Gao Xuan, do not disappoint me.
Okay.
Hello, Chun Yu. Where are you?
I'm out.
I was telling you I found something very important.
I'm busy, we'll talk later.
My dear daughter, you are so clever.
Your father is also Microtech's former chief engineer.
My project has been completed.
Microtech and Tianji have a very close connection.
This place has been untouched since your father's resignation.
Your father was one of the founders of Tianji.
This is President Nian's office.
These two companies' businesses are quite similar.
This indicates there is a connection between them.
I have a friend who wants to fund all of my research.
In the end, everything is related to you.
You are finally here, my daughter.
I know you have a lot of questions.
I'll tell you everything right now.
Where should I start?
Chun Yu, have you ever felt lonely?
It's not what you think.
This is what will make you fly in the sky
but only to find yourself in the abyss.
Do you know what it feels like?
Daddy, come play with me.
Maybe a lot of people thought I had a happy life.
I became a professor when I was 30 years old.
I had a wife, a child, and seemed to be happy.
However, deep inside my heart,
I always felt lonely.
This feeling of loneliness grew more intense.
I am obviously a genius,
but every day I had to do the most ordinary things.
So when you were with my mother and me,
instead of feeling happy, you felt lonely.
Don't interrupt me!
I'm sorry. Please let me finish.
This feeling of loneliness suddenly made me realize
that this world is too boring and too flawed.
With my talent,
I could create my own world, a perfect world!
Before long, I found a man called Yan Mingliang.
He was very wealthy. He was not just a businessman,
but also an idealistic dreamer.
That's why he was so easily convinced
and decided to invest in my project.
I had a sense of purpose again.
It was a wonderful time.
It was simple, pure. All my dreams before my eyes.
Do you know?
The beauty of a dream is that if you work hard enough,
it will be yours indefinitely.
How did it go?
We made it.
We made it!
No.
It's not enough.
Everyone thought this system called "Future Microworld"
was already magnificent enough.
Yet in my heart I still felt
it was not my ideal world.
Something seemed to be missing.
It's like writing a play without a core,
or painting a dragon without eyes.
It had no soul.
After a long period of research and development,
we finally entered the testing phase.
Mingliang!
Mingliang! Yan Mingliang, wake up!
Wake up, Mingliang!
How could it be?
This is a virtual world.
How would he be in a coma?
Mingliang! Yan Mingliang. Mingliang!
President Yan! President Yan!
Call 120. (Ambulance)
No, wait.
President Yan.
Mingliang!
He's awake.
President Yan, are you okay?
I passed out in the system.
How could this happen?
It was the moment you fell into the water.
Due to the extreme shock,
you briefly lost consciousness
and went into a coma within the system.
That's quite a bug.
What should we do?
Have we been working all these years for nothing?
No, it worked.
It worked.
At that moment,
I knew the perfect world I had been waiting for all my life
was finally here,
so I quickly developed a completely updated design proposal,
"19th Floor."
♫  I go from running  ♫
♫  To flying  ♫
♫  Through setbacks and hardship  ♫
♫  So what?  ♫
♫  Oh ~ the light  ♫
♫  It shines on my face  ♫
♫  Unwilling to lose hope  ♫
♫  I only want to bloom  ♫
♫  One must, time and time again, leap over the giant waves  ♫
♫  Trek through the wilderness over and over again  ♫
♫  When a new day begins, hope is born anew  ♫
♫  Once again, set sail for the distant place in your heart  ♫
♫  The triumphant song will eventually soar through time and space  ♫
♫  The desire for freedom is strong and cannot be extinguished  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I'm following the direction of my dreams  ♫
♫  Hey, let's embrace future challenges and opportunities  ♫
♫  Find clarity amid uncertainty  ♫
♫  I rise against the wind  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I must soar even with broken wings  ♫
♫  Hey, witness fate triumph over darkness  ♫
♫  Forge a medal using thorns  ♫
♫  One must, time and time again, leap over the giant waves  ♫
♫  Trek through the wilderness over and over again  ♫
♫  When a new day begins, hope is born anew  ♫
♫  Once again, set sail for the distant place in your heart  ♫
♫  The triumphant song will eventually soar through time and space  ♫
♫  The desire for freedom is strong and cannot be extinguished  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I'm following the direction of my dreams  ♫
♫  Hey, let's embrace future challenges and opportunities  ♫
♫  I rise against the wind  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I must soar even with broken wings  ♫
♫  Hey, witness fate triumph over darkness  ♫
♫  Forge a medal using thorns  ♫