Chun Yu.
I'll meet you at your dorm tomorrow morning at eight.
No. I need to sleep until at least nine in the morning,
otherwise, I'll be tired all day.
Did you forget?
I know. I must go to the hospital at 8:30 for physical therapy.
How could I forget? I was just kidding.
Right, how could you forget such an important thing?
Gao Xuan?
You're finally back!
I'm sorry, may I ask who you are?
Senior Brother.
Don't you remember me at all?
I joined the game at World of Joy level.
What about my brother? The delivery guy.
You helped him.
I'll show you his photo.
Look! That's him.
Think about it.
Do you remember?
Actually, it was Uncle Chun who told me about the game.
Maybe my consciousness was damaged in the system,
resulting in the loss of all memories from that time.
I am sorry.
What about Qing You? She's been in the game from the start.
Did you forget her?
I am sorry.
It doesn't matter if you remember me or not,
but how could you forget Chun Yu?
She's done so much for you.
Qing You, well…
You can't say that. Right?
You two team up as experts.No one owes anything to anyone.
- But they were a couple…
- Qing You.
Well…
I must go to the hospital for physical therapy. Bawan, let's go.
- Isn't it at 1:30 in the afternoon?
- Let's go.
Qing You, we are going to be late for our class.
- Come on.
- Chun Yu.
We're late, it's time for class. Hurry up, let's go.
Hurry up, let's go.
Let's go.
Chun Yu, they said…
Let's go back.
Bawan wants to see me. I'm going downstairs.
My parcel is here. I'll go too.
Let's go together.
Chun Yu.
It's not Gao Xuan's fault that he lost his memory.
I shouldn't have said that about him.
It's okay. I know you're worried about me.
I am worried about you,
but I want to say,
you've always been the toughest, the strongest among us.
I saw what happened to you and Gao Xuan,
and I sincerely wish you both the best.
You can't just give up.
If you need any help, just tell us.
Chun Yu.
Got it, thank you.
So…
Just let things take their course.
I almost forgot the password.
Zero, four, one, nine.
I wonder how their conversation went.
I hope Chun Yu will be fine.
Chun Yu, are you going for a run?
Hello, Mom.
I'm still the same,
but you're all alone. No one takes care of you.
Are you taking care of yourself?
Of course.
Recently, life and studies have been going smoothly.
You don't need to worry.
Besides life and studies…
Right, you mentioned a special feeling in your heart. What is it?
Tell me about it.
What special feeling?
You mentioned it yourself on your last phone call.
Are you that careless when you talk to me on the phone?
Did you forget what you said.
Is that special feeling in your heart for a girl?
Chun Yu.
All right, I'll stop teasing you.
Look. Your face is all red.
Hope to hear some good news from you next time.
Okay, I have to go.
Hello. Is this Yang Bawan?
I am Gao Xuan.
Chun Yu interfered when Qing You was about to speak.
Can you tell me what it was that she didn't finish?
Did you decide?
Just give me a second.
Cannon five, advances four.
Knight three, advances five.
What should be my next step, brother?
As you wish.
My name is Chun Yu, what's yours?
My…
My name is Zhao Lei.
Be careful.
Come on.
Didn't I get on the school bus?
When?
Mr. Huang, is there any empty seat?
Did I have a car accident?
Sir, you recovered from the accident long ago,
but then you participated in a game called 19th Floor,
and fell into a coma again.
Then you came to our hospital.
A game?
19th Floor?
Yes.
Why can't I remember any of this?
Maybe the car accident caused a side effect.
You should go home and get some rest.
Sometimes the memories come back later.
Hi.
What did you put there?
Yang Bawan put it on me.
He said it could relieve brain overload.
What did you put on Gao Xuan?
This is all for you.
It's an ancient secret recipe my dad had someone find.
It can help to recover memory.
Gao Xuan, get up.
What's the matter?
This is just some trick.
It's useless. I'll remove it for you.
Okay.
I know I've lost important memories,
especially the experience I had with you guys in the game.
But the memories about you didn't start with the game.
Chun Yu.
I will always protect you as I did when I was a child.
Take a look.
What?
Bawan.
I heard you gave a folk remedy to Gao Xuan.
Don't mention it again.
If Chun Yu hears about it, she'll beat me up.
You deserve it.
You've been tormenting Gao Xuan.
I did it out of kindness.
It would be great if he regains his memory.
Think about it. He even forgot me, his best teammate.
I am so upset.
You are the worst teammate ever.
What's the big day today? Such a feast.
It's nothing Old Gao. Just a gathering.
Enjoy. If it's not enough, I'll add more.
Okay.
It'd be very nice if you'd invite us to a proper restaurant.
Old Lin?
Uncle Lin.
Uncle Lin, why didn't you tell us about your return?
Do we know each other?
We played 19th Floor together. Don't you remember it?
19th Floor?
Yes, I-I've heard about it from the doctor.
I did play after the car accident,
but then I fell into a coma again.
So I don't remember anything about that time.
Uncle Lin's primary consciousness at that time was my father's.
So…
Uncle Lin.
No matter what happens, we are still teammates.
We are the best of teammates.
Enjoy your food. I'll get back to work.
Go ahead.
Go ahead, eat.
Come on, let's eat.
Best of teammates?
Hello.
How's it going, buddies? Were you scared?
Well, sorry about that.
The three of us opened an escape room.
It officially opens Saturday at 1 p.m.
Hope you guys find the time to come to our escape room.
Please come, brother.
It's all the same, no difference.
Anyway, you should all be there.
- See you then.
- Don't forget to show up.
- Remember to come by.
Are you going?
What else can Brother Qiang do? I can just imagine it.
That's right, I don't believe it.
If he could create an escape room, I could fly airplanes.
Brother Qiang is so unreliable.
I want to call him Stupid Qiang.
Do you like Brother Qiang?
Is that right?
Why did you call him Stupid Qiang?
Don't talk nonsense, Bawan.
I almost forgot, my grandma's medical check-up this afternoon.
I have to go to the hospital now. You guys eat.
- I'll go with you.
- Okay.
Bye.
- We are leaving.
- Go.
Qing You.
Is Chun Yu okay about Gao Xuan losing his memory?
I think so.
It's a shame, though.
Wait.
I just had an idea.
Why is it so dark?
You are right. Brother Qiang's shop isn't working.
Maybe this game should be played in the dark.
Am I right?
Here's a candle and matches.
A candle and matches?
There is a candle.
A candle?
It's lit.
What's this?
Old Gao, come and see this. Is this a clue?
Go and take a look.
I'll go check.
What is this?
What is this thing?
T-This is… a shadow puppet.
A shadow puppet?
What a creepy shadow puppet.
It does look weird.
What are you doing?
Just speak up.
Wait, what is this?
What is this?
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
Do the game rules imply
that these lights can be used against these monsters?
Is that so?
That's right.
Is that right?
Well, look.
There's also a flashlight.
Hurry, Old Gao.
They are rising.
Well…
You're good.
You're pretty smart.
Did you remember anything?
Did you?
Is that right?
Did you remember anything?
Hurry up.
Did you?
I…
All right.
I know you mean well,
but…
Wait.
Are you three doing the right thing?
No, the shadow puppets…
The shadow puppets... I wasn't there.
I was there. You are different from the rehearsal.
- Let's go.
- We did nothing wrong.
Right?
Right. That's not how they rehearsed it.
What's not right?
They're quite cute.
Brother Qiang, your escape room has a long way to go.
There is still a lot of room for improvement.
First, you three need to improve your performance.
The movement design is too sloppy.
Exactly.
All right, go on.
If you keep talking this way, no one's getting lunch.
No, no, no, Brother Qiang.
Personally, I think your escape room is perfect.
I can hardly find any flaws.
You're absolutely right.
Our Mirror Escape Room is the best.
It truly stands above all other escape rooms nearby.
What did you say?
Brother Qiang, what is this?
Did you also prepare for a show?
I don't know them.
Why are they here?
We are from every other escape room in the area!
Do you want to beat us?
- Come on.
What do you want?
I've warned you already.
There are too many escape rooms,
so you shouldn't open another one.
Why didn't you listen?
Why should I listen to you?
Besides, everyone runs a shop with their own skills.
What's wrong with that?
He is right. Brother Qiang, I support you.
What are we waiting for, Brother Xiao Zhuang?
Let's do it!
I said not to use my real name.
Sorry, sorry.
Duke, let's do it.
Let's go.
Old Gao, what should we do?
What else? Let's go all out.
Let's go all out.
♫  Through setbacks and hardship  ♫
♫  So what?  ♫
Let's go all out.
♫  It shines on my face  ♫
Let's buy Uncle Chun some time.
No problem.
Divide and conquer.
Defeat them one by one.
Everyone. We insert the tags simultaneously. Let's see if it works.
- Yes!
No.
There must be a way for everyone to pass.
Follow me. Hurry!
Brother, what's your name?
Gao Xuan.
♫  One must, time and time again, leap over the giant waves  ♫
♫  The desire for freedom is strong and cannot be extinguished  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I'm following the direction of my dreams  ♫
Go!
♫  Find clarity amid uncertainty  ♫
♫  I rise against the wind  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I must soar even with broken wings  ♫
♫  Hey, witness fate triumph over darkness  ♫
♫  Forge a medal using thorns  ♫
Brother, you don't keep your word either.
Teamwork.
Qing You is not a weakling.
She is the strongest among us.
Student Xu, as your senior, let me give you a friendly reminder.
This can be very dangerous. Be careful.
Give me the tag.
♫  Through setbacks and hardship  ♫
I trust Old Gao.
I think old Gao did all that for a reason.
Brother Qiang. He…
♫  Hey, I'm following the direction of my dreams  ♫
♫  Hey, let's embrace future challenges and opportunities  ♫
♫  Find clarity amid uncertainty  ♫
♫  I rise against the wind  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
Gao Xuan.
Chun Yu.
♫  Hey, witness fate triumph over darkness  ♫
♫  Forge a medal using thorns  ♫
Recently, the city police solved a major criminal case.
The suspect, President Yan, founder of a large tech company,
exploited a system vulnerability in a VR game,
forcing many players to enter the game.
As a result, a lot of users fell into a coma upon failure.
After extensive investigation,
the police found all relevant evidence of President Yan's criminal group
and quickly carried out the arrest operation.
As of now, the game has been removed completely
and all VR headsets and related devices have been confiscated.
Final credits
♫  I go from running  ♫
♫  To flying  ♫
♫  Through setbacks and hardship  ♫
♫  So what?  ♫
♫  Oh ~ the light  ♫
♫  It shines on my face  ♫
♫  Unwilling to lose hope  ♫
♫  I only want to bloom  ♫
♫  One must, time and time again, leap over the giant waves  ♫
♫  Trek through the wilderness over and over again  ♫
♫  When a new day begins, hope is born anew  ♫
♫  Once again, set sail for the distant place in your heart  ♫
♫  The triumphant song will eventually soar through time and space  ♫
♫  The desire for freedom is strong and cannot be extinguished  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I'm following the direction of my dreams  ♫
♫  Hey, let's embrace future challenges and opportunities  ♫
♫  Find clarity amid uncertainty  ♫
♫  I rise against the wind  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I must soar even with broken wings  ♫
♫  Hey, witness fate triumph over darkness  ♫
♫  Forge a medal using thorns  ♫
♫  One must, time and time again, leap over the giant waves  ♫
♫  Trek through the wilderness over and over again  ♫
♫  When a new day begins, hope is born anew  ♫
♫  Once again, set sail for the distant place in your heart  ♫
♫  The triumphant song will eventually soar through time and space  ♫
♫  The desire for freedom is strong and cannot be extinguished  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I'm following the direction of my dreams  ♫
♫  Hey, let's embrace future challenges and opportunities  ♫
♫  Find clarity amid uncertainty  ♫
♫  I rise against the wind  ♫
♫  Embracing light's power  ♫
♫  Hey, I must soar even with broken wings  ♫
♫  Hey, witness fate triumph over darkness  ♫
♫  Forge a medal using thorns  ♫