Let me see clearly.
With a face this ugly…
PREVIOUS EPISODE
…you still dare to show up at the event?
Not afraid of scaring everyone?
Are you here to be an extra?
It's called a backup singer.
Did you really have to do this to me?
Disqualify Poona!
All contestants must show sportsmanship.
But if there's bullying like this,
I'll disqualify you.
Good. Disqualify her.
We shouldn't let this be an example.
Please calm down.
I think before we disqualify anyone,
we should investigate to be sure.
I'm a YouTuber.
Huh? A YouTuber?
How's that relevant? Don't listen to him!
I'm asking seriously. Miss Maria,
did you see with your own eyes
that Poona put the glass into the shoe?
I didn't see it.
But she handed me the shoes to wear.
You told Poona to pick it up, Maria.
If you didn't ask,
she wouldn't have picked it up.
Or is this your plan?
- Don't blame others!
- False accusations!
Miss Maria was bullied
and injured like this,
and now you're making false accusations.
- That's not right, Judge.
- Yes.
To accuse someone of wrongdoing,
there must be clear evidence.
If there's no evidence,
you can't make accusations.
The evidence is the wound, Mr. Sornrak.
That's right.
Poona definitely put the glass pieces
in my shoes.
Yes.
In this case,
Poona should be disqualified.
That's the right thing to do.
Alright.
This gentleman is a YouTuber.
He took footage behind the scenes.
Let's watch and see what the truth is.
Yes, I filmed the video.
Let me play it for you.
What?
I think it's time
for the competition.
If we watch this, we'll waste time.
- What do you think?
- Yeah.
That's right.
I think we should all get ready
for the competition.
Otherwise, we'll miss it.
I won't hold what happened against you.
It's just a waste of time
talking about me.
Don't you want to know who bullied you?
Forget it. I'm a good sport.
It's just a small thing.
So don't hold a grudge against Poona.
Poona.
I forgive you.
Mr. Sornrak.
Mr. Singha asked me
to take you to the front stage.
- It's time for the competition.
- Alright.
Since we're not holding grudges anymore,
let's move on and continue. Okay?
Let's not make this into a big deal.
It'll spoil the competition atmosphere.
Maria, are you still able to compete?
I'm fine now. It doesn't hurt anymore.
Great!
I can dance--
Oh, it still hurts a little though.
Please, don't post this on YouTube.
- Okay, no problem.
- Alright.
Please head outside.
Poona, let's get ready.
When's your turn?
- I'm number nine.
- We still have enough time.
Yes. Teacher, I'll be back in a minute.
Sure.
There!
He's over there!
Hey, follow him!
Hey. Hey, stop for a second!
What is it?
What did you film? Can I see it?
Why do you want to see it?
You're not getting disqualified anymore.
I want to know the truth. Who did it?
But Mr. Sornrak doesn't want it
to be a big deal.
I want to know. Please, let me see it.
If you want to see it…
you'll need to pay.
You're charging me just to see the video?
Isn't that greedy?
Not paying?
No pay, no view.
I thought you were a good person.
Turns out you're just a crook.
Hey.
You're not grateful,
and now you're accusing me.
This is defamation, you know?
Go wherever you want.
I don't want to see it anymore.
If I let her see it,
she'd probably yell at me.
I forgot to hit record.
I'm just a YouTuber on a mission anyway.
It's really him.
Wait. Who are you following?
Someone who's already dead.
I think you're seeing things.
How can a dead person be around here?
Where did he go?
Where is he?
There he is!
Hey. Stop!
Hey!
Stop!
Who the hell are you?
I'm Jan. Please, don't hurt me.
Is this the guy you've been looking for?
No, he's not.
This is one of Weerachai's men.
You!
Catch him.
Onanong!
Where are you?
Don't think you can escape from me.
‪Oh no!
Namthip. Phupha.
- Namthip.
- Don't!
Phupha!
Found you, Onanong.
Chart!
A love triangle between them
is making them fight.
Hey, finish it.
Phupha, it's over for you.
You destroyed my family.
You hurt the people I love.
You've made me go through a living hell.
One of us has to die, Chart!
DARATHONG COUNTRY MUSIC SINGING CONTEST
Riding on a motorbike in a short skirt
It's my business, not anyone else's
Talk all you want, you sharp tongue
Are you crazy or what?
It's the trend these days, darling
Mr. Singha, Boss Nok is here.
Keep an eye on him.
Yes, sir.
It makes my figure look fabulous
Curvy and just right
That's what charm looks like…
Make sure you film the whole song.
Wow, she's really stunning.
Her moves are heart-stopping.
I think she's a clear winner.
You're exaggerating.
Listen to the whole song first.
There are plenty
of other good contestants too.
I like her.
I want her. I'm picking her.
Hey, stop shaking me!
Go away. You're being annoying.
- Fine, I'll just watch quietly.
- Yeah.
When the lights hit her,
she shines so beautifully.
She truly deserves to be a famous singer.
What's her name again?
Her original name was Malee,
but I changed it myself.
Once she enters the industry,
she needs a name like Maria
to sound more international.
You boys sure do love to talk
I like my freedom
In two days, I'll wear it even shorter
I've got what it takes
That's why I dare to show it
Thank you.
And the song we just heard
was performed by Maria,
the beautiful young lady from Nern Samran.
Her performance is absolutely amazing.
It melted all of our hearts!
Maria, do you have anything
to say to the judges?
My dream has always been to be a singer
since I was a child.
I want to bring happiness to everyone.
Now, my dream
is in the hands of the judges.
And I hope all of you
will support me.
Thank you.
Let's give a round of applause
to support Maria!
She's charming, has a great voice,
and shows respect.
Judges, with all that,
she deserves a perfect score!
- Tu.
- Yes, Boss?
You see the singers in this contest?
They are pretty good.
Which one do you like, Boss?
Just invite them to join our music label.
It's not that hard.
Excuse me.
Are you a contestant?
What time do you perform,
and when exactly?
I need to know.
Oh, that's a nice handbag you have!
I'm not a contestant.
I'm Kamnan Pong's personal secretary.
I see. No wonder you look so stunning.
If you ever want to become a singer,
just let me know.
Okay, I'll excuse myself now.
Okay.
- Aren't you giving me your number?
- Tu!
You can't just flirt like that!
Do you want me to take a bullet
for Kamnan Pong?
She's his secretary!
Am I the one in the wrong?
Hey, do you know?
I've had Singha steal singers
from me before.
Today, I'm going to do the same.
Alright, next up.
Let's hear from our next contestant.
Please welcome
the multi-talented singer,
Poona, from Nern Samran!
Sir, the next contestant is Poona.
If you'd like me to do anything,
just let me know. I'll handle it.
Got it.
What are you thinking about?
- What?
- Why are you smiling?
‪Look at you.
- Manat, hold the camera for me.
- Where are you going? Bathroom?
Yeah, I'll be right back.
Take the mic too.
Alright, I got it. I'll film.
- That's great.
- Amazing.
- Hey, you.
- Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Hey, dull face!
Does saying sorry make it better?
If Boss Nok, my boss, got knocked down
like that and ended up crippled,
lying in bed, drooling, unable to move,
with his lower body paralyzed,
who's gonna be responsible?
Who's going to take care of me?
- Tu!
- Yes, Boss?
Are you worried about me,
or are you cursing me?
- You jerk!
- Both.
I've waited
Waited so long
My heart unwavering and full
But he's forgotten
Forgotten me, with no certainty at all
I wait for him
But he forgets I'm waiting
Waiting and pleading
With this lonely heart
Still waiting
I kept hoping until I grew weary
For that heartless one
Crying day and night
He forgot his promise
Leaving this sad country girl behind
Waiting for him
Waiting for him alone…
Dad, is something wrong?
Who picked the song for the singer?
- I did.
- Hey.
This song is what made
Onanong Wongwichian famous.
She's the ex-lover of Kamnan Pong.
Don't bring this song up again.
Yes, Dad.
A pile of dry firewood and withered straw
Melancholic, just like us…
I never thought
Poona would sing this song.
I was the one who recommended
this song to her.
I knew Kamnan Pong really liked it.
You must really love Kamnan Pong.
Yes.
Kamnan Pong
is the only man I've ever loved.
I kept hoping until I grew weary
Still waiting
For that heartless one
Crying day and night…
Her voice is really good.
What are they doing?
Why just let her sing?
How's the voice? Is it good?
- Her voice is amazing!
- I can't compete with that.
That's true.
Seeing dry leaves fall and wither
DARATHONG COUNTRY MUSIC SINGING CONTEST
It's me.
Here it is. This one has to be it.
Really?
With all these wires plugged in like that,
how could it not be?
There are wires everywhere.
How do we know which one is which?
Just follow me. I'll tell you which one.
Are you an electrician?
Were you ever an electrician?
I used to be an electrician's wife.
Is that enough?
I also know which wire to pull
to make Poona lose points.
In that case, pull it.
- Go on.
- Hey.
I'm a small woman, like a fire ant.
How am I supposed to pull it?
You do it. I'll tell you which wire.
Do you really know which one?
This one. Today's Monday,
so it's the yellow wire.
If it's Wednesday,
then it must be the green one.
There are two colors.
Just pull the yellow one.
Here, you pull it.
I'll keep an eye out.
Once I give the signal, you pull it.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
I'll wait.
Should I pull it?
- Hey.
- What?
- Pull it!
What happened?
Why did the lights go out?
Hey.
‪Joey, are you alright?
Joey!
We're still alive!
Poona!
Poona, sing live! Sing it!
With the power out,
how can the sound be good?
It has to be Maria.
Only she can be the singer tonight.
He's forgotten
Forgotten about us
Leaving me heartbroken
Waiting for so many years
Now he has a new lover
Hey.
Even without music,
Poona's voice still captivates everyone.
This is the voice with magic.
Deceiving, making me wait
JUDGE
Her voice is really good.
What's going on here?
What's happening to everyone?
Damn you, Poona.
‪A ghost!
I'm not a ghost.
I'm Sophie.
A ghoul!
It's not a ghoul. It's Joey.
What did you idiots do?
Why do you look like this?
Joey made the electricity shock us.
I didn't! The electricity
shocked us by itself.
Idiot! Useless!
You're the useless one!
Who says they're married
to an electrician?
Neither of you is any good!
Did you hear how loud the applause was?
Huh?
Poona!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm waiting for the scores
from our esteemed panel of judges.
In just a moment,
we'll know who will be the winner
and the new singer
for Darathong Music.
The score results will be in my hands
in just a moment. And now,
the results are in my hands.
Sathu.
Please, let Poona win. If she does,
I'll skip fermented fish for a month.
And the winner of today's singing contest…
DARATHONG MUSIC
She is the beautiful lady
from Nern Samran.
JUDGE
The winner is…
Poona, with the song
"Wait for Him to Forget".
My daughter sings way better than this,
with more lighting.
How can she win
without the lights, judges?
Maria only got second place.
Now, may I invite Kamnan Pong,
the president of Darathong Music,
and Mr. Sornrak Darathong
to present the award
and the bouquet of flowers to our winner?
Let's give them a round of applause!
- Hello. Congratulations!
- Thank you.
Hand me the trophy first.
Hand me the trophy. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Let's give her a round of applause!
- Hey, Tu. Tu!
- Yes?
I'm right here. What's up?
I want this one.
This one's awesome.
‪FIRST PRIZE 10,000 BAHT
Please welcome Mr. Sornrak
to present the bouquet of flowers.
Darathong Music is happy to welcome you.
Thank you.
Poona won! She won!
If that's the case,
everything's falling into place.
Poona will be the one
to help us reveal the truth.
In no time.
You're good too.
Let's take a picture over there. Go ahead.
Joey, you'll regret this
when we get back home.
How could you let a dark-lit singer
beat my daughter?
Geez.
Let's take plenty of photos.
Smile for the cameras.
Judges.
How could you let a dark-lit singer
win over one with the spotlight?
I'll sue! Sue! I'm hiring a lawyer!
Look at you, all puffed up!
Your Pincher Poona
won first place.
My Maria only got second.
Hey, Pincher Poona's not mine!
Don't say things like that.
You don't feel anything, do you?
- I don't.
- Well, fine.
Let's go. The event's over. Let's leave.
Good job, Pincher Poona!
First, let's go collect the prize money.
Let's go wait for Poona at the car.
Let's go, Teacher.
Hey, hold on.
Wait a minute, beautiful.
My name is Boss Tu. No, I'm just Tu.
My boss is Boss Nok.
He loves your voice so much.
Well…
He has a little something… Hey!
A small gift to give you… Hey!
Don't interrupt!
- From…
- Tu!
Yes, Boss.
- Please go ahead.
- Sweetheart.
In all my 35 years,
I've never seen anyone
as beautiful as you.
It's 65. You're 65.
Hey!
- She sang beautifully, Boss.
- What?
You said she's beautiful.
I've never heard anyone
sing as beautifully as you.
Like nectar.
Your voice is like nectar.
- Truly amazing.
- You mean my voice?
- No!
Not your voice, Uncle!
Enough!
Here, a little gift
from my heart.
Come closer. Blessings to you.
May your spirit be with you.
Just hanging the garland
gives me goosebumps.
I don't even want to imagine.
It's a lot.
I'll treat you to dinner today.
‪Let’s go.
What's going on, Chart?
I saw Phupha at the event, Boss.
Are you drunk or something?
I haven't had any alcohol.
No, this can't be.
The incident happened 20 years ago.
And the body was confirmed.
I'll bring Phupha here to show you.
It's impossible.
He can't come back from hell.
No way, Phupha.
Uncle, I won!
Wow!
You did it! I'm so proud of you.
I'm going to be a singer now.
My dream is finally coming true!
Just a little more, dear.
You'll be an artist with your own songs.
Aunt Wilai, did you hear me sing
when the lights went out?
Yes! When Poona sang live,
everyone was speechless!
- Really?
- I heard it.
Your live voice,
anyone who hears it will fall in love.
You're really talented.
Let's walk a bit further.
I think he hasn't gone anywhere yet.
Even if he's a ghost,
I'll kill him again. Phupha.
It seems like he's looking for someone.
They look suspicious.
Let's follow them.
But after you join Darathong Music,
you have to be very careful.
And don't forget the promise we made.
Yes, I'll make sure
to bring that teddy bear out.
I'll help you reveal the truth.
Poona.
Whatever you do, your safety comes first.
If anything happens to you,
I won't be able to live on.
Don't worry, Uncle.
I'll make sure I'll be fine.
Let's not worry about revenge for now.
Let's celebrate
that Poona's going to be a singer!
Poona! Poona!
- Poona!
Everyone, get down!
- They're shooting!
- Let's go!
Don't go! It's too dangerous.
Don't worry. I'll lead them that way.
Please take care of Poona.
But it's too dangerous.
I promise, I'll be fine.
Hey, follow him!
Don't be afraid, dear. Mom's right here.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Poona!
Help Uncle Tharin! They're chasing him
and shooting in that direction!
- Take care of Poona.
- Be careful.
I think you two should leave this place.
But Uncle…
It's okay. Chaiya's gone after him.
They'll handle it.
Please, do what he says. If we stay here,
you might be in danger.
Come out!
I told you to come out!
Who the hell are you?
- This is bad.
- Over here, Captain.
Let's go.
There he is! He's here!
Let's go! Get in the car!
Hurry, dear!
Go straight home, no stops.
I'll go help Chaiya.
Thanks so much.
- Let's go, everyone.
- Yes.
Hey, stop! Stop right now!
Chart!
- What?
- Don't shoot. That's the police!
We should run.
- Let's go!
- Hurry, Chaiya!
They've already run away.
Don't worry, Captain.
I've got a contact. I'll have them follow.
Hello? What's up, Uncle Sergeant?
- Au, where are you?
- I'm guarding the van of Chart's guys.
Good. They're heading that way.
Follow them.
Got it, Uncle. I'll handle it!
Get in the car!
Run!
Hurry!
Go ahead if you can get away. Come on.
Wait, who's that? Who's covering my head?
Ugh, wrong side of the helmet!
Follow them, Sergeant.
This warehouse looks suspicious.
There could be something
we're looking for inside.
Yes, Mr. Kitti?
This is the moment. Let's go!
What's going on, Chart?
Who were you shooting at?
It was Phupha. I followed him.
But someone came to help him,
so I shot at them.
The police arrived just in time.
Are you sure it was Phupha?
I'm sure. His appearance, everything.
I think it has to be him.
We'll catch him first,
then we'll deal with it.
Chart,
he just confirmed it's really Phupha.
It's been almost 20 years.
How could he have survived?
Unbelievable.
Or is it Tharin, his twin brother?
But if Phupha really survived,
I'll send him back to hell myself.
They won't be free for long.
Excuse me, Captain.
Just got back, Sergeant?
Don't even ask, Captain.
I've been guarding the warehouse
all night. I'm so tired!
Any progress?
Uncle Sergeant and Captain Tom
found a chemical storage
hidden in the warehouse.
Right now, Captain Tom
is working on getting a search warrant.
I'll go see Uncle Sergeant.
You're leaving me again, Captain.
Dad!
Dad, I won't allow it.
Poona can't be a singer before me!
Right.
Do whatever it takes
for me to be a singer before her.
- True.
- Otherwise, I'll run away from home!
I'm coming with you.
Juab, can I stay at your house?
Of course! No problem at all.
No, you can't!
How can you stay with him?
Do you know what kind of person he is?
No way, you know?
Hey, Joey!
Hand me my love.
Your lover?
Gun!
Hurry up!
What's taking so long?
Geez.
Wait!
Are you really going to shoot?
I'm not involved in this!
How can you not be involved?
You've been charming
my daughter, haven't you?
I haven't! I'm not charming anyone.
Don't accuse me of that.
By the way, is my coffee ready?
I'm in a hurry today.
In a hurry? Why didn't
you come yesterday then?
What?
I'm angry now! No more coffee for you.
No coffee? What does that
have to do with me?
If you're not selling coffee today,
I don't want it.
I'll come back another time.
Dad!
Do you understand?
I can't lose to that Poona!
- Right.
- She already won.
What do you want me to do?
It's you, Village Head.
You had us do something stupid.
Look what happened.
Poona definitely got sympathy votes.
What did I have you do?
You told us to unplug the power
when she was singing!
Yes, that day, you told us
to unplug the power,
and we got shocked! That day!
So, you're saying it was my fault?
Yes, it's your fault, Dad!
Do whatever it takes for me
to be a singer before Poona.
Or I'll run away from home
and never come back!
I'm coming with you!
Her mother's blood runs deep!
It really runs deep!
I think, since she won,
it means she must have cheated.
- Yes.
- How did she cheat?
She might have used dark magic
on the judges.
Exactly.
Dark magic? Are you crazy?
It's because you two
turned off the lights.
Instead of her dying,
she came back stronger.
Everyone's enchanted by her voice.
Think before you act!
Was it harsh? Yes, it was.
But I don't mind,
because it's all your father's idea.
If you're going to blame someone,
blame your father.
Sophie! Are you saying my father
has no brains?
Yes.
Honestly, he probably doesn't have any.
Sophie!
I'm not involved.
Both of you!
NEXT EPISODE
Is this jar of fermented fish ruined too?
Are you really giving it to me?
I want to be famous
Can’t stand it anymore
I want people
To scream for me at the stage
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn