Then let me do it.
I'll steal the teddy bear.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
I don't want you putting yourself
at risk like that.
I can't stand seeing my father
being humiliated like this either, Uncle.
If we're doing this,
the first thing she has to do
is apply for the singing competition
at Darathong Music.
Alright, Village Head,
since we're old friends,
- Yes
- Maria doesn't need to go audition
or do a voice test in the other room.
Why did you come and fool me
Leaving me confused?
Teacher,
isn't that Maria's voice?
I can't believe
that the kind-hearted Kamnan Pong
knows people who deal drugs.
I don't want to jump
to conclusions just yet.
These things, you have
to watch unfold over time.
Hello, everyone!
Today is Kamnan Pong's birthday.
Feel free to pick up your donations here.
Free stuff!
What's available here?
FREE FOOD AND DRINKS
FOR PEOPLE OF KHOK TA YU
Why aren't you in line?
Oh no!
Who's trying to kill me?
Is it you?!
You too, huh? You!
Thanks, you two. What are your names?
- I'm Chaiya.
- I'm Manat, Sergeant Yot's nephew.
- Sergeant Yot's nephew?
- Yes.
So, are you two police officers?
No, we're YouTubers from Bangkok.
Actually, we're between jobs right now.
We came here to travel
and maybe make some content
that could be useful for society.
YouTube? Good.
If there's anything you need, let me know.
I'm happy to help.
- Don't hesitate.
- Thank you.
Hey, stop!
This is the police.
I need to search you.
Turn off the engine now! Get off the bike.
Quick!
- Come here.
- What's going on, Sergeant?
We got a report
that you guys are in possession of drugs.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm just telling you the truth.
Now, let me search you. Slowly.
This way.
Think you're tough, huh?
Boss, there's trouble.
Hey, Chaiya!
CHECKPOINT
If you hurt my uncle, you'll regret it!
Uncle, are you okay?
I'm fine. Follow them!
Quick! Go, now!
You hurt my man, you're dead!
Take this!
Well? Come on.
Let's go.
Thanks a lot, Chaiya. Manat.
I'll see you at home. Come here.
From now on
I'll stop being obsessed with you
DARATHONG MUSIC
Maria!
I'm nervous!
This is my daughter, Boss.
She's got potential.
She has the right look too.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll put Maria's name
through to the final stage.
She'll skip the preliminaries.
Wow!
- Thank you, Boss.
- We're friends.
Hey, are you here
for the singing competition?
Yeah, I'm about to leave.
Oh my gosh, Poona.
Did your uncle
let you enter the competition?
Yes, he gave me permission.
Did you know, Poona,
that Miss Maria sang for the boss,
just for him, privately?
Yeah, someone of Miss Maria's level,
when applying for the competition,
needs a special audience, you know.
Bet you're shocked!
I hope you make it through the rounds.
- Nice words!
- Correct.
I'm already in.
The boss has me set to win first place.
- She'll win!
- She'll get the prize.
Just wait until the real competition,
I'll beat you for sure.
- You're so good!
- Really good!
Has the label already rigged the results?
I thought it was about talent.
Guess no talent means
you just play the connections game.
Watch your mouth! This is Darathong Music.
- A major label.
- Right.
Not your petty little band!
- You can't talk like that here.
- Exactly.
- I'm just saying what I heard.
- Alright, enough.
Let's not waste time arguing.
We'll settle this on stage.
See you, Maria.
Yeah, you'll definitely see me.
Wait, I thought Wilai
was supposed to meet us here.
Why hasn't she shown up yet?
I'll go buy coffee in the meantime.
- Okay. I'll call her myself.
- Alright.
I'll have an iced coffee, please.
Here you go. Thank you.
- So good!
- I'll find something to eat--
Oh no.
- I'm so sorry!
- What's this? My shirt!
- You!
Hang on! Let's go to the police station.
Huh? Just spilled coffee
and you're taking me to the cops?
Don't pretend you don't know.
You know exactly what you did.
You ran away from me that night.
What are you talking about?
- Let go of me!
- No, come with me!
Hey, let go!
Take it! Throw it away!
I can't even drink it now.
Don't run away! Let me catch you first!
Geez!
Oops!
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
What should I do? He's coming!
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Where is she?
Hey! What are you doing in here?
I'm looking for someone.
Come to steal something?
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
Ugh.
Hey, stop!
Hey!
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Phew.
Hey.
Hey, stop!
Hey!
You didn't call me for all the fun, huh?
Stop! Stop right now!
What's going on here?
This guy broke into the factory.
He's here to steal something!
You're mistaken. I'm not here to steal,
just looking for someone.
Looking for who?
Is this the one?
Yeah, that's her.
Let go of me!
I haven't done anything wrong!
Hey, what's the deal
with you and these guys?
It's this guy.
He's a pervert, harassing women.
He grabbed my hand out of nowhere,
so I ran away.
Well then, I'll take them to the station.
Stop! This is my nephew! My nephew!
Hey, Sergeant.
Do you know these two guys?
Yeah, they're my nephews.
Don't arrest them.
It's just a misunderstanding.
But during the Agriculture Fair,
they were chasing me.
It was the same just now.
How is this a misunderstanding, Sergeant?
Well, I thought you and your friend…
Her name's Maria.
Yeah, I thought you and Maria
planted the bombs at the Agriculture Fair.
I'm just trying to be a good citizen
and turn you in.
Yeah, that's right.
Hey, Maria was caught
in the explosion too.
Sornrak Darathong
had to step in and help her.
How could she be involved
in planting bombs?
You're way off on this.
Exactly, and I was caught
in the explosion that night too.
If I were involved with the bombers,
I must be pretty stupid
to run right into the same explosion.
Alright, I get it now. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Now that we've apologized,
let's leave it at that.
No more trouble, alright?
Okay.
Thanks so much for clearing things up.
As for you,
next time,
don't come anywhere near me.
Poona, over here!
- Hello, Aunt Wilai.
- Hello.
Sorry, I had a little issue
with an idiot earlier.
But it's all cleared up now.
So, you signed up to sing, right?
Yes.
They had me sing live
in front of the judges.
But they'll post the shortlist
on their website.
- Alright.
- Wilai, look over there.
See that?
What's going on, Sergeant?
These two young guys here
caused some trouble,
so I had to give them a little talk.
Hello, Kamnan Pong. Do you remember me?
- I remember you.
- This is my nephew, Kamnan.
- Which one is your nephew?
- That's me.
I'm Sergeant Yot's nephew.
I've been free lately,
so I thought I'd come visit him.
We're both unemployed right now.
If there's any work at this factory,
we're happy to take it.
Sorry.
This factory is part
of the community product group
that I built to help people in the village
earn a living.
Only people from this village
are allowed to work here.
I see. No problem.
Ever since the incident 20 years ago,
Kamnan Pong hasn't been as cheerful
as he used to be.
He stopped managing
the music label he used to run
and let Singha take over.
He then focused
on running an agro-processing factory
to help the villagers.
Helping the villagers, huh?
More like covering up
for his drug dealing business.
Well, everyone knows
Kamnan Pong hates drugs.
He's helped the government
in the fight against drugs
and won an award
for being an outstanding leader.
Hates drugs,
but keeps drug dealers as his employees?
Believe whatever you want.
I don't buy it.
I believe what my own eyes have seen.
I saw with my own eyes,
heard with my own ears,
that Kamnan Pong ordered Phupha's murder.
And when I found out,
he ordered my death too.
Then why didn't you report it
to the police, Aunt Wilai?
If I wanted to film content inside,
would that be possible?
How about this? We'll sit down another day
and discuss the details
of what we'll be filming.
Sounds good.
Sergeant Biew and I
will take our leave now.
I can't. The police are all on their side.
As long as we don't have evidence,
there's nothing we can do about them.
Well then, my nephew and I
will take our leave.
- Go ahead.
- Goodbye.
- See you.
I just hope we get the teddy bear soon.
I'll use the evidence
to expose everything online.
I'll show everyone the truth.
I want everyone to know
what Kamnan Pong is really like.
Let's go. I don't want
to stay here any longer.
Wait!
Next time,
don't come anywhere near me.
Hey, buddy.
Huh?
Thinking about a girl?
What girl? I'm working!
Yeah, working, huh?
Here.
You can't lie to me.
Who do you think I am?
I'm Lieutenant Manat,
the love expert
from the Central Investigation Division.
Your eyes give you away.
Who are you thinking about?
Do I know her?
Or is it…
- Ms. Paula?
- Are you crazy?
It's not her.
Or maybe…
the local angel from around here?
- Hey, hey.
- Stop! Enough. No more guessing.
Go. Just go wherever.
Do you have work to do? Go ahead.
Go.
Kamnan Pong.
I think you should stop watching it.
I don't want you to get stuck in the past.
Kamnan, a woman like that
isn't worth you thinking about.
Let me find you someone new.
It'll be better for you.
I shouldn't be thinking
about any new love.
Actually, I have
the factory accounts for you to review
and a check for you to sign.
Put it down there.
I've come to invite you
to chair our label's singing contest.
- When?
- Next week.
I'm sure that at Darathong Music,
they're hiding some important secret
we never expected.
- What's up, Sergeant Au?
- Captain.
- They're having a party tonight.
- Where?
I'll follow them.
They're heading toward the foothills,
near Khok Ta Yu village.
As soon as I get a confirmed location,
I'll let you know.
Okay.
What's going on?
Sergeant Au invited us to a party.
It's near the foothills of Khok Ta Yoo.
Let's go, buddy! I've been itching
for something like this!
Let's go.
Hey!
Get out!
Sorry, guys.
What's this about?
No one's allowed through here. Got it?
Oh, I don't get it.
Why do you look like a cop?
Yeah, you're right.
I was thinking the same thing.
And if I look like a cop,
then you two
look like robbers.
Oops! Force of habit!
Is this the place Sergeant Au
mentioned we need to walk to?
Yeah.
If we drive in, they might notice us.
Then wait a sec.
Take this with you.
Sergeant Au said
Deputy Phuchong just sent it.
You little bastard.
Got something good and didn't share?
I'll smack you!
Take it easy. I just saw it with you.
You want a taste?
Here, this is yours.
Take it.
Thank you, Deputy Phuchong,
for always looking out for us.
Ready, Manat?
- Been ready for a while, buddy.
- Then…
let's go.
- Everything good to go?
- It's all set.
How's it going, Sergeant?
There's probably drugs in the car.
But why are they still staying quiet?
That guy must be their leader.
It looks like
they're waiting for something.
Waiting to go to jail.
I think you're right.
Hello, Boss Ah.
You're right on time.
Of course.
But isn't the boss here today?
He's not. He's caught up with something.
That's too bad.
I was hoping to meet him today.
I'll check the goods first.
No problem. Go ahead.
- How's it going?
- The goods are great.
This batch is excellent.
I should thank you
for trusting us, Boss Ah.
If it goes like this,
it will help my boss's products
get more recognition in the market.
Let your boss know
that I'll find a chance to visit.
Sure, I'll let him know.
I'm starting to want to see their boss.
Here's the full cash amount.
Check it.
The money's all here.
- Everything's good.
- Good.
You can take the goods now.
Hey, load it onto the truck.
Put the money away.
- Take care, Boss Ah.
- See you.
Hey, Captain!
Are we gonna let this slide?
Not yet. It's not over.
Sorry, Boss Ah. I didn't
get the chance to say goodbye.
Go to hell.
Let's go.
Who's that?
I'm asking, who's that?
Take them down!
Whoever kills them gets the reward!
Uncle Sergeant.
That Chart guy, he's the right-hand man
of Kitti and Singha.
He's known them since they were young.
He's been around for so long.
This means Chart
must know everything inside and out.
It's possible
that he's involved
in the Phupha and Onanong case too.
Then I'll leave.
I don't want to be seen. I'm out.
Come on!
I was going to take him in
for questioning.
Too late for that, Lieutenant.
Let's get out of here
before the local cops arrive.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
DARATHONG MUSIC
I need a sip of warm water, Teacher.
I'm so nervous right now.
You've been through
so many singing competitions already.
Why are you nervous now?
But this is the stage
that could shape my future as a singer.
Look at me, Teacher!
I'm so nervous, I'm getting goosebumps.
I wish Aunt Wilai were here.
I'd feel a bit more at ease.
If she came, people would recognize her.
You've got me here.
Doesn't that make you feel better?
It does.
Hey.
The boss told us to set up checkpoints.
Search everyone going in and out.
Don't let any of Boss Noo's people
sneak into the event.
Understood. Leave it to me.
Tod, Wong.
- Set up the checkpoints.
- Got it.
CHECKPOINT
Keep a close eye on Pleaw.
He's a slippery one.
If you see him
lurking around the competition,
get rid of him.
I remember all his men's faces.
No need to worry.
There he is.
If Chart showed up in person,
that means all the VIPs
are definitely here.
VIPs? More like gang bosses.
Sergeant Au, call Sergeant Yot.
Tell him there might be a clash tonight.
Roger that.
Yes, Boss.
They've set up checkpoints
to screen everyone coming in.
I'll make sure their event
falls apart tonight.
Captain, I've already reported
to Sergeant Yot.
The police unit is standing by and ready.
Pleaw, who's that?
Look, that's Chart!
Chart.
- That bastard.
- Stop!
What are you doing?
Chart. He killed Tha--
He killed Phupha.
- I'll kill him!
- Stop!
Poona is about to go on stage today.
If we cause trouble now,
everything will be over.
And if both of us end up dead,
who's going to expose them?
Come on.
We've been holding on
for 20 years already.
Just a little longer.
Don't let this blow up now.
I get it.
- I'll turn the car around.
- No need to turn back.
I'm sure he doesn't recognize you now.
You drive up to him.
I'll get out here.
We'll meet inside.
Roll the window down.
- Where are you going?
- To the contest.
Chit, what's going on?
Why are you covering your face?
Take it off.
I said, take it off!
What happened to your face?
My house burned down.
I couldn't get out in time.
Let me see clearly.
Hey, what is he doing?
With a face that ugly…
you still dare to show up at the event?
Not afraid of scaring everyone?
Those bastards, picking on a woman.
Wait, look at that.
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
Nothing, sir.
Have you all lost your minds?
Can't you see the traffic's backed up?
Stop messing around.
Move it!
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
Move. Go on, hurry up!
Go on!
Move it! Open it up.
Sergeant Au.
Keep an eye on those lackeys.
Let's go, Manat.
You go check the left side.
I'll take this side.
Then we'll meet inside.
Got it.
You bastard!
I remember you.
- We meet again.
- I'm ending this right here.
Boss, gunshots!
Let's go.
- You're dead!
- Take cover!
Hey, let's go!
Let's go.
Oh.
Oops.
Poona, we meet again.
Are you here to be an extra?
They don't call it an extra anymore.
It's called a backup singer.
That's right. Miss Maria's
definitely going to win this.
You might as well get ready to accept it.
If it's about outfits,
you win by a mile.
Of course.
I'll give you that.
But wait, isn't this
a singing competition?
Not a backup dancer contest.
- Ouch!
- That's harsh.
Are you saying my outfit
looks like a backup dancer?
Hey, watch your mouth!
If Miss Maria wasn't about to win,
I'd have slapped you already.
Go ahead, hit me.
I'll hit back. Fair game.
Just so you know,
singers are judged by their voice,
not their clothes.
Outfits,
performing, and dancing,
they're just extras.
Someone with an amazing voice
might not be able to dress or dance
and still win competitions.
Are you really a music teacher
or a professional insult machine?
That mouth cuts.
Let's go warm up over there.
No point wasting time here.
- Camera ready?
- Ready.
Go for it.
Tonight, we're YouTubers.
Hey.
Target locked,
and you're not stopping, huh?
- Hey.
- Look.
There's plenty of pretty faces over there.
- Hey.
- Go on, film that side.
We gotta commit to the role properly.
Go on. Get going.
Handle that side. I'll take care of this.
Go.
DARATHONG COUNTRY MUSIC SINGING CONTEST
- What are you filming?
- Is something wrong?
You are not allowed to film
without permission.
We're YouTubers.
We saw this big competition
and wanted to livestream to promote it.
Did you get permission from the organizer?
I don't know
where we were supposed to ask.
If you don't know, then don't film.
No manners at all.
You country fools.
Are we really fighting?
- Ugh!
- Stop it! Stop!
That's enough. Stop!
Chang.
What's going on?
These guys, Boss.
They were filming something
without permission.
We're YouTubers.
They're YouTubers.
If they want to film, let them film.
Film wherever you want.
Even backstage is fine. I allow it.
Make sure you help promote
our Darathong Music too.
- Yes.
Feel free.
That's enough.
Poona.
Can you pass me my heels?
That pair there, near you.
- They look great.
- Thanks.
So beautiful.
- Ouch!
- Miss Maria, what's wrong?
Something cut my foot!
Oh no! Blood!
Do we call an ambulance? Oh my God!
There's so much blood!
Where's the tissue?
Tissue! Tissue!
Oh my God, blood!
That's a lot of blood!
Poona.
Did you really have to do this to me?
What?
You're so desperate to win
that you'd use dirty tricks?
Wait, I didn't do anything, Maria.
If I hadn't moved my foot in time,
I would've lost my toe.
I couldn't compete.
Huh?
Why are you being so cruel to me?
Exactly! Why are you being so cruel?
Have you forgotten our friendship?
I swear I didn't do it.
I want to win,
but I wouldn't do anything like that.
There! Everyone heard it!
She just said she wants to win.
That's your true intention!
You did this because you want to win.
You'll do anything.
Am I right, everyone? She's the worst!
She should be disqualified.
We don't accept
this kind of dirty play.
Yeah, she looks good,
but how can her heart be so ugly?
I can't believe it.
- Disqualify Poona!
Disqualify Poona!
Poona, are you going to step out
of the competition yet?
So we don't waste everyone's time, right?
Poona hasn't even competed yet.
You can't disqualify her like this.
Hey, you two, go guard the checkpoint.
Wong and I will go check things inside.
Got it, Chart.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
He's still alive?
- Wong, come with me!
- Hey!
Here, Judge. This contestant is a bully.
Judge, Miss Maria was bullied.
We caught her red-handed.
The person who bullied her
is this woman.
Is this true?
It's not true. I didn't do anything.
I don't know what's going on.
Who would admit
to something like that so easily?
- Exactly.
- If there's no solid evidence,
- no one's going to admit to it, right?
- That's true.
According to the competition rules,
all contestants must show sportsmanship.
If there's bullying like this,
I'll disqualify you.
Disqualify Poona! Disqualify Poona!
Honestly, it's so annoying
Her moves are heart-stopping.
I think she's a clear winner.
This song is what made
Onanong Wongwichian famous.
She's the ex-lover of Kamnan Pong.
- Damn it!
- Don't go!
It's too dangerous.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn