Get revenge on Boss Noo.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
-Puna?
-Hurry up!
Hey, Chaiya!
Stay hidden here. Don't go anywhere.
I'll be back.
I saw Boss Noo around here.
-Are you okay, Boss?
-I'm fine!
If the police hadn't arrived in time,
I'd have been the shooter.
Don't worry about the message
you sent to Corporal Chom.
He won't be able to trace us.
The number I'm using is encrypted by HQ,
so it can't be traced back to us.
Puna.
Who exactly are you guys?
Well, I'm Chaiya.
And I'm Manat. We still need
to get the clothes from the office.
I heard everything you guys said.
Alright.
I'll tell you the truth.
Go on.
I used to be a food delivery rider.
In high school,
I was also a boxer.
That's right. I met Chaiya
at the boxing gym.
Then we started making YouTube videos.
We're actually police.
Don't worry.
Sergeant Au is on our side.
We work together.
Yes.
The three of us
were sent to investigate
a drug case in Ban Khok Ta Yu.
How does that relate
to Singha's Darathong Music?
We found clues
that the label's executives
are involved in drug trafficking.
That's why we had to go undercover
and work at the company.
Maybe…
the reason my father and mother died
is connected to this too.
The car accident case
with Phupha Thararin
falling off the cliff?
You know about this too?
Of course. We're police.
We have to check everyone's backgrounds.
I have something to tell you too.
The reason I applied
to be a singer at this label
is because I want to investigate
my parents' case as well.
Puna, we need to hurry back
and get the clothes.
Well, then.
You can tell us the details on the way.
Maybe we can help investigate as well.
Thanks.
Ahem.
Excuse me.
Will this take long?
The gas is running out.
-Please get in.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-Well…
If you want to chat,
we can do it in the car.
Wow, even prepared for that.
DARATHONG MUSIC
Then,
the proof that will clear
your parents' names
is in that teddy bear?
Yes.
Right now, that teddy bear
is in Singha's office,
but the opportunity hasn't come yet.
My mission isn't finished.
That's okay.
Manat and I will help.
If we get that evidence,
it'll help all of us too.
Thanks so much.
I promise I'll keep this a secret.
I won't tell anyone.
Thank you, Miss Puna.
This is life-or-death stuff.
If anyone else finds out, we're done for.
Thanks, Sergeant Au.
Yes, Captain.
Let's go. We should hurry
into the company.
SONRAK DARATHONG
Chaiya.
Yes, Mr. Kitti.
Follow me.
So today's plan failed.
The police got in the way.
Yes, Mr. Singha.
Chart called and reported
the same thing to me.
What about Boss Noo?
He's still alive, right?
Yes.
His men got him out in time.
The police shot him,
leaving him dragging his leg.
Boss Noo is in trouble now.
If we're dealing with him,
we have to act fast.
Or he'll come back for revenge.
Got it.
I'll check that Khod guy's family.
Let's go. The outfit's ready.
Got everything?
I've got the accessories too.
Nothing's missing.
Puna.
I found that teddy bear.
In Mr. Singha's office, right?
Yes.
Don't worry. I'll figure out
a way to help you.
I have to go.
Teacher Mueangphrai is calling.
Okay, see you later.
Yes, Teacher. I'm on my way.
DARATHONG MUSIC
Looks like something
really is hidden inside.
You've got an urgent schedule today.
You know that?
Yes, Dad. It's a product review, right?
Yes, the new products just came in.
Get them done quickly.
Have the products arrived?
Yes. Why, you haven't got them?
Not yet, Dad. Where are the products?
I saw it just now.
Yes, Dad.
Hey, Khod. Your wife came to visit.
Khod.
Nok, how did you get here?
-He brought me.
-Who?
It's me.
Too bad your kid
had to go to school today.
-What?
-Otherwise I'd have brought him too.
Don't do anything to my family! I beg you!
Don't worry. I won't hurt you.
As long as you behave.
What do you want me to do?
Just go back to Boss Noo
and send me the information
I need. That's all.
Easy.
Khod, do what he says.
He even sent someone
to watch our kid at school.
Uh…
Okay, I'll do it.
Whatever you want, I'll do it.
Oh, I'm so excited for you!
Step down, yeah.
We're almost there!
-Oops!
Hey.
What's this surprise?
Why do I have to be blindfolded?
Alright, we're here.
One, two, three!
-Ta-da!
Whose car is this, Dad?
It's your car, my daughter.
Mine? Really mine?
Whoa!
You're already a singer on TV.
Riding a motorbike
in the sun and wind?
You deserve a brand-new car
to match your status
as a singer, my daughter.
Yay!
-Aw.
-I'm no ordinary dad.
Thank you so much, Dad!
You're the best!
I'm no ordinary dad.
-The keys are with me.
-Alright.
Hand them over!
Here it is.
-Here.
-Give them to her.
This is your car.
Wow.
-Yippee!
-I've got the keys!
Post it! We have to show it to the world!
Quick, Joey, take the shot!
Good idea!
Go ahead. Strike a pose!
-Strike a pose!
-Pose now?
-Alright, good. One…
-Make it look nice!
-So beautiful!
-Okay, I'm taking it.
-Yay.
-Okay.
Puna, did you know?
Maria just got a brand-new car.
Great.
Just her first song,
and she can already afford a car.
Maybe Village Head Prueng
bought it for her.
He's ridiculously rich.
But
she really shouldn't post it
for everyone to see.
Forget it, Teacher.
That's their business.
Let's focus on our work.
DARATHONG MUSIC
Another box here!
Is it heavy, Ice?
Not at all!
These boxes are from fans
sending gifts to the artists.
The plushies
are for Mr. Sonrak and Maria.
There's a lot.
Looks like this ship couple trend
is really popular!
Is that all of them?
There's still a lot in the warehouse.
The team is bringing them in.
Enough already.
We can't even sort all of them.
Just a little more, Teacher.
-Can you help me carry them?
-Okay, let's go.
Puna.
I just went into Singha's office.
You got the bear, right?
Not yet.
But I squeezed it and shook it a bit.
There has to be something inside.
Just hang on. I'll try another way.
And what are you doing here?
These are fan gifts for the artists.
We were instructed to donate them.
Donate to whom?
Kamnan Pong is giving them
to the kids and villagers.
But we have to sort them first,
then send some to the laundry
because some are old and dusty.
Alright, I'll help.
When you become a singer someday,
I'll be your first fan,
buying a plushie for you.
That's up to you.
Someone like you
actually buys plushies for people?
Not really.
But I'll buy it sincerely.
We'll see.
Chaiya, go prepare the car for me.
I've got a product review
this afternoon. Let's go.
Yes.
Miss Maria! Hurry, hit the brakes!
Brake!
Don't scream! You're scaring me.
We're more scared! Be careful!
Ah!
Miss Maria, take it slow.
A brand-new car?
Miss Maria.
Should I get out and guide you?
I'll get out too then.
No need!
We'll stay in the car.
If we crash, we crash together.
-If we die, we die together.
-Ah!
Oh no!
What did you hit?
What is it?
Go check!
Mr. Assistant!
-Oh!
-Hey!
Miss Maria ran over someone! Police!
Why are you calling the police?
Call an ambulance!
Who do I call? Ambulance or police?
My legs are shaking.
Whoa, I'm about to pass out!
-Joey!
-Oh no!
Hey, Manat! Hey!
Don't pass out on me.
Manat , I'm sorry! Are you okay?
Hey, stay with me. Wake up!
Tell the people at home for me…
Tell them what?
Tell Mom…
Tell what?
Tell her what?
That I like you, Maria.
A dying person
always tells the truth.
-You idiot!
-Ouch!
That hurts, you know.
-Are you messing with me?
-Hey!
Don't!
Wait, you weren't actually run over?
Today it's the cone,
next time, it could be something else.
If you can't reverse, call me.
Don't interfere. Stay away!
Got it.
I'm easygoing.
Anyone who becomes my girlfriend
will be very lucky.
Very lucky?
-But today, let's make it bloody first!
-Hey!
Take that!
Stop smiling at me!
Miss Maria, why are you smiling?
Hey!
Wake up!
You're overdoing it.
Puna.
Hand it over. I'll help.
Thanks.
Put them in the van?
Yes. The van will take them
to the laundry.
This company is really kind.
Yeah.
Taking fan gifts
and giving them to the kids like this
is really admirable.
But the important part
is washing the plushies before donating.
I've never seen that before.
Exactly.
Normally, when I donate old things,
I never wash them.
This company does things right,
thinking about the kids' health.
Some of them
have been stored for a long time.
They might have dust or germs.
That's why Mr. Singha insisted
they be cleaned before donation.
Let me help.
Time's up, Chaiya.
Stop talking now.
Yes.
Manat too.
He's slacking off.
This isn't your business. Go to the car.
Yes.
Puna, I'll excuse myself now.
I have to go.
Okay.
See you later.
HT 2255 BANGKOK
Wait.
-The delivery van already left?
-Yes.
Is there anything I can help with?
I was going to send this one
to be cleaned too.
I can take it to get washed.
I'll take it instead.
I just got a new car,
so I'll drive it to the laundry myself.
I think I should do it.
I can clean it. It's just a little.
No need to send it to the shop.
Spend your time on something else.
Let Maria take it to the laundry.
You know the place, right?
Yes, I do. I'll take care of it myself.
Maria.
I'll take it to the laundry for you.
No need.
I promised Mr. Singha
I'd handle it myself.
-But I want to help.
-No!
-I really want to help.
-What's going on?
-Oh!
Why are you interfering, Puna?
Miss Maria, let's go for a drive.
Good idea.
We'll go for a drive. You stay here.
Teacher.
What should we do? Maria took the bear.
Let's follow her to the laundry.
Let's go.
All done. I've written down
all the medication instructions.
Make sure you take everything,
or the infection could become resistant.
Thanks, Doctor.
Give the money to him.
Khod.
How did you get out?
The court granted me bail, Boss.
For your case? They actually let you out?
My brother-in-law's a lawyer,
so he handled it.
Did you tell the police anything?
Didn't tell them a thing.
We're on the same side.
How could I snitch on you or Pleaw?
If you aren't comfortable,
let him rest for now.
Don't put him to work yet.
We're short on people anyway.
It's good to have Khod helping.
Thank you, Boss.
The car's ready, Boss.
Where are you going?
Somewhere quiet to rest a bit.
After I recover, I'll deal with them.
LAUNDRY SERVICE
This is the place.
Our company uses it regularly.
Hey.
You need to check quickly.
If the bear goes in the machine,
what's inside might get damaged.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm not sure if Sophie
brought the teddy bear here for cleaning?
It's in the machine. Being washed now.
-What?
No!
Is this the one?
Oh! Yes! That's it!
Hey!
Quick, check inside! Hurry up.
Found it?
There's nothing inside.
What?
Hey!
No way.
How is this possible?
The bow's a different color.
-Could it be a different bear, Teacher?
-Yeah.
I'll take a photo
and send it to Aunt Wilai first.
She replied!
What did she say?
IT'S A DIFFERENT ONE
It's a different one.
Nothing wrong. Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Luckily,
it was a different one.
Otherwise, the stuff inside
would have been ruined.
So where's that teddy bear now?
It's in Mr. Singha's office.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Hello? What is it?
Someone from your company came
and checked something inside a bear.
Who?
-Puna.
-Puna?
Sorry, but I don't like anyone
messing with my teddy bear.
Let me wash
this teddy bear for you.
Actually, never mind.
You don't need to wash it.
Mr. Singha.
The plushies sent in,
should I handle it like before?
Yes.
Put 20 kilos from this batch in,
separate the boxes.
Got it.
Puna.
Could she be a police informant?
Chaiya.
I saw the way Mr. Sonrak looks at Puna,
like he's hiding something.
I know.
I think he's serious about her.
I know that too.
Hey! I know! I know!
Nothing else to say?
Should I snap you out of it?
When I say I know, I mean
I won't step aside for Sonrak,
not even one step.
But you'll step back if I say so.
Here, take this!
Hey, stuff 20 kilos of these
into the plushies,
and pack them into boxes like before.
Got it, Aew.
The car's gone.
-Then let's head to the office.
-Okay.
Let's go.
DARATHONG MUSIC
Found it, Puna?
No.
I don't think the bear's
in this room anymore.
But I remember, it really was here before.
Think carefully.
Hey.
Maybe it's in the props room.
-Let's go check.
-Okay, let's go.
Hey.
Do you think it's in here, Puna?
If it's not in the office,
it has to be in this room, Teacher.
Alright.
These accessories
still look usable, Puna.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
They're all so pretty!
DARATHONG MUSIC
Has all our staff left yet?
The security said Puna
and Teacher Mueangphrai haven't left yet.
Found it yet, Teacher?
Nothing here.
I don't think it's in this room.
Mr. Singha.
What are you two doing here?
We came to look for accessories
to go with the outfits.
But earlier,
the laundry staff called
and said you went there.
Yes.
The accessories
had fallen off somewhere.
We saw someone took them to be washed,
so we went there.
That's right.
But we didn't find anything,
so we came back to check here.
Here.
We did find some old accessories
that can be used as replacements.
Okay.
Good that you found something.
You can leave now.
That was close, Teacher.
Yeah, indeed.
Let's head back. We can continue tomorrow.
Let's go.
When will you accept
When will you know
If you already have a love
Please hurry and tell me
If you're still single
I beg you, with kindness
Take a little time
To consider my heart
I offer you my heart
Waiting for your answer
I've told you so many times not to come!
Why won't you listen?
You know I'm famous right now.
I can't let anyone know
I already have a family.
But our son and I miss you.
I miss you and our son too.
But you have to understand me.
I brought Sonrak with me.
He is asleep at the temple hall.
Could you stop by
and see him for a moment?
I can't.
If anyone sees me, it's over.
We can't meet.
Then I'll give you this teddy bear.
And please, make sure
to read our son's letter.
I'll send money.
I have to go now.
Yes.
I'll take the fan gift
and store it at the company.
DADDY, I MISS YOU SO MUCH
Daddy, I miss you so much.
But Mommy says we can't see you yet,
because you're working
to earn money for us.
Daddy, Mommy is unwell
and can't go to work.
I really want to see you. Sonrak.
I can't go see you yet, son.
Back then,
if only I had taken better care of you…
you wouldn't have left me so soon.
Dad.
This is Mom's teddy bear, isn't it?
Today is…
the anniversary of her death.
You remember?
I could never forget.
I've regretted it every day.
I couldn't be there with you and your mom.
But you have to understand, Sonrak.
If the truth got out
that I had a family,
it would ruin our future.
I understand, Dad.
Now that I'm a singer like you,
I understand even more.
Fans are everything to us.
We have to do everything
to earn their support.
They give us a living.
We have to sacrifice our personal lives
to make them happy.
Poor thing.
Your mom was a volunteer,
always helping everyone
when the epidemic hit.
That's right.
She helped the villagers and ended up
catching tuberculosis herself.
No one, Dad.
No one cared about her at all.
She went to the villagers for help,
and they ignored her completely.
When she died,
I was furious at those villagers
at how they treated her.
It's all in the past.
Mom's been gone for years now.
Let's just move on from it.
You really are your mother's son.
This teddy bear, she gave it to me.
Do you want to keep it in your room?
Really, Dad?
I miss Mom too.
Thank you, Dad.
Everyone.
I want to show you something.
This is my teddy bear.
It's a little stand-in for my mom.
I miss her so much, everyone.
Good night.
Oh! Wow!
Too bad Wilai isn't here.
She'd get to see the my dance moves.
Lucky her! No nightmares for her!
You've got a sharp tongue, Puna.
-I'm just kidding. Just joking!
-Alright.
Teacher!
-Look at this!
-What?
Don't tell me that bear
ended up with Sonrak?
I think so.
I remember this one for sure.
Our target
just changed locations to his house.
This is gonna be tough.
What should we do?
How can we find a reason
to go to his place?
Just go be his girlfriend.
Forget the house.
You can even get
into that teddy bear's room.
-A girlfriend?
-Yeah.
Is that Chaiya's voice?
CHAIYA
Yeah, that's him singing.
I set it as my ringtone.
Hello?
Did you get a chance
to listen to the recording I sent?
Yes, I did.
How is it? Was it okay?
It's great!
So good that I set it as my ringtone.
Don't, Teacher.
I'm embarrassed!
Embarrassed? Your voice is amazing.
Don't worry. If no one asks,
I won't tell anyone who sang it.
And Teacher,
please don't let Puna find out.
I'm shy.
Too late!
I heard it loud and clear!
Alright, that's it for now. When we meet,
we'll talk about your singing.
Okay.
I have to figure out a way
to get that teddy bear
from Sonrak's house.
Here, take one.
Hey, whoa!
It's a bomb, Chart!
NEXT EPISODE
On, tell me.
What secret did you find out?
What are you looking for?
Is it the guy who walks with a limp?
Here they are!
The old plushies and its old clothes.
This car is carrying drugs.
-Drugs?
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn