I saw Chaiya sneaking into the room
behind the warehouse,
acting kind of strange.
How?
Maybe he's an undercover police captain
or something like that.
PREVIOUS EPISODE
Why didn't you tell me
that Mr. Sonrak has an interview
for a TV show in Bangkok?
I only know they contacted Mr. Sonrak
to record the show Top Country Hits.
I know you're tired, Puna.
I'm here to support you.
Thank you.
-Stop!
-Let go!
Let's go, Mr. Singha.
Go!
Hello. Is this the police?
Please send officers
to handle the situation.
Captain.
There's a clash happening.
We're not sure who's involved.
-Do you have any bullets left?
-None left.
Grenade! Watch out!
We need to fall back
and regroup. Let's go!
He's running into the woods!
After him!
Go! Quick, move!
Get down!
Mr. Singha, we're here to help!
Where the hell have you been?
I was about to die!
We need to get out of here!
Lead the way. Go!
-Let's go, Boss!
-Go!
The gunfire's coming from over there.
Get ready, everyone.
Go!
What's up, Sergeant? Huh?
Chart, the police are here.
Fall back! Fall back!
Got it. Let's go!
You think you can run?
Nuay, follow me.
The rest of you stay here.
Finish them off and follow me!
Got it!
Stop! Drop your weapons and surrender!
Hey, run!
Chase them down!
Yes, sir!
-Let's go, Sergeant!
-Let's go.
Let's go.
Stop!
Drop your weapons.
I told you to drop your weapons!
You guys are all dead today.
Singha, today's your last day.
Bring it on.
But if I make it out alive, your Boss Noo
is dead for sure.
Keep dreaming.
Hey, pretty boy.
This isn't your fight.
But if you get involved…
Hey! Ugh!
Drop your gun!
If you don't, I'll shoot. Now!
Ugh!
Oh, perfect evidence.
Gotcha.
Why is he so handsome?
Wait, why am I taking a selfie?
Hey, the cops are coming!
Ugh!
-Which way should I go?
-This way, Boss!
-Let's go!
-Grab the guns too!
Protect the boss!
Sergeant.
How's it going?
Were you able to get the photos?
Yes, Captain. I got
clear shots of their faces.
Great job.
Hurry and send the evidence.
Then, follow Pleaw's crew.
Got it, Captain.
-Hey, hold on!
-What?
They're all gone. Why are we still here?
We're here to collect evidence.
If you're free, please help with that.
They've all escaped.
All that's left are the bodies.
Then collect all the evidence in the area.
I want to know who those guys are,
who just fought.
Yes, Captain.
-Chart.
-The police got here too quickly today.
Or do we have a mole among us?
And where's Chaiya?
Why are you just getting here?
Sorry, Mr. Singha.
There were so many cops around,
I barely escaped. That's why I'm late.
Go drive the car.
Honestly, Chart, something
feels off about this guy.
Let it go for now.
Keep an eye on him from a distance.
Aha! Gotcha.
So this is where they've been hiding.
What's this?
You said there was
only one person with him.
Why couldn't you handle them?
But this guy is really skilled, Boss.
Who is he?
His name is Chaiya.
I've met him before, and he's really good.
No matter how skilled,
he'll make a mistake one day.
Find a way to take him down.
If you can't do it openly,
then do it quietly.
I'll never forget the pain from this.
Understood, Boss. I'll find a way.
Let's go.
Get in the van.
Yes.
Go check.
Alright, see you this evening.
Yeah, I hope so.
Puna, aren't you supposed
to be in the back seat?
When are you getting in the car?
We were about to get in!
You always talk back!
Hey, why are you always shadowing me?
Hurry up, so others can get in!
You're wasting our time.
Mr. Sonrak, want to use
the bathroom? I'll take you.
Sure, let's go.
This way.
STUDIO SEVEN
Is the back seat comfortable, Puna?
How could it be comfortable?
She has to squeeze in
with bags of clothes,
and the van's bouncing and shaking.
If it were me,
I wouldn't be able to sit at all.
Hey, Puna can handle it. She's good.
Don't use that word.
She's just used to it.
She's used to being like that.
As a lower-level employee,
she has to manage.
You can't compare her to Miss Maria.
Miss Maria's an artist.
La la la
Keep mocking us!
I think these guys want to get slapped!
Let it go, Teacher.
Let them talk.
Just ignore them, and let them be.
-I'll let it go for now.
-Let's go.
Take my heart for your consideration
Check it out and see
If my heart is new or old…
What a beautiful song.
Is it broken? Is there any damage…?
It's Mr. Singha's song.
Mr. Sonrak had it sung again.
You know too much.
Of course I do. I'm his assistant.
I know everything about Mr. Sonrak.
You know everything about others,
but do you know yourself?
Of course I do.
I know that I'm single right now,
with no girlfriend.
I'm looking for a serious relationship.
I've already found someone.
It's the person next to me.
What does that mean?
See?
I know my heart, unlike you.
You haven't been yourself.
People are messing with your head.
Who are you talking about?
I'm not talking about anyone.
I'm just saying,
I want you to be yourself.
I feel like lately,
you've been getting messed with.
What am I being messed around with?
Competing and outdoing others.
Let me ask you honestly.
If you win, are you truly happy
with a victory that comes
from hurting others?
If you still see
The value in my goodness
I'm ready to give my life
If you consider it…
Miss Maria.
STUDIO SEVEN
Just now, what did
that assistant guy say to you?
Nothing, really.
That's good. Don't get too close to him.
You might soften up.
Right now, your focus
should only be on Mr. Sonrak.
Don't look at any other men.
See Mr. Sonrak?
Keep your eyes on him, just on him.
That's the one. Over there.
That's the diamond.
Don't waste your time on the pebbles.
Please, have mercy
-Take the time to consider my heart…
-Dazzling diamond!
So handsome!
I offer you my heart
Waiting for your answer
I'm ready for you to test it
Inside the chamber of my heart
MARIA
I heard a rumor that Village Head Prueng
asked for Maria
to release her single first.
I believe it's true.
What do you think, Puna?
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, Maria is already a singer.
But if the village head
didn't play tricks,
you would have already become
a singer by now.
Who knows, the one filming the show today
might have been Puna Darathong,
not Maria.
Puna.
I'm sorry for what I said.
I didn't mean it.
I shouldn't have said that.
You don't have to apologize.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Everything you said is the truth.
I just have to accept it.
But just wait.
If one day I can't take it anymore,
you'll see what happens.
Oh, Maria!
Hello, Teacher.
Are you all set?
-Come on. Let me help you.
-Uh, no.
It's fine. Don't be shy.
Hurry, let's go.
I'll get your outfit ready.
-Well…
-Okay, come here.
Teacher, sorry for being late.
-Uh, okay.
-You look beautiful.
-Well, thank you.
-Really beautiful.
Thank you, but I'm…
-Just a little more.
-Alright.
Here.
-Huh?
-We're here. Oh no!
Excuse me. Hold on for a second.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
This isn't Miss Maria.
The real Miss Maria is right here.
This is Puna.
Yes! She's just an employee.
She prepares the clothes, irons them,
helps put them on, and serves the artists.
But Puna won the singing competition
and got first place, while Maria
only got second.
Don't forget to mention this,
so people know.
Hey!
Are you really a music teacher?
You have such a loose mouth.
How can you reveal company secrets
in front of everyone?
What secret? Everyone knows about this.
If you don't believe me,
check out the Facebook page
of Darathong Music. But wait,
you won't find it now.
Because Maria's dad…
Oops, the label
deleted the results already.
Miss Maria, don't let him get to you.
He's exposing you.
-Joey!
-Ouch!
I won't say anything.
But anyway, right now,
Miss Maria is the artist.
And Puna is just a staff.
Everyone has a role,
so they should stick to it.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, Puna's job
is to prepares the clothes.
Go help put the clothes on
and iron them. Got it?
Hey, stylist.
Miss Maria will change,
then come back for makeup and hair.
As for you,
go help her get dressed.
Hurry up, Puna. Come on!
Hurry up! You weren't hired
to stand around.
Tsk! You don't even know your place!
Ouch, that hurts!
Just stay still.
Are you trying to mess with me?
Why would I mess with you?
Turn around quickly.
Oh, you had to follow Puna
all the way here.
Probably worried that she might
get hurt by Miss Maria.
You never know.
Joey, do you see that?
If not, I wouldn't be like this.
All this food looks so good!
I want to sneak some and take it home.
Do you have a bag?
This set is amazing. So much food to eat!
Next time, I'll bring a bag
and take some home.
Wow.
Are you bringing a big bag to put it in?
Are you planning to sell it?
Your idea is good!
Should I sell them after taking them?
-No!
-What?
That's rude! I should sell them too.
Hurry up. Let's go!
A bunch of gluttons stealing food!
If you're being oppressed,
you need to stay even calmer.
Don't do anything reckless.
-Where are my heels?
-They're right there.
Pick them up and put them on for me.
Do it yourself.
Can't you see I'm busy working?
But I'm the artist.
And you're just a clothes ironer.
When you're done,
come put my shoes on for me.
Or I'll tell Mr. Singha
you're slacking off.
Wait.
Clean them first, then put them on for me.
You better know your place, Puna.
Your fate is probably
just to be an employee.
You should remember
who I am and who you are.
In the future, if I become
Mr. Sonrak's girlfriend,
I'd probably end up
being the president's wife.
At that point, I might show some mercy
and promote you
to a coffee-making employee.
Are you done yet?
When you're finished, put them on for me.
I can't take it anymore!
Come here!
Hey, you watch
too many moral dramas, don't you?
What are you going to do to me?
Do you want to know what happens
to the villains in those dramas?
How do you think their story ends?
No, I don't want to know.
If you don't want to know, that's fine.
I'll make you find out.
Stay away! Don't!
What are you going to do?
Why? Are you scared?
Stay away! Hey, don't come closer!
-Come here!
-No! What are you going to do to me?
Take it off!
-Take it off!
-Puna, let me go!
Hey, Puna!
Let me go right now!
Puna! You can't
keep me locked up like this!
Scream all you want. No one will hear.
Are you done? It's time for standby now.
You look amazing!
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
Puna! Let me go!
Who owns this famous music label?
They say the boss
Is good-looking
The singers of this label are all handsome
And famous, at the top level
I want to be famous, I want to try
I want to be one of the artists
At this label
I want to be famous
Can't stand it anymore
I want people
To scream for me at the stage
Please accept me as an artist
I promise I'll do well
No cheating, no running away
I'll sign a contract for years
If you want me to
I want to be famous, like a star
I want everyone
To cheer together
I'm serious about being famous
Let the music label fulfill my dream
I want to be famous…
Puna!
What's wrong with you?
Why are you zoning out?
Are you done yet? I'm in a hurry!
Almost done.
Took forever.
Where were you lost in thought?
Anyway, in the future,
if I become the wife of Mr. Sonrak,
the company president,
I'll give you the position
of shoe assistant.
Thank you for your kindness.
Miss Maria! Oh!
Are you wearing this outfit?
Yes, is there a problem?
The producer wants you
to wear a different outfit.
The one you wore
for the promotional poster shoot.
The team already informed
Miss Sophie about it.
Sophie!
Yes, Miss Maria. What's wrong?
The team said to bring the poster outfit.
Why didn't you tell me?
Oh!
-When was this mentioned?
-It was mentioned.
We even discussed through texts.
Do you want to see it?
Puna!
Why didn't you bring it?
Well, no one told me.
I told you. I remember.
When did you tell her? How do I not know?
-She told you when you weren't there.
-Yeah!
That's not true. You didn't tell me.
Can we stop arguing?
Let's focus on solving the problem.
Can we wear another outfit?
No.
It doesn't fit the theme of the show.
How about this?
Can you go get it?
-Go get it?
-Yes.
Yes!
You go get it. Quickly!
Hurry up!
I'll go. Puna, tell me
where you keep the outfit.
It's okay. The outfit is in the box.
You won't find it. I'll go get it.
We'll move forward
with another shoot in the meantime.
But please hurry up.
-Okay.
-Alright.
I'll go now.
Hurry up. Go!
Go!
This is how you work?
STUDIO SEVEN
-Chang.
-What?
I need to go back to the company
to pick up an outfit.
Can you give me a ride?
How do you all work like this?
Always causing trouble for others.
This isn't Puna's fault.
We only just found out
they need the poster outfit.
Please help her out.
I can't.
I need to stay here
and look after Mr. Sonrak.
-I can't leave.
-Then I'll go.
Thanks. I'll go ahead now, Teacher.
Hurry up and come back quickly.
If you're late,
I'll report you to Mr. Sonrak.
Please go ahead.
Hey, do it right! Come here.
Take it properly! Good!
Who owns this famous music label?
They say the boss is good looking
The singers of this label…
Yes, I got it.
Understood.
Thank you!
Director.
Maria forgot
to bring the poster outfit.
Can we start
with the interview tape instead?
Sure.
Hey, Praewa, you're here just in time.
I need a favor.
What is it?
Can you host the show for me?
You want me to interview for the show?
Yeah. Please help me out.
Sure, I'll do it.
DARATHONG MUSIC
Chaiya.
Yes, Ice?
Mr. Singha wants to see you in his office.
Come in.
What's going on, Mr. Singha?
I have a job for you.
What kind of job?
Get revenge on Boss Noo.
We know where he is now.
I want you to deal with him today.
But we just clashed with him.
Exactly! Don't give him
any chance to regroup.
You know,
I almost died because of him today.
Blow his head off, so he won't forget it.
You can do that, right, Chaiya?
But…
I've never killed anyone.
Hey! Are you disobeying my orders?
Did Mr. Singha scold you?
You look really stressed.
Just a little bit.
Don't worry too much.
Being his subordinate
means you have to be patient.
Okay, I'll be patient, just like you said.
Ice, with looks like yours,
don't you ever get scared being here?
I can handle myself just fine.
I'm going to grab something to eat.
I haven't eaten all day.
Sure, take your time.
Yes, Captain?
Hey, who am I? This is Sergeant Au.
I've found their hideout.
I also got a photo. How's that?
Great job, Sergeant Au.
Captain, what should I do next?
Quickly send the photo you took
to Captain Tom.
So, you want him to handle it?
Well…
I have something important today
that requires his help.
Find a way to send it for me.
How should I send it?
Sergeant Yot isn't here anymore.
Uncle Sergeant said Corporal Chom
is trustworthy.
Just send it to him.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
What are you looking at?
A picture of Boss Noo and Pleaw.
Looks like someone found his hideout,
so they sent the photo to the police.
Prepare the forces.
Yes, sir.
We're going in to capture them.
Alright, go get the team ready.
Understood.
Chaiya, where have you been?
I've been looking for you forever.
What's up? Just went to eat.
You better go take care of Boss Noo.
I've got a driver waiting for you
outside the building.
Are you coming along?
Whether I go or not
has nothing to do with you.
Hurry up, unless you want me
to roll out the red carpet.
Go!
-Chit.
-Yes?
Come with me and handle the job.
Got it.
If Chaiya messes around,
kill him along with Boss Noo.
Someone just texted
these photos to me, Captain.
The superintendent saw it
and ordered you to capture them.
Captain.
Is there a problem
with the superintendent's orders?
What problem could there be?
Good, no problem.
Make sure to capture them.
Now, get going.
Let's go.
Wait, Manat.
If we go the usual way,
we'll never make it in time.
Do you know a shortcut?
Let's turn right ahead. It's a shortcut.
Alright.
There they are, over there.
If we charge in now, we won't make it.
Come on. Just find the right moment!
It's Chart calling.
Yes?
What are you hesitating for?
Go in and shoot them.
But Pleaw and his men are standing there.
What are you afraid of?
Well…
I'm still a rookie, Chart.
Chit.
If you don't shoot,
I'll order him to shoot you.
Well, calm down, Chart.
Give me a moment.
I need to collect myself.
Just a second, okay?
When will the police arrive?
This is it. Everyone, get ready!
Go!
Boss, the police are raiding.
How did they find out?
Go out and block them.
Don't let them in. Go!
Got it.
We better hide, Boss.
Let's go!
Hey, stop!
You two go that way.
And you, follow me!
You two go that way!
Let's go, quickly!
Senior Sergeant, follow me!
Watch out!
Hey!
Puna, get out of here.
I'll handle this.
Hey! Watch out!
Run!
Puna.
Chaiya, hurry up and run! Daddy's coming!
-Puna?
-Hurry up!
Hey, Chaiya!
What are you doing here?
I came with Manat.
We were going back to get something.
What happened, Chaiya?
Boss Noo and his men
are being raided by the police.
-Boss, get down!
-Hey!
-Oh no!
-Get down!
Let's go, Boss.
Pleaw, help him up.
Hey.
That way, Boss.
Let's go.
Chaiya, what's happening?
What's your issue with them?
You don't need to know.
It's too dangerous.
Stay hidden here. Don't go anywhere.
I'll be back.
Chaiya!
Chart.
What are you doing here?
I saw Boss Noo around here,
so I was…
Good.
Kill Boss Noo
while he's escaping the police.
That way, no one will know.
I'll go corner him for you.
Then you shoot him in the head,
or I'll shoot you instead.
Follow me.
Now's the time. Take him out, Chaiya.
Hold on.
Are you going to shoot him,
or do you want me to shoot you?
Hurry up!
-This way, Boss.
-Let's go!
Hey, the police are coming. We should run.
Let's go.
Stay here, Corporal. I'll check that way.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Who's there?
Come out, or I'll shoot!
Officer!
What are you doing here?
I'm running from the criminals.
They ambushed me.
My van's broken. I can't go anywhere.
Where's your van?
Over there. I'll take you to it.
Let's go.
Stop, Boss Noo, if you don't want to die!
A man like me
doesn't die so easily
if I've done nothing wrong!
Boss, let's get out of here.
-Come on!
-Let's go!
Ouch!
Take cover!
Ugh!
Are you okay, Boss?
-I'm fine!
-Go!
This is what happened.
I was driving along when they appeared
and started shooting at me.
I had to swerve off the road
and hit a tree, radiator busted.
I almost died.
Where are you going?
Back to get the clothes from the company.
Open it up.
The artists need costumes for the show.
Not sure where my crew has gone.
I need to call them.
Alright, okay.
Captain, how did it go?
Boss Noo and Pleaw managed to escape.
What a shame we couldn't catch them.
Boss Noo got shot.
I think tracking him won't be too hard.
Send someone
to the hospitals or other places.
He might go get treated.
-Yes, sir.
-Corporal Chom.
I really want to know
who's your informant.
How do they know
such detailed information?
This person isn't my usual source.
Somehow, they just sent
Boss Noo's location.
I'll try to find out who it is.
Good. Very good.
Yes.
Puna!
Puna! Where are you?
Chaiya.
Puna's not here?
She's not.
-Maybe she already left?
-How? There aren't any taxis.
The van we drove can't continue.
I'll call Au to pick us up.
Hello, Au? Where are you?
I'm here with Chaiya.
Alright, you want to talk to Chaiya?
Hey, Sergeant Au.
If the police hadn't arrived in time,
I'd have been the shooter.
Don't worry about the message
you sent to Corporal Chom.
He won't be able to trace us.
The number I'm using is encrypted by HQ,
so it can't be traced back to us.
Hurry and pick us up.
I'll send the location.
Puna.
Who exactly are you guys?
Tell the people at home for me.
Tell them what?
NEXT EPISODE
What are you two doing here?
Hey, wait.
-Don't let anyone kiss this forehead
-Hey.
Is that Chaiya's voice?
Don't let anyone caress these cheeks
Yes, that's him singing.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn