What's she doing at Boss Nok's label?
PREVIOUS EPISODE
Is she switching labels?
Don't worry, Puna.
I'm the director.
I'll guide you to make it work.
No problem at all.
That's right! If Puna shoots
this commercial and becomes famous,
you'll be totally overshadowed.
No, I won't let that happen!
Get in the car.
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
There's definitely something in here.
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Hey! Don't touch that!
Teacher! Teacher!
Lock her up so she stays in there.
Finally, no more thorns!
Alright, time to announce.
Come on out, our commercial star!
-Ta-da!
I'm beautiful and look
like a real lead, right?
Miss Maria, you look amazing,
glowing, sparkling, like a diamond!
Hurry up, or we'll be late.
I was enjoying my moment!
Can you save that feeling
for Mr. Sonrak at the set?
Exactly! Hurry up. Let's go!
-You're beautiful.
-After you, gorgeous.
Absolutely gorgeous!
Turn around.
Come here, Teacher!
Hurry, Puna. We'll miss
the commercial shoot.
Help! Is anyone out there?
Ugh. Is anyone there? Please help us!
What should we do, Teacher?
Looks like it's locked from the outside.
Hey, I know!
-We have to go out this way.
-Which way?
Wait, don't tell me…
There's only one way.
It's the only way we can get out.
-Okay.
-Puna, step back!
Oops!
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Sorry.
UNINSPECTED, DO NOT OPEN!
Hey, Manat!
Chaiya.
-Yes, Mr. Sonrak.
-Yes?
Has Puna arrived yet?
Not yet.
I haven't seen her either.
Where's she gone? What will you do?
The extras playing villagers are ready.
Well, we could shoot the villagers first.
Maybe we should go straight to scene two?
Yeah, that works.
It's up to you. Hurry and get it done.
Okay, let's go.
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
Hey, that's Mr. Sonrak!
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
You're right! Let's hurry inside.
Oh no! We're dead!
What? Who's dead? Where?
It's us! We're the ones in trouble!
Calm down! Think clearly, then tell me!
Mr. Sonrak called Puna's phone.
What do we do, Miss Maria?
What should we do?
I don't know! Help me think!
Why are you asking me alone?
Why isn't she answering?
It's quiet now. Let's hurry inside.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Miss Maria!
It's ringing again. Mr. Sonrak
keeps calling Puna's phone!
Oh no!
Listen. I'll answer it and change
my voice to sound like Puna.
Hello, Mr. Sonrak! Are you okay?
Have you eaten yet?
That should settle it.
Yeah, good. No!
That will be the end of us.
If you try to sound like Puna,
he will catch you.
So what now?
Just pretend you're the one
who found her phone.
What if he comes to get the phone back?
What will you say?
That's true.
Well, then…
Ugh! Just let it ring like that.
What if someone hears the phone ringing?
What do we do, Miss Maria?
Just put it on silent!
Yeah, good point.
Right! Why couldn't you think
of such a simple solution, Joey?
You couldn't think of it either, Sophie.
Ugh! Let's hurry inside already!
You guys are talking too much.
I might miss my chance
to be the lead in the commercial.
Go get the stuff from the trunk!
-Hurry up!
-I'm hurrying!
So much stuff!
Put it away.
Let's go!
Hurry, Puna. They must
be waiting for us by now.
-Let's go. This way!
-Hurry!
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Wong, you're handsome!
Wait, don't you think
Sis Haan put on makeup
just to prank us?
No, she did not.
This is how a star does it.
Alright.
We'll be shooting some stock shots.
You guys keep packing the products.
Don't stiffen up or look at the camera.
Just act naturally.
Got it. Hey, come here!
Ready and…
action!
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
Didn't the director tell you?
Don't stiffen up!
Hey, man. We're on TV!
-Will my family recognize me?
-Of course, you're on TV!
Okay, cut.
Passed.
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Chang, go back to the company
and see if Puna is still there.
Mr. Sonrak, aren't you worrying
about her too much?
She'll be here soon.
Chang, listen carefully,
and remember this.
For me, there's no such thing
as worrying too much about Puna. Got it?
Go back and call me
as soon as you find out! Go!
Yes.
Hi! I brought some snacks
to visit the set.
Thank you. That's very kind of you.
Sophie, Joey, give the snacks to the crew.
It'll give them energy to work!
Got it. Here, snacks for everyone!
Maria, have you seen Puna anywhere?
Is something wrong?
Before coming here,
I heard Puna talking on the phone
with someone named Boss Nok.
Looks like he was coming to pick her up.
Oh, Boss Nok?
Yes. A few days ago,
I saw her leaving Boss Nok's music label.
But I don't know what she went there for.
I even took a photo.
-Sophie! The photo.
-Yes?
-The photo from that day.
-Yes.
Joey!
-The phone.
-Huh?
What?
-Here! Proof! You can see it clearly.
-Yes.
We really didn't frame Puna.
If someone isn't loyal,
don't support them.
Change the actor.
-Dad, I think…
-Maria.
Are you ready to shoot this commercial?
I'm ready!
Kamnan, I'd like to have Maria
act in this commercial instead.
Fine, do whatever you want.
No cars at all, Teacher.
Yeah, no idea where we are right now.
Our phone was stolen too.
We have to find a car somehow.
Let's walk a bit further.
Maybe we'll find a car or some locals.
Yeah, but what do we do?
There's still no car.
Here it is! Excuse me!
Hey! Excuse me!
Wait!
Hello! Do you happen to know
Kamnan Pong's factory?
Yes, I know.
Are you Teacher Mueangphrai?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, perfect! Could you take us
to Kamnan Pong's factory?
Sure. I'm heading that way anyway.
-Hop in!
-Perfect. We're in a rush.
-Let's go.
-Thank you!
Let's get in, teacher.
Thank you so much!
Right now, I've sent Chang to find Puna.
As for you, do whatever you can.
Shoot whichever scenes you can first.
I'll try to reach Puna by phone.
-But she's already been replaced.
-If Maria hasn't gone on set yet,
I still have the right
to put her back in. Understand?
Yes, I'll buy some time.
Don't try any tricks like this, Sonrak.
I know what you're thinking.
Dad, I think Maria isn't suitable
for this commercial.
I'll make her suitable.
I'll have you act in the commercial
alongside Maria.
Whoa, Dad!
-Add lines to the script?
-Yes.
Can you write extra lines to put Sonrak
in the commercial with Maria?
Yes.
Then do it this way.
Dad.
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
Thank you so much!
-Let's hurry inside, Teacher.
-Let's go.
Ready, everyone? Action!
AGRICULTURAL PRODUCT PROCESSING FACTORY
Cut!
Who do you think you are,
showing up this late?
Everyone's been waiting for hours!
Where have you been wandering?
I was being set up.
Don't make excuses.
I don't like people who are irresponsible.
Get out!
Really, I was being set up.
I said, get out!
Dad! Calm down. Please listen to Puna.
Stop defending her.
Just do your job properly. Go!
Well, Kamnan…
Could you give Puna one more chance?
Sonrak.
Puna brought this on herself.
I can't help with that.
Get back on set.
What are you waiting for?
Finish the shoot!
Hey! What's going on?
Get down!
Call the local police!
Got it, honey.
-Hey, fall back!
-Let's go!
Hey, Pleaw!
Ugh!
Go!
You're finished, Pleaw!
Chit, move the stuff quickly!
Yes, Boss! Let's go!
Go!
Let's go!
Good to see you, Captain.
Lucky you're here.
Otherwise, we'd be in big trouble.
Who are the attackers? What do they want?
Not sure, but probably competitors
who saw our factory doing well
and sent people to mess things up.
How many of them?
That's probably for you to figure out.
Mr. Sonrak! Blood!
Sonrak! You're hit!
-Don't pass out!
-Mr. Sonrak!
Oh, you passed out?
-Sonrak!
Sonrak! Call an ambulance!
Sonrak!
-Mr. Sonrak!
-Call an ambulance!
I'll take him to the hospital.
Hurry! Go quickly!
Please help!
Mr. Sonrak!
Manat, stay here and deal with this!
Sonrak! My son!
Sophie!
Yes, I'll check everything thoroughly.
I'll prepare a report for you.
Corporal.
Yes?
There's a suspicious box in the factory
with Do Not Open labels.
Get the captain to check it.
But don't say it came from me.
I don't want any trouble.
Where is the box?
Over there. I'll show you.
PROCESSED AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTS
Here it is.
UNINSPECTED, DO NOT OPEN!
There's a suspicious box inside, Captain.
-Where is it?
-This way.
Take me there.
It's gone. The box is missing.
It was just here a moment ago.
Split up and search everywhere.
If anyone finds anything,
report back to me.
-Yes, sir.
-Yes.
I've removed the bullet.
The initial check shows nothing serious,
since no vital organs were hit.
When will my son
be able to leave the hospital?
I expect it will take about two weeks.
That means his work
will have to be postponed.
I agree. He needs to rest
and recover first.
Don't overdo it,
or the wound could reopen.
-I'll excuse myself now.
-Thank you, Doctor.
How are you feeling, son?
It hurts, Dad.
The doctor said you need a long break.
No work for now.
Yes, Dad.
Dad.
They attacked me again.
I remember they're Boss Noo's men.
I remember, Dad.
Yes, they won't stop causing trouble.
I'm asking seriously, Dad.
Is there anything I don't know about?
What do you mean by that question?
I just want to know
if you're hiding something from me.
But if not, I apologize, Dad.
There isn't.
Why don't we let the law handle them?
Have the police deal with them,
or we could take them to court.
I've got the police helping,
but they haven't managed anything yet.
Then,
should I go to the media?
The media might be able to help us.
No! That'll only make things worse.
Dad, we're being targeted.
We can't keep putting up with this.
Let me find a way to deal with them.
You stay out of it.
Then what are you going to do?
I can handle this.
I don't want you getting involved.
Fine, Dad. But you need
to end this quickly.
It's affecting my work.
I will.
I'll end this problem
with Boss Noo very soon.
Puna, your rice porridge looks delicious.
Hopefully Sonrak will like it.
Is it really okay, Teacher?
Should I really go visit Mr. Sonrak?
Our goal is the teddy bear.
You need to get close to Mr. Sonrak.
Find a way into his house for that bear.
So I'm supposed to be his girlfriend?
You don't have to go that far.
You just need a reason to go to his house,
cook something for him,
and find a way inside.
But I'm afraid Mr. Sonrak
might misunderstand
and it could get out of hand.
What choice do we have, Puna?
If we don't do it,
there won't be any chance.
-Let's go.
Puna.
I'm so glad you came to visit me.
I'm a company artist.
After everything that happened with you,
it wouldn't be right if I didn't come.
It's past mealtime.
Mr. Sonrak, have you eaten yet?
No, it's fine. I'm not hungry yet.
Oh really? I brought
some rice porridge. Should I…
What? You made rice porridge for me?
Perfect timing, Puna! I'm hungry.
Go ahead and serve me, okay?
-Sure. Just a moment.
-I'm hungry.
Thank you.
You get hungry fast, huh?
Well, I haven't eaten anything
since this morning.
DARATHONG MUSIC
What are we waiting for?
We need to tell Mr. Singha first,
before he hears it from them!
Then let's go in together.
-Joey, you lead.
-Huh?
Why me?
-What?
-Why me?
-Why does it have to be me?
You're big. If anyone gets pushed,
it'll be you first.
-True.
-Go.
-Lead the way?
-Yeah.
Quickly!
-Alright, fine.
-Go.
Come in.
-Hello.
-What's this about?
Yesterday, Puna was late
to shoot the commercial
because we caused the delay.
How did it happen?
The reason we held Puna back from filming
is because we found out
she was planning to switch music labels.
It's the evidence we showed at the set.
If you want to see it again,
we secretly recorded a clip.
We were really angry that Puna
betrayed Darathong Music,
so we locked her up.
We didn't want her filming the commercial.
That's right. If Puna
filmed the commercial
and switched labels, it would clearly
be taking advantage of the company.
I'm sorry for acting on my own.
I was really angry at Puna. I don't want
a singer like that in our company.
Ice, call Boss Nok from Bai Tong Music.
Is it too bland?
I made it in a bit of a hurry.
Not bland at all.
It's just right, Puna. I really like it.
Then eat it all,
so you can get better quickly.
I don't want to get better.
I want you to make this porridge
for me every day.
If you want more of my cooking,
when you're better, I'll cook for you.
Really?
Yes, but if I make it at home
and bring it to the office,
it might get a little cold.
Then you can cook at my place too.
But if she goes to cook at your house,
I'll go along.
She doesn't want any gossips
That's fine, Teacher.
When I get out of the hospital,
Puna, you'll cook at my house, okay?
Yes.
Eat a lot, okay?
DARATHONG MUSIC
Wait, Boss!
-What?
-Are you really going in?
Yeah, why? What's it to you?
I'm just worried
something might happen.
But don't worry, Boss.
If anything goes wrong,
I'll take the bullets myself.
Tu, last time,
even a barking dog scared you
and you ran hiding over there.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
-Move aside!
-Got it.
Singha has a weakness. You'll see.
We have to face each other one-on-one.
Wake up, amulet. Trouble's coming!
Please wake up!
No, don't follow her!
Teacher.
Hey, his room is that way!
That's Boss Nok.
Yes, he's probably here to talk about you.
Let's go listen.
SONRAK DARATHONG
Calm down, Boss.
We meet again.
So glad to see you!
Hello. Please, this way.
Wait, seriously, from the heart,
you're perfect!
Do you want to be a singer?
I can train you.
You have such an aura.
It's really uplifting.
What?
-She's Kamnan Pong's secretary.
-Hey! What are you saying?
If I train you,
I could just look at your face all day.
I really like your looks.
Boss, you'll listen to her voice
all day and night, right?
-That's right.
-Yeah, her voice!
I'll listen to your voice
all day and night. I don't know why,
but your charm, it just grabs my heart!
Your face…
-Tu.
-Yes?
Isn't she Kamnan Pong's secretary?
Why didn't you warn me?
You let me get lost in her charm.
I've been saying it from the start!
My mouth's splitting, still not listening.
You said she's beautiful.
I said she's his secretary.
You're going to get shot!
You said nothing! You left me dreamy.
It's embarrassing.
-Everyone here saw it.
-Yeah.
Boss Nok, you're in a good mood today?
Oh, I'm in a good mood
because I got to see your face.
Please, this way.
Where?
Mr. Singha is waiting.
Fine, let's go. You lead.
Boss Nok is here, sir.
Come in.
SONRAK DARATHONG, MARIA DARATHONG
Please have a seat.
We need to talk.
Yeah, that's why I came myself.
About Puna.
You're interested in my artist?
Yes.
I want to ask, if you didn't plan
to produce music for her…
why trick her into signing a contract?
DARATHONG MUSIC
How did you know I tricked her?
Everyone in the industry knows.
I checked everything.
Everyone in the music industry says
you didn't order a new song for Puna.
I've been in this business forever.
Everyone knows that if a company
doesn't order a new song for a singer,
it clearly means
you're shelving them.
I shelved her
because I didn't think she'd be popular.
Nowadays, sweet singers
just don't sell anymore.
Puna.
Poor Puna.
The media's been reporting
everything to me.
Darathong Music
is pouring all its efforts
into promoting a singer
named Maria.
That means you have
high hopes for her, right?
So what?
Hey.
Calm down.
I come in peace. I just want to offer
a chance to break the contract.
That way, you could make more money
and boost Maria's promotion.
Why? Are you going to train this kid?
Yes. I've liked her since the competition.
It's a shame a talented kid like this
is being shelved.
Are you sure
you can make Puna famous if you take her?
So far, I haven't seen your label
make anyone famous.
Whether she becomes famous or not,
that depends on the kid's luck.
Let's be honest. How much are we talking?
Ten million.
Can you pay that?
Ten million?
I can't pay that.
But I do have…
photos showing your relationship
with Boss Noo.
I also have videos of the conflicts
between you and him.
And if these videos reach the police,
everyone will understand
what the conflict between you
and Boss Noo is really about.
DARATHONG MUSIC
And the winner
of today's singing contest is…
Puna, with the song
"Wait for Him to Forget".
DARATHONG COUNTRY MUSIC SINGING CONTEST
Uncle, I won!
My dream is finally coming true!
Just a little more, dear.
You'll be an artist with your own songs.
Your live voice,
anyone who hears it will fall in love.
Teacher.
Mr. Singha meant to shelve me.
He never even ordered the composer
to write me a song.
He just tricked me into working for him
every single day.
Now, you're officially an artist
under Darathong Music.
From now on, you need
to be careful with your behavior.
Don't do anything
that could damage the label's reputation.
Thank you so much for giving me
the opportunity to follow my dream.
Oh, what's this?
Shelved like a jar of pickled food, huh?
Poor thing, really pitiful.
Hey, why feel sorry for her, Miss Maria?
Some people are just luckier than others.
That's true. She won the competition,
but still hasn't had the chance
to sing a single song.
Well, you two are exaggerating.
But it's like this. Dirt is dirt.
No matter how hard
you try to make it a star,
no matter how high you climb,
it will eventually fall back
to the ground.
Is this the behavior of decent people,
mocking someone like this?
Let them talk, Teacher.
People like this have no filter.
Don't think your words
will make me feel defeated.
I may have no connections,
no parents pushing me,
but I have my voice. I have my dream.
And I will never stop running.
Then I'll just hope you can keep up.
Keep going!
We're cheering for you.
Mr. Singha.
Come here.
Puna.
I'm going to have you move
to Boss Nok's label.
What does that mean?
Boss Nok asked to take you in.
He promises to make you famous.
You have a great voice and potential,
so I want to give you the opportunity.
That must be them.
Uncle, is something wrong?
-Is someone following us?
-Let's talk inside.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
What? Singha actually agreed
to let you sing at Boss Nok's label?
Yes. I heard Boss Nok
offered a contract buyout,
so Mr. Singha agreed.
Does Aunt Wilai know about this?
She does, and she agrees.
It's a chance for me to have my own songs.
Also, the bear
isn't at the company anymore,
so there's no reason for me to stay there.
Where did Singha put it?
At his home, Uncle.
Don't worry. I've set it up
with Mr. Sonrak to cook for him
at his place on weekends.
I plan to use that chance
to get the bear back.
Puna.
Going into the tiger's den
is even riskier than the company.
I'm not going alone, Uncle.
Teacher Mueangphrai is coming with me.
Here's what we'll do. Whenever you go,
I'll wait outside.
If anything happens, call me.
I'll come in right away.
Yes, Uncle.
Mr. Sonrak, you're back.
Aunt Riam, can you get
the medicine ready upstairs for me?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Mr. Sonrak.
I heard, right now,
Boss Nok is setting up a room
to welcome Puna as a new singer.
What is going on?
Puna's moving to Boss Nok's label.
No way. I don't believe it. Where's Dad?
I'm here.
Dad.
-What's happening?
-That's right.
Tomorrow, Puna will move
to Boss Nok's label. Earlier today,
my discussion with him was final.
No, Dad!
I won't allow it!
I won't let Puna go to him.
I'll call him myself!
Sonrak.
What, Dad?
I know how you feel about Puna.
But listen, our company doesn't have
the budget to train her anymore.
That's why I have to send her to Boss Nok.
How can there be no budget?
I saw it myself!
Kamnan Pong signed the approval.
The budget's been used elsewhere.
There's nothing left for Puna.
Used elsewhere? But that's Puna's budget!
I spent the budget on you!
You and Maria are trending as a ship,
so I have to keep it going.
I need money to run events
to draw in fans.
It all costs money.
Come on. Don't worry.
I won't let Puna go easily
like others think.
So, you're using Boss Nok
to train Puna?
Yes, I have a plan.
Wen she becomes popular,
I'll bring her back.
Sonrak, don't worry.
Even if Puna's at another label,
she's still in the same circle.
She hasn't gone anywhere. I know…
I know how you feel about her.
If you want to date her, I won't stop you.
Just don't let the fans know yet. Got it?
You just got back
from the hospital. Go rest.
Chang.
Take care of your boss.
Leave me alone!
Sonrak.
Sonrak!
SONRAK DARATHONG, MARIA DARATHONG
Do you think I should get Puna
a mic keychain?
It's cute, right?
Are you spoiling girls now?
Go for it! I support you.
Maybe she'll finally accept you
as a boyfriend.
Just a keychain,
can it really change a girl's mind?
It's not spoiling.
It's a subtle way to show your feelings,
like water slowly seeping through sand.
You get it?
Got it, Master.
Hey, Ice is here.
Ice, have you seen Puna?
Someone around here
is looking for her.
Puna? She's just packing up in her room.
Packing up?
-Yeah.
-Where is she going?
Got an outside job today?
Mr. Sonrak didn't say he had to go out.
You two still don't know yet?
Know what?
Puna's moving to Boss Nok's label
as a singer.
What?
Puna.
Whoa, wait. What's going on?
DARATHONG MUSIC
Puna!
I hope you become the singer
you've dreamed of.
NEXT EPISODE
Just so you know,
you two can't measure up to Puna.
I want you to take
Captain Tom down. Got it?
Move, now!
-Sergeant!
Hey! Chit, don't shoot! Stop!
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn