[English subtitles are available]
[Fight for love]
[Episode 11]
Qingzhou Army and Yuzhou Army will have a martial arts competition.
If the Qingzhou Army wins,
not only you will get the provisions,
but also have a bargaining chip to negotiate with the crown prince.
What if the Yuzhou Army wins?
Shut up.
You have to die.
Are you crazy?
You gamble with Young Marquis's life?
Why are you shouting?
You're ruining the mood.
Get out and wait for me.
I...
I’ll go.
Mai.
I knew you wouldn’t leave me alone.
Young Marquis.
Mu Bai went out.
Just say what you want to say.
I don't seem to have anything to say.
I just suddenly feel that
we don't spend much time together.
He shouldn't even be here.
Are you out of your mind?
Mr. Yang,
I have an idea.
Would you like to hear it?
General Shi, tell me.
For those who practice martial arts, one's ability is the most important thing.
These Qingzhou soldiers risk their lives to protect Shang Yizhi
because they don't know Young Marquis's reputation
in Shengdu City.
They don’t know he’s a fool.
What do you mean?
Do you want me to compete with Shang Yizhi?
No, no.
There's a military competition in Yuzhou.
We'll let the Qingzhou soldiers and Yuzhou soldiers compete.
This Shang Yizhi is a fool.
Our Yuzhou Army is strong in every aspects.
And with Mr. Yang as the commander,
we can defeat Qingzhou soldiers effortlessly.
After the Qingzhou's military power collapsed,
we can deal with Shang Yizhi freely.
Without Qingzhou soldiers as backers,
so what if we force him to commit suicide?
General Shi,
this is a great idea.
[Qingzhou Army Training Ground]
Stand up straight.
One more group.
Start the training.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
One.
I think their training is pretty decent.
You call that decent?
Compared to the Yuzhou Army,
we still have a long way to go.
They have you training them.
Who are you?
I'm Lieutenant Wang Xun of Yuzhou Army
With your poor skills,
you'd better not practice martial arts here.
Go back before it's too late
so you won't embarrass the Qingzhou Army.
Come down if you dare.
Come down. Let's have a fight.
Come down.
Stop!
Lieutenant Wang,
please leave if there's nothing else.
You should go back.
Go back to Qingzhou.
The martial arts competition hasn't started yet.
Our Qingzhou Army may not lose.
You want to take the hard way.
Fine.
Then don't blame me for being merciless.
Let’s go.
Continue training.
Return!
Let's go.
Let's check up on Yuzhou Army.
[Shang]
[Yuzhou Army Training Ground]
Here.
I’ll put it here.
Mai, tell dad
how to move.
You're indeed my daughter.
You're smart.
I will make you
the first female general in Nanxia.
Okay?
Okay.
Look.
I put it here.
I’m coming.
Mai, listen.
In all fighting, the direct method may be used for joining battle,
but indirect methods will be needed in order to secure victory.
Therefore, indirect tactics, efficiently applied,
are inexhaustible as Heaven and Earth.
Do you understand?
Come.
Let me tell you.
In the future, on the battlefield,
you will meet enemies stronger than you.
But remember what I said.
Don't fight them head-on.
We need to use tactics to win.
Understand?
I lost. I lost.
I can't breathe.
It's obvious that
we are outnumbered and weaker.
If this continues,
we won’t have
the determination to win, right?
Who said we will most certainly win?
I'm just kidding.
I'm really confident.
The training is over.
Let's go to eat.
It's time to eat.
Why are they going so orderly ?
I'm hungry.
Let's go. It's time to eat.
Wait.
Wait for me here.
I'll get their food back.
What if they find out?
With my skills,
they won't notice it even if I play as a bowl.
Let me take you to a beautiful place.
Okay?
Sure.
Let's go.
Young Marquis.
Let's eat.
If you don't eat, the food will get cold.
Is this the beautiful scenery you mentioned?
With these delicacies,
isn't it something?
They must think it's really delicious.
Eat.
Brother Tang.
Mai.
You eat here.
I'll be back soon.
No.
Mai.
Why are you here?
I knew you were here.
I came here to for you.
What’s up?
I have something to do.
Eating?
He is obviously here for Tang.
Who is that?
Young Marquis.
General Shang.
Brother Tang, let me tell you.
Just talk.
Don't touch.
Remember.
[City Guard Mansion]
Why are you still following me?
No.
I-I came out for a walk after eating because I'm boring.
A walk after eating?
Have you even eaten yet?
Then why are you walking?
Well,
do you have something to say?
No.
Tell me.
Mu Bai and the others
are always suspicious.
They said there is something between you and Brother Tang.
I told them there is nothing
between Mai and Brother Tang, right?
I-Is there anything?
You hesitated.
Put your hand back.
What is it?
Do you like him?
No.
Not even a bit.
What about this much?
No.
Does he like you?
Don't talk nonsense.
Calm down.
My biggest strength
is a strong sense of responsibility.
Since everyone asked me,
I have the responsibility
to figure this out.
Right?
Now you know, It's not like that.
Fine.
Then swear to me.
I, Mai...
Why should I swear to you?
What does this have to do with you?
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll beat you up.
Get out!
-Get out!
-Okay.
That's all for today.
I'll tell them.
They are waiting for me.
If I go out now,
will I meet Brother Tang?
Get lost!
I found that they lack of food recently.
Some of them went to Yuzhou to borrow provisions.
Okay. Go back and report immediately.
I also got another information.
The crown prince of Nanxia is in Qingzhou City.
He will also take the route to Yuzhou soon.
Crown prince...
I can see the whole picture just by looking at a small part of it.
The military discipline of Yuzhou Army is strict.
They are obviously trained from the battlefield.
Look at the physical differences.
It seems that Your Grace accept the challenge
because you have some hidden talent?
I've never been a general or lead any soldiers.
How can I be the talented one?
But in my camp,
everyone is brave and good at fighting.
I know that I can
accept the challenge.
Okay.
Let's wait and see on the arena.
Let's see.
The martial arts competition of Qingzhou and Yuzhou Army begins now.
The first battle is infantry battle.
Each army will send 20 people to close combat.
Use the drum as a signal.
One to get ready and two to go!
Three stops.
Before the third sound,
the one with more people standing wins.
But please remember,
Soldiers in both Qingzhou Army and Yuzhou Army
are the people of Nanxia.
Although we are practicing martial arts, we should be careful.
We shouldn't overdo.
The first round starts.
This...
We're about to lose.
Why are you not worried at all?
Our audience is not here yet.
It's already this hour.
The martial arts competition has begun.
General, should you go now?
No hurry.
We have strong soldiers and horses.
I don't have to go.
What you did today
is really worrying me.
Although I'm a woman,
I can understand some things.
What are you doing?
I have something to ask you.
I'll get up after you answer.
How are you going to ask like this?
Sit on the chair and ask.
Just one question.
Go ahead.
You dragged Qingzhou Army to participate in martial arts competition.
Do you have other intentions?
One question.
Come on, get up.
No.
Are you going to help Shang Yizhi?
He's a criminal.
You shouldn't take your old relationship into consideration.
General.
You can't lie to
your wife.
Pass it on.
A win is a win.
Don't push too hard.
If we hurt a few,
people will say our Yuzhou Army bullies the weak.
I picked them myself.
I know what to do.
In the first game,
Yuzhou Army won!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
We won!
Great!
A bunch of losers.
That's easy.
Report!
Who won?
Yuzhou Army won the first round.
Okay, I got it.
Madam.
One is my old master,
another one is the crown prince.
H-How can I choose?
Who will be the winner of this martial arts competition?
It depends on God's will.
Young Marquis has accepted the fate.
Accept my fate?
Let me put it this way.
Yes, I accept it.
I don’t understand.
Mu Bai is the most skilled among us.
Why don’t you let him go?
Calm down.
Let's follow the plan I told you.
What plan did you tell me?
Didn't I tell you?
I have a better candidate.
Mr. Yang.
General Shi.
You’re not in a hurry.
What's the rush?
The Yuzhou Army is strong in every aspects.
The show is about to start.
The second battle is cavalry battle.
With the drum as the command,
whoever takes the red silk from the other general
wins.
General.
In my opinion,
the Qingzhou Army was scared by us.
What a bunch of cowards.
It's not his fault.
Young Marquis has been favored since he was born.
He has never suffered a day.
It would be strange if he could lead an army well.
That also need you to agree
to play with him.
Wang Xun,
I've told you many times.
Watch your mouth.
General,
If you think I'm an eyesore,
I'll go down and play with them.
Okay.
On behalf of the Qingzhou Army, I'll fight against five.
Tang Shaoyi.
He's alone.
Can he do it?
I forgot to tell you.
He wants to join our Qingzhou Army long ago.
If we can,
take him.
If we fail this time,
Yang Xuan will kill me.
Don't worry.
I haven't told you yet.
He used to be
Yinbao City's lieutenant of cavalry.
Did you see the maroon horse he rode?
He trained it himself.
I saw the maroon horse.
The color of his horse has nothing to do with
he fighting against five.
This move is called "Manipulation."
Remember.
Manipulation.
[Order]
Kill them!
We won!
The Qingzhou Army won!
Yes! Yes!
We won!
Won.
How did he win?
You saw it.
I'm only half dead now.
Can he join our Qingzhou Army this time?
Let's wait and see.
Pass it down.
The martial arts competition is over today.
Mr. Yang,
why?
With the Yuzhou Army's strength,
we lose even if we draw.
Let alone losing one game.
Besides,
how do you know they don't have countermeasures?
Mr. Yang,
even if we lose,
we can just take Shang Yizhi back to the prison.
We'll compensate him some food at most.
What does it have to do with Mr. Yang?
Besides, our Yuzhou Army is trying hard.
We will win the third round.
Mr. Yang,
why are you discouraging at this critical moment?
Fine.
I was just saying.
Military orders are like a mountain,
and can't be changed easily.
That's right.
If we stop now,
as if our Yuzhou Army is afraid of them.
The third round starts.
Third round.
Offense-defense Battle.
According to the draw,
Yuzhou is the attacker and Qingzhou is the defender.
The hourglass is the timer.
Within the time limit,
Yuzhou wins if it took the enemy's flag.
If it failed to take the flag, Qingzhou wins.
Protect the flag.
Young Marquis.
Sprinkle the powder.
What is this? What...
The game is over.
Qingzhou Army won!
We won!
You guys are cheating.
What are you talking about?
Who are you calling cheater?
You cheated!
Don't you know war is full of tricks?
The Beimo soldiers have more evil tricks than this.
Are you accusing them of cheating on the battlefield?
You...
Shi Dachun.
Did you do it on purpose?
Mr. Yang,
Why do you say that?
You've always been the military inspector.
You are watching my every moves.
Soldiers fight bravely.
Mai.
I’ve arranged someone
to send you out tomorrow.
As for how to go to Beimo,
you have to figure it out yourself.
What do you mean, General Shi?
Where did you take Young Marquis?
I am not the one who took him.
The crown prince wanted to kill Young Marquis.
As for how to save Young Marquis,
there is nothing I can do now.
Mr. Shi, please wait.
Since Young Marquis is my friend,
I won’t leave him alone.
You are so righteous.
General Shi.
I always speak my mind.
As far as I know,
the crown prince is here for military power,
right?
You even know that?
Yes.
Because the crown prince has no military power,
so he is in an awkward position in the imperial court.
He tried to win me over and over again.
I didn't want to get involved in the fight between the princes.
So I didn't give him a clear answer.
Young Marquis has just left Shengdu.
His foundation is not yet stable in the local.
Young Marquis's shallow foundation
is the bargaining chip for us to rescue him.
Do you have an idea?
Is there any martial arts competition in Yuzhou recently?
Yes.
Young Marquis.
Uncle Shi.
It’s all on you.
Young Marquis is still so naughty.
Young Marquis.
You're good at using troops.
I admit it.
All the provisions I promised will be delivered.
Thank you, Uncle Shi.
General.
The crown prince was abducted by the Beimo Army.
Please save His Majesty.
Young Marquis.
It's an emergency.
Let's go inside and discuss it.
Let's go.
What? You want me to save him?
Save the crown prince.
You lead the army.
You are in luck.
Uncle Shi,
I’m grateful
for your help.
But we both know
why crown prince came here.
Now you want me to save him?
I want to avoid him instead.
I didn't make it clear to the Young Marquis.
It's normal for you to misunderstand.
Fine.
[Shi]
I proposed to train soldiers
because I want a military coalition between Qingzhou and Yuzhou.
A military coalition?
Chang Yuqing led the elite cavalries of Beimo
to attack Yinbao and disappeared.
According to the military report,
there's no news regarding Qinshan sentry.
I guess it's the fall of the sentry.
Based on this,
the final target of the Beimo Army
should be the Jingyang Pass.
The people from Beimo worked together from inside
to breach Jingyang.
[Shi]
This is just a speculation.
But the Beimo Army is strong.
Your Qingzhou Army is weak.
If Qingzhou and Yuzhou can't form a military coalition,
we will lose Qingzhou and Yuzhou will be in danger.
By then, when the Beimo Army marches into Jingyang,
no one can stop them at the border.
I see.
You won the martial arts competition this time.
You can convince the people.
If a military coalition formed between Qingzhou and Yuzhou,
you'll be the commander in chief.
If you become the commander in chief of Qingzhou and Yuzhou,
the sword that tries to kill you
will become a shield to protect you.
Uncle Shi is really cunning.
No.
You are old but vigorous.
No, no, not old.
It doesn't matter if I'm old.
I hope you can be a good general
like the Old Marquis.
[Shi]
Don’t worry, Uncle Shi.
I’ll lead the military coalition to save crown prince.
I'm late.
Please forgive me.
[City Guard Mansion]
Shang Yizhi.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I can kill you
or let you go.
But you saved me.
We are even.
General Shi Dachun sneaked into Beimo's camp
and captured more than 20 of them.
He bravely saved the crown prince.
He's highly skilled in scheming and made great contributions.
He will be rewarded with 1,000 dan of military provisions.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
The Beimo Army is very aggressive.
In my opinion,
only a military coalition between Qingzhou and Yuzhou can protect the people.
Defend Shengdu to fight against foreign enemies.
Of course we’ll listen to General Shi.
I was attacked by bandits in Beimo.
Moreover, the enemy situation in Beimo is unpredictable.
I must go back to Shengdu immediately
to report to His Majesty.
Farewell, Your Highness.
General Shang.
The next time we meet,
It will be our first meeting.
Young Marquis didn't us down.
[To Counsellor Xu, we've received the provisions in Yuzhou]
Not only did he get the provisions,
but also became the commander in chief of Qingyu military coalition
Send His Grace's order.
Wei Peng and Liang Shao will guard Qingzhou.
Select a troop of elite soldiers
and follow me to Yuzhou.
Yes.
Awesome!
What's wrong? Can you add more?
More!
Good!
Way to go! Way to go!
Lieutenant.
What's wrong?
Is this the strength of your Yuzhou Army?
Lieutenant Tang,
your training is very strange.
We've never seen or trained like this.
Aren't you bullying Lieutenant Wang?
Yes, you are bullying us.
Yes, bullies, bullies.
How can you be defeated by a posture when you have the strength?
If Nanxia Army
gave up like this,
how can we resist the Beimo Army?
Lieutenant Wang,
can you do more?
Again.
Okay.
Okay!
Awesome!
We just settled down Mr. Xu
and stationed Qingzhou soldiers.
Then we came here to inspect the training of Yuzhou Army.
Now both Qingzhou and Yuzhou Army are yours.
You can rest assured now, right?
The Qingzhou and Yuzhou Army has two forces now.
How to combine these two forces
is what I'm most worried about.
Well done.
You look like a general now.
I'm not kidding.
I'm really worried.
It's simple.
As long as you take these recruits
out of the city.
No matter it’s bandits or a ranger,
as long as they can fight two real battles,
they'll be successful.
You're so smart.
It would be better if you could stay by my side forever.
Enough.
Don't whine in broad daylight.
Your problem is solved,
I have to think about a way to get to Beimo.
What Beimo?
There's still a war.
What does war have to do with me?
I'm neither a soldier nor a general.
Let's go.
I mean after the war is over,
we can go to Beimo with you.
When can we finish this war?
If you beat away Beimo, then there's Xihu.
You want to me to stay by your side forever?
I mean,
after this is over,
no one can change my decision.
I...
Don’t follow me.
What’s wrong, Mai?
Why pulling a long face?
Did someone bully you?
Brother.
I have something to tell you.
I plan to go to Beimo.
You've made your decision?
I know I can't persuade you.
But good men are ambitious.
If there is something you want to do,
try your best to do it.
Stop nagging
like a sissy.
Brother,
I have something to tell you.
Xiu'er…
Mai.
Now we’re going to face enemies.
I don't want any relationships.
I'm just saying.
Look how scared you are.
Let’s go.
Mai.
Let’s have a drink before you leave.
Okay.
You've been busy all day. Go back and rest.
Yes.
Are you here to make peace?
I have something to tell you.
Let's talk inside.
Let's talk here.
Go ahead.
I’m leaving.
I plan to go to Jingyang Pass to try my luck.
Maybe I can get out.
I don’t understand.
Why do you have to go to Beimo?
A woman going there alone.
Is it even safe?
Don't you know me?
I cherish my life the most.
I never do dangerous things.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have survived until now.
What about Xu Xiu'er?
Are you going to leave her alone in Yuzhou?
Is that taking responsibility?
I've entrusted Xiu'er to Brother Tang.
But Brother Tang is careless.
If you want to help taking care of Xiu'er,
you can do that.
Stop!