[English subtitles are available]
[Fighting for love]
[Episode 14]
Brother, look!
Let's go.
Go.
Mai.
Except a few fire pits we found,
we can't find any tracks.
Brother.
look up.
Look at the branches.
They are so dense.
Look over there.
It's bald.
They cut down the branches
and tied them behind the heavy truck
to erase all traces.
I know the direction.
Come with me.
Mai.
Where did you learn all this?
I like to study tactics.
If you'd like,
we can discuss it together when we get back to the camp.
Okay.
It is worth bringing you along.
Looks like this is the military camp of the Beimo Army.
Mai.
Let me teach you.
Men
are kind in nature.
Their natures are much the same.
Mai.
Brother.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Okay. Let’s go.
[Marquis Dingnan's Mansion]
Your Highness.
The Beimo Army is invading south.
I'm afraid some spies might sneak into Shengdu.
I’m ordered to guard Marquis Dingnan's Mansion.
No one is allowed to go in and out.
Your Highness.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
[Marquis Dingnan's Mansion]
Greetings, Mr. Xu.
What happened?
Sir,
I’m ordered to deliver the message to you.
Marquis Dingnan's Mansion has been surrounded by the imperial guards.
Princess Shenghua seems to be under house arrest.
His Majesty has ordered Young Marquis to return to Shengdu.
I'm afraid the imperial edict will arrive soon.
It's very dangerous.
Please ask Young Marquis to leave
to avoid emperor's special envoy.
I understand.
Let's go.
Brother, I'm not going.
Why not?
You found the military camp of the Beimo Army.
That's meritorious.
Isn't this the mission Mr. Xu assigned you?
Go ahead.
Mai.
Don’t move.
-Let go of me!
-Stay still!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Don't move!
Keep acting up.
Why did you stop?
Leaving the camp without permission?
You are getting bolder.
Pull him up.
Get up.
Same to you.
You're not bad either.
What do you mean?
I guess you haven’t reported it.
Otherwise, it's the patrol camp waiting for me.
If others know there is a deserter in the Eighth Squad,
I will be embarrassed.
If I were a deserter,
I wouldn't have come back to you.
Enough.
I don't think you're talented,
but you're the best at making excuses.
Take him away.
Wait.
You don't like me.
Why are you talking so much?
Why am I talking so much?
Because rats like you
got into the military camp,
and weakened Nanxia's military power.
It allows the people of Beimo march straight in.
I don't know how your parents taught you.
What did you say?
I said your parents are cowards.
Princess Shenghua also sent a letter saying
that His Majesty ordered Young Marquis to return to Shengdu.
I'm afraid that emperor's special envoy coming to Yuzhou
is not a good thing.
If we get the information about the enemy,
we must relocate immediately.
If that's the case,
we should fight
the Beimo Army.
Yes.
Only then
we can lead the army and leave Yuzhou above board.
Report!
General.
We've found them.
The middle troops of Beimo is hiding
in a valley 300 miles away.
How did you find them?
Thanks to Mai’s intelligence.
We found their camp because of him.
And we didn’t alert them.
Mai.
Yes.
Mai is familiar with wilderness camp defense.
If it weren’t for Mai,
I wouldn’t have come back with this information.
You’re right.
Mai has the skill of a general.
Sir.
Young Marquis better think about
how to deal with Mai.
What?
Why punish Mai when he made a contribution?
He left the camp without permission.
He should be punished for deserting.
He should be executed according to the law.
General.
Lieutenant Tang,
why are you doing this?
Even though Mai doesn’t know the rules,
Lieutenant Tang has been in the army for years.
You should understand that military orders are like a mountain.
Sir.
I understand.
But Mai left the camp to spy on the enemy.
It was meritorious.
Beat him!
Move!
Hit him! Hit him!
Harder! Hit him! Hit him!
Stop right now!
You two split up.
Which camp are you from?
Tell me.
The Seventh Battalion.
Fighting in the military.
Each of you should be flogged twenty times.
Sir.
He started it.
Execute Immediately.
Sir,
he left the camp without permission.
Left the camp?
When?
Five days ago.
I am asking him.
Five days ago afternoon.
Am I right?
He's just a deserter.
Why did you leave the camp?
No comment.
Look, he feels guilty.
Take him away.
No.
Why did you arrest you?
Leaving the camp is a big matter.
It should be reported to the general for punishment.
Take him away.
I want to see General Shang.
Come in.
General,
there were two people fighting in the camp.
And were arrested by the patrol camp.
After inquiry,
both of them belong to the Seventh Battalion.
I was going to punish them according to the military rules,
but I found out that one of them had left the camp for several days.
Please make a decision.
Let them in.
Yes.
Bring him here.
General, you should ask
what happened first.
Mai.
Tell me.
It seems that there's a bias.
General.
I caught him first.
You should ask me first.
What's your name?
Your Excellency,
I’m the sergeant in the Eighth Squad of the Fourth Platoon of the Seventh Battalion.
My name is Wang Qi.
You first.
Will you believe
what I said?
If it's true,
I’ll believe you.
Mai left the camp without permission.
I saw him when he came back.
Then he hit me.
I had no choice but to fight back.
And people from the patrol camp saw me just in time.
He left the camp without permission.
I didn't report it in time.
I also made a mistake.
I'm willing to accept the punishment.
Why do I think
this is unreasonable?
General.
I told you you wouldn't believe me.
Calm down.
Mai.
Is what Wang Qi said true?
Yes.
Did you see that, general?
He admitted it himself.
If you insist on being biased,
I'm afraid
those soldiers will be disappointed.
General will handled this impartially.
But according to military discipline,
leaving the camp and fighting are two different things.
They should be deal with separately.
Do you agree?
Yes.
Okay.
Let’s talk about the fight first.
Mai.
You started it.
Yes.
Why did you do that?
It's a military secret.
I can't tell you.
General will handle it impartially.
You may leave.
Yes.
Go ahead.
I followed Lieutenant Tang to investigate the location of Beimo's middle troops.
Due to an emergency,
I didn’t report in time.
Mai is willing to be punished.
Can you make a bigger lie?
General.
I can prove what Mai said is true.
I’ve told you.
Without Mai,
I couldn’t finish the mission.
Mai deserves the credits.
Did you really find the army of Beimo?
How did you find them?
If Mai hadn’t found the campsite of Beimo,
we could have been attacked at any time.
Don’t mind Mai’s leaving.
Lieutenant Tang,
since the truth has come to light,
I will make the verdict.
Do you agree?
But sir...
I'm sure you'll be fair.
Okay.
Mai, solider in Eighth Squad of Fourth Platoon of Seventh Battalion,
left the camp without permission. He should be executed according to the law.
But considering his merit in investigating military situation,
merits equal demerits.
The death penalty can be exempted. He will be imprisoned for three days.
Sir,
as a lieutenant of cavalry,
I didn’t stop Mai in time.
I’m willing to take the punishment for Mai.
Military orders are like a mountain.
No more pleading.
Yes, sir.
Sergeant Wang Qi
didn't report the army's whereabouts in time.
He should be flogged ten times.
You two will be flogged
twenty times for fighting.
Execute immediately.
Any objection?
No.
General.
Stop!
The general has ordered that
for the sake of fairness,
I will execute the bludgeon myself.
You may leave.
Your turn.
I'm sorry.
I missed.
Why are you here?
I came to see you.
It's all my fault.
It’s not your fault.
I left the camp without permission.
By the way,
these are all good medicines.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Let me apply the ointment for you.
I can apply it myself.
Go back.
I thought
that's all I can do for you.
You don't have to feel guilty.
You are the commander in chief.
You have to convince others.
Besides,
if you can't distinguish the reward and punishment,
I’ll suffer in the future.
Mai.
Let me ask you something.
You are lying down like this
and can't move a single step.
What if you want to go to the toilet,
what should you do?
Why do you ask?
Are you done? What do you want?
I can help you.
Okay, I'll stop.
I'm just kidding.
Besides,
I can't stand that smell.
Since we've found the Beimo Army,
what's your plan?
My uncle
wants me to take the chance to return to Shengdu.
And Mr. Xu wants me
to take the chance of going to the battlefield to leave Yuzhou.
Even so,
it's my first time
going to the battlefield.
I feel a little...
Afraid?
Are you looking down on me from the bottom of your heart?
Fear is the most normal reaction of a person.
I’m afraid too.
When Chang Yuqing attacked Yinbao City,
I was so scared that
I didn't even dare to move.
But if I don't rush forward desperately,
I might not even have a chance to live.
It seems that
Mr. Xu made the right choice.
But Mai,
The number of Qingyu military coalition
is less than Beimo Army's 30%.
How can we fight them?
It's about the quality of the soldiers and horses, not quantity.
If we can make a thorough plan,
we might not lose.
Do you have a plan?
Mai.
Y-Y-Your butt…
Gosh.
Look at you.
Just because of your little trouble,
I even forgot my butt hurts.
I will always remember
your kindness to me.
It's okay.
Let’s get down to business.
After Beimo opens the border of Jingyang,
they will be more cautious while fighting back.
When Brother Tang and I
went for investigation, we found out that
they brought a lot of army provisions.
I'm sure they won't be fast.
If we can get here in advance,
lay in ambush here,
we can just wait for them.
There will be a different result.
Yelanggou?
That's right.
We are fighting for speed.
We give up all the provisions
and only bring food on the way.
What will the soldiers eat?
If we win,
there will be food from the Beimo Army.
What if we lose?
Lose?
Why do you still need food?
You're burning bridges.
Young Marquis,
it's possible.
This plan
is too...
Yes.
But only when you're steady  the morale of the army be stable.
If you have any hesitation,
you'd better give up
and stay in Yuzhou
to save the soldiers.
Think about it.
I don't have time to think about it.
This is the only way.
If I don’t succeed, I’ll die.
Mai.
I trust you.
Not me.
From now on,
trust yourself.
You can do it.
It's all here.
Tie them tightly.
Okay.
Come, give me a hand.
Come on.
One, two, go.
There's more here.
Here.
I didn't expect
Young Marquis to be so decisive.
You can speed up a lot when traveling light.
It’s Mai’s idea.
I was right.
Mai indeed has the captainship.
Sir.
I have a question.
Go ahead, Young Marquis.
During this expedition,
we took all the elites.
There are less than 1,000 soldiers guarding the city.
If we catch up with the enemy's ambush,
we might lose the city.
What about the people in the city?
Young Marquis is kind-hearted.
But as the commander in chief,
you should focus on a bigger picture.
Sometimes, we have to sacrifice
for a greater good.
But the lives of the people are also lives.
They have the right to live.
If we insist to do this,
we are no different from the Beimo Army.
You're wise, Young Marquis.
Chen Qi,
who are you to frame my brother?
Get out!
Marshal.
What are you doing? Let's go.
I'm not going out.
I’d like to ask you.
My brother worked so hard to breach Jingyang.
Not only did the Marshal not reward him,
but also framed my brother
for killing Nanxia captives.
And put the blame on my brother.
Don't treat everyone as fools.
Aren't you afraid that my brother's reputation in the army is too good
and no one will obey you in the future?
How dare you!
Cui Yan.
Get out of here!
Cui Yan,
you have a good uncle.
If you feel sorry that
he's still throwing away pride for you at this age,
let him worry less.
This has nothing to do with my uncle.
I'm talking about my brother.
Your brother?
Chang Yuqing breached Jingyang
was under my order.
What reward do you think he should receive?
Chang Yuqing ignored the military order
and led troops to attack Yinbao without permission.
What he did alert the enemy.
What crime will that be?
Do you really want me to give him justice?
I...
I've already let him off the hook
so that he can make amends.
If you really think it's unfair,
you can make a new decision.
No need.
Greetings, Marshal.
Marshal is fair in rewarding and punishing,
I have no objection.
Brother.
Shut up!
Apologize to the Marshal.
Brother.
Apologize.
I was rude just now.
Please forgive me.
You disrespected the military discipline and disrespected your superior.
Go get ten strokes yourself.
Although the provisions are a few days late,
but it's finally here.
Tell the armies,
we will strike camp tomorrow
and go south.
Yes.
Back then,
I had a quarrel with you
because you couldn't go shopping with me.
Now my wish has come true.
You don't need to lead the army.
You can stay at home with me every day.
Mr. Xu.
Mrs. Shi.
Mr. Xu is here.
Have a seat.
General Shi.
With such a leisure time,
isn't it good?
I don't have to work hard,
it's all good.
Young Marquis can be independent,
I'm very pleased.
I'm here to inform you.
We found the main location of the Beimo Army.
The military coalition will strike camp immediately
and take the lead.
Young Little Marquis is determined to fight the enemy.
I will guard the rear.
But the Beimo Army and military coalition
are quite different in numbers.
How many soldiers does Young Marquis plan to lead?
How many soldiers is he going to keep?
As you said,
there is a huge difference in military power between the two.
Sir,
this military coalition fought against the enemy to protect the country.
But we also have to protect the people.
If there are fewer soldiers in Yuzhou,
what should I do
if the Beimo Army came?
That's exactly what Young Marquis was worried about.
I want to ask you, in your heart,
between securing the country and protecting the people,
which one is more important?
How about this?
Mai.
You’re back.
Erdan.
Do you miss me?
Of course.
You had a hard time.
No, it's not.
Not at all.
Have you had enough rest?
Sergeant.
What is it?
People who know the matter
know that you're in confinement.
People who don't might think you did something good.
Sergeant,
I did do something rewarding.
Sergeant, how could you forget?
My big butt has recovered.
How is yours?
Me too.
Why are you laughing?
To be honest,
we're going to march in two days.
Are you sure you are fine?
Sergeant, don’t worry.
The butt is fine.
It won't embarrass us.
See? See?
Qiang.
See?
You have guts.
Now you look like a soldier in Eighth Squad.
I'm serious.
We are really going to a battlefield.
If your big ass hurts,
just let us know.
We will carry you to the battlefield.
Sergeant,
something is wrong with you.
What’s wrong with me?
Why are you so nice to Mai?
What’s so strange about that?
Sergeant has always been like this.
Yes.
What kind of person am I?
Besides,
I don’t want to stop Mai from
making contributions for our Seventh Battalion.
Mai.
Come out.
Let's go.
Go.
Sergeant, where are they going?
Coming.
Have you recovered?
Almost.
General Shang asked for me?
I want you to see him.
What's wrong with him?
He's been restless all morning.
He must have something on his mind.
He won't tell me no matter how I ask him.
I want to see if you have any idea.
He is inside?
Okay, I'll go take a look.
We will departure tomorrow.
Is everything ready?
We've also selected
people to guard Yuzhou City.
What's going on?
You are not saying anything.
It's strange.
After listened to what you said that day,
I thought about it all night.
I found out that
I'm more afraid.
I don't know much about the imperial court,
but I can understand one thing.
He used to be very straightforward.
That's because you were just a Marquis with no power.
You don't have the ability to settle down.
But now,
there's a whole Qingyu military coalition stands behind you.
If he wants to hurt you again,
he has to think twice.
Besides, the most urgent thing now is to fight against foreign enemies.
With his position,
of course he won't disregard the overall situation.
What are you afraid of?
I remember everything you said.
I understand.
But I'm not afraid of death.
Then what are you afraid of?
If I only care about my own life,
am I be worthy of
the soldiers that follow me?
You may not believe me.
I'd rather be a soldier that follows order
than a general
who is responsible for everyone's life.
Once I talk,
a decision will be made.
It's fine if it's right.
If it's wrong,
how many soldiers
will die
because of my wrong decision.
My father once said,
a general builds his success on thousands bones.
The so-called great generals
are created
from countless flesh and blood.
Among these bones,
there are enemies'
and our own people's.
Since you chose this path,
the only thing you can do is to go on without hesitation.
You know better than me
how fierce the Beimo soldiers are.
Our soldiers following me,
they will have a slim chance of surviving.
There are two reasons
why the soldiers choose to join the army.
First, to protect our country,
and second, bring glory to their ancestors.
Since they chose to join the army,
there is the only way.
Go to the battlefield, forget about life and death,
so one day they will be rewarded and conferred with a title.
They chose you and trusted you.
Why don't you trust yourself?
If you can't make a decisive decision,
they will be cowardly on the battlefield.
Then they'll die for sure.
Have you figured it out?
What?
I think I've figured it out.
That's good.
We will strike camp tomorrow.
Go back and get ready.
I-I need more time.
Soldiers,
the people of Beimo breached our gate
and destroyed our home.
They killed 100,000 men of Nanxia.
This blood feud
is irreconcilable.
Now, the elites of the two armies
have formed an alliance.
We will never return until we breach Beimo.
We won't return until we break the Beimo!
Cheers!
All of you, go!
Here is the imperial edict.
Marquis Dingnan, Shang Yizhi, the Guard General of Qingzhou, accept the edict.
Sir,
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
It's a long journey.
May I know your name?
What are you doing?
My surname is Jin.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Jin.
You don't need to read the imperial edict.
I know what it is.
Nowadays, the Beimo Army is at the border.
Jingyang Pass has been lost.
They will go south in a moment.
We, the Qingyu military coalition, will fight
to protect our home.
Sir,
we're facing an enemy.
let's not talk about
manners and etiquettes.
I'll go to the battlefield first.
Wait.
You don't have to tell me.
I know what you're worried about.
The city is well prepared to defense the enemy.
It will protect you.
When I return in triumph,
let's drink three more cups, okay?
Military secrets are the most fleeting of all.
Protecting our country is the priority
Mr. Jin,
protect yourself.
Okay.
Let's go.
What do you mean?
All troops, depart!
Special envoy,
you must be tired from your long journey.
Why don’t you stay in the city for a few days
and wait for General Shang’s return?
Please. Please.
General Shang is a loyal man.
But there is something wrong.
No, no.
How can I wait if I have His Majesty's order?
Let's go after him.
Guards!
General Shi.
W-What are you doing?
I’m trying to protect the special envoy.
General Shang left in a hurry,
so he didn’t explain clearly.
The main force of the Beimo Army
is only a few hundred miles away from Yuzhou.
You didn't see meet them when you came?
No.
You are lucky, thanks to His Majesty.
Yuzhou and Yangshui are the main line of going south.
If no one can stop the main force of the Beimo Army,
they will go straight
to Shengdu and disturbed His Majesty.
What should we do?
Besides,
this...
If the Qingyu military coalition successfully stops the enemy,
special envoy is also a part of the contribution.
The Beimo Army is really that close?
How dare I lie to the special envoy?
If it wasn’t too late,
General Shang wouldn’t have risked his life ignoring the edict
to fight the enemy.
The special envoy is here under the order.
I have the responsibility to ensure the safety of the special envoy.
The city is safer than outside.
You'd better enter the city
and let me fulfill my duty as a host.
Thank you, General Shi.
Please.
Let's go.
Where should we go?
From the map...
Young Marquis,
This place should be...
Sir.
General Shi sent a letter.
He told us not to worry.
What do you mean?
He kidnapped the special envoy?
He's still alive.
But no information can get out of Yuzhou City.
It's too hasty.
Young Marquis,
I think we should focus on
the current war first.
If the military coalition can win,
there will be rooms to turn.
We must win this battle.
We can’t let Uncle Shi down.
Otherwise, all the efforts
will be in vain.
Yes.
Mu Bai.
Pass my order.
We have to arrive Yelanggou before sunset.
Yes.