[English subtitles are available]
[Fighting for love]
[Episode 12]
Stop right there!
You have to make it clear to me today.
Otherwise, you can't leave.
Didn't I tell you I'm going to Beimo?
-You and I...
-What Beimo?
You've arranged everyone well.
What about me?
Who will arrange for me?
You have Mr. Xu, right?
Mu Bai and Brother Tang.
All of them are better than me.
Stop it.
Don't talk about others.
Let's talk about you today.
You can't leave if you don't make it clear.
Why must you go to Beimo?
Why should I tell you?
Let me tell you.
In this world,
not everything revolves around you.
Young Marquis.
What did you call me?
Nice.
Young Marquis.
You are a liar.
What did I lie to you?
From the beginning, when you were on the street
holding a broken bowl
and a worn-out ball, you started deceiving me.
Now,
you've caused me infatuated
and sleepless at night.
I see your face every night, whether my eyes are open or closed.
You stole my heart.
Let me tell you.
I regret meeting you.
Now,
you call me Young Marquis?
You call me...
Shut up!
I won't call you Young Marquis anymore.
Shang Yizhi, let me tell you.
In this world,
not everyone is like you
who has clothes at hand and food on the table.
We are different.
I'm a good citizen.
You are a liar.
Fine.
I'll tell you now.
Calm down.
Listen.
Okay, I'll calm down.
Go ahead.
My surname is Han.
My name is Han Maisui.
Even your name is fake.
My father was Duke Shengguo.
She's such a big kid now.
She still sleeps beside you every day.
It won't last long.
It's almost the age for a marriage proposal.
There's still some time before the proposal.
Darling.
Do you have a plan?
Honey.
I want Mai to marry Qi.
What do you think?
They are brother and sister.
Dear.
You adopted Qi.
He’s not Mai’s biological brother.
Why can’t they get married?
But I don't want to get married.
I just want to play with Chen Qi every day.
Weren't you sleeping just now?
Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Beimo bastards.
How dare you break into Duke Shengguo's mansion!
None of you can escape!
Brother is here.
Father, I'm late.
Please forgive me.
I'm fine.
Be careful.
Honey.
Qi.
Mai.
Do you remember what your father told you
to do when you're in danger?
I remember.
Go.
Mother!
Go!
Honey!
Father! Mother!
-Go!
Go!
That's brilliant.
You could tell such a tragic story
so systematically.
If you're good,
come on, tell me all the truth today.
Don't come over.
If you don't believe me even in this,
then I have nothing to say.
I am a liar.
Goodbye.
[City Guard Mansion]
Are you going to leave just like this?
If that person sent you to persuade me,
there's no need.
The military coalition will go out for training tomorrow morning.
Go with the army.
Let the army send you off.
Did he arrange it?
I can go by myself.
I won't bother him.
Mai.
We’ve been through life and death.
We also want to see you off.
Let's meet at the city gate at 5 a.m. tomorrow.
Okay, thank you.
Rest early.
Brother Tang told me you're leaving.
Xiu'er.
Stay here well.
I will ask Brother Tang to take care of you.
That's not what I meant.
I'm afraid someone will bully you.
When I'm done,
I'll come back to see you if I can.
Really?
I'll wait for you to come back.
Thank you, Xiu'er.
Welcome, Marshal.
General Chang, you and all the soldiers have worked hard.
I won't let you down.
Marshal.
The Nanxia people just sent the peace envoy to the capital.
They would never imagine
that Jingyang Pass has fallen into your hands.
Since ancient times, the strong will be the king.
Peace negotiation is just a stalling strategy.
Only a foolish king would believe it.
We won the first battle in Jingyang.
Soldiers, recuperate tonight.
After a rest,
we'll head south.
Yes, Marshal.
[Jingyang Pass]
[City Guard Mansion]
Didn't you say you would go with Mu Bai?
Why did you come out at dawn?
I don't want to bother them.
♫Autumn feelings linger, how empty it is♫
What are you doing?
♫Apricot flowers fall, and people still gather♫
Are you selling things at a stall?
I'm here to apologize to you.
I prepared something for you last night.
♫Many partings in this world♫
♫Unintentional acquaintance, fateful encounter♫
This is fur.
It's too cold in Beimo.
Wear more if you're cold.
♫Several rounds of sorrow with the bright moon♫
If your neck is cold,
put this on your neck.
It works.
♫Moon is in sight, but the person is distant♫
This is the enemy's armor.
Wear it when you're in danger.
♫Slowly approaching, I've long♫
I've tried this many times.
♫Forgotten his appearance♫
It's very useful.
It's better than confronting them.
Don't get caught in the rain.
Take an umbrella and don't catch a cold.
This is a night jacket.
♫Recalling the joy and sorrow between us♫
When it gets dark,
put it on to enforce your tasks.
Don't wear your own clothes.
♫How many laughs and tears did we once own?♫
This is a rope hook.
If you want to go high,
♫In the vast sea of people♫
take the hook off.
♫My thoughts are like vast smoke♫
Throw the hook up first.
♫Endless pursuit with bitterness♫
You don't need me to teach you this.
I don't know what clothes you like.
♫Recalling the joy and sorrow between us♫
I bought one of each fabric.
They were made according to your figure.
♫How many laughs and tears did we once own?♫
If you don't like these,
there are many different fabrics below.
♫Past events are like wind and rain♫
Look, they are of various colors.
As long as you can find a suitable tailor,
♫I have never regretted♫
the clothes made should not look bad.
When you go out,
pull some water in it and bring it with you.
Otherwise, it'll be too late
when you're thirsty.
By the way,
these are some herbs.
Angelica, for removing humidity.
Dried tangerine, Ganoderma.
Ganoderma can calm your nerves.
You prepared so much.
How can I take them with me?
♫Recalling the joy and sorrow between us♫
And these.
♫How many laughs and tears did we once own?♫
I put all the herbs
I can think of in it.
If you feel unwell,
♫In the vast sea of people♫
search for the proper one yourself.
I think you can find any herb you need.
♫My thoughts are like vast smoke♫
And this wormwood is special.
It can not only relieve breathing but also calm coughing.
♫Endless pursuit with bitterness♫
If there are mosquitoes
in the forest or woods,
you can light it up.
♫Recalling the joy and sorrow between us♫
It'll be useful.
No matter what you do outside,
♫How many laughs and tears did we once own?♫
take a knife with you.
I've prepared different types for you.
If you can hide one in your shoes,
♫Past events are like wind and rain♫
just put it in.
If you can't bring weapons,
♫I have never regretted♫
take this with you.
It's better to use this in close combats.
♫The years flow like a lament, like water♫
There's a firestick here.
It's dangerous at night. So light it up at night.
♫At the ends of the world, each with half a dream♫
There's a flint here.
When you need fire,
there'll be fire with just a strike.
If you get hurt,
there are all kinds of tools here.
I've prepared two sets for you.
There's another layer at the bottom of this box.
There are coins and silver pieces here.
And silver notes.
Don't use silver notes unless necessary.
It's easy to get into trouble if you show your money.
These are some jewelry.
I don't know what kind of jewelry you like.
Enough.
I bought some based on my preferences.
That box of jewelry
was also prepared for you.
If you don't like them,
just pawn them
and buy some delicious food.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm speaking illogically.
I didn't sleep last night.
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Wait.
♫We walk slowly, holding hands again♫
♫Time flows slowly until the end♫
♫We walk slowly, and this life is enough♫.
♫Knowing and cherishing you until old age♫
♫We met in the starry night and embraced in the wind and rain♫
[Protect the country and the people]
Young Marquis.
Sir, you are here.
With the assistance of Chang Yuqing, the Beimo Army carried out a strategy of external attack with internal coordination.
They took down Jingyang Pass
and are heading south.
Is their whole army heading south?
Yes.
The escape strategy is really amazing.
I heard that Chen Qi, the Marshal of the Beimo Army, was born as a commoner.
He made it to the top in such a short time.
He's quite something.
Sir.
What's the General of Beimo Army's name?
Chen Qi.
[Protect the country and the people]
Young Marquis.
General.
General!
Bad news!
-Bad news!
-What happened?
General.
Jingyang has been breached.
The Beimo army has entered the border.
Jingyang has been breached? Tell me in detail.
A few days ago,
the Beimo Army attacked Jingyang at night.
The City Guard died in battle.
Jingyang was breached.
The people from Beimo worked together from both inside and outside
and introduce the Beimo army into the Pass.
Beimo soldiers?
Who was the leader?
It's Chang Yuqing.
Chang Yuqing.
I didn’t expect him to breach Jingyang
after he sieged Yinbao.
Beimo Army is so strong.
How can we defeat them?
I don't want to die in vain.
Young Marquis.
What happened?
Chen Qi and his army have broken through Jingyang Pass.
You are soldiers,
soldiers who protect our country.
Those who are afraid of death, come out now!
If you're not afraid of death,
let's make Chen Qi pay with his blood!
Blood for blood!
I want to join the army.
Young Marquis.
I beg you.
Let me join the army, Young Marquis.
Say something, Young Marquis.
Why don't you allow me to join the army?
You are a woman.
The law doesn't allow women to join the army,
You will be beheaded.
I'm not afraid.
As long as you don't expose me.
Let me ask you.
Do you want to join the army for revenge?
Yes.
I've been looking for him for so many years.
I must see him.
I must ask him face-to-face
why he killed my parents.
I can avenge you.
I can leave anything to you.
But I can't leave this one to anyone else.
I beg you.
He's the commander-in-chief of the army.
Tell me how you will take revenge.
He will kill you
before you can get to him.
The two armies will confront each other.
As long as you put me on the battlefield,
I'll have a chance to see him.
I don't agree.
Why?
I've been to the infantry camp.
A dozen of men slept on the same bed.
How can you sleep with them?
Others can, so can I.
I think you're possessed.
I beg you.
Let me get into the infantry camp.
You'll live with so many men.
How inappropriate!
Fine.
Since you don't agree,
I'll charge straight into his camp.
You always threaten me.
You agree?
Would I dare to disagree?
What happened?
Father,
you didn't see what happened that day.
I was besieged
and fought hard.
But we were outnumbered.
That's why I was captured.
You were captured alive?
You are the Crown Prince of the country.
If everyone in the court
knows that you were captured alive,
Can you still be the Crown Prince?
Father! Father!
Father!
Please spare my life!
Father.
Did Shang Yizhi save you?
It's...
General Shi Dachun who saved me.
I heard that Shang Yizhi captured the leader of Beimo Army
and collaborated with General Shi Dachun.
They attacked the bandits from Beimo by surprise.
In that case, I escaped from danger.
Your Majesty.
Who allowed you to come in?
[The Beimo army suddenly arrived. Our forces fought desperately to defend the city, but we were overpowered in the fierce battle.]
[Seven days ago, the frontier defense was breached, Jingyang fell, and the defending general Luo Yi died in battle. The enemy forces then marched southward.]
Jingyang has been breached.
How could it be?
[City Guard Mansion]
I was prepared.
But your kiss
messed me up.
That's bullying.
[Qingyu military coalition's camp]
Dude.
Are you new here?
Which squad are you in?
Infantry, Eighth Squad, Seventh Battalion.
Me too.
What's your name?
My name is Zhang Erdan.
Zhang Erdan, two eggs?
When my mother gave birth to me,
a hen of ours gave birth to two eggs.
My father said I was lucky.
So he named me Zhang Erdan.
What's your name?
Interesting.
My name is Maisui.
You can also call me Mai.
Maisui, wheat ear?
Did your mother give birth to you
when your family's wheat was in full harvest?
That's true.
You like shooting birds?
Yes.
Stop!
[Infantry, Zhang Erdan, Eighth Squad, Seventh Battalion]
Are you two of our squad's soldiers?
Yes.
[Infantry, Zhang Erdan, Eighth Squad, Seventh Battalion]
Look.
Didn't they send us two monkeys?
How old?
16.
19.
I'm wondering how the land of Yuzhou
nurtured the two fools of you.
We are not fools.
We are soldiers from Eighth Squad, Seventh Battalion.
I'm not a fool either.
I'm also a soldier of the Eighth Squad, Seventh Battalion.
The Eighth Squad is full of fools...
No.
All of us are elites.
What skills do you have?
How can you get into the Eighth Squad?
Because of this.
Look.
Isn't this something for kids to shoot birds?
Sergeant.
He can actually shoot stones
in a straight line.
And the depths of the stone marks are the same every time.
Good, you're good.
You're qualified to be Eighth Squad's soldier.
What about you?
What are you capable of?
Sergeant.
He was sent by Guard Mu himself.
It is said that he came to Yuzhou in the same carriage as the general.
No wonder.
It turned out
you came here through personal connections.
I don’t know General Shang well.
I just took a ride.
Stand up.
What's your name?
Maisui.
Okay.
Although you're not capable,
you should know how to work the night shift.
You two will be on duty tonight.
Our squad's mission
is to guard the armory of the Seventh Battalion.
Be careful.
Yes.
Let's go.
Don't move!
How dare they bully new recruits?
It's the military camp.
It's normal.
Just get used to it.
Sorry, bro.
I'm not good enough.
I've implicated you, making you accompany me for the night shift.
Nothing.
We came together.
We should take care of each other.
Well said.
You sleep first tonight.
Come to replace me when you wake up.
Okay.
Let's find a bed.
Let’s go.
Mai.
This one is vacant. I’ll sleep here.
Okay.
Assemble!
[Qingyu military coalition]
Let's go.
What are you doing?
What do they want?
Forget it.
The new recruits of the Seventh Battalion.
[Battalion Commander Lu Gang]
Fall out.
Listen up.
I don’t care what you did before.
Since you're in the Seventh Battalion,
you are my soldiers from now on.
You must follow my rules.
First,
our infantry is the hardest and most tiring soldiers in the army.
Whether it's fighting the enemy or traveling day and night,
you must depend on your own legs.
If anyone can't endure hardships or tiredness,
get lost as soon as possible.
I don't need cowards.
Second,
we infantry place the highest importance on coordinated formations.
In simple terms, it's about obedience.
I've never liked those who behave disobediently.
If anyone is caught disobeying orders,
they will face immediate military punishment.
Is that clear?
Understood.
New recruits, return to your positions.
Yes.
Start training.
The essence of a soldier's swift mobility lies in the horse.
As cavalry,
trust in your warhorses
surpasses even trust in your comrades on the battlefield.
Treat your warhorses as kin,
ensuring they are well-fed and cared for,
so they can adeptly maneuver in times of war.
This is the first point.
On the battlefield, the sound of drums and battle cries is incessant.
During training,
deliberately expose your horses to these sounds,
so that in the heat of battle, they won't be easily startled.
Those who lose their horses in the face of the enemy
will be executed.
However, those who fight valiantly and lose their horses
won't face penalties.
Lieutenant Tang.
Someone outside the camp wants to see you.
It's training time. I don't want to see him.
They brought this.
[Liu] [Dong]
Liu.
There are so many people with the same name.
Are you sure Brother Tang is here?
We'll know soon.
Calm down.
You're so impatient.
Brother Tang!
It's Brother Tang!
It's really you.
Boss, you really are here.
It's good that you're alive.
Both of you have lost weight.
I asked around for a long time, but I couldn't find you.
How did you find this place?
When Yinbao was destroyed,
only the two of us survived
among the guarding soldiers.
We wanted to live an ordinary life.
But when the Beimo Army invaded,
how can we soldiers sit still?
So we came together to join the army again.
After inquiry, we heard that
there's someone with the same name as you.
We wanted to try our luck.
You're lucky.
Brothers.
Let's get drunk tonight.
Come with me.
-Let’s go.
-Okay.
-Let’s get drunk!
-Let’s go.
We didn't believe it was you at the door.
I just recognized...
Guard Mu.
Lieutenant Tang.
These two look unfamiliar.
They are good friends I met in Yinbao.
Hurry up. Greet Guard Mu.
Greetings, Guard Mu.
Nice to meet you.
They came to join the army today.
By the way, is General Shang here?
General Shang hasn’t entered the camp yet.
But it's not difficult.
Just tell Counsellor Xu when you see him.
I thought General Shang would be here
since you are here.
Just like you,
I came to send someone to join the army.
You know this person.
Who?
Mai.
Mai joined the army?
Where is he?
Eighth Squad, Fourth Platoon of the Seventh Battalion.
Okay.
I’ll take you to Mai.
Mai just joined the army today.
He must be busy.
Take care of these two brothers
and go later.
Okay.
Thank you, Guard Mu.
Let's go.
[Shang]
Move.
Chen Qi.
I’ll kill you.
Mai.
Mai. Enough.
Stop. Stop.
Stop it.
Mai.
Are you crazy?
Do you have to be like this in the training?
Let's go to the barracks.
Aren't you full of energy?
I'll let you climb as much as you can today!
Go!
Yes.
Hurry up.
Erdan.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Shang Yizhi silently took away
the military power of Yuzhou.
His ambition is obvious.
I have to guard against him.
It's better to clear a passage than to block.
The Beimo army is heading south.
They will attack Qingzhou and Yuzhou first.
Your Majesty, why don't you allow the Qingyu military coalition
to fight the enemy?
You mean...
At the beginning of leading troops,
it's natural for Shang Yizhi not to handle it with ease.
Besides, he's young and passionate.
He is bound to be eager for achievements.
If he dies on the battlefield,
it would be a good story.
Let me think about it.
Please leave.
I shall take my leave.
Pass my order.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Order Shang Yizhi, Marquis Dingnan,
to return to Shengdu immediately.
Block the Marquis Dingnan's Mansion.
No one is allowed to go out without an edict.
Don't let even a pigeon
fly out.
Yes, Your Majesty.