[English subtitles are available]
[Fighting for love]
[Episode 15]
General Shi.
Come.
We are in the countryside.
I don't have anything good to treat you.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Help yourself.
General Shi,
I want you to tell me the truth.
When can General Shang come back?
The military coalition
went to defend against enemies for Nanxia.
They will come back
when they kick all the soldiers of Beimo
out of Nanxia.
You just stay in Yuzhou City and rest assured.
I'll ask someone to inform you if there's any news.
Fine.
I'll just stay in the city for a few more days.
The military coalition left in a hurry.
There are many things that haven't been dealt with.
I'll drink with you
some other day.
Suit yourself, General Shi.
Come.
Qingzhou and Yuzhou have been out of control.
Find a way to get out of the city as soon as possible
and report it to His Majesty.
Go now.
Okay.
Stop. Where are you going?
I have a stomachache and need to go to the toilet.
Come back as soon as possible.
Okay.
Set up a camp here.
Ask the scouts to work in a three-shift system.
Yes, Marshal.
Set up a camp.
Here.
Brother, look at him.
Stop talking.
Recently, the army has been very anxious.
Remember to remind our men
to be alert at night.
He's been asserting dominance over you. Why are you defending him?
I'm just not convinced.
He is deep and cunning.
I don't know what His Majesty likes about him.
He even made him the commander of the three armies.
I think he's so unwise.
Stop talking nonsense.
Cui Yan,
no wonder your uncle always scolded you.
Sooner or later, you'll be in trouble due to your careless talk.
Alright.
Ask the men in the Kitchen Battalion
to cook more dishes tonight.
There will be a fierce battle soon.
Brother, how do you know?
You won't understand even if I tell you.
Let's go.
Brother,
I'll follow you.
I'll do whatever you say.
Our scouts delivered a message.
The enemy forces set up a camp
10 km north of our location.
In tomorrow's battle, we will dispatch cavalries first,
followed closely by infantries.
As long as Beimo also dispatches cavalries first,
they will lose their advantage
after they arrive at Yelanggou.
And their infantries will not be a threat.
Then it will be only a matter of time
to win the battle.
We still have one day to get ready.
Tell the kitchen to prepare steamed buns,
so that the soldiers can be full.
The entire army will launch an attack tomorrow morning.
General, how do you plan to deal with Beimo's cavalries?
[Wait for a chance at Yelanggou]
Mai, have some water.
Are you okay?
Are you scared?
I... I am not nervous.
I... I am not scared.
I... I have never been to a battlefield.
I've never been in a battle either.
I don't know what it's like on the battlefield.
The battlefield is not that scary.
Since you chose to join the army,
for Nanxia
and the revenge you must take,
you have to stabilize your emotions.
Because there will be a battle of life and death tomorrow.
Well said.
Sergeant.
Brat,
what Mai said is right.
Mai,
let's take revenge
for Nanxia's men tomorrow.
Also,
if these Beimo people
dare to step on our land again,
let's kill them.
Kill them.
I think I should drink a toast to you with water
because you are so manly.
Sergeant.
And you, brat.
When you go to the battlefield tomorrow,
don't be afraid of death.
I'm emotionally touched by you.
It's not scary to die on the battlefield
for killing enemies.
It's normal to be afraid of death. Everyone is afraid of death.
You can't say that.
I'm not afraid of death.
Qi.
Do you have a wife or a mother?
My mother is at home.
It's very dangerous on the battlefield.
Sergeant, if you...
die on the battlefield tomorrow,
who will take care of your mother?
What you just said makes me a little scared.
Sergeant,
I have an idea.
Erdan.
Come.
Turn around, back to back.
Come, like this.
Sergeant, come here too.
Me... Me too?
Yes, the three of us.
Come.
Like this.
Back to back.
Try to spin around.
Spin.
Back to back tightly.
Yes.
What... What do you mean?
When the three of us go to the battlefield tomorrow,
let's form a team.
As long as we are back to back,
no matter how they attack us,
we can defend ourselves.
What do you think?
Good idea.
This is good.
It can prevent us from being attacked from all directions.
Yes. That's what I mean.
This is such a good idea.
Should we tell them?
Great.
Of course I'm willing.
Qi, please go tell them.
Okay, I'm going to tell them.
Guys.
This is great.
Erdan,
you won't die on the battlefield tomorrow.
Mai, I trust you.
Mai.
Brother Tang.
Go help Sergeant first.
Okay.
Mai.
Do you two still remember him?
He is Mai, who was in Yinbao City back then.
Yes.
Brother Mai.
Mai,
they are my brothers from Yinbao City.
He's Liu. He's Dong.
We met before.
It's great that you two are here.
Brother Tang can finally feel relieved now.
You two go to the camp
to see if there is anything else that should be prepared.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mai,
do you have something to tell me?
You are nervous before the battle.
I can't see through other things.
But I've been in many battles.
Remember,
when you are on the battlefield,
you have to be focused.
Got it, Brother Tang.
We'll go together,
and we'll come back together.
I'm not scared.
I really am not scared.
Look me in the eye.
Promise me.
I promise you.
Have a good sleep.
Only with a good night's sleep can you win the battle.
I'm leaving.
Got it.
What is this?
A bug.
What about this?
It's also a bug.
Mai,
you know clearly we are outnumbered
in the battle tomorrow.
I can't believe you still have the mood
to make bugs here.
Come on. Make some soldiers.
Okay.
Let's make some together.
This is for you.
Is this
an ancient divine beast mentioned in the ancient poems?
I see.
You want it to protect me.
Mai.
Actually, it's a dog.
Sorry.
I... I really couldn't tell.
It's okay.
I... I can make it a divine beast.
No... No need.
A dog is good too.
You are the boss in the military camp.
It's a dog if you say it's a dog.
It's late.
Go back and rest.
We'll have a battle tomorrow.
Sleep well to build up energy.
You too.
You go first.
I'm leaving first.
Come back alive.
Do you understand the plan I just made?
Yes.
Marshal,
I still think
Nanxia's army may set an ambush at Yelanggou.
If we attack rashly, we'll definitely fall into their trap.
Marshal, please think twice.
I made the plan
based on the message delivered by our scouts.
General Chang, what proof do you have
to support what you said?
My years of combat experience.
Yelanggou has a flat terrain...
General Chang...
But...
Have you forgotten our purpose of passing by Yelanggou
is to arrive in Yuzhou faster
and catch them off guard?
You just said
Yelanggou has a flat terrain.
There is nothing they can take advantage of.
How can Nanxia's army set an ambush?
Although Yelanggou has a flat terrain,
its topography is rugged.
Its east and west sides are narrow.
The north side is high and the south side is low.
If we dispatch cavalries as the vanguard
like you just planned,
they can only enter from the high ground in the north.
If cavalries rush to the plain from the high ground,
the horses won't be able to stop in time.
By that time, they just
need to set up a bayonet formation on the plain
to cause severe damage to our cavalries.
General Chang, what you said makes sense.
But in battles,
the priority is to know yourself and your enemy.
If our enemy is the Huainan Army,
of course we must be very cautious at this place.
But the soldiers in the Qingyu Military Coalition
are not professional at all.
Most of them haven't even been in a battle.
Why are you so panic, General Chang?
In that case,
I shall take my leave.
General Chang, suit yourself.
He's overconfident.
Brother, what happened?
Nothing.
I was just given the cold shoulder.
I knew he hasn't let it go.
He's so petty.
Brother,
you just put up with it?
He wouldn't listen to me.
I told him it's a trap of Nanxia's army, but he insisted on his plan.
I don't want my men to die in vain.
Come with me.
Are we going to fight on our own?
Where?
Yuzhou.
Fu Chong.
Yes.
I order you to lead your cavalries as the vanguard
and set off immediately.
Okay.
Pass my order.
Strike our camp
and head to Yelanggou.
Okay.
Done?
Done.
Yang Mo.
Big Brother.
Are you writing letters?
Help me write a letter to my family too.
Okay.
And I eat well and drink well
in the military camp.
I'll keep the extra pay
for her.
Of course.
And most importantly,
don't be reluctant to throw
the leftovers and the spoiled food away.
Give them to the pig.
No, wait.
They can't be given to the pig, right?
If the pig get sick after eating them,
we won't have pork for Chinese New Year, right?
Speaking of my pig...
Well...
Big Brother,
slow down.
Well,
I'm speaking slowly enough.
Do you know how to write?
Of course I know.
Listen, Big Brother.
When I studied in a private school back then,
I was a scholar in the village.
I'm telling you.
My handwriting was good.
Really?
Let me take a look.
They are all circles.
What is this?
I haven't written for a long time.
Is this what you called good handwriting? Do you know how to write?
Calm down, Big Brother.
How about this?
I'll draw a pig on it for you later.
I'm sure your mother can understand it.
Okay?
Then you need to draw a sow.
Because it's a sow we're raising, okay?
Okay.
Draw the pig well.
Mai.
You don't want to write a letter to your family?
Do you want me to write to you?
This boy...
General,
we found a small team of Nanxia's cavalries
10 km to Yelanggou just now.
It seems they are scouts.
Was General Chang right
about an ambush in Yelanggou?
So what?
Marshal said
they are not professional at all.
Should we report it to Marshal first?
No need for that.
The battle at Jingyang Pass
made Chang Yuqing famous.
If I can
defeat the Qingyu Military Coalition
before the army arrives,
I will be as famous as him.
Pass my order.
Speed up!
Okay.
[Yelanggou]
Charge!
The first arrow.
The second arrow.
The third arrow.
[Yuzhou]
General Shi.
What does this mean?
Yuzhou City has been taken over.
The special envoy was killed by the enemy.
Brother, just fight.
Waiting here makes me anxious.
Wait a little longer.
[Protect the country and the people]
Tell General Shi
I don't have patience anymore.
General Chang, sorry to keep you waiting.
Have you made up your mind, General Shi?
Are you going to fight or surrender?
General Chang,
you must be joking.
Even though you have an invincible army,
we can't disgrace our country.
General, do you mean you're going to fight?
We can't defeat you.
To be honest,
there are fewer than 1,000 soldiers in Yuzhou.
We can't even defeat
ordinary soldiers,
not to mention an invincible army.
Then General Shi, what do you have
to bargain with me?
The civilians in the city.
You enjoy the reputation of an invincible general.
If we die in the battle,
the civilians in Yuzhou City will fight to death.
General Chang, you don't want
a run-down Yuzhou City, right?
What exactly are you trying to say?
General Chang,
it doesn't matter if I die.
But the civilians in Yuzhou City are innocent.
If you promise me
that you won't kill a civilian after entering the city,
even if I'll bear the name of a traitor,
I will open the city gate to welcome the Beimo Army.
I promise you.
In the name of what?
In the name of my ancestors,
I promise I won't hurt a civilian in Yuzhou.
Open the gate.
General, we can't.
I will take all the blame.
Open the gate.
Okay.
Let's go.
Release the fourth arrow.
Kill!
[Chen]
-Father!
-Go!
Mother!
Go!
Kill!
Mai!
-Mai!
-Mai! Come back!
Mai!
-Kill!
-Mai!
Mai!
Now we can tell Lieutenant Tang to attack and surround them.
Tell...
Kill!
Mai!
Where's the Operation Supervision Team?
Shoot him!
Wait.
General,
those who disobey military orders in a battle shall be executed.
Mai is not someone who would disobey military discipline.
General,
you can't be merciful if you want to lead an army.
Sir, there is something you don't know.
Mai came up with the ideas.
Maybe she didn't tell me
about some details.
So let's wait
and see, okay?
Just wait and see.
[Chen]
Kill!
Chen Qi,
take care of Mai from now on.
Brother.
Sir, I'm giving you the authority temporarily.
Guards.
Yes.
Follow me.
Okay.
Young Marquis.
Brothers,
block the Beimo Army's escape route.
Charge!
Mai.
[Chen]
Be careful.
The army is trapped. Marshal, please tell us what to do.
Retreat.
Mai,
you'll be fine soon.
Doctor! Doctor!
Why isn't he here yet?
Make way!
Hurry up.
It must hurt a lot.
General,
pull out the arrow now.
Pull it out!
Of course we should pull it out!
General.
Bite it.
Mai.
It's okay.
It's okay, Mai.
Come.
Wait for me.
Report!
General,
Lieutenant Tang sent someone to report
that Beimo's army has retreated from Yelanggou.
There is no sign of a counterattack.
Mai, do you hear that?
Mr. Xu,
this is a secret letter.
[Beimo's Chang Yuqing led an army to attack Yuzhou, and Shi Dachun, the Guard General of Yuzhou, surrendered]
Sir,
why are you standing here?
[Beimo's Chang Yuqing led an army to attack Yuzhou, and Shi Dachun, the Guard General of Yuzhou, surrendered]
Take a look at this.
He chose to bear the name of a traitor
for the people of Yuzhou.
Yes.
I'm afraid General Shi
is expecting us to go back day and night.
But the Yuzhou Army has followed him for so many years.
If they know about this,
will it disrupt the morale of the army?
You've always wanted
to gain the military coalition's loyalty, right?
This is a good chance.
But General Shi will be wronged temporarily.
Marshal,
General Chang has taken over Yuzhou.
Marshal, you don't feel well.
And the soldiers have just finished a battle and need to rest and recover.
The nearest city is Yuzhou.
It's a good place for the entire army to recuperate.
Go to Yuzhou.
Okay.
Why are you doing this?
General,
we have followed Shi Dachun for many years.
We never thought
he would betray his own country.
We followed you to kill the enemies,
but he opened the gate and let the enemies in.
It's useless to say anything now.
General, please dismiss us.
We want to sneak back to Yuzhou City
to kill him. And then we'll kill ourselves as an apology.
I'm not going to stop you if you want to go.
But I'm going to ask you a question.
Are you Nanxia's soldiers
or Shi Dachun's soldiers?
Of course we are Nanxia's soldiers.
In that case,
what does it have to do with you
whether Shi Dachun betrayed the country or not?
For a long time, we've been fighting against the enemies
and protecting our country.
We are not protecting a city
or a family.
We are protecting the land of Nanxia
and
the people of Nanxia.
General,
considering what you just said, we'll follow you till we die
and do whatever you ask us to do.
Everyone, please stand up now.
Since you all think much of me,
from now on,
don't mention the Qingzhou Army or the Yuzhou Army anymore.
The military coalition will be a family from now on.
Okay.
Since the two armies have united as one,
there will be no Qingzhou or Yuzhou Army.
It's time to rename the military coalition.
General,
we're willing to follow you.
Please rename the military coalition.
Since you trust me,
I'm going to rename the military coalition today.
For such a long time, the Qingyu Military Coalition
has been guarding the border and fighting against Beimo.
How about the Zhenbei Army?
The Zhenbei Army! The Zhenbei Army!