[English subtitles are available]
[Fighting for love]
[Episode 33]
To inherit the throne,
one should be of royal blood.
Your Majesty, we know you have the legitimate right to be the emperor,
but other people do not know this.
If people question the legitimacy of you being the emperor,
there will be chaos in our country.
Besides,
Prince Qi Yu is alive.
Bai.
What are your thoughts?
I'll listen to you, Your Majesty.
I'll never disobey you.
Don't mention this thing again.
Let me think about
whether there'll be some other way to solve the problem.
You may leave.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What should I do?
[Crown Prince's Mansion]
I've met His Majesty.
Please let me in.
Marquis Zhongyong, it's so kind of you.
His Highness appreciates your kindness.
But it's not convenient for His Highness to see you anymore.
Go back and tell His Highness
that the nobles of Huainan Army
are all followers of the former Crown Prince.
His Majesty used to serve in the Zhenbei Army
so he will promote lots of soldiers of the Zhenbei Army.
We don't mean to trouble His Highness
but the nobles of Huainan Army cannot be dismissed.
But His Highness is too young.
Whether he's young or old, he needs to help us.
Go back and tell His Highness
that I'll be waiting here.
[Crown Prince's Mansion]
Your Highness.
Marquis Zhongyong won't leave.
How about
you eat first?
Marquis Zhongyong is my elder.
Anyway, I can’t let him starve.
Give this to him.
Tell him
that I appreciate his kindness
but I am too young
to live up to their expectations.
Yes.
[Crown Prince's Mansion]
Your Grace.
I’ve told His Highness that you came.
Marquis Zhongyong, please understand that His Highness cannot see you.
I see.
I understand.
I won't disturb His Highness anymore.
[Crown Prince's Mansion]
Bye, Marquis Zhongyong.
Marquis Zhongyong!
What's going on?
I'll call the imperial physician.
His Highness...
His Highness.
His Highness!
[Lin's Mansion]
How is Marquis Zhongyong?
He died on the spot.
It's said that those from Crown Prince's Mansion poisoned him
because he disturbed them too many times.
But some people said
Prince Qi Yu had almost had that fish soup
so they suspected that someone was trying to kill Prince Qi Yu.
It was an accident that Marquis Zhongyong had that soup.
You may leave.
Yes.
What happened to the palace recently?
So many accidents have happened.
The palace is not a safe place now.
Prime Minister.
Rou is pregnant now.
How about we let her live in our mansion for some time?
Nonsense!
She is the empress. How can she leave the palace?
Those from Crown Prince's Mansion must have offended someone.
Prince Qi Yu is too smart.
You mean His Majesty?
Looks like Prince Qi Yu is a big trouble.
Prime Minister.
What are you going to do?
We don't know whether Rou is pregnant with a boy or girl.
Qi Yu is a threat to the Lin family.
Honey.
I need you to do something.
What is it?
I want you to go to the palace and visit our daughter.
Okay.
Your Majesty, let me explain.
It has nothing to do with him.
I did everything on my own.
As long as Qi Yu is still alive...
How dare you!
Why don't you be the emperor?
I dare not.
I think you dare.
You may leave.
Your Majesty...
We'll take our leave.
Sir.
His Majesty really got angry this time.
What should we do?
If His Majesty had really got angry,
he would have punished us.
You mean...
Your Majesty, how have you been?
Mother.
I brought you some plum cakes, pickled bamboo shoots,
and some other good snacks.
Hope you'll find them appetizing.
Jinchu.
Take some snacks to the young prince in Crown Prince's Mansion.
Yes.
Mother.
You prepared some snacks for Qi Yu?
You father asked me to do it.
He said
you had hit the kid too hard last time.
You should be more friendly to Qi Yu.
Otherwise, people will say
you're a bad aunt
who treats a child badly.
If you and Qi Yu become enemies,
it won't be good for your child.
You’re right, Mother.
Is Mai really waiting for me outside the palace?
Of course.
Marshal Mai doesn’t want to be noticed so she didn't come.
She asked us to take you out of the palace.
Why hasn't Xing come yet?
We can serve you.
There is no need to let others follow.
Let's go.
Let's go, Your Highness.
I suddenly remembered that Master would check my homework.
Let me go back first.
Your Highness.
Let go of me!
Go!
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
What are you doing? Let him go!
Let him go!
What should we do about him?
Take him away.
Okay.
Your Ladyship, he's already in the carriage.
Is he resisting?
No, he's been quiet.
Let's go.
Yes.
Your Majesty, bad news!
Your Majesty.
Prince Qi Yu is missing.
Missing?
Have you searched the other rooms in the palace?
Yes, we have searched the whole palace.
Prince Qi Yu and his valet
are both missing.
The palace is heavily guarded.
How come they got missing all of a sudden?
Who
went or came to the palace recently?
Your Majesty,
Today,
only Mrs. Lin
came to visit Her Majesty.
You may leave.
Mu Bai.
Go to Prime Minister's Mansion.
Yes.
Wait.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
I'll take action only after I fully investigate it.
Leave.
Son.
You've lost weight.
Is your life difficult?
I haven't seen you for a long time.
So I got so emotional.
Son.
Take a seat.
Have a meal at home today.
I'll cook some dishes for you.
Mother, please wait.
I'm here today
to ask you a few questions.
What questions?
Why did you use two carriages when you came to the palace today?
Your sister is pregnant.
I brought her some snacks.
I knew it was not easy to go to the palace
so I brought a lot.
Son.
Why are you asking me this?
Mother.
You could bring things into the palace.
But you shouldn't have taken things out of the palace.
No matter what happened,
please be honest with me.
All right.
Get up.
Make a horse stance.
Hold it.
Straighten your waist.
Marshal Mai.
We found a letter at the door.
Bro.
Open it.
Bad news.
Prince Qi Yu is in danger.
[Come to the stage station next to the Ershili Shop in the south of the city if you want to save Prince Qi Yu.]
Mai.
Is it a trap?
[Come to the stage station next to the Ershili Shop in the south of the city if you want to save Prince Qi Yu.]
We'll know if it is a trap only when we get there.
Okay.
I'll get some men in the camp to go with us.
Bro.
What if it's true?
Too many people will alert the enemies.
I'm afraid Qi Yu will be hurt by them.
Just the two of us go there.
Okay.
Prime Minister.
Is everything done?
Yes, Prime Minister.
Everything is done.
Both sides are on their way.
But...
Say it.
I'm worried that he'll be hurt...
I believe in Minshen's ability.
Go.
Yes.
Mu Bai.
It's not Prince Qi Yu.
Let's go to East Market
and see if we can find any odd jobs.
How I wish Mai were here.
If she were, we wouldn't need to do manual labor to get money for food.
Look.
If we set up a gambling stall in East Market
and swindle two rich foreigners,
we'll get enough money to buy food that we need for half a month.
Why did you hit me?
Stop talking nonsense.
Let's go.
Okay.
It smells good.
Yu.
Isn't that Liu?
I remember he had no money for food a few days ago.
Why did he buy so much food today?
He's also wearing new clothes.
It's a little strange.
Let's go.
Mr. Liu.
What are you doing? You scared me.
Don't touch them.
You're rich!
You're a rich guy now.
How did you manage to make so much money?
Can you tell us how to become rich?
-Please.
-I don't know how to become rich.
I don't know how to become rich.
You two go away.
Get lost.
Who cares?
Let's go.
[Duke Sheng's Mansion]
Looks like Mu Bai
didn't try his best when fighting against me.
That's not true.
The more I think about it, the angrier I get.
Sit down.
People outside are listening.
Mai.
Stay out of this matter.
Stay out of it?
Isn't it obvious?
No one
could get Mu Bai to do that but him.
Now your relationship with him
is already so bad.
You'd better
stay out of this.
Have some tea.
I can stay out of other things.
But this is about Qi Yu and I must save him.
I'm his master.
How's the investigation going?
I was afraid that I'd get them alerted,
so I sent someone to investigate it secretly
but we couldn't find them.
I interrogated the two who had been saved by us.
They are brothers.
Someone gave them money and asked them to leave the city in disguise.
That's all they know.
Who gave them the money?
According to what the elder man said,
that man looked ordinary.
I think he was just on an errand.
Shengdu is so big.
It's not easy to find the culprit.
Bro.
Let's split up
and make everyone know we're looking for Prince Qi Yu.
Why
should we make everyone know we're looking for him?
If he really did it,
Qi Yu must still be alive.
So,
the more people know we're looking for Qi Yu,
the safer Qi Yu will be.
Okay, Mai.
I’ll get it done right now.
I'm here to ask you a question.
Was Mu Bai under your order
to assassinate Qi Yu last night?
I didn't give any order to Mu Bai.
Mu Bai is your guard.
If it wasn't you,
who else could it be?
Tell me then.
That child is not a member of the royal family.
Why do you think I would kill him?
Because only you and me
know Qi Yu's identity
while other people don't.
Let me tell you the truth.
I haven't decided what to do with him.
You shouldn't even have the slightest idea of hurting him.
If you hurt that child,
you’re no different from Qi Jing.
Mai.
I…
No matter what you're thinking about,
let me tell you,
I'll always protect that child.
-Have you ever seen him?
-No.
Have you ever seen these two?
No.
You two,
have you ever seen these two people?
No.
Attention, everyone.
These two
are very important persons in the palace.
Anyone who helps us find them
will be given 500 taels of silver.
500 taels?
Come to me if you have ever seen them.
-I've never seen them.
Let's go.
Let's take a look.
Yu.
Are we really going to eavesdrop on them?
The reward is 500 taels of silver.
Don't you want it?
Yes.
-Let’s go.
I won't put them on.
Buy me a new pair.
Sorry, Young Master.
Behave yourself, or I'll tie you up again.
I'm not afraid of you.
You want to be punished?
Let's go.
I must teach you a lesson.
Did you hear that?
It's the important person.
It is suspicious
that he keeps the door closed in daylight.
Besides, he got rich overnight.
There must be something wrong.
But we don't know what's going on inside.
I'll go check again.
No, wait.
Those who dared to kidnap the important persons from the palace
are definitely not good people.
Let's report it to the government.
Go to the government now.
I'll stay here.
Come back soon.
-Okay.
-Go.
I feel that my father
has been different recently.
Go out of the palace and go to the Prime Minister's Mansion.
Try to get some information from my mother.
Ask her where my father has been
and who he has met recently.
Qi Yu must be in one of those places he has been to recently.
Be careful. Don't make others notice you.
Okay.
Move!
Step back! Step aside!
Move! Move!
Move! Move! Step back.
Step back.
Are you sure it was Prince Qi Yu?
Yes.
I saw him clearly.
Both His Highness and his valet were here.
They were guarded by two martial artists.
I couldn't beat them.
They escaped.
Do you know where they went?
Sorry.
Rise.
It's not your fault.
Take him to a doctor.
Yes.
Mai.
Be careful with your words.
Mrs. Zhang.
It’s me.
You're really Mai!
Mai’s back.
Mai.
It’s really you.
It’s Mai. It’s Mai.
Mai is back.
Hello, everyone.
It’s me.
I’m Mai.
I'm busy today.
So I have no time to have a good chat with you.
I’ll visit you later.
Mai.
I know where the person you’re looking for is.
-Let’s go.
Bring more people.
There're many of them.
Okay.
Your Majesty, I'm back.
Have you got any information?
According to Her Ladyship,
Prime Minister only went to the villa outside the city once or twice recently.
He didn't go to any other special places.
Who has he met recently?
Her Ladyship said she didn't know.
Jinchu.
Let's spend some time outside the palace tomorrow.
Okay.
Mai.
It’s here.
I reported the case to the government this afternoon.
After they knocked out two officers,
they got a child and a servant into a carriage
and came here.
The two people being held by them
looked like the people in the portrait.
Find out whose villa this is.
Marshal Mai.
No need to do that.
This is Prime Minister Lin's villa.
Prime Minister Lin's?
Yes.
Let's go.
Be alert.
If anything happens to the people in the room,
you will be held accountable.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Pouring the water.
Let him do it.
Young Master.
There's a group of armed guards outside.
There're seven or eight of them.
But there're no special symbols on their uniforms.
I will try to find
more information about them tomorrow.
Xing, you must be careful.
I don't understand
why they all wanted to catch you.
I'm worried that
I won't be able to protect you even if I sacrifice my life.
If so, I would let the former Crown Prince and the Crown Princess down.
Xing, it's okay.
They will come to save us.
You're right.
You must be tired.
Have a good rest.
I'll watch you tonight.
Your Majesty.
Why did you ask me to come?
I want you to tell me
how Qi Yu is now.
He's fine.
Your child will be born soon.
But Crown Prince's Mansion is still occupied by someone else.
So I did you a favor.
But that child has lost his parents.
I feel sorry for him.
Besides, he has been living in the palace since he was born.
I'm afraid he's not used to living outside the palace.
Your Majesty, you're so busy every day.
The empress is pregnant.
You two have no time to take care of that child.
I'll take care of him for you.
With you taking care of him, I can rest assured.
But he is the son of the deceased Crown Prince.
If he lives outside the palace,
people will say I dislike him.
Who dares to say that?
Mai.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
The living room is still being cleaned.
Could you please go to the flower hall first?
No need.
Where is he?
What?
I'm sorry.
I have no idea who you're talking about.
Qi Yu.
Your Majesty, you must have misunderstood.
There are no others in the villa.
If my father hadn't told me about it,
how would I know he is here?
Get up and lead the way.
Yes.
He got missing.
Mai suspected that I had hidden him.
If the child is found in your place,
she will believe that I asked you to hide him.
The empress is like the mother of the people.
How about we let the empress
take care of the child?
What do you think, Prime Minister Lin?
Okay.
Let Qi Yu move to Kunning Palace.
That'll be great.
You're a very good official.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Bro.
Mai.
Is everyone ready?
Yes.
Are we really going to use violence?
We won't be punished
for using violence this time. It's rare.
But it’s Prime Minister Lin’s villa.
That’s why we shouldn't be afraid.
He is hiding a prince.
Even if we destroy his villa,
he won't dare to do anything to us.
Fine.
Let's destroy his villa.
Your Majesty.
He's inside.
You may leave.
Jinchu.
Wait for me here.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
You may leave.
Sorry I can't leave.
Qi Yu.
Believe it or not,
I'm not the one who forced you to stay here.
I'm here to take you back.
Where are you taking me?
To take you back to the palace.
Or I can take you anywhere you want to go.
I don't want to go anywhere.
You don't trust me?
Is it because I punished you last time?
You punished me
because I did something wrong.
But I can't go with you.
Why not?
If you take me away secretly,
you might get into trouble.
Are you worried about me?
I believe Master Mai will find me.
Take good care of your master.
Is everyone here?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Qi Yu, grandson of the former emperor,
is now in a villa of Lin's outside the city.
Send a team to get him back to the palace.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Make sure he comes back unscathed.
Move!
Stay still.
Stay still. Stay still.
Come here. Hurry.
Stay still. Hurry!
Master Mai.
Sorry.
I'm late.
I knew you would come to save me.
Let's go home.
What are you doing here?
I'm under His Majesty's order
to take Prince Qi Yu back to the palace.
Tell His Majesty
that it's safer for him to stay with me than to stay in the palace.
Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
How have you been?
Good.
I asked you to come today
to ask you a few questions.
Please go ahead, Your Majesty.
Father.
Why on earth
did you hide Qi Yu?
I did it for your own good.
And also for the good of the descendants of the Lin family.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
I've made all the necessary arrangements.
You just need to have a good rest.
Don't think too much or be too worried.
Take good care of your health.
Are you really planning on something?
I'm making some preparations in advance.
Though His Majesty promised that your son would be the Crown Prince,
I cannot wait too long and I don't trust him.
Father.
You're already the most powerful official in the country.
And your daughter is the empress.
Why are you still not satisfied?
Because I want the Lin family
to be prosperous forever.
To make the Lin family prosperous, you don't need to...
You don't need to rebel.
Rou.
Do you know
why I assisted and supported Qi Huan?
Because he had the legitimate right to be the emperor and he had no much talent.
So it would be good for us if I helped him become the emperor.
But he has been interested in getting more power lately.
Even if I don't rebel,
he will kill all the people of the Lin family in the near future.
Don't you care about me
when planning on rebelling?
I'm doing everything for your sake.
As a member of the Lin family,
you also have the responsibility to make the Lin family prosperous.
Only when the Lin family is prosperous
can you be safe and carefree.
You and the Lin family are closely related.
I understand.
So you have prepared two plans.
Whether I'm pregnant with a girl or boy, you'll take action.
If the imperial physician's guess is wrong,
you'll use Qi Yu,
right?
You may rest assured, Your Majesty.
No matter who ascends the throne,
you'll be the Empress Dowager.
Aren't you afraid that I won't be on your side
and that I'll tell His Majesty about your plan?
By then,
everything you've done will be in vain.
Your Majesty, it's okay if you don't care about my life.
It's okay if you don't care about the lives of your mother, your brothers,
or even your unborn child.
I won't stop you.
But you always have a kind heart.
I believe you won't tell on me.
Don't say that again.
Father.
What are you doing?
Get up.
Get up!
Please wait a little longer.
Fine.
I'll wait.
Get up.
What are you...
I'll take my leave.