END OF THE WORLD
ASTEROID COLLISION IN 200 DAYS
ASTEROID COLLISION IMMINENT
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
199 DAYS LEFT
CHANCES OF SURVIVAL?
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
198 DAYS LEFT
TOGETHER TO THE END
140 DAYS LEFT
COLLISION CRISIS ALERT
CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL CLOSED
DO NOT APPROACH
130 DAYS LEFT
SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
MISSING
BASED ON THE NOVEL SHUMATSU NO FURU
BY KOTARO ISAKA
80 DAYS LATER, OUR ETERNAL LIFE BEGINS
EXPERIENCE THE ETERNAL LIFE
50 DAYS UNTIL THE END
FLOATING BUNKER PRESENTATION
Yun-sang.
I'm going downstairs for some coffee.
DO NOT ENTER
Ms. Jin.
-Hmm?
-No one's in there.
Huh?
Guess I was only half awake.
I smelled coffee in my dream,
so I just came down for it.
That's right. It's vacant.
-Right.
-Ms. Jin?
-Huh?
-Um…
Bae Jong-su? He's dead.
Oh.
Huh.
The end draws ever nearer,
and you're listening to pirate radio.
Greetings, fellow soldiers.
I'm your favorite moon-dwelling rabbit,
Oktokki, with some news.
That monster who broke out of prison
and committed unspeakable things
against innocent children,
that evil punk, Bae Jong-su, is dead.
According to the Joint Investigation Unit,
the sick bastard put a bullet
through his own eye.
Whether he did it to himself
or if it was someone else,
who gives a crap?
The JIU was more than happy
to sit on their hands
while these scumbags roamed free.
But then… boom!
Down comes divine punishment!
You done here? Let's go.
Hold on. Let me see.
Remember, these assholes
broke out of prison amidst the chaos,
kidnapped children to sell,
and left them to die
in shipping containers.
I gotta say, it sure feels good…
This makes no sense.
I don't care if it was suicide or murder.
Either way, I'm just glad he's dead now.
The asteroid will
crash into Earth in 200 days.
And the safety zone?
Do you really think
you can survive…
Ugh! This is the worst.
I'm sick of being afraid of those jerks.
It really pisses me off!
If only someone could…
take out the whole gang or something.
If I had a gun, I'd just shoot 'em myself!
I am the punisher! Beware!
When the asteroid Dina comes,
pretty much everyone is gonna die.
-Ugh, gross.
-It doesn't matter what you do.
DELETING
I hope you've been
saving up your money, kids.
Your monthly maintenance fees are due.
We're still a little short.
You see? Bae Jong-su's death
doesn't change a thing.
Let's beg her again.
I'll see if I can negotiate.
♪ Born as a valiant son of this nation ♪
Yes, sir.
At ease. They say it's a suicide.
But… Um, the shot's angle
clearly looks like a homicide.
The JIU was sloppy, as usual.
They don't care about
some dead jailbreaker criminal.
Jesus, will you tell me what's going on?
I want answers!
Um, sir. Sir.
Please calm down. I'll-- I can explain.
Uh, as you know,
every country has different
eligibility conditions for migration.
In your case, you were trying
to go to the United States.
They're a member of the International
Convention on Personal Data Sharing.
Look here. Anyone who has broken
the Children and Youth Protection Act--
I can see the list!
Why in the world am I there?
Well, sir, if you've ever
frequented establishments
that use underage workers,
that could be why.
Right.
Also, as part of the agreement,
all your personal data is shared,
including… including medical records.
So, for some countries, you have--
Where are you going, sir?
Sir, you need to provide
your COVID vaccination card
and, um, proof that you're STD-free!
Ugh! That guy's an asshole.
I feel for his wife and kids.
Look, kid, our manager
is waiting for the maintenance fee.
This has a lot of movies on it.
The fuck is this?
An antique or something?
I can pay you the rest soon
when I sell the drive I'm working on.
How can I trust you?
If you think we're gonna go soft
'cause one of the lieutenants is dead…
You should bring those chicks over, hmm?
-We'll have some fun!
-Huh?
Ha-yul? Leave her out
'cause her dad's a creep.
So-min though…
Her mom's a lot scarier though.
Just do what we say.
I don't need your opinion,
you little shit.
Do not doubt.
-Our future selves are waiting for us.
-Eternal life!
Be free of all doubt!
A new, inextinguishable sun is burning.
-Eternal life!
The asteroid collision is just a lie.
The asteroid does not exist.
Don't be fooled, brothers and sisters.
The asteroid collision
is the start of eternal life.
It is a new beginning. Listen, everyone…
What are you doing here?
-You here alone?
-Uh-uh.
Don't wander around. Go home.
-Go on!
-Okay.
This kid…
-Be free of all doubt!
-Free yourself from it all!
Do not doubt!
Listen, even if
there was an asteroid collision,
the Earth would not cease to exist.
No living organism
can be completely exterminated.
This is impossible. I'll tell you why.
All right, sir, please stop.
Patrol is hard enough. It's so hot today.
Eternal life!
-A new sun is burning.
-Eternal life is not a religion.
-Eternal life!
Eternal life!
Be free of all doubt!
-Hey.
-Hey! How'd it go?
What did they say?
They threatened you, didn't they?
No more than usual.
They told me to stick to the pay schedule.
Write something. Here.
What should I write?
D-200.
I'M SURE IT'S NICER THERE
All right, all right! Quiet down, please.
Oh yes! Ha-yul? Hey.
Ms. Jin, why are we the only ones
writing down our secrets?
You should have to tell us one of yours.
Something that the principal
should never find out.
Come on, just one!
Hang on.
Remember, at work,
the principal is my boss, yeah?
It's too risky.
Plus, you'd be sad if you couldn't
see me anymore, wouldn't you?
So enough already.
Sit down. Open your books. Guys!
-Tell us one!
-Guys.
Tell us one!
Tell us one! Tell us one!
All right. Draw the curtains, then!
Cover those windows up!
You wanna know my secret, huh?
So, um, my secret is…
Hmm…
Okay, just a minute.
-Wow! What is that?
-What is she doing?
Whoa. What is that?
Be quiet, everybody!
Quiet, guys!
Is that a butterfly?
Ms. Jin,
do you like butterflies?
-Is that a butterfly?
-She has three butterflies.
-I wanna get a tattoo too.
-Wow! That's so cool!
Hold on, all right?
Make a line.
Okay, that's enough now.
You munchkins wanna slack off, huh?
Come on, back to your seats. Sit down.
All right,
since we're all sharing secrets,
I'll make an announcement.
-I'm going to make a soccer club.
-What?
-Why?
-Really?
-Any takers?
-Yeah!
-Oh! Me! Me!
-I'll be the manager!
-Oh wow!
I'll be the awesome, awesome,
super pretty cheerleader, then!
-Ha-yul! Min-ho.
-I'll be goalkeeper.
-Wow, a lot of you are interested.
-I'll cheer them up.
I guess we'll need to have tryouts, then.
Open your books.
Come on, you rascals.
-You have to learn something!
-Please? I wanna talk about soccer!
-Eternal life!
-Be free of all doubt!
-Ms. Jin!
-Yeah.
The deputy mayor
is looking for you.
Okay.
It was chaotic here
early this morning. Did you all see?
Soldiers swarming everywhere.
Even my daughter, Captain Kang, was there.
I heard it was a suicide.
But they're still not sure.
Oh.
That's the house next door
to where you're working now, yeah?
Well, sure, but I didn't know him at all.
I just saw some cars parked there
on my way to work. That's all.
Why kill yourself
with a home like that?
Those fancy houses
even have private bunkers.
I heard you can survive
a nuclear bomb in one.
-Oh, right. You would know!
-Huh?
You can tell us all about it.
You drove the concrete mixer
when those houses were built.
Oh yeah, they're plenty sturdy.
We dug, uh, ten meters into the ground
and covered it all
with a ceiling two meters thick.
At the place I work for,
they stocked up
all sorts of things in there.
Probably enough to last three years
for her and her grandson.
There's no point.
Everything will be underwater.
Everything! Those new apartments too.
They're nothing but fancy fish tanks.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Of course, we'll all probably burn up
long before the flood.
Looks like we're done
with the young summer radish.
We should plant some cabbages
to make kimchi.
Then, once we've made kimchi
to hold us over till next spring,
that'll be it for the world.
Think about it.
I won't have to make doenjang
or soy sauce anymore.
It really sinks in
when you say it like that.
It sure does.
Oh my.
Looks like it's gonna rain.
WOONGCHEON CITY
SHELTER NO.3 CONSTRUCTION SITE
There's still some water left
on the tracks.
-Watch your step.
-Oh, okay.
We need to go all the way down.
-Ah.
-Over there.
Right.
Section One, Section Two. All switched on.
What's with the long face?
Huh?
Stop zoning out over there.
Give me an estimation on this shelter.
You want… my estimate?
Yeah, who else?
You taught Home Ec, didn't you?
These days, I pretty much
only work with children.
And as a volunteer at that.
Besides, what's the point, hmm?
Building these shelters
is just insulting people's intelligence.
Everyone knows that.
But this is the safety measure
our all-knowing government came up with.
So we should at least
get a budget together, don't ya think?
I mean, we can't just sit and watch
all these people get scammed and tricked
by private bunker companies and cults.
But you already know
no place will be safe in the end.
-Se-kyung.
-Hmm?
Lighten up, huh?
Can't you just imagine
we're building a huge dance hall?
I like the sound of that.
Yeah. Sounds fun.
An end-of-the-world dance party
with the kids.
Mm-hmm.
Jin Se-kyung.
A dance party!
How's this?
-Dance party!
-Oh wow! You've got the moves!
You know, I used to be
this silly and happy all the time.
Yeah, and I used to be
a rational and reasonable person.
Oh! My baby Jesus!
Captain Kang?
What are you-- Did you come for me?
In-a?
Yeah.
So many people are still missing.
We don't know if they're alive or not.
Barely anyone comes here
to visit these days.
Remember, this whole square
used to be crowded.
I guess we're all pretty tired.
I'm just gonna come out and say it.
The dead guy, Bae Jong-su…
he was a total scumbag.
Jailbreakers, armed imposters,
low-life gangsters.
Under Martial Law,
they should be executed.
But this is something else.
Fake suicide.
Probably a warning to the other gangs.
A punishment, then.
No.
Personal revenge is not punishment.
It's a crime.
No matter what.
If anyone thoroughly investigated this--
"Anyone"? Such as?
You know the JIU won't do it.
You're right.
Neither can I.
My unit doesn't have jurisdiction.
But if I were to investigate it…
you'd be the prime suspect.
I did nothing.
-Why?
-You had a grudge against him.
Everyone did.
-If there's any chance it was you--
-Do you hear what you're saying?
I just hope you'd never even think about
doing something like that.
Mm-hmm.
I know things will never go
back to normal.
But a crime is still a crime.
Look, it seems like
no matter what I tell you,
you're gonna be suspicious of me.
-Say you didn't do it. I'll believe you.
-Well, I didn't.
I didn't do it.
I gotta go.
Forget it, then.
Just don't go around alone from now on.
And don't go out late at night.
But I work late, so…
Look.
Do you know what those scumbags are like?
They're powerful and ruthless.
They play dirty, and they never give up.
You can't--
Even if some punisher gets rid of a few,
there will always be
more crawling behind, out of the gutter.
They traffic people for sex.
Do you understand?
See ya.
302 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
Okay.
So the priest was the first one here, huh?
Dancing like a raver in his sacred gown!
Didn't wanna be late,
so I came straight after.
No time to change.
We can't be late
when Se-kyung calls us.
You got that right!
Yun-sang, you're in your lab.
Can you be on a video call?
It's not like I have a choice.
I'm stuck in here all day.
These little guys are
practically my family now.
Oh wow! They're so cute!
Hey!
Ever wondered
how many hairs are on a mouse?
Guess how many strands they have
in a five-millimeter area.
What? Are you working on hair loss pills
or something? A special new drug?
Oh man! Ha Yun-sang.
Come on home. Come on, huh?
Work will still be there
after your wedding to Se-kyung.
They say, "Out of sight, out of mind."
That happens to long-distance couples.
They forget each other and call it off.
What do you know?
-Good-looking jerk.
-Hey, priest, knock it off. Huh?
-All right, fine. Look.
-By the way, guys.
-I got promoted.
-This is what you want? Dancing?
-How do you like the new fit, huh?
-Like this?
-Kang In-a. Bam!
-Okay!
So, about our wedding…
At least try to look excited.
Okay. How about…
Hmm… Mm-hmm.
We'll just do it
like a video game side quest.
Is Father Baek still going to officiate?
-Mm-hmm.
-I hope I'm not bothering him.
You know how much he adores you.
I think it's bedtime.
Are you gonna stream tomorrow?
In-a's gonna make a video.
I'll send it after the game, yeah? Okay?
WE HOPE YOU GROW UP WITH DREAMS
AND HAPPINESS IN YOUR LIVES!
2025 WOONGCHEON'S FRIENDLY SOCCER MATCH
One, two, three!
Cheondong, Cheondong! Fight on!
Woongcheon!
We're here for you!
♪ Unbeatable Team Cheondong ♪
♪ Run ahead at full speed ♪
♪ Win the day, Team Cheondong ♪
♪ Show us what you're… ♪
Win it for us!
Fight on, Cheondong!
-Let's go!
-Go! Keep running! Run!
Come on!
Oh, come on, Mom!
It's okay, it's okay.
Min-ho, stand up.
Go Cheondong!
Completely shameless.
Yun-sang would fly back home
if he knew you were here.
What was that?
If Yun-sang knew you were here,
he would definitely fly back home!
Well, we're still waiting!
Come on, press up!
-Let's see some tackles!
-Great job.
Let's score more
in the second half.
Yeah! Good work!
-Are you okay? Are you okay?
-Hey, that's a foul!
Yeah!
Don't start going easy
on them, all right?
You all let them score, didn't you?
-I saw it all.
-What?
I'll have you know that was a clean goal!
Se-kyung.
I always knew you could play soccer,
but I never expected you
to set all this up.
I wanted to share my hobbies with them!
You'll understand if you teach kids.
You're great.
What is this?
-What? You pulling a prank?
-You didn't get anything?
-Let me check.
-What's happening?
-Look at this.
-I have no idea what this is.
-This is crazy.
-What is this?
I think it's a prank.
Hey, did you get it too?
What's that matter? Are we playing?
Are you all too tired?
Uh, Mom, watch my stuff.
I got an emergency call. I need to go.
-Hey, In-a!
-Hey, hey, hey! In-a!
In-a! In-a!
Wait, what?
"An important global announcement
will be made at midnight tonight"?
-Ms. Joo, In-a had to answer a call.
-That's normal for the SMU.
We're sorry,
but due to network difficulties--
Oh shit! We're fucked!
We're all screwed!
Noona, why aren't they playing?
Is it over?
Maybe?
I don't know.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
While tracking the orbit
of the asteroid 2012, Dina,
which disappeared in 2013,
we discovered
that it is heading towards the Earth.
We recognized the possibility
of a collision with the Earth,
and we did our best
to eliminate the threat,
but we failed to deflect it.
ASTEROID COLLISION ON KOREAN PENINSULA
THE LAST 300 DAYS
After 300 days from now,
the asteroid, which is 900 meters long…
-Let's stop feeding her.
-Okay, Mommy.
…will crash into the Earth.
Mom? Mom?
-Yeah?
-My phone has no signal.
I think tomorrow's schedule
will be canceled.
-Hello? Hello?
-What?
-There's no reception.
-Hey, you there?
The affected area is expected
to reach all of Japan,
the Korean Peninsula, Eastern China,
and the Indochina Peninsula.
What are we gonna do?
-Oh shoot!
-Yeah!
-Hurry up!
-Okay, I'm coming!
The impact would cause
a climate change beyond imagination.
And it would take at least 30 years
to restore the ecosystem of the Earth.
Dear citizens of Woongcheon.
This is Deputy Mayor Im Seon-ju.
Where is the asteroid?
I can't see it.
In light of rampant conspiracy theories
taking advantage of our anxieties
and the rise of crime, such as looting,
violence, as well as kidnapping of minors…
SEONJIN STAFFING INC.
…Woongcheon City declares
that it will take strong action
against any and all such disruptions.
Fellow citizens of Woongcheon,
as of this broadcast,
we have 199 days left.
Oh!
Okay, lunchtime!
This remaining time we have
with our loved ones…
-There we go.
-Oh boy. He likes it, doesn't he?
Hello, sweetie. Here's your food.
…than ever for us to be there
for one another until the last moment.
And that's a wrap!
Good work, everyone.
That's it for tonight.
Um, let's see. We have potatoes
and some Spam, I think. That's it, sir.
Wait. Where are the sausages I brought?
Don't get me started on those, Sergeant.
Those three boxes of sausages were
the most disgusting thing I've ever seen.
When I first opened them up,
it was just… the most vile thing.
I'm telling you, okay?
The ice block inside had melted.
There was meat-water… Disgusting.
…all over the place. Imagine the smell!
Also, there were tiny bugs crawling out!
-Enjoy your meal.
-That looks pretty good.
-Thank you.
What the fuck is this? Ugh.
We work our asses off
just to eat this shit?
You know what's worse?
I've got guard duty.
We don't even get
Spam anymore.
I'm gonna need
to take it up with our captain.
Really? That's a little…
Seriously though.
Putting ranks aside,
I could eat that for breakfast.
-Yeah, okay.
-Hyeon-sik.
No matter how messed up the military gets,
we don't allow insubordination, all right?
Enjoy your meal, Sergeant.
Ignore him, all right?
What do you say?
We play a little game later?
For a bit of money?
Oh yeah! We get paid today!
Ah, at least I've got
that to look forward to.
Tell me about it, huh.
ETERNAL LIFE STUDIES
Man, I'm starving.
There are three features
that distinguish quantum physics
from the classical physics.
The first is quantized energy,
which means that factors like momentum
are determined by a certain value.
The second is wave-particle duality.
On a microscopic scale,
these two properties
can be observed at the same time.
The last is the uncertainty principle.
This means some properties of things
cannot be observed at the same instant.
Excuse me, does that mean
our bodies will also become quantum?
Exactly! Look, everyone.
Eternal life is not a delusion.
It's cutting-edge medical science.
So, if we look beyond the apocalypse,
we'll find another world
made up of all the waves
that have accumulated there so far.
Eternal life!
Ugh, so gross.
Ugh.
The asteroid collision is
the beginning of eternal life.
Be free of all doubt.
Our future selves
await us on the other side.
-Eternal life.
♪ Through asteroid Dina
We move beyond Earth ♪
♪ To life eternal, to life eternal ♪
-I hope they have cream buns.
-I want fishcakes.
-They're out?
-You have to do it right.
It'll be like a shockwave.
-Like a storm with a giant earthquake.
-I got it.
-A tsunami and a great flood?
-Check it out. Looks good.
-What happens to the asteroid?
-Thanks, man.
Oh. Um, you still owe us some…
-Oh, ration ticket.
-Yeah, thanks.
It'll smash into Earth,
and the debris will
shoot up high in the air.
Oh, and then fall down like hot sky magma.
Or like a shotgun floating in the air
and blocking all sunlight.
I heard about that. Impact winter.
Yeah. Temperatures will drop,
plants will die,
then so will animals, one by one.
Just like how the dinosaurs went extinct.
It'll be goodbye for us all.
-Two ramyeon, please.
-Ramyeon?
-Yes!
-And plain!
You can't have both.
Once choice each.
-Huh?
-What do you mean? Why not?
We're low on supplies.
You should think about other people.
Where are you going?
Uh… just going to renew my gun license.
It's expiring soon.
-You're up to something, aren't you?
-Don't worry about it.
See you later.
Don't be stupid, all right? Huh?
I'm not that guy now.
See you later.
-Bye.
If he comes back here again
with some weird contract,
I'm kicking him out and locking the door.
It's like that guy wants
to be scammed by people.
How is he like this?
Even after losing our boy, he's still so…
I'll take over. Hmm?
You should take a five.
Yeah. Mmm.
-Good morning, Auntie.
-Hi, kids.
She must miss Min-ho.
Yeah.
Ugh! Why are all the dads
in the world so stupid?
How would I know?
It's not like I have one.
You want that?
Uh-huh.
-Thank you.
-We'll be off.
-I left them on the table.
-Okay, see you.
-Have a good day.
-Have a good one.
THE LATE KIM MIN-HO
SEPTEMBER 1, 2011 - MAY 10, 2025
If you want out of this country,
this is where you get info.
Oh, hi!
What is this?
Is there gambling here?
It's been a while.
What's with you, man?
Why would you bring me here?
Listen, I can't be around this.
Hey, wait up. Wait!
Chill out. Just follow my lead.
Okay, but hang on.
Does this floating bunker really work?
What's the down payment?
-Ah, yes! We have a few options.
-Would you just follow me?
Give me a second.
I see. Okay.
-Place the blinds, please.
-Thank you. Jeong.
This floating bunker's the real deal.
We don't even need a broker!
150k with a 50,000 deposit!
I need a permit to leave.
This dumb thing doesn't have that at all.
They expect us to pay
and take their word for it?
Did you get your money back
last time from the other guy, then?
The money you paid?
You know, to that guy? For departure.
That jerk ran off already.
Exactly.
You paid for that upfront.
Guess we can't trust anything.
What'd the broker charge ya?
Way too much.
It needs to be low-cost and efficient.
I don't know about efficiency,
but if you want something cheap,
you need to trust me and look at this.
-Let me know what you think.
-I'm not gonna pay to drown in that thing.
Ah, Jeong, it was designed by scientists,
so I doubt drowning
is gonna be an issue here.
Oh, look at that!
Let's go!
You know what?
I'm feeling extra generous today.
Wanna hear some hot intel?
-Yeah!
-Tell us!
Let's say the asteroid crashes into Korea.
What's the chance
it wipes out everything on Earth?
Is it high or low?
Low!
It's low, yeah? Not very high at all.
Let's say you manage
to live for two weeks after that.
The probability of you then surviving
the disaster is definitely high, I'd say!
-Sounds pretty good, right?
-You think he's right about that?
…you're still gonna have
lots of problems.
Why? Because there are just
too many people in this world.
All it takes is one quick look around,
and you'll agree. There are so many--
Hang on.
Are you… Jeong Su-geun?
The YouTuber with a million subscribers!
-It is him!
-You are!
You see that. Everyone recognizes you.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, I'm honored, really. Now, where was I?
Anyway, there are too many people
in this world, right?
Humans have done incredible things.
We've built civilizations, yeah?
Our technology, our medicine,
our triumphs, and our tragedies.
Overcoming all kinds of obstacles,
and now,
we face humanity's final challenge.
So tell me, everyone,
the new world is coming.
Are you one of the chosen, huh?
-Yes!
-Yeah!
Tell me!
You bet I am!
If you are, then let's play,
my fellow chosen ones. Another round!
-Go get the chips.
-Sounds pretty great, huh?
-Things are not looking good.
-She's really bad at this.
-She's gonna die, huh?
-Yep.
YOU DIED
You're kidding me!
How come you always die on that stage?
You were so close.
-Hey, you try beating it. It's super hard.
-What do you mean?
Obviously, I was the best.
-Yeah, right. You're the worst.
-Jin-seo, what was your score again? 15?
I was just taking it easy on you guys.
-Remember the last game you tried?
-Come on!
Huh?
-Oh!
-Huh?
Another blackout?
Nothing works
in this stupid country!
The lights will come back on.
-Hey, this one's amazing.
-Got more for us to watch?
-You gotta bring more.
-Sure.
-Like maybe some music videos?
-Yeah, okay.
How are things at home?
My dad's impossible.
He's a lost cause.
-Yeah, I get that.
-What are you complaining about?
My dad's like that too.
Hey, your dad might embarrass you,
but at least he didn't do anything dirty.
-Huh? The lights are back on!
-Oh? The lights are on!
-Okay.
-You wanna play more?
-Hey, wait!
-Wait up!
Whoa, you're pretty good.
Obviously, come on! Aim for the center…
Nice Shot!
Don't go.
Are you Ha-yul?
Yeah.
What do you want?
You don't take after your dad, do you?
She really doesn't.
I bet your mom is a lot prettier.
Aw, stop it.
You're scaring her.
Pathetic.
I have something to show ya.
Here!
Keep watching.
Look at her face.
That's your dad, right?
Oh!
-No, stay back!
-She fell.
Summer will come.
Then fall, then winter.
And when spring comes…
I can't believe that there's only one
of each season left before the end.
Stop being so depressing!
I'm not wrong though.
No, a woman like you
should just be whistling her entire life.
Make me some coffee.
Oh, please. What coffee?
Can you try not to look like that?
Ha-yul isn't
going to listen to you this way.
This is just what I look like!
Look at that condescending face.
It feels like you're saying
I'm an idiot when you get that look.
Plus, your eyes are scary.
'Cause you say stupid, pointless things
all day, like right now!
Is it you, Ha-yul?
Where the heck have you been?
None of your business.
You little…
How long are you gonna keep
this attitude, young lady?
199 days.
You think I don't see
what's going on here?
You're glad about the asteroid,
aren't you?
Oh yeah, so glad.
-You're going nowhere with those grades.
-Goodness, please don't start that again.
Even with my miserable upbringing,
I managed to get into a good school.
So what's your excuse for slacking off?
I've paid for all your trips abroad.
I get you the latest smartphones
as soon as they're released!
What have you done, huh?
Stop, stop!
You're always taking your anger
out on her!
-How does this make anything better?
-That's great!
Just take her side like always!
I'm disgusted. You're all crazy.
At least we got some snacks, right?
Yeah. It's hardtack,
but that's better than nothing.
There are still
so many people leaving.
They're not leaving.
They're just siphoning gas
from abandoned cars.
Yes, Sergeant.
For now, we need
to check the remaining stock.
First, we'll see what we need
and how much,
then we can make another plan.
Sounds good to me.
-Hey, Captain?
-Hmm?
A shuttle bus broke down up ahead.
INSPECTION UNDERWAY
HALT
-How long is this gonna take?
-Come on already.
-We've been here forever.
-We've been waiting forever.
-What's going on?
-How long till we get out of here?
-Please. How quickly can you fix it?
-The officers are here to help.
Don't worry.
I don't think we can
fix this bus right now.
What do we do?
-Okay.
-You gotta be kidding me!
Listen, it may be uncomfortable,
but we can take you all
on our supply truck.
Everyone, please exit the bus
in an orderly manner,
and we'll get you on.
-Excuse me.
-Sure. Take your time.
In-a.
Hi. High five!
-This is so stressful.
-Hmm.
-In-a.
-Please have a seat inside.
-Kang In-a.
-Watch your step, ma'am.
What can I do for you, Father?
-You coming back from somewhere?
-I was summoned by the bishop.
-Oh, I see.
-Mm-hmm.
-Uh…
-All done?
-Wait, wait, wait.
-Oh, right.
Oh, thank you.
-This is ridiculous.
-Huh?
How are they asking
such a talented officer
to beg for onions and potatoes?
I mean, don't get me wrong.
Onions and potatoes are needed,
but still, it…
-In-a, stop! In-a, stop it! Stop it!
-I'm on duty right now, Father.
Watch how you speak to me.
All right, I get it. All right.
Just let go, please.
Tie it up.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hey. Let's move.
Stop the car.
Wait here, please.
What is this?
Can you call the dispatcher?
They'd have my new registration number.
Sergeant.
-What's going on?
-I need your help.
They won't let me through.
He doesn't have a passport.
And this certificate here
is the only thing to verify his identity.
-Go, I'll take care of it.
-Yes, sir.
Step out of the vehicle.
Just call him.
It's his problem too.
If he wants his bus back…
Thank you for the ride, man.
I appreciate it.
What?
Not four digits maybe?
I'm gonna break this damn door!
Oh no! No!
Wait. You… you might
set off the alarm!
What am I supposed to do, then?
I have no way of knowing
how many digits there are!
That'll take forever!
I finally see her,
thanks to you, Father.
Why don't I see you at mass anymore?
Don't tell me you're facing
the end on your own.
You know, your mom--
No, it was Sister Myeong-ok
who said you loved coming to church
when you were young.
Well, back then,
I was coming for all the snacks.
Father Baek used to have
all sorts of treats stashed away.
Well, he still does.
In a secret room downstairs.
Ah, is that so?
Really? Then I guess
I should raid the place sometime.
Wait, you're serious?
I don't know the passcode.
If I just knew how many digits.
So this is the guy?
WOONGCHEON CITY MARTIAL LAW COMMAND
JOINT INVESTIGATION UNIT
-Uh-huh.
-After you.
You enjoy the meal?
Oh, I see you did.
Do you smoke?
No, I don't.
We've verified your identity,
but since your travel route
was a bit unusual,
there's a lot the JIU needs to confirm.
From now on, you'll be monitored
by Deputy Head Song over here
and me, the investigation team leader.
It's almost like I'm a wanted man here.
Yeah.
In a way, you are.
You'll make a report every day.
5:00 p.m., rain or shine.
Where you are. What you're doing.
It's not about you, of course.
It's just, given your profession,
there are some sensitive issues
to keep an eye on.
Okay, then.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Remember, 5:00 p.m.
Honestly, you were safer in the States
than you are at home.
I don't know who this friend
you came back for is,
but they must be special, huh?
Everybody else is
dying to get out these days.
City hall will be
contacting you soon.
Tell them you're not missing anymore.
Oh, and right here, this man.
He'll make sure you get home safely. Yeah.
He must be very tired from his journey.
Use every shortcut you know,
and get him home as quickly as you can.
Got it?
-This way.
-Please.
Excuse me, Mr. Ha.
Your seatbelt.
Now, off you go. Go.
-Ms. Jin! Whoa!
-Jesus!
How are you so scared? What's with you?
I thought I told you to go home early.
What are you doing out?
-You're out late, too, though, aren't you?
-Well, I'm not a kid.
No fair.
It's not like I'll get to grow up.
Are you all right there?
-All right, go home already.
-Okay.
By the way, So-min's worried about you.
Worried? About me?
So you shouldn't be
staying out late either.
Good evening.
Did you all arrive home safely?
Because this is the time of night
when those scumbags roam the streets.
My friends, we need
to stick together till the end.
I'm sure you all remember
the deplorable incident
where dozens of missing
and kidnapped children
were found dead in a shipping container.
This Oktokki has found out the reason.
After the asteroid collision,
what's the one thing
the king of survivors will need?
Slaves to rebuild the capitalist system.
An obedient working class.
The future needs its labor force,
and children will be its backbone.
That is why
all those kids keep disappearing.
These scumbags kidnap children
to offer them up to their king.
What they receive in return
is a guaranteed ticket to the safety zone.
A ticket to the safety zone!
Those trash bastards!
Oh dear.
Taller every day.
Calling me himself, huh?
-Hello?
-Why haven't I heard from you?
Did you sort out the goods?
What about the safe?
I took everything and left quickly.
But Jong-su's phone was missing,
along with some of the goods.
You should talk to Manager Im.
About what?
We gotta take care of that girl.
Just watch it, punk.
Don't do anything stupid.
Oh, these fucking JIU bastards.
What the hell are they up to now?
Don't tempt me.
I only wanna do it more
when you tell me not to.
Just you wait.
KIM JAE-U
(MURDER, FRAUD, RAPE, DRUG DEALING)
AN JI-SEOK
(FRAUD, LIKELY A BROKER)
LEE JAE-MIN
(MURDER SUSPECT)
BAE JONG-SU
(MURDER SUSPECT, PIMP)
TRAINING CENTER MANAGER IM
"Manager Im."
Not here.
TRAINING CENTER MANAGER IM
Zero-seven-two-three…
Who is it?
In-a?
Unni?
Who is it?
Is it you, In-a?
Sorry to stop by unannounced.
I forgot the passcode to my place,
so… so I came here instead.