Be your own superman
and work hard so--
Min-ho, make sure to remember
this is all thanks to me.
-Thanks.
-Hey!
-You can do anything you want.
-I put this picture up…
Min-ho, did you tell Yun-sang
that you're gonna be a scientist like him?
Uh, no. His fan club only.
-A toast!
-Cheers.
Beer always tastes best
after soccer practice.
-Well said.
-Yeah.
-Hello.
-Oh! Hello, Father.
-How was mass?
-Did you get your revenge?
What do you think?
-Father Woo.
-Yep?
You want a drink?
Let me tell you.
This one can hold his liquor.
You probably got that from your grandad.
Maybe so. He gets everything else
from you, though, Father.
Ah, you're always so kind to me.
-Oh, Clara?
-Uh, yeah?
How's your soccer team coming along?
Ah, really great! It's a good team!
Yeah.
She spends all her time there,
even though it's not a professional team.
-What's the point?
-You know I like passing out at night.
-Exercise is good for you, and it's fun.
-Right.
You pass out and never hang out.
A man gets lonely!
Come on, Yun-sang.
We're always together at night.
-What?
-Don't need that information, Se-kyung.
-Whoa! Keep those stories to yourself.
-There's a child here!
How dare you!
That's not what I said at all.
I didn't mean that!
About your wedding…
It's gotta be coming up.
I'll be officiating.
Please do!
Thank you in advance.
-Hello, Father.
-Oh, hello.
-Thank you.
-Hi.
Hey, come back, Father!
Yeah, a disgusting turn.
-What was that, honey?
-All right, come on now.
END OF THE WORLD
ASTEROID COLLISION IN 200 DAYS
ASTEROID COLLISION IMMINENT
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
199 DAYS LEFT
CHANCES OF SURVIVAL?
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
198 DAYS LEFT
TOGETHER TO THE END
140 DAYS LEFT
COLLISION CRISIS ALERT
CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL CLOSED
DO NOT APPROACH
130 DAYS LEFT
SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
MISSING
BASED ON THE NOVEL SHUMATSU NO FURU
BY KOTARO ISAKA
80 DAYS LATER, OUR ETERNAL LIFE BEGINS
EXPERIENCE THE ETERNAL LIFE
50 DAYS UNTIL THE END
FLOATING BUNKER PRESENTATION
153 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
Not this again.
Um, why are we meeting here?
I apologize.
It's 'cause my phone has no reception.
It wasn't the plan
for you to come all the way here.
Come look at this.
Ah. Yeah, that's him.
Th… that's my dad's driver right there.
Do you recognize this address?
Oh! Out of the five addresses,
I know this one.
It… it's the last place my dad's driver
w… w… went to drop something off.
You have to tell the captain
everything you know.
Okay. I'll do it.
Yeah, I hear you. Go ahead.
I can talk right now.
Yun-sang's driving.
Yeah. Can you hear me?
-Yeah--
-Hello?
This is driving me crazy.
Hey, Captain, are you all right?
18-1, GUGAK-RI, EUNGDEOK-MYEON
WOONGCHEON, GYEONGGI-DO
Did you get it?
Oh! Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, a deer.
Thank God.
Oh!
You got my text, right?
We're on our way there.
Hello?
You there?
In-a?
Officially, you're on
civilian protection duty.
The shortest route is an hour.
-Report to me in ten.
-Copy that.
Hyeon-jae.
Yes.
I'm worried. Are you sure you'll be okay?
I'm okay. Don't worry about us.
-I'll be heading out, then.
-Okay.
-Where are you going?
-Eungdeok-myeon, Gugak-ri.
You have to go back.
Please turn around.
Who are you looking for?
Answer the question.
Baek. We're here to see Father Baek.
Father Baek has visitors.
Okay.
Let 'em through!
Hello, Father.
You seem to have some concerning guests.
Oh!
Se-kyung.
Yun-sang.
A little tough to find this place, huh?
Goodness, you came all this way
just to speak with me.
Right, Clara?
And Thomas.
So happy you're here. Mmm.
We sure have a lot to talk about,
don't we?
Ah.
Oh, wait.
Let's start off with confessional.
Don't the two of you have
your wedding coming up?
Ah, no, no, no, no.
Confessional is one on one.
You must stand alone right before God
and really confront yourself.
That's not--
You know, with confessions,
when it hasn't been done in a while,
it becomes quite difficult.
I know.
I know my actions will lead me to hell.
I'm a murderer,
and it's happened three times now.
Sh! Hey.
Clara.
Now, what did I always say?
If you don't complete your homework
on time, it'll eventually catch up to you.
And the next thing you know,
you're overwhelmed with sin.
It's as if you have scabs
all over your body.
But even with sin,
God will always forgive you.
Every time.
God's forgiveness is endless and kind.
He never tires.
Instead, he always waits patiently.
Yeah, I understand that,
but I have no desire to repent.
Well, all right.
I will pray for you
to absolve you of sin.
Clara, you still must reflect, repent,
and find the resolve to not sin again.
God will wait for you
with love and patience.
Well then, what about you?
God is speaking to me.
You two have a purpose.
You may not think it so,
but God always knows.
It can indeed be difficult
to discern God's true intentions.
But the fact that we're here together
must mean something, wouldn't you agree?
On the way in,
I'd hoped that you weren't in here
'cause I had to believe it wasn't true.
That you'd--
I'm not sure what you have planned, but…
stop hiding out here, Father.
You have to explain to everyone
why you abandoned the church so suddenly.
Yun-sang.
Widen your horizons, child.
The outcome you seek…
…is reductive in nature and lacks wisdom.
Please.
It's not just us. So many people
have been hurt by your actions.
The end is near now.
They deserve closure, don't you think?
I know a four-year-old
who's envious of his older sister
'cause she's seven,
and he'll never get to be.
Have some empathy.
Don't your believers
deserve some compassion?
All of us.
We all trusted you to protect us.
Let's stick to the original plan.
Mm-hmm.
I'll prepare a plan B as well.
Yep, yep.
The best servants of God,
they are the ones who will go.
There is not much time to waste.
I trust you, Yun-sang.
I know you will make the wise choice.
On the day we leave…
an hour in advance, be ready.
I will rescue you.
Oh.
You went outside?
Can't remember the last time you were out.
You know, I was visiting my good friend.
Ah good. Yeah.
You ought to.
Getting some fresh air is nice.
-Isn't it better than your bedroom?
-Mmm.
G… G… Grandma? I was…
Huh?
I, uh…
Please don't leave me.
Huh?
Oh, now, what would make you say that?
Uh, my dad's, uh…
Well… well, his driver told me, uh,
you and I have to
move to Dad's official residence.
Don't mind him, In-tae.
The nerve. Spewing nonsense like that.
I would never abandon my grandson.
Though I would leave your dad.
-Don't worry too much now.
-Okay.
-Go get some rest.
-Mmm.
I had wished to provide you an escort,
but it seems that won't be necessary.
Oh.
A soldier will be driving you guys back.
Captain's orders.
Everyone on board!
Good luck, both of you.
And please,
I pray your choice will be wise.
Come on, Father!
Just open the door!
-Father!
-Give me something.
Just one word. Please, I'm begging you.
Just enough for me to carry on.
152 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
-Hey.
-Found a CD.
I found this.
Ooh! We can put videos in that.
-Mmm.
-Good find.
I heard that Netflix
won't be coming out with any new content,
not even in the US.
Yeah. Why would they these days?
There's no point
in making movies right now.
Yeah, I don't think
we'll get another season.
There's still a lot of weird directors
that wanna film their stuff,
but they don't have
any actors willing to work.
That makes sense to me.
Why act when the world is ending?
Yeah, I wouldn't act either.
Why else would they keep working?
For more money, obviously.
Wait, what?
Why are there so many people here?
I don't know.
-These guys have different uniforms too.
-Let's go to Ms. Jin.
-Yeah. Let's go. This way.
-Okay.
-You there!
-Hurry.
-Off the platform!
-Hurry up!
So the center's planning with the US.
-Are you--
-Are you gonna be--
Go ahead.
The training center.
With what went on,
I heard a rumor around the base
that you'd be dismissed.
Don't worry about me.
So Young-ji…
-Have you seen her since that day?
-Huh?
Nope. I haven't seen her a single time.
-It didn't seem like she had a cell phone.
-I guess so. It's okay, ma'am.
This airfield is packed
with division-level security right now.
If my instincts are correct,
they're definitely
planning something here.
I think they're trying to get
the remaining citizens home.
There's still a lot of Americans in Korea.
You're kidding me.
Hold on a minute.
The airstrip, right?
The US military base.
It has to be that!
Right. That makes sense.
I guess Sister Regina was right about it.
They're really moving up everything.
Uh, excuse me.
Se-kyung, can I speak to you?
Uh, oh.
Okay.
So, Father,
what are you planning to do now?
We have to do something,
and it's gotta be more
than prayers this time around.
Yun-sang.
Did Father Baek say anything else
to you during your visit?
He knows about the fire
at the church, right?
Here.
It's been a while.
When are you and Yun-sang leaving?
Se-kyung.
Mmm. What's up?
I wanted to ask.
Did In-a ever say anything to you
about In-seong?
You can tell me.
In-seong oppa?
Did she ever tell you
how In-seong died?
It was an accident, right? At the riot?
Mm-mm.
I guess I'll tell you, then.
After the riot,
most of the food was all gone.
In-a just disappeared.
She had to leave with her unit.
We couldn't reach her,
and In-seong was impatient.
He left to look for food one day.
He drove around everywhere.
He was downtown.
Those beasts, they murdered him.
He never had a chance.
My poor boy.
Killed just like that.
Murdered in daylight.
They got him in the red-light district
right near that brothel.
A parishioner
who'd done business there told me
she saw a tall, thin person there
behind In-seong.
And then, he…
So I told In-a.
And she
just said that
it could've been anyone.
A lot of people are tall and thin,
and that I shouldn't think about it.
That I should just carry on with my life
'cause there wasn't much that I could do.
So, sure, I thought.
There's not much time left anyway.
The clock's ticking.
So I told myself not to think about it,
but then these guys
just kept dying one after the other.
I felt like someone was trying
to get revenge for In-seong.
Justice, if you will.
I thought that…
In-a could never just let anything go.
Always so stubborn.
Your daughter's a hero.
In-a
would do anything to keep us safe.
Anything.
Yeah.
Do you think it's In-a?
What a world we live in, huh?
Filled with revenge.
And everyone knows that revenge
can never be forgiven by God.
Mess Sergeant, good work.
Does she have to stay around for this?
No, it'd be better without her.
Please head back first, then.
I heard Mess Sergeant So Ju-yeon
used to be a part of
the Special Missions Unit
before transferring.
She a buddy of yours?
Hmm?
You've been coming here too much.
How can I not when there've been
so many unreported operations?
-There's been just one.
-What about the missing ammunition?
Uh, that's already been addressed--
You know very well
that the ammunition was meant for the SMU.
So don't even bother lying.
Yeah?
-Search the place!
-Yes, sir.
299 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
Look at all the cars back there!
Let us pass!
We've been stuck here for hours!
The soldiers are blocking it!
Move it!
Still standing by.
It looks like they're stopping traffic
with a blockade.
A coup from the military.
It's a strategic takeover of our weapons.
We've got a mutiny now.
Those guys will try anything.
A few commanders have joined in as well,
so take caution.
Our unit won't be engaging.
The battalion's orders
are to guard the VIPs.
Understood?
I'm Major Jang, the aide-de-camp
to the division commander. Let us pass.
Yes, sir!
Let's go. Let 'em through.
It's all right. Come on.
Let us pass!
We've been stuck here for hours!
We're gonna break through
the opposite lane.
What the hell?
Sir.
That son of a bitch just ran off!
I should've known he'd do that.
Jesus Christ!
Ah!
-Oh, my leg!
-Ju-yeon!
-My leg. Help!
-Ju-yeon, are you okay?
Come on! We gotta stop the bleeding!
Hey, Hyeon-sik! Come here!
Help us.
-Come on! Come on!
-Ah!
General!
You okay, sir?
General! General!
The rebel leaders are running away.
We need to stop them.
Special Missions Unit,
all withdraw!
Sir!
I repeat. SMU, we need to retreat!
I can't follow an order
that lets the rebels escape.
-You're kidding?
-We're shooting warning shots.
Open fire.
Come on, get back!
Come on!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
The penalty for insubordination
during wartime is death!
Captain Kang!
Kang In-a!
Okay, ladies, still hungry?
Plenty for you to eat.
The world may be ending soon,
but food's still important.
That's it. Yeah, that's right.
-Mess Sergeant.
-Hmm?
Is everything okay?
They let you go?
You know, after you left,
the JIU went through our snacks.
Not sure why.
Hey, Pang.
Yeah?
All right.
We got things to do.
Okay. Go double time.
I need all these potatoes.
Take everything.
Are we seriously taking everything?
-Yep!
-There's so many.
You see? Does anyone happen to know
how to make all these multiply?
You got me beat.
First, take your potato. Okay.
You see where all the buds
are clumped together over here?
You just cut out a little piece
that's around there.
Keep about two or three. Just like that.
And then, add some ash to it
from your firewood.
The ash is there
as the potato's protector.
You put it here.
And by doing so, it'll shield it.
Got it?
So now we can plant them
right into the ground.
Wait until summertime,
and these spuds will taste delicious.
Good plan.
That'll be good.
Except, as we all know,
we won't have a next summer.
Oops!
I guess so-- It's hard to--
You know.
I don't like thinking about it too much.
Yeah, I try to forget.
-Hey, guys. What are we making today?
-Some pancakes.
With potatoes?
-You wanna make pancakes?
-You're uptight.
Why are we doing this out here?
This good enough for you?
Yeah, I guess. Pass it over.
Can you even shoot, huh?
I can, so come on.
Just give the gun to me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You gotta be careful.
This gun better not be fake.
Yeah!
Meow, meow.
Meow.
-Huh?
-Hey!
-What's this about?
-Come on!
Now get out!
No! No, no!
-No, no, no, no!
-Is she out of her mind? The fuck is this?
-Damn it!
-You won't get by!
Huh?
Oh, okay.
I just need the time and place to meet.
Okay.
Listen to me.
And trust Daddy's plan.
We're out of time, okay?
They're getting a chartered plane.
We need to get on it.
And once we do,
there won't be anything to worry about.
'Cause everything is just fine.
Anything wrong, honey?
Ha-yul?
That motherfucker.
They're all the same.
I know my actions
will lead me to hell.
I'm a murderer,
and it's happened three times now.
The best servants of God,
they are the ones who will go.
There's not much time to waste.
On the day we leave…
an hour in advance, be ready.
I will rescue you.
I trust you, Yun-sang.
I know you will make the wise choice.
There they go again.
Se-kyung.
Do you know what's happening?
Why they're here,
circling the area over and over again?
You've probably already heard.
It's true, then?
They're really planning to leave?
There's another aircraft?
I don't know.
Either way…
it can only leave if it takes off.
Why wouldn't it?
Huh?
Se-kyung.
-Yun-sang. I'll be right back.
-Hmm?
I see.
Why didn't you say anything, hmm?
I was embarrassed.
Even though everyone already knows
how shameless my dad is.
Ha-yul.
Always remember
that your number one priority
is yourself.
-But you're not like that.
-Mm-mm.
That's true for everyone.
Me included.
I have to take care of myself
so that I can care for you,
So-min, and Jin-seo.
You're precious, okay?
Your classmates were too.
Got it?
You can cry.
Come here. It's all right.
You're okay, Ha-yul.
You shouldn't be here, In-a.
Don't say that when you've already
prepared all of these supplies for us.
Besides, even though this is important,
I have another thing to discuss with you.
I have a plan, but I need your help.
I heard about everything.
It was a good move for your unit
to raid the training center.
And even though
it was probably an accident,
it's a good thing
your friend was there too.
They took all of that as a signal.
They're cracking down now.
The JIU is questioning everyone.
That's right.
The JIU is getting antsy, not knowing
where all of that ammunition is.
Yeah, I bet.
They're searching
every nook and cranny of the base.
And then you come in
with this conveniently timed raid?
Correct.
They're trying everything they can
to connect the ammunition to the SMU.
So all your ammunition
has been taken away, then?
Yeah. I'm not sure of the plan's details.
I just know it's gonna be big.
They've been organizing this for a while.
That can only mean one thing,
don't you think?
They're leaving.
There's been a change of plans.
Before we can evacuate,
we must rescue all of our children.
You all need to be ready
at a moment's notice.
Wait for my call to leave.
Until then,
leaving this building is now prohibited.
Over here. And so what about our kids?
Are they joining us?
I need my kids. I can't leave alone.
I hear you.
I understand your concerns.
There's no need to worry.
I will retrieve your children.
As long as you're ready,
you'll all be on the plane.
We'll break away from disease and war.
And together,
all shall arrive at a new heaven,
a new beginning!
All of us…
as God's chosen.
-How's that feel?
-Still examining him?
That's okay? And here?
Ah!
-Right there?
-Yeah.
-When I press down or pull away?
-Ah!
-They both hurt.
-Both, huh?
There's a lot of inflammation.
-Seems like appendicitis.
-Appendicitis--
You've been in pain for a while,
haven't you?
I tried to say it hurt.
-Yeah. Uh…
-Oh.
They would always say,
"We can't help you."
"Wait till we arrive,
and he'll get surgery."
When's he getting discharged?
We need to wait
for his ultrasound results.
We can't just let him go.
You'll have to wait.
All right? I'll proceed with
the abdominal ultrasound.
Okay.
How are you feeling?
ONLY ONE GUARDIAN ALLOWED
IN THE TREATMENT ROOM
Okay, here we go.
Just like that. There.
I'm losing my touch here.
Ah shit. Okay.
Ah! Uh…
Oh. Uh…
Ma'am.
Go get the children.
Uh, well…
The boy is, uh…
He's not healthy.
I said to get them!
Do I make myself clear?
At it again, already?
Don't they eat?
Hey! Hey, Seong-u?
Yes, Sergeant?
Just make sure
you don't overcook the rice.
-I won't.
-Thanks.
-Hey, Pang.
-Yeah?
You know what to do
with the aged sesame seeds?
-What?
-Aged sesame seeds!
-Yeah.
-Mix it all at once.
Here we go.
-Hey, listen up!
-Yes, what is it?
We take over the night shift
starting at nineteen hours.
-Ji-myeong! Code words?
-Sir? There's no dog hole.
-So we all know those, right?
-Yes!
We still don't have
bullets in our guns.
Hit 'em in the head.
How do we do guard duty
without bullets?
I know that. Okay. Here we go.
Get 'em up!
There's no ammunition.
Makes it hard for us to do guard duty.
You're connected.
Hello? This is Kang In-a speaking.
Tell me what's going on.
Why are there so many helicopters?
Matters regarding the US
are under Martial Law Command.
Are you disobeying orders?
I'm not challenging
the Martial Law Command.
Who is it?
Captain Kang In-a.
I'm calling because
there's anxiety in the community.
Civilians deserve to know what's going on.
Lower-level units
have no access to this information.
But as I said, the pe--
They're not gonna tell us anything.
Uh, what now?
They still need their food, right?
Take a look around
when you bring them their snacks.
I like your plan.
EMERGENCY AIRSTRIP
I'm at the church.
Ma'am.
Hello, sir.
State your business.
We're here with
the Combat Support Company.
I hear there are
no night shift changes tonight.
Does your team need a snack?
We had a bunch left over
that our unit didn't need.
Hey!
Late-night snacks over here!
Come and get it!
Enjoy.
-Wait, there's food?
-Hurry!
Yeah!
Okay.
Hey, bring this cord
to that walkie over there.
The time and place
might not be accurate,
but, uh, the house, the training center…
If they're flying out,
the military base seems most likely.
But the boarding location
could still change.
Father Baek said something
when we visited.
He wants to get Yun-sang.
He said he'll stop by
an hour before they take off.
-Yun-sang?
-Yeah.
He said Yun-sang was important
for the escape.
So it might not be
at the US base?
Maybe it's a private plane, then.
Wait a minute.
If it's one hour away
from where Father Baek is,
it could be the other one too.
There's an emergency airstrip big enough
for both military and private planes.
So there's a chance the US one is a decoy.
Yeah. Well, we've narrowed it down.
And my guess is that
Father Baek is already on his way there.
As for the training center,
there hasn't been any movement yet.
Sister, I think you should check again
with your source.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Okay, I'll call you back
when there's news.
You received the device, right?
Keep it on you.
Just in case something happens
to Captain Kang. Take this.
Okay, I think we've got it.
I'll keep checking, then.
You'll be safe for now.
They probably won't attack a church.
Stay safe, In-a. Get some rest for now.
-Okay, you stay here.
-Okay.
Hyung. I mean, Father…
Yun-sang.
You two go rest for a bit.
We can switch out at dawn.
Hey, So-min.
You're going to see Ha-yul, right?
Uh, take her some of
the pickled radish she liked.
Here, give this to her.
Take some dried seaweed too.
Auntie, where'd you go?
Oh, Auntie's right here.
What? You're resting here?
I think it's time we talked,
don't you think?
I suppose. Okay.
So what are you gonna do?
Stop talking like it's all on me.
It is though.
And you know it is.
The choice is yours.
I don't know what else to say.
I need to have you with me!
You "need" to?
Is that all I am?
A thing you "need"?
I understand.
I'm just a flower, a tree, a plant.
A thing in the corner
of a painting you made.
You "need" me. Is that it?
Se-kyung, why…
You're twisting my words around.
How does that help anything?
Do you really think I could just
leave you behind here?
I'm just a bitch who's crazy!
You gotta leave me behind, Yun-sang!
Wake up already!
Se-kyung…
…why do you keep trying to leave me, huh?
Yun-sang. Hey, listen to me. Stop.
Sit down.
I wouldn't be happy.
My kids are dead now.
I'm not able to let it go.
I don't think
I can go on living like that.
Only three of my kids are left.
They deserve dignity
and to be safe and taken care of.
And to not get threatened or used
where they end up going
until their very last breath.
And that's why I went
and killed all of those bastards,
those pieces of shit!
Yeah, and I'd do it all again.
I knew, but I still hoped it wasn't true.
-Why did you have to…
-Oh…
Why, Se-kyung?
Did you really think these guys
wouldn't find out what you did?
They probably already know.
Yeah.
They can't kill me yet
because they still need you.
Leave me behind.
Instead of me, take the kids with you.
The kids are innocent.
So take them with you, okay?
I'm being too selfish, aren't I?
They'd hate me for leaving you behind.
I know they're in good hands with you.
They'll treat you well in the safety zone
because of all your skills.
You can take care of them
until they're adults.
I know it's sad to separate them
from their families at such a young age.
But their parents trust you.
They'll be grateful.
They'll be relieved,
knowing their kids are all right.
You know I can't do that!
Don't be cruel.
This is the only thing that gives me hope.
I have nothing else.
Yun-sang.
♪ Though tomorrow may not come ♪
♪ Though you may bring me ♪
♪ Pain and hurt ♪
♪ Am I the one ♪
♪ The selfish one ♪
♪ All along? ♪
♪ Though tomorrow may not come ♪
♪ Though all my joy has gone ♪
♪ Forever and ever ♪
♪ Here for you ♪
♪ Where I come from ♪
♪ Wherever I go ♪
♪ It's not worth my focus ♪
♪ I live in wonder ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ How am I ♪
♪ How am I supposed to know? ♪
♪ I live in wonder ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ How can I ♪
♪ How can I already know? ♪
-♪ Ooh ♪
-♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I live in wonder ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ How am I ♪
♪ How am I supposed to know? ♪
♪ I live in wonder ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ How can I ♪