[Geng Piao is 'Save me'' and 'Save me']
-Save me -Save me
Save me
[Is Zhenjiu in the 5th tunnel?]
['Trail 5's request for help from the children]
Go and save them quickly
[Zhenjiu is the fifth tunnel starting from 710 meters. We are now 600 meters here]
Is this 600 meters?
[600 meters of tunnel 4th tunnel 3rd tunnel dormitory lounge administrator's office is currently located to move 710 meters of tunnel 8th, 9th tunnel 6th, 7th tunnel 5th tunnel]
600 meters We now have the 3rd tunnel and the 4th tunnel here
The dormitory lounge administrator's office is here
-So you have to take the elevator - Go down
Go to the 5th tunnel at 710 meters
-Do you want to go there?
[Elevator] [If Bingzai wants to take the elevator, he must have a key]
[Bingjae needs to find the key]
Does the key have a key?
[Fast search for elevator keys first]
You need to find the key
[Keybox!]
-Keybox-The keybox is written directly here
[The key box is written here]
[Keybox]
[Zhenjiu but cannot be opened]
Can be opened or opened
[I was anxious]
[No!?]
[Elevator key is kept in KKanChoPal] [No key is only a strange sentence]
Elevator key
-Safe in KKanChoPal -Safe in KKanChoPal
[What is KKanChoPal'?]
Kkanchopal
[This is this]
Isn't KKanCho that curator?
[Dong Hyun speculated: KKanCho=curator?]
- Curator-On the arm
[Dong Hyun speculated: KKanChoPal=curator's arm]
Curator Arm Curator
[KanChou(KKanCho) Japanese curator, captain's meaning]
Isn't the director called KKanCho?
-KKanCho -Previous
Japanese
[Kao Tong, but don’t you think this is weird]
-But- What is KKanChoPal
[Why, why is Baekhyun's handwriting very strange]
[Elevator keys are kept in KKanChoPal] [Why are 'Chi' and 'O' so far away?]
[I think it's like that, like the same letter and different order]
What is the same letter different order word
It appeared last time
[What should I get when I combine words like 'one by one']
[Kkanchopal] [po chal]
For example
Po Chal
Don't you think it's very similar?
That is to say, they are all written separately
[KKanChoPal] [The key is on KK?!]
It feels that the key is on KK
[Elevator key is kept in KKanChoPal] [Not many words containing KK]
There are not many single words that can be combined with KK
For example, dreams must
What are the single words that contain KK
[KKanChoPal] [First look for the word "KK"]
[KKanChoPal] [or switch to the ending sound...]
[KKanChoPal] [outside=no B]
But only Nakk can be combined with KK, Nakk
[Nakk is only fishing...] [NakkChoPal] [First of all, 'Nakk' is OK]
-KK is the key -Nakk Right
[Nakkchopal] [nakkchal, nakkpochal?]
[KKanChoPal] [The answer is not as decisive as before]
[Kkanchopal] [kko ...]
[Cans...] [What...?]
[It can't be combined into that single word at all...]
No matter what, the peppers cannot be combined into peppers.
No, Wu
[Isn't it enough to flip it over! Just add it to the bottom]
[Elevator keys are kept in KKanChoPal] [KKoChu]
[Can Chili...] [KKanChoPal]
[Ahhh...ohhh...ah this way...] [KKanChoPal]
That's it
[KKanChoPal] [Although a little strange, it is still convincing]
[Do you want to flip all over and see?] [KKanChoPal]
[KKonChoPal] [Flip the vowels of the son and the vowels over and see?]
[KKakChuPol] [There will be too many combinations if it rotates]
Can't find the direction
[Kwak? Chwakk? Cone?]
[KKot...Flowers?]
[flower?]
-Flowers -Flowers
The flowers are good, too
Flowers are OK
flower
[Move the words to the blackboard immediately]
Flower Pan
flower...
Wipe off the part contained in the word "花" Zhenjiu
[Bingzai wipes off the part contained in the word "Hua"]
Have the word "flower"
[KKANCANCHAPAL -> OO 花?]
Morning Glory
[Morning Glory]
[It turned out to be morning glory!]
-Morning Glory -Morning Glory
Right, right
-Chao-Yes...
Morning glory
-Morning Glory -Morning Glory
[Where is Dongxuan morning glory?]
Morning glory
[Morning Glory Morning Glory!]
-Morning Glory Morning Glory - Where is the morning glory
Morning Glory
-Here Here - Morning Glory Morning Glory
[Dong Xuan, what is there! What did you put in it]
What
[Baodhyun seems to be tearing it apart!]
Tear apart
Here
[Administrator's hidden elevator spare key]
Very awesome
[Get the key]
really
Now go to tunnel 5 710 meters
[Now take the elevator to the 5th tunnel]
Let's go
-It may collapse, we have to be careful - that is
OK...
[Elevator Administrator's Office]
Be careful
There are children in the 5th tunnel
In this place
What
elevator
-It's an elevator - Elevator
[Did the pickaxe drop by 100 meters?]
[There is a big deal in Geng Piao...]
Just now it was 600 meters and 600 meters, right?
[Current location]
- Here is 600 meters to go 710 meters-710 meters
[Tunnel 5 is here]
Follow the guess
[Bingjae, we are going to the 5th tunnel here now]
[Geng Piao is good for the children!]
Let's go
[Bingjae, we will save you!]
Set off
[Departure to 710 meters underground]
[Dong Xuanwu went down!]
Go down
What's this
[600 meters underground and 710 meters underground]
Why so fast
It's falling so fast
[Pinch your nose and jump into the tunnel] [600 meters underground in the elevator, 710 meters underground]
How long will it take to fall
[600 meters underground and 710 meters underground]
Keeps falling
How much to reduce
arrive
[Arriving at 710 meters underground area]
Open the door?
[Gengshu 710 meters! Pay attention to gas and pay attention to gas!!]
That's right
[Attention to gases 710 meters underground]
It's toxic
Toxic Gas There are toxic gases here
Xiaozhe also inhaled
Be careful
Be careful there is a hurdle here
[See through the glass door]
[Gas leakage status]
[What seems very dangerous here?]
[5th mineway entrance]
[Toxic gas compliance protection]
[Breathing hole] [Space for personal preparation before entering the tunnel]
[The entrance of the tunnel with toxic gas after the accident]
[There are kids somewhere here]
[Attention to gases 710 meters underground]
[As soon as I came in, I heard a loud noise from gas]
[Oh, this is everything dead!] [Birds are dead...]
[When Bingzai entered, the canary was the name of the bird]
[Note that when toxic gases enter the 5th tunnel, you must carry canary. Canary is sensitive to toxic gases. If it stops twitching or shows abnormal signs, please evacuate immediately and close the door. Please wear a gas mask when abnormal]
Must carry canary
Canary is sensitive to toxic gases
[If it stops tweeting or shows abnormal signs]
[To come out immediately]
[Because toxic gases will be emitted at that time]
[But the canary is dead]
-Toxic gases - When toxic gases leak out
[I saw the words written on the iron gate]
- Lower the body to 50 cm above the ground - Lower the body
[When the toxic gas leaks out, it lowers the body to 50 cm above the ground]
Then you have to lie down
[We must move Gengpao in a crawling position!]
That's right
When entering
[Note that when toxic gases enter the 5th tunnel, you must carry canary. Canary is sensitive to toxic gases. If it stops twitching or shows abnormal signs, please evacuate immediately and close the door. Please wear a gas mask when abnormal]
I said it is necessary to wear a gas mask
[Zhen Jiu writes breathing hole here...! It should be this?]
Can it be opened
[In the iron cabinet with breathing hole written...]
[Have a gas mask, work gloves, a pair of walkie-talkies]
It should be this
Can it be opened
Is there any
[Heard metal sound again]
There is one
- Yes - knocking again
[-Save us!]
[-Please come here!]
[The sound of children comes from the glass]
-Save us - Help us
We're here
[Over the gas somewhere]
-Then... -We are here
[And the kids are there...!]
The voices of the children
I know the children
[Go over now!!!]
[Bingjae wow... Damn...]
[How to walk through here...!]
[This code is applicable to computer room exhaust fan operation]
After confirming the color of the internal status indicator light in the computer room
[Confirm the instructions on the wall]
Operate the exhaust fan in the following order
[Exhaust Fan Operation Code · This Code is applicable to the exhaust fan operation in the computer room. After confirming the color of the internal status indicator light in the computer room, operate the exhaust fan in the following order. If the status indicator light does not light up ->If the emergency power supply equipment outside the computer room needs to be started (Note: If the status indicator light is turned off during operation due to power outage, re-power is required and then restarted) ·If the exhaust fan joystick is operating incorrectly, it will cause toxic gas leakage -> After all joysticks need to be restored to ON, re-operate from the initial step]
[Operation method of computer room exhaust fan joystick lever 1. If the fifth status indicator light is displayed in purple, switch the joystick number 4 and 5 to OFF 2. If one is displayed in the status indicator light red and one is displayed in yellow, switch the joystick number 1 to ON and the joystick number 2 to OFF 3. If there is green in the status indicator light, switch the joystick number 3 to OFF 4. If more than two (inclusive) colors are displayed in the status indicator light, switch the joystick number 3 to OFF at the same time, switch the joystick number 3 to OFF at the same time, and switch the joystick number 4 to ON
[5. If there are currently more than two (inclusive) joysticks in OFF state, switch the leftmost OFF joystick to ON 6. Switch all the joysticks that have never been operated to the opposite direction (ON↔OFF) 7. Finally, repeat the first operation again. Good general warning hazard status indicator air quality value]
[Instructions for starting exhaust fan when toxic gas leaks]
[According to the rules to operate the joystick, you can start the exhaust fan]
[After the toxic gas in the computer room dissipates]
[You can enter the 5th tunnel where the children are]
[If the status indicator does not light up...]
Need to start the emergency power supply equipment outside the computer room
this
[Oh? What does it mean...?]
-Status indicator - Is that one
Is this the case
[What is the status indicator?]
[Are those of Bingjae all lamps? No?]
No
Where to start...
[Other machines' equipment]
- It must not be this - It's not this
That's not it
[Is Zhenjiu there anything there?!]
[Exhaust fan joystick is inside the computer room?!]
Is the joystick in there?
-It feels inside - It seems like it's a brother
Right
[Zhen Jiu needs to communicate inside and outside now]
[Observe Baekhyun inside through the glass window]
Do you control this
[Is there anything?]
Someone must keep turning this
[There...]
[Baodhyun saw that there was a cave on the left side of it]
left
The middle there
The road in the middle
[There is a status indicator light or something written there?]
Have you written it
[A small space located at the end of the computer room]
[Status indicator]
[Wow, you have such a good vision~]
-That's what - where
Then turn it
[Bingjae status indicator may be off...]
[Bingzai, I'll try to start]
It says if the status indicator is not on
[Emergency Power Supply Equipment]
Emergency power supply equipment outside the computer room needs to be started
Need power supply
-One power supply - I'll transfer it
[Status indicator turned off attempted power supply]
-OK -OK
[Is there anything displayed?]
[One rotary power supply equipment]
[Light up!]
-It's bright and it's bright- Yes
-What is it? -Then and that side
-The inside is lit now-lit
[As soon as the power supply equipment stops rotating]
That's right
Disappeared and seemed to be turned off
[Close now]
- It disappeared and seemed to be turned off - Keep turning
Turn it all the time
[The lights will be turned off immediately when the power is stopped]
[Ah, there are five!]
Five
[Zhengjiu should have levers 1 to 5]
[Confirm 5 joysticks with Hawkeye]
[On the ceiling of the status indicator light connected to the joystick]
[Oxygen Carbon Dioxide Carbon Monoxide Methane Ammonia] [Show the air quality indicator in the computer room]
[How to operate the joystick to start the exhaust fan...]
[Explanation is being worked hard]
[Ah, what does this mean?!]
First of all, Bingzai...
[Conclusion: Bye-jae wants to stay here]
That's right
Just follow the command there, right?
right
[The strong people (?) go there]
[Dong Xuan wants to keep smart people here!]
OK
-Right - Right
[Business distribution is for smart people and strong people]
Byung Jae and Xiao Hyun must stay here
[Well~!] [Brother, go with me!]
No matter what you say, no matter what you say
[Even if Dong Xuan's big guy is infected by poison (?)]
That's right, it must be better
[Dong Hyun also spreads more slowly...!]
[We are big, so let’s sacrifice ourselves!]
OK
[Hao Tong & Dong Hyun who are ready to be dispatched]
This was really worn in the army
this...
I remembered to join the army
Oh my God
[Gas Mask ON]
this
So handsome
What should I do after I go in
[First after Brother Bingzai enters]
[Work briefing of the smart man Bingjae]
Tell me the structure inside
There are five joysticks
ON OFF ON OFF There are five
[Um!!]
[oh!!!]
First, all are adjusted to ON
[Trip and heroic]
Then I...
OK
[But Brother Picked...]
[Is it okay if your chin is not covered...?]
[There is no way to aim all the facial features!]
Eyes are aimed...
[ah...]
[If this gas mask is pointed at the eyes, your chin will not be covered]
[It's still too small to completely cover my brother's gas mask]
If your chin is covered, your eyes will be correct
That's it
-I... - Really
[Gas mask/One size I'm too small]
[Dong Xuan's chin is probably half leaking out...]
If your mouth is wide open, there may be poisonous gas and run in.
[Be careful not to open your mouth]
Be careful
Ready
Then please
-Walk slowly -Walk slowly
[Keep open the computer room door]
Pay attention to safety
Be careful
[After opening the door, I took a look inside]
[Throttle squirting poisonous gas]
[Back]
elder brother
[So scary, so scary...so scary!]
[Kao Child, but there is something to pull here (?) just as soon as the door is opened]
-Is there a cart to pull?
[What's the matter when the door is opened?!]
Really
It seems like you need to crawl forward directly
[Two trailers with wheels]
[Movement means to avoid toxic gases at a height of less than 50 cm]
[Press down the body!]
[Press below 50 cm!!!]
[Slide with your arms!!!]
good
[Do you know?!]
Um
[Brother, but the voice of your speaking]
[It seems to be emitted from outside the gas mask...?]
[No way to be loud!!]
Just lower your body
[Brother must come back alive...!]
- Just press it down a little - it doesn't matter if you press it down a little
[It is safe until 50 cm on the ground]
come on
[I'm really going now...!]
-Come on - Let's go
come on
[Lying down on the trailer against the belly]
[Move while avoiding toxic gases]
[Worry]
[Power supply]
[It's OK to go in!]
[Status indicator light that is turned on at the same time]
[The picks are all ON!]
[All joysticks are ON]
[Hao Tong said it all on the walkie-talkie]
[The intercom is ON(?!)]
It's not an intercom, but ON
[As long as the walkie-talkie is pressed, it will be ON...]
[Bingjae who received the radio]
The walkie-talkie is ON
[Um...?]
[Brother Bingzai, please tell me what color it is now?]
[Purple No. 1!]
[Blue No. 2!]
No. 3 yellow
[Baoxian who worked hard to record]
Purple blue yellow
No. 4 purple
No. 5 red over
Purple blue yellow purple red
Wait a little over
[That seems to be the second situation?]
[Current status indicator] [1. If the fifth status indicator is displayed in purple, switch the joysticks No. 4 and No. 5 to OFF] [Skip at point 1 because No. 5 is red]
[Current status indicator] [2. If the status indicator is red and yellow, each displays one, then switch No. 1 joystick to ON and No. 2 joystick to OFF] [Because each has one red and yellow, operate the joystick according to item 2]
So
[Switch to ON by 1 joystick, switch to OFF by 2 by 2!]
Please switch 1 joystick to ON
[Transfer command]
Switch to OFF over
No. 2 OFF
[No. 2 OFF over!]
[But suddenly an alarm sounded]
[What is this sound...?]
[As the alarm sounds, more toxic gases are sprayed]
[Geng Piao now makes this sound like he is about to be re-is...]
[Geng Piao operates again!]
[If the exhaust fan joystick is operating incorrectly, it is necessary to restore all joysticks to ON and then reoperate] [The joystick is operating incorrectly?!]
So go back to point 1
There is one red and yellow
[Recheck the members of the joystick operation method]
-Switch to ON by number 1 -OFF
But I just did this but the alarm sounded
[Where is wrong...?]
This one
[Discovered]
[Zhenjiu feels that seniors should also be familiar with the rules before entering?]
yes
[Brothers Geng Piao come back first over!]
You should understand the rules again before going over
[The poisonous gas is dangerous and decide to come back first]
[knew...!]
[We will be back over!]
[Back]
Thank you for your hard work over
[Dongxuan, I'll go faster!]
[Continuously discharge of toxic gases]
Really tiring
- Thank you for your hard work - Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work
[Bingjae can't see it? Can't see it clearly?]
Invisible
Because it's all gas
All are gases
[Because toxic gases and gas masks are hard to see clearly]
We have one to confirm
[Baodhyun has two purples, right?] [There are two purples!]
Yes OK
This one has been done, No. 1 ON, No. 2 OFF, No. 2 has been done, No. 1
[Baoxian who carefully observes the internal situation]
But it made a dripping sound and cut back to the original
The color has not changed, it has not changed
[The color of the status indicator has not changed in the middle]
No change or change
[Baodhyun should have to finish the operation in one go]
[Current status indicator] [1. If the fifth status indicator is displayed in purple, switch the joysticks No. 4 and No. 5 to OFF [The condition is not executed if the condition is incorrect]
[Current status indicator] [2. If one of the status indicators is red and one of the yellow colors is displayed in each, switch the joystick No. 1 to ON and the joystick No. 2 to OFF] [Conditions are executed correctly]
[Current status indicator 3. If green is displayed in the status indicator, switch No. 3 joystick to OFF] [Don't execute the condition error]
[Current status indicator 4. If the same color in the status indicator light displays more than two (inclusive), then switch No. 3 joystick to OFF and No. 4 joystick to ON] [Conditions are executed correctly]
[Because the alarm sounded after only point 2 was executed]
We only implemented point 2 but there was no change
Only the sound of the sound
Maybe try to execute points 2 and 4 together
[Points 2 and 4 that determine the correct conditions for continuous execution]
[Kao Tong is resilient...]
[The Ponyo has spent too much time now and it is difficult for two people to enter at the same time]
[Kao Tong, I will go in alone and finish it in order and tell you]
OK OK
[Dong Xuan goes in and if you need help, use the walkie-talkie to tell me that I will go in!]
-I know - OK
[The Pick Boy who walked into the computer room alone]
come on
[Because the road is very narrow (if two people go) it is even harder...]
well
come on
[I walked into the dead place alone]
[The computer room filled with more toxic gases]
[Erupt the hind legs strength]
I think that...
[To turn this!]
Why
[That status indicator light should be on!]
Keep turning
[Accidentally becoming a rotating man]
- Keep turning - Turn slowly
Do you want to keep turning
Um
[Emergency Power On]
I've arrived over
So
[First switch No. 1 joystick to ON, No. 2 joystick to OFF!]
No. 1 joystick ON No. 2 joystick OFF over
[First execute point 2. If one of the red and yellows is displayed in the status indicator, switch No. 1 joystick to ON and No. 2 joystick to OFF]
[No. 2 OFF]
alright
[And the alarm sounds again]
[Next to execute point 4. If two (inclusive) or more of the same color are displayed in the status indicator, switch No. 3 joystick to OFF and No. 4 joystick to ON]
No. 3 OFF
Switch to OFF
-Now - Want to be at the same time
Switch to OFF over
[after all...?]
[But the alarm sounded again]
[Baodhyun seems that something has not been solved now...]
[What's wrong now...]
No. 3 Yellow No. 4 Purple No. 5 Red over
[Based on the color of the status indicator light inside]
No. 2 joystick OFF over
[It is obvious that the joystick has been switched according to the conditions...]
No. 3 joystick OFF over
What to do
[No clues are found]
[Baodhyun If the alarm sounds are wrong]
[If Baekhyun means it is wrong, then he will be wrong at the beginning]
At the beginning
Purple blue yellow purple red
[An alarm sounded from the beginning of operating the first joystick]
[Is it purple over there...?]
-If so - So is the first one there
[Dong Xuan Lights on the Ceiling]
[The valve in front of Dong Xuan has numbers written]
[Then you can also see this way!]
Lying down...
[If you look lying down, you will see the opposite direction!]
That's how purple should be the fifth
[If you look at the valve light based on the front side]
[Although the order is purple, blue, yellow, purple and red]
[But lie down and look at the lights on the ceiling]
[Red-Purple-Yellow-Blue-Purple] [Sequence is reversed]
[Status indicator] [Re-crack it again in reverse order...!]
[Zheng Jiu imagined that what he saw was the opposite...]
It's the opposite
Assume
Then, do you want to try again according to this version?
[When solving problems with new ideas]
This is so complicated
[A person forgotten by everyone]
[My physical strength is not exhausted yet!]
My energy has not been exhausted yet.
[You can slowly and wisely untie it over!]
[...He seemed to say he was tired!]
[Tell us to hurry~]
[A small misunderstanding...]
OK, it will be fine immediately
[Take it slow~]
Am I going
[Worry about brother]
Who will...
I understand, I'll go
I understand, please transfer this to me
[Because of some misunderstandings, I sent Dong Hyun to enter]
I understand I understand
Brother Dongxuan will go in immediately
[Geng Piao Dong Xuan Ge will go in immediately!]
[It seems difficult for Geng Piao to have two people alone]
knew
[Agent Hao Tong Dongxuan must pay attention to safety when coming!]
[I'm here over!]
[It is worthy of being an experienced person moving forward skillfully]
[I understand!]
[The first and fifth ones should be seen in the opposite direction!]
Look at it the other way around
[Report the situation to the child who is anxious alone]
This is the first one
Purple inverse
Ready over
[No. 4 or 5 switch to OFF!]
Please switch No. 4 and No. 5 to OFF over
[Current status indicator] [1. If the fifth status indicator is purple, switch the joysticks No. 4 and No. 5 to OFF] [Because No. 5 is purple, No. 4 and No. 5 are OFF]
[No. 4, No. 5 OFF!]
-OFF-Yeah
OFF
Task completion over
The task is completed
[Baodian's voice is very good without Didi, it seems that this is right]
[The first alarm did not sound]
[Current status indicator] [2. If the status indicator is red and yellow, each displays one, then switch No. 1 joystick to ON and No. 2 joystick to OFF] [Because there is one red and yellow, No. 1 ON and No. 2 OFF]
Then No. 1 is ON and No. 2 is OFF
Please switch No. 1 to ON, No. 2 to OFF over
Task completion
[It's no sound intimacy! Did you feel like it!!]
[Geng Piao is now at the same time as No. 3 and No. 4]
[Bingjae No. 3 is OFF, No. 4 is ON]
[Current status indicator] [4. If the same color is displayed in the status indicator, switch No. 3 joystick to OFF and No. 4 joystick to ON] [Because there is the same color, No. 3 OFF and No. 4 ON]
[Geng Piao No. 3 is OFF, No. 4 is ON]
[Geng Piao must press over at the same time!]
1 2 3
alright
[No sound! Look~]
-Task completion over - OK - OK
[Current status indicator] [5. If there are currently more than two (inclusive) joysticks in the OFF state, switch the leftmost OFF joystick to ON] [What is the joystick that has been turned OFF?]
If more than two joysticks are in OFF state
According to our judgment
[What is the joystick that has become OFF at present?]
The leftmost OFF
[OFF on the left at the moment]
Cut into ON by number 2
Change to ON over on the 2nd
[Picka boy is over!]
He said it was OK
alright
No. 2 is ON
Which one hasn't been moved
[Current status indicator] [6. Switch all never-operated joysticks to the opposite direction (ON↔OFF)]
No sound has not been moved yet
[No. 1 is only No. 1!]
[The 4th moved~]
Change ON to OFF
[The joystick that has not been moved once is only No. 1]
Only No. 1 is changed to OFF
Change to OFF only No. 1
Please change number 1 to OFF over
Complete over
[Baoxian then repeat point 1 now]
[Current status indicator] [7. Repeat the first operation again last]
[Current status indicator] [1. If the fifth status indicator is purple, switch the joysticks No. 4 and No. 5 to OFF] [Because it is purple, No. 4 and No. 5 OFF]
Then because it is purple No. 4 No. 5, just change it to OFF.
Change to OFF on the 4th and 5th on the 5th over
[If this answer is correct, it will be successful...!]
[I'll try it!]
[It should be right...!]
[Switched to OFF!]
Complete over
[Buzz buzz ~] [Oh exhaust fan is running!]
alright
It's windy
[It's OK!!!]
-Successfully over - OK OK
[The exhaust fan is starting to run]
-The exhaust fan starts to run over - OK OK
Wow, OK
[Blowing away the toxic gases in the computer room]
[Thank you for your hard work in the head office of Gao Tong!]
[The boy heard the sound of the exhaust fan running!]
Thank you for your hard work
[Return to green safety light]
[The members of the gas mask can enter safely]
OK...
Thanks for your hard work...
-This is here - Too hard
[Meet with hard-earned brothers]
Wow, this breathing is not smooth
- Thank you for your hard work - You have to lie here and breathe well.
[Thanks for your hard work]
[Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!]
Go out from there
[Go to save the children as soon as possible]
Is it here
[Bingjae writes 'Trail 5' here]
-Trail 5 - This This This This
[Baodhyun wants to rescue the children as soon as possible!]
Leave
[Oh what!]
[Someone fainted!]
Is it because of toxic gases
Is it gas leaking?
[One other door and the fallen man]
[Baodhyun is suffocated because of the gas]
[Is Geng Piao seemingly not a child or a bad person?]
No, no, no
Now there are only children here
[Who is it?]
Dead
[Touch around]
[Dingding Dingding Ding] [Huh...!]
[They told us to save people quickly...!]
Save me Save me
-Save me - Hey
[A call for help in front of your eyes]
[Save me and save me!!]
Save me Save me
[The kids should be there!]
We need to save them as soon as possible
[Look for]
[Bingzai is the key!]
Key Key Key
[Dong Xuan is the administrator who locked over there!]
[Get the key to tunnel 5!]
-Have you found the key? -Yes
[Get close to him with the keys found from the corpse]
There is a key in your pocket
Want us to save them Want us to save them
[Geng Piao and the others want us to save them]
[It seems that it should be the 5th tunnel!]
Is it the 5th tunnel? Only the 5th tunnel appears?
[Follow the clues left by the kids]
-For the children - Let's go
[Escaper who came to tunnel 5]
We will save you
[Geng Piao and the others are in chaos!]
[Bingjae, I'm going to drive it!] [Dong Hyun wants to rescue them quickly!]
[What should I do with Geng Piao, they are in a mess]
[Has you been locked up here all the time!]
Why are you locked up here
[ah...!]
What's wrong
[Aren’t Geng Piao and the others dead...]
[What did Zhenjiu say? What I just heard was the voice of the children]
-Dead - Are they the children
[Dead...]
[Tunnel 5]
[Children who have turned into ashes]
[The way you stretched toward the door, you stopped doing it]
Really
[Zhenjiu I just heard the sound coming from here]
-It's the soul of the children - go in
Feeling like they are crying
Why
[Geng Piao is the children!]
[The size of Gengpo!]
[Is Geng Piao a little too small?]
- Are the children elementary school students - Are they so young
[It seems to be the soul of the children]
[A true shadow appears in the deepest part of the mine]
-Who are you - Is that just now
[Soaring sounds from the receiver]
Calm down
[And there are voices guiding them]
What is this? Help me
-Save me -Save me
-Save me - They are still alive now
[They are still alive now!]
-Living - Still alive
[Everyone said that they are still alive!!]
- Still alive - Everyone said that they are still alive
Yes, still alive
[Those are all]
[Signal sent by the soul]
[Dong Hyun's children are locked up here]
[Zhengjiu wrote a lot on the wall to save me]
The mine is about to collapse
[Why doesn't anyone come to save us? Such words...]
[The mine is about to collapse but why doesn't anyone come to save us...? Save me...]
[The mine seems to be collapsed]
[Kao Tong felt it]
[Save our mother, I'm so hungry, don't wait for me]
[Mom, I'm so hungry, mom, don't wait for me]
[There are still people here!!! Please... take us out...]
[Save us...]
[The director is the demon demon who let us die for his own desires. Why did we lock us up here and run away? I was wrong... I will not ask the director uncle to save us again... There are still people here!!! Please... take us out...]
[The mine is about to collapse but why doesn't anyone come to save us...? Save me...] [The wall full of pain]
[I feel I can't hold on anymore] [I feel I can't hold on anymore after writing here]
[I felt like I couldn't hold on anymore] [I thought they were all alive...]
[Zhen Jiu waited for the uncle of director]
[Zhengjiu seemed to lock them up here and run away!]
[Uncle Director... Why did you lock us here and run away? I was wrong... I won't ask Uncle Director to devil again to save us...]
It seems that he locked them here
I'm afraid of sucking toxic gas during the escape and die
That's it
[That demon Zhenjiu is the director]
[Zhenjiu writes here that he will no longer call him a demon]
Really bad guy
[This mine will be destroyed by that demon]
[The devil is watching]
[Brother Xiaozhe was captured by the devil and then... dead]
[That demon demon is watching Xiaozhe beheaded by the demon] [Demon of the mine]
[The director is the demon who makes us die for his own desires]
Want to meet this demon guy
[The devil is the director]
[It says here that you find them and ask us to hold a spiritual sacrifice]
If anyone finds us
[Bingjae found us]
[Bingzai also asked to hold a spiritual consolation ceremony for us]
[If anyone finds out we also, please hold a spiritual sacrifice for us, we also want to go to a warm paradise... Our name is Kim Yongji, Lee Young-ho, Gao Hyun-woo, Kim Yong-soo, Park Yoo-kwan, save our mother, I am so hungry, don't wait for me] [An extremely conspicuous sentence among many words]
[If anyone finds out we also please hold a spiritual sacrifice for us, we also want to go to a warm paradise... Our name is Kim Yongji Lee Young-ho Go Hyun-woo Kim Yong-soo Park Yoo-kun]
Comfort Festival
[Pick Boy, are we going to hold a spiritual consolation ceremony?]
I feel like we are going to hold a spiritual sacrifice
Ours
-Remember the Spirit Consolation Sacrifice - Here
[Around the kids...]
That's OK
[Please call the children's names]
[We will say three times, Ouch, hey]
[Children's simple last wish]
[Gengpo Jin Yongji]
[For the sake of my younger brothers, I can't even bear to eat beans, sesame rice]
[After going out here, I want to eat the real man of the Jin family with my brothers~15-year-old Kim Yongji! Gangwon Jeong-sun! I don’t know how the children in the village are living] [The real man of the Jin family, Kim Yongji]
Lee Young-ho
[12-year-old Kim Yong-soo at Chungbuk Cho-chi!] [13-year-old Lee Young-ho! Flowering small mountain village ~ Gangwon-do Goughson!] [Gyeong-pyeong at Gyeonggi-do! 11-year-old Park Yoo-kang] [I miss the flowering small mountain village]
[13-year-old Lee Young-ho]
Kim Yongsoo
[Responsible for communicating with children]
[Let's play with the dragon! The hometown of my life~ I am Kim Yongsoo, 12 years old from Chungbuk Choi!] [12-year-old Kim Yongsoo]
Park Yoo-kang
[I really want to eat it when I see caramel]
[Blooming small mountain village ~ Gangwon-do Gaocheng! Yang Ping, Gyeonggi-do! 11-year-old Park Yooka!! Grandma wanted me to become a gentle and fragrant person like peach blossom, apricot blossom, little azalea, so she gave this name~] [11-year-old Park Yooka]
Gao Xianyu
- Peach blossom apricot blossom small azalea - Peach blossom apricot blossom small azalea
[10-year-old Gao Hyun-woo was born in Daegu~ The flat dumplings near my house are delicious and want to eat them with your brothers after going out here] [10-year-old Gao Hyun-woo]
Oops, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
pray
[Hope you can rest in peace]
Rest in peace, children
What's going on? What's going on?
[oh...?]
It seems to be moving there
-Children-is children
[Bingjae! It's the children!]
What to do
-It's the children - the children
[Baodhyun is the kids...]
[Geng Piao Children...]
Oops hey
[Baoxian is bowing!]
What to do
[It seems like he lowered his head with thanks]
[Gone Kids]
Thanks for your hard work
[Bingjae made it with his hands to go out]
[Not in a good mood] [Bad guys]
Really
[Pick Boy But!]
[Pick Boy and the others saw...]
[The 'triangular gold' held by Director Hao Tong!] [Bingzai Jin Ruler!]
The children saw the golden ruler
[See the golden nuggets of the triangle held by the director]
If the director just ran out, the director
[If the one who fainted in the corridor is the director]
Feeling that's the director
If you see the director holding a triangle nugget
[Did that person have a gold ruler?]
Will the director have a ruler on his body?
-Director-Okay
[Bingzai went to find a golden ruler?]
Go and have a look
- Too angry - How can I do this to my children
[Look for it first...]
-His name is Su Shuhai, Su Shuhai - It's Su Shuhai
[His name is Su Shuhai!]
[The manager of Zhenjiu just now...!]
-Is it Su Shuhai - It's Su Shuhai
Is it Su Shuhai
It's Su Shuhai
[Work report time: March 10, 1942: Manager: Director Su Shuhai, the person in charge of settlement, was named Director Shu's work content - Level 2 workers sent by North Korea have increased significantly. The manpower is continuing to mine gold] [The body is not the director but the manager!]
-Su Shuhai is a manager - is a manager
[Manager Su Shuhai] [The body is not the director but the manager!]
Isn't he the director?
[The place where Director Bingjae is indeed 350 meters!]
[Baodhyun seems to be going to a 350-meter place] [You're dead] [Let's go!]
Go back on
[Chanjin Mine Profile]
[350 meters of tunnel 1st tunnel 2nd tunnel director's room is prohibited from entering and exiting]
[350 meters director's room]
[Check the keychain again]
The key we just did
The 350-meter key is here too
[Get the key at 350 meters!]
Yes, I'm going to get it
How to do this to children
[Wow Director is dead!]
[Go to the director's office to find a golden ruler!]
[Geng Piao, this is open!]
Opened
Come in
[Zhen Jiu really felt nervous at that moment...]
-Yes, kids - go
Go to 350 meters
[Go and catch the director now!]
[Press 350 meters to set off]
[710 meters: tunnel 5] [Elevator] [600 meters] [350 meters: director's room]
Go up
[Help them get revenge!] [Here do you want to get revenge!]
[Arrival 350 meters underground]
That's right
[Beat him! When you see him...]
[Face-to-face 5 minutes ago]
-Is it the place we just went? - Different and different
It's 350 meters
-350 meters-Length
[Elevator] [Shh] [Pick Boy is not sure what the situation is now...]
It's where
[It seems that Zhenjiu heard a voice from him]
[The door on Zhenjiu is open]
[It's all destroyed here]
[What's going on?]
It says the director's room
[...it was emptied]
[The Zhenjiu Gate has been destroyed, has it been emptied?]
[Dean's Office]
[Dean Office] [Dean Office]
This is indeed the director's room
[I don't know if it's because of the collapse, it has turned into a mess here]
[Director Kim Youluo]
Director Kim Youluo
Now it's all
[Bingjae feels like someone has come]
Could it be that I forced myself to break in and it was empty
[What's wrong with Geng Piao where did this kid go?]
What's going on
[No traces of the director]
We don't even know what Jin Youluo looks like
[Do Dong Xuan run away because she is about to collapse here? She ran away by herself?]
It is also possible
[Geng Piao is about to collapse here, so bring your own luggage...]
This kid
[Bingjae escaped to survive because he was about to collapse?]
-There is a lock here -There is a lock here
[There is a lock here!]
-Is the number - The lock head of the four-digit number
yes
[Bingjae feels like he wants to go out from here...]
[How to open it...?]
[Where should I have the Pickaxe boy]
The clue must be somewhere
[Dong Xuan survives for his own life...]
There is something, there is a manual, there is a manual
There is a manual and a manual
[Discovered the manual in the drawer]
- There is a manual and a manual - There is a manual
OK
There is a manual
[Bing Jae-sen started looking at it from the front]
[August 14, 1941]
[On August 14, 1941, I found a magical thing called a golden ruler deep in the tunnel. The legendary golden ruler was actually taken by me! My life has been digging coal for 10 years]
[The director who obtained the golden ruler]
There is also dawn
It's coal
[August 23, 1941]
[The golden veins started to flow near the golden ruler inserted]
[It's time to mine gold formally]
[Dongxuan coal has become gold mine]
[Because of the power of the gold ruler, coal becomes gold]
[February 5, 1942]
[Gold mining volume is rising vertically]
[Requires sending 2nd-level North Korean workers to support]
[When the limit is not met, the meal delivery time is reduced by half and the entry time is extended]
I have so much money...
[Baodhyun is really bad...]
May 17 stupid guys calling me devil
[You actually call him a demon who gives you food, clothing and work?] [Really...]
[Who is it thanks to you to be able to eat and live a full life]
[Geng Piao seems to not like to hear others calling him a demon]
[This demon guy...!]
[Bingzai is a word question and answer... It seems this is it!]
What
[Crossword] [A piece of paper sandwiched in the middle of the manual]
Words are filled in
[Crossword Game] [Today is very simple...]
[Uncle Golden Ruler is too bad, gold medal idiot] [Today is very simple...] [It seems that the director has unlocked it]
There are four grids here
[What about four lattices here?]
Four grids
[Bingjae is the first one to be the first!]
The person in charge of the company, the president No. 1 is 4 (Note: the same as the social pronunciation)
[① The person in charge of the company = president]
The word "Horizon" is to demean others' timidity
[After that's]
[⑤Terms that belittle others' timidity] [Coward]
- Coward-2 (Note: The ending pronunciation is the same as the second)
The 6th day and night cannot be forgotten
[Bing Jae-ji's No. 6 ⑥ Can't forget it day and night]
[Baodhyun is careful of fire!]
-Several characters - Four-character idioms
[Bingzai four-character idiom!]
Can't forget it day and night
What is the proof of the proof of the proof of the proof of the
[Bone-in-the-bone-in-the-bone-in-the-bone-in-the-bone
-Engraved on the bones - is unforgettable
[The unforgettable favors should be carved into bones and cannot be forgotten]
- It is unforgettable - engraved on the bones
[Awkward]
- It is unforgettable - it is unforgettable on the bones
[Ah!] [Don't forget to sleep!]
-Don't forget when you are asleep -Don't forget when you are awake
Never forget
That's 425
[Uncle President Jin Chi Tai Medal (same leader) Gold medal coward is sleeping and never forgets the idiot] [Today is very simple...]
Then there is the 8th of the horizontal
[⑧ Personal daily life] [Private life]
-Personal small daily private life -Private life
[Uncle (same pronunciation as four) President Jin Chi-ta Medal (same length) Gold medal coward (same pronunciation as two) Living (same fifth) Sleeping and not forgetting the idiot privately (same fourth) life] [Today is very simple...] [4254 Four numbers that appear after solving the puzzle]
-4 -4254
-4254 -4254
[Dong Xuan, OK!!]
very good
[Already waiting]
4254 Zhenjiu is over
Opened
-4254 - Very good
[Oh, it's open!]
[Geng Piao Wow 4254 is opened directly!]
-Is there anything else - What's wrong?
[Ha really...]
-What's wrong - Is there anything else
[I only saw a little bit of Geng Piao...?]
[Is there blood and the like on the ground?]
Really
Is there anything else
[Someone who died on the ground]
[Dong Xuan seems to be that person?]
[Isn't it Kim Woo-ro?]
-Isn't Kim Yoro-Rao-It's Kim Yoro
[And behind him]
[Dongxuan is the golden vein!]
That position is the position of the gold ruler
[Zheng Jiu turned over and took a look? See who it is?]
Usually the name is written
[Kim Woo-ro]
It's the director
[It's Kim Yoro]
It's Director Kim Youluo
[...But what is this?]
[The dead director is surrounded by blood-stained gold nuggets?]
Has anyone beat him with this
[Is Dong Hyun beaten like this?]
Really
[Like he killed]
That's it
[There are gold nuggets on Baekhyun]
[Baodhyun seemed to have been hit on the back of the head]
[So this is a killing]
[It must be a conflict with someone]
[Bingzai, let me read this]
[A special project to increase gold mining volume is carried out for logging Jin Youluo]
[Lampbook found in the director's clothes]
[November 5, 1941]
[After some inquiries, I got in touch with the tomb robbers introduced by Teacher Xiao Cang]
[Spend a lot of money to buy another gold ruler]
[Buy another gold ruler?]
Golden ruler
[...Are there two gold rulers?] [Since there are two gold rulers]
[Bingzai expects the mining volume to double up?]
[Can Geng Piao find two gold rulers here?]
Two gold rulers
[We want to find five gold rulers in Gengpao!]
Two pieces...
[If Geng Piao finds out this time, we will find all the gold rulers]
[There are two gold yards in this mine?]
[December 12, 1941]
[Researcher Li Shuojing found me and said she wanted to study the gold ruler]
[People who were awarded the National Golden Rhythm Medal]
-Increase the amount of gold mining - Brother, this seems to be the Golden Ruler and the Medal
[Zhen Jiu seems to be the Golden Ruler Medal!]
There are golden ruler patterns here
[The medal held by the dead director]
[Bingzai's golden ruler when he was a child...]
[Huh? Huh!]
-What's going on - What's wrong
[Proposal to maximize the power of the gold ruler to increase the amount of gold mining. When I was a child, I saw using the gold ruler to cultivate hallucinations to control others... I seem to know the gold ruler very well? Because there will be no losses, I agree to cooperate]
I wrote here that I have seen it since I was a child
Use a golden ruler to cultivate hallucination flowers to manipulate others
[Baodhyun, that's that]
[Baoxian Baibaijin Sect? It seems to be related to it]
That's it
-Last time-last time
[Concerned with Platinum Church?]
Related to that story
If I were a kid, there were only two children there.
[There are only two children in Bingjae]
-Yes, yes - does that mean
[Bingjae's children wearing owls...]
Let's relax first and quench your thirst
Is he Li Shuojing
[He is growing up now]
It's possible
-Grown up - But we
It seems to be that person
[December 28, 1941]
Teacher Li began to secretly study in the gold mine
[Li Shuojing, who officially started researching the golden ruler]
[A gold ruler for research was deployed in the laboratory]
[The first gold ruler I've been in metallurgy]
[The second gold ruler that Li Shuojing is studying]
[January 18, 1942]
Successfully increased gold mining volume in 710 meters tunnel
[Experiment successful in increasing gold mining]
Although Teacher Li is concerned
[Although I am worried that the mine will collapse due to side effects]
The mine may collapse due to side effects
[Mining of gold is the most preferred]
But mining gold is the most preferred
[February 14, 1942]
Teacher Li, do you want to use a golden ruler to study life?
[February 14, 1942 Teacher Li... Do you want to use a golden ruler to study life? A mere outsourcing research institute said such overestimating one's own ability... Instructed him to only focus on gold experiments]
A mere outsourcing research institute says such overestimating one's own ability
[Bingjae seems to have some conflicts between them]
[Li Shuojing, who wants to use the golden ruler for life research]
[The purpose of the director is to mine gold]
[April 5, 1942]
[A part of the tunnel collapsed 710 meters underground]
The 5th tunnel also shaking violently and gas leaked out
[Gas leakage also occurred in tunnel 5]
[Although there are several children working, they decided to lock down]
[Baodhyun so those kids were locked up just now...]
yes
[Into a dangerous mine]
[You can't die like this. I will take the golden ruler and gold out of here tomorrow. The golden ruler in the laboratory must be taken away.]
So he...
[I had a conflict with Mr. Lee and I originally wanted to go out]
[Teacher Bingzai Li uses gold nuggets to help him win his strength...]
-So Teacher Li used this to control him... -That's it
[Zhen Jiujin Ruler also took away]
[The bad guy is the best choice for the better. The bad guy is framed by the worse guy]
[Bingjae, the golden ruler is not here...]
It was originally embedded here
[Bingjae must find Teacher Lee?]
Yes, I want to find Teacher Li
[Baoxian, but Teacher Li said there are still remaining experiments...?]
Somewhere
[Geng Piao, we want to find the laboratory]
Did you have a similar laboratory just now?
Surely somewhere
Go to find a lab
[Baodhyun goes out here first?]
To get out we have to get out from here
-Li Shuojing is the child in religion-Platinum Education
[Go to the laboratory to find Li Shuojing...]
[Elevator of Director Kim Youluo's Room]
But there is a high chance that the kid is
-Because everyone else was poisoned - Yes
-Here-they
[Baodhyun feels a bit like a lab here]
[found at the end of the corridor]
Here is the experiment Here is the laboratory
[Elevator Laboratory of Director Jin Youluo's Office]
-The place just now - is it a laboratory
[Director Kim Youluo's Elevator Laboratory] [What's going on with this door...?]
[Baodhyun, I think this door will fall]
[Why is Zhenjiu so messy here?]
[The laboratory where even the door is incomplete]
-Now - Because of collapse
[Gengpo's probably crushed when it collapsed]
Stumped
[Zhen Jiu wants to move this away first]
This is for us
[The powerful pick boy who came forward naturally]
-It's the most basic - Be careful with your hands
[When you look at the crooked door]
Try backwards backwards
Brother Hao Tong will try it
Going in one direction
[Be careful I want to move]
A little back
-Backward and backward-what
[The heroes of the world who are directly pulled out]
Opened
[The rest is also broken]
Should this be opened like that?
[Tear the door down and appear the pane]
What's this to be pulled out
[The pane fell!]
Falled
[Since that's the case...]
-So it's just to pull it out to get in - No way
Is this how
-This - Be careful with your hands
[Panal also pulled off]
-How OK -How OK
It's okay, it's okay
[Breaking and smashing the active performance of the pick kid]
-This level - This is enough
It's okay, it's okay
[Dong Xuan! That's all!]
[After moving the box in front of the door]
OK, just turn it over
[Dong Xuan, I will turn over and help you]
[Dong Hyun Oh enough is enough!]
[Dong Hyun successfully entered]
Be careful
Come in
[Guardian]
careful
Sticked
Go here
-Because of long legs -Because of long legs, I will come in immediately
[All 6 people successfully entered]
[Bingjae seems to be the laboratory here]
[Space that has become ruins]
[Like a burned black furniture]
[and the remaining experimental traces]
[Li Shuojing's laboratory]
[Bingzai seems to have done a lot of animal experiments]
Yes, it seems that a lot of animal experiments have been done
[Posted everywhere]
[Traces of animal experiments]
[Geng Piao, however, looked like this, collapsed a lot]
[Geng Piao feels that it will collapse here soon]
This has been shaken once
[The laboratory that has collapsed once]
-Yes now - shaking so hurry up
[There is a burnt smell!] [It's a bit a little...]
Not so much time not so calm
[Not so calm!]
How many experiments have been done here
[The gold ruler that starts to shine at this time]
Here
-The golden ruler is ringing - The golden ruler is ringing
[Dong Xuan! It seems to be around here]
-Nearly here in here in here-In here
It's almost found
Yes, it seems that a lot of animal experiments have been done
[What is this Bingzai? This thread...?]
How many experiments have been done here
[The hanging line suddenly caught in the eyes]
It seems to extend from there
[Connect into the door]
[Do you want to open Zhenjiu and take a look?]
- Can it be opened - Can it be opened
[Zhenjiu can't open]
[There is a password with a number here]
[The safe has not been completely burned]
-Several digits -Four digits
- It should be unbuttoned - it should be opened with a safe
[oh?]
-What's wrong - What's wrong
Dogs, rats, what is chicken?
[Anatomy paintings are everywhere]
This is a chicken
Are they the twelve zodiac signs?
[The password is related to the twelve zodiac signs!?]
-But there are lions - there are crocodile
[But there is a lion...]
[Is it a giant python (?) a crocodile... it is a giant...]
[In short, it has nothing to do with the twelve zodiac signs] [Lion] [Crocodile or giant python]
There must be somewhere else
[Is Bingzai or the number of animal legs like this?]
[Number of legs...?]
-But there are too many here - Yes
[Ambiguous]
Four digits
But there are still people there
[Oh, there is!]
What's going on
Here
-What is it - Safe Password for this month
[Safe password for this month]
[Bingjae who slowly observes]
[367...]
[367...5!]
[Bingjae who says the numbers]
3 6 7
[Um?]
-What's wrong? -5
[What's wrong?...?]
[Doubt] [Bingzai uses a mirror to mirror]
-How to guess it - Do you use a mirror
[Unsolved]
[Wow...too strong]
[Wow, right]
-Yes, yes - How can I guess it right away
It turned out to be half divided
[Safe Password for this month] [Divide unknown shapes in half]
Divide in half
-Use this method - Divide into half
[Safe password 3675 this month] [You can see four digits]
[The genius Bingjae who will be mastered immediately]
[Real sigh]
-You really - This is really
[He is over!]
That's right, right
What is his reasoning
[Will the password be 3675?]
Scare me
[Password is 3675!!!]
Opened
[Hey! Wow, really...]
You really...
[How can I guess it at first glance?]
This level
[Not angry]
Too strong
[Why is it so powerful]
How could it be
-Thank you - This
[You are really excellent!]
It takes 1 hour
[shy]
real
-What is that - is the research log
-And - It's the key
[Research Log Qianjin Mining Institute]
[Bingjae seems to be the key to that door]
It should be
Take a look at the research log
[The log records Li Shuojing's detailed research content]
February 14, 1942
[Research content and results writing date: February 14, 1942 Writer: Researcher Li Shuojing's research content discovered the correlation between gold ruler and life phenomena]
The director said
[In the fifth experiment, the resurrection of the hibiscus bird that died around the golden ruler was observed to confirm that the golden ruler may have an impact on restoring life and treating wounds]
The one just now
[Use the golden ruler to restore life]
[The results of multiple research reveal the new power of the golden ruler]
[Additional research is needed on this, but the director only instructed me to study to increase the mining volume]
[Decided to conduct additional A-level confidential experiments (not reported to the director)]
[Confidential experiments were conducted without authorization]
Director Kim Youluo
The contradiction with him is this
[Research results use the magnetic field of the golden ruler amplifier in mice for the first experiment: the heartbeat is restored and life activities are observed successfully, but after 5 minutes, the second experiment: the dead rat completely restores life. It confirms that the golden ruler has a strong influence on restoring life and treating wounds. It is speculated that the golden ruler has supernatural ability to restore life and treat wounds. Decide to conduct additional S-class confidential experiments (maintain the status that has not been reported to the director): Hurry up before all the mines collapse]
The dead rat completely restores life
[Have the dead rats waiting for the Pakatani are resurrected??]
yes
-Resurrection completely -Resurrection completely
Confirmed the golden ruler
[A thing the more you experiment, the clearer it becomes]
It has a strong influence on restoring life and treating wounds
[Gold ruler can heal wounds and restore life]
Speculation of the golden ruler
Have supernatural abilities to restore life and heal wounds
[Bingzai uses the magnetic field of the gold ruler amplifier to the dead dog and cat]
[Forced animal experiments with the power of a golden ruler]
[The howling of animals that penetrates the walls...] [Reasons that the howling of animals resounds throughout the mine]
[Howl...creepy]
[But an extraordinary experiment brought disaster]
[final]
[Laboratory explosion]
[The tunnel collapsed one after another after the explosion]
[Cursed Mine]
[Laboratory is the source of all disasters]
A bunch of assholes
What is very disturbing is
[Bingjae's back was torn off]
[Research content and results are written on February 14, 1942 by: Researcher Li Shuojing's experiment on using the golden ruler to restore life and treat wounds (S-class confidential experiment) Research results The magnetic field of the golden ruler amplifier is suitable for dogs, cats' first experiment: Research topic for restoring heartbeat: humans in the future]
[Experiment of using the golden ruler to restore life and treat wounds (S-class confidential experiment) Research results Apply the large magnetic field of the golden ruler amplifier to dogs and cats for the first experiment: Research topic for restoring heartbeat: humans in the future]
[Bingjae research topic, human sex in the future...]
[Bingjae...it was torn off until here]
A confidentiality experiments were conducted on animals
[Maybe Li Shuojing]
It is intended to be upgraded to an S-class confidential experiment implemented on humans
[Try to expand the experiment further?]
This part was torn off
-In the end, disasters are brought to others - Yes
[Li Shuojing's whereabouts are unknown now]
[How about hurry up...]
[First decide to open the locked door!]
Want to open
[I'm opening?]
[Back]
1 2 3
[oh???]
What
-What is this - What is this
What is it
[Baodhyun is like the one who lives]
It's a gold ruler
Is there a gold ruler?
[The Pick Boy is now connected by wire]
[Zhen Jiu should have pulled all these forces to do research]
-The power of a gold ruler-Yes
Go to use
[Gold ruler amplifier]
There is a gold ruler and a key
[Familiar flower shapes and keyholes]
There is a hole in this
-What does it look like - Very thin
[What does Baekhyun look like?]
-Little key -Little key
- Do you want to go outside again? Find the keys
[Bingzai looks for the key?]
There is no place to hide the key
[Dong Hyun has no place to hide...]
Similar to the type of journal key
[Each one is spread out and carefully check each corner]
Where to find such a small key
[Not...Xiaoxian]
It should be here
[Will the Pickaxe boy be here? Will he be here?]
Yes here
[I think it's here]
[Is there something on the door? Patterns?]
What
[The metal sound comes again]
[What...?]
[When everyone was shocked]
Do you need to write it down quickly?
[Baoxian in the concentration]
[Ding Ding Ding Ding Ding Ding Ding]
[Singing singer]
[Chinese alphabet number playing method a ya gnd]
Ding Ding Ding Ding Ding Ding
[Record it now...!]
What's going on
[Wow...How did Xiaoxian memorize it?]
[It's really worthy of it!!!]
[Wow...so amazing...]
[alright!]
[Things like a cat boy are really amazing]
-That's to say - how did I memorize it?
[Hao Tong has a complete absolute sound feeling?]
[concentrated]
I was frightened in an instant and couldn't do anything
[I probably remembered the fourth one]
[If you analyze it now]
Ding Ding Ding Ding G
[go]
Then it seems to be o
[National letter code code type a ya eo yeo o yo u yu eu ign drmbs ng j ch ktphgoma ng u eo ng yo]
- the gymune
-Thank you - Thank you
[Chinese alphabet number playing method a ya eo yeo o yo u yu eu ign drmbs ng j ch ktph] [Thank you]
-No, no, no, none of them could save you
[Last message left by the children]
We're even more sorry
-No need to thank - Sorry
[I failed to save their guilty feelings faster]
Really heartache
[However, the key was not found]
What is this
[Is it a reminder for the 'thank you' what Bingjae children said?]
-Thank you - Thank you
[The sudden sound of the children is a reminder?]
[oh?]
What's wrong
[Is it here?]
-Where-What's wrong here
[What's there in it?]
Yes
-What - What, what
[Did the Bingjae children give us a big reminder?]
[Although it was extinguished when I first came in]
This is now connected by wire
-What is this - What is this
[The message starts to flash with the children]
-Thank you thank you - Thank you
[If you look at the light carefully]
[You can see the form of the key...!]
There is a small thing
[Bingjae now gives us a tip using this]
Use this light now
[Zhenjiu has something!]
[Dong Hyun, after all, I have done some exercises]
Be careful, be careful, be careful, be careful, be careful, be careful
[Da Xuan who lets Xiaoxian ride his neck]
Here
this
[Dong Xuan slow... Just do it quickly (?)]
This should be just taken out like this
[Slowly get the key quickly and successfully]
-1 2 3 -Thank you
[Thank you, Geng Piao children]
Thank you kids
-Thank you all - Thank you
[Thanks to the end]
[Geng Piao is good now! Let's open it]
[The gold ruler amplifier finally opened]
-But it's really too irritating - Is there any
have
It's a golden ruler
[Bingjae seems to Lee Shuo-jin take a piece and leave]
Only 1 yuan is left, wasn't there 2 yuan?
[The remaining gold ruler is only one piece]
[Finished...!]
- Found - We finally
-Yes with Li Shuojing-After all
[The fourth gold ruler is obtained from this]
Probably missed
[at this time]
What's going on...
[Roaring roar]
It's going to collapse
It collapsed and all collapsed
[Mine that began to collapse]
Go quickly...
-What to do - hurry up
[Take out a gold ruler]
-Hurry... -Hurry...
[Collapse at an astonishing speed]
Hurry up
[You have to leave here as soon as possible]
-Brother, this - Go quickly...
-It's this, this - Let's go...
[The light that shines out from the wall at that moment]
[It's this, this, this, this!]
[Two physically capable and instinctive kicks]
Hurry up
-Where there - Let's go...
[Waiting for time machine]
- Let's go - It's going to collapse.
[Put the mine that is about to collapse completely]
It's going to collapse
[Hurry to take the time machine]
OK
Too strong
Success
[A few days before the escapee arrived at the mine...]
[On the day of the laboratory explosion]
[Li Shuojing, who hurried to get the gold ruler]
Really
[However, I can't enter the lab that explodes]
How could it be damn why can't I open it
[Put down the remaining gold ruler and are arguing loudly with the director]
["Escape: The Story"]
[To find the last gold ruler fragment]
- Go and look for it quietly - Go and look for it quietly
[There are really many weapons!!!]
[Their secret battle has begun!]
[Bingjae must come back alive]
["Escape: The Story" - The Last Story-]
[However, unexpected attack]
Run quickly...
Too many
[Three people have died!]
Just arrived
Run quickly...
[The monster slowly threatens life]
You guys
[To be alive, you must find it]
-Here Here-Where
[Dong Xuan is looking for his life by betting on the ground. Is this a sign of plagiarism???]
[The final gold ruler]
It's a golden ruler
1 2 3 4 5 yuan
[and someone staring at them]
Shot
-Shooted
[Kao boy, I want to cry so much]
[The hidden power of the gold ruler]
- Go wherever you want to go - No
[The ending will be...?]
there...
Where to go...
Let's go
[Must kill]