[Episode 9]
[A Perfect Match]
Did you have sex with Lin Xiaonan?
Shut your mouth up.
-Zhang Weixiong!
-It hurts.
Show me some respect.
Go up yourself.
I'll leave.
It hurts! Help me up!
Come on!
Hurry up.
[Yulin Creative Soup]
I've already sent you home.
Don't call me again.
-Or Xiaonan will misunderstand me.
-Tianxiang,
I know you have Lin Xiaonan now,
who is the general manager of Mr. Wensen. So, you don't need me anymore.
Yes.
So, don't get in the way.
[Slide to answer]
[Xiaonan]
What?
Hey, Tianxiang, where are you?
I...
I'm in the gym.
Okay.
Enjoy your training.
I'll go back soon. Bye.
What?
You're in my house.
But you dare not let him know, huh?
None of your business.
I'm back.
Where did you go?
I went to the gym.
I told you before.
The gym?
Why didn't I see you when I went to the gym?
Grandma looked for me.
So, I went to see her.
Then what is this?
Tell me!
You misunderstood.
Cheng Tianxiang, I never thought you would lie to me.
I changed my life for you and compromised with you.
What did you do?
You two-timed me, and you want to cheat me?
There's nothing between me and Zhang Weixiong.
It was not what you saw.
I saw that
you two were intimate.
Stop quibbling.
It was not what you saw.
Get out!
Don't be angry. Listen to me.
Get lost.
Why are you back now?
Shouldn't you take care of Xiaoruo?
She went to bed, so I came back.
Something must be wrong.
Didn't you say you would go to the gym
to improve muscular endurance
for the tennis competition?
Why didn't you go to the gym?
I don't want to attend the competition.
What's wrong with him?
-Weixiong.
-Mr. Jiang.
It worked.
Haha.
-This if for you.
-Thank you.
Don't mention it. It's your idea.
You ruined the relationship between Tianxiang and Xiaonan.
They broke up.
I heard that Lin Xiaonan
hasn't gone to the court to practice these days.
Their company is in a mess.
Of course, they must be fighting right now.
How could they be in the mood to practice?
That's right. We'll wait for them to give up.
Then, the committee will announce that our company will replace them.
By then,
you can attend the competition as our representative.
Congratulations. Thank you, Mr. Jiang.
How dare Zhang Weixiong play such a trick?
I won't let him make it.
Tianxiang!
Why did you do this to me?
Don't you know I love you?
God,
why did you treat me like this?
My parents have left me.
I'm finally in love with someone
but you ruined everything.
What happened?
Grandma told me you were in a bad mood.
Did you quarrel with Xiaonan?
Tell me.
I went to the gym a few days ago.
Yes?
Guess who I met.
Zhang Weixiong.
He hurt his foot,
so he asked me to take him home.
And?
I'm
too soft-hearted.
I sent him home.
Guess who saw it?
-Lin Xiaonan.
I tried to explain but it was useless.
He got mad and kicked me out of his house.
What can I do?
Let me show you something.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. It's your idea.
You ruined the relationship between Tianxiang and Xiaonan.
They broke up.
I heard that Lin Xiaonan
hasn't gone to the court to practice these days.
Their company is in a mess.
Zhang Weixiong is a jerk.
I told you.
Thanks god. You have me as your best friend.
I met them at that cafe.
They were discussing
this stupid plan.
Send this to me.
What are you doing?
I'll show it to Xiaonan.
Now?
Yes.
I will accompany you.
I'm your witness.
Xiaonan.
Isn't he at home?
Check whether he is in his room.
Xiaoruo.
Xiaonan.
Xiaonan!
-Xiaoruo.
Xiaonan.
-Xiaoruo, why are you crying?
-What's wrong?
Xiaonan abandoned me.
Tianxiang abandoned me, too.
No, I will not abandon you.
Where is your brother?
He went for a walk on the beach. He hasn't come back yet.
I'll go find Xiaonan.
Take care of Xiaoruo.
Okay. Hurry up.
Good girl, don't cry.
Let's watch TV in the living room, okay?
Okay.