I'm not afraid of the future
Flowers fall and flowers bloom in the wind
The moon in the water
The hard part of the moon in the world
Always have a wind, a fog, a wolf, a wind, a river
The falling flowers, the flowing water, the rain, the flowers in the water
If the dream is like you
Always have a thousand years of life, no words, no breath
The rain is falling, the tears are all gone
The rain in another world
The snow in the snow is waiting for you
Waiting for you
Episode 1
Why are you still not asking?
Why?
Where is the antidote?
The antidote
You are not poisoned at all
It's not me
You knew it long ago
Yes
I did get poisoned
But I didn't get poisoned
I just didn't get poisoned
I lied to the Chinese
But because I was poisoned again
So all of this
Everything you see
The magic you see
It's not fake
Why did you do this?
You know it clearly
I want to kill you
Because of this
I can take this opportunity to show you the truth
I hope
This dream
Will never wake up
But this dream
Will still wake up
Yes
Because I am a demon
I am the leader of Mount Zu
I am the messenger of the wind and moon
I am the hope of many people
I will go down the road
And the door of the five-spirited forest
I will destroy the evil dream of demons
And the fate of my life
I will go down the road
And the light of the world
You did this for these people
Did you sacrifice yourself?
I did it for the people I love
Even if I die
I will save you
Ok
I tell you where I want to go
I want to save you in Li Guhe and Pupu
The red city is full of red waves
No one can cross the border
Do you want to go there?
I am the first one in Mount Zu
To protect the world and live for the people
To see people in life and death
I have no choice
I have never seen someone like you
So stupid
Wait for me to come back
You came back so early
Yes, we were tired of drinking water
Go to sleep
I'll go to the main court,
and find out what's going on inside the mansion.
Tell them to move.
As long as no one orders usIGotar to move,
then we'll grant one form of land and two charter.
All right.
We've already got the token that we can pass through the barrier.
We can't leave now either.
Why don't we just wander around here?
Walk around? What time is it?
Can we use the machine to do random changes?
There are still a few hours left before the sun rises.
Maybe we can find Mo Xiao before the sun rises.
Let's go.
Is this the dungeon that Senior Brother Lu mentioned?
We haven't found Mo Xiao for a long time.
I think he should be locked up here.
Let's go and see.
What are you doing?
You're here to pick the person from the county forest again?
Hurry up!
Let's go.
You must pass through the red dust on me.
Only seven emotions can pass through.
If you have the red dust in your heart,
you must be punished by the stone of the valley.
You can't use any magic power.
You can only use one body to come here.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Da گ ship.
Count the rest of them and tell yourself,
Auntie, I'll get rid of the Xiangido creature now.
Don't worry.
I won't only take revenge on a harem main characters
in the long drafts andン
Wait for it.
Third, you should eat with the kitchen knife.
You should use the soup.
You should use the soup stone.
The sun shines on the moon.
The moon shines on the moon.
Every morning when the storm stops,
the waves of taxes rise,
and we put on our deviceswhite.
I knew that you wouldn't leave.
I can't burgers.
Every moment,
hundreds, thousands,
years,
I can't quit my tear 낙兵,
流泛,
the rain on the other side.
After Ming meet you,
but have no one in the world know your name
And talk like bung Seto
Empress
Is Princess
Little Rare
If I'm always like this
I start to feel anxious
I contribute the most
protect you
I
Xia
I'm by His Majesty's side.
I am established by all of you through your warm love.
No one can save the cause by your love.
What do you want?
A good chance?
I will take it.
frog
I need etwas
Solus
Father, Father, that's much better.
Out of the above two?
fingertips must stay knotted like that.
And if his death sentence straightens to more then 60ч
his death sentence is no longer 20 frente
You're pregnant now.
How are you expecting your life in here?
We have got the token of Jincheng Huan Palace.
That's right.
But we haven't found the Demon Lord.
So it is.
Brother Xie.
These martial arts warriors are from the martial arts world.
They have been devoured.
They can't go through this barrier today.
You should find a safe place to hide.
And put them in place.
I will take them to find Demon Lord and get the antidote.
My Grand Master.
Then you all be careful.
Leave it to me.
Let's go.
Li Yun.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Who are you?
This is Demon Lord, Li leng.
Let's go.
Welcome to Changhuang Palace.
You are?
Murong Changfeng?
Chonggong.
The Temple..
really Instant firework
Your Art医
has caused Monitorая
To turn there
And I am a PHOENIC
哦
If you acted by force right now,
주볛會向外人策略終有你,
And continue saying that
if you are now trying to hide your right now
and hand your anger ontop you psychologicalThoughts,
your antidote away to Field of Plenty
and return to Mount Suyu for Classical Law.
Our candidates will be even more offshore
and not be willing to kill you.
You're threatening me?
But I need to be full of hatred.
Do you?
You don't have me.
Your sect leader is still in my hands.
What's wrong with Mo Xiao?
Village Leader, Mo Xiao has found the antidote.
All the symptoms in the city are gone.
Are you sure?
Mo Xiao, are you okay?
Village Leader.
Uncle Hongrong, you should leave the factory first.
Leave it to me.
Okay, then you should be more careful.
Let's go.
Feng Lixian.
I'm sorry.
Your poison is gone?
Jianchuan, you stay here.
Protect this place and help Village Leader.
Yes.
There is still some of the people who were killed by the devil.
I'll take them there.
Okay, you go.
Cui'er, Ling Yuanyuan.
Let's go to the small courtyard and meet Jing'er first.
Make arrangements.
We'll meet them at any time.
After the devil is gone,
we'll leave the people of the Valley of Love.
Yes.
Let's go.
You are indeed the heir of Feng Yue.
You are so young.
You made me love money.
How about this?
How about you and I?
Just like we were in the night court.
Only our两人是存税,
we had the same fate.
Others devised a hunre even after the fatal disaster.
Ors can help us.
18 years ago,
you and Demon Militia stole the Spear Devourer.
And you returned to Suyu Mountain.
I didn't expect about 18 years in the past,
you were still not young.
Was it you...
You just don't understand me at all?
You aren't thinking of joining me?
Isn'tths are my duty as a named warrior.
He has already entered the valley.
Maybe one day, you will discover
that I can change your fate.
You are optimistic and satisfied.
You will finally realize your own mistakes.
They are willing to let me go.
Just like
Feng Li Xue.
Next, you will be the one.
Then I will destroy your demon spirit.
Bring it on.
Jing Er, you were poisoned just now.
The poison has been removed. It's okay now.
Brother, I will not do anything
that can't be seen.
Of course not.
Jing Er, you have to ask me about this.
I can tell you about Luo Kuang.
Father.
I thought I would never see you again.
What are you talking about?
You are fine. I am relieved.
You are not?
Cui Er, hurry up and seal the seal.
Send this situation back to Mount Zu.
Let the sect leader and senior brother rest assured.
Yes, father.
Where are the three guards?
They are sitting in the middle of the street.
What happened to Zi Su?
Don't stand there.
Go and have a look.
Yes.
Huo Xiao.
It's okay.
You have saved the one you want to save.
Aren't you leaving?
There is one more person I want to save.
Li Xuan, follow me.
You have a chance to regret.
If I say I won't leave.
Li Xuan, you let go of the image we saw on the TV show of Snow Phoenix.
I will find out the truth about Fu Chou.
Take your Tong Wen Zong with you.
Master is a good person.
You broke his love.
He won't let go of his feelings.
Li Xuan, I will find out the truth.
You...
No need.
It has nothing to do with you.
Li Xuan.
We must do this.
I will find out the truth.
You are the heart of the mountain.
I am the star of the demon world.
There is no choice between us.
You don't understand.
I believed you.
But later I found out that everything is fake.
You are so naive.
I am indeed clever for being loved.
But because of this.
I am telling the truth.
If it is not for love.
I am the one who is the master of the mountain.
I am afraid I will never be able to say it.
Your Majesty.
We have no choice but to kiss.
I can only kiss at this song ceremony.
Without your permission.
You are not a good person.
Tu biomass man
Only last night.
Lord!
Xiao Hu.
Xiu...
I don't know what others think.
But I know it better than anyone.
Actually, you've always been loving the young master.
But you can't express your love to the door.
This time, you're addicted to love and love.
So you dare to be true to your love.
I made such a big mistake this time.
Do you think the young master will drive me out of the Heaven's Garden?
Silly girl.
What's wrong with liking?
The young master is so talented.
Which woman in the world doesn't like a man like him?
Besides, you two are in a relationship.
You're in love for a long time.
Zi Su.
Do you like the young master too?
I've already surpassed the love of the man and the woman
for the sake of my liking.
The young master is the future master of the Mount Zu.
The leader of the Immortal Sect is the one I want to follow in my life.
What I want to do in my life is to help him achieve the merit of the Immortal Sect.
So I can work hard for my life.
What else is not enough to satisfy me?
We've been cultivating together since we were young.
Why do you have so many things to do?
But you always make me feel uncomfortable.
I'm from Feng Yu Sect.
I wish the young master can do everything in his power.
I'm naturally more obedient.
So,
I've seen through some things.
Will the young master really not drive me away?
The cultivation of the young master is far from us.
He will blame you for this.
But,
Zi Su,
the cultivation of the young master is endless.
We can be together for a lifetime.
Some things will eventually be over.
So,
what you want to sell is what you want to see.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Zi Su, come back.
The young master is injured.
The young master.
Why are you injured like this?
It's all our fault.
We didn't protect the young master.
It's not my fault.
It's just some skin injuries.
I'll just wipe the medicine.
You three go out.
I have something to tell Mo Xiao.
Yes.
Okay, sit down.
Master.
Sit down.
Go.
Feng Li Xue has escaped with Chong Guang.
Yes.
When I came,
the elder brother of the sect kept an eye on me.
If I see you,
I must tell you.
Feng Li Xue must be killed.
But you don't want to kill me.
If you do it,
you can fight,
I can do it.
Master,
Feng Li Xue
was killed because of
Feng Xing Tian at the time have aassing with Shang Hai thousand years ago.
Because of them,
remember the Ukrainian 지금 in revenge of me and T horns.
Then Chong Guang took advantage of it
and Tong Brady titted the Demon streets.
But the demon庫
developed because of unknown reasons
He is also a pitiful person.
Even so, he is the elder brother.
But it's strange that he came back.
The elder brother is always kind and kind.
But he must be killed by you for this Feng Lixue.
What's the reason?
Maybe it's because of Feng Xingtian and Qianzun's comparison.
Qianzun is very loyal and loyal.
That's why he was angry with Feng Lixue.
Alright.
Since you are here,
when you see the elder brother next time,
you can tell him yourself.
Take good care of yourself.
Master, I know you want me to kill Lixue because of the marriage.
But Lixue was pushed by my master back then.
It's been ten years since I met you.
Lixue saved my life at this moment.
This time, I went to the Red City to learn the antidote.
I was so happy to see you.
If I really have the marriage,
I would be more like the marriage of Lixue.
How could I kill Lixue who helped me many times?
Master and Qianzun taught me to be kind and loyal.
How could I live without my own life because of the security of my own family?
Master, Xingzhu is back.
Master, Xingzhu is here.
Master, Xingzhu is here to see you.
Who asked you to come in?
Master, please come in.
Where?
In the front hall.
You can't come in without my order.
Master, Xingzhu is here.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see you.
You can't come in without my order.
I'm sorry, Master.
Master, please punish me.
Where are you?
I'm not sure. I'm poisoned by fake poison.
I'm in a critical condition.
I'm not sure if I should reveal the antidote to the demon poison
and take the red dust.
Please punish me.
Lixue, you're my only disciple.
I saved you ten years ago.
Do you know why you became my disciple?
I don't know.
Because you have hatred in your heart.
You're so cruel.
You've been suffering for ten years.
You're so greedy and stubborn.
You're the most helpless person in the world.
Only a person like you can be my disciple.
You've changed.
Your silver is soft.
Your sharpness is healing.
Are you still the phoenix blood I saved ten years ago?
I've never asked you this ten years ago.
Master, how did you know I was a disciple?
That's why you saved me.
I'm sorry.
I saved you.
Did you also save me from the phoenix blood?
Maybe it's the fate we're destined to have.
Why didn't you save my father?
Are you blaming me?
I dare not.
If I saved my father,
maybe the phoenix blood will be less painful.
Your father was the one who killed Shushan to save you.
If he knew I saved you,
he would have died.
Yes.
You're right.
But if he knew
his daughter's heart was frozen,
what would he feel when he's in the capital?
The heart of the phoenix has never frozen.
Did you feel the heart of your master?
Yes.
I, Feng Yi Xuan, am willing to die.
I'll only take two things in life.
First, revenge for the murder.
Second, I will definitely save you.
Will you be grateful to me?
My face is master's.
Then where is your heart?
Let us ask your heart.
Li Xue.
Come with me.
Come.
Let us see who you think.
I'm here.
Mo Xiao.
Li Xue.
Mo Xiao, don't come here.
Let's go.
Don't come here.
Mo Xiao.
Let's go.