(2 hours ago)
Mr. Thirteen.
(Fengxing House)
I asked you for info.
Can you just tell me?
Lan.
You know the rules here.
If you win, I'll give you the info.
But if you lose,
you have to take off your clothes.
(Tile)
- One Character.
- Pung.
- Five of Bamboos.
Why do you keep Punging?
What's going on with this game?
I'll take this tile too.
Mr. Thirteen.
I haven't played my tile yet.
Do you know what it is?
I want all your tiles.
Here.
Isn't that a win?
Alright.
Come on. Another round.
The outcome isn't settled yet.
Since this is the last round,
let's make it big.
If you lose,
you'll marry me.
Fine.
But if you lose,
you'll tell me
what new drug Kanghai Pharmaceuticals
is working on.
Alright.
Deal.
Come on.
Won.
Look at it. Right? Am I right?
Mr. Thirteen.
It's fine.
Losing to you isn't a loss.
Next time, I'll try harder.
Alright.
Ertiao, bring the things
to the lady.
Thanks.
Mr. Thirteen.
We've been mahjong mates for many years.
You owe me 99 pieces of information.
When can you repay them all?
Just owe it for now.
Let me take my time.
What's the rush?
By the way,
any news about Tingdong
recently?
See for yourself.
This is Tingdong?
=Be Your Knight=
=Episode 5 First Night=
Tingdong.
Look closely.
Is the person smoking opium
in this photo you?
The person in this photo
isn't me.
Still denying?
This person looks
almost exactly like me.
Tingdong.
What are you talking about?
Since you claim that person isn't you,
then
let me see your shoulder.
I remember about ten days ago,
I accidentally burned your shoulder
with moxibustion.
And the person in the photo
has the exact same burn.
Go ahead.
I can bear it.
Forget it.
If someone asks about the burn
on your right shoulder,
you just have to react.
Take off your shirt.
Grandma.
Isn't it inappropriate to do this
in front of so many family members?
Tingdong...
Yu.
Everyone out.
Xiang Tingdong.
Take off your shirt.
Didn't you hear that?
Yu, help him undress.
Mr. Tingdong.
Apologies.
Take off the bandage.
Uncle Yu.
I'll do it myself.
The person in the photo
has the exact same burn
on his shoulder.
The person in this photo
isn't me.
Since you say it's not you,
then let me see your shoulder.
Xiang Tingdong,
what else do you have to say?
This person is you.
Tingdong, why on earth did you do that?
It might be because
he got seriously ill in Southeast Asia.
His shoulder injury never healed.
There's no other reason.
I made a mistake.
- What's your attitude?
- Fine.
Yu.
Take out the whip.
Understood.
Grandma.
This is too cruel.
Any more and he'll suffer
serious injuries.
Yes, Mom. That's enough.
I'm afraid Tingdong can't take it.
Continue.
Mr. Tingdong, I'm sorry.
Uncle Yu.
Continue.
Grandma.
Please stop.
He doesn't want to say,
so I'll tell you why.
Alright, Cheng.
Tell us.
What really happened?
A year ago,
we went to Yunzhou.
He was kidnapped by a gang
because of me,
threatened, tortured,
and almost thrown into the sea.
His injuries kept him awake at night.
- That's why he…
- Enough with the excuses.
Keep going.
Any reason is just an excuse.
I was wrong
to smoke opium.
Continue.
Continue!
I knew something was off with you.
Turns out it's because of the opium.
Alright.
Tingdong.
You've finally learned
to admit your mistakes.
Now, I'll take care
of the rest.
Mom.
♪How many regretful endings
are there in this world♪
♪Like the fate of you and me♪
♪Missing each other by chance♪
Cheng, what are you doing?
Grandma.
I'm partly to blame for this too.
Please punish me too if you want.
Fine.
I'll punish you both
together.
♪Passionate love lost
in the ruins of time♪
♪Crying in endless dreams♪
Grandma,
just hit me.
Leave her alone.
You...
Mom!
- Grandma!
- Gran!
- What's wrong?
Mom, what happened?
Uncle Yu, take my mom
to the hospital now!
Mom!
Cui, get the car ready!
Got it!
Keep an eye on him.
♪Through the storm, I'll come to you♪
Ye Ran, are you alright?
Let me take you to the hospital.
I'm fine.
I won't die.
Why are you
doing this?
Glad we got through this.
I'm okay.
(I never expected)
(he'd pass this test)
(in this way.)
(I genuinely admire him)
(and also feel sorry for him.)
(Thank you.)
(Ye Ran.)
You really went all out today.
Your story was quite something too.
I merely repeated
what you did to me.
I was just reaffirming my identity.
Today, they all said it.
I am Xiang Tingdong.
What are you trying to achieve
by making yourself like this?
It's definitely not for you.
I never expected
you'd take the beating for me.
You were punished
for your brother because of me.
Don't let water touch your wound.
Alright.
Ye Ran.
Have some water.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to help me
find a key.
The agreement didn't say
I had to help you find any key.
Agreement?
What agreement?
Oh, this.
Do you even believe
in this kind of thing?
Alright.
Tell me.
What key are you looking for?
Xiang Tingdong has a safe deposit box
at Fenglong Bank.
(A month ago)
Hello, is this Mr. Xiang Tingdong?
Your safe deposit box here
is about to expire.
Would you like to renew it?
I've searched
every possible place,
but I still can't find the key.
But maybe, with that face of yours,
you can help me find a clue to the key.
What exactly happened
between you and my brother?
Or rather,
what did you do to him?
You don't need to know that.
I promise you.
His life is not in danger.
What's inside that safe deposit box
might hold the truth
I've been seeking for fifteen years.
Then tell me now.
What truth are you looking for?
You also don't need to know that.
As I don't need to know anything,
why should I help you
find this key?
Tingdong.
We're married now.
Mr. Tingdong, here's your medicine.
I'll leave it at the door.
Thanks, Uncle Yu.
Just now,
I...
It's alright.
You don't need to explain.
I don't need to know.
Thanks for what you did earlier today.
Don't touch my stuff.
I didn't.
I just wanted to find a book to read.
I brought a blanket.
Tonight,
you'll sleep here.
Where is this collar pin from?
How do you have this collar pin?
How do you know about this?
What else do you know?
Where are the manuscripts?
You are
a group of lunatics.
You're all going to hell.
Have you gone stupid from studying?
You won't talk, huh?
Then never say another word.
♪How much time can one fill♪
♪Melt then freeze
the warmth your eyes spill♪
This safe deposit box
might hold the truth
I've been searching
for over fifteen years.
♪Only half of the truth's fulfilled♪
(What's the story
behind that collar pin?)
(Could it be related
to the key she's looking for?)
(What has she gone through)
(in this house?)
♪No one's honest, they lie♪
♪The past is painful, you can't hide♪
♪What I said isn't right♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)