(September's Collaboration: Limited edition green milk tea)
Excuse me.
Yes, hello.
By any chance, is Ms. Han Ae Ri here?
Who are you? Why are you looking for her?
I'm from Yujung Constructions.
Yujung Constructions...
Are you here because of that recent incident?
Is she no longer working here?
She has a great sense of responsibility.
I told her I could wait, but she quit, saying she felt bad.
I thought that case was solved.
I came to ask her a few things...
in order to prevent similar cases from occurring.
I see.
Sir, please treat her well.
I have no idea how she got into that,
but there's no one like her.
She's hardworking, friendly,
and is more economical than me, the manager.
About that kidnapping case,
I'm certain she was just there to help.
Since a month ago... Was her name Da Bin?
She had put up the missing child flyers...
and had looked for her everywhere.
I'm so upset.
These days, she's been busy looking for her mother.
(Have You Seen My Mom?)
Why did she leave her house if she was ill?
"Kwak Song Ja".
Why does it sound familiar?
(Calling)
(Kim Seo Jin)
Han Ae Ri.
What's your relationship with Director Kim Seo Jin?
Hello?
Mr. Kim.
- Hello? - Who is this?
Director Kim?
Who are you? Let me speak to Han Ae Ri!
Hello? Mr. Kim.
Ms. Han. Is that really you?
Hello? Who are you? Let me speak to Han Ae Ri!
Director Kim?
Mr. Kim.
Hello?
What was that? That was me on the other end.
Why are you two in touch?
First, you snatched my phone away. And now, what are you talking about?
(Director Kim Seo Jin)
- Hello? - Sir.
Hey. Why are you calling me at this hour?
Did you just speak on the phone with Ms. Han Ae Ri?
What do you mean?
Why would I speak with her?
Hello? Mr. Seo.
I'm sorry.
I must have been overly sensitive since I've been busy lately.
Goodness.
All right. Good work today. Goodnight.
You better explain this, Mr. Seo.
What are you scheming?
Why were you looking for Lee Taek Gyu today?
How did you find the studio apartment?
How did you know about the studio apartment?
Did Lee Taek Gyu tell you?
Kwak Song Ja.
Why is he looking for your mother?
What are you trying to do?
Why are you always around Mr. Kim?
Ae Ri. Who are you?
- What's going on? - Who is he?
I asked you who you were. What's this about?
Are you okay?
(Text message records)
They were always in touch at 10:33pm sharp.
If you're really from the future,
- please help me. - These are the winning numbers...
for the 1st lottery on the 3rd week of August.
Will you trust me this time?
If these were sent a month after Han Ae Ri had sent the texts...
A woman named Han Ae Ri had visited Kim Jin Ho last night.
Da Bin will be kidnapped by Kim Jin Ho.
Let go of me. It's not me.
It's him! You must catch him!
Hello? Who are you? Let me speak to Han Ae Ri!
Director Kim?
Mr. Kim.
Hyun Chae.
I've finally figured out...
why this happened to me.
I can bring you back to life.
I will do that...
at all costs.
(Episode 10)
(Just be safe, Mr. Kim. Everything will change by tomorrow.)
Mr. Kim, are you okay?
Many things have happened while we were out of touch.
Do you know that?
My mom seems to be very ill.
I...
need your help once again.
Please find her.
(I need your help once again. Please find her.)
On the 10th, the mayor of Taejung...
and members of Yujung Constructions met with each other.
And we finally signed the contract...
regarding Taejung's development.
In compliance with our agreement, the city hall will be in charge...
of the working design and the impact assessment.
Yujung Constructions...
will be in charge of readjusting the re-plotting land.
How do the landowners feel about this?
We held a briefing session yesterday and invited all the residents.
The number of people who were against this...
had gone down significantly.
We've also prepared an analysis of a survey...
we had handed out after the briefing session.
Please look at the paper we've given you.
Please look at the results of the number five question.
There has been a 17.6-percent increase...
post briefing session regarding the residents...
feeling hopeful and thinking Taejung New Town project...
would benefit them.
This is a good start.
The speech you gave yesterday played a huge role.
Good work.
It's all thanks to the Planning Department's...
excellent planning and support.
Before ending, I would like...
to introduce our new team manager.
It's Team Manager Seo Do Kyun.
- Who? - Who is that?
- What's going on? - How could this be?
- Isn't he one of his men? - He is.
Goodness.
He was the one who led the Cheonan project...
which we reaped the most fruits from this year.
The entire project was overseen by him.
I believe he has proven himself...
and is eligible enough to play a crucial role...
in this Taejung project which will lead Yujung's future.
Everyone will be quite busy.
Mr. Seo. I mean, Team Manager Seo...
and everyone else, you better stay alert...
until the construction begins.
Help Director Kim as much as possible.
I must've taken you by surprise.
Let's do a good job once again.
I'll put together a report...
including everything that was announced today.
Sure.
It's already time for lunch when I barely have time to spare.
Let's quickly grab a bite to eat.
You'll be accompanying me this afternoon.
It was this guy, right? Seo Do Kyun of Yujung Constructions.
That's the guy we saw you with.
Where did you get this?
Our boss at the convenience store.
He came looking for you yesterday...
and asked about you in detail.
That's why the jerk was at your house last night.
We need to find my mom before they do.
- Hello? - Yes, hello.
Are you perhaps related to Ms. Kwak Song Ja?
Yes, I am. I'm her daughter.
May I ask who's calling?
(Yujung Constructions Must Answer to the Taejung Town Accident)
This is...
the Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association.
Taejung Town?
We're on our way to meet...
with the Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association.
Due to the lack of trust they have in us,
they have been adamantly opposed to this project.
Talking to them won't be easy.
Didn't you say what you could at yesterday's presentation?
A few words can't make up for all the damage.
A one-time apology might antagonize them even more.
Until the project is complete,
we must keep apologizing.
Sir,
could this change of heart...
be influenced by Han Ae Ri?
What?
That reminds me. What was with that call last night?
I didn't know she'd show up at the presentation.
I'm worried of her being more of a threat.
In any way,
you'd be better off staying away from her.
Don't worry. We won't ever come in contact again.
However,
what she said at the police station...
still feels like a hoax,
but something has changed in me...
ever since that concert.
Whether for the best or not...
is still undetermined at the moment.
Shall we?
(Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association)
Is anyone present?
Sure. Come on in.
(Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association)
Who...
Hello, I'm Kim Seo Jin of Yujung Constructions.
(Yujung Constructions Must Answer to the Taejung Town Accident)
Why are you here?
I apologize for not coming by sooner.
Since you're here, you can stay for some coffee.
- Have a seat. - Thank you.
If it's too much trouble, let me...
Did you perhaps know my father?
I'm only being polite since you're Yoo Seok's son.
Anyone else...
from Yujung Constructions...
wouldn't have been able to walk over the threshold.
Thank you.
I thank you for your time.
Why are you here?
What were your thoughts regarding yesterday's presentation?
If you're here for my opinion, don't expect it to be good.
The new project itself is just wrong to begin with.
Then enlighten us. We're all ears, sir.
Do you know...
why tragedies like this keep on happening in Korea?
Because only the executive lowest on the totem pole...
is ever punished.
The specific cause of why Taejung Town collapsed...
should've been investigated.
That's the only way to prevent further incidents.
However, Yujung Constructions took the first wrong step.
Are you saying that...
the initial investigation was inadequate?
Banyoung Constructions who was in charge...
didn't consider the possibility of a sink hole...
Mr. Kim, do you actually believe the words of Yu Seo Il?
So that the bereaved don't discover anything damning,
Chairman Yu has been...
holding information back and covering up certain facts.
If you're not interested...
in hearing the words of the bereaved or those who survived,
don't ever come here again.
I...
understand, sir.
Could I then have the list of the bereaved?
I'd like to speak to as many as possible.
I'd be happy to hand it over.
It's actually something I've been hoping for.
Do Kyun, wait for me back at the car.
Yes, sir.
(Yujung Constructions Must Answer to the Taejung Town Accident)
Sir,
if you have the time,
I'd like to hear about my father.
As you know, I was caved in at the site...
and couldn't be with him during his last moments.
(Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association)
Your father...
was my mentor.
Since his days as a chief,
I learned a lot from him.
If I ever got the chance to meet you,
this I wanted to say.
Your father isn't the kind of man...
who would've left his son all alone and committed suicide.
Of course, I don't have any evidence to back it up.
As you can guess, it happened while I was...
fighting for my life at the hospital.
Yoo Seok came by though when I woke up.
I couldn't even begin to imagine the agony he felt...
knowing that his son was caved in. However,
Yoo Seok...
believed that you'd come back to him.
More so than anyone, he aggressively fought...
to figure out why the accident happened.
And I'm sure...
that it didn't sit well for...
the higher-ups at Banyoung...
and Yujung Constructions.
He said that an accident like this should never happen again...
and that...
I should join his hunt for the truth once I got better.
So him taking his own life a few days later?
That...
is absurd.
Did you have a good discussion?
Yes.
Can you get me the materials...
related to the collapse of Taejung Town?
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
(Kangil Police Station, Detective Lee Tae Woo)
- Hello? - Mr. Seo Do Kyun.
This is Detective Lee.
Yes?
I think we found the car that caused the accident.
Where was it found?
- Is this it? - How did you know we were here?
Did you call him?
Why did you come this far? I said I'll call you when we're sure.
We'll call you after we're done investigating, so please leave.
- Is this the car? - That's as far as you can come.
You can't cross this line.
It looks right, but we're waiting for the test result from the NFS.
What more do you need to test?
People say there's a connection even if you brush by someone,
so when someone brushes by something, there's always a trace.
The skid marks left on the road show the type of wheels that are used.
We're checking to see if these tires match the skid marks.
And the damage on this truck coincides...
with the height of the damage made on the victim's car.
And lastly, the paint.
It's not visible to the naked eye. But by using a spectroscope,
we'll see if the paint left on the damage...
is the same type of paint used on the victim's car.
If so, it's game over.
When will the result come out?
Who found this car?
What about the driver?
A resident around here reported this car as abandoned for days.
And naturally, we found no dash cam or fingerprints.
That's all we found in the truck.
He's still here?
Stop messing with the scene and go.
- And you, come here. - Yes, sir.
(Anseong J Motel)
How did you find a place like this?
Are you sure there are no security cameras around here?
Look around. Nothing at all.
It's a perfect place if there are no witnesses.
- What about the dash cam? - Ours is planned to be inspected.
And I'll rent out a camping car with a broken dash cam.
Kim Seo Jin isn't a guy who'd let you do this that easily.
There's this medication he has been taking.
A tranquillizer.
It reduces his anxiety and calms him down.
The side effects include lethargy and sleepiness.
- And? - Seo Jin will end up driving...
while he's drowsy on that day.
I'll suggest...
that he takes a quick nap before we go on.
That's when Da Bin and I will leave the car.
And then you can come in and finish him off.
Easy, isn't it?
What about the rest of my money?
Of course, we'll balance our accounts.
Do you remember our terms?
(Taejung Council, Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association)
(Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association)
You're Ms. Kwak Song Ja's daughter?
Yes, my name is Han Ae Ri.
Then...
you must be Tae Gil's daughter.
Do you know my dad?
I know him very well.
I've worked with him for years.
It must've been traumatic for your mother.
We tried our best...
to contact her as the Victims' Association,
but we couldn't find her whereabouts.
But I saw your name on the list of visitors...
at the presentation yesterday...
and wanted to see if you were Tae Gil's family, so I called.
I see.
It's my first time meeting someone who's acquainted with my dad.
Director Kim Seo Jin of Yujung Constructions was just here.
His father, your father,
and I were all very close.
Who was that again?
Who else was close to my dad?
Director Kim Seo Jin's father, Mr. Kim Yoo Seok.
They had been close?
Of course.
Back then, Yoo Seok ran around...
trying to find the cause of the collapse.
I'm sure he met with your mother too.
(List of Visitors, Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association)
(Han Tae Gil, Wife: Kwak Song Ja, Daughter: Han Ae Ri)
Kwak Song Ja?
(Please help me find my missing mom.)
Where did I see her?
I'm sure I've seen her somewhere.
Are you talking about the Cheonan project?
Yes, the Cheonan project.
Seo Jin said...
you were the actual head of the entire project.
It's only because Mr. Kim guided me very well...
You just have to wrap it up.
Just do things as you've always done.
I need Seo Jin elsewhere.
Yes, sir.
You may go.
(Please help me find my missing mom.)
Why did she there to see Chairman Yu?
- Hey, Hyun Chae. - Where are you?
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
I'm almost there. See you upstairs.
I've come to a conclusion regarding what Han Ae Ri said.
What is it?
The text messages she claims to have gone...
back and forth between her and Kim...
seemed to be too accurate for her to have imagined everything,
so I was a bit worried.
But?
What I do know is...
that she hasn't been in touch with Kim Seo Jin.
But her mother has met with Chairman Yu.
Why did her mother see him?
She's a bereaved family member of a victim...
in the Taejung Town collapse.
Her mother came to see the chairman...
when Han Ae Ri was arrested for attempted kidnapping.
I guess she wanted to ask him to show mercy.
That's why I plan to start it again.
Start what?
The plan for us to leave this place together.
So please don't be anxious,
and give me a little more time.
Why should I be anxious? You'll take care of everything.
Should we go out this weekend?
Sure. Sounds great.
(Chon Tea Room, Motel)
Hello, do you need a room?
Excuse me.
Have you seen this man?
(Daeseong Internet Café)
What are you doing?
What is this?
Come outside.
Why? Why did you do that?
Have you gone insane?
Why did you kill Hyun Chae?
It's driving me crazy too.
Kang Hyun Chae put me up for this!
You need to hear me out.
What do you mean, she put you up for this?
She paid me to kill Kim Seo Jin.
And she found a place without any security cameras.
Once Kim Seo Jin takes his medicine and falls asleep,
she said she'll take her kid and get out of the car.
She said only Kim Seo Jin will die,
so I have no idea why she was in the car.
And I didn't even get paid!
Stop talking nonsense.
Hyun Chae never said anything.
She told me not to tell you. I mean it.
I'll show you all the text messages that went between us.
Kang Hyun Chae put me up for everything!
(Manager Seo Do Kyun)
There's no reason to kill you now.
I'll kill you a month ago.
Make sure you always pick up my calls.
What is that lunatic saying?
(Han Ae Ri)
(The culprit has been found. It's Lee Taek Gyu!)
(He must be killed before October 9th.)
Dad!
Da Bin, come here.
Dad, what are you doing?
Is there anywhere you want to go with Mom and Dad?
How about this place?
(Teddy Bear Museum)
- Gosh. - Do you want to go?
Really?
Dad, aren't you busy?
I'm busy, but I have enough time to hang out with you.
Gosh, it looks like so much fun.
- Da Bin. - Mom!
There's my girl.
- Did you have a great day? - Yes.
What were you up to?
- I was playing with my bear. - You were playing with your bear?
You're home. Have you eaten?
I already ate.
Mom, Dad wants to go on a trip!
- What? - Let's go on a trip this weekend.
How does this sound? Da Bin will love it too.
Is there anywhere you want to go to?
All of a sudden?
I thought you were busy with your project at work.
I work so hard for my family anyway.
I can catch up on my work after the trip.
You don't have to go out of your way to do this if you're busy.
You must be exhausted.
I'm not going out of my way. This is more important to me.
Go wash up. I'll reserve a room at a resort.
- Play with Dad, okay? - Okay.
I'd like to reserve a room for this Saturday.
What's he up to?
(Your reservation for a suite has been confirmed.)
- Da Bin, what are you up to? - Massaging my bear.
- Does it say it feels great? - Yes, it feels wonderful.
This is the midday news for September 8, 2020.
The emergency restoration of areas affected by...
- the Typhoon Chamsae... - The Typhoon Chamsae...
The roads and houses in affected areas are...
- slowly coming back... - Ma'am! Could you lower the volume?
- Who are you? - Typhoon Chamsae is...
moving north from Okinawa as of now, August 8.
- In the afternoon of August 9... - I'm the owner of this phone.
Dad, are you sick?
No. Give me a second.
It wasn't a delusion.
(Kim Seo Jin)
The person you have reached is unavailable.
You'll be redirected to voice mail.
This is Kim Seo Jin. There had been an accident.
- On October 9, I lost my wife... - On October 9, I lost my wife...
- and my kid due to a car accident. - and my kid due to a car accident.
You must prevent it from happening. Please help me.
I'm severely injured as well, so I'm afraid we won't be able...
to talk on the phone for the time being.
I'll text you all the information you need.
First, you must...
ask Mr. Seo Do Kyun for help.
"You must ask Mr. Seo Do Kyun for help"?
No way.
I'm sure he knows that Mr. Seo was also at that studio apartment.
I know who did it. It was Lee Taek Gyu.
You must kill him before October 9.
I beg you. If you kill him...
If you kill him, I'll do whatever you want me to do.
He wants me to kill Lee Taek Gyu?
Why are you here?
Am I not allowed here?
I'm giving Seo Jin a quick visit.
I'm afraid I won't be able to spend time with you this weekend.
My family's going on a surprise trip.
Come in.
What brings you here? You didn't even call beforehand.
I had some errands to run nearby, so I just dropped by.
I thought we could have lunch together.
What should I do? I have a luncheon appointment.
I won't be coming to work tomorrow, so I have a lot to do today.
Don't worry about it. I came unannounced anyway.
Would you like something to drink at least?
No, thanks. You should work.
I don't want you to cancel our trip tomorrow...
because I bothered you today.
- Let me walk outside with you. - Just work.
At least until the elevator.
You drove, right? Which floor did you park at?
Third level basement.
It was your first time visiting in a long time.
I'm sorry we couldn't have lunch.
It's okay. We're going on a trip anyway. Bye.
Bye.
The door is closing.
(This is Kim Seo Jin. There had been an accident.)
(On October 9, I lost my wife and my kid due to a car accident.)
Hey, didn't I tell you to never contact him again?
Do you want to get into a mess again?
That's why I'm telling you about this first.
And...
I visited the Taejung Town Collapse Victims' Association...
and found out that my father was close with his.
All the new information I've been discovering...
is pointing toward one fact.
That my mom's disappearance...
is linked with Yujung Constructions.
I must...
stay in touch with him.
So what do you want to do?
This last part sounded strange.
If you kill Taek Gyu, I'll do whatever you want me to do.
There's no way he would want me to ask Mr. Seo for help.
The Kim Seo Jin I know...
wouldn't ask me to kill anyone.
Who else other than us knows that you two were in touch?
No one...
The police do.
They printed out all the texts during my interrogation.
What if someone got their hands on those texts?
And what if it was Seo Do Kyun?
(Han Ae Ri)
- Hello? - I'm in front of your office.
Can I speak with you for a bit?
I'll go out right now.
(The Cause of Taejung Town's Collapse)
(Article About the Collapse)
Why is the report so short?
- Yes, sir. - Please call Mr. Seo over.
Kim Seo Jin speaking.
Mr. Seo isn't in his office.
Would you like to call him?
No, it's not urgent.
Please tell him to come when you see him.
We should continue our chat.
Bella Studio. Why did you go there?
Whom did you meet with?
What do you mean?
If it's something reasonable, there's no need to hide it from me.
I don't know if you truly want Mr. Kim to be safe.
I don't know what kind of picture you've imagined in your head,
but back off if this is related to Director Kim.
He won't drop the charges next time around.
What are you getting out of this?
He's going to find my mom for me.
Ask the police for help.
How will he be able to find your mother?
He had helped me find her once in the past.
Write this down.
This is where your mom will be starting from September 14.
- Illju-gun, Gyeonggi Province. - Illju-gun, Gyeonggi Province.
- Gyeongil-myeon. - Gyeongil-myeon.
Yeongwon Farm, Jeonghui Diner.
Mr. Kim had found out that my mom was staying in Gangwon Province...
at a place called Hanjoon Sauna.
I don't want to hear your nonsense anymore.
I'll get going first.
Something bad is going to happen to you in the near future.
It doesn't matter what you say.
I'm going to prevent it from happening.
(Contacts)
(Han Ae Ri)
The phone is turned off.
- You'll be connected to voice mail. - Darn it.
Where are you?
Hey, it's me.
It's been ages.
I thought you had forgotten about me.
You've transformed into a righteous citizen.
I can barely recognize you.
I need a favour.
Is something wrong?
I want you to find them as quickly as possible.
(Personal Details Report, Kwak Song Ja)
(Personal Details Report, Han Ae Ri)
Did you get it?
Yes, I did.
If something happens to me or my daughter,
send it to the aforementioned media outlets and the prosecution.
Got it.
I'm heading back to my daughter now.
Thank you for everything.
- One ticket to Seoul, please. - Sure.
Thank you.
(Dongseosan Bus Terminal)
(October 15, Thursday)
I was worried that there might be some kind of accident.
After all the work we did,
my mom is still missing...
and your family is dead again.
But I guess I have no choice.
I'll do what I can to prevent the accident on October 9.
Please do what you can to find my mom.
I have a feeling that my mom is in a rural area.
Could you send me the address...
and phone number of the sauna you once found her at?
I was able to find her thanks to Mr. Kim once.
At a Hanjoon Sauna in Gangwon Province.
I found her...
- Mom, did you pack my swimsuit? - Of course.
Maybe I should've packed more clothes.
I made sure to pack extra.
Mom, I'm super excited!
The teddy bear is too. Are you as well?
Of course, I'm excited to go on a trip with you.
You should behave in the car though.
- Okay? - Sure.
- Are you ready? Off we go. - Off we go!
- Let's go. - Yes, let's go!
Catch me if you can.
Mom, wait!
Catch me if you can!
- Catch these! - Honey, where's our camera?
- Can you take some pictures? - Sure.
Off I go again.
Only if there was a witness...
I think I ate some.
Mom, look at me!
1, 2... 3.
Let's take another. All right.
1, 2, 3.
Da Bin, come on. Let's take a selfie.
Sure.
Over here.
All right.
1, 2, 3.
- Are you a flower? - Yes.
One more. 1, 2, 3.
Another.
There we go.
Mom, can I play with this?
Sure, have fun.
You're not one to take selfies.
This is the first time I've seen you take one.
It turns out...
that I never took one with Da Bin.
Her first day at kindergarten,
picnics, and show-and-tell events.
I'm not present in the photos she took on special occasions.
Did you look through her photos?
I'm hungry. Let me get started on dinner.
Da Bin, I'll soon get you some grilled corn.
I'll play with Da Bin after dinner,
so get some rest.
What's with you these days? Is this out of some guilt?
I haven't been attentive toward you and Da Bin.
That's why.
We should do this occasionally.
Do you mean that?
Can I plan our next trip then?
Sure.
How about September 9? If you're not busy, I mean.
Well...
It's good. I'll keep my schedule cleared.
I'll decide on the location too.
Sounds good.
Da Bin, you should eat your meat.
Here.
- Say, "Ah." - Ah.
- Wasn't it grilled properly? - It was.
Meanwhile, I'll have some cheese.
(Kim Seo Jin)
Wasn't it Hanjoon Sauna in Gangwon Province?
I couldn't find the memo I wrote down the address on though.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
(Kim Seo Jin)
(Han Ae Ri)
Mr. Kim, where are you?
What happened to you?
Are you sure you're in no condition to talk?
Answer me, Seo Do Kyun.
(Delete message)
If you're not going to die, wake up already.
You must wake up...
for Hyun Chae to be saved.
Sir?
- Did he get a CT scan yesterday? - Yes.
Mr. Kim?
Mr. Kim.
Please move your hand if you can hear me.
Pinch me.
Mr. Kim, do you hear me?
How is he?
He's not completely lucid just yet.
He is not in the state of staying awake on his own...
or being aware of his surroundings, people, places, and time.
When do you think he could speak with us?
For now, it's still uncertain. This is already a miracle.
- I see. Thank you. - Goodbye.
What did the doctor say?
He's not fully awake just yet.
When will he be able to talk?
He doesn't know either.
Mr. Seo.
I heard you were in the room when he first woke up.
Why were you there?
Ever since the accident,
I've been visiting him from time to time.
The company is extremely concerned...
about his well-being as well.
I see.
We'll stay here, so you can leave.
(Emergency)
Have you gotten in touch with her guardian?
No, she didn't have a phone on her,
and we couldn't find her family either.
I found her ID card, so I checked,
but she had never visited our hospital.
She could've run away from home, so let the health department know.
Okay.
So who has Mr. Kim's phone right now?
It's not him for sure.
How do you know?
Remember Jeonghui Diner?
He didn't recognize that place.
That fraudster.
Then it's Seo Do Kyun.
Hold on.
Does that mean he knows that you and Kim Seo Jin...
are in different time frames?
I think so.
He's trying to use me to prevent Kang Hyun Chae's death.
Anyway, I'm positive that something will happen to Mr. Kim in a month.
So for now, you can't reach him.
I think it's all for the best.
Forget everything about him. Pretend like it was all a dream.
Please?
Hello, Detective Choi.
Ms. Han, I think I found your mother.
She had recently gone to a hospital.
Are you serious?
I took a look at her medical record.
But I should go there myself and check if she's really there.
Which hospital is it? I'll go there right now.
He found her?
Come in.
Hey.
I heard Seo Jin regained consciousness.
So? Did you talk with him?
He can't talk yet.
But there's a high chance that he'll recover soon.
That's a relief.
I'm glad he didn't get any more injuries.
Seo Jin will overcome this hardship as well.
Right. He wouldn't give up due to something so trivial.
By the way, how will we tell him about his family?
Yes?
Minister Park?
Put him through.
I know.
Director Kim woke up.
This won't affect the Taejung Project.
Don't worry.
Business is important, but people come first.
I see.
Goodbye.
Ae Ri?
Are you awake?
How did you come here?
There's someone I need to see.
(Lee Taek Gyu)
Of course.
Bye.
Cancelled.
Going up.
I know that you were working for someone else as well...
when you were working for Do Kyun.
Who's paying you?
Who's looking for Han Ae Ri's mother?
What's it to you?
You just need Kim Seo Jin dead.
Wealthy people are so funny.
It was Chairman Yu Seo Il.
He wanted me to find out where Han Ae Ri's mom was.
- Why? - I don't know. I don't care either.
Did he give her money as well?
(Text message records)
(Please found out who wired 100,000 dollars to my mom.)
Did you send 100,000 dollars to her on August 27?
Chairman Yu did that, didn't he?
Then did you think it was my money?
She...
has something.
Are you awake?
Where is that recording?
Where's your lifeline?
(Kairos)
Mom, do you know a man named Kim Yoo Seok?
- Keep it for the time being. - What is this?
Tell me everything. What is this that you're keeping from me?
They tried to get rid of people's homes. That's absurd.
What's the real cause?
They keep talking about it. It's getting too noisy.
- It will be that road. - And the date?
We'll have a family trip on October 9.
It will work no matter what.
Mr. Kim had accelerated right before the crash.
Were you trying to commit suicide together?
That's nonsense.
Mr. Kim, you'll be interrogated.
Hire a lawyer if needed.
Kim Seo Jin! Stay where you are!