Mom!
Mom.
Don't go. Don't.
Mom...
Don't go.
(Do not cross, police line)
(Kairos)
(Episode 7)
Have you all eaten?
What about you?
I just keep getting thirsty.
- I missed you two too. - I missed you too.
Let's give them some time and sit further back.
Come with me.
We still have some time until we get there. Take a nap.
I won't go anywhere.
(Violent Crimes Team 2)
(Violent Crimes Team 1, Violent Crimes Team 2)
(Meeting Room)
Kwak Song Ja?
I don't think there's a victim by that name.
Didn't you ask me something like this before?
- It was Han... - No, it's nothing.
What happened to Kim Jin Ho?
He killed himself.
He came for the outpatient clinic,
then threw himself off from the rooftop of the hospital.
But are you sure he killed himself?
We're sure.
Our forensics team are done investigating,
and they've finished analyzing the handwriting of his will too.
Where's the hospital?
A hospital for inmates. Seoul Dongcheon Hospital.
The court will close the case for dismissal of the indictment.
And the articles will be returned.
I understand.
Mr. Kim.
If anything happens, don't agonize over it by yourself.
You can call me anytime.
It's kind of odd for me to tell you this,
but I'm also a dad who has a daughter.
I can connect with what happened...
to Kim Jin Ho and you.
Turn yourself in this instant.
If you do, I'll try my best to plead for a lighter punishment.
So please turn yourself in.
I already rely on you quite a lot.
Thank you.
(Location Tracker: Yujung Building 172 Dongha-ro, Jungan-Gu, Seoul)
The tracked vehicle has just left Yujung Constructions.
(Yujung Building)
The location tracker is still on.
Mom, we need to talk.
About what?
You have a lot to tell me.
May we do that tomorrow?
I'm too tired.
Why did you leave the hospital?
Why did you disappear without a word?
Where did you get that money in your account?
Ae Ri, I'm not feeling well today.
I'll tell you everything tomorrow.
How are you feeling ill?
I'll be fine once I get some sleep.
(Han Ae Ri)
Ms. Han, have you found your mother?
Yes, I met her today thanks to your help.
I was arrested for murdering your mother,
but the situation has changed.
You saved me too, Ms. Han.
Wait, then did Lee Taek Gyu blame what he did on you?
You have to catch him.
If you don't, my mom will fall in danger again.
Thankfully, the location tracker I put on him came back.
I'll track him down right away if he does anything suspicious.
Have you met with Kim Jin Ho?
Did he say anything?
Kim Jin Ho...
killed himself.
To sum it up, after you found your mother,
the only thing that changed is how Lee Taek Gyu didn't kill anyone.
Did your mother tell you about her relationship...
with Yujung Constructions?
No, not yet. She's very tired, so...
Kim Jin Ho killed himself?
If the tracker is still there,
I can see where Lee Taek Gyu has been.
(Rain Ville, Fresh Mill Mart 24)
(Yujung Building, Seoul Dongcheon Hospital)
Seoul Dongcheon Hospital.
Where's the hospital?
A hospital for inmates. Seoul Dongcheon Hospital.
(Seoul Dongcheon Hospital)
He was there.
Mom.
Mom!
- Are you up? - Mom!
- Mom! - Goodness.
What's gotten into you?
There's nothing in the fridge.
What were you eating while I was gone?
You're old enough...
to cook for yourself.
I thought you had left again.
Let me know when you need to go somewhere.
You were sound asleep, so I didn't wake you up.
Don't cry.
Let's go inside and eat.
Let's have a simple breakfast.
I should make some side dishes.
Let's go grocery shopping together.
No, let's go to the hospital first.
Have you been taking your medication?
Of course, I have.
You should eat up.
Your face has become even thinner. It breaks my heart.
Don't you know I lost weight...
because I was worried sick about you?
I like this.
Like what?
Just seeing you smile makes me happy.
I was going...
to ask you so many questions throughout the night.
But just looking at you makes me happy already.
Ask me.
I'll answer all of your questions.
Then...
promise me you'll tell me the truth.
Why did you leave the hospital all of a sudden?
I'm sorry about not telling you. I was wrong.
But I had my reasons.
You know I received a lot of money recently, right?
Yes.
Your father had a sizeable land in the countryside.
I didn't think anyone would buy it, so I didn't think much of it.
But they were going to develop the area, so I sold it.
That's where the money came from.
If that wasn't dirty money,
why did you suddenly disappear and hide?
People always find out when you get a lot of money...
and ask you for some. That's why I hid.
I was going to come back once the dust settled.
I didn't tell you...
because I was worried they'd pester you.
Then why did Kim Jin Ho look for you?
You disappeared out of the blue after meeting with him.
You don't know...
how Dad died, do you?
It was an accident.
Yujung Constructions was building a building in Taejung,
and it collapsed.
But that man...
knew I had lost your dad during that accident and visited me.
He said he was also in pain because of Yujung Constructions...
and asked for my help.
But there was nothing I could do to help.
What about Lee Taek Gyu?
What's your relationship with him?
He was the one who had sent you that money.
He works at Yujung Constructions.
What?
What are you saying? He must've had the same name.
Lee Taek Gyu is the name of the man who bought that land.
Are you really telling me the truth?
Ae Ri, let's go to the hospital and the market tomorrow.
Today, how about we visit your dad?
(Seoul Dongcheon Hospital)
(Police Line, Do Not Cross)
He limped, yet he climbed over this while his hands were cuffed?
There's a news article about Kim Jin Ho's suicide.
(There's a news article about Kim Jin Ho's suicide.)
("Jungdong Detention Center Inmate Who Visited a Hospital...")
("Leaves a Suicide Note and Kills Himself")
He jumped from the rooftop of Seoul Dongcheon Hospital at 10am.
(Seoul Dongcheon Hospital, 29 Sept, 9:34am to 10:09am)
That scumbag...
(Han Tae Gil, 41, male, Banyoung Constructions)
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm sorry for coming so late.
Are you okay?
It's been 19 years.
But it still feels like it was yesterday.
I should've bought some flowers.
There must be a flower shop nearby, right?
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Will you?
I won't take long.
Hello.
Do you sell condolence flowers?
Mom.
Mom?
Don't look for me.
That's the only way for us both to live.
The quicker you forget about me, the safer I'll be.
- Trust me when I say this. - Mom...
Mom, my gosh.
You'll end up dead at this rate.
Relay my words loud and clear.
If you wish to keep me from spilling what my husband knew...
about the accident involving Yujung Constructions,
you'll stay away from Ae Ri.
Lay a hand on her,
and I'll kill you all myself.
Do you think I'm bluffing?
I'm already dying anyway,
so I can easily leave a few bodies in my wake.
Once I know that my daughter is safe,
I'll hand in everything I have.
(Telecom)
(Location trackers for kids)
- Hey, Ae Ri. - Geon Wook, it's me.
Can you get me a taser gun?
A taser gun? That's out of the blue.
I think I should have one for self-protection...
and hand another to my mom.
Are you home? Did your mom go out?
Yes, I'm home...
and Mom's home too.
Just for self-protection, right? I'll swing by with them later.
No, I'll come and collect them.
Where's Da Bin? Is she elsewhere?
Taek Gyu took her.
For Da Bin to follow Kim Jin Ho out on the day of the concert,
she needs to be well-acquainted with him.
He has a daughter her age,
so he'll easily befriend her.
Are you sure Kim Jin Ho is on board?
Can we safely leave her with him?
Will Kim Jin Ho really do as we want?
He believes that Seo Jin actually used illegal materials...
and that it caused the death of his daughter.
Also,
his second daughter is ill.
I doubt he'll do anything stupid...
when her life's on the line.
All right.
I'll trust you and believe it to be a safe plan.
I'll soon have the passports ready, so consider that taken care of too.
Only one more thing remains.
From there to here is the camera blind spot.
Walk into it starting from that point...
and leave a voice message to Seo Jin right there.
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
I can't take this anymore. Honey...
I'll pick you up while you're still within the blind spot.
I won't be caught on camera here?
I'm sure of it.
Can I use it right away?
Yes, turn on the power and press that button.
Be careful with it. The voltage on that is no joke.
Sure. Catch you later.
Did you take your mom to the hospital?
I'm heading home right now.
Da Bin went back to her mother after spending time with Kim Jin Ho.
Yes, Mr. Seo.
Let me go.
Let go!
What on earth are you doing?
Do you have a death wish?
If not, my mom will die.
I have no choice but to kill him first.
He must die for my mom to live.
What? Where's your mom?
Where is she right now?
Geon Wook,
I need your help.
No, I won't help you.
I can't anymore.
Not until you tell me everything you know.
(Ae Ri, don't look for me.)
Tell me again what's going on.
When...
I lost my phone,
I made contact with the one who found it.
He's Kim Seo Jin...
but from a month later.
What? A month later?
Today's date is August 30, right?
The Kim Seo Jin I'm in contact with...
lives in September 30.
What? This isn't funny, you know.
What's with the serious faces?
Are you sick by any chance? Do you have a fever?
This'll help you understand.
Let me give you a massage. How about a glass of water?
(Missing Child)
(Kim Da Bin, 6)
Why are you taking this seriously?
(Missing Child, September 6, 2020)
His daughter was kidnapped.
I mean,
she'll soon be kidnapped.
Ms. Han?
But then he said you were going to die.
The place we're headed to...
is where Mom will stay starting September 14.
That's where I'll start backtracking her steps.
What does he have to do with your mom's disappearance?
I don't know. Mom won't tell me the truth.
So this Lee Taek Gyu will hurt your mom?
What's up with you two?
Exactly!
It's why I should kill him before he gets to Mom.
Are you saying you'd rather be a killer?
Besides, who says he'll let you kill him?
You'll only get hurt if you go after him.
Then what option do I have?
Darn it! We need a way to catch this scumbag.
Guys, you're scaring me.
Let's just look for Ae Ri's mom instead.
We found her once, so we'll be able to do it again.
Finding her will solve everything.
But there's only one thing we could do at this point.
We have to stop Lee Taek Gyu from doing what he did.
We don't have any other options.
Hey, how do you want us to help you? Tell me.
Have you two gone insane? You're both crazy.
Hey.
(My mom is gone again! Lee Taek Gyu... I'll kill that man!)
My mom is gone again!
Lee Taek Gyu... I'll kill that man!
Mr. Kim.
Ms. Han, is everything all right?
Did you really see Lee Taek Gyu?
No.
I'm so glad.
You should never meet him whenever you're alone.
Let's find your mother once again.
I'm sure we'll be able to find him.
I went to the hospital where Kim Jin Ho killed himself...
and found out new information...
Lee Taek Gyu was there at that hospital...
when Kim Jin Ho died.
There's only one thing I can do.
What is it?
We have to stop Da Bin's abduction.
That's the only thing I could do over here.
I'll make sure I stop Da Bin from getting abducted,
then persuade Kim Jin Ho to get Lee Taek Gyu arrested.
Please keep my mother safe over there, Mr. Kim.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
I'll make sure...
I protect your mother no matter what happens.
All right, we're going to begin treasure hunting.
- Okay. - Find the coloured paper we hid.
- Okay! - Don't go too far.
- Ready, go! - Let's go!
- Let's go. - Let's find it.
- I found it! - I found it too.
I found it!
You found one?
Ta-Da.
Hello, lady.
This is for you, Da Bin.
Where did you find it?
I can see all the treasure.
Then can you find me another one?
Then should we give the treasure to your stuffed doll too?
I'll have that.
Now, close your eyes, turn around, and count to 10.
You have to keep your eyes closed.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
We found another treasure!
Da Bin, this treasure you got today is quite special.
If you keep this doll with you,
we can find you no matter where you are.
You have to tell your dad about it.
Okay?
Dad!
Some lady came today and gave this doll a treasure.
If I keep this with me, I can always be found.
Dad! I'm here!
Hey, Da Bin.
Dad, look at this. This doll is now very special.
- Why is it special? - Some lady came today...
and gave this doll a treasure.
If I keep this with me, I can always be found.
Is that so? One second.
She told me to tell you about it.
All right, I get it. One second.
A location tracker?
I put in a location tracker in Da Bin's stuffed teddy bear.
If I can't stop her from getting abducted until the recital,
I'll look at this to find her.
The app can be installed on more than one phone.
The locations are stored for about 10 days, so you can take a look.
I'm sending you the app address and the registration number.
The tracked vehicle has just left Yujung Constructions.
(Yujung Building)
The tracked vehicle has just left Bella Studio.
("An Inmate from Jungdong Detention Center...")
("Leaves a Will and Commits Suicide While Receiving Hospital Care")
What's this article?
I took care of Kim Jin Ho.
So why did you kill him?
I told you to just make him scared.
The investigation was concluded as suicide, so it'll be fine.
Who are you to make decisions?
My plan doesn't include murder.
Do Kyun.
Are you kidding me?
What about my money?
- What? - What if Kim Jin Ho...
spills the truth to Kim Seo Jin?
Kim Seo Jin's money isn't yours yet.
I just need my money according to the contract.
Taek Gyu.
Remember what that contract was about.
If you don't stick to the contract, you won't get any money.
Just do as I tell you, okay?
Call me if something happens.
Don't do anything stupid.
(Villa de Foret)
Turn right after 200m.
Drive in the first lane from the right.
Hello, Ms. Han.
Did you read my texts?
I've put a tracker inside Da Bin's teddy bear.
I know.
I've obtained a new memory of her telling me about that teddy bear.
If it's only been a month, I'm sure there's still battery life.
Open it right now.
There could be a record...
of all the past locations where she's been.
I'm connecting right now.
While tailing Lee Taek Gyu today,
I saw Seo Do Kyun with him.
They were at that studio where you almost lost your life.
Why were they there?
Did you find any new information?
No, I haven't.
I was chasing Mr. Seo up until a while ago when I lost him.
(The service is unavailable.)
It says that the service is unavailable.
That can't be. I can...
(Connecting)
(The service is unavailable.)
Should we just leave?
The passports are still valid.
I haven't seen that face in a while.
When I had left you back then,
you had the same expression on your face.
Give me a bit more time.
I'll take care of everything.
Are you worried?
Should I be?
No. I'll take care of Kim Seo Jin first...
I don't want to lose...
any of the things I have.
Whether it be money, Da Bin,
or you.
That was also something you promised me.
You can trust me.
It's the first day of September, the start of the fall season.
The sweltering heat has gone away,
and September will be full of various cultural events.
On September 6...
at the grand ballroom of Saint Mayott Hotel,
Yujung Constructions will be hosting a charity performance.
Violinist Kang Hyun Chae...
and Pianist Ko Jeong Min will be performing.
On the same day in Yangwon-Gu, Seoul,
60 different dishes from all around the world...
Are you having dinner at home tonight?
I'm not sure. Why?
The recital is around the corner.
I'll be coming home late after the practice.
Then I'll take care...
of dinner myself.
- Bye. - Bye.
I think I've given you enough time. Are you fully prepared?
Let's meet first.
You should hurry.
(You should hurry.)
We could've just told Mr. Lee to take care of it.
Will you really be okay?
I should be the one to choose my daughter's double.
She has similar hair length.
I'll take her hair today.
Get in.
Yes, sir.
Why did you come to work?
You should rest more.
I had some matters to take care of.
I read about how that man committed suicide.
All lives are important,
but he reaped what he sowed.
What goes around comes around.
Everything will find its place,
so hang in there.
Yes, sir.
Someone put a tracker on my car.
Any guesses as to who put it there?
My guess would be Director Kim.
We took my car when we went to see Kim Jin Ho.
I'm not sure how he found a moment to attach it,
but he must've been tracking me since that day.
It's good to see you, Mr. Kim.
What brings you by the office?
I had business at HR.
- Are you heading outside today? - No, sir.
Then be at my office in 30 minutes.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
Mr. Kim.
Do you have what I requested yesterday?
Yes, here you go.
Thank you.
(Personnel Record: Seo Do Kyun)
(Personnel Record: Lee Taek Gyu)
Do you also have the files on Mr. Han Tae Gil that I requested?
You see,
it's hard to find the files on an employee...
who's not in the database.
Do you perhaps know his title or when he joined the company?
Truth be told, he passed away in the Taejung Town incident.
That's all I know about him.
Oh, I see.
Then he could've been an employee...
at Banyoung Constructions instead.
The database update is an ongoing project,
so you could have your answer when it's over.
Banyoung Constructions?
Got it. Carry on then.
(Employee Evaluation)
(Personnel Record: Lee Taek Gyu)
(Director Kim Seo Jin)
(Daeseung High School)
Is there anything you need me to do?
Have a seat.
I'm grateful for you filling in for me.
I hear you're down by the site often too.
Oh, please. It's not a hassle.
Did you go by the site too?
According to your work schedule,
you were at the site on the 29th with Taek Gyu.
That's right.
Not according to the people there though.
Sorry?
They say it was only you.
Are they wrong?
Let me apologize. I must've had it mixed up.
Then where was Taek Gyu...
on the morning of the 29th?
To tell you the truth, I'm not sure.
I didn't even know that that's what he wrote.
Kim Jin Ho is dead.
I read the article regarding his suicide.
It wasn't suicide.
He was murdered on the morning of the 29th.
Are you sure?
The day Kim Jin Ho died,
didn't you two leave the office to head to the construction site?
No.
I don't know where he was that day.
Why are you suddenly asking me about him?
Aren't I allowed to check up on my personal assistant?
Do my questions bother you?
No, of course not.
It's just odd that you're asking about his whereabouts...
on the day Kim Jin Ho died.
Are you covering for him...
because you come from the same hometown?
I already told you...
that I didn't know him prior to coming to work here.
You don't know anything, is that it?
That's right. I don't.
(Personnel Record: Lee Taek Gyu)
(Personnel Record: Seo Do Kyun)
You and your trust issues.
You never think you're wrong, do you?
What do you mean by that?
You've always had your way and failure is a foreign concept to you.
I'm sure you don't care about other people's stories,
but we're not failures...
just because we don't meet your standards.
Life isn't easy for anyone, you know.
I'm talking about Mr. Lee, sir.
It's wrong to jump to conclusions about your subordinates.
Are you sure it's about Taek Gyu?
To me, it sounds biographical.
You're dismissed.
- Hello? - Mr. Kim,
I have the test result regarding Da Bin's belongings.
Did you find anything related to her stuffed animal?
No, should I have found something?
No, forget I said anything.
When can I come to collect it?
Come by the station tomorrow
(State Exam Study Book)
Do you need anything?
That'll be 2.5 dollars.
There you go.
I'm sure you remember me.
You're Da Bin's mother.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't easily mention my daughter's name.
From what I understand,
ex-cons can't apply for any state exam.
Being connected to us in some way...
might seem like finding gold to you,
but you should watch yourself.
If you wish to keep what you have, of course.
If you called yourself a mother,
shouldn't you have heard me out...
when I said that your child was in danger?
You.
What did I tell you about mentioning my daughter?
Cross the line again and I'll take action too.
Do you hear me?
I feel bad for Mr. Kim.
What did you just say?
I don't know what family means to you,
but he's doing everything possible to save his family...
even if it means losing all he has.
Who's trying to save what?
Even being accused of murder...
hasn't stopped him from trying to save you and your daughter.
Am I talking to a lunatic?
You can think I'm crazy all you want.
But at least notify the police...
and protect your child that day.
Ms. Han,
I doubt this'll get through your thick skull,
but I'll say it anyway.
Don't...
take my warning lightly.
Hello.
Hey, what's wrong?
It's nothing.
Did you look into what I asked?
Log in with this.
(ID: gw0407, Password: rjsdnrWkd!)
I changed the registered name to me.
Does it work?
Yes.
By the way, your ID worked. Why did you ask for a new one?
It works for now. But after a month, it won't.
Why not?
I'm not sure.
It's not like I know everything that'll happen next month.
Did Mr. Kim tell you anything else?
No. He just said he couldn't log in.
Hey, it works.
You're right.
Hello? Ms. Han.
The teddy bear you inserted that tracker into...
was the one she had on the day of her disappearance, right?
The one she always carries around.
Are you sure that was the right one?
Yes, I'm sure. Just in case, I changed the registered name.
Did you get the new ID and password?
Okay, let me log in again.
(Han Ae Ri: This is the ID and password.)
I'll check the teddy bear myself tomorrow.
But the police said they found nothing inside.
That can't be.
Then...
did Kim Jin Ho move?
(Find My Child)
It's working.
(Connecting)
The signal is...
(Villa de Foret)
- Hello, Mr. Kim. - Mr. Park.
You said there was nothing in the teddy bear, right?
Yes.
Should there have been something inside?
Where are Da Bin's belongings right now?
They're back at the station. I just checked before leaving.
I'll go there right now.
Mr. Kim...
Okay. I'll see you at the station.
It must've been extremely tough.
I know it's hard not to go insane...
Thank you.
(Connecting)
(Villa de Foret)
Da Bin.
(Villa de Foret, Time remaining: 4 hours 40 minutes)
(September 2, Wednesday)
(How did it go? Did you find the toy?)
Excuse me. I'm looking for a child.
Is your child missing? What's your room number?
She's a six-year-old girl. Have you seen her around here?
Her name is Kim Da Bin.
I'm sorry, but we don't include children's names in our name list.
Do you know her guardian's name?
Da Bin.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
(Villa de Foret)
Is this also a part of your hotel?
I think there are villas there.
Villas? Thank you.
Where is it?
Goodness.
You've prepared so much.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Let's eat.
Kim Jin Ho probably kidnapped Da Bin in the hallway...
and took her to his car, so this would be the exit.
You'll follow Da Bin from the event hall...
and you'll stay in the lobby.
I'll trail Kim Jin Ho.
Do you mean we should split apart?
I'll get us all a communicating device.
I doubt there will be any blind spots.
Ae Ri, I'm scared.
Must we go this far?
She's all we have.
It's up to us to prevent this kidnapping.
(Soo Jung, Kitchen)
(Concert Hall)
(Kairos)
I told you to be patient.
I've been patient for over 20 years.
I'm ready to give it all up.
Hyun Chae, I will keep every promise I made to you.
I don't care what happens to me. Just make sure you keep your word.
They're entering right now.
This isn't because I believe you two.
Just make sure you get the job done.
Is Da Bin here?
Yes, Da Bin's here.
Why don't we have some fun later?
Where's my stuffed animal?
He's here! Kim Jin Ho is entering the building.
Ms. Han? Why are you here?
It's Section 5-B.
Please be okay, Mr. Kim.
Everything will change tomorrow. I'm sure of it.
Da Bin!