We aren't open yet.
We aren't open...
I'm here to see the manager.
Pardon?
Hey, turn off the music!
How may I help you again?
I'm here to see the manager.
Oh, the manager.
Hey!
Are you Ms. Kang Hyun Chae?
- Yes. - I see. Come this way.
Kang Hyun Chae?
You can take this.
I live nearby. Or I can just sleep in the bar.
No, it's okay. You shouldn't get that wet, right?
That thing you are holding.
Come on.
Man!
- Don't go. - Come on.
Where are you going?
How much do you get paid here?
Do you want to leave with me now?
I'll pay you in advance.
Come on, it's your pay.
Man, you must know you're pretty to be acting so haughty.
What's this? Do you play this too?
Get your hands off.
Yes, so let's grab a drink.
Get your hands off my instrument.
Do you want a piece of me?
- What's he doing? - What was that?
- Are you okay? - Get him!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
You got me fired.
Sorry. Oh, I'm sorry.
It looks like you got fired because of me too.
Let's call it even.
Okay, sure.
Why are you speaking casually to me?
I thought you were younger than me.
Right.
Where do you live? I'll take you home.
Pyeongchang-dong.
You can't get to my place without a car.
A car?
I'll grab a taxi.
Do you believe that?
What?
That I live in Pyeongchang-dong.
That's a rich town.
It suits you, Hyun Chae.
To be honest, I have nowhere to go.
No.
I don't want to go home.
Then...
do you want to come to my place?
Man, I told them to clean up before they leave.
We just moved in.
- This place is a mess. - Gosh.
What's this? Oh, a book I've been reading.
I'm really tired right now, so...
I'll use the bed.
Sure. Suit yourself.
Gosh, it's hot.
What in the world?
Do you have any coffee?
I'll buy some.
Coffee.
Would she prefer latte? Americano?
She looks like the espresso type.
I didn't know what you preferred, so I was going to buy everything.
Sorry. I didn't have any spare clothes.
Your death has been pushed back one day.
Tomorrow night, you'll be murdered once again.
At unit 609 of a studio apartment in Yeoksam-dong,
you will be found dead.
Save yourself.
(Han Ae Ri)
Han Ae Ri?
Hand it over!
(Han Ae Ri)
The call cannot be connected. You'll be transferred to voicemail.
I asked if that's how you think as well.
You punk. Have you gone crazy?
The call cannot be connected.
(10:34pm, September 24, Thursday)
What is the meaning of this?
Seo Do Kyun,
who do you think you are?
(Episode 5)
(Lee Taek Gyu)
Let's go.
I'll drop you off at home.
Why?
Seo Jin will be late today.
You don't know the exact time.
Is something wrong?
No.
I don't need to worry about anything, right?
Do you want to listen to some music?
Sure.
(Unknown Album)
(Unknown Artist)
(Director Kim Seo Jin)
(Missed call)
Why is he calling at this hour?
(Seo Jin)
- Hi, honey. - Hi, are you still up?
Yes. When are you coming home?
I don't think I can tonight. I called to tell you that.
Can you send over some spare clothes?
- Okay. - Bye.
(Missed Call: Director Kim Seo Jin)
- Hey. - Sir, did you call?
I'm sorry I couldn't pick up.
It's okay. I took care of it.
Are you still at the office?
Why are you still there at this hour?
Are you with someone?
No, it's the television.
It's getting late. I'm hanging up.
Everything was going perfect...
for the first time in a long time.
Seo Do Kyun.
Help me understand...
this situation.
I thought you had trust in me.
I thought you were at least honest with me,
so I trusted you as well.
You trusted me?
Illegal materials were used for the amusement complex?
That's not who you are.
I'm just upset that everything you've done until now...
has gone to waste.
What?
Is that really what you think?
What is it?
Do you think this incident will destroy me?
Is that what you wanted?
- Pardon? - I don't think...
you of all people should talk about "trust".
The testing process was a total mess.
You've looked over...
everything that I've done all this time.
The numbers...
you had shown me were fine.
But what about the testing institutions?
They were all trustworthy institutions.
Did you not know that it had expired?
I renewed it.
They had deliberately changed the date of issue,
and the mandatory information wasn't there.
The private testing institution you had found...
were still undergoing the test under a different standard.
You had already given me...
the approval to go through with that.
I have no idea why you're...
Shouldn't you have checked?
(Manager Seo Do Kyun, Hyun Chae)
Are you still up? I'll see you at the office.
Are you still at the office?
Why are you still there at this hour?
- Are you with someone? - No,
- it's the television. - It's getting late. I'm hanging up.
Mr. Kim, I've faxed the test results.
So?
Are you blaming me for everything?
You used illegal materials.
You've wronged an innocent and told me to take care of it!
Is this what you call trust?
How much more do I need to be disappointed in you?
(Korea Testing Laboratory)
Sir.
Check this out. Have you gone over these?
What is it?
I checked the report.
I see you received an evaluation...
from even the officially authorized Korea Testing Laboratory.
I personally requested for...
an additional test.
Everything's clean.
Why didn't you tell me about this sooner?
It would've saved us both a lot of time.
You may go now.
Please let me know if you need anything else.
We're sorry for any inconvenience.
(Prosecution Service)
Mr. Kim.
I'm glad you're off the hook.
I know it wasn't easy being questioned for so long.
Even though your work can be considered as a mistake,
what you said back in there...
points to you playing the blame game.
I'm sorry.
My mind started to paint scenarios ever since the prosecution took you.
That was thoughtless of me.
Just like you wanted,
I'm going to thoroughly check who is responsible.
Hello?
What happened to Han Ae Ri's case?
Han... What? What case?
The Yeoksam-dong studio apartment murder case.
Did such a murder occur?
Where did you hear that?
Are you saying that no one was killed...
at a studio apartment in Yeoksam-dong?
That's within our jurisdiction, but it doesn't ring a bell.
I guess I got it mixed up.
If it weren't for Ms. Han...
Why was I almost murdered again?
I managed to escape that fate twice thanks to you,
but no one can guarantee that it won't happen again.
I'm frustrated and scared...
how I don't even know why someone wants me dead.
Hello.
Good morning, Mr. Kim.
I want to see Manager Seo in my office.
He's working outside the office at the moment.
- Move. - You're to head home, sir.
What?
What did you just say to me?
I'll escort you home.
It's best if you head home...
(Chairman)
Yes, Mr. Yu. This is Kim Seo Jin.
Come see me at my office.
Yes, sir.
I ordered him to take you home.
The questioning was wrapped up without any hitches.
The chief prosecutor is a hometown friend,
so I already heard the news.
Still, you should lay low for the time being.
It's actually for your own sake.
Contrary to popular belief,
people don't care about others' lives.
It won't have to be for long.
Come back to the office once people lose interest.
The press will soon report my innocence.
If that's not enough, I'll sue Kim Jin Ho for defamation.
You're not hearing me.
Being mentioned at all right now will hurt you,
so let time be on your side.
I'm going to do whatever I can...
to put things back to normal.
I hear you, all right?
Still, Manager Seo can take over for you.
He's your most trusted man, isn't he?
Take a break when the opportunity allows it.
I'll escort you home, sir.
Did you grab a few drinks last night?
Don't tell me you got into a fight.
I didn't, sir.
You're my personal assistant,
not some hormonal teenager.
If you're going to drink, be a gentleman about it.
Yes, sir. It won't happen again.
A man I couldn't identify was at his house last night.
I threw something at him while running away,
and it scratched his face a little.
- Has the scar fully healed? - Sorry?
Oh, that. Yes, sir.
When did it happen again?
Was it a month ago?
I've been carrying myself better ever since that day.
I apologize for troubling you, sir.
Please call me whenever you need a driver.
Thanks.
Mr. Kim.
If... And this is a big if.
What if my mom is a part of the reason I almost got killed?
(What if my mom is a part of the reason I almost got killed?)
Then I can't just sit like this.
I need...
to know the reason.
Instead of worrying about something that hasn't happened,
I'd rather face it.
Ji Ah, do you want to get changed into new clothes?
No?
Why not?
Okay, then. Let's get changed tomorrow.
My princess, you're so adorable even in a patient's gown.
Mr. Kim.
You know my mother, don't you?
Her name is Kwak Song Ja.
Why did you come to my mother's hospital room?
My mom disappeared right after you came to see her.
What did you say to her?
Please tell me. This is very important to me.
The man who was with you on that day...
followed me and tried to kill me.
I kept thinking about it, but I have no idea why.
I just went there to help you...
How can you help me anyway?
Will you turn back the time and bring back my dead kid?
Or can you help my dying daughter get better?
Don't do anything, okay?
Da Bin is also someone's precious daughter, just like Ji Ah.
If Mr. Kim Seo Jin did something wrong, make him pay for it.
You're a father too!
What about Han Tae Gil?
What about your father, Mr. Han Tae Gil?
Don't put desperate fathers like Mr. Han and me...
in the same category as Kim Seo Jin.
I'm not going to end this like how your father died in vain...
at Taejung Town.
What do you mean?
My dad? Where and how did my father die again?
(Phone Booth)
You must keep your promise.
You don't have much time left.
If you don't transfer the money until that day,
I will do as I've already told you.
And do not lay a finger on my daughter.
She doesn't know anything.
I'm going to die of my heart condition anyway.
I'll go somewhere far away, live quietly, and die quietly too.
So keep your promise.
If you mess with my daughter,
I'll not let you live.
(Total confidentiality, Taeheung Planning)
Hey, you're here.
That's the name and the number. Please run a background check.
Find out as much as you can.
(Han Ae Ri)
(Seoul to Taejung)
What about your father, Mr. Han Tae Gil?
I'm not going to end this like how your father died in vain...
at Taejung Town.
("Taejung Town Collapses")
("The Collapse of Taejung Town, the Truth Behind the Accident?")
(Taejung Station)
Mr. Kim.
I came back to my old neighbourhood for the 1st time in 19 years.
The rescue of the buried at Taejung Town continues today.
There were many sad stories...
behind the collapse of Taejung Town.
Lee, a construction worker who was found dead...
on the first basement,
is a father of an infant who's about to turn one year old.
Among those who were buried, there was a high school student...
who just finished taking their college entrance exam.
Lee was found next to his father...
My mother never told me...
how my father passed away.
We almost ran off from this town 19 years ago.
Although I was very young,
I realized that my father had gone away to a place...
where he can never return from.
(Taejung Town Collapse Memorial Park)
(May you rest in peace.)
I couldn't imagine something so tragic had happened...
(Kim Jung Hoon, Noh Myung Soon, Song Joo Min, Lee Kyung Soo...)
that she was afraid to bring it up.
(Han Tae Gil, 41 years old, male, Banyoung Constructions)
(About the Accident)
(Through the accident, 68 died, 3 went missing, and 132 injured.)
Yujung Constructions.
(Banyoung and Yujung Constructions signed a co-contract...)
I hope you safely escaped...
from the studio apartment last night.
I know it's tough, but please hang in there.
Once everything is over, Our families...
should meet.
I believe I can start afresh with my wife and my daughter.
Is anyone in?
How may I help you?
Does unit 609 have a registered vehicle?
What is this about? Are you the resident?
No.
Actually, I had gotten into a car accident a few days ago.
The owner of the other car lived in unit 609.
And?
But I lost their number.
Could you tell me?
Didn't you guys call the insurance company?
- Show me your ID card, please. - Sure.
The crash wasn't big enough to call the insurance company.
Here.
Yes.
One minute.
Unit 609 does have a registered vehicle, right?
Registered vehicle...
Here it is.
Do you just need the number?
Yes, hold on.
- Okay. - 010.
- 010. - 0412.
0412.
1207.
Is that all?
(General Manager Lee Taek Gyu)
Is he the one who was chasing us that night?
I recorded this yesterday in front of Kim Jin Ho's place.
I couldn't see his face clearly that night...
because it was dark and I was running.
It's him. Do you know who he is?
I only got his license plate number and this video.
Darn it. I should've chased after him.
Send that to me right now.
(Geon Wook)
And the license plate number?
Hurry.
Whom are you sending it to?
That fraud who said you'd die?
- He's not a fraud. - He's from Yujung Constructions,
isn't he?
I knew something was odd when I had gotten you that ID card.
What's his name?
I should know the entire picture if I want to help.
Director Kim Seo Jin.
His daughter was kidnapped.
Kidnapped?
When? Was it on the news?
No. I mean...
She'll be kidnapped soon.
That's why I agreed to help him.
How exactly?
I'll tell you next time.
Gosh, this is...
Does Soo Jung know this?
I don't want to burden her.
You're the only person I've told.
How old is his daughter? Are they being threatened?
Something like that. She's six.
Then he should attach a tracker on her...
and download the lost child prevention app.
That way, he'll be able to find her even if she gets kidnapped.
I'll get a tracker for you.
I won't ask any more questions until you tell me yourself.
So feel free to ask me for help.
Don't keep it all bottled up.
Thank you.
- Ae Ri. - You were on the phone all day.
Bring your own chair.
Ae Ri, about that from earlier...
I can't take it any longer.
- Are you guys dating? - Have you gone insane?
Up until recently, she was about to kill you for stealing her money.
So why are you guys whispering in front of the dinner table?
You helped us reconcile.
Me? When?
You're so mentally strong.
That's true. I am.
It's all thanks to receiving my grandma's love growing up.
- Lucky you. - Hey.
Do you guys...
remember everything from when you were 5 or 6?
- Of course. - Of course.
To be honest, I don't remember every single thing.
But I do remember the impactful ones.
For example, I remember my mom only buying my sister...
a new pair of shoes.
Stuff like that.
If you were...
kidnapped as a little kid...
or something like that,
it'll traumatize you for life, right?
That's a terrifying thought.
What is it?
Is there a little customer who pulls at your heartstrings?
How did she know?
She gives special attention to a middle-aged drunkard...
because he's a regular at her convenience store.
He is a regular. He buys soju every day.
Oh, my.
Is that why you got hold of his wife's number?
What if he gets into an accident while drunk?
He has a family too, you know?
Whether it's my family or not, I hate seeing people get injured.
Come on.
Your mom will be fine.
Wherever she may be, she'll think of you and stay strong.
So eat up and restore your energy. Here.
Wider.
This is some mean chicken.
It is.
- You're eating so well. - I'm famished.
(Han Ae Ri)
What is this?
Where and how did you record this?
It's the man who chased after me from Kim Jin Ho's place.
Geon Wook recorded that the following day...
after hiding in front of Kim Jin Ho's.
He's Lee Taek Gyu, my personal assistant.
Why was your personal assistant...
with Kim Jin Ho?
He also stopped by that studio apartment...
where you could've gotten murdered.
I've put together the incidents that you've experienced...
and the information I've discovered.
There's a link between Kim Jin Ho and him.
And the 1st 2 murder attempts...
were carried out by my personal assistant.
Yujung Constructions.
What did you say?
Did you listen to the voicemail I sent today?
No.
Not yet. Did something happen?
I met with Kim Jin Ho...
and found out how my dad died.
A tall building collapsed in Taejung 19 years ago.
And...
that was how he died.
One of the construction companies responsible for the disaster...
was Yujung Constructions.
Hello? Mr. Kim?
- Are you still there? - Ms. Han,
are you sure?
What I know for sure now...
is that my parents are connected to Yujung Constructions.
My mom's disappearance...
- Let's go. - Sure.
You should catch up on your sleep now that the CSAT is over,
not follow me out.
I've been dying to see where you work, Dad.
Not everyone can work at construction sites.
Not being prepared lead to accidents.
- Dad... - Again with the cheekiness.
Keep it on. It's chilly.
- Since it's cold... - I told you to keep it on.
Come on, let's go.
It's chilly, so put it on.
Get closer.
Come on.
Dad, I'm going to the restroom.
- It's inside. - Got it.
(Restroom)
(Yujung Constructions)
Everybody, run!
- Run! - Get out of here.
- Run out of here. - Get going!
- My gosh. - Get out of here!
What's going on?
The structure's collapsing.
Seo Jin? Seo Jin!
Seo Jin!
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Taek Gyu, it's me.
My car's in the shop, and I needed to go somewhere.
Could you perhaps drive me in yours?
Mr. Kim.
Where to, sir?
I'm off to see Kim Jin Ho.
I'll need an address.
Jungdong Detention Center.
Yes, sir.
I requested a visit,
but I don't remember for which time slot.
I've had too much on my mind lately.
I'll go and ask, sir.
Right. The reception is that way.
Sir, you can go and visit him now.
Sure. Good work.
I'll wait here until you're done.
It's fine. You can get going. I have some place else to be anyway.
Yes, sir.
(Jungdong Detention Center)
You still have something more to say?
How do you know Lee Taek Gyu, my personal assistant?
It was him who followed Ms. Han Ae Ri...
with the intention of killing her.
I knew it. It wasn't just your personal vendetta.
So tell me.
- What did you receive in return? - I don't know what you mean.
I didn't expect you to talk so easily.
Mr. Kim, I went by...
the hospital your second child is at.
You still have a reason to live.
I...
can't even give up the one I lost,
so how could you abandon the one that's still alive?
You should leave.
I don't know what you were promised,
but those who kidnapped and murdered my child...
won't protect you.
They were ruthless enough to kill a child for their goal.
Do you seriously think they'd protect yours?
Tell me the truth, and I'll help you.
I promise...
on my child's soul.
I have nothing to say.
I'm... I'm going back to my cell now.
No...
(Visiting Room 1)
(Recipient: Kwak Song Ja)
My gosh. Are you kidding me with this electricity bill?
What on earth? That's all we used?
Mom! You don't turn on the AC when I'm not home, do you?
Why would I need to...
when I can open the windows and let the breeze cool me down?
Mom, please. Turn on the AC in the summer...
and the heater in the winter.
It'll cost us more if you get sick.
Got it?
They keep the AC on all day at your workplace, right?
Mom, can you make me doenjang stew...
with pork and ugeoji?
Sure. Let's have a lovely dinner.
Mom, where are you right now?
I have so much to ask you.
Mr. Park.
- What is it? - Have you read the article?
- About what? - About Mr. Kim Seo Jin.
He has been cleared of all charges.
("Director Kim Seo Jin of Yujung Constructions...")
("Cleared of Charges Regarding Illegal Materials")
("Rumours About Illegal Materials Turn Out to be False")
Why are they making a fuss out of something that's obvious?
Did Seo Jin see this? Let him know.
Yes, sir.
Also, make a dinner appointment with him.
Hold on.
What's a good, rejuvenating dish?
- I'll look for a place. - Okay.
(Chief secretary)
(They published an article about your acquittal.)
The vehicle you're tracking is in Yujung Constructions' basement.
(Kim Seo Jin cleared)
("Director Kim Seo Jin of Yujung Constructions...")
("Cleared of Charges Regarding Illegal Materials")
Hello?
I'm certain that it's Han Ae Ri.
You gave me her number and told me to look into it,
so I did.
She was just someone preparing for the civil service test.
Is something wrong?
She's still contacting Kim Seo Jin.
Look into the call history.
Yes, sir.
Where did it go awry?
Sir.
Because he killed my Da Bin.
Mr. Kim, please let me know if there's anything...
you need.
Thank you for today. I'll be in touch.
The chairman said that even though you trust nobody,
you still rely on me in a certain way.
Is that what you think as well?
- Han Ae Ri. - Han Ae Ri.
Han Ae Ri.
(Han Ae Ri)
- Han Ae Ri? - Hand it over!
Da Bin will be kidnapped by Kim Jin Ho.
That's exactly why you should meet with him to prevent that.
("Director Kim Seo Jin of Yujung Constructions...")
("Cleared of Charges Regarding Illegal Materials")
Did you see this?
("Director Kim Seo Jin of Yujung Constructions...")
("Cleared of Charges Regarding Illegal Materials")
Mom!
So?
What's your next move?
The vehicle you're tracking has entered...
Yeongdong Expressway.
(Yeongdong Expressway)
(Mom, Kim Jin Ho)
("What Is the Truth Behind the Fall of Taejung Town?")
(Mom, Kim Jin Ho, Yujung Constructions, Dad)
(Lee Taek Gyu)
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Hey, I'm sorry for calling you so late.
Where are you right now?
I'm home.
I should've called you sooner. You're already home?
Yes.
How may I help you?
It's nothing much.
I must be out of it these days. I keep leaving things behind.
I think I left my wallet in your car.
Can you check right now?
Okay. I'll look for it and call you back.
(Illju)
Is anyone here?
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
Right.
Ms. Kwak Song Ja?
I'm here on behalf of Yujung Constructions.
Could we talk?
(Kairos)
I followed Lee Taek Gyu only to find a dead body.
Where are you? Tell me where you are!
I wish to leave the country with you as soon as possible.
It's been a long desire of mine.
Life has been exceptionally cruel to Seo Jin.
What were you notified of?
I received an odd text.
I can't lie to Ae Ri anymore!
Director Kim used the illegal materials.
Must I keep my silence?
Yes, exactly.
I'll kill them all.
Why not point that anger at a specific someone?
You must find her before September 26.
Why the deadline?
Mr. Kim, are you sure you didn't recognize the body?
I'll find your mother no matter what.