=The Tale of Rose=
=Episode 19=
How did you get soaked like this?
Is something wrong?
Let's break up.
Change your clothes for dinner.
Someone has to take the fall for this.
Jason meant
that Zhou was the best choice.
But he did nothing wrong.
Neither did you.
But I'm his supervisor.
What can I do?
He just graduated
and still shares a place.
His mom is also sick recently.
It's my fault.
I'm just not cut out for management.
The client will demand compensation.
The company won't give me
a recommendation letter
and will blame everything on me.
I won't be able
to find a job easily.
I don't want to drag you down.
Let's...
Let's get married.
Well,
I don't have a job now,
and I have no money.
The marriage license is only nine yuan.
Rose,
I'm not in the mood to joke.
I'm not joking.
You can find another job.
You can earn more money.
My salary
is enough for both of us.
You don't need to pity me.
I'm not Tiny.
I'm not a stray cat you picked up.
You don't have to
take responsibility for me.
Rose,
I...
I love you very much.
But I have nothing now.
Marrying you like this
would make me a loser.
Don't forget to
wash the dishes after dinner.
But,
Rose...
♪A rose alive♪
♪With a post-storm glow♪
♪Sunlight on her skirt♪
Get up.
♪Like a splash of red in a dull world♪
Come on, come on.
We have a task today.
♪I'll take her away at all costs♪
What are you doing?
♪Plant her in the warmest corner
of my heart♪
♪Give my love to her♪
♪Give everything to her♪
♪Watch her bloom proudly, just for me♪
♪I'll give her shelter♪
Why did you push me?
It's okay.
It's not that deep.
Stand up.
It's fine.
♪In the end♪
- Come on.
- You know I can't swim.
♪She is my only rose♪
♪Please grant her forever♪
You're too bad.
♪I want to give her a home,
years of happiness♪
♪And the deepest love with me♪
Are you okay now?
You were so scared just now.
It wasn't that serious, was it?
This setback too.
Losing a job
isn't the end of the world.
Finding another job
shouldn't be hard for you.
Have you thought
that this might be an opportunity?
Senior Fang,
what's your dream?
My dream?
I want to start my own company,
gradually grow it,
and
develop a product
that everyone can use.
Get started then.
I support you.
What is this?
A bank card.
Starting a business is fine,
but why give this to me?
For the company.
I can't use your money for that.
Rationally,
you paid my rent for three years,
so I should repay you.
Romantically,
I don't want to say anything mushy.
You've only been working
for a short time.
Keep it for yourself.
It's not much,
all saved from working in Beijing
before grad school.
I can't accept it.
No way.
- Boss, boss, boss.
- I really can't.
Can I invest in your dream?
Take it, Boss Fang.
(Industrial and Commercial Bank of China)
Rose,
thank you.
I won't let you down.
Can you
teach me to swim?
Let's go.
Come on.
Especially the third floor.
It's been here for decades.
Can we rent just one floor?
It's all or nothing.
Cyan's website
hasn't been updated in years.
He made some web page demos.
I'll send you the link.
Take a look.
I don't have the budget.
Even if I did, I wouldn't outsource
to an individual.
No budget, it's free.
If you don't like it, forget it.
But I trust his skills.
I'll be his art consultant.
It'll work.
If it's free,
let's give it a try.
That chair is still crooked
even after being fixed.
Buy two new ones.
Our startup funds are limited.
We need to save where we can.
Right.
Hao,
send me the test results
from this afternoon.
I'll review them.
Okay.
You're back.
Why don't you turn on the lights?
It's bad for your eyes.
It's so dark already.
I've been testing a new version.
I might be busy for a while
and won't have time to cook.
It's a bit cold. I'll heat it up.
No need, it's fine.
It's fine.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Not at all.
Tired?
A bit,
but having you here
makes me feel secure.
Why?
Having you behind me
gives me a sense of security.
(From Bai Xiaohe)
Working overtime this week?
Want to go fishing together?
I steamed fish perfectly.
(From Bai Xiaohe)
Want to come and try?
Hello?
What's wrong?
Nothing, nothing much.
Just haven't called you for a while.
Found a job, right?
Didn't I tell you last week?
I've been working for a few days now.
Yes, at a publishing house.
What exactly do you do?
Do you have something to say or not?
No, I do. I have something to say.
Well.
How are things with Fang?
No arguments?
I'll hang up if there's nothing else.
Wait, wait.
I have something to tell you.
I saw Bai Xiaohe a few days ago.
Tell me.
What's going on?
Why did you come all the way here
for this on the weekend?
Stop babbling.
Su is my best friend.
I need to know what's going on.
You didn't tell her anything, right?
I came straight from the airport
to hear the truth from you.
Don't hide anything from me.
Xiaohe, come here.
Look.
After cleaning the fish,
lay ginger slices on it.
Once the water boils,
put it into steam.
Steam for about ten minutes,
and drizzle some oil before serving.
I thought living alone would make me
more self-sufficient.
But compared to you,
I see
that household skills
are really about talent.
Handling pots and pans
can't be harder than doing experiments.
Didn't you eat the fish you catch?
Sometimes I gave it to Professor Liang.
Mostly I released them.
Professor Liang?
How's he doing?
He's fine.
Still setting you up with guys?
Not like in my twenties.
His enthusiasm for matchmaking
has waned.
Do you still keep in touch with your ex?
No, we don't.
I'm single not because I can't move on,
but because I've moved on
and enjoy my freedom.
It's carefree
and quite relaxing.
I can see that.
You seem to be
very used to living alone.
Yes, I am.
I sleep whenever I want,
wake up whenever I want,
skip meals if I feel like it,
and don't bathe if I don't want to.
No one bothers me.
If you don't bathe for six months,
someone will complain.
Neighbors might report
that someone
is illegally making stinky tofu
in the building.
Almost done.
Look.
Now,
sprinkle cilantro and green onions.
Let it sit for a few seconds
for flavor.
There.
Take the fish out.
Be careful.
Pour the sauce made before
and hot oil
over it.
Try it.
Smells great.
Tastes good.
Good indeed.
I may not be as good at cooking as you,
but I think I'm quite handy.
I can handle
most small life issues,
except for a few unsolvable ones.
I enjoy being single.
What unsolvable issues?
Nothing.
Tell me.
Maybe I can help.
I love children.
I've always wanted them.
But...
What?
Do you want to help her have a baby?
What are you talking about?
It's a heartfelt issue.
Why make it sleazy?
Your girlfriend was not here,
so she invited you to go to her place,
cook, and discuss private matters.
She's crossed the line.
Is she sincere
or does she have an ulterior motive?
Doesn't she know you have a girlfriend?
I didn't tell her I have a girlfriend.
Don't mess around in the lab
to make a baby.
Sci-fi movies show
that scientists create many monsters.
Don't worry. I can't do that.
But the thought
of needing to date
and marry a man first to have a child
seems
troublesome.
I wonder
if I'll regret it in a few years,
or compromise
with reality.
Don't think about unsolvable things.
At least today, I'm happy.
You fished and talked with me
and taught me to cook.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, I forgot.
I have a video meeting scheduled.
I need to go.
Stay for dinner.
No, I'm late.
Work is important.
I won't keep you.
If you can't finish the fish,
put it in the fridge.
Reheat it in the microwave tomorrow.
I see steaming isn't that hard.
I'll try it in a few days.
When I get it right, I'll invite you over.
Okay.
I'm really late. I have to go.
Take care.
So, there was no chance.
Besides,
talking to a loner about this
feels like showing off.
Don't look at me like that.
I really didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything.
You didn't tell Bai Xiaohe
you have a girlfriend.
You didn't tell Su
you met Bai Xiaohe again.
I'm just dating her.
Do I have to report every detail
of who I see and what I do?
You should share the important things.
Well.
Did she tell you she bought a house?
I only found out
after she paid the deposit.
I feel like I'm not in her future plans.
I admit that going fishing
with Bai Xiaohe
was partly out of spite,
but I swear
I didn't think of anything else.
Su is different from us.
The house is her way of feeling secure.
I understand.
That's why I regret it.
I feel really guilty now.
If you miss the chance to apologize,
it will become a different issue.
So, let's not tell her about it.
I promise I won't see her again.
I'm telling you.
My flight is at 6 pm tomorrow.
Either you confess
before then,
or I'll expose you.
Fine, I'll confess tomorrow.
I'll confess tomorrow, okay?
Zhenhua,
are you doing well financially lately?
I knew
you wouldn't come all this way
just for this.
If you have extra money, lend me more.
If not, a little will do.
What happened?
It's not about your boyfriend, is it?
Spending money on a man is a big no-no.
It's for me.
Serious stuff.
I'll pay you back in installments
over six months.
Here's your IOU.
(Signature of borrower: Huang Yimei)
You even came prepared.
How much do you need?
How much do you have?
As much as I can spare?
Seems like confessing now is too late.
If you want to break up with me now,
I'd understand.
Hearing you say this,
I feel a complex mix of emotions.
Disappointment,
jealousy,
and a bit of anger.
I've never felt
such strong emotions for anyone.
A long time ago,
Rose asked me a question.
She asked
if there's a switch in the human brain
that controls emotions,
allowing you to start
or stop liking someone at will.
Back then, I couldn't answer it
because I didn't know.
Well,
now,
I can be sure.
Emotions
can't be turned off by sheer will.
Like
I know you saw the girl
you once liked behind my back.
Though it hurts,
I can't
stop liking you
because the switch is already on.
But relationships are mutual.
If one side feels uncomfortable,
they can choose to end it.
I don't want to break up
because I really like you a lot.
But this
is my wish,
my choice.
You can have yours too.
No need to choose.
I want to be with you.
I want to.
I'm sorry.
If you agree
that Bai Xiaohe is part of your past,
then I think
this can be
a milestone in our relationship.
Because it made me
see my feelings for you more clearly.
Thank you for the stone.
No, no.
The milestone.
This part is just...
- Let's finish this later.
- Take a break.
Here you are.
This is much better
and more comfortable.
Milk tea?
Thanks.
Sit down first. Come, come.
This is the homepage interface for Cyan.
Give me some feedback.
(Cyan Art Co., Ltd.)
These two pages are parallel, right?
The background color contrast
is too strong.
You'd better use the same template
and adjust the shades.
What do you think?
You're right.
I'll change it right away.
Here.
Thank you.
("Game Time" Children's Day Art Exhibition
Location: Yafeng Art Gallery)
(Curated by: Cyan Art Co., Ltd.
Partner: French Galant S. A.)
(Partner: French Galant S. A.)
Fang.
Later, the network department
checked the server logs.
Jason's account
logged in on the release day.
It was definitely him.
Why did he do it?
It's still unclear.
Some say they saw
a scratched CD in his trash,
suspecting he accidentally scratched it
and then burned a new one,
mixing them up.
Others say
he did it on purpose
because Mr. Shao values Fang
and Jason feared
Fang would take his place.
None of that matters anymore.
Actually,
I should thank him.
If I hadn't taken the blame,
I wouldn't have left the high-paying job
at the big company.
A blessing in disguise.
Follow him
and he'll make sure we live well.
Stop that.
Fang,
I know
Jason originally wanted me to leave.
It wasn't your fault.
In the company,
my happiest moments
were working with you.
The new leader
isn't doing much good either.
Lately, it's been all meetings.
Now I spend more time
writing reports than coding.
At least the salary is high.
Fang,
is there anything
I can help with here?
Well...
You're the boss.
I'm okay with it.
But I can't
offer a high salary.
No problem.
What matters is working with you.
I... I really...
Why don't you
come over and try?
Thank you, Fang.
Thank you, Miss Yimei.
Thank you, Hao.
I will definitely work hard.
Here's a toast to everyone.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, cheers.
Alright, I can rest easy
knowing you've forgiven him.
Maybe it's because I've seen
the ugliness of human nature.
Your brother's minor flaws
are acceptable.
My brother is so lucky
to find such a generous girlfriend
like you.
If I can't stand
a grain of sand in my eye,
I might as well just keep them shut.
Okay, I've got work. Gotta go.
Yimei.
I've finished the book
you borrowed me last time.
Okay.
This is for you.
I'm too lazy to wrap it.
Anyway, you don't care
about appearances.
I don't know how to fish.
Why give me a fishing rod?
I can teach you.
You want me to show off
in front of Bai Xiaohe?
No need to do that.
Your banner has already been planted
on my city gate tower.
I told her
I have a girlfriend now.
Last time you said
fishing is my personal space.
You won't interfere.
But there's no need to avoid it, right?
You said I can fish with anyone I like.
Then
I want to fish with you.
And this fishing rod.
You can use it to fish,
or even hit me with it
when you're upset.
Is fishing fun?
You have to try it.
You might get hooked after just one try.
Even if you don't like it,
when I'm fishing,
you can enjoy the sun and read a book.
Just don't disturb the fish
when they're biting.
Alright then.
I'll accept this gift.
Thank you.
You're the one who's got a gift.
Why am I happier than you?
(2007/Spring, Gulou)
You can get off at the door.
I'm coming out.
Your son is back.
Yeah.
You have luggage.
Come on.
No need. Let me.
Come on, give it to me.
Give it to me.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- No problem.
- Let's go.
- You're back.
- He's back.
Ms. Yuan.
- You're back.
- He's back.
- Uncle Jia.
- Here, here.
Come on.
Give it to me.
You must be thirsty.
Same as always.
Nothing's changed at all.
(Galaxy Cup, Outstanding Work Award)
(First Prize)
(Outstanding Novel Award)
From last year.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Have you grown taller?
Look.
Dad, I'm over thirty.
How can I get taller?
That's just me being silly.
Let's eat.
I've prepared everything. Let's go.
Come help me bring it over.
Dad, your kitchen cabinet
is about to fall off.
This house has been lived in
for many years.
It's time to renovate.
Renovate what?
I'm used to living alone.
Exactly because you live alone,
you need to tidy up properly.
All these old and broken things
are safety hazards.
I'll pay for it.
It's not about money.
This is public housing.
We don't have property rights.
Who knows when it'll be demolished?
No need to renovate.
Try this.
I'll fix the cabinet for you later.
- Try the lamb.
- Thank you.
Wait. Let's have a drink first.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Is it tasty?
Delicious.
Is it just you now?
Who else could there be?
Try the fish.
No one comes to see you?
Sometimes editors and reporters
come looking for me.
But I always arrange
to meet them outside.
During festivals and holidays,
no one comes to visit you?
You're asking about Rose, aren't you?
During Chinese New Year three years ago,
we talked on the phone.
I wanted to help
make peace between you two,
but she didn't respond.
Since then,
we've been in touch.
During holidays,
she sends me a text message
to wish me well.
Polite and formal.
When I won an award back then,
she called to congratulate me.
Suddenly,
things weren't so formal anymore.
I asked, and sure enough,
she has a boyfriend now.
Dad, where's your phone?
Let me see your messages.
She's put the past behind her.
Let me see it.
Where's your phone?
You're in your thirties now.
I won't rush you about marriage.
As for your feelings,
(Huang Yimei)
you can't keep floating like this.
(Uncle Zhuang: May every day of the new year
be bathed in the sunshine of happiness.)
(Uncle Zhuang:
May you be safe, healthy, happy, and joyful.)
After I fix the cabinet doors,
I'll head back to the hotel.
(Huang Yimei)
(May you have a prosperous new year.)
Aren't you going back to your place?
I'll need to tidy up there.
Staying at a hotel is more convenient.
Besides, I can't stay long
in Beijing this time.
I'll be visiting several cities on this trip.
Where are you going?
Stop asking.
Will you go to Shanghai?
Don't go looking for her.
It's been many years.
She's moved on with her life.
Don't disturb her.
Come on.
- Take a look.
- How's this? Look good?
The tie is a bit off.
Doesn't it match?
Well.
Isn't this too flashy?
Try this one?
Who are you meeting today,
a female client?
Manager of Lanxing's
After-sales Department.
They want
to develop a customer service system.
If I can secure this project,
I could earn at least this much this year.
If it goes through,
I might need to hire two more people.
Right now, the three of us
handle both sales and development.
We can manage small projects,
but big clients
all have dedicated customer service.
Good luck with that.
I'll design recruitment ads for you.
Really?
Alright.
Good eye.
It's a male.
The client is male.
(Manager's Office)
Tina, you wanted to see me?
Ms. Su.
Hello.
Eric is currently
the Operations Director
at Galant's French headquarters.
He has a project
and wants to collaborate with us.
You'll be in charge.
Alright, Mr. Zhuang.
Let's discuss it in the reception room.
I need to review the documents again.
I'll prepare a budget
and risk assessment report
to submit to the headquarters.
I'll need their feedback first.
I'll give you an answer
about whether we can cooperate
next week.
I really want to cooperate with Cyan.
If you think
something's wrong with our terms,
we can always negotiate.
Sure. I'll tell you next week.
Ms. Su,
I have something else to ask you.
Rose has left our company.
She resigned four or five years ago.
She has no ties to our company.
But you're her best friend.
You've been gone so long.
Why bring her up now?
Because you've made it big
and found success?
I understand you want
to protect your friend.
She was the one
who initiated the breakup
and blocked me.
Even if I wanted to reconcile,
I wouldn't have had the chance.
If you wanted to reconcile,
you'd always had the chance.
It was just about a plane ticket.
Back then, it wasn't.
It was about my job and future.
I couldn't risk it.
What do you want to know?
If I go to her now,
what would she think?
I want to hear your opinion.
I don't know.
After all, I'm not her.
Does she still hate me?
She's never hated you.
Hatred only complicates things.
She doesn't want
to be entangled with you.
Though I'm her friend,
I believe
in matters of work and love,
when you can only choose one,
either choice is understandable.
You weren't wrong.
But since you've made your choice,
don't expect
to have both fish and bear paws.
That's exactly what I think.
Almost done.
Alright, I'll head over first.
Both plans are viable.
One is high-risk with high returns,
and the other is safer
but with less profit.
If you were the manager,
which would you choose?
The first one.
Our fiscal year starts in March,
and this project
is the highlight of the year.
Even if it exceeds the budget,
we still have a chance to recover
in the second half of the year.
Then proceed with that.
If there are any issues,
you can communicate
with the headquarters.
I'm resigning.
I recommended you to the headquarters
to take over my position.
Tina.
It's personal reasons.
Last month, you asked me to find buyers
for your two paintings.
Are you short on money?
If you were going solo,
you'd surely ask if I wanted to join you.
So,
what difficulties are you facing?
It's not me.
It's Gu.
He's ill,
alone in Hong Kong, China,
with not much time left.
I plan to go there to accompany him.
But the company's headquarters
are in Hong Kong, China.
You could apply for a transfer.
I don't want others and other things
to disturb us.
I just want
to focus on accompanying him.
I still have two paintings there.
If I need money later,
sell them for me.
Isn't Gu wealthy?
His parents are still alive,
and he has an ex-wife and a daughter.
If I go now, everyone will think
I'm going after his inheritance.
We're divorced.
His money has nothing to do with me.
Gu is the most important person to me.
I just want to accompany him
through this final journey in peace.
Alright.
Leave the company to me.
You go ahead.
I'm capable of taking over from you.
Every time you get a promotion and raise,
there's always someone
saying I favor you.
But they don't know
that in hiring,
what I value most
is confidence and courage.
Only those brave enough
to take responsibility
are qualified to make demands of me.
That's why you
valued Huang Yimei back then.
Eric's here this time
for Huang Yimei, right?
Judging by his demeanor,
he'll probably go see her.
I was just thinking.
Should I give her a call to remind her?
She's not suited
for calm and quiet days.
Even if she doesn't want to,
there will be troublemakers.
You can remind her once,
but you can't keep
reminding her every time.
Let her face it herself.
After all, she's Huang Yimei.
♪Rain♪
♪Falls on my forehead♪
♪The wind fills my sleeves♪
♪I pass through intersections♪
♪Changing trains♪
♪Stopping at each station♪
♪Encounters in the bustling streets♪
♪Freedom in farewells♪
♪May I accompany myself♪
♪Throughout this life's journey♪
♪Loving someone is the best♪
♪But not obligatory♪
♪As long as the wind blows♪
♪Good luck is on the way♪
♪Happiness should come from within♪
♪No need for anyone else♪
♪Watching the sunset along the way♪
♪Like flowers sent from afar♪
♪Rainy or sunny, keep moving forward♪
♪I want to move forward♪
♪So let go of my hand♪
♪The road can be run on♪
♪It can also be danced on♪
♪The crossroads I want to go to♪
♪Are beyond where you stand♪
♪No regrets left behind♪
♪May I keep moving forward♪
♪Whether rainy or sunny♪
♪Empty-handed along the way♪
♪Only needing health♪
♪Happiness♪
♪and a free spirit♪
♪Like a bird in flight♪
♪Born♪
♪With the entire♪
♪Sky♪