=The Tale of Rose=
=Episode 24=
By the way, Dad, Mom,
how about
I drive you around tomorrow?
You can see the new house I bought.
There are sample rooms.
No need.
The house is for you to live in.
As long as you two like it, it's fine.
Yes.
It's also close to my company.
You can visit my office.
Next time.
Rose hasn't been home for a year.
We want to stay
and spend time with her.
This smells amazing.
Smell it.
- Smells good, right?
- Yes, it smells great.
You've cooked so much.
We won't finish it all.
Won't it go to waste?
No, whatever we can't finish
goes in the fridge.
We can reheat it whenever we want.
Mom, the fridge is only this big.
A few meals and it's gone.
That's because you don't cook.
How about
I take turns with your mother-in-law?
Let her go back home and rest.
I can stay here and cook.
- That'll work.
- Good.
What now?
Come on.
What are they doing?
Are they trying to send me away?
Isn't that perfect?
Haven't you been wanting
to go back home?
Did I really want to leave?
I'm doing it for you!
Oh my.
Son, you're so naive.
You won't even realize
when you're screwed.
Mom, aren't you overthinking this?
Overthinking?
Since you got married,
they never came over.
Now they hear about a new house,
so they rush over.
Why?
The money for the house is yours.
Why should their family live in it?
Mom,
let me tell you.
After marriage,
earnings are shared property.
They said
the house is for us to live in.
They don't care about that.
They just say it nicely.
University professors.
We can't outsmart them.
Son,
I'm talking to you.
Don't tell your wife how much you make.
Got it.
I thought she didn't know how to laugh.
I've lived here so long
and never seen her laugh.
Now her parents are here,
and she's all laughs.
Her parents are here, so she's happy.
What's wrong with that?
Why do you have
to comment on everything?
I didn't say anything.
Where are you going?
Always siding with your wife.
Dad.
- Good.
- Let me toast to you.
This is delicious.
How is it? Still like the food?
Yes.
- It's very tasty.
- Delicious.
The stir-fried celery is really good.
- Delicious, right?
- Yes, delicious.
Son, have some meat.
- Here.
- Eat, eat, eat.
How is it?
It's good.
Fang,
how's work lately?
The Development Department
has grown to six employees this year.
I'm planning
to hire two more testers.
The office is almost full.
I'm looking for a new place.
I plan to move to the Xuhui District.
Isn't the rent there expensive?
Yes, it's much higher than before.
But the environment is good.
It can improve the company's image.
You should stay within your means.
Appearance is important,
but it's not your core strength.
Eat more.
Don't you love bamboo shoots?
Yes, I have them.
- Dad, I have them.
- Oh, you do.
Good.
Son, don't just talk.
Here. Eat some food.
Eat more. You've worked hard all day.
- Eat some.
- We made this especially for you.
I'll try some.
Rose seems different.
Like she has a lot on her mind.
She was carefree since she was little.
Now she's
full of worries.
She told me
she wants to return to Beijing with us.
Is she not doing well here?
It shouldn't be.
Fang and his mother treat her well.
We'll observe for a few days.
If she's really unhappy,
we'll take her back to Beijing.
Is that appropriate?
(From Mom: We've checked into the hotel.
Everything's fine.)
Have your parents
checked into the hotel?
(From Mom: Do you have enough money?)
(No need, I have money.)
(From Mom: It's not for you.
It's for my grandchild.)
(You'll need more money
being pregnant now.)
Didn't you see them today?
Didn't talk enough?
I'm asking if they'll have breakfast
at the hotel or wait for me.
Do you think they came suddenly
because they're worried about you
or don't trust me?
No, they just missed me,
so they came to see me.
They came straight here
from the train station.
Is it to check on me?
See how I'm doing?
Didn't my dad tell you?
He put the luggage here
to save the trouble from moving them.
Did you not tell them everything?
You didn't say you quit
and didn't mention my mom being here.
How could I say it?
If I did, they'd think
I can't take care of myself.
Is it that serious?
Besides, it wasn't my idea to quit.
What do you mean?
Is that my fault?
After you quit your job
and my mom came,
you're much better now, right?
My mom cares for you all day
and still gets blamed.
When did I ever blame her?
You're always out.
Isn't it because you find her annoying?
She watches me like a hawk.
I just want some fresh air.
Fine.
All in all,
no matter what we do,
it's never right for you.
My mom takes care of you every day,
and you never smile at her.
Your parents came,
and you're all smiles.
When my mom saw that,
how would she feel?
It's been so long since I saw them.
I can't cry.
I can't smile.
That's not what I meant.
Of course, I'm happy
your parents are here.
I wanted to take them
to see the new house,
but they didn't appreciate it at all.
I don't know
what I should do
to earn their respect.
They don't look down on you.
They just don't want to bother you.
Last time we had a fight
with the roast duck.
Today I called you out to exercise,
just to blow off some steam.
Why exercise to blow off steam?
We middle-aged men
don't have that kind of fire
that can't be extinguished
with chrysanthemum tea.
It's been fine for a while.
How's work going for you?
Our boss got into trouble recently,
and I've figured out a lot of things.
You can't live too comfortably.
If you don't find trouble for yourself,
the heavens will find it for you.
What trouble have you
found for yourself?
There's someone
who wants me to design
a homestay hotel.
That's a good opportunity.
It is a good opportunity,
but this project is too big in scale.
It has to be business to business.
If I agree to it,
I'll have to quit my job
and start my own company.
Haven't you been wanting
to start your own business?
Now, there's a project,
an opportunity, and the motivation.
It's a great thing.
The opportunity is indeed good,
but something's off with the person
offering the opportunity.
Who is it?
This person
is Bai Xiaohe's father.
I didn't think it through.
I'll turn him down.
Though this has nothing to do
with Bai Xiaohe,
after all,
he's her biological father.
Owing him such a huge favor
makes it awkward for me,
let alone you.
Accept it.
I support you.
I'll come home early after work tonight,
and take your parents
to the Fairmont Peace Hotel
for dinner tonight.
It's far and expensive.
Why go there?
They came all the way here.
We should show them some hospitality.
I'll keep them company
and show them around,
and we'll just eat casually.
Yesterday they arrived
and rushed to cook.
If we don't treat them to a meal,
we'll seem impolite.
They're family,
not guests.
Let's discuss something.
What is it?
Your mother has been taking care
of me for quite a while.
Could my mom come over
and stay with me for a while?
Your mom wouldn't be used to it.
What do you mean?
Your mom's stay here
would be inconvenient.
I mean it'll be inconvenient for me.
Look.
I'm more casual at home.
I'll just throw on shorts
or go shirtless in the summer.
If your mom were here...
Right?
Come on.
Why are you always like this?
One idea today,
and another tomorrow.
So,
since your parents are here,
you want to drive my mom away, right?
I'm discussing it with you.
Your family
always does whatever they like,
letting things go.
So can I go back to Beijing
for a few days?
Do you really not mind?
If you got this project
because of connections, I would mind,
but if it's because of your abilities,
I don't mind.
Does that mean
you believe in my abilities now?
I don't know much about your industry,
but I've read online about your work,
and your reputation seems good.
You...
Are you talking about
separating from me?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I didn't say that.
I just wanted to go back to Beijing
for a few days.
You know I'm busy right now
and can't make time.
Why do you have to go back now?
Didn't you say
we could stay in Beijing or Shanghai
if I wanted to?
Remember.
You are
part of my family now.
You can't always think of yourself.
What did you use to say to me?
You said after we got married,
I wouldn't leave my old home,
but you would give me another one.
Now you say I'm part of your family.
What do you mean?
Isn't that right?
You married me.
You're pregnant with my child,
so I should take responsibility for you.
What's wrong with that?
Taking responsibility means
arranging my life
and restricting my freedom.
Fang Xiewen,
how did you become like this?
No, Huang Yimei, it's you who's changed.
No matter what I do,
I can never meet your expectations.
I can't be compared with others.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have let you meet him.
Since then, you've been paranoid.
I'm not.
Then why don't you let me go to work?
Why do you control my freedom?
Even when I bought some flowers,
you sneakily asked me about it for ages.
And why did you buy such a big house,
putting so much pressure on yourself?
Isn't it just to compete with him?
I didn't.
I didn't want to compete with him.
I bought the big house
entirely to make you comfortable.
What do you mean
by the pigeonhole in Paris?
Why do you insist on going to Beijing?
Who exactly is in Beijing?
During this period,
I can clearly sense this
restless and anxious mood in you.
Of course, part of it is because of me,
and another part
is due to the issues at work.
Especially being implicated by those
unscrupulous individuals.
After our leader's incident,
the project I worked on
for two years was halted.
It's particularly frustrating.
I understand
your enthusiasm for work.
If I ask you to let go
of such a great opportunity
because of Bai Xiaohe,
am I being too narrow-minded?
Su,
I've noticed you've changed
and become softer.
Who let you down?
Go back up.
Quickly.
I'm saying such affectionate words.
What's the matter with you?
I used to be calmer
and less willing to take risks.
But now,
I'm willing to take a risk with you.
But what if my startup fails
and I lose our footing?
I'll support you.
With Mr. Bai's vision and capability,
since he chose you for this project,
I'm definitely going
to invest alongside.
Learning investment
from successful people
certainly increases success rates.
Why do I feel so energetic today?
Then add some resistance.
Sure.
Challenge accepted.
Good for you.
There's endless energy.
Then maintain this pace.
Keep it up for a minute.
Son.
Going to work.
Eat something.
Don't go on an empty stomach.
Can't go like this.
Hurry, eat something.
What's wrong?
Is she going back to Beijing?
No, just something she said.
If she wants to go back, let her,
so she won't be moody here every day.
Wherever she goes,
the child in her belly
is still ours, right?
I won't let her go.
I'm also uncomfortable here.
I want to go back to our hometown.
Every month in the future,
I'll give you an extra 5,000.
Come on.
Here is just so small.
Why did you buy it?
Wasn't it good
running around outside before?
This is my gift to you.
Well,
I'm going to the north of Jiangsu
these days
for Zhou Shihui.
I'll be gone for a few days.
During my absence,
you can use it to run.
Otherwise, you'd go out
for a night run alone,
and I'd be worried.
I happen to have a gift for you too.
I have a gift too?
Are you saying I can
freely come and go from this house now?
Rightfully.
This gift is too precious.
With yours and mine,
plus my parents',
I can live in three places.
If I move in,
won't my house be empty?
Should I quit my place?
No, no, no.
Keep yours for now.
If I ever find you annoying one day,
you can find another place to go.
If you find me annoying one day,
you can find a place
to take shelter too.
That's right.
Every month during your period,
I can hide in my place.
Last month was...
Next week it's your period again.
- I have to hide for a while.
- What are you talking about?
Get away from me.
So annoying.
Is that about it?
It'll be ready soon.
Come in.
Mr. Fang, we have a few issues
with the contract with Lingfeng.
Tell me.
First, their payment cycle is too long,
which is not favorable
for our cash flow.
Secondly, the final payment
of the contract
needs to wait
until the system goes online
one year later,
which is also unreasonable.
I understand.
You can leave now.
Okay.
(To Honey)
(Sorry.)
(I shouldn't have argued with you this morning.
What do you want to eat tonight?)
(Send)
(Route 53)
(Sorry, I shouldn't have argued with you
this morning. What do you want to eat tonight?)
Hello?
Hello, Su.
It kicked me.
Who?
The baby.
The baby kicked me.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to see my parents.
I'm on the bus.
It kicked me.
What does it feel like?
It's quite amazing.
I've heard the fetal heartbeat
at the hospital,
but
I've never felt him move.
Gave you a fright, didn't it?
My goodness.
He's really a living person.
This is real.
You'll feel it more often.
I shouldn't have argued
with Fang Xiewen.
The baby must have heard it.
The baby's upset.
Did you guys argue?
Why?
It doesn't matter.
Suddenly, nothing seems to matter now.
It kicked me.
Su,
do you think I've become tacky,
become a woman who only talks
about children all the time?
No.
You've become an ordinary woman.
I feel
it's especially wonderful.
Fang,
why haven't you left yet?
Zhou,
do you have plans tonight?
Fang,
it's warmed up a bit.
Don't just drink, okay?
Have some dishes. Here.
Have a shrimp.
It's quite hot.
- Have a shrimp?
- No.
Fang,
I thought you didn't drink.
It's rare you're in the mood today.
Fang.
Let me say a few words.
Fang,
over these years
at the company,
you've helped me,
mentored me,
and given me opportunities.
I've never properly
thanked you.
Today,
I'll also have a drink
and toast to you.
Cheers, Zhou.
Thanks, Fang.
I know.
They all find me troublesome.
Tell me.
What am I doing it for?
What for?
Every matter I must oversee personally.
I must worry about everything
because
this is my own company.
You're the boss.
You naturally have the right
to oversee, Fang.
Let me tell you.
I'm very good
at reading people.
When you joined me back then,
you had just graduated
with no experience,
but at a glance,
I knew you had potential.
You were eager to learn and worked hard.
Look.
I entrusted you with the QA Department.
See?
How well have you done?
Fang,
I definitely won't embarrass you.
I won't.
Lin Hao
is bad at judging people.
He always wants to hire returnees
to boost our company's image.
That won't work.
Fang,
this is how I see it.
Our company now
actually has quite a few foreign clients.
Being able
to speak English well, and fluently
is useful for this kind of sales.
Really.
Isn't it just a few years abroad?
They were all within
the Chinese community.
To be blunt,
their English might
not be better than mine.
Fang,
don't drink anymore.
If you continue,
Miss Yimei will scold you.
By then, you... Don't.
Let her scold me then.
Anyway, she looks down on me.
Why do you talk like this, Fang?
Miss Yimei is so nice to you.
Zhou,
do you know
someone who's eaten French cuisine
can also eat street food?
Not because they love to eat,
but because they can eat.
Fang,
I haven't seen you eat street food much.
Liking to eat and being able to eat
are two different things.
Did you drink?
Rose,
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to go
because I'm afraid
you might not come back.
I'm afraid of losing you.
I was anxious for a moment
and said something harsh.
Don't be angry, okay?
I felt really upset,
so I had a few drinks.
I'm sorry.
Let's never
argue again,
okay?
Whoever you want to take care of you,
let them.
I won't stop you anymore.
Just don't go.
Just don't leave me,
okay?
It kicked me today.
These are all new today.
Do you want a bunch?
No.
Here, here.
Give me your bag.
You've bought a car.
A second-hand one.
Get in the car.
A child seat.
When? A boy or a girl?
A boy. He's two years old.
Then I have to give a big red envelope.
Looks like I came for nothing this time.
(Beipu Station)
Come on.
Have you thought it through?
Are you going to Beijing
and leave the child here?
I have to earn money, Zhenhua.
My wife and I
are both locals.
Both sets of parents can help
look after the child.
You've seen it yourself.
This place is tiny.
Even if everything's
torn down and rebuilt,
it still can't compare to Beijing's CBD.
Small place but stable.
No matter what, you'll make money.
Yuan Zheng and I
are leaving the Institute
to take huge risks.
We've either become millionaires
or down-and-out poor.
Zhenhua,
no need to say more.
I'm with you.
Come on.
There's an ugly truth I have to say now.
I know.
Don't go looking for Rose.
She's doing well now,
isn't she?
Yes.
I'm about to become an uncle.
(Outpatient Department, Huashan Hospital,
Fudan University)
Rose, it'll be okay.
Don't worry.
We're all here, Rose.
Don't be scared.
You'll be giving birth soon.
(Delivery Room)
We're waiting outside for you.
Go for it.
Take deep breaths.
Push slowly.
Listen to me.
Deep breaths.
Then push downwards.
This will be very smooth.
Don't be nervous.
Relax.
Mom?
You're at the hospital?
Yes.
Rose has been taken
to the delivery room.
She's in the delivery room?
Wasn't her due date next week?
As long as it's full term,
she could give birth at any time.
It's your fault. We should have gone
to Shanghai earlier.
Okay, okay. It's my fault.
Mom, don't worry.
Both Su and I are here.
When everything's arranged here,
we'll book your tickets
so you can come.
I'll give you a call after this.
Alright, alright.
We'll leave it to you and Su.
Sure.
Your mom must be worried.
Yes. This is so sudden.
Who would have known?
Have you decided?
Do you want an epidural or not?
What's the situation now?
Hurry up and decide.
Stop dilly-dallying.
The anesthesia goes into the spine,
not into the uterus.
It won't affect the child.
You're a graduate student.
Don't you even know
this common knowledge?
No, no, no.
Don't be in such a hurry.
Women have to endure pain
when giving birth.
There's no need for anesthesia.
It's not good for the child,
absolutely not.
It's my sister who's in pain.
I'll pay for the epidural. Quickly!
Come here and sign. Hurry up and sign.
No, what are you doing?
- Don't rush like that.
- Please keep quiet.
This is the operating room.
Will you sign or not?
If you don't sign, I'll tell the nurse
the child's father was killed
in a car accident on his way here.
I'll sign as the uncle.
Why are you speaking so harshly?
Are you cursing my son?
- This is too much.
- Hesitate for one more minute,
and she'll have to endure
another minute of pain.
What? Don't rush.
- I'll sign.
- This...
We have to think it through
before we sign.
What's this?
Who hasn't given birth?
What's wrong with pain?
Things are different now.
Different how?
Who hasn't given birth?
My niece.
I'm an uncle now.
Such a big fuss,
and it turns out to be a girl.
I'm an uncle now.
Hug her.
So adorable.
Look how pretty our little girl is.
No scars, right?
None.
Absolutely none?
Absolutely. I told you earlier.
Come.
Uncle will bless you
with all his lifelong skills,
guaranteeing you get into Tsinghua.
Look, her eyes are open.
Did she just open her eyes?
She received the blessings.
Baby.
(My dear daughter,)
(today marks our first farewell.)
(You bid farewell to my body,)
(hastening to arrive in this world.)
(From now on,)
(I can no longer
protect you with my body,)
(and separate you from this world.)
(Just thinking about this)
(makes me feel
incredibly lost and worried.)
(Compared to this loss and worry,)
(all the pain in childbirth is trivial.)
(I am your mother,)
(but what I can and cannot do)
(is extremely limited,)
(yet you have given me so much.)
(The fact that you exist)
(makes me happy.)
(The world is vast.)
(One can hardly know
a fraction in a lifetime.)
(My dear,)
(I chose to bring you into this world)
(because I truly believe)
(no matter if it's joy or pain,)
(it's worth experiencing in life.)
♪We find our way♪
♪Stars above♪
♪They guide the play♪
♪No matter what♪
♪We'll rise above♪
♪Shine brighter♪
♪Like the morning sun♪
♪Through every battle♪
♪We'll overcome♪
♪In our hearts♪
♪The fire will ignite♪
Just drank 150 milliliters
of milk powder,
and now sleeping again.
This little one can eat and sleep well.
She'll definitely grow up big.
Here.
I asked the master to do this.
Pick one.
♪Wearing our crown♪
Fang Zining.
Fang Ruofan.
Fang Taichu.
Fang Taichu?
♪We will break the chains♪
This name sounds grand and imposing.
♪Forever♪
Taichu.
Indeed, it's grand.
It's also special.
Taichu.
Mom.
Mom, keep it down.
The baby just fell asleep.
Leave it there. Let me do it.
No need. It's quite tiring.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
Every day, there is
pork trotter soup and crucian carp.
She drinks so much soup,
but she does not have much milk.
How much does a can of milk powder cost?
That's just a girl.
You don't need to raise her so lavishly.
That's my daughter.
Of course, I have to raise her lavishly.
♪Rain♪
♪Falls on my forehead♪
♪The wind fills my sleeves♪
♪I pass through intersections♪
♪Changing trains♪
♪Stopping at each station♪
♪Encounters in the bustling streets♪
♪Freedom in farewells♪
♪May I accompany myself♪
♪Throughout this life's journey♪
♪Loving someone is the best♪
♪But not obligatory♪
♪As long as the wind blows♪
♪Good luck is on the way♪
♪Happiness should come from within♪
♪No need for anyone else♪
♪Watching the sunset along the way♪
♪Like flowers sent from afar♪
♪Rainy or sunny, keep moving forward♪
♪I want to move forward♪
♪So let go of my hand♪
♪The road can be run on♪
♪It can also be danced on♪
♪The crossroads I want to go to♪
♪Are beyond where you stand♪
♪No regrets left behind♪
♪May I keep moving forward♪
♪Whether rainy or sunny♪
♪Empty-handed along the way♪
♪Only needing health♪
♪Happiness♪
♪and a free spirit♪
♪Like a bird in flight♪
♪Born♪
♪With the entire♪
♪Sky♪