=The Tale of Rose=
=Episode 11=
Do I have to report to you every detail
of what I do
and who I meet every day?
Even if it's not overtime,
do I not have the right to have a drink?
Do you want to control everything like my mom?
I'm not trying to control you.
There's a six-hour time difference between us.
We have to catch each other
at the right time to talk.
If you're not saying anything,
what else is there to talk about?
I really don't have the energy
to argue with you.
(Video connecting)
♪It comes raining♪
♪Is your love in pain♪
♪Or I'm getting touched tonight♪
(To Zhuang Guodong:
Let's stop for now. Rest early.)
(From Huang Yimei:
♪Sure I got the answer♪
♪From your meditation♪
♪Ours is not a love in vain♪
♪However, it's raining♪
♪Yes, yearning were always♪
♪Mingled the night♪
♪You were always on my mind♪
♪Like the stars, lighting in the heart♪
(To Huang Yimei:
I can't. I promised you.)
(Problems must be solved immediately.)
♪Is your heart tearing♪
(From Zhuang Guodong:
I can't. I promised you)
(Problems must be solved immediately.)
♪Ours is not a love in vain♪
♪However, it's raining♪
(Video connecting)
♪Mingled the night♪
(From Zhuang Guodong:
I know you're there. Answer it.)
♪Like the stars, lighting in the heart♪
♪It comes raining♪
(Video chat)
Sorry,
Rose.
I work every day.
Overtime, training,
and socializing.
I'm really exhausted.
Sorry for losing control earlier.
You don't know
how much I miss you every day.
The thought of you
motivates me to get up every day.
I wish you were by my side
when I open my eyes.
I want to hold you in my arms
and hug you tightly.
Please don't be mad, okay?
I'm sorry.
Coach, good evening.
So formal.
I think we should run near a hospital.
(Architectural Design Institute)
In case something happens to me,
we'd be close to the ICU.
Like this, right?
Yes.
Warm-up.
Huang.
Take a rain check?
No.
Well.
Sorry, I'll schedule another day with you.
Uncle Bai,
sorry I didn't accompany you to Guangxi.
I should have told you in person.
It's fine. I know.
It was Xiaohe who didn't let you go.
Don't cover for her.
Then you should know,
Xiaohe and I already broke up.
It's all Xiaohe's fault.
She hurt you,
I apologize on her behalf.
Please don't say that.
Xiaohe didn't lie to me. I'm grateful to her.
I wonder how she's doing recently.
Xiaohe told us
she broke up with you.
Her mom had a big fight with her.
Then she went back
to live at school
and hasn't come home since.
Not even answering our calls.
I shouldn't meddle in your relationship,
And now,
I have no right to ask you
for anything regarding Xiaohe.
But
we are really worried about her.
Huang,
you live at school,
Could you check on her for us?
She's our only daughter.
As long as she's safe and healthy,
we won't oppose
whatever she does in the future.
Okay, Uncle Bai, I'll check on her.
Thank you, Huang.
You're welcome.
If only my daughter
had met you first.
Have you heard of Hu Kejia?
She's a nine-year-old girl
with autism.
I've seen her work.
She's incredibly talented.
Her parents
are planning a charity sale of her works.
All proceeds
will be donated to autism charities.
Who is interested in this project?
Huang Yimei?
I don't really want it.
What are we eating tonight?
Huang Yimei, are you out of your mind?
Tina gave you this project
in front of everyone.
Do you not understand
what that means?
I know, but I have other plans.
Who can assign you work besides the boss?
I'm going to France
to see Eric.
To you, is a man more important
than work?
You just curated an exhibition.
Don't think
you've secured this job.
But he needs me now.
Do you think Tina will approve your leave
because of it?
Will she?
(Application for Leave: Visit my boyfriend)
I'll follow up on the contract this week.
The design for the brochure
has also been confirmed.
We can place the prepayment order this week.
I'll need you to confirm it.
Before my vacation,
I'll get all the work arranged.
So, I have no choice
but to approve your leave.
If there's no other way,
then
there's no other option.
(Resignation Letter)
Now you're threatening me?
I've already arranged my schedule.
Sacrificing work
for a few days of romance.
Is it worth it?
Yes, it's worth it.
You're so unambitious,
without career planning at all.
Is love your only goal?
For now, yes.
As long as I love him, he comes first.
And I don't think this is inferior to others.
(Application for Leave)
Thank you.
Based on your performance,
this takes effect at any time.
Mr. Martin, nice to meet you.
Ma'am, nice to meet you.
You may enter the palace.
Thank you. Do you smoke?
No, thank you.
How about a cup of tea?
I'd love to.
I love freedom.
We're going on a trip.
Rose,
I wish you were by my side
when I open my eyes.
I want to hold you in my arms
and hug you tightly.
That's enough.
Eight laps for a starter.
How do you feel?
Have you vented your emotions?
How did you know?
The person who came last time
seemed like an elder,
but
from your attitude towards him,
it wasn't like family familiarity,
nor like courteousness to a boss.
Also
you both seemed sensitive
about having a woman around.
You didn't dare to tell him
I was your friend.
It's not that I didn't dare.
After that night, you disappeared for two days.
No messages from you.
I figured
either he gave you
a huge task,
or his appearance affected your emotions.
So this person
came because of your ex-girlfriend.
One look and you understood everything.
Seems palace dramas aren't entirely made up.
- Here's some water.
- Thanks.
Here.
What excuse should I use to reject him?
You can't reject him.
You would've rejected him at the time
if you wanted to do it.
The reason you're still torn
is because you haven't let her go.
You still want to see her.
I've let go.
When it comes to stubbornness,
women are nothing
compared to men.
Don't struggle anymore.
Go and see her.
When I first met you,
I thought you were very cold.
I didn't expect
you to be both perceptive and sensitive.
I'm a realist.
If the time and effort
spent on something
exceed its value,
either do it immediately,
or don't do it at all.
I can't stand
seeing a grown man
hesitating
over something so minor.
That's the Coach I know.
Feels good to be scolded.
Feels great.
I need to make up for the past two days.
I'll run two more laps.
Look, I've gained a lot.
I found a coach and a confidant.
Run more laps.
Come on.
(China Customs)
♪What should I do to make it last♪
♪Can you taste sweetness in the rain♪
♪Once again twilight takes me home♪
♪Dance in the starlight♪
♪Shimmering light falls in my eyes♪
♪Within my heart, a flame ignites♪
♪Question the silence of the sun♪
♪Paint the night♪
♪In a trance♪
♪Our love's a puzzle♪
♪Never before I found myself alive♪
♪Words untold♪
♪Hearts unfold♪
♪Now the sign is so clear♪
♪A petal tells me how to shine♪
I thought you Chinese were good at math.
It was my oversight. I'll fix it right away.
We're about to sign the contract,
and I just realized the amount is wrong.
I heard you're working overtime every day.
What have you been doing?
Just making international calls at the office?
Eric is on my team.
This is my responsibility.
The contract will be signed on time.
I guarantee it.
Eric, you're in my team,
and this is my responsibility.
You won't be having a second way out.
I know you're working very hard,
but don't let that
get in the way of your job.
Alright?
Alright.
Thank you.
The contract terms within the validity period
are extremely important.
Once it expires,
it's a disaster.
- Okay.
- You know.
The financial risk is huge.
Why are you here?
Sorry.
This is Naomi, my team leader.
My girlfriend, Rose.
Hello.
- Hi.
- Very pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- I'm setting you free and see you tomorrow.
- Okay
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Oh, wait.
I'll send you the new contract tonight.
My girlfriend suddenly arrived.
It's a bit complicated.
Don't worry.
If there are any issues,
call me, okay?
See you tomorrow.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Bye.
How did you get here?
With a tour group.
A seven-day tour of France.
I can only stay in Paris for two days,
so I came to find you right from the airport.
♪Once aimlessly searching♪
♪Listen to the sound of the wind♪
♪In the vast sky♪
♪Like my love for you♪
♪Like gentle oxygen♪
♪Healing and transparent♪
♪The sound of the wind♪
♪Listen, memories are light and clear♪
♪I'm snuggling in your arms♪
♪Sleep peacefully♪
♪Have a sweet dream♪
Why are you up?
Aren't you going to sleep?
This contract must be finished today,
so I have time for you tomorrow.
Where's your roommate?
Still not back this late?
On a business trip.
Why did Naomi come home with you?
To help me revise this contract.
I never thought you'd come and see me.
Because you said
you wished to wake up with me by your side,
so you could hold me.
When will you finish?
Almost done.
Management training requires rotation
through various departments.
Now I'm in the operations department.
I'm not very familiar with it,
so it takes more time.
Luckily, the rotation ends next year,
and I might be assigned
to the marketing department.
Once settled, I can apply
for permanent residency.
You're applying for permanent residency?
Not returning to China?
I'll get the permanent residency
and decide later whether to return.
What about me?
If I become marketing manager,
my salary will double,
and we could rent an apartment together.
It'd be more convenient for you to stay.
You want me to move to France?
Yes.
You study art.
This is the art capital.
Perfect for you.
What about my parents?
And my job?
Your brother is in Beijing.
What are you worried about?
Your job is just an assistant,
with no great future.
I'm a curator.
Alright, a curator.
Cyan isn't a big company.
It claims to be a joint venture,
but it's just registered in Hong Kong, China,
with not much scale or reputation
in the industry.
Why do you get to decide for me?
It's the right decision.
But it's not my decision.
So many people are desperate to go abroad
because there are more opportunities there.
But my life is in China.
If you place me in France,
what will I do?
Will my life revolve around you?
Is that it?
I never said that.
Your attitude implies
I should come to France
to follow you,
because my job isn't good enough,
isn't important,
not as valuable as yours.
I never devalued your work.
People aim higher. It's a fact.
I'm applying for permanent residency
for our future.
That's your future.
You never considered me.
You didn't even discuss it with me.
Your words are so disheartening.
I did all this for us.
I just think you shouldn't decide alone.
You're overthinking.
I was just planning.
The training isn't over.
Nothing is certain yet.
Don't be angry.
I must finish my work today.
I have to finish it before it's too late.
Go to sleep.
Not angry, right?
Not angry.
What does "compliquer" mean?
Troublesome?
Go to sleep.
(School of Chemistry)
Thank you for visiting me
and bringing so much good food.
Your parents are very worried about you.
How have you been?
I can't live in the past forever.
So,
I made one last effort.
I went to his hometown
to see him one last time.
The subscriber you dialed
can not be connected for the moment.
Please try again later.
The subscriber you dialed
can not be connected for the moment.
Please try again later.
Xiaohe.
Can't we say goodbye in person?
See?
This is where I grew up.
You're a city girl.
You don't understand my pressure
and inferiority.
My family introduced me to a local girl.
We've been seeing each other for months.
Unless something unexpected happens,
I'll marry her.
Forget about me.
We shall never see each other again.
Being with you for those years
exhausted my lifetime's happiness.
I don't deserve that kind of life.
Sorry, Xiaohe.
From the start,
I shouldn't have met you.
After I came back, I vomited all day.
I completely figured it out.
Now,
I just want to focus on my studies.
After getting my PhD,
I want to find a research institute abroad,
quietly doing experiments
and research.
Nothing else matters.
Having a plan is good.
I hope it works out.
I didn't tell my parents
about going to his hometown.
Understood. I won't tell them.
Thank you.
Advice without concrete solutions
is just empty talk.
My suggestion is
don't stay cooped up.
Go out more.
Watch comedy shows, movies,
or find a hobby.
Like me.
Since I started exercising,
I feel much better.
You really look different from before.
I even got a personal coach.
How about joining us for workouts?
Rose?
Rose,
Rose.
Wake up. Get up.
Our plans have changed.
I took a day off,
but the big boss is coming
for a meeting this afternoon.
So we have to hurry.
Come on, get up.
We'll visit the Louvre in the morning,
see the Eiffel Tower at 1 pm,
and I must be back at work by 3 pm.
Get up.
♪This an ode to love♪
♪Strolling hand in hand
under the blue sky and white clouds♪
♪In harmony♪
♪Happiness beyond words♪
♪This is an ode to love♪
♪Happy moments echo in my heart♪
♪Wonderful love, forever lasting♪
♪This is an ode to love♪
Come here and look.
Portrait of a Man.
In our freshman year,
the whole class saw this portrait.
Now we see the real thing.
Isn't it amazing?
Look at the brushwork.
See how fine it is.
There are many paintings
you saw in school here.
Let's go.
- There are many more inside.
- Just look at it.
♪Wonderful love, forever lasting♪
♪Loving each other, happiness forever♪
♪Eyes shining, illuminating everything♪
From the 18th century.
♪It's so good to be with you♪
♪We are gentle and intoxicated together♪
♪This is the melody of happy times♪
♪As long as you're willing♪
♪I will bring you happiness for life♪
♪My beloved♪
♪Let's sing and dance together♪
♪Whisper prayers♪
♪We will always be together♪
How about it? Have you decided?
This one.
Moules Marinières?
That takes too long.
We don't have enough time.
Let's have something simpler, okay?
Sandwiches?
Waitress.
Two sandwiches, please.
Alright.
Thank you.
Wait a moment.
Can you take a photo for us?
Sure.
Thank you.
Alright, alright.
Okay.
You wait here for me.
Have a seat.
Naomi,
please come here.
Everyone, gather around.
Today is a very special day.
I want to share my joy with you.
First,
this month we finally completed
the "City and Artists" project.
We've been working on it
for the past six months.
This project received
very positive feedback.
(Before this moment,)
(I never realized)
(we were heading in opposite directions.)
(What I thought was closeness)
(was actually just passing by.)
Let's go. I'll make you a big meal.
Alright.
Sir.
With pleasure.
With great pleasure.
Is this what you want?
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
Hello, sir, what would you like?
Alright, of course.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
Hello.
Please give me a baguette.
Alright.
Anything else?
A Camembert cheese, please.
Okay.
Would you like some caviar?
Sure.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
You're welcome.
No need for caviar. It's too expensive.
It's fine.
Tonight, I must make it up to you.
Here's your change.
Hello?
I can't. I have plans tonight.
Alright.
But I have to bring my girlfriend.
Okay.
Don't worry. These parties are very relaxed.
Does your mom often bring you
to her company events?
She knows many people
in the fashion and business circles.
Wealthy people are very interested
in art and cultural activities.
Eric,
I'm Chris,
Jessica's boyfriend.
By the way, she's arriving soon.
What would you like?
Champagne or red wine?
Would you like some champagne?
Yeah, champagne.
Waiter.
Chris, this is my girlfriend, Rose.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Cheers.
I'll go meet your mom.
Everything is great.
Chris is my mom's
boyfriend.
This is my mom.
Welcome.
Rose, my girlfriend, Huang Yimei.
I mentioned her to you before.
- Hello, hello.
- Hi, Ms. Song.
Lulu is here too.
Go and say hi to her later.
Okay.
Feel free.
Thank you.
Who's Lulu?
♪Rain♪
♪Falls on my forehead♪
♪The wind fills my sleeves♪
♪I pass through intersections♪
♪Changing trains♪
♪Stopping at each station♪
♪Encounters in the bustling streets♪
♪Freedom in farewells♪
♪May I accompany myself♪
♪Throughout this life's journey♪
♪Loving someone is the best♪
♪But not obligatory♪
♪As long as the wind blows♪
♪Good luck is on the way♪
♪Happiness should come from within♪
♪No need for anyone else♪
♪Watching the sunset along the way♪
♪Like flowers sent from afar♪
♪Rainy or sunny, keep moving forward♪
♪I want to move forward♪
♪So let go of my hand♪
♪The road can be run on♪
♪It can also be danced on♪
♪The crossroads I want to go to♪
♪Are beyond where you stand♪
♪No regrets left behind♪
♪May I keep moving forward♪
♪Whether rainy or sunny♪
♪Empty-handed along the way♪
♪Only needing health♪
♪Happiness♪
♪and a free spirit♪
♪Like a bird in flight♪
♪Born♪
♪With the entire♪
♪Sky♪