[This program is intended for
mature audiences aged 18 and over]
[It may contain explicit visuals, audio,
behavior, intense violence,
sexual content, and strong language]
[Viewer discretion is advised]
[This series is entirely fictional]
[It is not based on,
nor intended to represent,
any real individuals or organizations]
This store probably has it.
Oh!
That's the one.
Oh, this too!
Here.
Look at you gliding like a princess.
I pay, so you carry the bags.
What?
Weren't you the one who sold them?
Take them!
What?
This one's not for sale.
How about this?
Can I record a video of you
dancing for my kids?
I'll sell you this model car
if you agree.
Alright. "Print's Payday."
Print's Payday.
Print's Payday...
Dance like you mean it!
Alright.
Print's Payday,
Pay Up Babies,
The Basket Awaits!
Thank you.
Thank you, sis!
Thank you, too.
Here are free gifts!
Oh!
See?
We don't have to go separate ways
to work things out.
That's because we haven't figured out
how to switch back to our bodies,
so I had no choice.
From this moment forth,
you are me,
I am you.
We're on the same team now.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Say it first.
Should we try bumping our heads?
Are you insane?
I'm not doing that.
Just once.
We've tried everything, haven't we?
Mm.
Just once.
Am I late?
The bathtub is ready, Miss.
The bathtub?
Want some?
I bought some for you.
Everything is white!
Oh!
This is it!
This is what I'm looking for!
From now on,
I am gonna turn Miss Rey into...
a fashion icon.
You're gonna go do some reforestation
in that outfit?
Reforestation?
Rey,
be honest with me.
What's going on lately?
You can tell me if you're not okay.
I'm fine!
Then, let's get changed.
Let's go.
I'll give you a recap on the car.
What reforestation?
Rey!
Oh, right.
Give me my phone.
What do you want it for?
To switch our accounts.
Good idea!
What if someone called?
We didn't switch our numbers.
Well, just text instead.
So, from now on,
we'll text each other to keep up
with schedules and life?
What freaking reforestation!?
It's for charity. No big deal.
It's time to leave!
Okay!
Print!
Have you seen our family group chat?
Nope.
Our sister got in trouble at school!
Who?
Right, what happened?
Read the group chat.
Okay.
Frank said your sister
got into trouble at school.
What do I do?
Are you going to her school?
I'm not.
I'm rushing to my internship interview.
- Then...
- You have to go.
Patty is waiting for you.
Didn't someone say
she'd be a better version of me,
one who would wipe out the old me?
I am going to be you.
I scheduled a meeting with you because,
earlier this morning,
other students said
Patty purposely hosed down Ekkasit.
That's not what happened, Miss.
I...
I was watering the plants
behind the school
when I saw Ekkasit take money
from another student.
I was just trying to stop them,
so I sprayed the water
in their direction.
The real problem is...
the person who was extorting the money.
We don't even know if she's lying.
But one thing for sure is that
your sister soaked my son
from head to toe.
You okay, my dear?
Hope you're not catching a cold.
How are you going to pay for this?
But Miss...
We are so sorry.
From what I gathered...
I think they are both at fault.
Please don't make a big deal out of it.
Uhm...
- Mom, but she isn't...
- Print...
Why didn't you keep that?
Or don't you trust my decision?
I must apologize on her behalf.
My dear, we've won.
[Reforestation Drive:
Protect the Green, Protect Our Planet]
Could you squeeze in a little?
Here we go.
Smile, please.
Alright.
Three, two, one.
- One more!
- With heart on the cheek pose.
Three, two, one.
- I wanna look young like her.
- One more!
Three, two...
Are you sure this is a charity event,
not a fan meeting?
They took way too many pics.
Hm?
Huh?
Let's go. You need to get changed.
Huh?!
There's more?!
Rey!
Are you feeling okay today?
You just said,
"Being me is not all that hard."
Oh, Rey!
Your dad took you golfing today?
Hi, Mister...
Uncle.
Seeing you here means
you're stepping up
to help your dad, right?
For the family business...
I think I still have a lot to figure out.
An acting career would be easy for you.
That's perfect for your pretty face.
I don't think
there's an easy job out there.
I've put so much effort into acting.
Even today, I deal with
a lot of disrespectful people.
I have to act like I'm not offended.
If I were bad at acting,
I would have cussed them out.
Alright...
You're being all nice to me.
What do you want?
Who said I was being nice?
I just wanted to kill his vibe.
What did you say?
Oh...
It's nothing.
Thank you.
Rey, what are you doing?
I'm hungry, so I'm eating.
It's already 4 P.M.
But you're allergic to shrimp.
Rey!
Rey!!
No, Rey!!
I need some help here!
An antihistamine injection
has been administered.
She should recover soon.
Thank you.
Rey,
I know you're still awake.
Once I'm back,
I expect you to be ready to talk.
Your body is having an allergic reaction.
Come to the hospital right now.
What? I'm on my way.
Where are you now?
Ugh...
You've finally arrived, Miss Real Rey.
Don't scratch.
Stop scratching!
Don't tell me you ate shrimp.
Who would've known
you're allergic to them?
Why didn't you ask me before having it?
I don't have time for that.
I had to do some reforestation,
then went golfing.
I was also busy helping out
with your family stuff.
The other student's mom
wasn't giving up that easily.
And your mom was...
She just said sorry
to get it over with, right?
I'm sorry.
I...
I can never be you.
What do you mean?
Well, I...
I made your sister
feel disappointed in you.
I can never be you, either.
What kind of person
has a schedule that packed?
I don't even have time to eat.
If we tell Fon,
she'll probably believe us.
What about Wanmai?
Someone like her
would never believe what happened.
Well, what happened?
Shit.
What now?
She's your person.
So, anything you wanna say?
Well...
Print and I...
We swapped bodies.
Wait.
Mai,
what is she trying
to put in Print's head?
Rey?
Wanmai,
my mom chose you...
out of 200 applicants for this position.
During the interview,
you were the only one bold enough
to point out my weakness.
That's why my mom trusted you
and picked you for this job.
Do you remember
when our car broke down
and we ended up
having a deep talk for two hours?
Print also told this story
during live streams.
But there's one story
Print hasn't told yet.
It's about how you can't move on
from that person.
Want me to let that slip?
Don't say it!
That person...
Shh!
- Do you believe...
- Stop!
Do you believe us now?
Alright, I believe you guys!
Hold on...
Are you really Print?
What?
Print?
Oh, Print!
My sweet girl!
That's why we need your help.
While you're figuring out
how to get back into your real bodies,
you need to live each other's lives
as normally as possible
like you're living your own.
To help the process go faster,
you'll have to move in together.
I think we should stay
at each other's places every other week
to be fair.
Whose place do we start with?
Fair and square,
let's settle this
with Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Good luck, baby.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Wow!
Whoa!
What a million-dollar view!
These three drawers are yours.
This space here is mine.
Don't cross the line.
What?
Why is my space smaller?
Because I own this place.
Wow.
I never thought...
you'd like something like this.
Hold up.
I'll tell you the rules.
The green scourer is for the plates
and the pink one is for glasses.
Got it?
Do the dishes.
"The green scourer is for the glasses
and the pink one is for plates.
Do the dishes."
Hey,
your spot...
is over there.
Get up.
Just wait till it's my turn.
Here's your spot.
And this is our working space.
Before you sleep,
have you gone through the script?
Our roles will be switched.
But I've already done the research.
Try to rehearse
with the notes I wrote down.
Thank you, Miss Rey.
If you really want to thank me,
why not work hard on my script?
Hi.
Hello.
Excuse me,
may I check
who entered the building
on the day of Rey's workshop?
Please allow me to refer
to the institution's director.
Honestly,
you didn't even have to come
'cause I've got everything under control.
There's no one
resembling your description.
Miss Mangosteen
didn't return to that class either.
Wait.
How is that possible?
That's what she told me.
How about this?
Can I review the security footage?
I'm deeply sorry.
Our institution does not permit
non-staff to review the security footage.
- But I really need...
- What if we have this?
Can we see the footage now?
[Police Report: The complainant reported
losing her cellphone at Method Academy]
[Your cooperation regarding
the security footage is hereby requested]
Wow, that's totally you, Mai.
Always prepared!
I love how the staff here
are following the rules.
Now, no one can try to be sneaky.
In that case,
let's go review the footage.
Right away.
This way, please.
Honestly, you didn't even have to come
'cause I've got everything under control.
"Honestly, you didn't even have to come
'cause I've got everything under control."
Hey, wait for me!
It's her.
This one?
Hang on a moment.
Who the heck is that?
She is not one of our staff.
What?
Are you saying
you just let anyone roam around?
Hey.
- Mai!
- Hm?
Are you really not
going to file a report?
They let anyone in here,
and it's causing problems for our girls.
If you're not filing a report,
I'll do it.
What are you gonna tell them?
A case of body swapping?
What do you think
affects the girls the most?
Gosh!
[Your rider has canceled the ride]
There won't be any riders
out in this rain.
Well...
How about you tag along,
and I'll drop you off?
It's fine.
You sure?
What if you got sick
and couldn't work?
Well then, I'm leaving.
I'll tag along until Main Street.
Mm!
[We've found your rider!]
I just got a ride.
I'm heading out.
What's with you?
Call me if you need anything.
You got my number, right?
You just call me if you need anything.
Alright.
Don't worry about the Mysterious Person.
We'll figure it out.
I'm gonna find other ways to help them.
Can you lift these?
Is there anyone
who can help me with the setup?
Can you help move this stuff?
Is the camera ready?
Have you finished the setup?
We've got to be ready in 10 minutes.
Hello,
I bought you guys some donuts.
Thank you so much, Rey.
I'll take one.
Everyone, Rey bought us some donuts!
Come grab some.
- Thank you so much.
- Let's take a break.
Rey's bought us snacks!
Let's go.
Thank you so much.
It's nice to meet you.
I promise I'll do my best.
Wow.
Thank you!
Uh...
Hang in there!
You too!
Thank you.
Care for a donut, Teacher?
Why are you so laid-back?
Stay focused.
It's time to review your script.
Today's scene is difficult.
I know! I've been rehearsing all night!
Look at my under eyes.
Look.
Here!
It's good that you've rehearsed.
I'll keep an eye on you.
We'll be going to shoot scene 27.
Print will be playing Auer's lover.
Auer, you just realized
you were forced into a marriage,
so you're sneaking out to meet Print.
That's about it.
- Alright.
- All good.
- I got it.
- Let's give them a room.
- Alright, are you two ready?
- Yes.
Stand by.
Camera,
And action!
Miss Grace,
no matter what,
I want you to know
you're the only one
I want to spend my life with.
But it's impossible for us
to be together, Mr. Prachak.
You're now betrothed to Miss Rin.
Miss Grace...
Please don't make this hard for me.
You told me
to be honest with my feelings.
I'm gonna break off the engagement.
But if you do that,
your mother won't be happy.
I don't want you to argue with her.
Whoa.
Is this truly her debut acting role?
She's the realness.
Can my body even cry like that?
It's your cue now, Rey.
Miss Rin...
Cut!
Excellent job.
We're moving on to Rey's scene now.
The villain has shown you how it's done.
It's time for the lead.
This is the next scene
after the last one.
Rey's mad
'cause he's in love with someone else.
So, you're gonna slap Auer
and cry out loud.
- Okay.
- That's about it.
Easy peasy.
- Let's do it.
- Ready?
Okay!
Let's get started.
Where do I stand?
Right here on the green mark.
- Okay.
- Alright.
You can really slap me, Rey.
- I'm used to it.
Alright, let's begin.
Camera,
And action!
Mr. Prachak,
I hate you!
Can we start over?
Cut!
Let's start over.
Mr. Prachak!
I hate you!
Cut!
One more time.
One more.
Let's do it.
Stay focused, everyone.
Camera,
And action!
Mr. Prachak!
I hate you!
Again.
Mr. Prachak!
I hate you!!
Action!
I hate you!
Mr. Prachak!
Cut!
If this keeps up,
Auer's face is gonna be all bruised.
I'm so sorry.
Can we do it again?
Rey, you never needed more than 10 takes.
This scene...
is not that hard.
I'm really sorry.
Are you okay?
Stay calm.
Try to stay focused
and close your eyes before you start.
Can I try it my way first?
I know I can do it.
- Right.
- Come on.
Let's do it again.
Alright.
And action!
Mr. Prachak...
I hate you.
Let's go!
Get the tears going!
Tears!
Are the tears coming?
Come on!
I hate you!
Cut!
Rey, this is...
not your first time acting.
It's not a hard scene, right?
Should we move on
to the other scenes first
and come back to this later?
One of you can't act,
and the other just wants to run the show.
If that's how you want to work,
then do it yourself.
Please calm down.
Hey...
Hey,
you should cry in front of the camera,
not here.
Who cried?
My eyes are just dry
from the contact lenses.
Just memorizing the script
won't get you through the scenes.
What do I have to do, then?
You wanna know?
Then beg for it.
Tell me.
How should I do it?
First of all,
you need to do as I say.
Everything I say.
Let's start with...
the happiest scene.
Okay...
That's enough.
Your problem is the way
you express your emotions
and act.
So, what do you think I should do?
Uh...
Alright, try imagining what it's like
to play the happiest person.
What comes to your mind?
Letting myself relax
in a nice Jacuzzi tub...
Wearing pretty clothes...
Breakfast prepared by the maids...
Happiness...
Are you...
enjoying living my happy life?
I'm not.
It's just my imagination.
Imagination?
Um.
Alright.
That was fine.
How about...
a crying scene?
I just can't cry no matter what.
In a crying scene,
it's not about forcing the tears.
You have to truly feel it.
Actually,
there's a trick to these scenes.
Try to think of sad experiences
in your life.
That'll help.
Does swapping bodies with you
count as a sad experience?
Be serious.
Try to think about it.
Are there any sad experiences
you can't forget?
Let me know if you think of one.
Glitter Girl...
If I were you,
I would have felt so hurt.
If you hadn't lost that day,
you would've...
lived in a big penthouse,
lain on a soft mattress,
bathed in a nice Jacuzzi tub,
worn pretty clothes,
and had maids tending to you.
More than that,
you could easily
support your family financially.
If you hadn't lost that day,
today,
you'd be the actress
you've always wanted.
Alright, you ready?
And action!
Mr. Prachak,
I hate you...
Cut!
There you go.
That looks like the Rey we know.
Great job.
Well,
someone was urging her
to rehearse yesterday.
Now she's acting like herself again.
Right...
I'm sorry for the way I talked to you.
No worries.
I really messed up yesterday.
I'm sorry, too.
Go take a break, Rey.
Come on.
You're awesome.
See?
I can do it if I give it my all.
If you had done it from the start,
we'd be done by now.
Quit crying.
I'm done reading the script for tomorrow.
I'm off to bed now.
Hold up.
We have a difficult scene to work on.
Check page 27.
But I'm sleepy.
I've been through a lot today.
Can we do it tomorrow?
[Prachak: But I've never breathed
the word 'love' to anyone but you]
["Prachak makes up with Rin
by kissing her"]
A kissing scene?
Easy.
Have you ever kissed someone?
Well,
occasionally, yeah.
What tips do you have for this scene?
You have kissed someone?
Why do you ask me that?
What?
Why did you ask me, then?
I've had some experience
with kissing scenes.
If you want it to feel natural,
you have to truly feel it deep inside.
Alright.
For example,
this scene isn't just about kissing.
You need to feel slighted
by the person you're in love with.
Okay.
How hard could it be?
Let's roll.
I'm sleepy.
Come on.
Let's start with blocking.
Try lying down like this, okay?
We'll go with this.
All set?
Mm.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me, Mr. Prachak?
I...
After all this,
you're still going to lie to me?
So,
please listen closely
to what I'm saying.
The first time we met,
I despised you.
Who on earth
could be such a nuisance?
A nuisance like me
and an insolent person like you
make a perfect match.
I suppose you take pleasure
in making me...
feel this way?
And what way is that, exactly?
Well,
in a way...
I've never felt for anyone before.
You...
Coming from someone like you,
I bet you say that to all the girls.
But I've never breathed
the word 'love' to anyone
but you.