♪A beautiful place full of smiles♪
♪Where imaginations about you grow wildly♪
♪The winter sun is like your white teeth♪
♪Expecting your visit all day long♪
♪Like the light breeze
and the fragrance of flowers in May and June♪
♪Hesitate to embrace you and my words stumble♪
♪Time passes hurriedly,
leaving a photo of us and sunflowers♪
♪Too flimsy to be scrutinized♪
♪Welcome to my world and explore its beauty♪
♪I can offer you my clumsy gentleness♪
♪Welcome to my lonely island, too♪
♪Only fish and migratory birds have been here♪
♪Maybe I'm too clumsy and evasive♪
♪Tired of troubles,
all I want is to hide you secretly♪
[Hidden Love]
[Episode 6]
But I can't resist temptation.
What kind of temptation?
If someone
is dating in front of me,
I'll also want to be in a relationship.
You've watched too many idol dramas.
Who do you mean?
The people close to you.
Those who are around.
Are you talking about me?
Kiddo,
why are you so petty?
You can't stop others from dating
just because you can't date.
Isn't it provoking me
to date in front of me?
Fine,
let's say you're right.
I won't talk
about future matters with you for now.
But regarding
your ex-boyfriend
who asked you to go to Yihe to find him.
It's quite a coincidence
because I'm from Yihe.
So
if I find out
that you go and see him
when you're still underage,
then I'm afraid
you won't see
what you look like after adulthood.
Let's start studying.
How was the last exam?
Take point M as the intersection of sides AB.
I've explained this problem to you before.
Like this question.
Then try
to recall the formula.
♪And ripples of excitement
sprawling across my vision♪
Let me explain static electricity first.
You got this question right.
♪A bright face under a calm disguising face♪
♪But I can't contain my joy♪
♪I have a weird intuition♪
♪My heart jingles when I think of you♪
This question...
I was originally going to choose option C.
Choose option C?
It's D?
♪To check if my secret liking isn't unrequited♪
It's option D for this question.
Pay more attention next time.
One wrong multiple-choice question.
So you scored 97 points.
Not bad.
You've improved a lot.
So
you have no problem
with physics now.
I won't come to tutor you anymore
after this.
If you still have something
you don't understand,
you can ask your brother
or your teacher.
You can ask me too.
Just take a picture of what you don't understand
and send it to me.
I'll reply after I go through it.
My phone was confiscated.
Your brother will go
and plead with your parents for you.
Don't worry.
Be happy.
Now that you've improved so much.
So did I teach well?
All right then.
So
after school starts,
will you have any more exams?
Yes.
Then,
send me the result
of each exam.
You'd better get good results.
As long as there's improvement,
I'll give you a gift.
Let's stop here for today.
You're doing the housework?
You're done with the tutoring?
Come here.
Come and have some fruit.
Thank you, ma'am.
Have some fruit.
I was just talking
to her dad.
How about celebrating
Chinese New Year's Eve together tomorrow night?
Come and join us.
Thank you for inviting me.
But
I think I should stay on campus.
The campus is impressive now.
They organize New Year's Eve dinner
and give us red packets.
Just don't go back.
It's boring to go back alone.
In that case,
all right then.
Let me help you, Mr. Sang.
Okay.
Zhi, pass that to me.
[Happy New Year]
We'll stick
this one here.
We should stick this "fu" character upside down.
Dear.
Is this one good, dear?
Make it a bit bigger?
(If I give him a red packet,)
(it will seem a bit strange.)
(He definitely won't accept it.)
(Jiaxu,)
(Happy New Year.)
Sang Yan said
you plan to stay in Nanwu
after graduation.
Have you found a job?
Yes,
I plan
to work at a game company
where I interned.
That sounds good.
Keep it up.
Okay, paste it.
Give it to me.
Put it on top, that's good.
Higher.
A bit higher.
Zhi.
Perfect, all right.
Help me clear the table.
Stop sweeping already.
Wash the rag and wipe the table.
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
I should help around.
What do you think?
Okay, okay.
-That's enough.
-So little?
That's enough for me.
Thank you.
Okay.
It's time to toast.
Happy New Year!
-Happy New Year!
Dear, Happy New Year.
Let's clink glasses.
I dare you to finish all of this.
Cheers.
Go away!
He doesn't want to clink glasses with me.
You used such a big bottle.
The most exciting part
is yet to come.
Dear,
you'll be the first to get this.
I have a red packet too?
Perfect.
Thank you, dear.
I love you.
-I wish Dad and Mom a Happy New Year!
-May all your wishes come true!
Be happy...
Stay healthy...
We were supposed to start with "Be happy."
It's "Stay healthy."
No, it's "Be happy!"
Fine.
-Be happy every day!
-Stay healthy!
I like it.
Here you go, Yan.
Thank you, Dad.
Zhi, this is yours.
-Thank you, Dad.
-Thank you, Mom.
Dad,
you're being unfair.
You're about to graduate from the university.
You're lucky to receive even one.
Zhi,
what are you going to do when you have your phone?
I'll uninstall the games.
What else?
What about your online dating prospect?
I already deleted it long ago.
What about the phone number?
I don't have his number.
We don't use phone numbers for online dating.
I'm telling the truth.
Really?
You can check if you don't believe me.
You don't even have that much money
to afford game currency.
Why are you dating online?
Stop talking already.
All right.
Cut it out. Stop arguing.
Let's eat.
Eat up.
I have something to say before we start eating.
I hope
my two lovely children
will grow up
and behave a bit more in this new year.
And you,
be more mature.
Dad meant you.
All right, let's eat.
Okay, let's dig in.
By the way, Zhi,
didn't you want to buy
a set of anime merchandise?
Now that your brother has red packet money,
ask him to give it to you.
Why should I? No way.
Thank you, Yan. Thank you.
Yan is the most generous.
Yan, have some of these.
A toast to Yan.
Happy New Year.
This is for you.
At least you have a conscience.
But it's not much.
You like it.
It's delicious.
Is it?
I want this one.
[Jiaxu]
[I wish you happiness every day]
[and find your dreams soon.]
[Happy Spring Festival.]
It's from Jiaxu.
Yan, you did well. Have some more.
Thank you, Mom.
What's the plan for the next couple of days?
(I wish you happiness every day)
(and find your dreams soon.)
(Happy Spring Festival.)
Okay.
Zhi,
we'll go skiing in a few days.
What do you think?
Skiing? Sure.
Okay then.
So you'll make the plan
and see where we should go.
Okay.
The Spring Festival is the peak season.
So book early.
That's right.
Next to No. 3.
(Forget about the number. It's useless.)
(How about just salt with vinegar?)
(Salt with vinegar?)
I heard footsteps.
(Listen to my upper couplet.)
(My upper couplet will start with "Perfectly.")
("Perfectly matched.")
(What matched?)
Behind the bridge.
(Perfectly matched,)
(matched as in paired.)
(That's a good way to start a couplet.)
(Now the other part, it would be "Shi.")
[*Shi in Chinese chess means Minister]
Move.
("Shi" against "Pao.")
[*Pao in Chinese chess means cannon]
(Why is it minister against cannon?)
(You move the minister, and I move the cannon.)
[Sang Zhi]
(So Minister against Cannon.)
(It's Chinese chess, you know?)
(I'll put it this way.)
(It's right)
(when I structured
these five characters together.)
(Thank you, Jiaxu.)
(Happy New Year.)
[Yihe City Nursing Home]
Hello?
Hello.
Are you Mr. Duan Jiaxu?
Yes.
Your father has severe lung water accumulation
caused by a lung infection.
He needs to be transferred immediately
for drainage.
The current condition is quite urgent.
We kindly request you to come as soon as possible
to sign the consent form.
Okay, I understand. Thank you.
[Chapter 6 Distance.
When there's you in another city.]
Mr. Sang, your package.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, silly doggie.
It has a name.
Its name is Winner.
Silly doggie, come here.
Come here. I have something to tell you.
Just come here.
Listen.
You see,
you and he look so similar.
You two look exactly alike.
Wait right there.
Duan Jiaxu sent this to you.
It says this is your reward
for ranking 20th
in the mock exam
and scoring 95 in Physics.
Why didn't he give it to me himself?
Didn't he tell you?
He went back to his hometown
Yihe.
After hesitating for a while,
he said there was something going on at home.
It's his own matter.
Why didn't you ask him yourself?
Wait.
Then
will he come back for the graduation ceremony?
Of course,
he will.
(Why did he leave)
(without saying goodbye?)
[Xuri Middle School——Nanwu University, Drive]
[2 hours 33 minutes]
[Sang Zhi]
(Yan, are you coming home today?)
[Silly Dog: ?]
What's this?
What's wrong?
Why are you taking your time when class is over?
My sister is probably in trouble again.
She asked if I was going home.
She got into trouble again?
It was awesome just now.
The position
when the ball was tossed.
The main point
is I didn't play that well.
Hello?
Yan.
It's already Friday.
Why are you not coming home?
That candy from the convenience store today
has a promotion of buy one get one free.
So I bought an extra pack.
I can share it with you.
If I want to eat candy,
I can buy it myself.
Just tell me what you want.
Nothing.
I was just asking casually.
Then, I can just casually not go home.
Am I right?
I just wanted to say it's cheap.
You can invite your classmates to come over
and eat at home.
Duan Jiaxu,
where are you going?
Where are you guys going?
I'm going home for a bit.
I happen to be going to your area.
Let's go together.
Sure. If you're free,
come to my house for dinner.
Okay.
Then I won't join.
I have to go back to the dorm and do my assignment.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Bye.
Hello, little demon.
You hung up, huh?
What's wrong?
She hung up on me.
Let's go.
(Why don't I call Sang Yan)
(and ask where they are?)
(Forget it.)
(They should be here soon.)
Don't worry.
What's the situation?
Chen Junwen...
(He's finally home.)
How many times have you forgotten your keys?
I can't get it for you.
If you want, you have to get it yourself.
Are you that foolish
or just clumsy, huh?
I'm already home.
How can I open it for you?
(Why is he alone?)
Little demon!
Why didn't you close the door?
Don't you know there are mosquitoes?
Duan Jiaxu
was supposed to come to my house.
But the library
gave him a call.
So he had to go back to work.
I'm sure you know
making money is all he could think about.
All right, that's all.
I'm hanging up now.
Bye-bye.
Little demon,
why did you ask me to come back?
Dad and Mom said
to come back
to have dinner together this weekend.
Eat dinner together?
Can't you tell me over the phone?
Dad! Mom!
Yan?
Yan is back.
Why are you back?
I thought you were coming home tomorrow.
It's the weekend. So let's have dinner together.
You're getting more thoughtful.
Your dad and I have been busy working
outside all day and are sweating.
We'll go and take a shower first.
-Okay.
After a shower, I'll make dinner for you.
Okay.
Mom, why don't
you let Yan make dinner?
Him? Dinner?
That would work too.
Cook the rice first.
Then wash the vegetables.
I think cooking rice is too simple.
It's okay.
Let him cook the rice.
I'll make the dishes.
Yan.
Which library
is Jiaxu working at?
Is it the university's library?
Why are you asking me this?
Nothing.
I'm just curious.
Are university students
so busy?
What do you guys usually busy with?
Busy trying to get away
from a little demon like you.
Busy sleeping in class.
Isn't that
the same as middle school students like us?
How can that be the same?
We university students
have one more thing to do,
which is dating.
Dating?
Well, I should've known.
A kid like you
wouldn't understand this.
How is that possible?
How is it possible for any girl
to like you?
Listen,
there are plenty of girls chasing after me.
Even the CRH-train series
can't accommodate all of them.
What's wrong with you?
It's been so long
since I heard
someone could brag this exaggeratedly.
You don't believe me, huh?
Okay, listen.
Do you know
why all of my roommates have no girlfriends?
All of them have no girlfriends at all?
Because those girls
are lining up to pursue me.
Do you think I'd believe that nonsense?
[Sender: Duan Jiaxu]
(Another reward from Jiaxu)
(for my exam scores.)
Hello?
Hello, Jiaxu.
I received
the package you sent.
It's a black doggie soft toy.
So?
Do you like it?
It looks familiar.
Is that so?
Does it look like Sang Yan?
You still remember my essay.
Of course, I do.
I was on the street one day,
and I saw this dog.
It reminded me
of the drawing you made.
So I thought
it would be a perfect gift for you.
Congratulations!
You scored 95 on the physics exam this time,
right?
Oh, Jiaxu.
Give me your address.
I want to send you something.
You want to send me something?
Just exchanging favors.
No need.
Why? It's important.
How much pocket money
do you have in a month?
Keep the money
and spend it on yourself, okay?
No need to send me any gifts.
Let me send it to you.
Really, no need.
Your thoughtfulness
already makes me happy.
So
Yan said
you'll come back
for your graduation ceremony.
Is that so?
Yes.
Are you going?
That's great.
We'll see each other then.
I have to go now.
Bye-bye.
(Then, consider it as your graduation gift.)
Who's there?
Long time no see.
Why are you here?
Aren't you inviting me in?
It's not convenient.
Sorry about that.
Here.
Isn't that person
in a bad condition?
Don't worry
about returning the money this month.
It's fine.
I can figure it out myself.
I just don't want you
to have a hard time.
Really, no need.
Thank you for the offer.
By the way,
has the time for your graduation ceremony
been decided yet?
Can I go too?
No need.
All right.
Since you're returning to Yihe,
we'll have time to meet again.
Then,
I wish you an early happy graduation.
Thank you.
I'll keep in touch with you again.
Three, two, one!
Cheese!
(Smile a little.)
(A bit lower.)
(Okay, smile.)
(Three, two, one.)
Your classmate?
Actually, we don't know each other.
Sang Yan, come here quickly!
Over there.
Hello, Mr. Sang.
Congratulations.
All of you have graduated.
Thank you, Mr. Sang.
Mr. Sang,
where's Mrs. Sang?
She's sick with a cold and fever.
I told her to rest at home.
Many people have fallen sick lately.
Yeah.
Sang Yan,
you came late.
I haven't taken pictures with you.
Let's take some pictures.
Okay, let's go.
Let me help you guys take it.
-Thank you, Mr. Sang.
Thank you, Mr. Sang.
It's all right.
Look this way.
One, two, three.
Change a different pose.
Ready? One, two, three.
All done. Take a look.
Thank you, Mr. Sang.
Qian Fei!
Qian Fei, come and take some pictures with us!
Come on!
Let's go.
Dad, I'll go over.
Jia, come and join us.
Come.
I heard
you'll work in your hometown.
Yes.
I've already found a job.
It's not bad to work back in your hometown.
After all,
it's a familiar place.
When you have time, come to Nanwu.
Remember to come to my house for a meal.
Okay, that's for sure.
Good.
Let's go find your brother
and take a photo together.
Let's take it together.
Okay.
Long time no see, Zhi.
This is for you.
For me?
I thought
it was for your brother.
He... He already has one.
This one is for my physics tutor.
I hope he
has a happy graduation
and be happy every day.
Thank you.
I like it very much.
Then, I wish my student
a bright future and smooth academic progress.
(The graduation ceremony is about to begin.)
(All graduating students,)
(please gather in the auditorium.)
Jiaxu, you should go ahead.
I'll go and find my brother
by myself.
It's okay. I'll take you there.
I'll text your brother.
Come on.
Duan.
Hey, Duan.
[Nanwu University Class of 2016 Graduation]
Come and join us.
Let's take a picture together.
Okay.
I'll go and take a picture with them.
Duan, who's this?
My sister.
Oh, hi.
Can you help us take a photo?
Okay.
Thank you.
Just press this.
Okay.
Come on, everyone.
Let's take a picture.
-Okay.
-This is it.
-Stand over here. Closer.
-Okay.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Good.
Okay. Thank you.
Jiaxu.
Professor Zhang,
thank you for your help.
I hope to see you shine and excel
in the gaming industry.
I'll do my best.
I believe in you.
Thank you.
Okay, guys.
I'm going inside first.
Okay.
Okay, Professor.
Duan,
participating in competitions
and research projects with you
at this university
was the most painful and happiest thing
for me in these four years.
Both painful and happy?
Yeah.
It sounded complicated.
Do you remember the time
we stayed up late every night
and could only eat instant noodles
when we were hungry?
It was so difficult at that time.
But it will all pay off.
Tomorrow,
I'll be returning to my hometown.
You're leaving tomorrow?
What about you two?
I'll probably leave tomorrow too.
I don't know
if we'll have a chance to meet again in the future.
It's okay.
There'll always be an opportunity to meet again.
I have to go inside first.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Okay.
Jiaxu,
does that mean
it'll be difficult to meet your classmates
after graduation?
I guess so.
How do I explain this to you?
We may take
the same course.
But after we enter society,
everyone
will make their own choice.
Gradually, we'll take
a different path.
Maybe
it'll be really hard to meet again.
Then,
what about me?
You?
You're not the same as them.
They
won't be like you,
who secretly gave me red packets
during the Chinese New Year
and even came to give me flowers
on my graduation day.
Don't worry.
After I leave,
I'll come back to see you whenever I have free time.
When
will you be free?
I'll let you know in advance
before I come back,
okay?
Zhou,
can you do me a favor?
Sure.
Help me take a photo with my sister.
Okay.
Hold this.
Here.
Look at the camera, both of you.
Okay, smile again.
♪I wipe off the dust because you're still there♪
-Happy graduation!
♪I hide my wish under a band of stars
like a clumsy kid♪
Enough. Don't drink too much.
You can't hold your drinks.
So don't drink too much.
♪The time difference♪
You two are inseparable again.
I have to ask clearly
about this matter today.
You two always stick together
and never find a girlfriend.
Forget about Sang Yan.
With this temper,
who would like him?
Xu, what about you?
Yeah.
Why didn't you get one?
♪Every inch of the wound is softly veiled
within the halo's radiance♪
What do you mean?
See?
That's why we're best friends.
Why?
Is it wrong?
♪Every night freezes into an eternal day
amidst the fireworks♪
Duan Jiaxu!
Am I not
both of your best friends?
How could you have a change of heart?
You are. Of course, you are.
Let him be. He's such a crybaby.
He's ignoring me.
It's okay. I'll take care of you.
Come here.
You're crying for real?
How can you cry for real?
Why are you crying when you're all grown up?
Can someone open a bottle for me?
Give it to me.
Thanks.
Xu,
come and have a drink.
Cheers!
Cheers, guys.
Happy graduation day.
We've graduated,
and you're drinking Coca-Cola?
You should drink beer.
I can't drink alcoholic drinks.
No, you can't.
You're spoiling the fun.
Come.
Give it here. Give it to me.
Okay, cheers!
Come on, guys.
There they go again.
So if you drink on his behalf, right?
Stop wasting time and drink up.
-Come on, drink.
-Cheers!
Okay!
Xu, drink up.
Don't stop drinking. You'd better finish it.
Are you leaving it for the whales
or the sharks, huh?
You think I won't finish it, huh?
I'll drink it first.
Listen.
Wait for a bit.
Before you drink, I want to ask you something.
Let me ask you first.
No, I'll ask you.
Do you have a crush on her?
Me?
Do you?
Let me finish this drink first.
Today is the last day.
It's the last day, right?
It's the last day.
If you don't spill,
I'm telling you,
you won't get another chance after this.
[Jiang Ying]
(I'm happy you're coming back to Yihe.)
(Happy graduation day.)
-What's wrong?
-Xu,
I can't bear to part with you.
Did you have too much to drink?
No.
Why are you sitting here alone?
He drank too much.
I did not.
You did. Stop denying it.
Come.
Let's drink.
Who turned Qian Fei
into this?
Come and drink.
Qian Fei, come here.
No, don't drink with him.
This will be our last time.
Come here.
Happy graduation day, guys!
Come.
Drink up.
You drank too much.
Jiaxu,
I want to ask you something.
When I'm no longer around,
who's going to watch over you?
Don't worry.
Many people are eyeing me.
Duan Jiaxu,
you and Chen Junwen
are going back to your hometown.
There will be only Sang Yan and me left in Nanwu.
I don't know
what's good about Yihe.
Why do you have to go back?
There, there.
Let's keep drinking.
You were loud earlier.
Look at you now.
You're right.
You're home.
Jiaxu,
will you be okay if you return to Yihe?
Promise me
you'll live well in Yihe.
Of course, I'll be fine.
Sit.
Jiaxu,
you must come
and visit us regularly.
I'll always come back.
Sang Yan,
you're home.
Mr. Sang, Mrs. Sang.
Duan, you're here too.
What's wrong? Did he drink too much?
We graduated today, so they had some drinks.
Why did he have to drink so much?
Thank you for taking him home.
Give him some water.
Okay.
I'll make some hangover soup
for him.
Okay.
Why did he push himself to drink so much?
Yan, have some water.
Slowly.
Then, I'll make a move first, Mrs. Sang.
Wait.
Where are you spending the night?
There's an inn nearby.
Don't waste money.
You can just sleep in Sang Yan's room.
It's okay.
Not at all.
Zhi, you're here too.
Duan will spend the night here.
So go and get him a towel
and toothbrush.
It's really okay, Mrs. Sang.
I can manage.
Stop rejecting.
Go upstairs now.
It's all right.
Are you feeling better now?
Then thank you for having me.
It's nothing.
Bring him upstairs.
Are you feeling better now?
You're such a little mischief. Go on now.
Okay, it's fine.
You don't have to worry about it. Let me handle it.
Okay.
Zhi, bring him upstairs.
Why did the kid drink so much?
Dear, is the soup ready?
Just wait a little longer.
Give him some more water.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Jiaxu,
do you want some hangover soup?
I don't drink alcoholic drinks.
So no need to go through the trouble.
It's already late. You should go to bed.
I'll sleep after taking a shower.
By the way,
your
towel and those things.
(Ladies and gentlemen, please pay attention.)
(Passengers traveling)
(to Yihe on Nanwu Airlines)
(on Flight NW413,)
(please proceed to Gate 8)
(for boarding.)
(Passengers traveling)
(to Yihe on Nanwu Airlines)
(on Flight NW413,)
(please proceed to Gate 8)
(for boarding.)
♪I wipe off the dust because you're still there♪
♪I hide my wish under a band of stars
like a clumsy kid♪
(Jiaxu,)
(Happy New Year.)
♪When you adapt♪
♪The time difference♪
♪A fairy tale about the fallen Milky Way♪
♪Every inch of the wound is softly veiled
within the halo's radiance♪
♪Every night freezes into an eternal day
amidst the fireworks♪
♪You unlocked the hidden corners of my heart♪
♪I can no longer hide all those sweet thoughts♪
♪Growing up with you♪
♪Love is when butterflies spring from my eyes♪
♪And ripples of excitement
sprawling across my vision♪
♪A bright face under a calm disguising face♪
♪But I can't contain my joy♪
♪I have someone I really like♪
♪My heart jingles when I think of you♪
♪I wish I could read your mind♪
♪To check if my secret liking isn't unrequited♪