♪A beautiful place full of smiles♪
♪Where imaginations about you grow wildly♪
♪The winter sun is like your white teeth♪
♪Expecting your visit all day long♪
♪Like the light breeze
and the fragrance of flowers in May and June♪
♪Hesitate to embrace you and my words stumble♪
♪Time passes hurriedly,
leaving a photo of us and sunflowers♪
♪Too flimsy to be scrutinized♪
♪Welcome to my world and explore its beauty♪
♪I can offer you my clumsy gentleness♪
♪Welcome to my lonely island, too♪
♪Only fish and migratory birds have been here♪
♪Maybe I'm too clumsy and evasive♪
♪Tired of troubles,
all I want is to hide you secretly♪
[Hidden Love]
[Adapted from the novel Hidden Love by Zhu Yi]
[Episode 16]
[Watch on www.kisskh.co]
[Brother No.2]
(Did you like your gift?)
He's really thick-skinned.
He actually took such a picture
and asked me if I liked it or not.
(What's with that picture?)
[Sang Zhi]
(I can't see it clearly.)
(This gift is a defect.)
[Brother No.2]
(If you say yes to me,)
(I'll send you an HD version of it immediately.)
[Duan Jiaxu]
(Just you wish.)
(Initially, I wanted to use this)
(to hasten the courting process.)
(I never expected you)
(to reject me from the start.)
(I can only resort to this)
(to win a chance for myself.)
You old fox.
(You old fox.)
(I have to be)
(one step ahead)
(to deal with a young fox like you.)
(I'll go to sleep now.)
(Good night.)
[Brother No.2]
[Set Remarks and Tags]
[Suitor]
[Silly Dog]
[Happy birthday]
(Little demon,)
(you can buy whatever you want with that money.)
If you move it there,
the pool table will be blocked.
You see that?
Okay, boss.
(Yan,)
[Sang Yan, Sang Zhi]
(I might be getting into a relationship.)
(Did you attend university)
(to study or to get into a relationship?)
(Isn't it common to get into a relationship)
(during university?)
(Suit yourself.)
(Be careful. Don't get scammed.)
Yes, place the stool
over there.
That's right. Over there.
Yes.
(He's quite old.)
Hello?
Don't tell me he's older than me?
Lower your volume.
Where did you get to know him?
He...
He's a postgraduate student.
Listen.
You should study hard at your age.
Forget about getting into a relationship.
I won't accept it
even if he's one day older than me.
I cannot accept it
if he addresses me formally
when he's older than me.
Even if he's one day older than you...
Isn't it your gain when someone
older than you addresses you formally?
[Chapter 16: Feelings. Waiting for your date.]
A present from your "elder brother"?
If so, have you decided on
when to say yes to him?
Do I need to think about that?
Of course.
Since he said he wanted to court you,
you have to think about
how long you'll let him court you.
How long should it be then?
About that,
it depends.
I said yes to Chen Qiang not long after
he started courting me.
But it depends on you.
It's the best moment
when you think
it's appropriate.
I think right now is appropriate enough.
You're something else.
But, Sang,
you have to protect yourself,
understood?
Wei,
I'm a little worried.
Worried about what?
I'm just afraid that he's doing it on a whim.
Will he stop courting me when he's tired of it?
I don't think that's likely to happen.
You two
have known each other for a long time.
Since he has decided to court you,
that means he must be determined.
What do you think?
You have a point.
It'll be fine.
If you're worried about that,
you should test him.
I'll go to sleep now.
Come on, don't give in yet.
Here's your favorite.
Thank you.
Your Americano.
Coming.
Thank you, Wang.
Here's your latte.
Thank you.
Is that a new bracelet?
It looks great.
What are you saying?
It's a present from her "elder brother".
-A present from her "elder brother"?
-Really?
Come on. Let me take a look.
It's pretty nice.
This is?
Is that a mouse?
It's a fox.
A fox?
I couldn't tell.
A mouse?
He has good taste.
This one.
[Suitor]
(Are you free tomorrow?)
Did your suitor text you?
Wait.
What will you reply?
Let me reply to him for you.
Didn't we say
that we would test him?
It'll be fine. Trust me.
I'm not free. Send.
Stop messing around.
What do you know?
Sang and I
talked about this before.
Sang, am I right?
What did you guys talk about?
(I'm not free.)
[Sang Zhi]
Did he reply to you?
What about the day after tomorrow?
I might not
be free either.
(I might not)
(be free either.)
But
what if
he fails to meet the expectations?
That's impossible.
He'll definitely pass the test.
He'll definitely pass it.
Listen.
No one can say for sure when you test people
in a relationship.
Sang, you better think twice.
Let me ask you guys something.
If you asked
someone out
and she replied
that she might not be free,
is she free or not then?
She might not be free?
That means it depends on your performance.
Why don't I call him?
You don't understand.
This is the charm of love.
Understood?
Okay, okay.
Reply to him like that.
Wait.
Hold it in.
Just endure it for a little longer.
Have something.
You should have something first.
Don't meddle when you don't know anything.
That means she's free then?
Duan, look into my eyes.
Who is it?
Who might not be free?
Eat your food.
Don't be nosy.
Something's going on.
Here he is.
Look!
I told you already.
I knew he would reply to her.
What did he write?
Let me see.
(What about Thursday night?)
What about Thursday night?
Fine.
Since he has tried this for the third time,
let's give him a pass then.
Hurry.
Stop being pretentious.
Hurry up.
(That's fine.)
[Sang Zhi]
Do I look okay?
Yeah.
You look beautiful.
There's a new noodles shop on the street
to the right of our university.
I heard that it was pretty good.
Is that so?
Let's go there together.
You guys can go by yourselves then.
I...
Sure.
We'll do a taste test for you.
What noodles do you guys want to try?
I heard from Yuting
that their shrimp...
Sang Zhi.
Sorry about this.
What's the matter?
Why did you start with an apology?
It's like this.
There's a bug
in the system we developed.
So,
we're dealing with it urgently.
I think
I might not be able
to join you for a meal today.
Okay.
Will you work until very late?
Will you take dinner?
Do you want me to order something for you?
Why did the alarm sound again?
Duan.
Duan,
save us.
Lower your volume.
Hello?
You should get back to work then.
That's fine.
Don't worry about me.
Sorry about that.
Remember to take dinner, okay?
Okay.
Goodbye.
Done.
Looks like
I have to join you guys today.
Where's the shop?
It's to the right of the university's entrance.
You're all dolled up.
Are you sure you want to have noodles?
Can't I have noodles like this?
I guess so.
Let's go.
See you.
Goodbye.
She's so pretty.
Hello, Jiaxu?
Sorry.
You're apologizing again?
This time,
a colleague of mine
encountered some issues.
We have to change the program
and add more functions to it.
I guess you don't have a choice.
If so,
you can call me when you're free then.
You're not upset, aren't you?
Once I'm done here,
I'll take you out for some good food.
I'll hang up first.
(Didn't he say that he was going to court me?)
(Is he even trying here?)
I don't want it.
Wait for me!
I'll stop.
What's the matter?
Why did you come back?
You...
What are you doing here?
I thought you were going on a date?
Yeah.
You scared me.
He canceled the date.
Didn't he say he wanted to court you?
Do you know how many times he has stood you up?
It doesn't look like he's trying to court you.
He's busy with work.
He didn't do it on purpose.
So what if he's busy with work?
Don't tell me he has no time for you at all?
I'm sure he has time before
and after work.
I'm sure he has time
to see you if he wants to.
Precisely.
But he's really busy.
He's so busy that he has no time
to sleep.
It's already curfew
when he comes after work.
Why are you still defending him?
Sang,
don't you blame him?
It's fine.
I'm utterly speechless.
I can't just teach him
how to court you.
Sang,
did you not have dinner?
Are you hungry?
Oh, yeah.
Where's the leftover food we packed...
It's delicious.
That's right.
We packed some fruit too.
They're delicious.
Here. Take it.
You haven't had dinner, right?
Take a sniff. It's nice...
Don't eat that first.
You should finish the hamburger first.
Let me have some fruit first.
Don't.
You shouldn't have the fruits first.
But why?
You see,
the hamburger will spoil
if you keep it until tomorrow.
You should finish this first.
It'll fill up your tummy.
Have this.
Take a sniff. It smells great.
Currently,
the character modeling
is basically completed.
Regarding that,
we actually
optimized the fluidity
of the characters'
techniques.
Currently,
we've basically
optimized
everything there is.
There's no issue for now.
Yes.
I'm sure everyone knows
how much Jia Yang has improved.
You flatter me.
It's been tough on you guys.
Our optimization
has proved
to be effective.
So,
I would like to congratulate you guys.
We don't need to work overtime today.
Let's go back and rest.
We can finally get off work on time.
[Nursing Home]
This won't do.
What are you drawing?
Sang.
Why are you back again?
Don't tell me he canceled the date again?
I was stood up again today.
Wait, what?
How many times has he stood you up?
Was it work again?
It's not work this time.
However,
I didn't ask him about it.
And I don't bother doing so.
Does it count as courting
when he doesn't take her out for dates?
Of course not.
What is he doing?
All right.
It'll be fine.
Even if he's not here for you, we're here for you.
We'll keep you company.
Yeah.
Let's grab some coffee.
No.
I don't
feel like going out today.
Come on.
-Let's go.
-No.
You have to.
No thanks.
You have to go.
Let's go.
[Jianfa Yibai Nursing Home]
(Mr. Duan,)
your father isn't doing well
lately.
I see.
Dr. Yang, thank you.
He has been bedridden for nine years.
His health and immunity
are subpar.
His pulmonary edema
is getting worse lately.
I suggest you take him to the hospital
for surgery
to remove the excess water in his lungs.
If not, an infection
might occur.
It'll be worse by then.
Do you think
he can regain consciousness?
Miracles will happen
as long as he's still alive.
If so, Dr. Yang, please deal with
the hospital transfer procedures for me.
I'll make a move first.
Okay.
Jiaxu!
Mom, look.
It's snowing today.
Call your dad.
Why isn't he back yet?
Didn't we say we were going
to celebrate your success
for getting 1st place in the city's
physics contest?
I'll ask him.
Don't eat it yet.
How is it?
He didn't pick up.
Call him again.
Dear, you're back.
Dad.
What's the matter?
Did you take alcohol?
I'm done for.
What do you mean?
Dad, what's the matter?
I crashed into someone.
Where did it happen?
At the hamburger shop on Renmin Road.
How is that person doing then?
You see,
no one saw it.
I drank.
I can't afford to call the cops.
Duan Zhicheng!
Have you lost your mind?
How could you drive after drinking?
Are you out of your mind?
What were you thinking?
Jiaxu!
Don't call the cops.
Don't call them.
Dad, listen to me!
We have to save that person!
It'll get worse
if something happens to him!
Dad, you can't escape from this.
Dear,
go and turn yourself in.
We'll figure something out together.
I don't want to go to jail.
Dear, go and turn yourself in.
Jiaxu!
Dear!
A car accident happened outside
the hamburger shop on Renmin Road!
Please save him!
Go and turn yourself in!
Dad!
Dear!
(Dear!)
You're back.
Why are you still awake?
You're making that again?
You came back late too.
Look at the time.
Did you skip dinner again?
I wasn't hungry. I was waiting for you.
I brought back some noodles for you.
You should put that aside.
Let's have dinner together.
You're wasting your money again.
They don't cost
that much.
Let me finish this first.
-Let's eat first.
-Okay.
Try this.
I heard from my colleagues
that this restaurant was pretty good.
Here.
Other kids are enjoying themselves
after the college entrance exam.
But my son has to do two jobs
right after the exam.
And you work from morning until night.
It's because I'm young.
Young people should endure more hardships.
By the way, Mom,
I told
my boss
about the advance.
But he told me
that I could only take
half a month's worth as I'm a newcomer.
But that's fine.
I'll think of something else.
Just let me handle this.
I'll try to borrow money from our relatives.
You should stop borrowing money from them.
I'm serious.
Mom, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
After giving it some thought,
I think I won't attend university in Nanwu.
Right now, earning money is more important.
That won't do.
You have to attend university.
You see,
our family is in huge debt.
There's no need for me to attend university.
I will work in the morning
and do part-time jobs
at night.
We'll be able to repay the debt eventually.
You mustn't
let our mistakes
affect your future.
But you know that...
No buts.
You have to attend university.
If not,
don't call me Mom.
Mom, what's wrong?
I'm fine. Maybe it's because I skipped dinner.
My tummy
is protesting.
How many times have I told you this?
You can't just skip your meals.
I'll get you some water.
Mom, time to eat.
Are you done with the discharging procedures?
You're not going to be discharged.
What are you doing?
Sit down and rest.
Mom,
you don't need to be discharged.
I managed to borrow 30,000 yuan
from my university friend.
You can stay here
and recuperate.
Jiaxu,
I feel much better now.
I feel like going home.
I'm serious.
You should return the money to your friend.
I already borrowed it from him.
Your health matters the most.
Rest well.
Son,
are you not tired
of owing other people money?
We cannot stand with our heads up high
until the day we finish repaying our debt.
I don't want you to be burdened
by this.
Mom, don't worry.
I can earn back
the money in the future.
Don't overthink it.
Now,
you should have your meal, okay?
I brought you some...
I'm begging you!
Can you please return the money to him?
We haven't finished repaying our debt yet.
And we still need to
take care of Ying and her mother.
We can't afford to borrow money from other people.
What if I die
and the debt is not repaid?
What will you do then?
Mom, you won't die.
What are you saying?
(What are you doing?)
[Sang Zhi]
[Duan Jiaxu]
(I just reached home.)
Hello, Jiaxu?
What's the matter?
What are you doing right now?
I'm in the dorm.
I'll go and see you.
Right now?
It's 8:30 PM.
We still have three and a half hours
before your curfew time.
Okay then.
I'll take you out for supper.
What do you want to have?
I'm fine with anything. I'm not hungry.
I'll...
Wait.
Don't wait.
Wait, I...
Hurry up.
What are you busy with lately?
Plenty of things.
I had lectures to attend,
assignments to finish,
and
a drawing exhibition to hold.
I was busy with my club too.
And I was waiting for someone to ask me out.
Lately...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to stand you up.
There are just too many messy things
happening around me lately.
Messy things?
Those are just trivial affairs.
They're not important.
If so, why didn't you
ask me out then?
I didn't know
that you wanted me to ask you out.
Are you upset?
That's not it.
I feel like
you're upset.
Were you burned out from working too much?
That's impossible.
I'm finally having a meal with you
after so long.
I'm elated.
I'm serious.
If so,
give me a smile.
Wait here.
Where are you going?
♪How do I describe this feeling?♪
Hello.
Can I make one?
Hi.
You want to make one?
I'd like to have a try.
Thank you.
It's pretty difficult.
Like this?
♪I once tried to hide it♪
♪The love that's hidden within time♪
♪The starry sky shining
upon the past and future♪
♪You'll walk toward me one day♪
Cut it for me.
Okay.
♪A crystal clear presence♪
Take your time.
♪Until a long time ahead♪
Make it lower.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
You want cotton candy?
I'll pay you later.
Okay.
This is for you.
It's for me?
It's as if you're coaxing a child.
Yeah.
I'm coaxing an old child.
When I was upset in the past,
I would be happy after having something sweet.
Do you want to give it a try?
I'll try it.
Is it sweet?
It's very sweet.
Thank you.
♪I was once lost in the dark♪
♪Dawning upon countless expectations♪
It's my first time
being coaxed like this.
♪Facing the light and walking toward me♪
Do you want to try it?
♪A crystal clear love♪
♪The past, the present, and always♪
Is it sweet?
♪You're the only one I wish for♪
It's sweet.
You're pretty good
at making cotton candy.
Did you make it for someone else before?
No, I didn't.
So, I'm the first person
who tried the cotton candy you make, huh?
Yeah.
I understand what you mean now.
What do you mean?
I understand now.
What do you understand?
You agreed, right?
You agreed to be my girlfriend.
Since when did I agree to that?
Why would someone make cotton candy
for an ordinary friend?
Ordinary...
And
you're wearing the bracelet I bought for you.
Jiaxu,
you...
You should stop being deceitful.
You won't be able to win my heart like this.
How can I win your heart then?
You can
surf the Internet
or ask other people
about it.
You should ask other people how to woo a girl.
How do I woo a girl then?
Must you ask me?
Can you teach me?
Anyway,
listen.
If we only
text each other,
call each other occasionally,
and meet each other
after a long time,
that definitely
won't do.
It's not online dating, you know?
Do you know how old you are?
Speaking of online dating,
I was suddenly reminded of something.
Someone was...
All right, that's enough.
That's enough.
Great job.
Please don't bring that up again.
I was just joking with you.
I'm serious.
Today,
I realized
my mistakes.
From today onward,
I will
be serious
and work hard
to court you.
I'm serious.
Great.
I will
look forward to your performance.
Are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow morning?
I'm not free tomorrow morning.
I need to be at uni.
You still have lectures during the weekends?
That's not it.
An alumnus
is going to do a sharing session for us.
But...
I see.
But in the afternoon...
I guess I'll work overtime
tomorrow then.
It's fine.
I will work hard.
I said "But" loudly, didn't I?
Don't tell me he didn't hear me.
I'm looking forward
to this sharing session.
We should tell them to come.
All right.
I'll text them
right now.
Let's sit here.
Okay.
You should
text them right now.
I'll ask them on WeChat.
Sang,
I can't see
the blackboard clearly over here.
I'll sit in front.
Morning.
What's the matter?
[Future Career Plan]
Who's that guy
beside Sang?
Is that her boyfriend?
I don't know.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say
that there was a sharing session today?
Yeah.
That's why I inquired about the time
and location.
Don't you need to work today?
I'm taking time off in lieu.
So,
are you going to keep me company?
What are you saying?
We just met by coincidence.
Coincidence?
You've graduated from university
for almost two years.
And now, you're meeting
a freshman like me by coincidence?
Look at your getup.
Do I look young?
It's pretty good.
If so, I'll stick to this style, then.
Sang Zhi's boyfriend
keeps staring at her.
He's so gentle.
(Why is he staring at me?)
(Maybe I should pretend to be asleep.)
I feel sleepy all of a sudden.
♪I have someone I really like♪
It's not time yet. I'll take a nap.
♪My heart jingles when I think of you♪
Why are you sleepy now that I'm here?
That's not it.
I'm sleepy no matter if you're here or not.
Go ahead then.
Go to sleep.
(This kid is pretending to be asleep.)
[Sang Yan]
(I think my sister seeing someone.)
(She's all by herself out there.)
(Keep an eye on her.)
(Make sure she doesn't get cheated.)
(Okay.)
♪My universe is hidden somewhere♪
♪No one can figure out with the glass in between♪
♪Which planet♪
♪Your name is engraved on♪
♪I'm like a balloon
that is quietly getting lighter♪
♪My worries are running away from my mind♪
♪Silently floating around you♪
♪As I get closer to you♪
♪A lime-scented breeze blows♪
♪My fingertips♪
♪Pass by your cuffs♪
♪Completing a secret love tour♪
♪Could I see you one more time?♪
♪Let my heartbeat have one more second♪
♪It's so strange that my gaze♪
♪Always follows you around♪
♪Could I think of you one more time?♪
♪Feeling the unstoppable excitement♪
♪Like the first snow waiting for a clear sky♪
♪I've been waiting for your appearance♪