♪A beautiful place full of smiles♪
♪Where imaginations about you grow wildly♪
♪The winter sun is like your white teeth♪
♪Expecting your visit all day long♪
♪Like the light breeze
and the fragrance of flowers in May and June♪
♪Hesitate to embrace you and my words stumble♪
♪Time passes hurriedly,
leaving a photo of us and sunflowers♪
♪Too flimsy to be scrutinized♪
♪Welcome to my world and explore its beauty♪
♪I can offer you my clumsy gentleness♪
♪Welcome to my lonely island, too♪
♪Only fish and migratory birds have been here♪
♪Maybe I'm too clumsy and evasive♪
♪Tired of troubles,
all I want is to hide you secretly♪
[Hidden Love]
[Watch on www.kisskh.co]
[Episode 8]
Go upstairs and get changed.
It's all right.
Yan,
how's your sister?
She's okay.
Let's talk to her
over dinner later.
We don't have to.
She knows she made a mistake.
She cried all the way back.
I scolded her just now too.
I think she had enough for one day.
Do you think she's...
Duan Jiaxu said
that guy never promised her anything.
It was her wishful thinking.
With
her proud personality,
if she said it's over, it's really over.
She would see it through.
Think about it. Since she was little,
as long she said
she would stop bingeing animations,
she would stop.
Have we seen her keeping
any plush toys that she dislikes?
You're right about that.
It's the rebellious phase of youth.
It's normal to rebel once.
How
about not nagging at her then?
Okay.
When we have dinner,
let's pretend nothing happened.
We'll pretend as if she came home
from school as usual.
We need
to keep her ID card
and pay attention
to what she does online.
We also need to take back her phone.
Yes, we have to confiscate her phone.
Later,
bring this cold medicine upstairs
to her.
She wore a short skirt.
Don't let her catch a cold again.
Okay.
[Yihe University]
(Jiaxu,)
(I've finally found)
(my dream.)
(I want to go to Yihe University.)
(Jiaxu,)
(see you again.)
[November, 5th. Saturday]
[See you again, Jiaxu]
(So I've fulfilled my dream)
(and been admitted into Yihe University.)
(I started)
(a new life here.)
(I've attended military training,)
(and now attending my lectures.)
(I've also made new friends)
(and lovely roommates.)
Hello, everyone.
Welcome
to my vlog.
Today,
I want to show you
the most beautiful view
of my university.
So what could it be?
(Hello and sorry about that.)
Hi.
He's so handsome.
So proud.
(On my side)
(is our lecture building.)
(Let me show you around.)
(Let's see)
(who's that cool girl!)
This is Yu Xin,
the coolest girl on our campus.
(I didn't expect)
(her first appearance in my vlog)
(would be in such an embarrassing state.)
(How can I not fall when you ran toward me?)
(Delete it.)
Oh,
sorry about that.
I'll go and check on her.
Miss, are you okay?
Yeah.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Why are you carrying
so many books alone?
My classmates are all busy.
So I'm helping my lecturer to borrow some books.
Where are you going?
I'll help you send these books.
The Digital Media Department is ahead.
Let's go then.
Thank you.
Sang!
Where's Wang?
Wang?
Let me show you my best friend.
She's over there.
Hi, guys.
Who's this?
He's someone
who just...
Hi, I'm Jiang Ming.
I'm from the Sports Department's
long-distance running team.
I'm here to carry these books for her.
So you're from the Sports Department.
We're from the Digital Media Department.
We're all roommates.
Hello.
Anyway, we all know each other.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Tomorrow happens to be my birthday.
You can invite your friends
from the Sports Department
to join the celebration together.
Sure, no problem.
Let me scan your QR code.
Sure, here you go.
Come on, guys. Scan his code.
She can forward it to us later.
Okay, I'll forward it to them later.
Then
you can send me
the time and location.
No problem.
I'll take over. Thank you for your help.
But...
It's okay.
Why don't you walk her?
Go with her.
Okay. Then...
It's that building.
Okay.
Then we'll get going.
-Bye-bye.
-Yeah, go ahead.
Bye-bye.
Don't forget to come tomorrow.
Remember to invite those
from the Sports Department.
Cut it out, will up?
What are we having for lunch?
Anything will do.
Can you keep up with us?
No.
Oh, yes you can.
This place is pretty spacious.
Yes.
I think my lipstick is too bright.
Let me wipe some...
No.
I think it looks very pretty.
I thought
you weren't wearing any lipstick today.
This is the latest
and most trendy color this year.
Anyone who wears it looks pretty.
Just look at her complexion
still can't be compared to mine.
Hey, Ning Wei.
Hi, Jiang Ming.
Hello.
This is my teammate, Chen Qiang.
Hi.
These guys are my classmates and juniors
from the Sports Department.
-Hello.
-Hi.
These guys are my other good friend
from the club I joined.
-Hello.
So many people here.
This is the birthday girl, Ning Wei.
These are her roommates.
-Happy Birthday!
Thank you so much.
Since everyone is here, let's head inside.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Let's go inside.
Sang,
today is my first birthday party
at university.
The first one?
How do you want to celebrate?
I want
to eat well, have fun, and then party.
Control yourself.
[Chapter 8 Re-encounter
Say see you again before meeting again]
♪The restless traveler♪
♪Thinking that...♪
-Duan.
-Sit here.
Why are you late?
-I had to go to the washroom.
-Sit down.
Duan,
let me introduce you.
She's my best friend, Xu.
She works in a foreign company's
Human Resources Department.
She happened to be eating nearby today.
So I asked her
to join us.
This is Duan Jiaxu,
the chief programmer of our company.
Young and promising.
Isn't he handsome?
He is indeed handsome.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Stop being awkward. Come.
Let's have a drink.
We're all friends after a drink.
I know you don't drink.
We know you don't drink.
Thanks, bro.
Let's all have
a drink together.
Cheers.
Cheers to Xu.
-Here.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
Dear,
what's the title of the song
that
we just dueted?
It's called
"It's like falling into a sea of love."
Ah, yes. That's the one.
Don't just stand there.
Pick this song. Pick this.
Skip the rest.
Duan,
our companies are nearby.
You guys can meet up for coffee if you have time.
Okay.
It's been a long time since I heard you sing.
Sing one for me.
The song is playing.
Xu, why don't you sing too?
♪I want to live in your heart♪
♪We are all happy fruit people♪
♪You are also happy fruit people♪
♪They are also happy fruit people♪
What do you usually like to do?
What do you usually enjoy doing?
Read comics.
Do you have any recommendations?
It depends on
what type you like.
Do you like outdoor activities?
Like hiking?
No.
What about the amusement park?
No, I don't like it.
Next time, do you want to...
It's my birthday today.
Why are you three
sitting here dating?
Hurry up and sing and dance for me.
Go quickly.
Hurry up.
Wei, happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
I'm going outside for some fresh air.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Sang Zhi?
Did you start smoking?
I don't smoke. That's not mine.
I clearly saw it fall
from you.
You've learned all the bad stuff.
I'm confiscating it.
No.
I told you
it belongs to my friend.
They may have misplaced it.
If you don't return it to me...
You even drink.
Just a little.
I'll put the rest aside.
It's been so long, and you didn't even greet me.
Jia... Jiaxu.
Did you come here to have fun?
My roommate is celebrating her birthday.
When did the military training end?
It ended in mid-September last month.
There were seven days of holiday for National Day.
Why didn't you come and look for me?
I had classes.
You had classes during the holidays?
My mistake.
I went for a part-time job.
I see, part-time job.
Yeah.
I used to have part-time jobs too.
Other than working part-time,
I had to meet your teacher,
do your homework,
and send you to school.
Ungrateful thing.
This kiddo has no conscience at all.
Well, it was okay.
Jiaxu,
you were in your fourth year.
I'm only in my first year.
Maybe I'm just
a little busier than you.
Are you attacking my age now?
Sang Zhi,
take a moment and reflect.
What exactly
did I do wrong to you?
I never said that.
Also,
I'm a grown-up now.
If you keep calling me a "kiddo,"
don't you think
it's a little
awkward?
How much can you grow?
You're still a kiddo.
Yes.
I'm still a kid.
Two years...
After two years,
you've indeed grown older
and weathered.
Sang Zhi,
check your phone and see
how many messages I sent you.
You didn't reply even once.
Why?
It's what I told you before.
I have classes.
Do you need to isolate yourself
from the world during classes?
Of course, I have to isolate myself
from the world.
If I didn't,
how else could I get into Yihe University?
Fine.
It's past nine, and you're still not going back.
I'm leaving soon.
Pack your things. I'll send you back.
It's okay.
I can go back
with my friends.
That'll work too.
Sang Zhi,
it's been so long since I last saw you.
You've learned how to put on makeup.
You're indeed different from before.
Okay, okay, this looks good.
Don't move.
Okay, change your pose.
I'll take one of you and the cake.
Sang!
Where were you?
-Everyone is waiting for you.
-Yeah.
We're about to cut the cake.
I'm so sorry.
Come on, everyone. Gather around.
Come here.
Time to cut the cake.
-Light it.
-Light the candle.
Take the picture.
Take a picture first.
Wait, hold on.
Three, two, one!
♪Happy Birthday to you!♪
♪Happy Birthday to you♪
Make a wish.
Okay, here I go.
It's recording now.
-Happy Birthday!
Time to cut the cake.
Let's move the cake over there.
There's more space there.
Wei, what time are we leaving?
I reserved this room
until 11PM.
Why?
Eleven o'clock?
My mom will call me.
You're right.
I almost forgot.
Why don't you go back first?
How long will you guys be here?
We won't stay too late.
In any case, you should go back first.
Just in case, your mom calls.
Okay, I'll go back first.
Don't stay out here too late.
Don't worry.
I'm going back first.
Remember to text us.
Stay safe.
Be careful on your way back.
Come back early.
Okay.
Take care.
Bring the leftovers for me.
Just leave.
Bring more.
Remember to text us when you arrive.
Be careful.
(I'm a grown-up now.)
(I'm no longer a kid.)
How much can you grow?
You're still a kiddo.
That old thing.
Did you scold me?
It should be me.
I'm the only "old thing"
you met tonight.
I wasn't talking about you.
Then who did you mean?
I just...
Just casually talking.
So tell me
who made you say that?
I'd like to know too.
Jiaxu, the thing is,
you don't have to be nosy about it.
Wait.
Didn't you say
you're going back with your friends?
Let's go.
Let this "old thing" send you back to campus.
Are you still cold?
No.
Jiaxu,
where's your house?
Wenting Garden.
Near the city library.
That's in the opposite direction
of my campus.
You have to take a big detour.
Actually,
I could go directly to the metro station.
Then...
Young lady,
I
wanted to settle a score with you
while sending you back.
Actually...
Actually,
that term
is considered civilized
in the young people's vocabulary
I think
it's not considered offensive, right?
How much did you drink tonight?
One bottle.
When you go out,
you should be more careful.
When you're out with strangers,
you shouldn't drink any alcoholic drinks.
They're not entirely strangers
We're from the same university,
just different departments.
Besides, my roommates were around.
I know.
I was just reminding you.
Why don't
we talk for a bit?
Why
do I feel you have something against me,
kiddo?
I don't like it when you call me that.
Kiddo,
I'm indeed five years older than you.
And after you're married,
your parents
will still think you're a kid.
So you want to be my dad?
It's just...
I mean
I'm already a grown-up.
So
if you keep calling me that,
I'll feel very uncomfortable.
Okay.
I get it.
Jiaxu,
what are you working as now?
Yan said you're a programmer.
Yes,
I'm a game developer.
Game developer?
I have a roommate
who's very good at playing games.
What's the name of the game you developed?
I can ask her.
"Tales of Adventures."
By the way,
I just remembered something.
Did you choose Yihe University
because of your old online friend?
Did you?
No.
No?
It's not because of that.
It's because Yihe University's
digital media program
is the best in the country.
And my scores were good enough.
So of course I came to Yi University.
I talked to your brother on the phone before.
He seemed to be quite angry
about you coming to Yihe University.
I thought
it was because of that old online friend.
No, it's not.
I...
I... I've...
I haven't been in contact with him
for a long time.
I'm glad to hear that.
My brother was angry
because I didn't tell him
when I applied to the university.
But I did tell my parents,
and they supported me in coming
to Yihe University.
I don't know what kept him busy.
He didn't ask me anyway.
So I didn't tell him.
I thought he didn't care.
But after I applied,
he criticize me
and argue with me.
So of course, I argued back.
Besides...
Besides, I'm an adult now.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah,
Sang Zhi is all grown up now.
(But you still see me)
(as a kid.)
You came all the way here
by yourself
to attend university.
If you have any difficulties in the future,
you can come to me,
understand?
I was just joking
with you earlier.
I know
people your age
have your own things to do.
It's very normal.
I really didn't think you had no conscience.
But you did call me an "old thing."
How is that not considered offensive?
A young lady
should speak more politely.
Sorry.
I won't say that again.
It's good that you realize your mistake.
When you have free time in the future,
you can come and find me to have a meal.
Is it here?
Go back and make some honey water to drink.
Or else you'll wake up tomorrow with a headache.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
By the way,
I've been all by myself here.
So when I heard your brother say
you're coming to study at the university here,
I was really happy.
Okay, go inside.
I'll head inside then.
Jiaxu, see you again.
Good night.
♪I'm like a balloon
that is quietly getting lighter♪
♪Transparent worries are running away♪
♪Silently floating around you♪
♪As I get closer to you♪
♪A lime-scented breeze blows♪
♪My fingertips♪
♪Pass by your cuffs♪
♪Completing a hidden love tour♪
♪Could I look at you one more time?♪
♪Let my heartbeat steal a second♪
♪How strange is my gaze♪
♪Always circling around you♪
♪Can I think of you a little more?♪
♪Feeling the unstoppable excitement♪
♪Like the first snow waiting for a clear sky♪
♪Waiting for your appearance♪
♪Facing the fox plush toy on the bedside♪
♪We've hidden the exchanged secrets
for a long time♪
♪Letting it remain untold, preserving this story♪
♪As I get closer to you♪
(By the way,)
I've been all by myself here.
So when I heard your brother say
you're coming to study at the university here,
I was really happy.
♪Completing a hidden love tour♪
♪Could I look at you one more time?♪
♪Let my heartbeat steal a second♪
(Why would he)
(be alone here?)
(Isn't his home in Yihe?)
(And)
(what about his girlfriend?)
[Jiaxu]
(If you go back to the campus late next time,)
(find someone to accompany you.)
♪In my secret universe♪
♪You were the one who stole my heart♪
♪Every inch of my heart♪
♪Revolves around you♪
♪My whole world twinkles in your name♪
[Sang Zhi]
(Okay.)
♪Could I see you one more time?♪
[Jiaxu]
(Sang Zhi,)
(check your phone and see)
(how many messages I sent you.)
You didn't reply even once.
♪Joy I can't hide♪
Don't you find
Chen Qiang from the Sports Department
a little strange?
He always looks at me and laughs foolishly.
The Sports Department has Jiang Ming.
A cheerful and warm guy.
Is he strange?
Well, he's not strange.
But Jiang Ming likes someone else.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Is there?
I don't know.
I know.
I didn't drink a lot.
Yan,
can you stop yelling at me?
What's so funny?
Sang.
After you left last night,
Jiang Ming kept asking
if it was safe for you to come back alone.
He's quite a nice person.
Did he contact you?
I haven't read my text messages.
[Jiang Ming]
(If you go back to the campus late next time,)
(I can accompany you.)
[Jiaxu]
(If you go back to the campus late next time,)
(find someone to accompany you.)
What did he send you?
Show me.
What did he say?
He didn't say anything.
Is there something
that you can't share with the girls
from dormitory Room 202?
Well, there is actually something.
But it's not about me.
It's about my friend.
Okay, a friend.
You see, this friend of mine
likes her brother's friend
when she was young.
After that, her brother's friend
started dating.
Then she gave up on him.
But they ran into each other lately.
So she doesn't know
what to do.
Brother's friend, huh?
How much older is he?
It has been two years
since he graduated from university.
That would mean
he's about 24 to 25...
He's 24.
What is he working as?
My brother said
he's a game developer.
Game developer?
I'm good in that area.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Yu Xin,
have you ever heard
of a game called,
"Tales of Adventures?"
Well,
"Tales of Adventures"
is the most popular game this year.
And I'm playing it now.
Since you're not a gamer,
I need to recommend it to you.
This game
can be said to be
the hottest mobile game of the year.
Whether it's the characters, scenes,
or plot design,
you can say
they're all top-notch.
See that?
Your brother developed it?
That means your brother is impressive.
Wait a minute. This isn't the point.
The point is,
does he have a girlfriend now?
That's right.
Does he have one?
I don't think so.
You think?
So does your friend
still like him?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
Then it's easy.
If you like him, go for it.
If you don't, treat him as an ordinary friend
and chat when free.
What's the point of overthinking?
What is your friend
worrying about?
She's worried
if that brother
only sees her
as a younger sister.
So
how old was your friend
when she liked the brother?
It was in high school.
That's normal.
You were underage at the time.
If he likes you
at that time,
then he would be the one with issues.
Let's not interrupt.
Sang,
describe this guy
to us?
He's handsome.
Good grades.
He's very amusing when speaking.
He's...
What?
Very charismatic.
He's handsome and charismatic.
Then how did you two
know each other?
He's my brother's best friend.
He often comes to our house.
So that's how we got close.
Based on your description,
he definitely has a girlfriend.
It has to be.
Case closed.
You don't even know him.
Don't leave now.
Let's talk some more.
Wang, come on.
Time to get back to studying.
You guys are such mood spoilers.
Forget it.
I'll go and focus on my great endeavors.
Don't come back too late.
Okay.
Be careful.
Bye-bye.
Don't rush.
Welcome.
Excuse me, where's the honey?
Mister, it's on the last aisle.
Okay, thanks.
[Honey]
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
♪I can taste you whenever I'm breathing♪
♪Thinking that if you want me too♪
♪Love is when butterflies flutter in my heart♪
♪And ripples of excitement
sprawling across my vision♪
♪Tell me are you listening The world moving fast♪
♪Here's all secrets I hope you like that♪
♪Trying to hide the happiness under a calm face♪
♪But I can't contain my joy♪
♪I have someone I really like♪
♪My heart jingles when I think of you♪
♪I wish I could read your mind♪
♪To find out if you like me too♪
♪I'm falling in love with you♪