♪A beautiful place full of smiles♪
♪Where imaginations about you grow wildly♪
♪The winter sun is like your white teeth♪
♪Expecting your visit all day long♪
♪Like the light breeze and
the fragrance of flowers in May and June♪
♪Hesitate to embrace you and my words stumble♪
♪Time passes hurriedly,
leaving a photo of us and sunflowers♪
♪Too flimsy to be scrutinized♪
♪Welcome to my world and explore its beauty♪
♪I can offer you with my clumsy gentleness♪
♪Welcome to my lonely island, too♪
♪Only fish and migratory birds have been here♪
♪Maybe I'm too clumsy and evasive♪
♪Tired of troubles,
all I want is to hide you secretly♪
[Hidden Love]
[Watch on www.kisskh.co]
[Episode 2]
(Forget it, I'm not waiting any longer.)
(That's it if he's not coming.)
Liar.
Not doing anything to help.
Just the same as Sang Yan.
Liar.
Sang Zhi?
Get up.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Why aren't you speaking?
No one comes so late.
When should I come then?
My class ended at 4:20 pm.
It's way past that time.
I don't know.
Then,
I'll apologise to you.
Later,
I'll get scolded by your teacher in your place.
-All right?
-No need.
Let's go.
(Will he)
(appear today as well?)
Hello, Jiaxu.
Are you awake?
If you're late by too long,
you will
never find a girlfriend forever.
Do you...
I already reached.
I went to buy milk for you.
You ingrate.
You can't simply say stuff.
If I can't
find a girlfriend forever,
you are doomed.
Let's go.
Go and do your homework at the breakfast shop
in front.
Let's go.
Essay booklet.
[Essay booklet]
Start writing.
(I don't think he read it.)
Have you eaten breakfast?
I'll go and get some breakfast.
Do you have something nice?
[Cake Shop]
This is our latest
Red Bean Bun. Do you want one?
Sure.
Give me a bottle
of that.
Honey water?
Are you really not going to eat?
Do you need anything else?
This too.
Yes. One of these.
♪But I can't contain my joy♪
Okay.
How much?
♪I have a weird intuition♪
Just scan the QR code.
♪To check if my secret liking isn't unrequited♪
Later,
the teacher will complain to you.
You just need to
agree with him.
I'm experienced in this.
Oh,
don't say anything else later.
If you get caught
and we are exposed,
it'll be over.
Sounds very scary.
Be bold.
We are here.
It'll be fine.
I can do it.
Reporting,
Sir.
My brother is here.
Hello, Teacher.
I am Sang Zhi's brother,
Sang Yan.
Sang Zhi's brother?
Sir,
it's obvious he is my brother
since he is so good-looking.
Why is
Sang Zhi's brother coming today?
My parents...
Sorry, Teacher.
It's like this.
My parents
have to go to the construction site
to have a meeting with the material supplier
so they called me here.
Recently,
we realised Sang Zhi has not been
very active in doing her homework
after going home
so we are here to learn more
about her situation.
You must help us.
Yes.
Come and sit here.
What's your name, Teacher?
I'm Chen.
Sang Zhi's
academic results
have no problem.
Her result
has always been
top of the class.
Her foundation
is also very good.
However, one still needs
the right attitude
in studying.
She cannot be proud.
Yes.
Right?
Her Mathematics...
Your brother is so tall.
Why are you so short?
What?
Is something wrong?
(All of them are linked.)
(If this lesson...)
Your class teacher can really talk.
His content
is always the same.
(The quality of study)
(and her mentality...)
Look at him go.
Look how obedient your brother is.
In study,
we must
grasp both aspects.
Sang Zhi's brother,
take a seat.
I can sit down myself.
Thank you, Teacher.
Sang Zhi's brother.
Actually,
I don't want
to trouble you to come to school.
No.
This is troubling you instead.
However, Sang Zhi
gives me a headache.
When I'm giving lessons,
she is drawing.
I called her up
to answer questions
because I wanted her
to focus on her studies
and attend lessons.
Yes.
In the end,
she stood up
and asked me where I was
as if she was right.
Tell me. How will her behaviour
help other students study?
That actually happened, Teacher?
Sang Zhi.
Come here.
How could you
talk to your teacher in that manner?
That's wrong.
You must respect the teacher.
Let's forget about this for now.
Last time,
I called your parents
because of Sang Zhi's issue.
Yes.
Was it your mother
or your father who came?
It was...
Your mother.
That's right.
Yes. Your mother.
I wasted a lot of
your mother's time.
Yes.
In the end, time was wasted.
But nothing changed.
Sang Zhi's brother.
When you go back,
you must tell your mother
about our conversation
without leaving anything out...
Your father!
Tell your father
so he can help
Sang Zhi's mentality.
Of course.
Sang Zhi
is very smart.
Her results
are outstanding.
No.
What is so smart about her?
She is top of her class
because you taught her well.
All of us know
Mr. Chen is an excellent teacher.
I've heard a lot about you.
Sang Zhi
has caused you trouble.
Hit and scold her as necessary.
No. I can't hit her.
It's fine.
If you are strict,
we will be relieved.
Yes.
The kid is smart.
All of us want her to be good.
Yes.
Right?
If she studies well,
I'm sure
she can go to high school directly in the future.
I believe
Sang Zhi will have a bright future
with Mr. Chen teaching her.
Sure.
This conversation
is very successful.
Go back.
Sure.
Apologise to Mr. Chen.
Goodbye, Mr. Chen.
Apologise.
Sorry.
♪My universe is hidden in somewhere♪
♪No one can figure it out through the glass♪
Do it well.
There's cake when you're done.
♪In that planet♪
♪I'm like a balloon
that is quietly getting lighter♪
[Asimov: The End of Eternity]
♪Transparent worries are running away♪
♪Silently floating around you♪
Do your homework well.
♪As I get closer to you♪
Why don't you drink the milk first?
It won't be nice when it's cold.
♪A lime-scented breeze blows♪
What's wrong?
♪My fingertips♪
♪Pass by your cuffs♪
You are
making it seem like I'm taking your food.
♪Completing a hidden love tour♪
Zhi.
Did you
get angry at me
because of my joke?
You just won't say anything.
I want to do my homework.
Fine.
Do it.
Jiaxu.
Are you from Nanwu?
No.
I'm from Yihe.
Yihe?
Then,
will you return to Yihe
during the summer holidays?
No.
Why not?
Why do you
care about that?
Well...
Do your homework.
♪Could I see you one more time?♪
♪I won't let courage lose to retreat♪
♪My hidden longing will become♪
♪Joy I can't hide♪
[Chapter 2 Get Closer.
What Made Me Meet Someone Like You]
[Xuri Middle School]
I'm going in.
Wait.
What is this?
I read your essay
so I wrote a new one
as compensation.
You...
You read my essay?
I wrote it for fun.
[A Stray Dog]
(When I saw this scene,)
(I stopped in my tracks.)
(My mood)
(was as bad as the weather.)
(When I realised the dog's face,)
(I became more upset.)
(I couldn't help but speak to it.)
(When I saw it,)
(it reminds me of my brother)
(because he looks exactly)
(like my brother)
(like they are made from the same mould.)
(It is like my brother's son.)
Sleep early.
-I'm going.
-What?
Last night...
[Helping Brother Move]
"Helping Brother Move."
Sang Zhi.
What is this?
It's nothing.
Nothing?
Is it a love letter?
No.
Yesterday's homework.
Homework?
It really is homework.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Sang Zhi.
Let's go.
One, two, three, four.
Enough, Fu Zhengchu. That's enough.
What a coincidence.
A coincidence, Fu Zhengchu?
You are dancing once every day.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I worked hard
to join this school
because I can
meet you...
Guys anywhere.
Sang Zhi.
Am I
not dancing well enough today?
I said it.
One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four. Rhythm.
Two, two, three, four.
Three, four. Rhythm.
I heard
there's an important day next week.
Do you want to know what day it is?
I don't.
It's my birthday.
Sang Zhi!
Next week is my birthday!
You must come!
It's your birthday next week?
I will think of a way
to ask Sang Zhi to come.
Really?
Leave it to me.
Then I...
Come together, Yin Zhenru.
Order anything you want.
Sure.
Zhi, do you know?
Just now, Fu Zhengchu...
Aren't you allergic to milk?
Why are you still drinking it?
I didn't say I will drink it.
Good morning.
Why did you buy it then?
Let's begin our lesson.
Attention.
Good morning, Sir.
Sit down.
Everyone, open page 17
of the textbook.
[Brother is a Pig]
"Helping Brother Move."
Today, I helped my brother move to his dorm.
My brother has many things.
I really don't know
why a guy like him
will have
so many useless things.
Dot dot dot.
Thankfully, I'm here to help him.
It's really childish.
It's like a primary school child wrote it.
Luckily,
the silver lining is
that I met my brother's housemate
that I've not seen for years.
Although he called me a thief
when we first met,
I know
he was only joking with me.
Where did this thief come from?
Since he
helped me before
and wanted
to help me again,
I won't hold any grudges this time.
I won't
call him old anymore.
I will still do that.
Also, the fox doll he gave
is not ugly at all.
Although...
I still
want a brother
like him.
As for my brother,
he can go anywhere he wants.
If you want him,
just take my brother away.
P.S.
The brother told me
he was very happy
to meet Sang Zhi again.
[DJX]
[I am Sang Zhi, Remark, Jiaxu]
[Remark, Duan XX]
[I am Sang Zhi]
Zhi.
Have some grapes.
What are you doing? Drawing?
You...
You can't drink milk.
I'm not drinking it.
Why do you have it then?
Well...
I think the bottle looks nice
I want to draw it.
You still can't take the milk.
I'll pour the milk.
I won't drink it.
Honey, you're here?
Dear, you're back?
She...
Well,
she has a bottle of milk in her room.
I don't know where she got it.
Zhi.
This weekend, your father and I
will be going to a friend's house
to attend his wedding.
Do you want to come with us?
No.
I'll ask Yan to accompany you then.
I don't want to be together
with Brother.
I'm worried
when you are alone at home.
I just don't want that.
Zhi.
What's the thing I always say?
Listen to your mother.
Don't let your mother worry.
I'll deal with
your brother.
Don't worry.
I will never let him bully you.
Otherwise, I'll cut
all his pocket money.
He won't listen to you.
I'll talk to him then.
Sure.
There's no problem with me around.
Enough drawing.
Come down and eat.
[Asimov: The End of Eternity]
[Pure Milk]
[17th September, Thursday]
[That guy told me]
[he was very happy to meet Sang Zhi again.]
Little Demon!
Why didn't you close the door?
Mom asked me to eat with you.
Little Demon!
Little Demon.
Is she in my room?
Little Demon!
Where is she?
Why didn't you answer me?
Who are you trying to scare?
Why should I answer?
Bring it here.
Give it to me.
I'm going to eat later.
Hotpot. Are you going?
No.
What do you want to eat?
Take a guess.
Little Demon,
when I was your age,
I had to cook my own meals
and even made yours
when Mom and Dad weren't home.
That was different.
How so?
Because you didn't
have a brother back then
but I do.
Cut it out.
Give it to me.
Hello.
You're not at the dorm?
Sure.
I'll go pick you up
at your workplace.
Half an hour.
Don't worry.
I won't forget about you.
Bye.
Brother,
who are you eating with?
Why do you care?
I even have to beg you to eat with me.
I'm going alone if you don't. Bye.
Hello, Mom.
Stop that.
Hello, Dad.
That's going overboard.
I was wrong!
That's right.
Right?
You should've just done that
instead of being naughty.
I'm telling you.
If you are obedient,
I'll let you eat anything. Let's go.
I'm going to pack up.
Two minutes.
Three minutes.
Fine. 30 minutes. Go on.
Help me grab my phone.
It's inside the fort.
You're still playing forts at high school?
Let me feel it.
Little Demon,
why are you so quiet?
Zhi,
are you happy to see me?
Me too.
Cut the nonsense. What are we eating?
Aren't we eating hotpot at the mall?
You won't treat me because it's expensive?
Do you think I'll complain about being expensive?
You always do that.
When did I?
(The roommate he is picking up)
(is Fei.)
Precious Dog!
-Wake up!
-Duan Jiaxu!
Hurry up! Sang Yan is treating!
Didn't you say ten minutes?
There was congestion.
Didn't you say you were hungry?
Hurry up.
What's wrong with you? So sleepy?
He's lying by my side again.
You're so sleepy.
Are you sacrificing your life for money?
Hurry up.
I'm starving to death.
(He's working so hard)
(yet I'm still always troubling him.)
(It shouldn't be. I've lost weight.)
Have you ever lost weight?
No. I weigh myself.
I did lose weight.
Why didn't you greet me
when I got in the car.
Hey, you.
You what?
Just you.
You are handsome.
No, you're not.
Am I not?
Then why did you blush
when you see me?
You're shameless!
You are always like this.
Sang Yan.
Do you remember
the last physical exam
when I ran 1,000 metres?
When I completed it,
I was out of breath
and this guy came over.
He asked me,
"Why are you blushing
when you saw me?"
I almost
fell in love with him.
You are a human.
He even speaks like that to a dog.
Zhi.
Ignore him.
He is not a good guy.
He is not a good guy indeed.
Why are you sowing discord?
Did I?
Zhi,
Did I sow discord?
I think
he isn't a good person as well.
I'm not a good person?
Fine.
I'm not a good person.
Don't you know that?
Duan still knows
he is bad.
How can you be good when you're so vicious?
All right.
Get off here.
I'm going to park the car.
Sure.
I'm starving.
Can I wait for a while?
What for?
Just a while.
I want to stay with you.
No. I can't park here.
Are you going to pay the fine?
No. I want to...
Are we going?
Take her.
Let's go.
Hurry up. I can't park here.
You are really annoying.
I can't stop here.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
A little.
I want to find a toilet.
Is it a stomachache?
Qian Fei.
It's almost time.
Go ahead.
Sure.
Let me find a toilet with you.
There's no need.
I can go on my own.
I'll go with you.
Well,
do you have any tissue?
It's fine.
Go inside and wait for me.
I'll buy it for you.
Go ahead.
(So,)
(he saw it?)
Pig's brain.
Did you order that?
Yes. I ticked it.
Do you eat it?
I do.
Chen Junwen just won't eat it
when he came here.
Hello.
We ordered everything.
Why are you still not here yet?
Your sister...
What's wrong with my sister?
Your sister is not feeling well.
What should I do?
Why are you asking me?
Buddy.
Help me out.
Help me buy it.
Buddy.
Is she your sister or mine?
It's not necessary for me
as a brother to care about this.
I've never cared
about this in the past few years.
Enough nonsense.
I'm at the supermarket.
Come down immediately.
Fine.
Buy it with me.
This one...
Go.
Nude S,
using it feels like...
Not so loud!
Then...
Buy the night-use one.
Sure.
This is 42.
Are the sizes different?
I don't know.
42.
Is 42
longer than 35?
Just buy the pocket packs.
Let's go.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Get a skirt.
She got it on her skirt too?
Yes.
This one then.
Wait.
She is wearing a dark-coloured skirt.
This is better.
Sure.
They are the same. Let's go.
(It's so embarrassing.)
(He saw it.)
Hello,
are you Sang Zhi?
Yes.
Someone outside
asks me to give this to you.
Thank you.
It's fine.
There are times like this
for girls.
Change it.
Thank you, Miss.
(How am I going to face him later?)
What's wrong?
It's embarrassing.
Who said so?
Let's go.
Time to eat.
Why are you angry? You're not a child.
Sang Yan.
Over here.
Why are you so late?
I dare not eat
before all of you are here.
She went to play claw machines
and wouldn't come back.
Did you not get any prize?
Yes. She cried as well.
You cried too?
I'll help you
after this.
It's not hard to get a prize.
Just use the claw
and spin it around.
Forget it.
You'll know when I show it
to you later.
I'll order a few more dishes.
Zhi.
Order some.
Tick a few dishes.
It's my treat.
Thank you.
It's all right.
What do you usually order?
What is nice here?
Order this.
Shrimp paste?
Forget it.
I ordered it.
Do you want it or not?
No.
It's prosperous.
Who eats black chicken while eating hotpot?
Order something expensive.
Eating chicken for a hotpot meal
and also in games.
[Chaoshan Beef Balls]
Know your own limits.
I don't want to remind you again.
Eating one is fine.
If something happens,
I won't take care of you.
What's wrong with
her ordering?
It's my treat and not yours.
Shut up.
She is allergic to beef and mutton.
Let's not eat it then
in case you get sick.
Give it to me.
Waiter.
Here. Help me
place this order.
Thank you.
Drink a glass of warm water.
Here.
Drink some wine.
I'm driving. I can't drink.
If no one drinks,
are we eating hotpot without drinking?
Can't you see this?
Iced tea with hotpot is the best combination.
Understand?
Yes.
I'm telling you.
I won't drink because I'm driving.
Fine. Just drink.
I'm telling you.
That day when you weren't in the dorm,
I played solo.
My stupid teammate was so useless.
Do you know how bad it was
to have that teammate?
I couldn't stand it.
Wait.
Let me eat first.
The three of us
were in a ranked match.
In the end,
I answered a call.
You even scolded me.
The day we almost won?
Yes. That day.
[Toilet]
Hello.
Can you help me
deliver this
to the female toilet?
There's a girl inside
who might need this.
Sure.
The girl's name is Sang Zhi.
Thank you.
It's all right.
Wait for
your sister here later.
I'm going to find Qian Fei.
Nonsense.
Wait for her together with me.
My sister is your sister.
Are you a fool?
Your sister will feel awkward
when she sees me
after what happened.
You are right.
You better think of an excuse as well.
If Qian Fei asks,
we won't know what to say.
Just say
she went to play with the claw machine
after she went to the toilet.
Sure.
Your gum.
Keep it for me.
♪I can taste you whenever I'm breathing♪
♪Thinking that if you want me too♪
♪Love is when butterflies spring from my eyes♪
♪And ripples of excitement
sprawling across my vision♪
♪Tell me are you listening The world moving fast♪
♪Here's all secrets I hope you like that ♪
♪A bright face under a calm disguising face♪
♪But I can't contain my joy♪
♪I have someone I really like♪
♪My heart jingles when I think of you♪
♪I wish I could read your mind♪
♪To check if my secret liking isn't unrequited♪
♪I'm falling in love with you♪