ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
COMPANIES, AND INCIDENTS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 8
What are you doing in front of my car?
Well,
I was worried about you.
So you just stayed here
and waited for me until now?
Happy birthday.
I hope you're never sick again.
Especially on your birthdays.
I don't remember
when my heart
started to flutter for him.
Neither do I remember
when the thought of him
and the memories we shared
started to fill my days.
I can't exactly remember
when my feelings for him
started to grow.
And the score is...
LOVE MATCH SCORE: 98
Lee Kang and Moon Cha-young
are a match made in heaven.
I approve of this marriage.
All right. Then now,
let's find out how good a match Kang is
with his lovely
future brother-in-law here.
How much money will he invest
in my future businesses?
And when will he hand down
that dream car of mine to me?
Here we go.
The score is...
RESULTS: 0
Lee Kang is the cop,
whereas Moon Tae-hyun is the thief.
Get caught, you'll be screwed.
What the hell? Screw you, scam.
Come on, seriously?
What kind of dumb prick
coded this messed up application?
NEW MESSAGE FROM GAMNARA5289
What? Who is this?
The pair of shoes
you posted about yesterday.
Did you actually buy it yourself?
Of course.
I bought it as a gift
for my girlfriend to thank her
for not leaving me for another guy
while I was in the military.
I brought it all the way from Pocheon,
and I treasure it with all my heart.
Can you give me a discount?
Unbelievable.
Trying to skin a flea
for its hide and tallow, are you?
Like I wrote in my post yesterday,
my girlfriend dumped me
on the day I bought these shoes.
They're brand new
and haven't even touched the ground,
but I'm selling them to you
for the price of soju
and some stir-fried octopus.
Then let's meet.
Can I pick the time and place?
Sure, whatever you want.
What a perfect day
to get me a shot of soju,
wash my feet, and go to bed.
Go find my hanbok and shoes.
Sun-sik bought them for me.
Go find them at once!
Why did she want to meet here
of all places? This is making me nervous.
Are you Oneshotatlife?
Gamnara5289?
-You brought it, right?
-Well, this is...
-Ms. Ha, I caught the thief.
-Why is this in my hands?
Open it.
Didn't you know they were stolen?
No, I didn't.
Yong-sun said she told you
she stole them from Suk-ja.
No, she didn't. I swear.
You fully knew that they were stolen,
yet you still posted them
on the online thrift store.
Come on, that's not even close.
If you don't believe me,
let me talk to those two ladies.
You can cross-examine the three of us.
Their son apparently bought
this hanbok and the pair of shoes
as a matching set as a gift for Suk-ja.
I want you to give them back
to Suk-ja yourself, Tae-hyun.
Don't tell her
about Yong-sun stealing them.
For God's sake.
I told you
I didn't get them from Yong-sun.
This is a sting operation.
You found my username
and surveilled an innocent civilian.
This is illegal!
If you do this again, I will sue you!
Give me the shoes!
I'll buy you stir-fried octopus.
The one on an iron griddle!
With fresh octopus, not the frozen ones.
The ones that get all stuck.
I just didn't want to burden you.
I wanted to set you free
as quickly as I could.
I regret that I ever liked you.
If you're ending your life this way,
then don't to be born again.
I made steamed croaker
for Hui-ju's lunch today.
She could only finish half of it,
but don't worry too much.
I'm not worried.
She has nothing to do with me now.
Please throw out the plate I gave you.
Thanks for everything.
Later on,
when you no longer regret
falling for Hui-ju,
please stop by at our cafeteria.
If I'm still working here,
I'll make you a warm bowl of rice
and a delicious doenjang stew.
Suk-ja won't eat because she's mad at me.
For dinner, I'll make doenjang stew
with snails, which she loves.
Yes, that'd be great.
And make rice cakes with raspberries too.
-Rice cakes with raspberries?
-Yes.
Suk-ja loves eating raspberry rice cakes
more than anything in the world.
Okay. I'll make that too, then.
Great.
Then I'll go get some raspberries.
Now? You'll go pick raspberries now?
Yes.
Ms. Bong!
It's Cha-young.
I'll come to you.
You shouldn't come here alone.
You'll get lost.
I'm not a fool.
I know. I'm the fool here.
Right.
I know that too.
-You knew?
-Yes.
Don't tell anyone that I'm a fool.
You have to keep it to yourself.
But the doctor knows that you're a fool.
-Who?
-The handsome doctor.
He said that you're a fool.
Don't worry though. I won't tell anyone.
Ms. Bong!
Hello? This is 911, right?
We have an emergency here.
I think she got bitten by a snake.
Yes, I gave her first aid.
Our exact location is...
Hello?
Dinnertime is almost over. Where is she?
She's not even picking up.
This way.
You're okay, right? Hang in there.
We're almost there. This way.
This will sting a little.
Here we go.
The pain will be gone soon,
so you don't need to worry.
But it looks like
you got proper first aid.
So someone who was hiking found her?
Yes. It could've been very dangerous,
Yong-sun.
She said she'd go get someone.
She told me to just wait there.
Who?
Cha-cha.
-Who?
-It must be Cha-young.
Cha-young!
I think something happened to Cha-young.
She called 911 at around 5:30 p.m.
But the call
got disconnected after a scream.
Cha-young!
Cha-young.
They're all mushy.
You went to the mountains
to pick these for me?
I thought
I wouldn't get to eat raspberries
this year.
Thanks to you,
I get to enjoy this delicacy.
You can't have them just yet.
Cha-cha said she'll make
rice cakes with them for you.
Rice cakes are great,
but these berries are so sweet.
They're delicious.
Have some.
No, it's okay. They're all for you.
I'm sorry.
If Sun-sik asks you to live with him,
don't say anything
and just go live with him.
Cha-young!
He doesn't dislike you.
Sun-sik is actually very fond of you.
Cha-young!
It's just that
he doesn't know it yet.
Cha-young!
He and I don't even share a drop of blood.
But he's still so sweet to me.
So why would he hate his own mom
who gave birth to him?
When we were young, I was mean to you,
and I was also jealous of you
like any other first wives would be.
But you still stayed glued to me
and followed me everywhere.
Because you have a heart of gold,
I was able to not get lost
and keep my focus thanks to you.
No.
I'm bad. You're the good one.
I'm mean.
You're a much better person than I am.
Everyone thinks
that the wife and the mistress
would hate and be jealous of each other,
and also fight all the time.
But we were never like that.
It was all because
you have a heart of gold.
And together,
we proved the prejudice wrong.
Cha-young!
In our next lives,
let's meet as something else.
We could meet again as sisters.
If we're born as a man and woman,
we could get married.
In our next lives, I'll do all the things
that I never got to do for you
in this lifetime.
I'll be
a lot more affectionate toward you.
Let's...
meet again no matter what.
I gave you first aid for now,
but the bones and ligaments
need to be looked at.
Let's do an X-ray.
We don't have X-ray facilities here,
-so let's find a hospital nearby with--
-It's okay.
Let's go to this one.
Get on my back.
Come on. Hurry.
It's really okay.
It doesn't hurt at all now.
-It really doesn't hurt?
-No, it doesn't hurt at all.
Then get up and try walking.
You said it doesn't hurt anymore.
Get up and walk, then.
What were you thinking?
Why are you so stubborn?
I'm a doctor. Won't you just listen
when I say you're hurt?
Also, what do you mean you're okay?
Go look at yourself in the mirror.
You're not okay at all.
Do you think I'm a joke
because I got kicked out of Geosung
and now work at this hospice?
Are you belittling me now?
If you're a chef, just make food.
Why must you follow the patients around
and cause trouble?
Do you know how worried I was
while I was searching the mountain?
I'll just stop caring altogether.
I won't care if you live or die,
so just do as you please.
Any pain or discomfort?
She's been
vomiting a little.
But other than that, she's okay.
Her BP is fine,
and so are her motor responses.
Then let's give her
some macperin starting this evening.
I heard you saved my wife.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Let me check your pupils.
Why don't we stop here?
She's not feeling the greatest.
I think she needs some sleep.
All right, sure.
Thank you.
Ms. Ha? It's me, Dr. Lee.
Could you send me
Kim Hui-ju's medical chart?
No, I just need to check something.
Please enjoy.
Grandma Fartsy.
Ms. Bong.
Here, I made the raspberry rice cake.
Please give it to Ms. Jang.
Director Kwon and the nurses
were all waiting to see Ms. Jang,
but I think they're busy now
as a new patient just arrived.
It's warm.
This will
keep her warm
even inside her grave, right?
I'm going to go
live with my son now.
That's great.
-Cha-cha.
-Yes?
Thank you for coming with me
to pick raspberries.
Suk-ja said
she thought she wouldn't get to eat
raspberries this year,
but thanks to me,
she really enjoyed them before she left.
Okay. I'm glad to hear that.
Are you done crying?
How long have you been here?
Before you came here.
Did you cry because of pain?
Did you fall down the mountain again?
No.
Thank you.
I think you said that like 37 times.
Aren't you going back to Greece?
What?
Didn't you once say
you're going back?
Oh, right. I...
I'm going to go back.
When?
Soon.
I'll leave soon.
If you're going to leave anyway,
shouldn't you just go as soon as you can?
This doesn't seem
the best job for you.
Aren't you going back to Greece?
What?
Didn't you once say
you're going back?
Oh, right. I...
I'm going to go back.
Yes?
I'm Yun Seong-eun from Donghyun Hospital,
Ms. Kim Hui-ju's doctor.
I heard you called me.
Ms. Kim Hui-ju
is also my colleague's wife.
I've known her personally.
Three years ago, she suddenly had
symptoms of vomiting
and mental deterioration,
so she was taken to our ER--
She got surgery for acute hydro,
but why not the secondary surgery
for craniopharyngioma?
I did remove the tumor
during the first operation.
But some parts
in her cranial nerves and hypothalamus
showed serious tumor adhesion,
so it was impossible
to remove it 100 percent.
The recurrence of the remaining tumor
led to an acute hydrocephalus.
But considering the endocrine control
and other circumstances,
we had to give up the secondary operation.
Can you tell me about the circumstances
that made you give up
the second operation?
Why do I have to explain that to you?
Even her husband agreed with my choice.
I just don't understand
how her husband was entirely convinced
to give up his wife's surgery.
Try and convince me too,
entirely.
Once the hydro is fixed,
you could've used a shunt
to solve all the issues at once.
And the hypothalamic damage could've
been treated with another operation.
What are you trying to say?
Are you saying that
I'm an incompetent doctor?
Is that how it sounds?
I'm sorry, but I have an operation
to perform. I should get going.
I'm saying this is an accessory to murder.
Do you think
I'm just blaming you
for being an incompetent doctor?
What do we do, honey?
I think he knows everything.
What do we do?
It's okay. It will be all right.
Cancel the appointments
for the afternoon and come right away.
Yes.
Get in.
Hang on.
How may I help you?
POLICE
Are you Professor Jung Se-un?
Yes, I am.
And is the lady next to you
Professor Yun Seong-eun?
I'm from Yongsan Police Station.
Ms. Kim Hui-ju's family
accused Professor Jung
and Professor Yun of attempted murder.
Would you come with me to the station?
Please hang in there.
We are administering the painkiller,
so the pain will be much better soon.
Open it up a little.
Please hang in there.
Excuse me.
She's crying.
She's not crying.
She just finds kimchi stew too spicy.
Susan.
Michael's mom?
Have some of this.
When you eat something spicy,
you should drink milk.
It will get rid of the spicy taste.
Is she the one who came here
with her son from New York?
I made kimchi stew with some pork.
But I guess that's not it.
If it's not pork,
is it anchovy or mackerel pike?
What do you mean?
His name is Michael.
He was adopted
from Korea to the States
when he was seven.
Recently, he found out
that he was terminally ill.
He wants to finish his life
with his free will,
so he refused
life-prolonging medical treatment.
He wanted to have
the kimchi stew his birth mom made
when he was little,
one last time before he died,
so his foster mom brought him to Korea.
People are
just amazing.
How does he remember
what he had when he was seven?
Try this.
The kimchi tastes really good.
-I have something to tell you.
-Aren't you eating it?
I...
I'm going back to Greece.
I was going to let you go anyway.
If you stay here longer,
I think you will fall sick.
Yesterday, I got lost
on my way to work.
And today, I forgot to come here.
I went to King's Table instead.
I don't think I can work here anymore.
After making kimchi stew for Michael,
let's quit together, okay?
Je suis.
Je suis, je suis.
Nous sommes, nous sommes.
Nous sommes.
Nous sommes...
FRENCH FOR BEGINNERS
I know we're married,
but you're supposed to knock at work.
Did you see the news? Did you see it?
What article?
I recently had an interview
with the new medical journal.
Is it out already?
Why did you mess with Seongju Daily
when you can't even deal with them?
Who is this "Dr. L of G Hospital" here?
Is it me?
Who else do you think it is?
Why would they fuck with me,
out of all people?
You said there are 308 doctors.
Does it even matter now?
Goddamnit, that mistress
of Seongju Daily.
Where did that bitch even come from?
What do I do, honey?
Let go of me.
My gosh.
Before anything,
I will let him resign from his post.
Having him resign from his post
won't solve the problem.
If resigning is the case,
he should resign as a director as well.
-Excuse me.
-It's not the first time
that Seung-hun shamed
the Foundation.
I'm sorry.
I'll give him a good talking.
He's a hopeless moron.
Do you think talking to him will work?
He didn't deserve
to take the position in the first place.
Let's just take this opportunity
to wipe the slate clean.
If we look closely,
we can find someone
who's just as good as he is.
Uncle.
-How could you say--
-Look who's talking.
So you're good at management
and put the hospital in danger
of bankruptcy 40 years ago?
Back then, I had to spend my own money
to save this hospital.
If you succeeded
in taking this hospital with that money,
then you are supposed
to run it the right way.
We can't let your family
run this hospital anymore.
The directors all agreed.
It's not true
that the directors all agreed.
My brother and sister-in-law didn't.
Is it you
who tipped off Seongju Daily
with the news?
What are you talking about, you brat?
Daughters are strangers after marriage.
This is none of your business.
I just signed my divorce papers yesterday,
so I'm no stranger here.
And I can see
you're trying to kick Seung-hun
out of this hospital
and take it back by placing
your kids in the post of director.
If I were you,
I wouldn't even come
near the hospital from feeling bad.
-Seo-hun.
-Why do you think my dad killed himself?
You guys conspired and slandered him
to take this hospital from him.
You even put him
under prosecutors' investigation.
The shock of being betrayed
by his brothers--
What do you know
to even say such reckless things?
It's just foolish of him
to kill himself for such reasons.
Who are we going to blame?
We're going to protect Geosung.
My grandchildren, Jun and Kang,
who are way smarter than your kids,
will protect it no matter what.
So don't worry and just leave.
I told you to leave!
I have to say, you were amazing out there.
I could've done better.
Your putting was really great, too.
-No, it wasn't.
-She's always very good.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive us just this once.
Isn't she the daughter-in-law
of Geosung family?
What's with her?
What do you want?
What?
Who mentioned
the director's real name on a comment?
You idiot! Why would you answer
a reporter's call right now?
Hold on, you should answer them.
Answer all their calls
and tell them everything
that could promote the hospital
including our staffs' community service
and the donations we made.
I also want you to find
a trustworthy marketing firm
to get rid of the hospital
and director's name
from the most-searched list.
I don't care how much it costs,
just get it done!
Dr. Lee Jun assaulted Professor Jung
as he was leaving after his investigation.
In front of everyone
including the cops.
Are you a gangster?
You look like a gentleman.
How could you beat someone up
who's just been interrogated?
You're in a police station!
And you call yourself a doctor?
Professor Jung
filed a lawsuit against you for assault.
You're getting a lawyer, right?
I hope your surgery goes well.
And I hope you're better
when we meet again.
We'll pray for you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I thought you quit smoking.
I picked it back up today.
Give that to me.
That imbecile.
How could he scheme with his mistress
and do such thing to his wife?
They're not even human.
I even officiated their wedding.
I can't believe that jerk
used to be my student.
He'd better not run into me.
I'll kill him the moment I see him.
Give it back, you punk.
They aren't even yours!
If you want to kill that bastard,
you need to be healthy.
Thank you, Kang.
I was so close
to unknowingly help their crazy plan.
I was able to avoid
being part of a big sin.
Thank you for saving me.
Cha-young!
Really?
My gosh, that's crazy.
This is a big secret.
So you can't tell anyone, okay?
If the bad guy, Manos,
finds out that I'm here,
he might send all his underlings here
to come and get me.
Okay, I won't tell anyone
that you're actually Iron Man
who's here to maintain peace on Earth.
I'm not Iron Man. I'm Iron Ranger.
Iron Ranger!
Oh, sorry.
You're Iron Ranger Number Two.
No, I'm not Number Two. I'm Number Three.
I'm sorry.
You're Iron Ranger Number Three.
When you look up into the night sky,
you see something sparkling, right?
You mean a satellite?
No, not that.
It's actually a signal
that's being sent from my planet.
The name of my planet is Iron 130.
What kind of signals do they send you?
They keep telling me to come back
because keeping peace on Earth
seems to be a difficult job.
You should tell them
that you're going to stay for a bit more.
Tell them that you have
your mom, grandmother,
and older brother here on Earth.
Tell them you'll return
after you spend a long time here
with your family.
I want to do that.
But there are rules, so I can't.
I need to quickly go back.
But I'm still here,
and that's why I keep getting sick.
I'm going to leave
once my spaceship arrives.
But...
I have to make sure Earth
is able to keep its peace first.
GEOSUNG HOSPICE
Min-yong, look over there.
Do you think that's the planet
where Ji-yong is from?
Over there. Iron 130.
Do you actually believe that?
It's all a load of crap.
You don't believe him then?
Of course not.
Ji-yong thinks he's a space warrior
who's here to keep peace on Earth,
because of a lie our dad told him.
Back when he was young,
he caused so much trouble
and never listened to our parents.
That's why our dad made up that lie.
"You're from outer space,
to maintain peace on Earth.
But you won't even
listen to your parents."
That's what he said to him.
That's when he began
to come to his senses
and became a nice kid.
He really thinks
that he's Iron Ranger Number Three.
I don't think your dad lied.
Ji-yong
might really be a space warrior
from outer space.
Cha-young, don't say stuff like this
to anyone else.
They'll think you're crazy--
Anyway, let's just keep this story
between the two of us.
Do you really think
a spaceship will come for Ji-yong?
My gosh, Cha-young!
I hope the spaceship
that Ji-yong is waiting for
will get lost
and end up coming here
really late after about 100 years.
You should eat this.
Here. Have a bite.
It's not your fault.
Our family gets unlucky every ten years.
And this year just happens to be
that tenth year.
So it's not my fault either.
We're talking about fate here.
Humans have no control over that.
Why aren't you eating this?
I even got myself
a parking ticket while buying this.
We're not going home.
We're going to a hotel.
Your mom wants you and me
gone from her sight for a while.
We got kicked out.
Seriously, what were you thinking?
Why would you hit anyone?
You're an intellectual.
You're not a gangster.
You couldn't just talk to him?
You speak amazing French.
Can't you do the same with Korean?
Who do you even take after?
Is that how I taught you?
But come to think of it,
I bet you hit him because he deserved it.
You're not the type
who beats people up for no reason.
Why did you hit him?
I heard he's also a doctor.
What did he do to deserve a beating?
Did he steal your girlfriend?
Who is that? Is it your mom?
Jun, you should tell her
that you're really sorry.
Try to be a cute son
so it'll soothe her anger.
Hurry.
It's me, Hui-ju.
I'll be getting surgery in a little bit.
I'm sorry, Jun.
I'm really sorry.
I hope
we'll get to meet next time.
Why aren't you saying anything? Who is it?
My gosh, it's like I'm talking to a ghost.
My mom, wife, and son are all the same.
No one cares about me.
You heartless boy.
My goodness.
Min-yong.
Can you please save my brother, Dr. Lee?
You saved Ms. Kim.
Can you save him as well?
I still have so many stuff
I want to do for him.
Ji-yong.
Ji-yong, your mom says
she wants to look into your eyes.
Why do you keep looking away?
What are you looking at?
I think he's showing symptoms of delirium.
Ji-yong.
Will you please look at me?
I have
something to say to you.
Don't you want
to look at me?
What's wrong with him?
Ji-yong,
can you hear me?
Will you try looking at me?
-Cha-young.
-Min-yong.
Can you hear me?
Will you try looking at me?
It's okay.
Ji-yong.
What are they saying
from your planet?
Do they want you to come back?
What do you want?
Do you also want to go back?
But I don't think
the spaceship has arrived yet.
-I couldn't...
-You couldn't?
-finish...
-Finish?
-my mission.
-You couldn't finish your mission?
What mission?
Keeping peace on Earth.
Oh, that mission
where you have to maintain peace on Earth?
Ji-yong.
You have no idea
how peaceful Earth has become
thanks to you.
Thanks to you,
your grandmother
was able to cure her back.
And your mother finally returned.
Your grandmother forgave her,
and they made up with each other.
And you brought so much joy
to all the people who work here
at the hospice.
You were the mascot here.
The mascot of happiness.
You were like our guardian angel.
You have no idea
how grateful we are to you.
Is that true?
Did I really make everyone happy
just like what Nurse Ha just said?
Ji-yong!
THANK YOU
IRON RANGER NUMBER THREE
IRON RANGER
Ji-yong.
Don't get lost.
And have a safe trip back home.
We'll do our best
to keep Earth safe without you.
Goodbye, Iron Ranger Number Three.
We're going to get rid
of that useless hospice
and replace it with the best exclusive
retirement community in the country.
I want you to be in charge of that place.
I can't trust the others.
That's just our fate.
We need to fight until either of us wins.
I got beaten up too, you know.
Here and here.
You don't even know Kang that well.
You don't know how evil he is--
I do know him. I know
that he isn't someone you can criticize,
badmouth, and judge however you want.
I'm sorry
if I did anything
to cause a misunderstanding.
Subtitle translation by Young-ju Kim