[countdown playing]
[light music playing]
BINI Chapter 3: Jhoanna Take 1.
- [thrilling music playing]
- [laughter]
BINI Chapter 3: Aiah Take 1.
- [thrilling music continues]
- [squealing]
BINI Chapter 3: Gwen Take 1.
[loud cheer]
BINI Chapter 3: BINI Stacey Take 1.
[thrilling music continues]
[hissing, humming]
Scene 1-- Oops.
- [staff] It's "take one."
- [laughter]
- Go on.
- Alright.
BINI Mikha Chapter 3...
Take 1.
- [snaps]
- [Mikha] Action.
[thrilling music continues]
BINI Chapter 3: Colet Take 1.
[growls]
BINI Chapter 3: Maloi Take 1.
[snaps]
- Hey!
Will there be more takes?
[all chuckling]
- BINI Chapter 3, Sheena Take 1!
- [snaps]
[thunder rolling]
[muffled voices]
After thirty days of BINIverse,
we move to regionals.
Are you ready for Canada and the US?
Yes, of course!
We're ready but of
course, it'll be more difficult.
["Huwag Muna Tayong Umuwi" playing]
["Huwag Muna Tayong Umuwi" continues]
Oh, you guys are here already.
Wow. [chuckles]
It's early.
- Hi, Director!
- [director] Hello.
Hi, Blooms. We are here!
Hello!
I'm tired! [chuckles]
[laughs]
It was only our second time in the US,
but we were happy
because even as soon
as we reached the airport,
we didn't expect
that people would recognize us.
[cameraman] Ready? One, two, three...
- Eyes here.
- [camera shutter clicking]
After the regionals,
we prepared for the LA tour.
The flight was organized by batch.
Why were we the first ones to fly?
Ah, right, because we're older.
[p.a. Announcer speaking indistinctly]
[man] Take care.
The batch one were the older members.
The last batch were the younger members,
me, Mikha, and Jhoanna.
Ah, right.
Yes, we got there first.
Why did we get there first?
Why did we split into groups?
[staff] You changed flights.
There was a typhoon!
Right. Okay.
We're only five now.
[staff] How was your flight?
It was okay.
It was our first time
flying business class.
We really enjoyed it! [chuckles]
It was our first time
flying business class together for work.
I didn't hold back.
I ate all the offered food.
They were like,
"You want dessert or something?"
It felt like a dream.
I used to just watch
Blackpink flying business class.
Now, it's BINI. Like, wow, who are we?
Oh, shucks. Things have really changed.
That's where we made up for all the sleep
we missed back in the Philippines.
We're on the way to our AIRBNB.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Colet] By the time we got to the airport,
we thought Jhoanna was pulling a prank.
We were about to check in
when Jhoanna suddenly felt dizzy.
I told Sheena,
"Shee, I feel like something hit me."
I mean, everything suddenly felt off.
I sat down, gripping my suitcase.
I was like, "I can't take this anymore."
[engine humming]
[Gwen] At first,
they kept updating the group chat.
It was very sudden.
Jho was still fine, joking with Sheena.
Then just as I turned around...
She went down like that.
Good thing someone beside her caught her.
Something bad really happened to her.
Of course, we got worried,
especially since we weren't there for her.
[Anna] Is someone taking
over the choreography or what?
[Machu] I think it should be Maloi.
[Jhoanna] Until
they took me to the hospital.
That's when they told
me I needed to be admitted.
I was crying in the emergency room.
And I said, "Miss MQ, I can still fly."
That's when we heard
that Jhoanna couldn't make it.
We were unsure if
she would be able to catch up.
When that happened,
I asked, "Lord, why am I here?"
[thriller music playing]
[train engine rumbling]
[upbeat music playing]
Wow.
[upbeat music continues]
Hold on.
We can survive this.
[Jonathan] there will come a point
when you'll saturate the local market.
They really made it to the top.
And what do you do with all
that clout and success you've earned?
The next step for
growth is to go international.
[cameraman] Sorry, one more.
- [chuckling]
- I accidentally covered it.
One, two, three...
- [light music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[overlapping chatter]
It's like all my hard work just vanished.
I really went all out. [chuckles softly]
[faint chatter, chuckling]
- Money's gone.
- [laughter]
[Aiah] There's bread.
I don't like that.
[Stacey] It was so nice
to feel that sisterhood again.
We're not always together now.
It felt like the first
time in a long while
we got to do things
like grocery shopping
and having sleepovers.
What's yours?
Coffee? [laughing]
I want to go back to the Philippines now.
- [fake crying]
- [chuckles]
U-S-A.
I love the Philippines.
But during that time, I developed anxiety.
So, I just really looked
forward to stepping out from here.
To be somewhere
I could walk around freely again,
even go jogging without worry.
I have a video of him saying...
[in deep voice] "Girls,
whose charger is this?"
- That charger!
- It's Aiah's!
- [laughter]
- It's not mine!
It's not yours?
[Maloi] "Whose charger is this?"
"Whose charger is this?"
- [makes noises]
- "Whose charger is this?"
[Gwen] I have lots of videos of that too.
We love Coach Mickey. We miss him so much.
But he barely shows up.
[chuckles]
2024 was obviously a roller coaster.
When we started working with the girls,
we tried to prepare
them for a lot of things.
We tried to prepare
them for what might happen.
But everything happened so fast.
Come on, look.
This is next level.
It's so high-tech. [chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh.
Here's more.
[somber music playing]
[Mickey] There were so
many voices and so much attention.
Who do you trust?
What should you listen to?
How do you deal with the pressure?
It was changing fast, and it was scary.
[Aiah] We weren't
used to Jho not being there.
It felt so different without her.
[somber music continues]
But we were already there,
so we had to keep going.
And Jhoanna would just catch up later.
Of course, it felt like going
through a serious heartbreak.
[laughs]
We weren't even sure if
Sheena and Mikha would make it.
- [airplane rumbling]
- [thrilling music playing]
[Lauren] I think we're
the first Filipino act to appear in KCON.
So through that,
through the marketing
efforts of Star Events and Star Music,
we got into KCON.
- Thank you.
- [Mikha] You guys are here?
- You're here! Hello!
- Hello! Aww!
[Sheena] It's sad because we were the
first-ever P-Pop group to perform at KCON.
It was such a huge
event and opportunity for us.
We felt so lost without Jhoanna.
[upbeat music playing]
Bye, thanks!
[Mikha] Oh, my god! The house is big.
Hello!
- Oh, my god!
- [laughter]
This is your room, Sheena and Mikha.
[chuckling]
[Mikha] We weren't used to it.
It's weird not having your leader around.
- Have you guys slept?
- Yes, we just woke up.
That's our problem.
You might not get any sleep later.
[Lauren] Of course, I panicked.
Not because she couldn't perform,
but because I was more
worried about her condition.
Because they said it was...
- [Lauren] UTI.
- Jho has UTI?
[Lauren] She rarely
drinks water, that's why.
Keep that in mind.
The test result says she has UTI?
So far, she still needs
to undergo a lot of tests.
All the girls would have to
make an adjustment because,
from an eight-girl
performance, it came down to seven.
And that wasn't easy.
[overlapping chatter]
- Group photo.
- Nice.
Okay, let's make Jhoanna jealous.
[Maloi] We had a missing piece.
It's like we couldn't
stand properly without her.
We struggled while she wasn't around,
trying to figure out who would stand where
and who would do what.
How many of this should we order?
Who else wants milkshake?
Who wants a burger? You guys can share.
[Colet] Wait a second.
Get four, so they can have some too.
Just that, Sheena, Jhoanna, oh, Stacks.
Yeah, right.
[Colet] Goodness,
Jhoanna is really the one leading BINI.
She usually speaks on behalf of the group.
Since Jhoanna wouldn't
make it, we had to re-block.
- Move backwards.
- Who'll be at the center?
One more.
You can't see
the gaps at the back anymore.
They're not noticeable.
[Maloi] 360? So it's visible?
[Sheena] Oh, this is a 360.
[Aiah] That's also my formation,
then she'll push the other two.
Then on my side is Jho.
Who's going to sing? She's supposed to.
I think we need to
adjust the blocking here.
This block here?
This one.
[singing "Cherry On Top" by BINI]
[Mickey] You need to understand
that wherever we go
or whatever we're doing,
we still have a long way to go,
so we have to work
hard to climb the ladder.
- Eyy!
- [Mickey] You learn fast!
- [laughter]
[upbeat music playing]
- That's right.
- Okay, that's good.
Let's try it from the top.
- Come on.
- Turn on the music.
So it's fine that Jho's not around.
- We can manage.
- [chuckling]
- We can do this.
- It seems easy, right?
At the end of the day,
because they were eight
and all together as a group,
they should act like a family.
If a member goes through something,
they just have to
learn how to deal with it.
[instrumental music playing]
It's a good starting point
because it's not just for Filipinos.
It's for a mixed audience
who appreciates Asian music.
To be on that stage
and to be performing
alongside other groups...
It's definitely a huge boost for us.
[thrilling music playing]
[loud cheering]
[audience] Whoo!
[faint chatter]
[upbeat music playing]
[Machu] In Team BINI,
you don't just carry one title.
As a coach, you need to know how to sew,
you need to know how to give massages.
Everything. Oh, goodness.
All Team BINI members are talented.
[upbeat music continues then stops]
[Colet] It's a lot of
pressure every time I listen to OPM
or Filipino talents being
introduced on the global stage.
But we're just doing
what we've always done.
It's like we haven't really changed.
Lord, thank You for
this day You've given us.
Thank You for
bringing us safely here to LA.
[Gwen] The preparation in
the Philippines took a long time.
Now for global domination,
we're still finding
our way and working on it.
[Sheena] Coach Mach.
- Go.
- Oh, my god.
- [chuckles]
- Let's go!
- Go for it.
- Ouch.
Ouch.
- [hands clapping]
- [chuckling]
Ouch.
[engine revving]
[Aiah] We were actually really nervous
because most of
the people there were K-pop artists.
And it felt like
we were the only P-pop group.
We were worried about
what if people didn't know us,
what if they didn't like us,
and what if we faced a black ocean
where no one lit their light sticks,
didn't cheer, and just sat quietly.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, go.
Two, three...
- Long live!
- Hi, I'm Aiah!
- I'm Colet.
- Hi, I'm Maloi.
- I'm Gwen.
- I'm Stacey.
- I'm Mikha.
I'm Sheena.
[all] And we are BINI!
From the Philippines!
Oh, right.
Just continue.
And we're from the Philippines.
- Alright, one more.
- And we are...
Sheena will speak first. After that...
Hi, I'm Sheena.
[all] And we are...
- BINI from the Philippines!
- [loud cheering, applauding]
[Gwen] Never in my whole
life did I think I'd get to perform.
It felt impossible before.
All we ever dreamed of
was to do a mall show, right?
["Cherry On Top" by BINI playing]
[audience cheering, applauding]
["Cherry On Top" continues]
[Stacey] The fans
didn't just come for K-pop.
They were also there for BINI.
They cheered for us too.
They didn't give us a black ocean.
Give it up one more time for BINI!
[loud cheering, applauding]
[Sheena] Our performance was a free show
and not part of the main show.
But wow, the cheer was so loud!
And we found out there
were a lot of Filipinos there.
A lot of them came.
[squealing, cheering]
[audience member] Maloi, I love you!
Oh my gosh, wow.
It's really a dream come true.
As a K-pop fan, I'm so happy at KCON
because the K-pop groups
I used to idolize and
watch on TikTok were there.
[Aiah] Wow,
I used to just watch them in videos
or hear their songs.
And we finally met them.
It felt so surreal.
[upbeat music playing]
[screams] We were really like that.
Of course, we had to be professional.
But behind closed doors,
I was totally smitten.
It was just me and Colet.
Then at the last minute, they told us,
"Girls, they allowed
three members from BINI."
And Stacku quickly raised her hand, "Me!"
Guys, I'm going for it.
This only happens once.
The opportunity knocks just once.
So, I really grabbed
it and didn't want to miss out
because I've been
watching them for so long.
- Hello!
- BINI!
[Maloi] Oh my gosh! You look so good!
[fan] Hi, Mikha!
Hi there!
Hi, Maloi!
Come on, let's take pictures!
We already saw foreigners so I said,
"Wow, so they really like our songs?"
It's amazing.
Did you get that? That Pantropiko outfit?
- Huh? Yeah.
- Of the girl.
[giggles]
[woman] Colet,
can I get a picture, please?
[Maloi] With the help of
our fans and management,
we're really starting to
get recognized, little by little.
And our experience at KCON
is hands down one of
the highlights in BINI's journey
this 2024.
- You're beautiful!
- Thank you!
Thank you!
So far.
[Stacey] After KCON,
we were looking for our service,
but we were told
it couldn't go into that area.
So, what we did was
we walked a really long distance.
From Tomas Morato, to EDSA, to Cubao.
That was like the distance we walked.
This is part of our bonding.
No, we're helping the driver.
We don't want him to get
tired, so we'll approach him.
We're the service for the driver,
not the other way around.
It’s a very humbling feeling,
like going back to day one,
when no one knows you.
But it’s great because, in a way,
it gives you a fresh start.
We're now seeing
the evacuees from the Crypto Arena.
These are
Where is the service?
[laughter]
- Where...
- [woman] Are you guys BINI?
- Yes!
- [squealing]
We came all the way
from Canada! [chuckles]
[Maloi] It's your lucky day!
- Can we take a picture?
- Sure!
[woman] Aren't
you going to Canada on August 9?
Yes! Are you going to watch?
- Of course!
- Hopefully!
But your tickets are already sold out.
- Ow!
- That's how...
[Maloi] Let’s take a picture.
[gentle music playing]
[Stacey] We're not
used to this because, of course,
that’s another country.
We really expected
that we wouldn't be recognized,
but we're so happy that at least,
even if just one person knows us,
our hearts are already so happy.
[woman shrieks]
Hi! We love you!
(In Bisaya) Come here, until the concert.
[IVY] I can't, I have school.
- Oh, come on.
- [girl] Ma! Ma!
[Colet] All the first
times we experience in life,
we should really be complete.
But of course,
there are things that can't be avoided.
It has become our inside joke,
“Oh, Jhoanna's not here,”
but deep down, we're really sad.
[indistinct chatter, p.a. announcement]
[laughing]
- Bye bye!
Bye!
- Why?
- Uh, can I...
[quizzical music playing]
[Lauren] Going to America,
we take on a different strategy.
We can't go there and
pretend to know the market.
- I thought it was just us?
- I thought it was casual?
- I thought it was just us.
- I thought she's just on live.
Show your goofy side,
so you girls can be funny.
But in English.
That’s also the worry of the other girls,
they're saying they're
not used to speaking English.
[laughs] Oh my gosh!
I feel like, us girls,
we've improved in speaking in English.
But good thing we have
our strong representatives,
Aiah and Mikha.
- Ready, guys?
- Ready?
Anytime now.
[mimics drum roll, fanfare]
- [crowd roaring]
- [host] What's up?
How are you guys doing today?
Humor in Tagalog is like,
you say it in Tagalog.
It’s super funny.
But if you translate it to
your American friend or something,
they won't laugh.
[host] BINI!
[crowd cheers]
[lively music playing]
Thank you!
[crowd cheers]
Yes, we get it!
[laughter]
- Yeah...
- [HOST] Yeah, alright.
It’s really hard to explain.
[Maloi] In that whole interview,
we only spoke in English.
I was laughing at ourselves.
We can joke even in English?
Hmm, watch this!
[laughs]
[interviewer] My question is,
if you are to switch
with one of your members,
who would it be and why?
Switch places?
[crowd laughs]
[Sheena] I'm so fluent in English now.
So the conversation just flows smoothly,
so the nervousness went away.
It was only at the beginning.
I'll hold your leg up.
[giggling, laughing]
[upbeat music playing]
[laughing]
["Cherry On Top" plays]
- Okay!
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
Thank you for coming!
It feels like
I worked out for three hours.
Oh my, our content shoots. [laughs]
We ran out of battery. [laughs]
If Gwen’s battery ran out, I was next.
[laughs]
The things we went through...
The whole day we were...
[upbeat music continues]
- Ah.
- Good afternoon!
Good morning!
After he said that, everyone agrees like,
"Oh my god, that’s a great idea!"
[laughs]
[upbeat music continues]
Ready? One, two...
[indistinct chatter]
Wait, I'm going to quit.
Just kidding. [laughs]
[soft music playing]
[exhales]
[Gwen] I didn't really see myself
going into this industry and this track.
So I'm slowly
adjusting to what’s happening.
[Aiah] I enjoyed it.
But I did see others thinking,
[gasps] "What is this
again?" Something like that.
I get it, we all have
different levels of energy.
[Stacey] It’s really hard for us
to fake that you're really happy.
You can't hide if you're tired.
Your face really shows it,
but of course, we're in the industry,
so you really need to push yourself.
And the things
that truly make us happy are food.
- [diners chattering]
- [utensils clinking]
[Maloi] I can't believe the scheduling.
In one day,
there are like three or four schedules.
I can't imagine how it’s
possible to happen in one day.
It felt like we were in LA forever
because of how much we did.
- Thank you!
[chattering]
[Sheena] Even though it was non-stop,
we were just happy, us girls.
Of course, we also
wanted the videos to turn out great.
We know we'll be
reaching different audiences.
- Thank you!
Bye!
[Aiah] I think we also needed that time,
that break.
Even though we were there for work,
it felt like work and play for me. Yeah.
Don't move anymore!
The battery is about to die!
- Yay!
[reel rolling]
[Colet] Even though
we were completely drained after that,
we could still see the importance
of that collaboration for BINI,
because that’s one of the steps
to getting BINI
recognized on the international stage.
- Thank you!
- Thank you! Thank you!
[Lauren] It’s like day zero again.
When you get to America,
there are millions and millions of artists
who want to penetrate Hollywood.
The real measure of
success for an international career
is being able to penetrate the US.
[indistinct chatter]
[Jonathan]
What BINI is doing is very important
for the Filipino music industry.
If BINI makes it to the global stage
and reaches a wider audience,
gets global recognition,
it will benefit us.
People around the world will get curious.
They will see that BINI is a great group,
so, there must be
more artists in the Philippines
of the same caliber
waiting to be discovered.
[airplane engine roaring]
- [staff] How are you, Jho?
- [giggles]
Okay? Am I okay?
I am okay.
Wow, she's back!
- Hello!
- Gwen's not responding.
Hello, what's your name?
- [Jhoanna] I'm Jhoanna.
- [Aiah giggles]
Hello, I'm Joan.
[squeals] Jho!
Did your chin get longer?
My face got longer.
Just kidding. I missed you.
I was only gone for five days,
but I feel like I missed a lot already.
When I arrived, the girls were glowing.
They could pass as locals. [chuckles]
We can't be friends anymore.
We have American humor now.
[laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Did you miss me?
Yeah.
How dare you.
Do you know what happened?
You say the word "blond" differently now.
[chanting] BINI! BINI! BINI!
- Hi!
- Hello!
- [chanting continues]
- [screaming]
[Aiah] It was so heartwarming.
Most of the second
generation of Filipinos here
weren't born in the Philippines,
but they know our songs.
I'm BINI Louise.
So my question is,
I came all the way from Seattle...
- Wow!
- [claps]
[Maloi] There were Blooms
who came from different states.
We were amazed
that we have fans everywhere.
[woman] One, two, three, smile!
[Sheena] Hi, thank you!
- [woman] Jho!
- Hi! Bye!
[Jhoanna] It's great that
we're getting
recognized individually as well.
Like, "Hi, BINI Jhoanna!"
People call us by our names.
[woman] Ready?
Three, two, one!
Hey!
- Hey!
[stirring music playing]
Whoo!
Aah!
[laughs]
Come on!
I'll give you a tour.
[stirring music continues]
For the last ASAP show,
which was in Vegas,
we had such a small part.
But we were grateful to just be there
considering we weren't that popular yet.
So for ASAP California, we were surprised.
We were in the spotlight.
- [Jolina] Sisters!
- [BINI cheer]
- Let's dance!
- [laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[Mikha] This was different from 2022.
We weren't that popular yet.
There were less cheers.
[Stacey] What if
we only had fans in the Philippines?
[upbeat music continues]
[Colet] Our goal is to entertain
all the Filipinos who were going to watch.
We gave our best,
from rehearsals to the actual performance.
[upbeat music continues]
- Are there people?
- No.
- Proceed to the elevator.
- Okay.
You didn't eat?
I did.
I'm sleepy.
Where's Stacey?
[Maloi] We had such a busy schedule.
We were maximizing each day we were there.
We weren't just there for ASAP.
We had a lot of content
to shoot and interviews to do.
We were tired. Our energy was down.
We just wanted to rest
when we got to the hotel.
[harmonizing]
[Jhoanna] What are you looking at?
Hmm?
Can I help you?
[Mickey] There are
times you feel helpless.
We don't always know
how to deal with everything.
They're not little girls anymore
that cry for no reason.
No. I think right now...
I appreciate that they're slowly finding
their voice as artists.
[upbeat music playing]
[Corey] They're a phenomenal new
generation Filipino girl group.
They've made noise all over.
[upbeat music continues]
You can feel that they're bound by love.
It's a genuine sisterhood,
it's genuine camaraderie
that really speaks to the audience.
We're all here back in
California to celebrate...
[Corey] When we brought ASAP to the US,
the Blooms were there.
What they went through in 2024,
it was growth that I feel like
was very challenging and scary.
But it was part of
the process of who they are now.
They won't stop until they reach
their global aspirations.
[audience cheering]
[cheering continues]
[upbeat music continues]
[Corey] I call it good noise.
That good noise
spreads around like wildfire.
Can I do it like this?
[chuckles]
- [audience cheering]
- [upbeat music continues]
[cheering continues]
[Robi] California, get ready for
a mini concert like no other
from the nation's girl group, BINI!
["Cherry On Top" by BINI playing]
[Aiah] It's like we had a mini concert.
We performed and had spiels.
Before, we would
just leave after performing.
But we've leveled up on ASAP.
["Cherry On Top" continues]
[cheering, whooping]
[Sheena] There were so many Blooms there.
They showed us that we're loved
and that we have fans in California.
The Blooms around the world
have been the ambassadors of BINI.
And that attracts the attention
of the international audience.
I'm very proud. I'm very grateful.
It's not an overnight success.
It's not just talent,
of course, excellent talent,
but it's their story.
- Wow!
- [Martin] There you go.
Surprise, BINI.
We'd like to present this recognition
of the record industry's
Certified Gold Album Award
for the albums Feel Good and Talaarawan.
Whoo!
[Jhoanna] We made it to the big leagues.
Then we saw
Director Lauren tearing up on the side.
- [cheering, whopping]
- [clapping]
What a surprise.
You deserve it.
[Maloi] It was
touching to see how proud he was
of what we had achieved.
It was a proud moment to
be awarded in front of our fans.
We were so happy.
Yeah, it was very memorable.
Finally, after years of hard work,
we are now being seen and heard.
I am over the moon
that BINI is finally being recognized.
Hopefully, we make it globally as well.
[gentle music playing]
[shouts, laughs]
[laughing, shouting]
- [exclaims]
- Whoa!
Whoo!
BINI Jhoanna, hi!
We had a music camp two years ago.
We invited the BINI girls,
but only two of them were available.
- Maloi and Colet.
- Mm-hmm.
[humming]
[singing] ♪ In the idea... ♪
They were interviewed
by songwriters and producers
from the US.
And then, the girls shared their ideas.
That's how Cherry On Top was made
- in the music camp. Yeah.
- That was in Davao.
[mellow music playing]
So, that started
our push for globalization.
[Sheena] The girls
and I always feel anxious
every time we release a song.
We're worried if people
will accept and love the song.
[mellow music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
Some Filipinos think,
including the old me,
that a full-English song
can't be considered OPM,
which is not the case.
- [mellow music continues]
- [indistinct chatter]
Some people comment,
"Why is BINI's song in English?
They're transitioning too fast.
Cherries don't even grow in our country."
We've encountered comments like that.
[Mikha] When we went to the Wish Bus,
we noticed that there
were only four Blooms.
I didn't say anything
because I didn't want
to bring the energy down.
Mic. Mic check. One, two.
[Mikha] One of
the Wishbus staff members said,
"Hi, a lot of fans are
waiting for you, guys."
I was surprised because
I thought there were only four.
- ["Cherry On Top" playing]
- [cheering]
There were more people than when we did
our first Wish Bus performance
in the Philippines, which was amazing.
["Cherry On Top" continues]
We see a significant
rise in the number of streams.
I think we're able to
target more Blooms overseas.
Cherry On Top received
a million streams in less than 24 hours.
The girls and I were really amazed.
People are now looking
forward to our new releases.
["Cherry On Top" continues]
Good morning.
[indistinct chatter]
It's moving.
- So, it's easier?
- Yeah.
I will teach this second eight.
Who will she be paired with?
So, we can break down the voice.
So, who will it be?
You can pair me with Maloi.
I'll do the dancing.
Alright.
You will explain it, and I will dance.
- In English.
- Yeah.
["Cherry On Top" by BINI playing]
Historically, when we created BINI,
we weren't sure yet
what their music would be like.
The first two EPs,
especially the first EP...
["Born To Win" by BINI playing]
That album is
a sampler of different sounds
that BINI can make.
The first year was okay.
There were some who liked them.
The second one which is...
["I Feel Good" by BINI playing]
We were slightly trying Asian pop songs.
Come closer.
[indistinct chatter]
You two were late, Mikha.
I can't believe we're here.
- This is Steezy.
- [chuckles]
I could only watch this before.
Oh my god.
Thank you, Lord.
Was it good?
This one's better. Next take.
For the third one, we wanted
to revolutionize OPM
through BINI.
That's why we created...
["Pantropiko" by BINI playing]
[Aiah] Pantropiko is so important
because without Pantropiko,
where would BINI be?
Just kidding!
You see, we didn't really expect it.
Pantropiko is what...
placed us on the map.
[music playing over speakers]
You got it.
I think that's it.
I'm fine.
That's when Sheena's
iconic dance chorus happened.
Everything started there for me.
["Cherry On Top" playing over speakers]
[cheering]
My partner and
I watched you grow on Instagram.
Not just because of the following but...
everything you're producing,
like your vocals and new music.
All of my friends went to KCON.
- Wow!
- They were gushing about you.
And I was like...
[laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
Come here.
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [upbeat music playing]
BINI's sound is
the sound of the current generation.
We've been observing the trends
so we can catch up to that style of music,
which will be
the perfect sound for BINI to carry.
That will put them on
the global map as BINI.
Based on our experience
in the music industry...
["Pantropiko" by BINI playing]
["Cherry On Top" by BINI playing]
We know that once an artist or group
from another country
dances to a certain song,
the owner of that song
is ready to go international.
[mellow music playing]
When Billboard Philippines called
to inform us that BINI and
SB19 would receive awards
in Seoul, South Korea,
we realized that was the start of...
The Philippine music wave.
...the invasion of Asian music.
So, I think that's the first step.
They also won awards
from MTV Europe Music Awards
and BreakTudo Awards in Brazil.
They were recognized
with the help of the Blooms.
We're done, guys. [claps]
It was really fun.
I learned a lot, I swear.
- Oh!
- Yeah!
We have Filipinos right here.
- Certified.
- Certified. [laughs]
Maloi-certified.
[Gwen] BINI has been so busy that
sometimes,
we only find out about our awards
in the middle of our events.
It's always a surprise for us.
But of course, we're really grateful.
It's a clear manifestation
that our hard work pays off.
We also see on social media
how busy the Blooms are
when there's voting involved.
Sometimes, we feel guilty because we don't
get to interact with them
that much due to our busy schedule.
But their support is never-ending
even though they don't see us often.
[indistinct chatter]
[Aiah] Every time we receive awards,
I always look back on
our humble beginnings,
those times when
we doubted if we would make it.
We really didn't expect
that it would be possible.
[singing] ♪ You know I'm runnin' it ♪
[Aiah] We got to meet the American
producers in person for the first time.
[singing]
♪ 'Cause you know I'm runnin' it ♪
Okay, just two more.
Really good.
[singing] ♪ I heard you like confidence ♪
Uh-oh! Who's the next victim?
Miss Sheena! Ah!
Can you at least make it hard on us
- a little bit?
- [laughs] Okay.
Yeah.
Try not to make it so easy on us.
This is our third
time recording with them.
We record multiple times
until we warm up our voices.
And then, they will pick the best takes.
I'm nervous. [breathes deeply]
Brrt!
[Gwen] It was our first time
recording overseas. [chuckles]
Yes, it was a very different vibe.
[Colet] We did the recording with Greg.
He was there with me and Maloi
when Cherry On Top was created in Davao.
After Cherry On Top,
they gave us another song.
It's called Blink Twice.
[singing] ♪ Symphony... ♪
- [clapping]
- [upbeat music playing]
Is it over already?
- Not yet, sir.
- We can still watch?
Our bosses are here.
We were in the middle of recording
when they suddenly arrived.
They're going to watch us record.
But we're all done, except for Colet.
I feel nervous.
I thought it'd just be a video call.
I forgot that they're in the US, too.
[upbeat music continues]
[vocalizing]
This is the most
nervous I've been while recording.
[upbeat music continues]
[singing]
♪ He's not even thinkin' 'bout me ♪
- I'm good?
- You're great.
Yes!
Headphones off.
Thank you, Lord. Hallelujah.
- Ah!
- Damn!
Next time make
it a little harder on us, would you?
- [chuckling]
- [clapping]
I'm glad I made it in time to watch you.
[laughing]
I just have to say that you girls
are seriously one of
the easiest vocal sessions
- I've ever done.
- Wow! [clapping]
And I've done some
heavy-duty vocal sessions.
Yay! [clapping]
[all] Hi, we are BINI,
and you’re listening to KPOP radio.
[all] Eyyy!
[Carlo] They have the heart for it
a different kind of
passion for what they do,
but there's also
that element of Filipino kindness.
It shines through.
I think that's what makes them special.
I think the success of BINI
should be based not on
the need to have a diverse representation
but really because their talent is unique
and their talent is amazing.
Not because of
their ethnicity or nationality.
Let them shine
because of how great they are.
Let them shine because of who they are.
[upbeat music playing]
- Miss Agnez.
- [Agnez] Oh, hey!
This is Agnez Mo.
- [Agnez] Hey!
- Hi!
How are you doing? Hey, I'm Agnez.
[Mikha] We were all intimidated at first
because she’s
a very big artist in Indonesia
and everywhere else.
It was nice to talk to
her because she was very humble,
down to earth.
She was giving us advice.
[Gwen] Actually, I saw her outside,
she was sitting at that time.
Good thing I was
smiling when I went out. [laughs]
[Agnez] It’s not even
about being the most talented,
but I think it’s who’s the better student.
That means listening to,
you know, your team,
but also at the same time, um...
you know, stand your ground.
[Jhoanna] She was
very sisterly when we met her.
[Colet] She’s been in
the industry for such a long time,
so she gave us advice
on how to last in this business
and how to keep
the passion for performing.
[Agnez] This is
definitely the most important.
Get rid of toxic people.
- Whoa.
- Yes!
[Stacey] She said to
always have a good attitude.
She taught us a lot
about how to handle bashers,
those people who won’t leave us alone.
[Maloi] Learn to say no.
You shouldn't say yes to everything.
You should have dignity.
Stand firm in your beliefs.
If you don't like something,
then you don't like it.
Apart from her music,
her personality has also played a big role
to sustain such a long career.
You should make
mistakes to learn from them
and be better as an artist.
[photographer] One, two, three...
[Gwen] We thank her for sharing
her nuggets of wisdom,
especially when it comes
to reaching global audiences.
[thunder rolling]
As if nothing happened, guys.
- [chuckles]
- We're all packing.
[mellow music playing]
Is Care Bear a priority?
Oh, you're trying to fit everything in.
- [marker scribbling]
- [overlapping chatter]
Girls, our checkout time is 11 AM.
Could you come picks us up from the lobby?
[chuckles]
Oh, okay.
[Gwen] I don't have much stuff to pack.
Well, that's good.
I didn’t overpack. I’m proud of that.
Bye, everyone.
- Bye, good night.
- Rest well.
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [wind howling]
[car revving]
- [airplane engine droning]
- [water rushing]
[airplane engine humming]
[camera shutter clicks]
[indistinct flight announcement]
over p.a.]
[mellow music continues]
[ambient city noise]
Okay.
[Aiah] Actually,
we didn’t expect to go to Canada.
I honestly thought
we would have a tour in the US.
But it’s nice.
We got to go to four different cities.
[guide] If you want to film
the bridge here, it’s really nice.
[Jhoanna] The difficult
part of our Canada tour
was that it was just basically us.
We didn’t have a big team,
unlike our NFT concert
where everyone was there.
[thrilling music playing]
- Good morning!
It's our concert day today.
- Finally, some Filipino food!
- Thank You, Lord!
[Jhoanna] For our Canada stops,
we only had Coach Mickey...
That's the problem with tours abroad.
And you only have
the day itself for everything.
Sometimes, things get lost in translation.
[Jhoanna] ...Mommy Jho, and Miss Ice.
So we had a hard time,
especially backstage during the concert.
There really wasn’t anyone helping us.
[light music playing]
- Toronto!
Hi, Toronto!
- Mic check.
- Guys, I think--
[Stacey] We rehearsed the whole day.
Endless rehearsals.
We always have to train
ourselves on different stages.
And that one was new for us.
[stirring music playing]
- Oh my!
- [chuckles]
[Jhoanna] No backup
dancers, so we go straight...
Who didn't eat? Why didn't you eat?
Girls, help each other backstage, okay?
One, two...
[all] BINI!
- Alright. Cool, cool.
- Wow.
- Wow, that was on three.
- That was on three.
[thrilling music playing]
[Coach Mickey]
Talent is important in anything
that you’re doing.
But as it shows...
Let's go!
...skill will always outdo talent.
Because if you’re talented,
sometimes you get lazy.
Complacent.
But if you’re skilled,
you know you worked hard for it,
and you keep on learning.
What we did with
BINI was talent and skill.
[cheering, applause]
[thrilling music continues]
[camera shutter clicking]
[whooping]
- Hi, BINI!
[Mikha] Wow, we were able
to actually fill that many people.
Like that amount of people,
in a different country.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
[fan] Aiah!
[crowd screaming]
[Aiah] That was a "wow" moment for us.
The fact that we sold out all four cities.
[film rolling, clicking]
[vocalizing]
[Maloi] Those are different cities.
They really showed us warmth and love.
We still have a lot to learn
to truly reach the level of excellence
required in the international scene.
But with the help of our foundation,
the Filipino fans,
if they keep believing in our talents,
if they continue giving us
the courage to push ahead,
and if they keep
showing us their all-out support,
then we can definitely do it.
["Diyan Ka Lang" playing]
[coach Mickey]
In Canada, we were able to see
that it was the kids who attended.
Music is a language,
and it will help
you get closer to your culture,
or in this case, to other cultures.
To show them the culture,
especially this generation’s culture,
and to tell it through songs...
Personally,
I think it was a big stepping stone,
what we did here,
but I think we’re still very far.
So we were like, "If we sold out there,
maybe we can also sell out Araneta."
["Diyan Ka Lang" instrumental playing]
We thought we'd only
have a few concerts this year,
the NFT concert.
Then suddenly there’s an announcement
that we’ll have
the Grand BINIverse at Araneta.
Two days weren’t enough,
we needed a third day.
So even though
we were tired, we pushed through
because we felt bad for
the Blooms who couldn’t come.
We really wanted many
Blooms to watch the Grand BINIverse.
It really was grand.
["Diyan Ka Lang" playing]
[music fading]
We'll be joined by the members of BINI.
We have Jhoanna, we have Maloi,
we have Mikha, and we have Colet.
Of course, girls,
first of all, congratulations...
- [static noise]
- [camera shutters clicking]
[music fades]
[Colet] At that moment,
I wasn't feeling okay anymore.
The fans had given us letters,
and the one that reached me
said something like, um...
Uh...
"Your music saved me.
BINI is always my source...
- [somber music playing]
- [indistinct chattering]
...of happiness.
My anxiety goes away
because you girls always make me laugh.
You're all so authentic.
And then it hit me.
I’m helping other people,
but no one is helping me figure out
how-- how to make...
how to make my anxiety go away,
how deal with this feeling.
Because the other girls
have someone waiting
for them when they get home.
Whether it's family or someone else.
But who doesn't have anyone? Me.
I'm always alone.
So, I'd rather be outside,
I'd rather keep training
even though it's exhausting.
At least then, I'm not alone.
So, during that time at the screening...
[crowd cheering]
[emcee] BINI Colet!
BINI Mikha!
...I couldn't look at the crowd.
I don't know why,
but whenever I see a lot of people,
I start to panic.
All I really wanted at
that time was to sit down. [chuckles]
- [loud thumping]
- [gloomy music playing]
[Mikha] She was crying so much.
Like, she couldn’t stop herself.
We were surprised,
and then we realized
that something was wrong.
[tender music playing]
[Colet] My sisters were checking on me,
but I don’t usually
share much with my family.
They even used to say
that what happened to me
was the same as what happened to Aiah.
My family was really panicking.
My sister even said
that she'd file for leave for me.
She flew here to see me.
[film rolling]
That month had been so exhausting for us,
so we decided to spend a rest day
doing Bible study.
I remember Aiah leading it then.
[soft music playing]
[Aiah] And that was when she shared
that she had an anxiety attack,
and I told her some things
about what I went through as well.
What I felt, how I overcame it.
It happens to a lot of
people more than you think,
but they don’t show it.
I felt sad I wasn't
aware of her struggles.
[photographer] Family picture!
Okay, get closer, Staku.
[Colet] I took the risk and told myself,
"Okay, I’ll share this."
[Maloi] She allowed us,
her fellow BINI girls,
to cross that line and embrace her fully.
We heard stories that we don't
usually share with each other.
It’s nice to know
that we all came together to...
to focus on...
making a connection with God
and making a connection
with everyone else in the group.
[Gwen] Especially in this era of BINI,
where things happen so quickly.
The pressure, the changes...
That’s why, sometimes,
negative thoughts are inevitable.
Aside from a support system,
which I think is very essential,
it’s also important for us girls,
who are so immersed in work
and with everything happening in BINI,
that we always have
someone professional looking after us.
We’re grateful because we have One Core.
We’ve been celebrating
Christmas together for six years.
- Six years together.
- Six years?
- Yeah.
- Six Christmases.
[coach Mickey] Creating a group,
honestly, I believe, is very easy.
Anyone can create a group.
But to sustain a group,
it has not just to do with talent,
but it also has to do with understanding
and working with each other
and loving each other during
the bad times and the good times.
[somber music playing]
[machine whirring]
[metal clanking]
[indistinct chattering]
Did we do that? The DJ booth?
I asked Jeff to handle it.
- Will we have one?
- Yeah.
Hello?
What's your role?
Where?
[bright music playing]
[coach Mickey]
The Grand BINIverse was basically
a BINIverse spin-off,
which was their first
concert at the New Frontier Theater.
And the BINIverse
was an introduction to BINI.
[upbeat music playing]
For us, Grand BINIverse was a party,
but the party was no
longer just about BINI.
You were also part of it.
So, it was more like an experience.
An exchange between BINI
and the people watching them, the Blooms,
and those who fell
in love with their songs.
To us, it was a big party
where they were at the center,
and everyone joined in.
[upbeat music continues]
From the NFT
concert and performing abroad,
to KCON, to their performances on ASAP,
to Canada...
When they returned,
you could see their growth
and everything
that they had learned there.
It truly felt like a homecoming.
[Lauren] The stress was high at that level
because our NFT concert went really well.
People will always
expect a better show after that.
Okay, are we complete? Don't show me.
- This is it!
- Okay.
Ah! Oh my god!
[Stacey] It felt like
everythinghappened so fast
during the Grand BINIverse.
We only ran through
the whole show a few times.
I'm panicking! I'm panicking!
Ah!
[Sheena] BINI is in
a good place right now.
Every time I feel exhausted,
like really tired and completely drained,
I just remind myself
that this is what we dreamed of.
What would I rather choose?
Being exhausted from
work or having nothing going on?
[laughs] There’s no
time to breathe, just kidding!
If I got through it before, why not now?
[Maloi] We were able to
focus just months or weeks prior.
That’s the most
challenging part: having time. It’s time.
[upbeat music continues]
[Aiah] The Grand BINIverse
was lighter for us
compared to the last time.
In NFT, it was our first concert,
so we were still gauging,
still figuring things out.
Wow!
- Relax.
- [laughs]
[laughing]
We have more rest days these days.
We started talking
about needing this and that,
and we decided to set a hard
stop somewhere in our schedule.
That really helped a lot.
I mean, it shows.
So, more rest days! [chuckles]
[stirring music playing]
[Colet] BINI is still healthy for us.
We really had a great
time during the Grand BINIverse.
We didn't have to worry
too much about the possibility
of someone missing the rest of the concert
due to illness.
[Lauren] Their bodies
and minds were already trained
to perform at Araneta.
So, they felt more confident
in their ability to deliver
an outstanding performance.
- Oh my!
- Ah!
Oh my god!
[laughter]
[screaming]
[stirring music continues]
Oh no!
I really can’t do this!
Oh my god!
That was the Grand BINIverse,
and it had to be grand.
I’m not really into rides, guys.
This feels like one.
And Gwen has a fear of
heights. Just our luck, really.
We're so high up.
[Mikha] Who would want to
perform on a 360-degree stage
with an 8-member
girl group and 26 besties?
Just us.
For me, I have full
trust in Director Lauren.
When he says it,
I'm really confident that we can do it.
Ready? Lift the stage.
[chuckles nervously]
- Oh my god.
- Ooh la la, Mamma Mia!
[screaming]
[stirring music continues]
[coach Mickey] It was a discomfort.
No one was in their comfort zone.
Being in that situation,
we had to learn to
adapt and figure things out.
"How will we make it work?"
I think that was the biggest challenge.
We were only able to
put everything together
during the technical rehearsals.
[stirring music continues]
- [bell dings]
- [music stops]
[Colet] She was always
good at hiding her problems.
She always looked happy,
so it was really hard to tell
if she had a problem or not.
[morose music playing]
[Jhoanna] She told us in our group chat
that her dad wasn't doing well,
but we decided not to press.
We held back from
asking, "How's your dad?"
because we wanted to give her space.
A few days before,
Maloi was still with her family
because we were coming
from the All Saint’s Day break.
[somber music playing]
[Maloi] Two weeks before Grand BINIverse,
Mama noticed,
“Your dad is getting thinner.”
I told them to have him checked.
Then, we found out
that he had an enlargement of the heart.
He was okay though,
I even saw his test results.
Everything was fine except for his heart,
which had an enlargement.
So, he really needed to be taken care of.
We haven't rehearsed everything yet.
So...
I feel like we'll be here until 3 AM.
3 AM.
The next day,
my sibling messaged me saying
that Papa had a stroke.
They took him to the hospital,
and I wasn't able to
go because I had work.
I was shocked. I was at work at the time.
I can't remember what I was working on,
I was in the middle of it,
so I couldn't function properly.
We messaged her, "What happened?"
And she wanted to
continue with the training.
- [somber music continues]
- Whoa!
Louder. One more time, let's go.
I couldn't hear.
His voice was so loud. It hurt.
Could you please tell them...
[Maloi] The voice
message my sibling received
was just a voice message.
He said,
"Where’s Mama? I can't move."
Turns out he had a stroke.
I really cried for several days.
Because, you know,
my frustration from last time
was that no one would
greet me when I'd come home
Then I find out that Papa got sick.
[Mikha] Of course, when a parent of ours
gets sick or has a problem,
it affects all of us
because it feels like
they're also our moms and dads,
or something like that.
We worried about Maloi
because it's not...
It's not easy especially if it's family.
And then,
on top of all the training and fatigue,
I still have to think about it.
I'm training for what? For who?
A-And they're incomplete.
We were shocked to find
out she was just in the condo.
Then she said she wasn't going home.
So we said, "Why? You need to go home
so at least you'll feel at
ease being by your dad’s side."
She really didn't want to,
despite all our insistence.
Because she wanted to distract herself
and didn't want to bother us
since the concert was coming up.
[somber music continues]
[Sheena] She chose to stay in training
because if you miss
even just one day of training
for the Grand BINIverse,
you'll miss so much.
Us girls, we felt bad because we thought,
"Oh no, maybe Maloi will get distracted."
Because of what happened with her dad,
she didn't know what to prioritize.
But it seems
she prefers having someone with her
rather than being alone.
So, we understood. Okay.
[somber music continues]
I went home for just one night,
he was already in the hospital.
He was so thin,
so restless.
He wasn't
the dad I was used to.
The doctor said that his brain
He had like a--
It's a--
He had some bleeding.
So when I had
the opportunity to go home, I went home.
I just spent that time with Papa.
[Colet] I saw
that Maloi can handle herself well.
She's very
professional in everything she does.
[Mikha] We're proud of you, Maloi.
And we're so glad you pushed through it.
It definitely hasn't been easy.
I know how much your family means to you,
and I hope your dad gets well.
Yeah.
[thrilling music playing]
[crowd screaming]
[crowd chanting “ey”]
[Stacey] I think about the time
when I was lining up in
the parking lot of Araneta Coliseum,
with thousands of
others who were also dreaming.
We all shared
the same dream of getting in.
Mommy said she remembered,
we were just on the side, sitting down.
We didn't know what to do.
Then we were watching
the dancers, the ones auditioning.
[Stacey] From not knowing what to do
to having BINI's first-ever
concert at the Araneta Coliseum,
It’s just so amazing. Truly,
God aligned the stars for BINI.
[staff squealing]
[thrilling music continues]
[Colet] When we were still trainees,
we would just edit BINI,
put them on stage.
And that was
our phone wallpaper for months.
[thrilling music continues]
[Colet] So now
we really see that it’s happening.
The impact of
our Grand BINIverse is amazing
because we didn't know
that it would happen this year.
Aah! Lord!
[Mickey] Jhoanna says it all the time,
"Araneta!"
Good luck, girls!
Because every artist here,
in OPM history,
they always talk about Araneta.
[thrilling music continues]
Let's go, let's go!
[music fades]
[flatline sfx]
- ["Pantropiko" by BINI playing]
- [crowd screaming, applauding]
[BINI singing]
♪ Pantropiko, Pantropiko, oh ♪
Pantropiko, Pantropiko, oh
[BINI] Let me hear you say, B-I-N-I, BINI!
Everybody! B-I-N-I, BINI!
Louder! B-I-N-I, BINI!
One more time! B-I-N-I, BINI!
[Lauren] With all the light sticks-- Wow,
it looked beautiful,
they were surrounded by stars all around.
It was quite an achievement.
I saw you At an unexpected time
You came suddenly
As if it was no coincidence
Is this fate?
If you're there and
you can even be closer,
it gives them a different feeling,
that you’re reaching out to them
and you're even closer to them.
Because I’ve realized
and I keep on telling them,
“Girls, every time you perform,
one smile from
you means the world to everyone.”
What is this that I'm feeling?
Oh, shocks, is this love?
Is what I'm feeling for real?
[Maloi] So during Karera, right?
We were in the cart...
Every day, I feel happier
Ever since I saw
you The worries are fading away
[Maloi] At that time,
he stood at the side of the stairs,
and that's when I cried so much
because I didn't
know he was going to watch.
I was just so happy because...
even though he was sick,
he still came.
["Pantropiko" continues]
[Lauren] A lot has been posted on TikTok
and various social media platforms
about how BINI,
the girls, and BINI's music
have affected many people
during their most challenging times.
It got to a point where
I didn't know what I was fighting for.
I didn't know what
life I was fighting for.
But because of BINI and their songs,
I was reminded
that maybe it's not too late
to try for my dreams again.
Maybe I guess I'll try again,
maybe life's still worth living.
[Sheena] And then,
when I looked up, the place was packed.
It was so beautiful, I thought,
maybe it would've been
better if Mommy was here watching.
Because she never
got to see me in BINI at all.
She didn't get to see BINI Sheena,
and that was her dream.
Mommy was a huge
KPOP fan, so if she saw me,
she'd be so proud.
And if she were still here,
she would've watched the whole three days.
It was so beautiful.
I'm getting teary-eyed.
Maybe if the concert
wasn't good, I wouldn't cry.
It would've been like,
"It's okay, if you missed this,
it wasn't good anyway."
But it was beautiful.
[Lauren] You're not just performers,
you are a source of inspiration.
That's enough reason for you
to give your 100% performing on stage.
[coach Mickey] To be BINI,
you have to be involved.
You have to share
your opinion and your heart.
Is it a heartbreak,
is it pain, or whatever?
This all matters to become an artist.
So now I see that they're maturing more.
Their voice is now
very important to everyone.
[Jonathan] Through
the music of BINI right now,
we've encapsulated
the pop culture of today.
This is the music I danced to,
the one we sang at graduation...
those kinds of
memories are embedded forever.
[Corey] The BINI girls
are very, very good women.
Their advocacies are noble.
And they incorporate that in their music,
from self love to mental health.
And when they believe in something,
they really stand by that.
[Carlo] What BINI represents
is the unlimited
potential for Filipino talent to shine.
I'd like to think BINI opened the doors
for many other Filipino artists
to be recognized globally.
[Roxy] Making music
should touch the heart of the Filipinos.
That's what's very important for us.
[coach Mickey] What they did right now,
seeing their hard work and discipline,
and talent and where it can lead,
I think that's the legacy
that they are doing already now
for the next generation.
That will last forever,
because I think that's
the change we needed.
[Lauren] As they carry
the banner of the Philippines
to the international arena,
the Blooms will still be
with them on that journey.
Nothing is impossible, we can dream big,
and we can really aspire to be bigger than
what we thought we could do.
[audience cheering, applauding]
[Gwen] Infinity.
It reminds me of the time when we started.
We were so young
when we first did this hand sign,
and having something like that
made us feel like we're getting there.
Like, we're about to debut--
I mean, we trained for a long time.
Even though the figure was repetitive,
it means that the eight
of us all dreamed together,
and little by little,
we achieved our dreams.
We come from different backgrounds,
but we all meet at a certain point.
We went through a lot together,
and at the same time,
we are still growing.
We are continuously growing.
We are never stagnant for a long time.
We are always willing to
get to know each other more
and willing to
connect with each other more.
It's not just the good times,
we're also there for
each other during bad times.
Of course,
they have their own struggles too,
but I know I can always count on them,
and I'm so grateful for that.
BINI still has a long way to go,
and I know we'll achieve so much more.
Like I said,
I'm excited to grow old with them.
And our goal is to
have kids together, right?
[chuckles]
It's engraved in me. It's like a tattoo.
It has been my life.
It's part of my blood.
Who I am and who I will be...
It's because I was a BINI
that made me who I will be.
Our love for each other is endless.
It's infinite.
We will treasure
our memories, our moments together,
the struggles,
the laughter, and the tears.
We'll treasure it forever.
I love them so much.
Aww. Uh...
Eight until the end.
That's what we hold on to,
that no one will give up.
There's still a lot of
people we can inspire,
and we have a long
journey ahead as a group.
["Na Na Na" by BINI playing]
[Sheena] Wow,
our leader is booked and busy.
She's doing so many things.
But it's not like she was forced into it.
She does everything because she wants to.
[Colet] Twenty four hours isn't enough
for her to do everything she wants to do.
[Maloi] I'm so proud
to see her handling it all,
and that she takes
care of us like her sisters
even though we're older than her.
Is that true?
They're just trying to flatter me.
Being a leader also means
being able to follow your members
and listening to them.
[screaming]
[overlapping chatter]
[Mikha] Aiah
focused on herself a lot more.
She really tried to
build herself up from that.
She has found
her happiness and what she wants to do.
When Aiah isn't around,
it feels like our day isn't complete
because we don't
have anyone to laugh with.
She's naturally funny, too.
[Aiah] Based on my dad's words,
it felt like I just played around,
which is actually a good thing.
I just enjoyed myself.
[Jhoanna] She's not "Anger" anymore.
So when I see
tweets about her being angry,
I want to reply and say,
"Hey, remove that image of Colet,
she's really changed now."
She said, "They were
the ones who said I was always angry,
and now they're mad at me." [chuckles]
[Aiah] She is joy,
sadness, and even anxiety.
And it turns out she's just
like everyone else. She's human.
She experiences all those emotions.
[Colet] I really
enjoyed the Grand BINIverse.
My goal was just to smile and smile.
[Maloi] Stacey's
growth this year is also incredible.
She really bloomed this year.
She found what's perfect for her.
[Sheena] I also see that she's really
fighting for her confidence,
and once she finds it, that's it.
She's slaying it.
She's able to show
her natural self on camera.
[Colet] With Gwen, you can see her growth
when she tries new things that scare her.
She's really out there facing her fears.
[Mikha] Gwen is also one of my babies,
even though she is older than me.
She may seem quiet and shy,
but when it's just us two,
she'll talk your ears off.
Gwen was so extra
during the Grand BINIverse.
She was so extra.
[Gwen] It was the first
time all of my family got to watch.
I felt very inspired to
perform since my family was there.
[Sheena] With Maloi, seeing her okay,
and that she's fighting makes me happy.
And it warms my heart to
see that she's managing all this.
[Stacey] I admire
how skilled she is in her art,
her style, and how smart she thinks.
[Maloi] I'm super
grateful that I am emotionally stable.
I'm mentally stable,
despite what happened to my father.
I don't want to! I might cry if I do.
[Colet] Sheena is so mature now.
But no matter what,
she listens to us, her sisters.
[Gwen] She just
keeps getting better and better.
She's more agile, and more energetic.
I don't know why she's like that.
They say the older you get,
the less energy you have.
But it's the opposite for her.
Even if she wants to be joyful,
and she wants us to be happy,
it's also okay to
open up the sadness to us.
[Sheena] I grew up. I'm 20 years old.
There are no more teens in BINI.
The girls used to say that if
we're not teenagers anymore,
or once I turn 20,
that means we're getting old.
That's what changed in me.
I want to improve my dancing.
I want to dance really good, you know?
[Aiah] People know
Mikha as the nonchalant one.
But she's really extra, too.
She's super extra.
[Jhoanna] I noticed
her growth and how she's opening up more.
I noticed how Mikha
started to enjoy things more,
and she's more vocal
about her love for BINI.
I don't know why,
but she wasn't like that before.
She told us how being in
BINI is one of her life's highlights.
I was surprised to hear
Mikha say something like that.
It's fate.
Corny, right?
Fate brought us all together,
and how everything is happening.
But I'm sure this will be a long journey.
It's a big accomplishment
to be known in the Philippines.
But to be known worldwide?
That's another story.
And that's another story that we will tell
in the next chapter.
["Na Na Na" by BINI playing]
This is BINI Jhoanna.
Two, three, thank you!
["Huwag Muna
Tayong Umuwi" by BINI playing]
Bye.
Hi guys, I'm Mikha. Two, three, thank you!
What did the other girls say?
Hi, I'm BINI Stacey.
Two, three, thank you!
This one?
Hi guys, I'm BINI Gwen.
Two, three, thank you!
- Aah! Oh, there's more.
- Last one, Maloi.
Hi everyone, I'm Maloi from BINI.
Two, three, thank you!
I'm BINI Colet. Two, three, thank you!
Eyy!
Hi, I'm BINI Sheena.
Two, three, thank you!
Who's your bias? [laughter]
Hi, I'm BINI Aiah. Two, three, thank you!
["Huwag Muna
Tayong Umuwi" by BINI continues]