What did you think?
Are you a woman?
Yes
I'm a man
But I'm not a woman
You can't call me that
I'm a man
I was like, can I be a little fatter?
I was like...
A little fatter?
Okay
Oh, I'm in the wrong place
So, I really want to ask
Does this count as a double-double?
It does
Okay, this gentleman
I'm curious, is this person next to you a friend or girlfriend?
Girlfriend
Wedding date
I think we need to understand
Why two people have double standards for each other
Congratulations
I want to tell everyone
I want to encourage the audience
Including you
To be in a relationship
If you are in a relationship
Don't let go easily
Really
Because you may be in a relationship
You have been too long
Too long
So long that you have forgotten how ugly you look now
Do you know?
If you forget how to judge your beauty
Or the state you are in now
I will teach you a method
If you see a person on the road
And that person is yourself
Then you ask yourself
Would I want to date this person?
Wow
So sad and silent
I have to say that letting go is harder than I thought
If you have to find another person
The one who is willing to hold your hand
It's harder
Especially at my middle age
I don't know why every time I see someone getting married
I have some feelings
Then I will write those feelings
In the wedding card to be sent out
I will write
The future
It can't be sweet forever
So when you want to grab her face
Please think about it
I will think about it
When you want to grab her face
Please think about it
The reason you fell in love with her
I want to go to Singapore
Today is decided
They want me to manage your office
Can we
Try again?
Bye bye
Lele
Are you interested in coming back to talk show?
Yes
Sorry, are you serious?
You have potential
Are you following me?
No, don't misunderstand
I am the audience
Okay
I just want to say
Thank you tonight
Thank you for what?
Thank you for making me
More happy
You are welcome
Hello
Do you have any more play?
No
Okay
Okay, thank you
Thank you
Now is the time
I will wait
Thank you
Okay
See me
See
Don't be like this
You are not yet accurate
Really
See
Lele
So happy
Oh my god
Let me see
Is it you?
So happy
Sorry
Cheers
It's all watermelon flavor
Let's welcome Chen Lele
Chen Lele
So hot
So scared
So sweet
Yes
In those
Seems to be relaxed daily life
When did we start to forget
The reason for chasing each other
So happy
Thank you
I am Chen Lele
I know
I will be at my dad's house
I will be there on time
The restaurant looks really expensive
The pressure is too big
Without money
It's just that your house
You are here
The show is all in a hurry
Can't come
How long have you been here
I have been here for half a year
For a lifetime
Yes, my dad is back
You came just right
Take a picture with me
Wait a minute
My dad is back
Low angle
Low
Lower
Wait a minute
All in
Yes
Right
Okay
Thank you
I received your address
Not bad
Okay
Bye
I'll buy you something
In the kitchen
I don't need anything
Just need you to accompany me
You are busy too
How about it
Now the mahjong doesn't fight
That Mrs. Li
The knuckles are too long
The fingers are deformed
Can't wear the ring
She said it's not good to play cards like this
Then you find
You find a new card
We are old
I'm used to playing with the old
Come a new one
I have to get used to it again
Forget it
Come on
Hurry up
This big thing
Wait a minute
Don't touch
Hurry up
This game is really a long time
Okay, now it's finally water to the city
You know
How long did this guy count on you
So you can become a close partner
Wait a minute
Please prove it
What is算計
You have to have a comment
I think
My junior has studied abroad
Then know how to deal with foreigners
So Zhang Kai promised
What did you promise
The main thing today is to celebrate
Our Singapore branch is open
Yes
Then I want to invite my junior today
Are you interested in going abroad
I understand what the senior means
For overseas expansion
I am interested
Then it's done
Interested
No no no
What are you talking about
Golden ball
Thank you senior
Thank you
Okay, don't mind them
Legal men
Just talk about work
it is good
But
Wait a minute
The most important but came out
But
But I just came back to Taiwan
Then I want to spend more time with me
With my wife and my father-in-law
But senior, I will
Take a good care of it
Thank you senior
Will your wife come
Correct
I said I would come several times before
Didn't appear
Correct
Is he working
Yes
He is busy recently
Your Internet pot
I'm sorry
I'll wash it again
No need
The water in the water tank is clean
No need to eat
No problem
I'm looking for time
Let people look at the keys again
Don't worry about me
I can do it myself
By the way
Next weekend
I'm going to go to the Dandan Valley with your uncle
Two days of recording
Two days
What age recording
Younger than you
By the way
After eating
You take a few packs of noodles back to Zhang Kai
He said he liked it very much last time
He is talking to you
What son-in-law
See the donkey
Oh my god
What's wrong
What's the matter
I think Zhang Kai has a very important party tonight
I forgot
Take it after eating
No no no
Be careful
I will call me
Come with me
I have to go
I play crazy all day
Can't stand it
Sorry Kai
I'm on the way now
Almost there
Wait for me
Jason, what are you doing
It's not coming after dragging for so long
This is a private conversation
Do you think Jason is one or zero
You are very boring
Wait a minute
Let me tell you
Our office is very open
As long as the ability is OK
Nothing else
Because I think
I'm quite humorous
But sometimes I can't get his jokes
Really?
Can't get
Come
Let me introduce to you
This is my partner
Roger
Hello
Come
Sit down
Let's introduce
Just let me go
Hello
This is my in-law
Yes, I am his in-law
I am Amy
Hello
I
Is your wife here?
Yes
Hello
There are many cars outside
Sorry for being late
Your wife is not here
Do you think it's a joke?
Is it a joke to run to the school?
I am
Excuse me, sir
Can you help me change it?
Are you sure I'm older than you?
Excuse me, sir
Can you help me change it?
I really have
I'm in a hurry
I'm sorry
Okay, I'm going in
I really envy the life of my sister
She has artistic spirit
I'm interested in it
It's fun
If you're envious
I was the only one who didn't come last time
She doesn't have time
What kind of life is it now?
Write a report every day
Write it in the middle of the night
Are you a new assistant professor?
Yes, I am a deputy professor
I really became a student soldier
Please
Everyone is so hard
I'm the only one who wants to retire soon
You've earned enough
You can retire quickly
You can rely on you
Her name is
Roger
Roger, what do you do?
Wait, let me try it
She looks very tasteful when she wears clothes
It should be related to art
She just started to get in touch with stage plays
She is really into art
So strange
Stage play
Last time I had a classmate
Asked me to sponsor a stage play
I asked around
I heard that stage plays now
Make a lot of money
But no one watches
What do you know?
You're the only one who doesn't watch
Actors' work is actually very hard
They have to burn the money on the stage
And many people's income is unstable
No, your friends don't understand
They are outsiders
Actually they may think
It's easy for actors to talk on stage
It's actually called training, right?
Not easy
Thank you
Wait, wait
How is Singapore?
I will consider
Sorry
Come
Sorry to keep you waiting
My wife is here
Welcome
Look
I'll sit here
Wait
Honey, are you too rushed?
I think she is too rushed
So
Do you want to sort it out?
No, it's okay
Sorry
I'm sorry
First time meeting
Okay
Take your time
She just came and she is leaving
Are you okay?
Do you want to take care of her?
It's okay
Enough
Come
I'm also having breakfast
Thank you
Never mind
I have something better
See you
Okay
I have to go
Our usual wait
I have a very pinny National Monument
Am I です
Sorry
Okay
Goodbye
How are you doing?
Have you been well?
I've been fine
Really?
I see
Don't worry
Bye
See you
You're tired after working so late.
You must be very hungry.
Hurry up and eat.
Okay, thank you.
Wait.
Before we eat, we need to celebrate.
Today is the first time we all gathered together.
We're late.
Let's have a toast.
Let's have a toast first.
No problem.
Sorry.
Let's drink together.
I'll pay.
Sorry.
We were just talking about you.
Really?
We're really curious about you.
What kind of job are you doing?
You work so late.
No, I like to work during the day.
He's working at a bank.
Bank?
Really?
Yes.
He just became the director recently.
So he's a bit busier.
Thank you.
You can ask him about any financial issues in the future.
That's great.
You're amazing.
I've always been different about numbers.
I'll ask Le Le more questions if I have any problems.
By the way, we have a reading meeting.
How about we meet up?
We can share some financial information with the ladies.
Okay.
What kind of reading is it?
We usually read about our children,
cooking, and spiritual growth.
Sometimes, we'll have art.
Let's all come together next time.
How about this?
Let's toast to everyone.
Let's make the overseas version of the painting
more famous.
Let's toast to everyone.
The overseas version of the painting can be more famous.
I'm relieved to hear you say that.
Let's toast.
To us, overseas...
I broke the pipe in the kitchen.
Is it fixed?
Yes.
They said they'd send me to...
You think I'm embarrassing you?
I'm sorry.
Are you going to stop now?
Do you think you'll be okay every time you don't talk?
I think you're in a bad mood now.
I can't discuss things with you.
So you chose not to talk?
My dad said he and my mom have never had a fight in our lives.
It's fine if we don't argue or communicate.
But what happened?
We're in a different situation from your parents.
No.
We're exactly the same.
I remember this expression of yours.
Why can you always escape so calmly?
Why do you always need to be so educated?
Do you know silence is the most perfect way to express your feelings?
Is this thing that serious?
You don't recognize my job?
I don't not recognize your job.
But have you ever cared about how I feel?
Have you put me in the top priority?
I told you about something so important today.
But you still forgot.
I told you.
My dad's kitchen is ruined.
Don't take your dad as an excuse.
You know how much you care about your dad.
To be honest,
I eat more than you do.
You're just like your dad.
You're just yourself.
Living in your own world.
I'm sorry.
I was talking...
No, no.
It's my fault.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have been late.
But this doesn't mean
you can humiliate me in front of everyone.
Why would I humiliate you?
If my job
is not enough to make Ge
a wife to me,
then we have nothing to say.
Don't be like this, okay?
Just think about it.
You're not in the same social circle.
I forgot.
I was bullied tonight.
I was bullied.
I was invited to their reading party tonight.
What?
Do you want to pee?
I want to pee, too.
You go first.
You...
Let's go together.
Okay.
It's okay.
I'll go first.
Honestly,
we've discussed it many times.
I can afford to support you now.
You can change to a relatively
easy job.
What kind of job is easy?
Staying at home without working is the easiest.
I didn't ask you to quit your job.
You go to the hospital to work during the day.
You tell jokes at night.
Did I say anything?
I come back from work every night.
I can't see anyone.
I also hope that
we have our own little days.
At the same time, I also hope
you can slowly
integrate into my life.
Do you understand?
I know.
But
I'm just not used to
that kind of occasion, that kind of social circle.
Are you okay?
You don't need to be so hostile.
I'm not.
You're not?
Are you sure?
You really have a good eye
to see me
and my colleagues from the office.
Even if they are good friends,
you still think they have a purpose.
They don't?
Why do they have to?
They just want to know
what my wife looks like.
They want to see and understand you more.
That's all.
I really doubt that
they want to understand me more.
I'm not.
Didn't your dad always tell you
to face everyone
with a relaxed attitude.
No matter if that person is better
or better than you,
you don't need to please or flatter them.
So I'm not trying to please them.
Then you don't need to be a thorn in their side.
Why do you have to choose
such a fancy restaurant?
They want to celebrate.
Of course you have to choose a restaurant.
Did you hear that?
They were chatting
and talking about something all night.
That's how their lives are.
So you can't be sure of anything.
Calm down. Listen to me.
Look at my face.
You're my wife.
You're a very important part of my life.
I just want you to
get to know them
and understand them.
That's all.
Is it hard?
But am I...
Am I also
a part of your life
that you want to be?
So you're back to normal now?
You know, I really...
I really don't understand you.
You were so happy
and humorous on stage.
You're so good at joking.
So you think I'm a
boring person
in private?
I don't think so.
I just hope you don't take
this matter so seriously.
So you don't think
what you did today is not okay?
I think I'm not okay.
I want to apologize to you.
Are you serious?
What do you want me to do
to make you think
I'm serious?
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
I...
I really want to believe that...
I work very hard every day.
I work very hard,
but I'm also very anxious.
Not everyone
is like you.
Your family is rich
and you can send me to school.
Your parents
can be old and happy now.
And you can be free and free every day.
What's the biggest
mistake in your life?
It's probably that time
when you thought
you were a partner.
You failed.
What's wrong with you?
Are you belittling
my effort?
Is this how my family is?
Am I wrong?
That's not what I meant.
You're not.
I was born in a poor family.
I'm a good teacher.
Am I wrong?
Or is it my parents' fault?
Do I live a hard life?
Even if I work twice or three times
more than others,
they don't even recognize me.
Do you know that
I'm a partner today?
Everyone thinks
I'm relying on my family,
my dad, and my mom.
That's not what I meant.
Then what do you mean?
I can tell you today
that I'm working harder than anyone else.
I'm working harder
than anyone else in this world.
I said I didn't mean that.
But everyone has their own hardships.
Then what do you mean?
You said it.
But you're easier than anyone else.
Do you always imagine
other people's lives
in your head?
Can you try to think
about other people's lives
a little more seriously?
Where are you going from now on?
I'm going to contact
careful concern to it.
But what about your harvesting skills?
Can you tell me...
This job...
What did they do wrong to annoy you?
They didn't bother me or annoy me at all
But I want to know...
I'm the only one in this world who feels helpless in life.
I stand on stage and talk about the problems I can't solve.
I laugh at those sad things.
And then those strangers laugh.
They understand.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Can you just...
Can you just tell me honestly...
What kind of trouble did this job cause you?
Can you stop being a funny actor?
Thank you for listening to me.
Where are you going?
Do you want me to tell you the truth?
You're leaving again.
I'm afraid I'll say something that will make us both regret it.
Le Le. Le Le.
I didn't mean that.
I didn't mean that either.
Honestly, why did you want to marry me?
Do you want to say it?
Because I...
I'm happy when I see you.
It's going to rain.
Come down.
What's wrong with your foot?
Do you need a doctor?
No.
Here, I'll give you this.
I'm sorry.
Le Le.
You're a hanger.
Let me through.
Le Le.
You feel very embarrassed.
You're embarrassed for saying that out loud.
You...
I'm embarrassed for saying that out loud.
I...
How do you like it?
I can't feel something Special.
What has happened?
Don't worry
But I have something to tell you
Forget it
You know
Just hateuga
Go
The pink is bad
Why is it not a pink?
Is it auxiliary?
Bye
Antigen
Second
Third
Four
five
Look
So cool
Second
Well
D入
patt considering
I
So
The pink
Everyone, let's welcome Chen Le Le!
Hello everyone, how are you? I'm Le Le.
I took a break for two weeks.
These two weeks are really important to me.
Because I need to think about whether I should get divorced or not.
I know, some of you must be thinking,
you need to think about the divorce for two weeks?
Okay, here's the thing.
I wanted to get divorced because two weeks ago,
I went to a very important dinner party at my husband's Lawyer's Office.
It was the one that celebrated the establishment of overseas branch companies.
They were meeting at a very high-end French restaurant.
The partner saw me and asked,
what does your wife do?
Let me add something.
I worked at a convenience store during the day,
and performed here at night.
My husband, a handsome and talented lawyer,
and a law firm partner,
stopped to think about it.
I was thinking, what would he say?
Would he say, I'm a convenience store employee,
or a talk show actor?
And in the middle of these two answers,
he finally decided to choose the bank's high-end manager.
Wow, that was really complicated for me.
You always didn't like my job.
You were so embarrassed to say it.
On the other hand, I thought,
the bank's high-end manager and the law firm partner
sounded like they were in the same team.
But I had limited knowledge.
I thought the bank's high-end manager
was very sensitive to numbers.
So that night, I was in all the conversations,
and added all kinds of numbers.
Did you know that last year,
there were 114,606 couples in Taiwan
who got married in the 4.88% interest rate.
But there were 47,887 couples who got divorced.
But it didn't work.
The divorce rate was 9.32%.
That's it!
I just pretended.
I pretended to be the last one.
I was about to succeed, but I failed.
Because when the dinner was over,
the ladies were waving their hands and saying goodbye.
Bye-bye, see you.
It was a very international farewell.
I said,
thank you for coming.
Please enjoy.
But you know what?
What made me the most angry was
that there were a couple in the partner group
who said,
Comrade Nan, you're so cool.
They didn't need to hide their identities.
So, can anyone tell me
that it's harder to be a comedy actor
than Comrade Nan?
But I think comedy actors are actually
a very noble profession.
Because they are very similar to lawyers.
We put our happiness
on the pain of others.
So, being a lawyer is amazing.
Okay, I admit it's amazing.
Because now, after I thought about the divorce,
I realized that if you're a lawyer,
you can help yourself to save a lawyer's fee.
Isn't that important?
So, I have to say,
my husband...
I remember when we were getting married,
I asked my husband
why he wanted to marry me.
He said he was happy to see me.
But now,
why can't he be happy to see me?
What's wrong with me?
Whether it's a smooth or a tough life,
rich or poor,
healthy or ill...
I'm sorry, I have to go.
We will be loyal to each other.
We will love each other
until the end of time.
When we were talking about this,
we didn't lie, did we?
No, right?
I remember every moment of the wedding.
We used to love each other so much.
But...
Why can't we love each other now?
Okay.
I am going to Singapore.
Alright.
Don't be angry.
Tell me,
do you stillの right to reserve a room for all of us?
I'll be working for the department now,
We've been working too hard.
Zhang Kai fell in love with me on the lowest day of his life.
But he decided to leave me on the highest day of his life.
Maybe we're not not in love anymore.
We've been working too hard.
Zhang Kai
Do you want us to be together and scold Zhang Kai?
Or do you want to go on the road that says,
I don't allow you to say that?
I respect his decision.
It's too official.
I mean it.
Why don't you move back to your dad's house?
I don't want to move back to that old house that looks like a ghost.
This bag is for you.
I forgot how nice it is to live alone.
You can go home and cook.
You won't feel guilty.
You can also carry a weight loss band at home.
Weight loss band?
Okay.
You have to become beautiful.
Everyone will come back.
Living alone is great.
You just have to take care of yourself.
At this age, everything has been filled with possibilities.
How about we live together after 30 years?
I went to see a community development.
That house is so beautiful.
It's perfect for the life of an old man.
Wait a minute, old man.
Are you serious?
Is this the topic of our dreams now?
You're exaggerating.
You're here.
Dad.
Kaihan.
You guys.
We're here to help.
Thank you.
You guys.
A-mei.
You can't.
You can just come home and live here.
I'll take care of you.
That's right.
How could Mr. Cheng say such a warm word?
Thank you.
You guys.
A-mei.
It's a waste of money.
You can just come home and live here.
Why do you rent a small room that's only ten minutes away from home?
I want to start over.
And if I really live there,
I'll start to clean up.
You'll regret it.
You put this down.
If you can't put it down, you put it there first.
No, no, no.
Don't move the garbage home.
You also piled up a pile of garbage at home.
You put it there first.
I'll clean up the garbage.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Okay.
I'm going to get something.
What?
Thank you.
Sure.
Leave it to us.
I also want something.
I'll get it for you.
Okay?
Hello, Mr. Cheng.
Hello.
This way, please.
Thank you.
What's going on between you and Zhang Kai?
Please.
I ran away from the scene.
I just don't want to talk about Zhang Kai and me.
It's a blessing to see you guys.
I heard a joke a few days ago.
The elder asked the child,
you won't get married or have children in the future.
When the family lights up during the New Year,
you'll know how lonely you are.
The daughter said,
I just don't get married.
I don't pay the electricity bill.
It's cold.
According to my experience,
I want to give you some advice on marriage.
You're the most unfit for marriage in Taipei, aren't you?
Listen to me.
It's the heaven and earth that makes people happy when they're together.
When they're not together,
it's the heaven that makes the earth unhappy.
Okay.
You should tell this to the aliens.
Aliens are willing to visit the earth
and look at the earth.
Don't you think they're very intelligent?
It's incredible.
I didn't expect that on the first day I moved in,
I was talking to my dad about aliens.
Don't you have something to take me back?
Here.
In the kitchen.
Okay.
Where do you think I should go?
Go home.
Su Fei and Jiayun are waiting for me there.
You go home. I go home.
My home is your home.
Okay.
Su Fei.
Su元.
Su Yuan.