[English subtitles are available]
[In A Class of Her Own]
[Episode 10]
Mr. Feng, what brings you here?
Mr. Feng is finally meeting me in person.
Did you hear thunder?
Crack boom, crack boom.
I need to collect my clothes.
Mr. Feng, what brings you here?
Lady Han,
I've read your letter.
There may be a misunderstanding
between us.
Mr. Feng, you exaggerate.
I've heard it all from Mr. Wen.
There's no misunderstanding between us.
I feel that...
my presence is quite unnecessary.
I should get going.
One thing at a time.
Set things straight with her.
Then we can talk.
I want you to be my witness.
It's so awkward.
Awkward? What about me?
That's not what I meant.
I'm just feeling embarrassed.
It's too late now.
Mr. Feng,
what were you saying?
Misunderstanding.
That's incorrect.
We have no misunderstanding.
Please forgive me, Ms. Han.
Today,
I have to clarify this matter.
Please speak your mind, Mr. Feng.
Thank you for you admiration.
But I'm busy with my school work.
Before I graduate,
I have no intention for romance.
I hope you understand.
Mr. Feng,
why are you saying things
that I don't like to hear?
You told me how touched you were
in your letter,
and you praised Mr. Wen's
literary talent.
Perhaps Mr. Wen didn't comprehend...
what I meant in the letter.
What do you mean then, Mr. Feng?
Lady Han, I'm telling you,
do not give your heart away easily,
don't be too subservient.
You'll only hurt yourself.
You can't force yourself to like someone.
Mr. Feng, I see your point.
I'm sorry to have bothered you
so many times.
Young Lady.
Young Lady, don't be sad.
-Young Lady.
-What should I do?
Will Mr. Feng hate me?
He won't. You're a nice girl.
Why would Mr. Feng hate you?
Young Lady,
don't be upset.
Even if you don't like Lady Han,
that was kind of harsh.
Look how upset you've made her.
You've played a prank on me
and lied to me.
Shouldn't I be upset, too?
I didn't intend for this to happen.
I think you just didn't intend to tell me.
A noble man makes an honourable living.
As a scholar, don't you know this?
I didn't mean to do it.
But you did it.
Can't you focus your efforts
on your studies instead?
I didn't mean to.
Can't you give me a different answer?
Believe it or not,
I didn't intend for this to happen.
I'm upset about it, too.
Mr. Yu, Young Lady has spent
so much money.
Yet this happened.
Don't you feel sorry?
You've paid so much for the lesson.
Of course it's worth it.
What lesson?
Feng Cheng Jun's message is clear.
He likes a girl who is
principled and has personality.
Lady Han, what you should do now...
is transform your pain into strength.
Better yourself.
Make yourself a person with dignity.
He'll look at you differently, then.
Once you have a clear goal,
everything will work in your favour.
Carry on.
-Young Lady...
-Xiao Qin, don't interrupt.
I thought you'd focus on your
studies after the observation period,
yet you started writing dialogue novels.
I thought you'd focus on your studies
after earning enough money,
yet you did such disgraceful thing.
I don't know whether
I can still trust you.
Don't yell at me. It's my fault
that I lied to you this time.
But you've been forcing your
beliefs on me time and again.
I've gotten over it.
So don't push it with me.
Little Brother,
you've disappointed me.
From now on, you're not allowed
to leave the academy.
I'm not a prisoner.
You have no power over me.
Get out of my way.
[I...]
[Was I wrong to speak to him like that?]
[How could I speak to him that way?]
[I was too rash.]
Mr. Yu, you're absolutely right.
I believe you.
Lady Han, you're indeed sensible.
Feng Cheng Jun has no idea
how lucky he is.
Xiao Qin.
How much do you need this time?
Let me see.
The concept, material, manpower...
all comes down to...
Le Xuan, I need to speak with you.
Excuse us, we're talking business here.
Lady Han, I'll tell you the truth.
Brother Feng was never pleased to receive
your love letters.
Le Xuan and I have been lying to you.
-Wait...
-I'd like to apologize to you.
Le Xuan,
you can keep the money.
Lady Han is a kind girl.
We should stop deceiving her.
Wen Bin, are you drunk?
What nonsense are you talking about?
This is none of your business.
Go away...
I'm chiefly responsible for this matter.
I must set Lady Han straight.
Lady Han, don't mind him.
He doesn't know what we are talking
about right now.
That's why he's speaking rashly.
Lady Han,
I'm telling the truth.
You're a beautiful girl.
You shouldn't pander to others
in a humble manner.
That's not the kind of girl
Brother Feng likes.
You're right.
Lady Han, did you hear that?
Wise advice, isn't it?
Mr. Yu told me the same thing just now.
You two are such good friends.
Xiao Qin.
-Young Lady...
-That's enough.
Mr. Yu.
Have you lost your conscience?
What a flake.
Young Lady,
judging by Mr. Wen and Mr. Yu's behavior,
they must've fallen out.
Probably because of money.
So unreliable.
Looks like he has swindled
a lot of money out of us.
He's a fraud, a big fat fraud.
Is that so?
No wonder they look like
they're having a dispute.
Young Lady, let's hire someone better.
Let's go.
Hey, Lady Han.
Wen Bin,
do you realise you've just ruined
a big deal?
Le Xuan,
stop making money through unethical means.
Do you know you've just cost me
a rich client?
Let us make some plans together...
to make money morally.
Us?
Who was the one that boldly declared...
he doesn't want ill-gotten gains?
And now you say "us"?
Excuse me, Brother Wen Bin.
Our friend-ship has
been scuttled by you.
We can still raise it out of the water.
Even if we salvage it,
it'd have been wrecked.
It's too late.
Don't be so petty.
You're interesting.
How can someone desperate for money
do such a stupid thing?
I know what I can or cannot do
to make money.
Le Xuan, you call
yourself a businessman.
You should know...
that credibility is the
foundation of a business.
I'm a bit confused today.
I can't talk about this right now.
I've learned a lot from today's class.
-Have you?
-Yes.
It's good that you're learning.
I like this teacher's teaching style.
I see.
You guys go ahead.
If I'm not mistaken,
you're thinking about how to make money.
Do you regret it?
I would only regret...
if I make ill-gotten money.
Then what are you planning to do?
What else can I do?
I'll take up writing jobs from Mr. Chao...
to stay afloat.
Good for you.
However,
you should stop writing
your dialogue novel.
Your fourth volume of Where Love Begins...
is too brilliant.
It was being circulated
among the students.
In the end, Mr. Li Hu found out about it.
It's now under strict investigation,
do you understand?
Every time I see your pitiful face,
it makes my heart ache.
How about this? I'll look for...
some better paying writing jobs for you.
I thought you said our friend-ship...
has been scuttled by me?
I bought a new ship.
You're the best, Le Xuan.
Well,
that's because I like you a lot.
It's such a cheesy thing...
to say between two men.
Alright,
I have an errand to run
in South Street tonight.
I'll see you at...
Mu Lai Bookstore then.
"Eminence is the source from which
all goodness spring."
"Expansion is the amalgamation
of excellences."
"Fruitfulness is the harmony
of all that is right."
"Determination is the faculty of action."
The benevolent shall preside over men.
The righteous shall appease all creation.
The powerful shall live in harmony
with nature.
The steadfast shall rule nations.
A noble man practises four virtues.
Namely eminence, expansion, fruitfulness
and determination.
Wen Bin is giving me such a headache.
You're such a selfish guy.
I haven't even spoken,
and you're having a headache already?
Is something giving you a headache?
I need you to ask around about two men.
Which daring duo...
has offended the notorious Lei Ao?
Ke Shi Jun, Qin Bei Chuan.
I've never heard of them before.
You have a lot of connections.
Help me to find out their whereabouts.
This is the first time I've heard you
ask for help.
Alright. I'll do it.
I'll help you.
The class is not until later.
Is he in a hurry?
You're going out again?
Yes.
I'm going to South Street.
It's midnight.
Here.
Make two copies...
for each of these books.
How much can I earn from these?
I've pulled some strings...
to get you these copying jobs.
He's right.
Thank you for helping us again,
Mr. Le Xuan.
Not you.
Just him.
The one and only Wen Bin.
You won't be able to make
a profit from it this time.
I understand.
You seem reluctant.
Why? Do you still want to
earn money unethically?
I do not.
A noble man makes money
through honourable means.
Listen to yourself,
you sound like Feng Cheng Jun.
Don't talk about that petty guy.
What's wrong?
Did you scuttle your friend-ship with him?
He was the one who scuttled it.
Aren't you going to buy a new ship?
No, it's better this way.
I'm free to come and go everyday.
Just leave it there.
Go back to your room.
Put out the lights.
Here, please lift your arm.
Junior, you're so hardworking.
Unlike some people...
who don't clean up their own mess.
Excuse me.
Come here.
Are you two having a fight?
I don't know if this could
be considered a fight.
So it's a fight.
How about this?
Let's work together tonight...
and kick this obnoxious
guy out of here.
This sounds bad.
There's nothing bad about it.
He has been really
annoying these few days.
Moping about every day...
like the world owes him something.
Senior,
let's just pretend he's invisible.
Have you found anything on those men?
Shush.
Lower your voice.
I don't understand what you're afraid of.
You missed out a man.
Who?
Li Hu.
According to sources from the capital,
Qin Bei Chuan, Ke Shi Jun...
were fugitives, wanted
by the imperial court.
The other man who was on the run
with them was Li Hu.
Tell me more about it.
I've also heard that...
Ke Shi Jun, Qin Bei Chuan and Li Hu...
were the students of Yunzhou
scholar Xue Ding Kun,
like your brother Lei Ze Xun 18 years ago.
They were scholars
of Yun Shang Academy.
But why aren't their names...
on the executioner's list?
They are wanted by the imperial court.
They must've escaped from execution.
Do you know where they are?
Brother,
calm down.
I've heard that...
they disappeared without a trace
when things went south.
I think they must have gone into hiding...
to save their skins.
No matter where they're hiding,
I'll find them and get to the bottom
of this.
Yun is so vast.
It won't be easy...
to find those guys.
They were scholars
of Yun Shang Academy.
There must be records of them.
They were expelled.
Their names were taken off the book.
Unless...
[Diligence Pavilion]
Here, take a look.
This essay...
is so...
What's with that get-up?
Are you here to clean...
the Diligence Pavilion?
Mr. Li,
Lei Ze Xin has become rather cute
these days.
Stop punishing him.
I didn't give them any punishment.
Principal Feng, you've misunderstood.
We've come here to clean
on our own initiative.
Lei Ze Xin saw how dusty
this pavilion was.
It has been troubling him ever since.
How could he let his teachers dwell
in such filth?
He won't allow it.
So...
he brought me here...
to do our beloved teachers a favour.
Are you sure...
these were the words Lei Ze Xin said?
Of course.
Good for him.
Wonderful.
Good, he's worthy to be taught.
What a miracle it is to hear Lei Ze Xin
refer to us as his "beloved teachers".
It doesn't make sense at all.
Miss, how about this?
Let's take a walk in front.
Sure, let's go.
What a coincidence.
Are you talking to me?
Is there anyone else here?
So you can talk.
I'm not a mute.
You have been silent for a while.
I thought you've become mute.
It's my freedom to pretend
to be deaf or mute.
Aren't you mad at me?
It's been so long.
I'm not angry anymore.
Such a bore.
Has your anger subsided,
or has it worsened?
Take a guess.
I'm too stupid for that.
You're so good at lying.
You call yourself stupid?
So, Mr. Deaf and Mute,
where are you going?
South Street.
What a coincidence. Me too.
Let's walk together.
This is the only way.
We can only walk together.
Come again.
I'll walk this way.
Me too.
It seems inconvenient.
Nothing is inconvenient.
You do your things, I do mine.
Let's go our separate ways.
Mr. Chao.
Misters,
how are you here together?
We met each other on our way here.
What should I do?
Deal with Mr. Feng first.
My work will be overdue.
I've copied it all for you.
If you say so, Mr. Feng.
There should be no problem,
You've been working day and night...
just to copy this for me?
If I hadn't done it,
how could you focus on your studies?
I may be poor,
but I have integrity.
I don't accept charity.
I've earned these with my labour.
It didn't come from my family.
If you feel bad about it,
you can pay me back.
You should've told me.
Why did you lie to me?
You were the one who lied.
Mr. Wen, don't let...
Mr. Feng's hard work go into waste.
The fact that he hunkered down...
shows how much he cares about you.
I hope you understand.
Is there anything else you've
been lying to me about?
Nothing.
Don't lie to me again.
You too.
I'll do my best.
What do you mean by that?
You can lie to me...
but I can't lie to you?
Of course.
What gives you the right?
Don't be so petty.
You're older than me, so you
you should treat me nicely.
I'll do my best.
Mr. Li,
you look so tired.
Why don't you go back and rest?
Your suggestion...
is very wise.
And you've reminded me that...
I do feel a little tired.
I'll leave it to you, then.
I'll go back now.
Alright.
You tidy up this place.
I'll look for clues.
No.
Why?
Because you're better at it.
I'm better than you when it
comes to snooping around.
Lei Ao,
here.
This is the only box here that is locked.
It must be holding a secret.
Find a way to open it.
[When Love Begins, Volume 4]
"All of you,"
"do you have a death wish
or are you tired of living?"
Why does this guy talk like that?
Did you write this dialogue novel?
I'm not that capable.
Who is it then?
Little Brother,
I have a question for you.
Brother Feng, you can ask me anything.
You're welcome to do so.
About that limping man...
with a big mole on his face,
how did he turn into...
a formidable hero?
How is it possible?
I don't think it's possible, either.
Brother Feng, what are you talking about?
I don't understand a word of it.
I've read all your dialogue novels.
Shush.
Keep your voice down.
The academy is cracking down...
on the dialogue novels.
For safety's sake,
let's not talk about it.
Actually, you wrote well.
Your ideas are original.
It's just that this
part doesn't make sense.
I have little talent
and limited knowledge.
I would appreciate your guidance
in the future.
In the future?
I guess not.
I'll focus on my studies from now on.
Do you have a death wish
or do you want to die?
What's wrong, Senior?
Tell me,
why is my catch phrase
in the dialogue novel?
What are you talking about, Senior?
I don't understand a word of it.
I've read Volume 3 and Volume 4
of your novel, Where Love Begins.
Shush, keep it down.
The academy is cracking
down on the dialogue novels.
Aren't you afraid of having
your buttocks hit by Mr. Li?
If you're not afraid, why should I be?
What are you so happy about?
Limping man...
with a big disgusting mole on his face...
who betrayed the lead character.
You're so gross.
Little Brother,
tell me honestly,
is that really me?
-No.
-Of course it is.
The way he talks resembles somebody.
Little Brother,
I understand your motives.
I finally realize...
why this chapter doesn't make sense.
I hope you'll give a logical
explanation in the next volume.
What's there to explain?
A disgusting person like you...
should be run over and killed by cow...
in the beginning of the next volume.
The formidable hero even saved
the maiden, Xi.
How could he be so easily killed by a cow?
Ran over and killed by cow?
Are these two people
actually the same person?
Your writing is nonsensical.
It's illogical.
I'm warning you,
I'm the knight in Volume 3.
You made me look so
reckless in Volume 4...
vying with this disgusting loser
for the woman I love.
You're ruining my image.
I'm very unhappy about it.
You better watch out.
I might actually punch you.
I get it, Senior.
You are laughing?
Behave yourself.
Little Brother,
as a scholar of Yun Shang Academy,
your writing must be fair and just.
I get it, Brother Feng.
What are you two doing?
Don't worry.
The academy has been so strict.
I'll never write again.
And...
it's getting late now.
Senior, Brother Feng,
how about we get some rest now?
You've sabotaged my image...
and now you're just going
to walk away?
Don't worry, Senior.
No one knows you are that knight.
I don't care.
You have to clear my name.
Little Brother, I hope to see...
a reasonable resolution
in the next volume.
Okay.
Such a hypocrite.