[English subtitles are available]
[In A Class of Her Own]
[Episode 2]
Flowers. Take a look.
Flowers.
Why did you return?
It's Feng Cheng Jun.
Feng Cheng Jun? Where's he?
He's outside.
Le... leave, quick.
You must be careful too.
Just go.
You're Mr. Chao, right?
Don't be nervous.
I... I'm not.
Mr. Feng, please forgive me.
Give me a chance to start over.
I won't break the law any more.
Don't worry,
I'm not here to give you a hard time.
I just want to know where the copier is.
He made a huge mistake,
I've punished him severely...
by throwing him off South Street.
Rest assured that he'll never
show up in front of you any more.
What?
What, what?
Why?
What is it?
Watch out.
Come and take a look, it's freshly
plucked. There's even dew on it.
Take a look.
You?
Here, please.
[Yu Le House]
Take a look.
This is where I do my business.
Isn't it brilliant?
Le Xuan.
Are you a scholar...
or a merchant?
I'm a scholar as well as a merchant.
I do anything that can make money.
I can handle both.
Seems to me like you're wiser
in doing business than studying.
You don't know how good I am in studying.
Don't judge.
I was just kidding.
How interesting.
You were so panic a while ago,
but now, you have the mood
to joke already.
What can I do?
Now matter how suffering or tired, I
still need to make money and pay my debts.
Why are you always in debt?
Did you sign a contract to sell yourself?
In fact,
I have a business,
and I need you to do it.
When you're done,
you'll get 200 taels, how about it?
I'll do it.
What is it?
You don't think I can do it?
I haven't said what it is
that I need you to do.
The money matters a lot to me.
I'd do anything for it.
But this is a very dangerous task...
I'd even go to hell for the 200 taels.
Have some tea, Mr. Feng.
Mr. Feng,
you made me frighten out of my wits.
Here you go.
Well, Mr. Wen Bin is like a "goose-man".
A mysterious man, you mean?
A "goose-man".
Splendid as a peach blossom,
and bright as autumn moon.
At first sight,
you'd mistake him for a girl.
Mr. Chao, I can tell that by myself.
I wish to know his personality.
Do you get what I mean?
I got it.
Actually,
all I know is his name's Wen Bin.
But I don't have a clue about
where or with whom he lives.
As far as I know,
he needs money.
In order to increase his income,
he'd even copy the books
all day and night for days.
There were times when his eyes
turned red from the copying.
How pitiful.
Yet, as poor as he is,
he's a man of principle.
He'd never hurt or deceive others.
I've known Mr. Wen for a few years.
This is the only time...
he gave up his principle entirely.
Maybe...
he is really in a big trouble
Isn't this Feng Cheng Jun,
the popular student at the exam hall?
What a coincidence to meet you here.
And you are...
I'm Yu Le Xuan.
Brother Cheng Jun,
are you looking for someone?
I think you're looking for the person
who tricked you in the exam hall.
I won't call that "being tricked".
I can help you find him.
Why would you?
I thought you'd be grateful for that.
Fine, forget it.
No, I just felt that...
you don't have to help me.
What if I say...
I'm doing this out of my care and
concern for a fellow classmate...
who'll be living with me...
and for the friend whom I took
as confidant when we first met?
Will you believe that?
Well, forget it. Even I don't believe it.
At 7.15 p.m. tonight.
In front of San Shen Temple.
What is he doing there?
He's a poor man.
Of course he'll be making money there.
But, a gentle reminder.
He wouldn't be doing
anything good there at this hour.
If you went there,
and it were to be found out,
and someone saw that...
the young master of
the Feng family is breaking the law...
with a commoner,
the Feng family's reputation
might be tarnished.
Why are you warning me about that?
I'm curious about your intention.
But here's a piece of advice.
You'd better not go.
I won't change my decision.
What kind of person
would choose such a place?
This is what you asked for.
What is this?
You again?
Brother Wen Bin, we need to talk.
We've nothing to talk about.
Don't you know how messed up you made me?
There must be a
misunderstanding between us.
I can explain.
Capture all those trading the banned book.
-Yes, sir.
-You...
-Brother Wen Bin.
-Stay there. After them!
Yes!
[Book of 10 Thousand Words]
Feng Cheng Jun's done for this time.
He's done for.
Stop there!
This way. Quick!
Hurry up.
This way.
Stop there!
Come on.
Commander, there's sound
coming from the right.
This way.
Move it.
I'll carry you, come on.
Search carefully.
Yes, sir.
You two, go that side.
Yes.
Take a look there.
Search carefully.
This area is clear.
There's no one here too.
Go that way.
Commander.
Commander, I think...
that they climbed upwards.
Do you find anything down there?
There's nothing here.
Everybody, go up the mountain!
Yes, sir.
Commander, there's a path.
After them! Quick!
It's so packed in here. Get out.
Be patient.
Pull your stomach in.
What a nasty man.
I...
How am I nasty?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I have given you the book,
you have to pay.
Did someone ask you to hand me that book?
Didn't you buy it?
Why would I buy that book?
I just wanted to talk to you.
Talk to me?
Talk about what?
Mr. Wen,
please take the second exam
of Yun Shang Academy.
You're too talented.
I don't want your talent to
be used in the wrong way.
The wrong way?
You tricked me into meeting you.
Is this how a scholar is?
Or did you plan to make me
realise my mistake with all this?
Thank you for your favour,
I'm unworthy of it.
Why don't you just pay up?
And we can go our separate ways.
You'll head to the right direction,
and I'll continue on the wrong way.
Okay?
I'll pay, Mr. Wen.
Thanks then.
It's 200 taels.
What is it, no money?
No more talking then.
Hang on.
Why are you so reluctant to take the exam?
As a scholar,
don't you want to have a bright future?
That's not my life's goal.
Why did you study then?
There's no reason. I just study.
And why did you write on my back?
I don't mean to blame you.
The words you wrote on my back...
[were criticising my lack of
knowledge about hunger and cold.]
[You were implicating that...]
[you are experiencing hunger and cold.]
That's why you couldn't spare
any effort to pursue your ambition.
Was that what it was about?
Yes, am I wrong?
No, you're not.
That's why...
I'm asking you to take the second exam.
You said that you wouldn't
do such thing in the past.
But you have no choice as
you've encountered difficulties.
I can help you...
as long as you're willing to
sit for the second exam.
Thank you for your kind intention.
One more question.
You can't help a person forever.
It'd be better to teach someone
to fish than to give him a fish.
All I ask is this stable life
I'm having now.
I don't care about having an ambitious goal in life,
yet, I would hanker
after some salted fish.
So, stop wasting your time
on a man without vision.
As for the exam,
I'm not going.
Mr. Wen.
It seems like...
he is really in difficulty.
Mother,
you should eat well...
and take good care of yourself.
You need to look after
Wen Bin when he's back.
Tomorrow's the last day.
I'm so useless.
Stay there.
How could you ignore the President?
Are you blind?
He must be missing his father,
wishing that he could be home now...
to complain about us to Governor Feng.
Feng Cheng Jun,
you're from a noble family.
Yet, you wouldn't hesitate to
destroy your people's honour,
instead of fighting for them.
Whose side are you on exactly?
Are you going to stay silent?
I'm only on the side of justice.
These candidates even
cheated during the exam.
They're simply shameless.
As a scholar,
I should set an example...
by changing this decadent condition.
Very well.
How righteous.
To be frank,
I admire your daring and fearlessness...
in speaking up and making moves.
However,
I'm warning you.
Yun Shang Academy isn't a
place you can do whatever you like.
Here,
you're bounded by the rules.
Nor is Yun Shang Academy...
a place for you to deceive others.
How dare you be
disrespectful to the President.
I...
Mr. Chao.
This...
[Tomorrow's the last day.]
[I must get enough
money to redeem Wen Bin.]
Mr. Wen,
I was just thinking about finding you.
And here you are.
Mr. Chao,
is there a job in which I can make
800 taels before the end of tomorrow?
I need it urgently.
Please help me.
I got it.
But 800 taels...
is quite a lot.
How about this?
Will you take another risk?
A risk?
This time, you don't have
to help with someone's exam.
Instead, disguise yourself as a candidate
and take the exam.
Got it?
No.
The rules have been
rectified after the first exam.
It's impossible for me to
replace anyone to take the exam.
Rumours had it that...
the rectification during the first exam...
was just a show for
Mr. Feng Cheng Jun's sake.
So,
you can still do it
during the second exam.
The employer has even
guaranteed your safety,
as long as you do it.
As long as I do it?
You mean, the employer appointed me?
No, he didn't do that.
It's just my word choice.
The employer also said...
that he'll pay no matter the outcome.
How much is he paying?
Five hundred taels?
One... One thousand taels?
For the second exam,
the exam hall will be strictly guarded.
If you try cheating, by any means,
you'll be taken to the court and punished.
You may enter the exam hall.
Principal Feng.
Grand Secretary Ding,
what brings you here?
I'm invited by Master Wang...
to join both of you as the invigilators.
He wants me to pass this order.
Here, please.
Have a seat.
Candidates, take your seats.
Are there any surrogate exam-takers?
If you are,
turn yourself in now,
and tell us who is your employer.
Your punishment shall endorse leniency.
Otherwise...
I have something to report.
Say it up here.
This is a recommendation letter.
[This is my only recommendation letter.]
[You may fill in the name of the recipient.]
[Thank you, Principal Feng.]
[He's a talented scholar and
he cares about the people.]
[Yet, he couldn't participate in
the exam because he's poor.]
[I don't want such
talent to be overlooked.]
[That's why I hope you'd give him a
chance to serve the country.]
Get him up here.
Mr. Wen.
Mr. Wen, you must be really knowledgeable.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't gain such
recognition from Mr. Feng.
Grand Secretary Ding,
what do you think?
Since both Principal Feng and
Mr. Feng recommended him,
and there was a similar case
previously in Yun Shang,
then...
I approve it.
About what?
You're allowed to skip the first exam
and take the second exam.
[View on National Policies]
Mr. Wen,
why aren't you writing?
I've never wanted to be
enrolled in the Academy.
Why should I write?
If you hand in a blank paper,
you will be sentenced to
the national law of contempt,
and be treated as cheating.
[I've got the money, anyway.]
[I can write anything I want.]
I spoke very highly of you
to Principal Feng...
so that you can take
the second exam directly.
If your answer is much
worse than other candidates',
you'll still be sentenced to the national
law of contempt by Principal Feng.
In what way did I offend you?
Why did you beset me?
I'm helping you.
I have a question.
What is it?
If I passed the second exam...
but was absent during the third exam,
what punishment would I get?
Being absent for the third exam...
equals to giving up on all of the exams.
You won't be punished.
Thank you, invigilator.
Mr. Wen, what are you doing?
Be disciplined in the exam hall.
Hand in your paper.
What's going on?
This year,
for Yun Shang Academy's third exam,
Master Wang will be inspecting
your papers for the second exam here.
Come to Ming Lun Hall with me.
Move now.
Let's go.
All of a sudden.
Mr. Wen,
let's go.
[Ming Lun Hall]
Cheng Jun,
I know what you're capable of.
I intend to...
recommend you to the imperial court and
you can serve the country right away.
What do you think?
I wish to stay in
Yun Shang Academy and learn more.
The reason why I wish
to continue studying...
is because I'm not knowledgeable
enough to serve the country now.
Also, coming from a noble family,
I should set an example...
by following the rules.
What's happening?
-They're out.
-They came out.
The candidate, Wen Bin, come inside.
Don't be nervous.
Master Wang's not that scary.
He cherishes people's talent.
He'll notice how talented you are.
I'm not talented.
All I wish is to walk out
of this Academy safely.
Wen Bin.
Get up.
Thank you, Master Wang.
Student,
look up.
Stop looking down...
or you'll be taken as
disrespecting Master Wang.
What's your family name?
It's Wen.
Wen Bin,
your essay may not be one of the best,
but you're very lucky.
Master Wang has granted you...
entrance into Yun Shang Academy as
the last candidate during the second exam.
I'm guilty,
please forgive me.
Student,
how are you guilty?
[How should I answer him?]
[I can't enter the Academy,
no matter what.]
I...
I got the last place,
I'm unworthy to be
given the chance by Master Wang.
This student is really funny.
I have high expectations for all of you.
I hope you'll study well
at Yun Sheng Academy.
Be virtuous and loyal.
Congratulations, Brother Wen Bin.
You finally got in.
Aren't you happy making fun of me?
I am happy,
but I wasn't making fun of you.
You should be proud to become a scholar.
Be proud?
I don't come from a family that wants
me to become an official like yours.
I just want to feed my family,
and be able to live in peace
during this difficult times.
Live in peace?
Can scribing bring you peace?
A man should be ambitious.
I know you're naggy, but don't go too far.
You're an accomplished scholar,
but lack common sense.
I was hoping you can
put what you learned to use,
and not let your talent go to waste.
Why don't you get it?
Why should I?
Did I ask for your help?
No.
Absolutely.
You made the decision yourself,
forced me to accept it,
and now you're putting
me in a difficult position.
Aren't you exaggerating?
Anyway,
you're imposing your thoughts on me.
This is very ungentlemanly.
And all those teachings about study well.
You should focus on
perfecting yourself instead.
You put yourself in danger
out of greed for money,
and I got you out of it.
Why am I immoral?
Congratulations, Mr. Wen.
Tell me honestly.
Was it Feng Cheng Jun who employed
me as the surrogate exam-taker?
Mr. Wen, you must be kidding.
If you think it's Mr. Feng,
you should be thanking him now.
Yes, you're right.
I should thank him by chopping him off!
This is something every scholar
would be delighted to receive.
Mr. Wen,
why aren't you happy?
And you shouldn't look so despaired.
You're now a scholar of Yun Shang Academy.
With who you are now,
you'll worth ten times more as a copier.
Don't take it for granted.
What did you say?
What, what?
What did you just say?
Don't take it for granted.
The previous line.
As a copier...
No, the next line.
Worth ten times more.
[In this case,]
[I'll have the money
to get Wen Bin treated.]
A scholar will even receive
300 taels every month.
[300 taels?]
[But if they found out that I'm a girl...]
[Well...]
[I've cleared the debt with Lord Gu.]
[Now, I need to return the
money for betrothal gifts,]
[and I'll be free.]
[A very beautiful lady...]
I have nothing.
Aren't you afraid of the hard life when
you're not the daughter of an official?
I will travel to the end of the
world with you until we grow old.
Rebel,
don't trouble the fine lady.
You miserable people,
you'll never know
what it's like to be in love.
Take this.
-You...
-Let's go.
[She left with the man.]
Take a look.
Give me one.
I want one.
Wait for your turn.
Wait for your turn, you'll get yours.
[He's inside.]
[That evil man.]
Sir, did you see a lady in red?
I want the book. Do you still have it?
-Take turns, queue up.
-I want my book.
You'll get yours.
I told you, they'd be together.
It's brilliantly written.
That's right.
We're not meant to be together.
See you in the next life.
[What will happen next? To be continued]
You're really good-looking, mister.
How old are you?
Where're you from? Are you married?
Look at my pretty daughter.
-No, thanks.
-Just take a look.
Mr. Handsome
my young master has asked me
to carry your baggage.
Never mind.
I'm not so precious that I can't
punch my way out of a paper bag.
I'll carry it myself.
It's okay, let me carry it.
Do... Don't touch me!
I...
This feels like nothing.
I was being nosy then.
Woman.
What?
I said, even women are stronger than you.
You're too weak as a man.
What? Am I wrong?
Exactly, Mr. Handsome
You're indeed less masculine.
Young Master, is he angry?
I told you to watch what you say.
Let's go.
Mr. Pretty.
Cheng Jun,
you're here.
You're finally here.
I've been waiting for you.
Come on, let's go inside.
-Let's...
-Isn't this inappropriate?
They're still checking our names.
It is appropriate.
Don't you know the son of the Governor?
Let's go inside now.
You'll get tanned standing
under the scorching sun.
Come on. You, carry his things.
Come, let's go inside.
Hurry up.
Young Master, take good care of yourself.
Young Master,
take care.
You may enter.
Put your things here for now.
We'll meet here after two hours...
to assign you to your dorms.
Let me carry that for you.
I'm Mo Xiao Huan from the eastern area.
My father is an official.
What about you?
I'm Wen Bin,
a commoner.
I live in the West Village.
Birds of a feather flock together.
Both of you aren't meant to be friends.
Ridiculous.
How should I address you, mister?
Brother Zi Feng, keep it low.
Brother Yi De, I am keeping it low.
I never do this to anyone...
I'm Yang Yi De.
I'm Wen Bin.
Brother Wen Bin,
you impressed me at the
exam hall the other day.
We're of the same status.
Why don't you, I and Zi Feng...
choose the same room later?
So we can take care of each other.
Never mind, I have my own plan.
Your own plan?
Staying with your fellow townsman?
Something like that. I'm taking
a look at the study hall up ahead.
[Ming Lun Hall]
To learn something and timely practice it,
isn't that a pleasure?
To have friends coming from afar,
isn't it a delight?
Do not blame a person
who does not recognise you.
That's gentlemanly, is it not?
Zengzi said,
[Every day, I examine
myself in three ways.]
[When I work for others,
have I been disloyal?]
Shoot.
Here, here.
Pass to me.
Take it.
Here, pass it here.
The President's here.
The President's coming.
Congratulations to all of you for
becoming scholars of Yun Shang Academy.
-You're full of surprises.
-I'm Han Sheng Zhi.
It seems like you've
abandoned your principles.
And we're closer now.
I dare not get involved with Mr. Yu,
as I might get caught
by the Imperial Brigade.
You still resent me for
what happened that day?
But I paid you to work.
Why the resentment?
Had I known that was a banned book,
I would've asked for more.
A man must be forgiving.
Moreover, aren't you alive and kicking?
You've even become a scholar.
Mr. Wen,
your courage is indeed admirable.
But I'm warning you.
This is Yun Shang Academy,
not the market where
you can always be carefree.
Here,
you have to follow the rules, got it?
I will keep that in mind,
and always listen to you, President.
Next,
you'll be assigned to your dorm
by Steward Han Sheng Xiong.
Every common room
is shared by three people.
You may choose your own roommates.
I'll be taking you to your rooms.
You may move your things into
your room when you've chosen it.
Why is it shared by three people?
Yes.
I discussed with you just now, didn't I?
What is it?
You want to sleep alone?
What are you doing?
Why did you blush?
Did I?
Room Five of Regular Dorm.
Jin Pei Feng and two other friends.
Where is it? Where is it?
Room Three of Regular Dorm.
Guo Dong and two other friends.
Here!
Room One of Regular Dorm.
Chen Yun and two other friends.
It's here.
Room Six of Regular Dorm.
Chen Zhi Qian and two other friends.
Here it is.
What a nice room.
There're windows on its south and north.
Who dares to stay with Lei Ao?
He must have a death wish.
Who's Lei Ao?
He's three years more senior than us...
and is known for his stupidity.
He failed all subjects
other than martial arts.
He's been staying only here
since he joined the Academy.
How did someone this stupid
enter Yun Shang Academy...
and stay in a single room?
Call him stupid when
you meet him in person.
Believe it or not, he can beat up
10 students like you easily.
We're at Yun Shang Academy.
Students aren't allowed
to fight in the Academy.
But,
a friendly fight is allowed.
Wen Bin,
the President specially arranged you
to stay in Room Two.
Lei Ao seldom comes back here.
So, you'll be alone most of the time.
Sure. Thank you, Steward.
Brother Wen Bin, are you crazy?
You look really weak.
Are you sure you want to stay here?
What if Lei Ao comes back...
-and wants to try out martial arts on you?
-I'll take this room.
He's crazy.
He really is.
[It's quite dirty and messy,]
[but still liveable after cleaning up.]
[Continuation of Confucius]
All done.
Where is Wen Bin staying?
Room Two of Regular Dorm.
Why does it happen to be that room?
He didn't choose it.
Sheng Xiong assigned him to the room.
Isn't that Feng Cheng Jun?
Feng Cheng Jun.
Your room isn't that way.
We've prepared a superior room for you.
Follow me.
A superior room?
Why did you prepare
a superior room for me?
Aren't all freshmen
living at Regular Dorm?
How can we let someone
like you live in Regular Dorm?
The President suggested this.
So you can live more comfortably.
I'm treated specially because I'm a noble?
When did the Student Council start
doing things based on hierarchy?
Feng Cheng Jun.
Since you want it the hard way...
and wasted our good intention,
fine, we'll assign you to a room.
Which room in Regular Dorm
is not fully occupied?
Lei Ao,
please don't ever come back.
It's wonderful to live here alone.
Hi.