[English subtitles are available]
[In A Class of Her Own]
[Episode 24]
What's the matter with Wen Bin?
Why is he taking a bath here?
Mr Ding.
Why are you here?
I...
You're taking a bath here?
Are you serious?
Wen Bin,
what are you thinking, taking a bath here?
Well,
I fell down due to the
slippery road after rain.
I came here to clean up my messy self
to avoid others' teasing.
This is unacceptable.
Is this a place for bathing?
Get back to your room.
Go to Ming Lun Hall.
Thank you, Mr Ding.
Go now.
Are you feeling better?
I made a new medicine for you.
Mr Ding.
Was this from you?
Ke Shi Jun, Qin Bei Chuan.
Where did you get this?
Didn't you leave it for me?
No, I didn't.
Oh, no.
Someone knew who you are.
And he must be a teacher in the Academy.
Why do you think so?
I fought him before.
He was carrying a teacher's tag.
The only teacher in the
Academy who knows martial arts...
is Mr Liu.
No.
It couldn't be my master.
Senior.
Ze Xin is fine now.
Mr Ding is treating him.
Don't worry.
You can be at ease,
Ze Xin's staying with
Feng Cheng Jun and Wen Bin.
Because of their high aspirations,
he has improved a lot.
Judging from his performances today,
he has changed indeed.
In the future,
I'm still counting on you
to look after him.
Of course, I'll keep an eye on him.
In that case,
it's almost impossible
for us to find Ke Shi Jun.
I'm to blame for my negligence.
Leave that masked man to me.
You stay out of it.
Yes, Sir.
You look happy, Brother Feng.
What's the good news?
It's true that something
interesting happened today.
During your wine party?
Could you have met a woman there?
I met Ms Han Shu Min.
But this is nothing romantic.
She went there...
No wonder you're joyful as a fluffy
cloud and droplets dancing in the rain.
Little Brother, don't make fun of me.
I told you, I won't be engaged in a
relationship before I become an official.
That's very thoughtful of you.
You nurture your affection before that,
and she'll be with you
after you become an official.
It seems like you are an expert
in romantic relationships.
So, when I meet a woman I like,
I'm counting on you to help me.
You're such a womaniser.
Lady Han loves you deeply.
Yet, you're thinking about
meeting another woman.
Do you think Ms Han Shu Min and I...
are so close that we will be in love?
Everyone with eyes can tell...
that she loves you a lot
and you're not rejecting her.
What is this if it's not
a romantic relationship?
You think I fancy Ms Han Shu Min?
Do you think I like her?
Why are you asking me?
I'm going to sleep.
You look too happy, don't you?
I am quite happy.
During the party,
I performed for everyone.
All of them liked it.
So, I want you to watch it too.
Little kid, don't be gluttonous.
New Year comes after the Laba Festival.
After you had some Laba Congee,
it'll suddenly become the 23rd.
On 23rd, have malt sugar candy.
On 24th, clean up the house.
On 25th, fry tofu.
On 26th, make stewed mutton.
On 27th, eat some chicken.
On 28th...
-Ferment the dough.
On 29th, steam the buns.
On 30th, have fun throughout the night.
-On the first day of the new year...
-Twist your body.
Twist your body.
So, are you happy now?
More or less so.
I wonder why you got upset every day.
Just go and sleep.
Let's sleep.
You sleep first.
[Feng Cheng Jun was
smiling all the time just now.]
[Turned out he wanted to cheer me up.]
[So that I will be happy.]
Mr Ding, did you ask for me?
Come here.
I've been thinking about this.
You still need to leave the school.
Why did you go back on your word?
Master Wang wants to
learn about your background.
Why did he want to know
about my background?
Who am I to arouse his interest?
This is because...
he thinks very highly of you.
He wishes to know more about you.
The holidays are coming in a few days.
You may return home and visit your family.
After that,
don't come back anymore.
I will handle the rest.
You may leave now.
Yes, Sir.
[Wen Xi,]
[don't feel bad for yourself.]
[You can go back to
becoming a lady after you left.]
[Then, you and Brother Feng...]
Why are the two of you together?
Brother Le Xuan wants my calligraphy.
You're deceived.
He must be wanting to sell it.
I do wonder...
how much is
Brother Cheng Jun's calligraphy worth.
Let's go.
What? Can't I read?
Brother Ze Xin, you finally came back!
Did you think I died?
If you don't come back by today,
we would really think that you have died.
You're asking for a beating. Stay there.
Do you dare to compete with me?
Sure.
Compete in what?
What else?
The only thing he can do best is drinking.
I can't drink.
Your victory has no honour
if you drink with him...
who has a low tolerance to alcohol.
Little Brother,
you're always siding with the outsider.
What outsider? There's no outsider here.
Exactly.
We're buddies.
Little Brother,
we got in the first place together.
No matter what, you must
drink with me tonight.
He'll take care of it.
Of course.
As we're buddies.
But you can't force us to drink more.
I don't care about you,
as long as I can have my drink.
So, are you going or not?
Brother Feng, let's join him.
Okay.
My son.
-Sir, I'm begging you.
-Darling.
My son.
May I know what happened?
These are despicable commoners.
They didn't pay their debt
for a very long time.
So, they have to be taken
to do hard labour.
Brother Feng.
Little Brother,
when we become government officials,
we must change this.
Little Brother, let's toast.
I'll just take a sip.
I don't care.
Do you really have to sigh
over so little dishes?
This time,
I have suffered a huge loss.
Even Le Xuan would sustain losses
in business?
Everything is unpredictable.
My goods aren't selling.
Why?
The locust plague has
affected this year's harvests.
The people have no extra
money to do new year shopping.
They don't even have enough
to eat and wear.
Life is hard.
Wine is the only comfort.
That's right. Let's drink.
[Fu Ze Hall]
I can finally go home to my family.
-Yeah.
-Here.
Thanks. Thank you, President.
Your food.
Forget it.
Zi Ming,
get someone to take these to Bing Shen.
Everything must be returned to the school.
Why are you standing there?
Come in.
You're collecting herbs
so early in the morning?
Mr Yu has registered these herbs.
Collecting them in the morning with
the crowd may make me return home late.
Come on.
Enough.
Take what belongs to you and leave.
President.
It was all my fault.
Thanks for your reminder.
Did we forget to apologise to Wen Bin?
President, but...
A man must keep his words.
Apologise when we should.
But, President,
I should be the one apologising to him.
Don't force yourself to do it.
If you want to make things easier for me,
please do something...
so that Feng Cheng Jun
and Wen Bin would listen to me.
That's impossible.
Both of them won't yell to others.
Unless you did something...
that would impress them.
He's right.
Brother Feng.
Little Brother. Here.
These are...
Why are the things from superior rooms
the same as mine?
The Academy's quite fair on this.
You can have all these.
For me?
But not the money.
You do know me well.
I'll have these things then.
Little Brother.
Look.
Is this enough?
Is it for me?
Is it enough?
I can't carry all of these.
If you can't carry the things from others,
take only mine.
Here, Little Brother.
Hold them.
How dare you put yours atop mine.
Get in line.
Only the two of you would have
such eagerness to give things away.
Funny.
I think I'd join too.
Take them.
Just take all of them.
Or "Three Kingdoms War"
will start in this room.
Okay, I'll take them all.
Wen Bin, you're loaded with stuff.
Come on, slowly.
Slowly and gently.
There are more.
Look, we also have some for you.
Some of our schoolmates from
common and regular dorms...
took the herbs especially for you,
as you have a sick family member.
I have enough herbs.
Well, Brother Wen Bin,
it's stated in the school rules that
the herbs are for the needy students,
and not for sale.
We took them for you.
Just take them.
-Thanks.
-Wen Bin.
You're really popular.
Little Brother,
you can open a medical hall now.
This is great.
The students gave Wen Bin all the herbs.
I'm really glad to see this.
If Master Wang...
learnt that the students
get along so well,
he must be delighted.
Principal Feng has
done well in educating them.
Not at all.
Mr Ding,
how shall I tell Master
Wang regarding this?
Aren't we overreacting...
if we report such a trivial matter?
Mr Liu,
many drops make a shower.
Don't you know that?
We lost in the archery ceremony.
As promised,
we're here to apologise to Wen Bin.
It's okay. You don't have to do that.
A real man is true to his word.
I'll do what I have said.
Please accept our apologies.
Yeah, count me in.
-We're sorry.
-Please don't.
Okay, I've accepted it.
This is the food the academy
gave to students in superior rooms.
They don't care about it.
And we're going to throw it away.
Didn't Wen Bin mention...
that all the food came from
people's hard work?
Instead of wasting them,
why not give them to Wen Bin?
Wen Bin, feel free to take them all.
They will be enough
for your family for months.
Are you done?
You don't want us to help Wen Bin?
Do you have a death wish?
Brother Ze Xin.
Stop it.
I will take all these.
We have gone too far.
Since he took our food,
-it means that he accepted our help.
-That's right, President.
You looked awesome.
-I felt really good.
-Shut up!
Don't you think I'll easily
forgive you for your despicability.
President, I...
This is a large amount of food.
Le Xuan,
carry all these to my room, please.
Sure.
Little Brother,
where's your dignity?
Brother Feng,
do you also think that I've lost the
integrity of a scholar by receiving these?
But, look.
These foods can support
the poor for several days.
And I've been studying
medicine all the while I'm here.
With these herbs,
I can help those who are poor
and sick in the Western District.
Wen Bin, you're always full of surprises.
Interesting.
Little Brother,
I don't know anything,
but I can help carry these.
Let's go.
This vicious thing.
Sir, it's okay.
This is the medicine
to treat colds and flu.
Take it regularly.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
For you.
What's wrong with him?
He's brooding over the fact
that he was bullied by a dog.
Are you asking for a beating?
Knock it off.
Let's head to the next village.
Mother.
There you are. Massage my shoulder.
Mother, Sister's coming back, isn't she?
I hear she's giving out medicine at
the Western District with some scholars.
I supposed she'll be home soon.
Looks like she's doing really
well in Yun Shang Academy.
People are calling your sister
and the three other scholars...
the Four Gentlemen of Yun Shang.
The Four Gentlemen of Yun Shang?
Principal Feng,
Yunzhou citizens have elected
the Four Gentlemen of Yun Shang...
from among the students.
Congratulations.
It's all thanks to your blessings,
Master Wang.
You have taught and guided them properly.
Don't be humble, Principal Feng.
I always knew what you've
done for Yun Shang Academy.
And I've been keeping it in my mind.
Principal Feng,
looks like you're now one step closer
to your final goal.
Principal Feng,
stick to your faith,
and bring the spirit of Yun Shang Academy
to a great height.
Little Brother.
[South Street Market]
Let me take you home.
No, it's okay.
We finally get to be with our families.
You should go home now.
Brother Ze Xin.
Stop drinking. You should
spend more time with your family.
Be a good boy and listen to him.
Look, he's being naughty again.
Le Xuan,
you're a good boy too
when you be more decent.
You're no better than me.
Be a decent man.
Little Brother,
be fair.
As for Brother Feng...
You're a good boy when you
make friends with other students.
This is a difficult task
for Brother Cheng Jun.
I'll try it.
Little Brother, what about you?
Me?
I have always been a good boy.
No, you're not.
I am.
Bye.
[Bye, Brother Feng,]
[Brother Ze Xin,]
[and Brother Le Xuan.]
Take care, guys. I shall leave too.
What are you doing?
You should go home too.
Don't you want to have
a drink with me tonight?
Brother, your family's waiting for you.
No?
I don't need you to drink with me.
Goodbye then. Take care.
You too.
I'm really envious of your close
friendship with the three of them.
But it must be hard for you
to act like a man all the time.
I'm already an expert in that.
No one ever suspected me.
What about the food in the academy?
Great, of course.
We have meat every day.
I can even have a man's portion.
Now I've gained some weight
after half a year.
You must be kidding.
Don't eat too much.
What if no one wants to marry you
because you're fat?
You can't keep staying at home too.
Here, take a look.
New clothes?
Sister,
in order to make the new clothes for you,
Mother had been really busy.
Try on.
This must cost a lot.
You should've bought
supplement for Wen Bin.
Sister,
don't worry about me.
I've been recovering...
since I took the remedies you made.
Sell it away.
You don't want it?
-Yes.
-Are you sure?
Very well.
-I'll wear it myself.
-No.
If you go out in these clothes,
and charm someone to death,
we have no money for compensation.
Try it now.
Okay.
Mother,
Sister is really pretty.
Of course.
She's my daughter.
Young Master,
it's been years since you came home.
Madam misses you a lot.
You should return.
I get the busiest
during the school holidays.
I have no time to spare.
Okay.
I shall take my leave.
Hold on.
-You may leave.
-Yes, Young Master.
[Le Xuan...]
is a funny guy,
as well as a good businessman.
He always has lots of ideas.
Initially, I was most
afraid of being found out by him.
Could he have noticed who you are?
I don't think so.
-What about Lei Ze Xin?
-Brother Ze Xin?
He's what his name implies.
But he cares about me,
and is very protective of me.
Despite his wilfulness,
his mind seems to be loaded
with worries sometimes.
Xin, the food's getting cold.
I'll have them warm it up.
I've had my dinner.
What about Feng Cheng Jun?
He...
Looks like...
Feng Cheng Jun is the closest to you.
[Fu Ze Hall]
Principal Feng, teachers.
Did you handle the lingzhi powder
for the imperial court yourself?
Yes, Sir.
Did you remember where it was kept?
Of course.
Wha... what happened?
Are you sure it was here?
I am certain.
I put it there myself.
What are we going to do about this?
I'm frantic with worry.
Wen Bin, come here.
What's the matter?
Wen Bin, where's your student tag?
I left it at school.
Change into a man's clothes
and come to school with me.
What happened?
I'll tell you on the road.
Take this.
-Thank you, Mr Ding.
-Hurry up.
-Okay.
-I'll be waiting. Hurry up.
On the night the thief
broke into Fu Ze Hall,
he left the student tag there.
Someone saw you entered the hall.
Now that you don't have your student tag,
you might face some trouble.
In case they want to take
it back after I left school,
I put it in a noticeable place.
Calm down.
I believe you.
I'm taking you back...
to keep the people from
the school from finding out...
who you are if they send someone
to your house.
It is a crime of deceit.
Thank you, Mr Ding.
-Why are you all here?
-Principal Feng.
Wen Bin's here.
Let's get started.
Wen Bin,
where's your student tag?
I left it in the dorm, it's gone missing.
I suppose this is the one?
Wen Bin,
is that your student tag?
Yes, it is.
We found your student tag...
at the place where we
lost the lingzhi powder.
Can you explain it?
I have no idea.
Please do me justice.
Such an unconvincing explanation.
Come on.
Wen Bin must have been framed.
Then tell us who framed him.
Could the person be practising magic...
that he was able to make things disappear
without anyone noticing?
And transferred Wen Bin's student tag...
to Fu Ze Hall secretly?
What a joke.
What did you say?
You accused me of theft
because of a student tag?
That's also an unconvincing excuse.
Exactly.
We can't prove that Wen Bin is innocent,
but you can't prove that
he stole it either.
So, you aren't convinced
by the physical evidence.
But we have a witness.
Wen Bin,
did you go to Fu Ze Hall alone...
on midnight of the day you went home?
[Mr Yu has registered these herbs.]
[Collecting them in the morning with
the crowd may make me return home late.]
Wen Bin,
stop making excuses.
The guard saw you when he was patrolling.
Feng Cheng Jun was at the door too.
Cheng Jun,
is that true?
I did see Wen Bin coming out
from Fu Ze Hall that midnight.
But I believe Wen Bin.
The herbs he took were registered.
He wasn't stealing.
Your words can't prove
Wen Bin's innocence.
You're close friends and
everybody knows that.
Exactly.
Wen Bin,
where did you keep those herbs?
-I brought them home.
-Easy.
We may take a look at Wen Bin's home.
The truth will come to light.
The Principal's right.
In order to clear Wen Bin's name,
we have to visit his house.
No way.
Why not?
Are you afraid of being found out?
I... I sold it already.
You can punish me however you like.
Wen Bin,
when are you telling the truth?
I don't get you.
Little Brother.
Master Wang's here!
Master Wang.
Skip the formalities.
I can't help but wonder...
how much money did Wen Bin get...
from our tribute.
Wen Bin,
say that again in front of Master Wang.
Did you steal it?
If you lie to us,
you're being very disrespectful.
I don't even know how the powder
looks like.
Then, why did you admit...
that you stole it?
I didn't want to make my mother worry
when all of you go to my house.
That's why I...
So, he's a filial son.
Master Wang,
all evidence implicated
that Wen Bin did it,
but there are many questionable points.
Please do him justice.
Wen Bin was with us
after he left school.
He wouldn't have time to sell the powder.
Who knows if Wen Bin has gotten
help from others?
If someone's helping him,
then that'd be me.
Cheng Jun,
don't say things out of pique.
Brother Feng, how could you...
Little Brother,
birds of a feather flock together.
If you're a thief, then,
I'm not a good and honest person either.
Since Feng Cheng Jun said that,
well, count me in too.
Me, as well.
What do you think, President?
I think that it's only appropriate
if we bring this to the court.
No, not at all.
If we let the court handle this,
everybody would know that
either one of our students is a thief,
or Yun Shang has falsely
accused a student of stealing.
Yun Shang would be the
country's laughing stock.
So, we should settle this quietly.
You need to find out the truth yourselves.
Yes, Sir.
-Han Sheng Zhi.
-Yes.
You don't have sufficient
evidence to prove...
that Wen Bin is the thief.
I'll talk to the governor and appoint
you as the supervisor tomorrow.
Find a stronger evidence
that's favourable to you...
and make Wen Bin admit it willingly.
Yes, Sir.
I'm not siding with anyone.
The four of you will be
given a chance as well.
Find the clues to prove your innocence.
Yes, Sir.
Yun Shang Academy reopens in two days.
Keep this in mind, you only have two days.
If you fail to find evidence...
that can clear Wen Bin's name,
I will expel Wen Bin,
and punish you for protecting the culprit.
But of course,
if you found out the person
who framed Wen Bin,
I will punish him severely.