Just this scrap metal?
Who are you trying to fool, Ji Qingchen?
Exactly.
You've been the Holy Maiden for so many years.
You must have hoarded the precious treasures
granted by the sect.
Hoarded?
Other than the basic cultivation method given by the sect,
every bit of resource I, Ji Qingchen, used for cultivation,
and every magical artifact I used,
were all earned with my life.
Would the grand senior disciple of Taixuan
be this poor?
Summon the Taixuan Heart-Questioning Mirror.
Even so,
Holy Master, according to sect rules,
since Ji Qingchen insists on leaving the sect,
the sect's cultivation methods she practiced
should be completely abolished.
We absolutely cannot let the Taixuan secret methods
fall into the hands of outsiders.
What a Taixuan Holy Land.
So-called orthodox sect.
It wasn't enough to exploit me for so many years.
Now you want to cripple my cultivation before I leave,
cutting off my livelihood.
I see right through you now.
Fine, I'll cripple it.
Hold on.
That Gu fiend, he...
No.
Master,
is he standing up for me?
Master Gu.
Ji Qingchen crippling her cultivation
is a private matter of our Taixuan Holy Land.
Please do not interfere.
Private matter?
What private matter?
Are you blind?
Didn't you see I just accepted her as my disciple?
My disciple's matter,
you dare tell me it's a private matter?
My disciple
guarded the Heavenly Abyss for your Taixuan Holy Land for so many years.
Not only are you ungrateful,
but you also want to cripple her.
First, tell me,
how does your Taixuan Holy Land plan to compensate her?
Bullshit.
You old fiend, you've only had her as a disciple for less than half an incense stick of time.
What does her guarding the Heavenly Abyss have to do with you?
You clearly just want to take advantage of the situation
and fleece us.
This rebellious disciple, Ji Qingchen,
you can just take her away.
I
won't cripple her cultivation either.
Unwilling to compensate?
Could it be that your Taixuan Holy Land wants something for nothing?
Looking at the entire Xuantian Continent,
it's always been me, Gu Linyuan, bullying others.
Today, your Taixuan Holy Land dares to be so shameless and bullying,
bullying my disciple for being young and ignorant,
actually wanting her to work for hundreds of years for free.
Halberd, come.
If you don't give me and my disciple a satisfactory explanation,
the worst I can do is sink the Central State.
Maniac!
He's a maniac.
Who takes an Extreme Dao Emperor Weapon
with them on a stroll?
Aren't these things usually kept deep in the ancestral land
to suppress the foundation and destiny?
This cheap master is so domineering.
But it feels great to be protected without reservation.
Master Gu, don't be impulsive.
Let's talk this out.
I said this guy is a maniac,
an unforgivable fiend.
Billions of lives in the Central State,
and he says he'll sink them.
Extreme Dao Emperor's might.
Who is the Taixuan Holy Land going to war with?
What's going on?
The Emperor Weapon awakened on its own.
Did a Supreme from the Forbidden Zone attack us?
Taixuan is in danger.
Today,
your Taixuan Holy Land must give me an explanation.
Otherwise, if word gets out,
people will think I, Gu Linyuan, am easy to bully.
Fellow Daoist, please wait.
Just because of this trivial matter.
I thought a mortal enemy was attacking.
I wasted a top-grade divine source for extending life.
I really want to give these unworthy descendants
a big slap in the face.
Fellow Daoist.
You are not qualified.
Let Li Taixuan come.
So damn shameless.
Li Taixuan is the real name of our Taixuan Emperor,
who passed away tens of thousands of years ago.
If the Emperor were still alive,
you wouldn't be so arrogant.
You must be joking.
Our Taixuan Holy Emperor is willing to compensate.
Please put away the Emperor Weapon first.
Oh.