It is not a difficult dance. Why am I still unable to execute things properly?
I know, right? I have singing practice coming up. I am not sure I can handle it.
How long will you practice?
Until 5pm.
We will have a little talk outside
Thank you, bro.
Hey, are you okay?
Not really.
Mungkorn, where is Mawin
Is anything up?
Why does it have to be me every time you bring up his case?
He never shows up for practice.
We have yet to begin practising Teacher Kawee's assignment.
We cannot even begin practising Teacher Bee's one because of him.
What? again?
Calm down
Hold on
Go get him.
Why the fuck can't he pick up the phone?
Phupa, calm down a bit.
Don't worry, he'll come.
Shoot! I'll get scolded again.
Sorry, I'm late.
Now you show up.
Why the hell can't you pick up the phone?
Mungkorn, take it easy.
Control your temper.
Yes, speak nicely. You don't have to make a storm in a tea cup.
Why? Do you want to get away from your guilt? You promised not to come late. You're super irresponsible.
With this mindset? Do not even think of being in a boyband. You're dragging us down.
Mungkorn, chill out! control your rage!
Mawin's matter is better left to adults to handle. Not doing something like this.
Doing this will only have negative consequences. Especially to you.
What are you guys doing?
You are aware that this room is monitored by CCTV, aren't you?
Mungkorn and Mawin, Araya wants to meet you.
Continue practising.
Hello
You know why you're being called, don't you?
We do.
Fighting is another prohibited behaviour.
Whatever happened, tell Pim. The company will find a solution to the situation.
Do not make judgments based on your feelings. It is not beneficial and will only have negative consequences.
I'm sorry.
In Mawin's case, I am aware of your situation, but if you choose this path in life, you must also be able to handle it effectively.
I get it. I'm sorry.
I won't let this kind of situation happen again. I am going to work on myself.
Words are not as powerful as actions. I will keep an eye on everyone.
This must not happen again. Otherwise, the two of you will be dropped from the project. Got it?
We got it.
Hey
I'm sorry.
I was impulsive just now.
Um
I just do not like the fact that you cannot manage your time. You act as if practising is not important.
It's not the way you thought. But I have a duty to take responsibility for.
A duty? Is there anything more important than practising?
Is it really that important? No need to make excuses.
I didn't make excuses. I have to work part-time.
In order to support myself and my family
I am determined, and I have worked hard to make the most of my time.
I say this not because I want your sympathy.
I just want you to know that I'm doing my best.
Do you realise how exhausted I am? I need to practice while also working. What else do you expect from me?
I didn't mean to..
Unlike you, I have had no familial support from birth. I will not be able to make ends meet if I do not work.
I'm really sorry.
Never mind. I'm sorry, too.
I only make trouble wherever I go. I simply want you to know that I am doing my absolute best.
Being part of this project is my only hope and my sole chance to brighten up my future.
Do you understand me?
Thank you. I'll pay by cards. Hello, Phu.
Hi, hand me your bag. I'll carry it.
Thank you.
Slowly
Alright
Are you alright?
I am.
How's everything going, guys?
/Hello
Are you ready for today's class?
/ Yes!
Teacher, Tonnam has a sprained leg, so he probably won't be able to dance.
Accidents, I understand, are unavoidable.
But we can be careful to prevent it from happening.
I would like to offer some criticism. Why don't you realise you should be cautious?
Because it will be a burden on your friends
I'm sorry.
It's okay; it has happened, and there's nothing you can do to change it now.
Okay, Tonnam. You can take a break and review the dance for today.
Let's continue, the rest of you. Okay, come on.
Review from the basics first. Can you still remember?
Starting from bouncing. 5 6 7 8 Go! 1 2 3..
Hold on. Try again. You guys already forgot. 5 6 7 8 Go! 1 2..
Why are you here?
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just thinking about this and that.
If there's anything uncomfortable, please let me know.
I miss mom and dad.
Call then if you miss them.
I can't call them now; they passed away last month.
I'm sorry.
Life is funny sometimes, don't you think so?
It's like..
I tried so hard just to be here. I wanted them to be proud of me. But, you see, they're not here anymore.
Now, I don't know what I'm trying so hard for.
Another thing, I feel like I no longer belong here.
What makes you think that way?
Look at me. I'm not good at dancing.
And I hurt my leg. I feel like a burden.
I believe in you. You the best in my eyes.
The accident is not a big deal.
It's okay. I've got your back.
Really?
Really. Why would I lie to you?
I'm sure you can do it.
Okay
Oh? Pim, aren't you leaving yet?
I'm about to leave.
I'm leaving. Bye.
Anyway, I'd appreciate it if you could take care of the boys too. Consider yourself a senior. If there's anything, please help advise and teach them."
Consider yourself a senior. If there's anything, please help advise and teach them.
Copy that.
Wait!
Yes?
Keep it friendly with a senior and junior vibe; no need to flirt with everyone, okay?
I'd rather not keep solving your problems, so let's try to avoid creating more, okay?
I'll try, but I won't promise
Huh? You're gonna get it!
Today is the first testing day. Please make a lot of comments.
So they'll know where to improve and can do it right away.
Alright
Pim, please take notes on the boys' progress so that we can make improvements in the future.
Roger that.
For mr.Kong, please take a close look at the boys and determine the best way to adjust their appearance.
Or you can watch their show first, so you'll know how to groom them best.
Noted! I guarantee our costumes are going to be the best ever.
I'm counting on all of you. Let's talk again after the test.
Are you guys ready?
Hello
How's everything going? Are you nervous?
For the first evaluation, do your best.
I believe everyone is well prepared. So, let's don't waste time.
I know everyone is determined, but, to be honest, I'm a bit disappointed
I expected something better than this but it's alright.
For dancing, Kengkla did the best today but could be better.
As for others, you may not yet have the right direction in mind
But It's okay. It's a chance for improvement.
We might have to practise more basics. I'll talk about it later in class.
For singing, you guys need to practise more. Because your singing is still not good yet.
For those still out of tune, my advice is to listen more.
I like Tul and Trin's singing the most. Don't forget to practise more.
The teachers covered everything on point.
I quite agreed. From now on, you guys should train harder.
I hope to see improvements from everybody next time.
Let me be honest, if things don't go well, I might reconsider the project. I don't want to waste money.
I want to work with people who give their 100% in their work.
Go back and practise. I'm rooting for you all.
Thank you for today. See you next time.
Thank you
Before leaving, everyone goes to Mr. Kong to have your body measurements taken. He'll be in charge of your appearance.
How pathetic you all look. Let's take the measurements. Come one! so you can take a rest.
Hold it. Help me out. Hurry up boys. Don't you want to go home? Or do you want to stay here with me?
Chest..
Namo! Namo! Why are you here alone?
I'm listening to music and thinking about stuff.
Can I listen with you?
What song are you listening to?
This one
Listening to this song brings up old memories.
Do you still remember?
How can I forget? Isn't it the one you wrote?
Yes, it is.
How about singing it again?
Good idea
But you play the guitar
I should, It's my song.
Of course.
Wait, let me look at the chords first.
What? It's your own song. How could you forget the chords?
I didn't play it for a while.
Alright, alright.
I'll hold it for you.
Alright, 5 4 3 2 1
We have this many members in today's class, right?
Yes, that's right.
Has anyone done the 'reflection assignment'?
We haven't
It's okay. We'll do it together
'Reflection assignment', just like its name. The mirror will reflect everything we do.
We'll split into two teams. One team is the leader and another team is the follower.
Whatever the leader does, the follower has to follow.
The most important thing to keep in mind is that the leader must not do anything that can cause harm to the follower.
Don't forget to take care of your friends. If you understand, you can pair up now.
Phupa pairs up with Tonnam and Namo with Kengkla. Let's start.
Be focused. And start when you're ready.
Who's gonna be the leader?
Okay, Phupa and Kengklas are the leader.
You reflect each other.
Keep an eye contact. Be focused. Move closer a bit.
That was great, everyone.
Now, switch partners.
Bring Tonnam here?
/I'll go there
Walk properly and stay here.
This time Namo and Tonnam are gonna be the leader.
/ I'll lead.
Okay, look at your friends slowly.
Keep and eye contact and be focused. Don't forget you're reflecting each other.
Tonnam, be concentrated.
I learned about concentration and focus today.
You learned a lot today. Don't forget to do your homework.
And that's it for today.
I'll leave. / Take me with you. / No!
Phupa
hm?
Nothing
I'll pack your stuff for you.
Is something good? You were walking around with a smile.
I have something to boast about.
hm? what is it?
What is this?
It's the video of Namo and Kengkla playing guitar and singing together. The views on the video have surpassed 100,000.
People are shipping Kengkla and Namo.
At first, I thought I would just post a video, but the response has been surprisingly good.
People are starting to ask about their work and talking about the 'Beyond the Star' project.
Good, then.
They're talking a lot about Namo and Kengkla.
You did a great job.
Um, but if they sue you, you'll be responsible. It has nothing to do with me.
You secretly took a video of them and even posted it on social media without their permission. If they're not okay with it, I won't be able to help you."
Are we going to abandon each other so easily? I'm trying to help create a trend, and the company also benefits
Also, the boys benefit from it. I don't think they would sue me.
Who knows? I don't know.
Boss!
I don't know.
Don't know. Don't know. Don't know.
Kengkla, I want to sleep.
Kengkla!
Why are you praying so early in the morning? Don't you think Buddha also wants to sleep like me?
Namo, be quiet.
I'm praying so that our project will be amazing. Got it?
Wake up.
Wake up. You'll be late.
If you don't get up, you'll go to practise late.
But I don't want to get up.
Stubborn
I'm not stubborn.
Do you know what will stubborn kid get?
A morning kiss
I was waiting for this.
Then go take a shower, or we'll be late.
I'll take a shower later.
What do you think?
They're getting better everyday.
Seeing this makes me a little relieved. I think we should start preparing for their debut.
Sounds like a lot of fun.
I know, right? Let's see, between MChange and KJ, who's going to win this game?
Say the prayers together.
Namo, wake up.
I'm sleepy.
I know but say the prayers first.
The monk is saying it, though.
Looks yummy. I'll have two. Oh! I don't need a plastic bag, thank you.
Are you Namo?
Kita! How are you? I missed you so much!
How are you? Haven't seen you for a long time.
I'm good, what about you?
I'm good, the usual, you know?
Um, I was a little bit too happy. I forgot to introduce him. This is Kita. Do you remember? I've told you about him during our time in University.
Hello
Hi
And this is Kengkla, my friend from the agency. He's also my roommate.
Is Kengkla your best friend from university?
Yes, I am
We haven't met since then, have we?
We haven't.
I try texting you but you don't even read.
That was when we just broke up. Who would dare to read?
I thought it was something else. Why did you choose to break up with me then?
Namo, didn't you say you were hungry? Let's go get some food.
Oh right? Let's have a meal together since we haven't met for so long.
Are you hungry? So we can talk.