Boys, who's finished with their hair and makeup?
Come by and show me how it turned out, I want to see how neat it look.
Because today's event must be outstanding, exceptional, and truly impressive.
Hey.
Oh?
Hey! How did you get in?
I just walked in, saying I'm your friend.
Are you looking for someone?
No, I'm not.
You're acting a bit odd today
Let's fight today.
Do your best.
Namo.
Yes, Namo. I'm calling you. Come over here
I'll be right back.
Let me help.
It's okay.
Kita
Hello.
How are you? Where's your mum?
How did you get here?
Eye and Pim mentioned that your mother is sick, so I hurried here.
That would be correct.
She's waiting for surgery,
but the doctor mentioned they still couldn't proceed with the procedure.
But I heard it's an urgent surgery. What are we waiting for?
Well,
I don't have enough money.
You don't have to worry. I'll take care of it.
You called me. What's going on?
I've got something I need your help with
What do you need help with?
I'd like you to do whatever it takes to ruin the Beyond The Star project.
Pardon?
I think I made it clear.
What can I do alone?
I heard you and Namo were dating.
Approaching that side wouldn't be difficult, would it?
Um
Is your mother's health better now?
Yes.
Good
Then you would help me, wouldn't you?
Who has already done their makeup and hair?
Please stay still.
Because there are so many of you but only one me. It's very chaotic now.
So please have mercy on me.
We understand.
Kengkla
Yeah?
Do you think we can really pull it off?
Namo, why do you have to worry? We've already come this far
Fight on.
Boys, listen up. How's everything going? Don't be nervous, just do your best.
Don't forget your goals. What are you here for?
Don't forget to eat while you're waiting. It'll give you more energy for the performance. Fighting!
Thank you!
I hope you won't be ashamed if you lose today.
Have you heard the saying, 'Who laughs last, laughs best"?
Anything can happen.
Are you ready?
Who are here for Red King?
And who are here for Beyond the Star?
Alright! I think everybody's ready.
If you're ready, let's enjoy the showcase battle between Red King and Beyond the Star!
The showcase battle between Red King and Beyond the Star is over.
Now, let's hear comments from the commentators.
I want to compliment both teams on your performance
Both teams have clearly different styles. It's kind of hard to make a comparison.
I like both teams. You're both very good, but I prefer Red King a little bit more.
Your talent and confidence shine through.
It might be because Red King has more experience, so Red King dominated the stage.
For me, I prefer Beyond the Star's performance.
Everyone seems happy to perform in front of the audience, adding to the joy of the spectators.
I really liked it for both singing and communication.
For Beyond the Star, each member did their homework. All maintained a consistent standard in singing levels,
with some even surpassing their practice.
Red King did great. Benefitting from having more experience.
How did you like the performance?
I really enjoyed the performance. It was very impressive. They all did great.
Wishing both teams luck.
Thank you for the commentary
And the winning team is!
Red King!
Congratulations to the winning team!
And for Beyond the Star, you did great today. Keep on fighting!
What a pity.
We were so close to winning.
It's okay. You're already very good.
Here
An award for someone with talent.
Thanks.
Let's snap a picture for an Instagram story.
Hey, Kengkla. Let's take a picture together.
It's okay, you guys can take pictures first.
I'll be back.
Is anything wrong?
I just want to say that you did very well today. Nothing much.
Then I'm leaving now.
Take care.
I'm off.
Namo.
Yes?
Well
Do you still remember our last conversation about what to do when you lose?
I never said I agreed to your offer.
I just mentioned that I would like to think about it first.
I'll stay here.
I'm here to prove to you that KJ Agency is just as good as any other.
Hope you can do what you said.
I will be watching.
As for you, we need to have a conversation.
Shall we go home now?
You can go first. I'll head inside and meet Natee.
Okay.
See you later.
We apologise, Ms. Araya, for causing the company to lose face
Forget it, it's okay.
At least today, everyone showed me determination and dedication.
You did very well. I noticed your improvement.
I'm very proud of you all today.
You must be very tired after the whole day today
Thank you.
Tonnam, why did you make a mistake in the dance? You didn't seem focused.
I'm sorry.
What about you? You stood in the wrong blocking during both rehearsal and performance.
Instead of taking responsibility, you only blamed other people.
But at least I didn't make a mistake in the dance
If that's the case, Mawin also made a mistake. Why don't you go and scold him?
And what are you being nosy about?
No, stop it!
Stop!
What the hell are you guys doing?
You're fighting like little kids
Hey! If you're going to be like this, please go home.
Go back and reflect on yourself.
Come back when you're more self-aware.
Sorry.
Alright, I'm sorry.
Are you hungry?
Yes, I am.
Do you want to have some?
No, thanks. I'm currently on a low-carb diet.
It's very delicious. Please give it a try.
If it's so delicious, why don't you have more?
Eat properly. Your mouth is all messy.
Where?
It's not messy.
Here.
Phupa
I cleaned it up for you.
Someone will see us.
No one's going to see us. They all went home.
Let's go somewhere else. It's too risky here.
Here is fine.
Let me help.
Thank you so much.
How is it? I brought you to make merit. Does it make you feel better?
I feel nothing.
But how?
I'm kidding.
My overthinking has lessened.
We lost, and there's nothing we can do about it anyway. What about you?
I feel a whole lot better. Maybe I've just accepted the fact that we lost.
And I've got to punch you in the face.
Do you want to punch me one more time?
Oh, please let me.
Tonnam, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
It's okay. From now on, let's give it another try.
Because we started from zero.
Now, there are many people notice us.
If we continue to improve, we're going to get better.
I believe,
Come one, let's give it another try.
Come on.
Let's do it.
Inside the temple?
Why not?
You're so slow.
Do it quietly. One, two ,three "Hey!".
Hey.
Please smile. Hey.
Let's go.
Why are you here alone?
Are you stressed about something?
I think I will withdraw. I might not be able to continue with you guys
Why?
Do you really think I am suited for this path?
Why do you feel that way?
You guys might shine brighter without me in this project.
Don't think like that.
I believe in you.
Take your time and reconsider, is it a good idea?
I've made a decision, and I hope you understand
If that's your decision, I respect it.
Hey! What’s wrong with you?
I'm truly sorry, sir.
Hey, let me handle it. I apologise on behalf of my friend.
My friend really didn't mean to.
Hey, can we talk?
I'm working.
I'm sorry about that day and for not believing that your mum was sick.
Can you stop talking about this matter?
I know you're angry. I'm genuinely sorry.
It was my fault for judging you before knowing the truth.
I'm truly sorry.
You're a deadweight, heard that?
It's none of your business.
Forgive me, please.
You really won't forgive me?
I'm working. Can't you see? Just go back.
If you won't forgive me, I won't leave.
Okay, I forgive you. Are you satisfied now?
Yes, I am.
Let me do that.
Okay, wipe it.
Do you want to do everything instead of me?
Make yourself at home, Copper.
You can put your bag here.
What do you want to drink?
Just water would be fine.
Water? I'll get it for you.
The new dance moves are so difficult. Can you memorise them?
Yes, I can.
Really? How can you memorise it? There were a lot of dance moves
If you practise a lot, then you'll memorise it.
I can't memorise anything. My brain can't accept new movements.
Here's your water.
Thank you.
Shall we play a game?
That sounds fun.
Play a game?
Yes.
What game?
The game we used to play.
But last time, you lost to me.
It's time for a rematch.
Let's see.
Yes, let's see. The loser will have to go and buy ingredients for the BBQ alone.
Really?
Really.
Then okay.
Do you guys even place bets?
Of course.