Kita! How are you? I missed you so much!
How are you? Haven't seen you for a long time.
I'm good, what about you?
I'm good, the usual, you know?
Um, I was a little bit too happy. I forgot to introduce him. This is Kita. Do you remember? I've told you about him during our time in University.
Hello
And this is Kengkla, my friend from the agency. He's also my roommate.
Is Kengkla your best friend from university?
Yes, I am
We haven't met since then, have we?
We haven't.
I tried texting you, but you don't even read.
That was when we just broke up. Who would dare to read?
I thought it was something else. Why did you choose to break up with me then?
Namo, didn't you say you were hungry? Let's go get some food.
Oh right? Let's have a meal together since we haven't met for so long.
Are you hungry? So we can talk.
Please.
I'll wait here.
I'll take this one and that one.
Umm and which one else should I take? Okay, this one and this one and that one.
What would you like to order?
I'd like to have Chicken Kaphrao rice with fried egg on top.
Me too
Then two.
Two Kraphrao rice.
Three
Alright, three kraphrao rice.
What are you doing lately?
Lately? I'm a trainee under MChange. How about you?
I'm also a trainee but under KJ Agency.
Oh? We're rivals, then.
Yes
Where did it go?
What happened?
Nothing; I'm finding something but can’t find it.
Kita, so now you're under MChange. Is it hard?
Yes, It's quite difficult. And I'm tired and..
Is weight training the main thing you do when you're there?
Does it hurt because you work out so hard? You look muscly.
well, yeah
You look buff. Can you tighten your shoulders a bit?
Wow, so thick. Your shoulders look circular.
Really? maybe because I train so hard.
Is that so? Can you help me with training as well?
Of course, yes.
I'm glad I met you today
So am I.
You can call me any time
I'll go now.
Bye-bye; see you later.
I'm going.
Bye
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Okay then.
Where did you go?
I went out to find something to eat.
Why didn't you invite me?
I thought you weren't hungry.
I'm sorry.
Don't touch me.
Here! I bought you your favourite cake.
Please don't sulk.
Let me give you a kiss on the cheek.
Alright, don't do it again next time.
Then go take a shower first, and I'll make you breakfast.
Cook later. Let's take a shower together.
Then what are you waiting for?
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
"It's okay, not a big deal. I'm willing to help.
I really feel like I am a burden on everyone
Do you have something to say?
Don't think that way. It's an accident. No one wants to hurt their own leg, right?
Good, let's go to practise.
What's wrong? Why are you angry with me?
I don't like it.
You don't like it? like what?
When you met that Kita boy.
You made me feel like I'm not there. I'm your best friend, though?
Not funny.
I'm sorry.
I actually knew it that you're not okay.
But you were cute, so I wanted to tease you.
Is it fun for you to toy with other people's feelings like this?
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I'm not that angry.
If so..
we're okay then?
yes
Tonnam
What's up?
Let's practise.
Fortunately, I'm the one who saw it.
If it wasn't me, you and Kengkla will be in trouble.
I know.
Like this. One, two, three.
Hello
Today, I'll give you a new assignment.
I'll regroup, so everyone will be able to work together more thoroughly.
Today's assignment will be about singing and dancing as usual.
Singing and dancing again?
Yes, so I can see the improvement from last time.
Again? I don't wanna do this anymore.
Just do it.
The first group includes Trin, Copper and Namo.
The second group includes Tul, Kengkla and Mungkorn.
The last group, Phupa, Tonnam and Mawin.
I'll let Pim hand out the song.
Okay
Pass them on to your friends.
This time, I want everyone to give their best effort, focusing on both singing and dancing well
The company will grant a 'pass' in the evaluation for those who performed better than last time
Also, this is going to be your song.
I hope all of you will do a better job than last time.
Anyway, keep going.
Thank you.
Everyone, come here. Come.
So, are we here to be actors or a boy band?
I'm getting confused now. Didn't we audition for actors?
Yeah
I'm getting bored now.
Come on. Keep calm. The company might already have a plan.
We just have to do our best.
Let's practise.
We can now disperse into the groups we divided up just now.
Tul, let's go.
So last time..
Is Mungkorn coming?
So they want us to come up with our own choreography?
Tonnam
Thank you
It's itchy, isn't it?
Yes and it is very annoying.
When are you taking it off?
I'm wearing it for the last day. I also have an appointment with the doctor today.
Do you want me to accompany you?
Are you sure? I really appreciate it
Of course! I have time now. No worries.
Alright then.
No need to scratch. You'll be taking it off tomorrow.
Did you wait long? My practice ended late.
It's okay. Someone on my team had to leave early, so the practice ended more quickly.
Are you upset?
No, I'm not.
If so, why are you making that face?
Well, maybe a little bit upset. I'm hungry, and I've been waiting for so long.
I'll get you some yummy stuff then.
Um, can I have another yummy thing?
Stop being so cheeky.
I didn't have enough this morning.
Kita
Are you tired today?
A little.
What do you want to eat? Hungry?
Very much.
You just said I'm cheeky but you're the one being cheeky now.
I'm joking.
I'm up for anything! Let's go; I'm getting super hungry.
Let's go.
What should we eat?
Are you still here?
Yeah
I thought you had already left.
I continued practising because I feel like I didn't do well today.
Why are you two not leaving yet?
We practised too. I couldn't catch up with the dance.
It's good that you're aware of it. Practice makes perfect.
Don't assume being the president's nephew gives you the freedom to do whatever you want.
I won't be okay with that.
What's the matter with him?
Don't know. Let's just go.
Take a seat slowly.
Okay
Be careful.
Here's the medicine. I'm leaving. Call me if you need something.
Wait.
Can you stay with me for a little while?
Sure.
I'm very grateful to you for taking care of me.
Anytime.
Okay
Do you have something on your mind?
You look like you want to say something, but you never actually say it.
Well..
So, so I..
I've got feelings for you.
Aha
Are you cool with the idea of continuing our relationship, I mean, like talking?
But if you're not, that's totally okay. I can handle my own feelings.
I don't want to cause you discomfort. I can hold back.
I wouldn't want to bother you or make things difficult.
Let's talk and get to know each other better.
If things click, we can see where it takes us, Sounds good?
Yes.
I'm going now.
Don't forget to take your medicine.
Any updates for today?
Well, things at KJ Agency aren't moving forward at all. I heard the first evaluation didn't go well.
I knew it. Araya alone is not that good.
Why are you so sure about it?
Mr. In, we were lovers.
Former lovers turned enemies are the most daunting.
Because we know each other too well.
Hello
Have you handled the matter I requested?
The process has already started, Boss, but it needs to be done gradually.
Great job! I'll leave it in your hands. And, most importantly, keep it under wraps, okay?
Roger that.
Oh my god!
What happened?
This is Kengkla, what could it be? It won't be anything but Mutelu? I'll bet a hundred.
I'll bet a thousand.
So what happened, Kengkla?
Tonight is a good night.
It's the new moon. It's the night of the full moon, the most powerful one
You can make a wish about anything, and it will come true.
You guys are not leaving early today. I'll take you to pray so that we can be super famous and no one can drag us down.
Good idea, right?
Can you walk faster? If you walk this slow, it won't be in time.
We're following. Why rush?
You're always so excited. Aren't you tired?
I mean well; I'm doing this for all of you. So we can pray to the moon for good fortune
for our beyond the star project to go big!
I'm starting.
Phupa, help me block the wind.
The wind is blowing this way.
The moonlight is out now
Hold on, hold on. It's going to be on time
Done. Come on
He looks more serious than when he practises.
Of course, he does.
I can hear what you're saying. Hands together.
Everyone, drink as much as you like tonight. It's a day off tomorrow!
But the last one who's sober will have to take care of the party aftermath.
Looks like it's going to be me.
Tonnam, are you alcohol-tolerant?
No, I don't drink.
Then you should go home.
What?
Just kidding.
It's okay, you don't have to drink. Just chilling with us.
If you're not drinking, fill up my cup.
Fill up mine too.
That bottle is not strong enough. Yes, that bottle.
Hurry up. Fill up mine. Wow, overflowing.
I'm going to feel the buzz.
Cheers? Come on.
Cheers!
Phupa, I think we should go home. I'm sleepy now.
Look at Kengkla and Namo. They're both drunk; I don't think they'll be having any more drinks.
Okay
Namo, Namo, Namo. I'm going now.
I'm leaving.
Yes? Oh, okay. Go home safely.
Bye Kengkla, bye Namo.
I'll carry it.
Thank you
Kengkla
Kengkla, go sleep on the bed properly.
Go sleep properly. Let me help.
Get up.
Quickly
Do you want to throw up?
Where are we going?
We're going to sleep.
Be careful.
Kengkla, don't touch.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Can I kiss you?
Don't be funny.
What are you doing?
I have a good feeling for you.
But I'm confused.
Whether it's really love,
or just a strong bond.
Kengkla
I'm sorry.
It's okay, don't worry.
Our feelings
are the same anyway, right?
No, it's not like that. It's just both of us are drunk.
If you don't like me
the way I like you,
why did we kiss, though?
It happened in the heat of the moment. Do you understand?
No
but I have to, right?
I'll take a shower.
You made me all sober now.
Hello, everyone!
Welcome, everyone, to the press conference for the debut of the boy band Red King from MChange Entertainment.
Yes, first of all, please allow me to introduce our CEO. Please come up to the stage.
Hello to all honored guests, media, and fans
First of all, I want to express my gratitude to everyone who has joined this press conference.
Red King is our rookie group, and I aim for them to excel both in their image and dance.
The members include Film, Phark, Cream, Phat, Natee and Phuri.
Please give them love and support. Thank you.
Are you ready?
If you're ready, please welcome Red King for their debut performance!
Kita, do you know that in our company, fighting is prohibited? It could lead to serious consequences, including termination.
Yes, I know.
How do you plan to take responsibility for this?
But he was the one who started the quarrel with me first.
You pissed me off first. / It was you..
Stop!
Kita, you punched him first.
Yes, I did. I'm sorry.
So, how do you want to be punished?
I've made a decision. To take responsibility for the incident,
I'd like to withdraw from the Red King project.
Hold a second.
What is it?
Why didn't you knock the door?
I'm sorry.
I understand that what Kita did was wrong, but please don't remove him from the project.
Then what do you want me to do? Remove you instead?
Is it possible for me to take on his punishment instead and swap positions?
Kawi
You don't have to do it this way.
I don't understand.
Give the copyright of the songs you wrote,
to the company and I'll pretend this never happened.
Mr. Kiat, he punched me.
I stand by my words. I will resign from being a teacher here.
Please don't.
I'm okay. Just doing the right thing.
I respect your decision, Kawi but Kita has to take his responsibility.
because it's going to be unfair to Film.
Kita, I'll remove you from the Red King project but you'll continue to be a trainee in our company.
Until we have a new project.
I want you to practise and improve yourself, understood?
Understood.