ALL CHARACTERS, NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
ANY RESEMBLANCE IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL
EPISODE 6
Don't go to Naksan Medical Center.
I won't send you.
What do you mean?
What don't you understand?
You don't have to go.
Is that a good thing or not?
Is he kidding?
What about the strike?
It's all thanks to you, Dr. Joo.
-What's going on?
-Is he serious?
That's a relief.
This is a bit awkward.
It's all thanks to you.
One thing is for sure.
Our fate
is in Mr. Gu's hands.
He proved that just now.
Dr. Lee.
I have big news.
Big news? What now?
We don't have to go.
The relocation has been canceled.
Who said that? How?
Mr. Gu. He just said it himself.
The president said it himself,
so it's for sure, right?
-Really?
-I'm going to spread the word.
I'll go with you.
How do I…
Thanks.
No way.
Let's go get some coffee. My treat.
Yes!
Again?
Are you still taking care of
all those patients?
When will they let you off?
My sentiments exactly.
Hello?
How many people will get dragged into it?
Technically, it was the chief
of the Cancer Center who covered it up.
It won't make much of a difference.
Even doctors who kill patients
wherever they go
still go around the rural areas
and perform surgeries.
It's because they rarely revoke
doctors' licenses.
That resident at the Cancer Center
is your classmate, right?
Yes.
Being punished is one thing…
How could he make such a mistake?
We trained like crazy. How could he…
He didn't get dragged into it.
The chief is also at fault.
Jae-hyeok.
Yes?
Did you give Clamoxin
to the patient in Bed 11?
Well… I did.
You said to give him Clamoxin
instead of Cefotam.
It wasn't checked off.
What if I didn't check
and ended up giving him double doses?
I'm sorry.
Do you think it is okay
because it doesn't kill?
No, I don't. I'm sorry.
We're no better than the Cancer Center.
We've just been lucky.
You said you trained like crazy,
but you rely on luck?
Did you study for nothing?
I'll be more careful.
Everyone!
Listen up. We're not…
being kicked out.
Chief.
I've been thinking…
Since the strike is off,
the management will no longer consider
meeting our demands, will they?
I don't think they will.
Is it true?
Are we really not going?
That's… right.
That's great…
Wait.
It's that detective.
They could've just summoned him.
Did they have to come to his workplace
and humiliate him?
They have no consideration
since we have no shield.
Including that jerk up there.
How long will we keep
the director position vacant?
That's right. Let's fill it soon.
We need a representative
in order to fight the president.
Well, we made all that noise
about the strike,
but we ended up calling it off
without even making a peep.
So if there's anything you did
that needs cleaning up,
clean it up quickly so that
we don't become a laughing stock.
I'm going back to work.
Neither of them even stood a chance
when Director Lee was here,
but it could've been a tight race
between the chief of the Cancer Center
and the deputy director in this election.
That's right. The deputy director
had it handed to him on a platter.
Look at him just now.
The conference was held
by Cardiothoracic Surgery.
Why was he leading it?
He made a fool out of the chief
of Cardiothoracic Surgery
in front of everyone.
See you later.
If you keep pretending not to care,
all your efforts could go in vain.
What do you mean?
We are going to hold an election anyway.
No one will say anything even if you show
your willingness to become the director.
You know, there's someone
who is eager to get the position.
Who?
Dr. Joo.
See you later.
Dr. Joo?
What the…
Get your act together.
You need to become the director
for the deputy director position
to open up.
JANG SEONG-JA SPEECH THERAPY ROOM
THIS ROOM WAS OPENED WITH THE DONATION
OF DR. JANG SEONG-JA,
FORMERLY RADIOLOGIST AT THIS HOSPITAL
DR. JANG SEONG-JA IS THE MOTHER
OF OUR ALUMNI, DR. OH SE-HWA
OF NEUROSURGERY
DR. JANG SEONG-JA
Yes.
Because I made a promise to you, Mr. Cho,
that people won't say
the hospital is having problems.
Yes.
I should set it straight with the doctors
that Hwajeong Group owns this hospital.
They should know
that we hold their lives in our hands.
The Greek god doctor is staying.
Yes.
The result of the efficiency evaluation
is being put together.
I'll bring it over once it's done.
I see. Like that. Okay.
SAEGEUL21
Hello, Dr. Ye.
Hello?
Hello.
I have some bad news.
What is it?
It looks like
we are calling off the strike.
If you publish my interview,
it will make you look like
you are reporting false information.
You must be the thoughtful type.
Pardon?
I've never had anyone tell me in advance.
I see.
Was the strike just called off
or did the parties come to an agreement?
Such swift settlements
often lead to trouble later.
We'll just have to wait and see for now
since the relocation has been canceled.
That's a good thing then,
so let's be happy. Congratulations.
You don't have to feel bad
since many articles
end up unpublished anyway.
Ms. Choi! Let's go.
Just a minute.
May I call you again if I have questions
about the medical field?
Yes,
of course.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but we're on our way somewhere.
Have a nice day.
You, too.
You must be the thoughtful type.
I'm not.
Such swift settlements
often lead to trouble later.
I once read a saying
that life is like a spiral staircase.
You may think you climbed high,
but when you look down,
you can still see the path you walked on.
Director Lee,
why do I feel like it's been so long
since you've been here?
NOTICE OF ELECTION
They are now accepting candidates.
It's finally starting.
It's only a competition of their own.
We don't have a say in it anyway.
There has been only one director
during my time here.
NOTICE OF ELECTION
"A competition of their own…"
Anyone at a chief level
can be a candidate for the director.
There are 44 doctors
who are eligible to vote,
so the person must receive
22 votes or more to become the director.
Previously, the board of directors
approved the appointment of the candidate,
but now… How would you like to…
Does Sangkook University Hospital
still have a board of directors?
Right. We've granted all the authorities
to one person.
That means that the elected candidate
needs your approval
in order to be appointed
as the hospital director.
The previous director
really was impressive,
serving four consecutive terms.
He had many who followed him.
Even for a private institution,
four terms…
-How many years did he--
-Eleven years.
Time really flies.
Do you really think
eleven years was short?
I learned a lot thanks to him.
Well,
I'm glad to know that you are all ready
to become the director.
"All ready"?
The candidate registration
hasn't even been closed yet.
Let me be straightforward.
I want you as the director.
Why?
Because we'll work well together.
Aren't I right?
It will be…
the best decision for you.
MS. KANG
CONNECTIONS BETWEEN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
HOSPITALS AND HEALTHCARE INDUSTRY
I'm going to start a subsidiary.
A pharmaceutical distribution company.
The company will supply medicines
only to us.
Then the pharmacies near the hospital
would have to buy medicines
from the subsidiary
since doctors
at Sangkook University Hospital
will only prescribe
our subsidiary's drugs.
This is unbelievable.
We work so well together already.
But general hospitals
are nonprofit corporations,
so they can't set up subsidiaries.
I'm sure you're aware of that, of course.
Yes, it is technically impossible,
but every organization has subsidiaries.
Even public universities do.
That's right. It's possible
if the subsidiary is also a nonprofit.
The profit can be given to the foundation
as donations.
Then it won't be taxed, either.
Let's say we took bids
from pharmaceutical distributors
and made the decision quietly
within the hospital.
And tell every department
to submit a protocol
for the prevention of medication errors.
I will have the chiefs present them to me.
The Cancer Center included.
Yes, sir.
I have a question.
Why does everyone want to be
the hospital director?
It's not like anyone would nag
doctors at that level.
You all cure diseases.
Why do company workers want
to get promoted and become president?
For the salary?
If you don't, it means
they want you out.
We lose our jobs.
Did you climb this high up the ladder
because you were afraid of
losing your job?
Good day.
Candidates…
2017 SECOND HALF PROFIT RANKINGS
1. OPHTHALMOLOGY, 2. ORTHOPEDICS,
3. CANCER CENTER
We are going to hold an election anyway.
No one will say anything even if you show
your willingness to become the director.
You know, there's someone
who is eager to get the position.
HWAJEONG CHEMICAL
Please take a look at that machine
on the right.
That is an empty bottle inspection machine
that is used to check
the quality of the bottles we use.
Over here, the bottles
are filled with the product.
Then they are capped…
You'd like to set up
a pharmaceutical distribution company?
As a subsidiary?
Since supplements have the same
distribution route as medicines,
we will send the person
who will be in charge.
Please educate that person
on the distribution process.
Can a subsidiary be formed
that quickly overnight?
We aren't making the drugs ourselves.
We are only setting up
a single supplier framework.
A pharmaceutical company
that supplies medicines
to the hospital that owns the company.
You'd have exclusivity.
You'd benefit as well
since you'll have no competition.
That's totally up to you.
With an exclusive arrangement,
we take it all if we are your supplier,
but if you cut us loose,
we'd lose it all in an instant.
We'd lose everything.
I guess we'll have to cooperate. Right?
Send the person in charge.
Thank you. And one more thing.
I'd like you to fund equipment purchases
for our hospital.
If I tell the doctors to sell
Hwajeong Chemical's drugs to the patients,
their egos won't let them
agree to do so that easily.
So, I plan to make
a justification for you.
I'll look it over and get back to you.
Thank you.
RFID MEDICAL SYSTEM
RFID READER
Goodness.
PARATRANSIT
Hello?
I just checked.
Please keep monitoring
the oxygen saturation.
Thank you.
That was him.
Hi, No-eul.
Hey, Seon-woo. Where are you right now?
Me? Where else? I'm at work.
Why?
-I thought--
-In ten meters,
turn left.
These damn calls.
Don't pick up. Ignore it.
Should I?
I'll call you back.
Hey, you're the one who called me.
I will get mad at you if you hang up.
Whatever. I'll call you back.
Hello?
The lab results are out?
What did they say?
I don't think he was here for work.
I just asked the insurance claims office
if someone from the HIRA was here.
They said no.
Are you sure it was him?
How could I not recognize Seon-woo?
True.
He has no reason to come here.
You don't think he's sick, do you?
If he was,
he wouldn't have come to where I work at.
You know…
Sorry.
Are you still doing all the work?
Did you get any sleep?
I'm going to get some sleep now.
See you tomorrow.
You'll get yourself killed.
What?
Push the seat back.
Why are you so short?
It's so cramped.
I'm of average height.
You're the unusual one.
Push the seat back.
Then you'll have to struggle
to pull it forward again tomorrow
with those twiggy arms.
I said we could take your car.
And pick you up in the morning?
I never asked you to.
Hey.
What?
Look at you.
You must be waiting for someone's call.
How dare a runt try to meddle in
an adult's business?
You call me a runt
whenever you're at a disadvantage.
You'll get wrinkles.
Jin-woo.
Yes?
Chodang Apartment.
Dr. Joo!
-Get in.
-Hey.
-We'll drop you off.
-Thanks.
It's nice living close by,
but it's hard to get a taxi
for a short ride.
You haven't been home in a while.
You go only a few times a month, right?
Is that right? Could that be why?
What do you mean?
I recently learned
that my daughter is in high school.
I was sure that she was in junior high.
Anyway, am I being the third wheel?
No, sir.
We're practically sisters.
Don't worry about it.
We are brothers.
You are too pretty to be a brother.
You aren't that pretty to be a sister.
You're practically sisters.
Thank you.
The leaves are so green.
They will probably wither soon.
Are you okay?
What were you going to say…
It's okay. I don't keep anything
from Dr. Lee.
Remember that time
right before the mortality conference?
You were about to say something to me.
Something about the past.
A long time ago,
a family member of mine
was hospitalized for quite a while.
I know.
One time, his condition got worse
all of a sudden.
I thought it was because
he wasn't well in the first place.
When I think about it now,
it was because of a medical error.
I was reminded of that time
when I didn't know anything.
Maybe because of
the Cancer Center incident
or the anaphylactic shock death…
I realized that I was both
a victim and a perpetrator.
We all are.
I wasn't trying to throw stones
at your department along with Mr. Gu.
I do not go along with the likes of him.
What do you mean by "the likes of him"?
What do you think?
What is he like?
He puts numbers above people's lives.
Are we any different?
We always complain about
how little we get paid from the HIRA.
"Several highly skilled people like us
operated on a patient for hours.
How could they pay
only 200 to 300 thousand won
for the surgery?" We always say that.
That's different.
How is it different?
Are you saying we can put numbers above
our patients' lives since we are doctors,
but he isn't qualified to do so?
Because he didn't go to medical school?
We talk about those things
because the policy is wrong.
The government failed
to set a reasonable fee schedule,
so doctors are suffering.
It's only natural for them to complain.
What about you?
Do you agree with Mr. Gu's idea
to kick out unprofitable departments?
Don't twist my words.
That's clearly wrong.
However,
I think even someone like Mr. Gu
has a role in our group.
He is a businessman to the bone.
If you naively go along with him,
you'll be eaten alive in no time.
And what do we learn by ostracizing him?
We know better than anyone how clannish
and self-centered
a group of people we are.
I think Mr. Gu is someone
who can cast a stone.
If we don't want to get eaten alive,
we should keep our eyes wide open.
But if we stop him from casting a stone
just because we are too busy
and do not want to be bothered,
nothing will change.
We will forever remain
a stagnant body of water.
Hey.
Yes? Go ahead.
That's my apartment building.
Okay.
Good night.
He'll remember where he lives, right?
What do you mean?
He doesn't even know his daughter's age.
The buildings all look alike.
I'm telling Dr. Joo on you.
Mr. Gu was the first person
who wasn't from the owner's family
to become a CEO in his group
before the age of 40.
He isn't your average guy.
I looked him up, too.
You did?
Why did you look him up?
How could I not look up our new president?
You did it too.
I was…
I showed him around the wards.
Personally? Why?
I thought he might feel something
if he saw the kids.
Like he would ever.
So? Did he?
-I'm not sure.
-I am.
You should've seen him
during the mortality conference.
-I heard.
-It's different from seeing it.
Exactly. His thoughts
could have changed from before
when he just knew
that there are patients in the hospital
after seeing those sick babies
with his own eyes.
It would be awesome
if everything works out as you expected.
Does Dr. Joo know Seon-woo?
No.
Then how did he know
Seon-woo was hospitalized for a while?
When you say a family member
was sick for a while,
most people ask who it was, don't they?
Even if not,
when you said a family member was sick,
he went, "I know."
Director Lee probably told him.
I think he told Dr. Joo about me.
Everything about your family?
Even about Seon-woo's illness?
Were they that close?
Even if they were,
why would he tell Dr. Joo about you?
I don't know.
Hang in there a little longer.
They rarely go after the chiefs.
I regretted becoming a doctor
for the first time in my life.
That detective's questions…
He knew nothing about what we do.
They should at least bring in an expert.
By the way, what do you think will happen
to the resident?
The deceased's family pressed charges.
The president uncovered it,
so he's screwed.
He should feel guilty.
What do you think
Mr. Gu is planning to do next?
What will he try to get?
I think the expulsion order
and the efficiency evaluation
were all just bait.
Let's make a move.
We've treated the Prime Minister before.
We've also operated
on conglomerates' chairmen.
You've been the chair of the National
Ophthalmologists Association twice,
and you are the first female chief
of Neurosurgery.
You've gained recognition
from NCI and MD Anderson,
the two most
respected cancer institutes in the US.
Please…
support me.
I'll push out Mr. Gu.
Go and tell everyone…
to support me.
-Did you eat?
-Yes.
Do you know Dr. Joo Kyung-moon
at my hospital?
I know people in Orthopedics.
I saw their names while working.
No, he isn't…
Forget it.
I told you not to bring the towel out.
Just use the one in your room.
You're such a nag.
Stop leaving wet towels on the sofa.
Go out and get some fresh air
instead of watching TV--
It's too much of a hassle to go out.
Hey, let's go out.
At this hour? Where?
-The flowers have bloomed.
-I'm sure they have.
I have to watch TV. I'm busy.
Hey. Your brother's trapped
in the hospital all day and wants…
The strike that began last year…
Hey.
Switch back to that channel.
What? Which one?
Both the entertainment department
and the radio station…
Does just hearing the word "strike"
get to you?
…in charge of the news and current events…
Hey! Your towel!
CHOI SEO-HYEON
ABS ANNOUNCER
FROM MARCH 2013 TO APRIL 2017
That's why…
ABS NEWS CHOI SEO-HYEON
Regarding the embezzlement allegations
made against the clothing manufacturer,
Black & Missus,
the prosecution conducted
a search and seizure.
The Prosecutors' Office sent investigators
to the head office
as well as to CEO Kim Yo-han's home
and obtained the relevant documents.
Each of the vials
will have different colored labels.
As you can see, we'll use
the colors of the traffic lights
so that they are distinguishable
to anyone.
Yes. So… As you can see,
the drugs wouldn't get mixed up.
So, that is the protocol
Emergency Medical Center came up with.
Okay.
Pediatrics plans to put up these posters
in clearly visible areas…
LOOK BEFORE YOU LEAP
Is this really Sangkook
University Hospital?
Not Sangkook Elementary School?
I mean…
Is this how you've been doing things?
Working like this?
This is a barcode reader
that has an RFID chip embedded within it.
From now on, all drugs,
expensive surgical equipment,
and patients' wristbands
will have these barcodes.
All the data will be managed
in a cloud-based system.
It will not only prevent
medication errors,
but also significantly reduce
the time spent in managing
the inventory
of medicines and medical supplies.
We won't have to argue
about why we're short on supplies
and whose fault it is anymore.
I thought Mr. Gu would only give us grief,
but he actually gave us something good.
QUANTITY OF MEDICINE: MATCH
PRESCRIBED MEDICINE: MATCH
Hwajeong being our owner
does have a benefit.
Don't rely purely on that.
I won't.
I really can't read that guy.
HOSPITAL INTERNAL REGULATIONS
"Roles and power to call meetings."
THE ROLES OF THE HOSPITAL DIRECTOR
AND POWER TO CALL MEETINGS
Director Lee. You wore many hats.
You reviewed the budget and accounts
and handled matters
regarding the organization.
You did things like that, too.
We will only prescribe medications
that are on this list.
This is a subsidiary we recently set up
in order to ensure
an adequate supply of medicines.
"Right to propose
the president's dismissal.
If the president commits
any misdeed or illegal act
in the course of managing the hospital,
the director may propose
the president's dismissal."
This was also within your authority.
It's what the new director
must do.
He operates on
around 5,600 patients a year.
That's incredible.
Is there anything you'd like to say
to the patients?
You know how the mothers
put the rest of the family first
and delay getting treated
even if they are sick.
But you need to get treated early on
to go on the trips
that your daughters send you to.
They keep pushing it off
and then end up going to you.
You're one of the top five in the nation
among joint replacement specialists.
Not at all. There are plenty of doctors
who are better than I am,
so don't come to me.
I never get a chance to rest.
DR. KIM TAE-SANG PERFORMS
5,600 JOINT REPLACEMENT SURGERIES ANNUALLY
CAN WALK UNASSISTED IN 7 DAYS
CONTINUOUS REHABILITATION
Who could do it?
Who would follow in your footsteps
and walk this path…
without being swayed?
Jeong-hu, let me take a look, okay?
Jeong-hu, should we pretend
that we are at a supermarket?
Look at this. I'm going to buy this.
What about you? What do you want to buy?
Why don't you buy it yourself?
Here. Press this.
Whose name is that?
That's right. It's your name, Jeong-hu.
That's so cool.
Do you want to try it again?
It says your name.
What is that sound?
Having this system puts me at ease.
I don't need to worry about
getting things mixed up.
They must have thought about it a lot,
to have come up with this.
Even if they thought of it, it wouldn't
have happened if it weren't for Mr. Gu.
We couldn't afford it.
Right?
We've got a group of fangirls here.
Keep complimenting him.
It'll be his first and last achievement.
Kids are clueless, so they like it.
But what about the parents?
If you walk around with that,
they'll criticize doctors for not being
able to remember what they do.
We need to earn patients' trust
in order to make them respect what we say.
Shit. How dare that kid
treat us like children?
Mr. Gu will keep doing stuff.
Do you think it'll be his last?
Once we have a director,
we'll kick him out right away.
Will the new director be able to do it?
He made a promise. He'd better crush him.
Sure.
Dr. Lee.
I heard you have someone
presumed brain-dead.
But the guardian
doesn't want to donate the organs.
Of course. It's their child.
Some people hit me
when I bring up organ donation.
If they start the evaluation tomorrow,
they should finish
with the brain wave scan in two days.
I'll talk to the guardian then.
Be careful. Don't get beat up.
The new president is a pain, isn't he?
-What do you mean?
-The response is a bit…
The chiefs, too…
Once we have a director,
we'll kick him out right away.
He made a promise.
What about you?
Me?
How I feel isn't important.
It is important.
It is.
ANIMAL SHELTER VOLUNTEER SIGN-UP
VOLUNTEER DAY WITH PRESIDENT GU SEUNG-HYO
Hold the elevator!
Oh, hello.
Thank you.
Have you had breakfast?
I don't usually eat breakfast.
You shouldn't skip breakfast.
Do you want some?
Pardon?
Thank you.
Hello?
Lee No-eul speaking.
What about his fever?
Since last night?
Please schedule an x-ray.
Thank you.
Hello?
Yes, I'm her attending physician.
She's still vomiting?
She just got off NPO.
I'll come by.
I'm sorry.
Have a nice day.
You forgot…
Don't skip breakfast.
It's hot!
SURGICAL REHEARSAL ON THE BRAIN MODEL
CONSTRUCTED WITH 3-D BIOSIMULATOR
I wish we had one of these.
How much does something like this cost?
MEDICAL 3-D SIMULATOR
PRICE ESTIMATED TO BE OVER 100 MILLION WON
Gosh. Everything costs
over 100 million won.
Yes?
You were asked to come to the station.
This is effective for boosting cognitive
function and brain health in general.
If you stress this
and recommend this drug,
the people who received brain surgery
here would get intrigued.
Not just the patients.
If students would take a few
every morning and night…
I received permission from the president…
Where did he run off to
after pulling this crap?
You, too?
These punks shoved this stupid box
in my face,
saying it's made of sharks' livers
or whales' fat or something…
Hey! Chief Oh!
He talked about how it improves vision…
How dare he tell us to sell this stuff?
How dare he?
These punks take us for fools!
After my rounds…
I'll just…
I almost got dragged into it.
Mr. Gu just left.
Mr. Gu!
What do you see these people as, Mr. Gu?
These people who came here in pain,
asking for our help…
What do you see them as?
"Memory enhancement."
"Stress reduction. Deep sleep."
How dare you throw these cheap ads
at us and at the patients…
They aren't cheap.
You don't trust their efficacy?
Are we drug peddlers at a market?
What do you gain by making your colleagues
feel a deep sense of shame like this?
-How could you--
-Enough!
Chief Oh Se-hwa.
When you found out that Hwajeong Group
was acquiring this hospital,
you should've refused firmly then.
Why are you whining now?
Chief Oh. Along with all
the employees here,
you became Hwajeong's employees
through the acquisition.
Then you should work.
What do you think
is the duty of employees?
Isn't it to provide service and get paid?
I can't understand why
you're bringing up your sense of shame.
Are you ashamed of doing sales?
What about it? Why?
Do salespeople seem that lowly
to you people?
They work hard to put food
on the table for their families, too.
Are doctors so noble
that they're different from other people?
Listen up.
If you don't want to get paid,
you don't have to sell the drugs.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
REALIZING THE VALUE OF HUMANITY
HWAJEONG
MULTIVITAMIN
I heard they supplied this.
I didn't borrow any money,
but I feel like a debtor.
It's not like I can just stop using it.
I can't just take what they offered
and not sell their drugs.
What?
Your name got removed
from the list of attending physicians.
Were they canceled
since we're not going to Naksan anyway?
Who knows?
Congratulations regardless.
You will get fewer calls now.
That's right.
KITEUN GROW UP
PROMOTE HEALTHY CHILD GROWTH
Just what…
ANIMAL SHELTER VOLUNTEER SIGN-UP
VOLUNTEER DAY WITH PRESIDENT GU SEUNG-HYO
WE URGE YOU TO PARTICIPATE
IN THE VOLUNTEER WORK
THIS PART IS…
-Where's Jae-hyeok?
-He clocked out.
That lazy first year.
We couldn't clock out in my day.
Forge his handwriting and pass it on.
Why is he asking others to join?
I don't even bathe my own dog.
The president is going himself, too.
You should go, too.
Forget it.
The election is coming up.
So?
Chief,
why don't you register as a candidate?
Are you kidding?
The deputy director clearly wants it.
How could we have only one candidate?
Why do you think no one else stepped up?
The director has to work
closely with the president.
It's better for the deputy director
to take the fall.
Let him do it.
If Jae-hyeok refuses to go, send someone
who's off over the weekend.
They want one per department.
We should send someone.
Otherwise, we'll look bad.
Okay.
EMERGENCY MEDICINE: PARK JAE-HYEOK
PEDIATRICS: LEE NO-EUL
What…
What is Mr. Gu like?
I showed him around the wards.
Personally? Why?
I thought he might feel something
if he saw the kids.
ANIMAL SHELTER VOLUNTEER SIGN-UP
VOLUNTEER DAY WITH PRESIDENT GU SEUNG-HYO
Here we go. Look here.
Let's all make a heart with your fingers.
One, two, three.
Let's take one more.
People on the outside,
please gather closer. Okay.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
I'll tell you the order.
First, clean the cages,
feed them, bathe them,
then play with them.
We'll go in that order.
-Please show them the way.
-Please, come with me.
This group, come with me.
I didn't know you liked animals as well.
You look ten years younger,
dressed like that.
Thank you.
Mr. Gu.
May I get a personal interview?
Sure. How should we do it?
If you'd tell us
your objective as we walk,
we'll edit it to make it look natural.
Let's keep it short
since I'm not here to play.
We'll include clips of you volunteering
as well.
I apologize for the trouble.
Which way should we go?
Let's go that way.
I've always had a soft spot
for abandoned dogs
and abandoned cats.
The fact that people from our hospital…
You're leading by example.
I have no choice.
He has my life in his hands.
What about you?
You said you'd push him out.
I need to stick closely to his side
if I'm going to push him out.
How did we get like this?
Let's go.
It stinks.
It's been a while.
Come here and eat.
Who gave you your name?
You're so cute.
What's this?
Good boy. You're so cute.
Your cap…
-Yes.
We should've fought back about this.
Mr. Gu totally got us.
How long can we rely on our conscience?
For some, it'll probably go up
hundreds of millions of won.
I can't do anything
until the police investigation is over.
Are you saying that is how
he built his reputation until now?
-We still have to look into it.
-And if it's true?
To be honest,
the water will stay stagnant, and only
the one who casts the stone will change.
Things will soon be forgotten anyway.
Is that what you were after?
Is that important?
Because it says a lot about
what kind of person you are.
Did you know then? Why you?
Why did you come?
There was a chance you'd change your plan.
Why didn't you tell me?
Check what?
A government employee is coming here?
He's already here.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee