ALL CHARACTERS, NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
ANY RESEMBLANCE IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL
EPISODE 5
How long do you expect the strike to last?
We'll have to see
how the foundation responds.
We'll end it
as soon as they withdraw the order.
Is there a special reason
for taking such an extreme measure?
As you know, there are factors
specific to the field of medicine.
But if you completely disregard those,
it would cause harm…
It would cause harm
to the people, obviously.
Our strike is a means for us
to ask the public for understanding
of the harsh reality we are facing
and for help.
Thank you.
Where's Dr. Ye?
He must have gone to Pediatrics already.
To see Dr. Lee No-eul.
Our on-call doctor's gone.
Of course he should go there.
I don't think that's why
he went to see her.
Forget it.
What would you know about dating?
Which doctor?
Who's dating?
Why would I bother explaining it to you?
There should be articles about our strike.
Well… there is, but…
Is this really about us?
-What? When did he…
-Hold on.
"The medical staff's assertion
about the expulsion
of the unprofitable departments
is not true.
-It stems from the difference…"
-…in understanding
the reason
behind the relocation to a rural hospital.
I take responsibility for not achieving
a mutual understanding sooner.
This is not due to the hostility
between the medical staff
and a non-medically trained leader,
but due to the lack of transparency
deeply entrenched
in the field of medicine.
Nonetheless, despite the opposition
from the medical staff,
the management has assessed
the operational efficiency
of all the departments for the first time
since the hospital's establishment.
Through the assessment,
we uncovered a medication error
that had resulted in a patient's death.
We consider it a small success
amidst misfortune.
Strike that.
"Amidst heartbreaking misfortune."
"We consider it a small success
amidst heartbreaking misfortune."
Done.
The foundation immediately
notified the victim's family
of the result of the investigation.
Likewise,
we promise you all that we will do our all
to come to an agreement
with the medical staff
to prevent the strike before it starts.
That's all.
"Announcement of strike.
Sangkook University Hospital
will go on a strike to demand
that the expulsion order
on Obstetrics and Gynecology, Pediatrics,
and Emergency Medicine…"
MANAGEMENT'S STANCE ON HOSPITAL STRIKE
HEAD OF MANAGEMENT
WITH NO MEDICAL BACKGROUND
UNCOVERS MEDICAL ERROR
MEDICATION ERROR REVEALED
CANCER CENTER REMAINED SILENT
SANGKOOK HOSPITAL MEDICATION ERROR
The parent complained that the child keeps
waking up in the middle of the night.
No. Keep administering Clamoxin.
We are only changing the dosage
from QID to TID.
Okay.
What--
Sorry.
Yes. Who?
Kim Ye-jin?
KIM YE-JIN, PNEUMONIA
Is there any PRN order for her?
How high did it go?
ATTENDING PHYSICIAN: LEE NO-EUL
Then switch to Denogan.
Okay.
Everything is a mess.
Isn't this what residents
are supposed to do?
What is up with this?
I have no clue.
What's going on? Almost all the patients
are assigned to you.
What about the other fellows?
They must be preparing for the relocation.
What does giving you all the work
have anything to do with it?
We'll have much less manpower there
than we have here.
But why must you…
Did you even eat breakfast?
If I eat now, it'll just make me sick.
Let's go.
Our end must be near,
seeing what Mr. Gu is doing
even with our threat of striking.
Is this all his doing?
Who is he to change the schedules?
That jerk is out of his mind.
It's just my guess.
Don't be so negative about him.
He isn't wrong. It's all true.
Everything is way too concentrated
in Seoul.
It's not just some imbalance.
It'll topple over soon at this rate.
If he were really trying to fix that,
I wouldn't complain.
I've been thinking a lot about it,
whether it's right to stay in Seoul.
It's different from going voluntarily.
But I didn't go. I only thought about it.
Who would go if they're not forced?
No-eul.
Everyone in this hospital can go, but you…
Me? What about me?
You…
You can't. Not today.
You're on call for us today.
I don't care how busy you are.
Brace yourself.
Jin-woo.
Hi. I'm coming.
It got much better.
Hey, No-eul…
Skin tags are for Plastic Surgery.
Why do you keep including them
in the charts?
You can explain those
to the guardians directly.
That's hot.
Why are you breathing down my neck?
I almost got the wrong idea.
I heard about a chief
getting revenge on a fellow
by dumping patients on her.
Are you saying I did that?
Of course not, Chief.
But seriously,
who messed with the schedule?
I don't know, either.
It seems like the Restructure Team
will meddle with things like this too.
Restructure Team?
That means this is Mr. Gu's doing.
Do you think he's teaching us a lesson?
For not leaving when he told us to?
Then why would he dump all the work
on one person?
I've never heard of any fellow
questioning a chief incessantly
for dumping work on his friend.
Whom should we call today
instead of Dr. Lee?
-You?
-Shoot. Wait.
We're short-staffed already.
PEDIATRICS DEPARTMENT SCHEDULE
He was on call last night, so not him.
The foundation immediately
notified the victim's family
of the result of the investigation.
Likewise,
we promise you all that we will do our all
to come to an agreement
with the medical staff
to prevent the strike before it starts.
If we go on strike,
Mr. Gu won't sit still.
He has something huge on us.
Even if we push Mr. Gu out,
the foundation will just send another one.
It's not like
we'll replace the foundation.
Getting rid of him
would not make much difference.
If all the doctors go against him
and get him kicked out,
they will appoint more a docile one
to the position.
What if they send someone worse than him
to avoid a repeat of the predecessor?
Let's push Mr. Gu out first
and get involved in the appointment
of the successor.
It's all up to the chairman.
How could we get involved in that?
Is there anyone here
who hasn't treated politicians,
people in law, and wives of chairmen
of huge corporations at some point?
We have a massive network.
How dare they disrespect us?
He says to submit a plan
before his inauguration.
That's in less than ten days.
What will you do?
You need to take action.
You need to put an end to it
before he starts officially.
I told you,
my brother-in-law says
Gu Seung-hyo is no joke.
The cargo union is super tough,
but he destroyed them.
That young kid did.
Director Lee.
This is the fourth time already.
This is your fourth term as director.
If we had not voted for you,
it would have been impossible.
In other words,
everyone is looking at you.
You need to do something.
Dr. Kim. I'm sorry.
You said to let you know
if interview requests came in.
Sorry? What did you say?
They're called Saegeul21.
Should I tell them you'll do it?
"Saegeul21"?
Yes. I think it's a new media company.
Where have I heard that name before?
Saegeul…
We're done.
SAEGEUL21
Why don't you do it yourself?
You like giving interviews.
Chief.
I'm not making anything up here.
SAEGEUL21 REVEALS HWAJEONG GROUP HEIRS'
EVASION OF MILITARY DUTY
Okay. I understand.
It's that company.
The one that exposed Hwajeong heirs
for not going to the army.
That's why he…
Gosh.
EMERGENCY MEDICINE CHIEF LEE DONG-SU
We measured it, and it was 130 over 80.
Yes.
There was no problem. Okay. Got it.
VARICOSE VEIN SURGERY DEATH
Why did they send their mortality
conference schedule to us?
SAEGEUL21
What's this?
If I had half your looks,
I would've done it myself.
What do your looks keep you from doing?
Must you ask me that question?
My mother will be hurt.
Give an interview later at 7 p.m.
What?
Mr. Gu put up a powerful defense.
We need to fight back.
Make them understand why we must go so far
as to go on strike.
Since you…
know well.
Don't be too… you know…
Try not to drag Hwajeong Group into it.
I heard Saegeul21
is full of anti-authority reporters.
Just give them enough.
"Saegeul21."
Also, I heard you sent up
that varicose vein patient.
The one who died during the surgery?
They're holding a conference soon.
I think you should attend.
Why did they call us
about an anesthesia-related death?
To avoid ending up like the Cancer Center?
They were told to, that's why.
-By who?
-Who else?
You should be fine.
Dr. Yang is the one I'm worried about.
Anyway, you take care of
the mortality conference
and the interview later.
Chief…
Since you…
know well.
SAEGEUL21
In our university,
we hold mortality conferences
only to learn from different cases.
"Our university?"
Yes.
But he wants us to criticize ourselves
in front of other departments.
This is a warning that the management
will interfere with everything.
We didn't get anyone new
since early last year.
We're all stretched too thin,
and we're barely hanging on.
If they truly want to evaluate efficiency,
they should consider that
rather than publicly shame someone
who did his best.
Chief.
How long are you going to keep quiet?
RESULT OF THE VOTE ON THE STRIKE
RESULT: 81.3% AGREE
DEMANDS: GRANT REGULAR STATUS
TO TEMPORARY WORKERS
OPEN TRAUMA AND BURN CENTER,
HIRE MORE PERSONNEL
He opened a can of worms.
It's not his fault.
Everyone is set to go on strike.
That's because someone blabbed about
the reason behind the relocation decision.
They're all selfish,
so they would've been fine
as long as it didn't concern them.
Following two private hospitals
and one public university hospital,
Sangkook University Hospital
is fourth in revenue.
So, we don't dominate the market,
and the profits are barely there.
But it's impressive that they've been
maintaining their Big Five status.
The other hospitals
strive to make it into the Big Five.
It means that it can lose its place
in a second.
Everyone makes money the same way.
There are two very basic methods.
Charge the consumers more
or cut labor costs.
Which of the two should we go with?
A hospital's consumers are patients.
We can't just raise
the price of treatments.
If those departments are gone,
there will be a considerable reduction
in labor costs.
-And the OR utilization rate?
-Even if we designate three ORs
only for emergency operations,
we can raise the utilization rate by 12%.
We have 35 ORs in our hospital,
but setting aside three does that? How?
The chiefs don't like to wait,
so they book a few in advance,
but no one can complain.
Then the surgeries keep getting delayed,
and the utilization rate drops.
If a hospital is particularly good
at certain types of surgeries,
ORs can be specialized
for those specific surgeries.
However, Sangkook's evaluation
was that although it is good overall,
there is nothing that it is the best at
in particular.
Let's say we maximized the utilization
rate. Are there any surgeries
that lead to more losses
if we perform more?
There are surprisingly many.
Since patients don't pay
for the surgeries in full,
the hospital must collect fees
from the health insurance service.
But they don't even pay enough
to cover the cost.
It's our first time evaluating a hospital,
so we only just found out.
It's like when production
creates losses in factories.
So, if you want to convert those losses
into profits…
We can't do anything about how much
the health insurance service pays.
The quickest way
is to provide more non-covered treatments
that require patients to pay 100%.
Those treatments don't really
have a fixed price.
-Okay, then we can set aside three ORs.
-Okay.
Let's start with the areas
that are not covered
such as obesity, smoking cessation,
hair loss, and anti-aging.
Cosmetic procedures are specialties
of midsized
and small hospitals, so we could do harm…
Yes, sir.
Ms. Kang, where do you want to hold
your parents' funeral when they pass away?
Pardon?
Why is he mentioning…
What about you, Mr. Gu?
Funeral parlors in this country
aren't just for funerals.
It's a means to display
the child's social status and filial love.
Even people who don't care
where their own ashes are spread
won't send their parents off
to some hick town hospital.
Why not?
Because they'll look bad.
Let's expand the funeral parlor,
which people will not skimp on cost,
and the Health Examination Center,
which guarantees a high return.
Expand the pay-for-performance program.
Yes, sir.
Schedule a meeting
with Chairman Hong Seong-chan of QL.
With QL's chairman? Okay.
And let's start a subsidiary.
What needs to be done?
I'll look into it.
What else is there
that patients will pay
regardless of what we charge?
There is something.
When my baby got sick recently,
the cost of surgery was insane.
Your child was sick?
Oh, my. No, not my child. My dog.
There's no insurance for pets.
How much was it? They charged me
millions of won.
Mr. Gu. Everyone wants to interview you
about uncovering the medication error.
Do you want to do it?
Since we don't know anything,
we have no choice
but to believe what the doctors say.
They said it was meningitis.
They said there was nothing they could do.
But they…
killed my husband.
How is this different from murder?
If it weren't for the president,
we would have…
The president of Sangkook
University Hospital told you first?
Yes.
Thanks to him,
at least we know the truth now.
At least he apologized
for the doctors covering it up, but…
My husband is dead.
He died because he was given
the wrong medication,
but the doctors didn't notify you,
and the management uncovered it?
I had no idea…
It's been the most trending article
all day.
They already found out about the resident
who gave the wrong medication.
I think he's a first year.
Isn't the timing a bit suspicious?
It diverted attention from the strike.
We just need to do our jobs.
We don't get involved
in hospital management.
What's going on in there?
JIN-WOO
JIN-WOO…
SANGKOOK HOSPITAL STRIKE
MANAGEMENT REVEALED PAST MEDICATION ERROR
MEDICATION ERROR IN SANGKOOK HOSPITAL
MOM
Mom.
Seon-woo.
My gosh. My son.
My gosh.
Why are you dressed so lightly?
Although it is spring, it is still cold.
You should've at least worn a scarf.
Spring is over. It's summer now.
Listen to me.
I can never stop worrying about you.
Aren't you old enough to know better?
Don't forget to take this home later.
I made your favorites including
scallion kimchi and braised lotus root.
I made these all day long.
You come back from Europe
and bring us side dishes?
There's nothing to buy in Europe.
We have all the pretty stuff here.
Jin-woo likes scallion kimchi, not me.
I don't even eat that.
How old are you?
You shouldn't be so picky.
You need to eat better.
I've gained weight from eating so well.
Don't be ridiculous. You're so scrawny.
Am I?
Yes. You're all skin and bone. Goodness.
Hello.
This way, please.
Hold on. Let me get the chairs.
May I take your order?
Two dried corvina sets, please.
All right. It will be right up.
Where did you like the best? France?
Spain.
The food was a bit salty,
but the men were so good-looking.
All the men I ran into
were as handsome as James Bond.
Put sunglasses on them,
and they'd all look like actors.
It must not have been fun
for your husband.
The women were…
-Mom.
-Yes?
He says he'll go back by himself
next year.
He saw young people… Was it Santiago?
He saw them walking the pilgrimage route,
and he wants to do it too.
He said to make sure
to thank Jin-woo for him.
-He did?
-Yes.
For what?
His brother was at Jin-woo's hospital
for colitis before.
I didn't know, but I guess
he asked the doctor
to take extra good care of him.
He said he was treated like a VIP
thanks to him and was super happy.
Having a doctor son paid off.
You got to look good to your in-laws.
Of course.
And I don't have just one, but two.
At my age, bragging about your children
brings more joy
than bragging about wealth.
Everybody calls me a doctor's mom,
you know.
What did your brother say?
About what?
I heard that his hospital
is going on strike.
I only read articles about it.
He wasn't answering his phone.
It's nearly impossible to speak
with him on the phone.
Seon-woo.
It's really cold out today.
Let's hurry home.
Put this on.
How was class today?
Let's just go home.
I don't think things are the same anymore
after Director Lee passed away.
Gosh. Every time I think about it…
Had I known he'd pass away like that,
I would've called him…
and asked him how he was doing
at least one more time.
Mom.
Yes?
It's getting cold.
When I saw his picture at the funeral,
I wondered how such a thing…
could happen to him all of a sudden…
You went to the funeral?
Of course, I did.
With your husband?
No. Why would he go?
He doesn't even know Director Lee.
You should've gone with me.
I just ended up going alone.
What about Jin-woo?
You should've stopped by to see him.
I stopped by the ER,
but he seemed busy.
At least I got to see his face.
Should I ask him to come?
Do you think he can?
Or should we go to him?
Jin-woo, can you come out?
Tell him we'll go to him if he's busy.
Yes, I'm with Mom. Yes.
Okay.
Oh, well.
Plans? At this hour?
Don't give it to me.
Eat up.
Eat this. I deboned this for you.
My gosh. You're all grown up.
Of course, I am.
TA patient. A truck hit his chest
and ran over his hip.
Get a CT and find out if we can get
a cardiothoracic surgeon right away.
Okay.
Can anyone operate
on a TA patient right away?
In 15 minutes? Okay.
-Contact Orthopedics later. Get GS first.
-Okay.
He has a tension pneumothorax.
Prepare for a CTA.
-Run a blood test for transfusion.
-Take these.
Rosette K is available.
Dr. Joo can operate in an hour.
Okay.
Scissors.
Here's the tube.
Right now? Okay.
Dr. Joo just arrived.
He'll start right away.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry I'm late.
You're with Saegeul21, right?
I'm Choi Seo-hyeon. It's nice to meet you.
I'm Ye Jin-woo.
I've never met anyone
with the last name Ye.
You should say, "I've met many."
You always do.
It isn't a common last name.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Excuse me.
Where can I find Dr. Ye Jin-woo?
He's treating an urgent patient right now.
Why aren't you eating this?
What happened to the patient?
-Pardon?
-He was bleeding a lot.
Did you think I would just sit here
and wait around for someone
who was an hour late without even calling?
I'm sorry.
You apologized three times already.
I thought you'd need this.
Excuse me.
Yes?
-Do you mind if I go get some coffee?
-Go ahead.
One iced Americano, please.
I'll ring that up for you.
She's pretty.
Go away.
By the way,
doesn't she seem familiar?
Ask her if you've met before--
Get lost.
That malicious jerk is making life hell
for all of us.
Do I really have to look through
all these old records?
Cardiothoracic Surgery
is freaking out too.
Even we, doctors, don't interfere
in other departments' business.
Who is he to talk?
He knows nothing. Who gives him the right
to judge and evaluate us?
Shit. He's not even a doctor.
Someone has to make a fuss
about things like this.
We, doctors, couldn't do it,
and that is why
the Cancer Center incident occurred.
Was it you?
-What?
-Only one person in our department
voted against striking.
Gosh. You must feel so wronged.
You're the only one
who took Mr. Gu's side,
but he dumped all the work on you.
-I didn't take his side--
-Gosh.
JIN-WOO
"Malicious jerk."
Is he really one?
NO-EUL
Sorry.
You were talking about
the pay-for-performance program.
We are not opposed to it
because we don't like competition
or being ranked.
It's fundamentally different from seeing
who sells more of the same product
manufactured in a factory.
It's about who orders more tests
and performs
more costly surgical procedures.
For example, a doctor can order
a million-won test for a patient
when a more inexpensive one
is enough to diagnose the disease.
It would be worse for surgeries.
So it must vary drastically
based on the doctor's judgment.
This was the first thing the new president
initiated as soon as he started.
I can only say that he made it clear
what his objectives were.
Was the report
about the death at the Cancer Center
fabricated by the management as well?
No.
You can't criticize the management
entirely, then.
Does that happen often?
Medical errors are prevalent
in the hospital, right?
At times,
when I ask something difficult to answer,
an awkward silence persists.
It becomes obvious that the person
is trying to protect him or herself.
I don't think cornering an interviewee
for an answer
necessarily makes a good interview.
But not answering is an answer in itself.
I've decided to ask
the difficult questions myself,
so…
There are different levels
of medical errors.
What levels?
Near miss, adverse, and sentinel errors.
Those are the three levels of errors
categorized by the level of danger.
Based on how fatal the error was?
Yes. It also varies by who made the error.
If it was a doctor,
it was a prescription error.
A nurse, an administration error.
If it was a pharmacist,
we call it a preparation error.
Sometimes it's the patient's fault.
The names are so detailed.
The fact that they've been
categorized like that
means errors occur that often,
whether they be mistakes or accidents.
We're human too.
How bad must it be for you people
to announce it publicly?
You never do, do you?
You'd never announce it
before it somehow gets out, right?
Like anyone would know.
You assholes.
I repeat. Like anyone would know.
What's your problem?
I'm not like that.
You only care about profit.
Why do you care about such a thing?
They're not mutually exclusive.
I'll accomplish both.
Quality and profit.
You'll see once you've been through it.
If you'd like, I'll send you the draft
before it gets published
so that you can review it.
Okay. Thank you.
By the way…
Yes?
Well…
By any chance, have we met before?
I think it's a bit clichéd line…
No. It's not like that.
I really feel like we've met before.
Thank you for your time today.
Are you expecting someone?
Who…
You know. The one I told you about.
-Who?
-Dr. Lee No-eul.
Why is she here?
So, that's her.
Yes.
I'm Lee No-eul from Pediatrics.
Okay.
Mr. Gu.
You haven't been to all
of our wards yet, have you?
I thought it'd be easier for you
to do your job
if you saw things for yourself.
Do you have some time?
Shall I show you around?
Sure.
You're still up?
When is my mommy coming?
It's too dark for her to come right now.
Go to sleep
and let's wait for her tomorrow.
Go to bed.
Or you'll get sick and need to get a shot.
Go on.
Good night.
This is the general ward.
That's the Neonatal Intensive Care Unit.
When is my mommy coming?
She'll be here soon,
so go inside and get some sleep.
What is his condition?
He had pneumonia.
Where's his guardian?
We can't reach her.
The child is sick,
but the parent can't be reached?
His mom had him admitted.
She came with him at first, but…
He doesn't require treatment,
so it doesn't cost us much.
He won't be here forever, either.
He'll be moved soon.
This way.
You need to put this over your shoes
and sterilize your hands here.
KIM TAE-MIN
MOTHER'S NAME: CHOI SEONG-JU
How's the cyanosis?
The baby didn't show cyanosis today,
but the heart isn't beating normally yet.
Keep checking the blood pressure.
The mother had preeclampsia.
The baby suffered hypoxia,
so we almost lost him.
We adopted kangaroo care a few years ago.
We prohibited all contact in the past.
It's the first time in 74 days
that the mother nestles her son
in her arms.
This unit is for premature babies
born weighing 2.5kg or less.
This is the area
that requires the most care.
Well, it is the same everywhere.
Dr. Lee.
Excuse me.
Yes?
What time?
There's a risk of a hernia…
Thank you.
Mr. Gu.
No. Please prepare for ultrasonography.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Should I not have done that?
Is he really a malicious jerk?
Why aren't you asking me about your mommy?
Mommy?
My mommy?
Oh, no.
My goodness.
Why are you out here? Don't cry.
Go to sleep. That way Mommy will come.
She'll be here tomorrow. Come on.
Good boy.
A bug will fly into your mouth.
You're going into where?
It's nothing.
You're still up?
It's all stuff you like.
Eat them all this time.
I read articles about your hospital.
Mom saw the articles, too. I think
she came because she was worried.
She's always worried.
She went to Director Lee's funeral
by herself.
She must've needed to get closure alone.
Closure? Why would she need that?
You know about them.
Too bad it didn't work out between them.
It could've worked out well.
What are you talking about?
Don't make it sound like
they had an affair.
From the day we first met him,
Director Lee was a married man.
And if he wasn't?
It would've been okay then?
He isn't Mom's type.
He has no sense of humor.
We should've let her start over
with someone new sooner.
Whether it be Director Lee
or someone else.
Why did we think
that we were protecting her back then?
I'll pick it up…
Sorry.
For what?
Turn that on.
I told you to eat the food.
She worked hard to make them.
SAEGEUL21
I'm not sleeping.
Sleep in the bedroom.
Your dad's snoring.
Gosh.
Go sleep in your bed.
You'll hurt your back.
Mother.
Was I sick often as a child?
Children get sick all the time.
Are you sick?
No.
You scared me.
Your hospital…
Yes?
It keeps coming out on the news.
I know.
So?
What?
MORTALITY CONFERENCE
ON VARICOSE VEIN SURGERY DEATH
It had been 15 months
since the initial diagnosis.
since the initial diagnosis, and…
Where's Dr. Yang?
He went ahead.
It is unusual.
Nothing is usual
in this hospital these days.
I was referring to the death
during phlebectomy.
Do you enjoy throwing stones at us
along with the others?
A long time ago…
MORTALITY CONFERENCE
ON VARICOSE VEIN SURGERY DEATH
We'll begin with Dr. Ye Jin-woo
from Emergency Medicine.
The patient was admitted
to the ER on April 7.
He had difficulty walking
due to severe pain.
Like he'd understand
what we are talking about.
Does that matter right now?
-He's here to show off his authority.
-"Show off"?
I performed the initial examination.
The sonogram showed varicose veins,
so I transferred him
to Cardiothoracic Surgery.
The patient said his previous doctor
had said he had varicose veins
and had taken naftazone.
Why did you conduct
a basic examination knowing that?
At the time--
At the time, it had been 15 months
since the initial diagnosis.
He had stopped taking the medication
for four months as well.
Thus, I considered the chance
that his condition had worsened.
Any special conditions?
None. That was all for our department.
Dr. Choi Yeong-jin from Anesthesiology.
Yes.
What was the cause of death?
The cause of death was anaphylactic shock.
ANAPHYLACTIC SHOCK:
SHOCK FROM SEVERE ALLERGIC REACTION
Around 3:15 p.m. on April 8,
I administered Robinul and Midazolam
via intramuscular injection,
then I administered a 2.5% solution
of Pentothal for his anesthesia.
At the onset of the anesthesia,
his blood pressure was 110 over 60,
his heart rate was 80 beats per minute,
his breathing rate
was under 20 breaths per minute,
and his body temperature was normal.
About five minutes after the anesthesia,
his blood pressure dropped to 90 over 50,
and about ten minutes later,
it dropped drastically to 50 over 30,
and his heart rate
went up to 140 beats per minute.
His vitals showed that he went into shock.
Did his surgery consent form
indicate any history of anaphylaxis?
No. As Emergency Medicine
mentioned earlier,
there was no history
of receiving surgery or anesthesia,
so I'm sure even the patient did not know.
Any other conditions?
He had minor bronchial spasms,
but according to the order…
from Dr. Yang,
I administered dopamine and ephedrine.
What was the patient's state after that?
The low blood pressure persisted
for 15 minutes, and…
his heart stopped.
Cardiothoracic Surgery…
Dr. Yang Jun-hui.
Please explain why you deduced
that the patient went into shock
and what you did to treat it thereafter.
After his blood pressure dropped
and heart rate increased,
he had bronchial spasms,
but his arterial blood gas
and electrolyte analysis
didn't indicate anything unusual,
so I deduced
that he went into anaphylactic shock.
When did you administer epinephrine?
I administered it immediately
through continuous IV infusion.
Just a minute.
Why was it via IV?
According to the guidelines,
aren't you supposed to
administer it intramuscularly
due to potential volume errors
or risk of cardiovascular complications?
Why didn't you administer it
intramuscularly?
Well…
I saw redness on his skin,
so I removed the drape,
and he had red spots all over his body.
And his blood pressure dropped… I mean,
his blood pressure had already dropped,
so I didn't think it would be
effective via IM.
That was why I went straight
for an IV injection.
Was that purely your decision?
The chart stated Dr. Joo Kyung-moon was
brought in near the end of the operation.
Another reason…
Another reason for ordering the IV
was that there were signs
of circulatory collapse.
The question was not
why you ordered the IV,
but who gave the order.
Oh, I see.
I gave the order.
And what happened to the patient?
His heart stopped,
and he died.
What's the risk of anaphylactic shock
during general anesthesia?
Pardon?
It's 1 in 10,000. It occurs
in 1 in 10,000 anesthesia.
I'm Joo Kyung-moon,
the chief of Cardiothoracic Surgery.
I'm a native of Gimhae.
I was born there, grew up there,
and studied there.
I left that place in 2013
because I lost my patients.
I lost 160 patients.
I lost them all
when the medical center
where I worked was shut down.
I saw
a medical center get shut down.
I read countless comments.
"Neglect of duty.
Waste of taxes.
Unfriendly.
Huge losses."
There were countless comments
that criticized the medical center
and agreed with the closure.
You, my colleagues,
probably remember it best.
Even if it was old and unfriendly,
those welfare recipients, the elderly,
and children
had to get treated
at the public medical center.
The primary reason for kicking them out
onto the street
was financial loss.
The medical center had been losing
three to four billion won a year.
Three to four billion won.
That's a lot of money.
And it came from our taxes.
However,
do you know what the province's
annual budget for that year was?
It was 12 trillion won.
Only 10% of public medical centers remain
because they're getting pushed out
by private hospitals
due to financial losses,
but three to four billion won
was only 0.025% of the budget.
I have…
always wanted to ask this.
Was that money that precious to you?
Did you want
that money that badly?
The real problem
isn't in the center being shut down.
The medical center had many problems.
Yes, I admit it.
But discovering a problem
is a chance to fix it
and make improvements.
But they just shut it down.
It was our final chance to salvage
the rural medical center,
but they got rid of it instead.
Mr. Gu.
We, at Cardiothoracic Surgery,
are always short-staffed.
People are quick to explain why.
They say young doctors nowadays
flock to fields that are easy
and help them make good money.
But not all of the young doctors
are like that.
Then why…
are there fewer than 20
new cardiothoracic surgeons
in Korea every year?
It's because…
hospitals won't invest
in cardiothoracic surgery.
Too many of the surgeries lose money.
It's because
hospitals won't hire them.
There's nowhere for them to work.
But we will…
keep walking into the operating room.
Even if we are criticized
and accused of killing a patient…
because of a 1 in 10,000 risk.
Did you give Clamoxin
to the patient in Bed 11?
It wasn't checked off.
What if I didn't check
and ended up giving him double doses?
I'm sorry.
We're no better than the Cancer Center.
We've just been lucky.
What do you think
Mr. Gu is planning to do next?
What will he try to get?
What do you see these people as, Mr. Gu?
These people who came here in pain,
asking for our help…
What do you see them as?
What do you think
is the duty of employees?
Isn't it to provide service and get paid?
I can't understand why
you're bringing up your sense of shame.
Mr. Gu will keep doing stuff.
Do you think it'll be his last?
We'll kick him out right away.
Will the new director be able to do it?
Please support me.
I'll push out Mr. Gu.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee