ALL CHARACTERS, NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
ANY RESEMBLANCE IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL
EPISODE 1
EMERGENCY RESPONSE
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
They are almost here.
Dr. Ye,
-OR One in Rosette C is ready.
-Who's operating?
Dr. Joo Kyung-moon
and Dr. Oh Se-hwa of Neurosurgery.
They are here.
Time of death…
Deputy Director Kim.
What time is it?
It's 11:48 p.m.
Time of death, 11:47 p.m.
ORGAN DONATION CONSENT FORM
CORNEAL TRANSPLANTATION WAITING LIST
PATIENT NAME: PARK JI-AE
ORGAN AND TISSUE DONOR REGISTRATION
CONDITION: KERATOCONUS
I'm sorry to disturb you at home, but…
the hospital director passed away. Yes.
Just now. In an accident. Yes.
Everyone else is coming in now.
I think you should come too, Dr. Seo.
Yes.
REQUEST FOR AUTHORIZATION
OF ORGAN PROCUREMENT PRIOR TO AUTOPSY
I have to go now
to get consent from the prosecutor
for the organ procurement.
Which one of you is in charge?
-What about his family?
-They consented.
-I'll sign it after the autopsy.
-It won't affect the autopsy. As you know,
-we will just recover his corneas.
-No ophthalmologist is available now.
Dr. Seo is on his way.
I believe…
this is what Director Lee wants.
If we wait too long,
we'll lose the corneas.
REQUEST FOR AUTHORIZATION
OF ORGAN PROCUREMENT PRIOR TO AUTOPSY
Thank you. I'll come back in a moment.
-Bye.
-Okay.
-Hey, hold on.
-What?
-Just a moment.
-What is it?
What?
I'll gladly take it.
Hold up, punk.
Here.
That's what… You really did it.
DONOR
I'd like you to do it for me
when the time comes.
Don't ask me.
Ask the organ transplant team.
When the time comes.
I don't want anyone else to see my belly.
What will you do for me if I do it?
Come on. I'll be dead already.
What can I possibly do for you?
Then why would a dead man care
about someone else seeing his belly?
-Why you…
-Seriously.
Hey. Wait up.
No. I don't want to.
Stop asking me to do it.
-How about for 2,000 won?
-Don't be ridiculous.
You punk.
Father, please give my brother,
who has returned to Heaven,
eternal light and peace.
And to those left behind,
please provide…
comfort and strength.
He fell.
All the bones were crushed,
even his hip bone.
When I moved him,
his back folded like a piece of paper.
Jin-woo.
That's enough.
Sorry.
Did you talk to the director about that?
Did he know that you knew…
when he passed away?
Yes.
Please keep it…
from getting out.
It has already been reported.
Everyone will find out about it soon.
Still, do something.
I'll try.
After what happened to him,
I doubt we'll make a big deal out of it.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
MEDICAL CERTIFICATE OF DEATH
NAME: LEE BO-HUN
OCCUPATION: DOCTOR
PLACE OF DEATH: OTHER
TYPE OF ACCIDENT: TRAFFIC, POISONING,
FALLING, FIRE, DROWNING, OTHER
INTENT OF INJURY: ACCIDENT, HOMICIDE,
SUICIDE, COULD NOT BE DETERMINED
HOMICIDE, SUICIDE
They're almost here. A six-year-old girl
was stabbed about five times.
Who would do that to a child?
What happened? Is she alert?
I don't know, and they say she's alert.
-Control her bleeding and take her to CT.
-Okay.
DIRECT CAUSE OF DEATH: FALL
Did you hear
where that happened to the director?
Yes.
DATE OF DEATH
Why did it happen
at the deputy director's house?
I don't know.
-Don't you find it strange?
-Yes.
What?
What's wrong?
Pediatric CPR needed. She's the stab
victim we called in about earlier.
-This way.
-Okay.
-I thought she was alert.
-She just went into cardiac arrest.
On my count. One, two, three.
-Check her pulse.
-She has none.
Compression.
Let me check the rhythm.
Asystole. Compression.
Prepare for intubation.
Administer epinephrine. Continue CPR.
She was stabbed in the side,
abdomen, arm, and leg.
-Twice in the abdomen.
-Where's her guardian?
Over there.
-This way.
-Here's another patient.
Okay.
Sir, please stay alert.
-We'll move him. Two, three.
-Okay. Two, three.
Sir, do you hear me?
Sir, do you know where you are?
-Where does it hurt the most?
-Administer oxygen and take him to CT.
Okay. Two liters of oxygen please.
-Okay.
-Any other wounds?
No. Just this. The dad has one stab wound.
Defibrillator. Charge to 40 joules.
Clear.
One, two, three!
-Doctor, please!
-How long do we have to wait?
Please help my baby.
-He is in so much pain.
-Please help my baby first.
Sir, I'll stitch you up
after we check your CT scan.
Excuse me.
Which way is the ER?
Go down to the first floor
and exit the building.
You'll see it.
-Thank you.
The police…
came all the way here.
Since it was an accidental death.
That's not the only reason.
They probably came to talk to you
because the ambulance came…
from your house.
Because it happened at my house.
What happened?
What do you think?
You're answering a question
with a question.
By the time…
Director Lee got to my place,
he was already drunk.
He still couldn't quit smoking.
He took out his cigarettes,
so I asked him if he must smoke
in front of someone who already quit
and told him to go smoke on the roof.
Then I heard a thud,
so I went up…
I couldn't even get myself to think
that he fell.
The heart attack…
finally got the director this time.
That's right.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
I'll be right over.
I guess Mr. Gu came back.
I thought I saw him leave earlier.
Of course, he should come back.
He only recently became the president.
The head of the hospital died.
You should be mindful
of how you look to others.
People are talking already.
About what?
Regardless of what really happened,
you're the only person who witnessed
Director Lee's last moment.
THE CHILD PATIENT WITH STAB WOUNDS
WENT INTO CARDIAC ARREST
AT 12:40 A.M. IN THE AMBULANCE
Excuse me.
We're with Hanseong Police Station.
A child was brought in with her dad…
The dad is over there.
The young thing died already.
We should've come here first.
What happened?
Was it an armed robbery?
Was the child stabbed in front of the dad?
He attempted suicide.
It was a murder-suicide.
He did that to his own daughter?
He stabbed his child five times,
but he…
Admit him.
Doctor.
How is he?
He won't end up like his daughter.
Did you visit somewhere else first?
The deputy director's office.
Why?
I see.
Excuse me.
Why didn't he answer my question?
They're just running some tests,
so don't get too excited yet.
Okay.
Jin-woo.
It could be true.
They could've had drinks together.
-What?
-The director and the deputy director…
They both reeked of alcohol.
Since when were they drinking buddies
who pay visits to each other's houses?
Then what?
Why do you think he went over?
I don't know.
I see. You don't know about that.
SHORTAGE OF PEDIATRIC CARE
LED TO TRAGIC DEATH
Then what do you know?
What do you find strange about it?
You're right.
Everyone knows that they didn't get along.
But no one will say anything.
Because that would mean they're suspecting
the deputy director of a person's death.
Am I putting you in a bad spot?
They had an argument.
Someone overheard them arguing.
When?
Who heard them?
Tonight. Around 7 p.m.
It doesn't matter who heard them.
What bullshit are you trying to pull?
Are you trying to ruin my life?
I'll get you for this!
The person tried to avoid the scene
because it sounded like
the deputy director
was ranting at someone.
"Bullshit…"
Given how he was cursing,
the person assumed
that he was ranting at a fellow
or somebody in a lower position,
but he was with Director Lee.
He was talking to the director.
And then, the accident happened
that very night.
At the house of the man
who said he'd get him,
and that man is the only witness.
That doesn't happen in real life.
You don't kill a colleague
because of an argument.
No one does that.
Such a thing only happens in movies.
Right, Jin-woo?
Should I…
tell the police?
What?
Dr. Ye.
The Department of Surgery won't accept
that attempted suicide patient.
They won't admit him
because it was a suicide.
Dr. Joo wouldn't have refused
to admit the patient,
but he's in the organ recovery surgery…
What do you mean?
For Director Lee's cornea donation.
He's watching over that, so he's out.
I'm sorry.
Admit him under my name. I'm coming.
Okay.
April 5, 2018.
DOA.
DOA: BROUGHT IN DEAD
There were two so far tonight.
One died after getting stabbed
by her trusted father.
One was stabbed by the words
of a trusted junior
and died.
Dr. Ye, here are the test results
for the traffic accident patient.
Thank you.
One lived only six brief years…
in this world.
To me, even the life of someone
who lived ten times that
feels so short.
Sir, is it hurting anywhere?
I'm fine.
You can feel where I am touching, right?
You may go home.
Good night.
It must've been an exhausting night
for them both.
April 5, 2018.
The day I said hurtful things to you.
The very last day of your life.
-Hello.
-Hi.
You're here early.
I'm Ye Jin-woo.
We met last night.
You must've been very curious,
seeing how you came straight from work.
I need to fill out the death certificate,
but I don't know anything.
What happened?
You should ask the deputy director.
He knows the most since he witnessed it.
Don't you feel uncomfortable
taking questions
directly to the Chief of Police?
When did you last see Director Lee?
Yesterday afternoon.
Afternoon…
We paid in a lump sum at the time,
so we didn't notice,
but it just got uncovered.
The quality improvement incentive
was deposited into…
Director Lee's personal account.
Was there anything unusual
the last time you saw him?
He funneled 360 million won
paid out to the hospital
into his personal account.
I think we tried to retrieve it quietly
in case it became a problem,
but it seemed like
he had already moved it.
Stop the bullshit.
Where did you hear that nonsense?
No one from your hospital knew?
Who said that?
If you have nothing better to do,
reimburse our fees!
How dare he…
Was there anything strange?
No, there wasn't.
During your last conversation with him,
what did you two talk about?
The usual. About work.
What were you thinking?
Just how long did you think
you could hide it?
Who… Who said that?
What was he like?
He was a good person.
We all respected him.
We haven't found anything suspicious,
and everything is consistent
with the witness' statement.
Was there a witness?
The next-door neighbor.
Did the witness see the director
come out to the roof alone?
Was he really alone?
What if he wasn't?
The witness is certain
that there was only one man.
-I see.
-I heard he had a heart condition.
And he drank and smoked.
I think he fell like this.
-I guess.
-Don't you just need
the cause and time of death
for the death certificate?
Why are you really here?
Because his friend died.
He was like a father to him.
Right?
Give me a break.
Don't get all worked up.
What really happened?
He said Director Lee
had drunk elsewhere first
and showed up at his door already drunk.
You're drunk already.
-I want some soup.
-I asked him why
there was no one else
at home so late at night,
and he asked how many moms and kids
actually stay in this country.
Good.
-I wondered what he meant at first,
-Cheers!
but I figured that he was saying
that his child was studying abroad.
This is so good.
Smoke on the roof, will you?
Go up to the roof.
You know I quit smoking.
Fine. You're such a nag. Gosh.
When will you quit?
He said that was the usual between them.
Then, he heard something.
Director Lee.
Someone fell!
Bo-hun!
A witness…
The next-door neighbor
was on his roof around the same time,
and he saw a man come out
to the roof alone.
Then he heard a thud shortly after.
If doctors start to see patients
as profit centers,
they can no longer be considered doctors.
How can one call oneself a teacher
when all they think about
is how to rip off their students?
A student at least knows
if the teacher's answer is wrong.
But what about the surgeries we perform
and the prescriptions we write?
Regular people
can never fully understand them.
That's why we need to take them seriously.
That's why we must be more alert.
But how could they tell us
to follow these guidelines?
Even if the university's foundation
was acquired by a private company,
this isn't right. This is wrong!
I think the management believes
that the pay-for-performance program
is directly related to productivity.
Productivity?
They will reward doctors
who will administer costly medications
and treatments to patients.
What does that have anything
to do with productivity?
If a patient's life is ever in danger,
everyone should rush over.
If you won't treat a patient
in case something might happen to yours
and your performance goes down,
how do we evaluate that performance?
The first ones who rush over to patients
when something happens are the nurses.
How would you quantify their performance?
What will you do?
This is the first thing the president did
as soon as he got appointed.
He won't back down.
We'll see who backs down.
Are you going to the president's office?
Yes.
The new president looked like
he'd be a real hard ass.
-I only saw him once, but…
-You saw him right.
Why are you trying to face him alone?
You have hundreds of soldiers behind you.
If I get them involved, it will be a war.
It's quicker for the generals to duel.
If the general falls, it's over.
No one is for the program he suggested.
Don't make it a battle
between you and him.
Make it a battle
between the medical staff and him.
A large corporation appointed that guy.
There must be a reason for that.
But the deputy director--
Director Lee, let me join you.
I will go with you
and let him know of our opinion.
This isn't our opinion.
This is our ultimatum.
Yes, of course.
Chief.
Weren't you on call last night?
Why are you back?
One of my patients was admitted.
I was going to go alone,
but since you are here…
Aren't you going
to the department meeting?
This first.
What is it?
What do you think?
A person died.
Only one of them is gone.
There's no need to leave both seats empty.
So? Who received Director Lee's eyes?
The surgery is in progress.
-It should be over by now.
-Who was that punk who called me
from the Organ Transplant Center
last night?
I thought he called me to come
to the wake, but as soon as I came,
he told me to recover the director's
corneas, of all people's.
What was that about?
What were your doctors doing?
He did?
Did you all stop by the funeral hall?
He was just brought back
after his autopsy this morning,
so the funeral will be arranged soon.
-What did the autopsy show?
-We don't have the report yet.
But he did die from a heart attack.
He should have cut down on alcohol.
Did his youngest son get married?
I don't think so.
-Will you go to the funeral?
-Of course. It's tomorrow, right?
I visited the Ministry
of Health and Welfare
before coming in this morning
because they called me in.
They say in rural and remote areas,
many people are having a hard time
because their local hospitals
cannot cater to their medical needs.
There's nowhere for women to give birth,
and there aren't enough pediatricians.
The Ministry called you in
first thing in the morning
to talk about something so meaningful.
Did they play a rerun just in case
we forgot what they say all the time?
They want to create a network
among hospitals in rural and remote areas
and public healthcare providers.
Our hospital has been chosen
to be part of it.
Do they want us to enter
into a partnership with a rural hospital?
They would like us to send some
of our doctors to a rural hospital.
What do you mean? To where?
Naksan Medical Center.
Which departments?
Obstetrics and Gynecology.
Pediatrics.
How many doctors--
Emergency Medical Center.
Those three departments.
All three departments? Until when?
Who will remain here? How many?
How can you get rid of
the essential departments?
We're not getting rid of them.
It's only temporary.
Are we setting up a branch hospital?
Or are we merging with them?
They'll subsidize the labor cost, so…
So, are they telling us
to take the money and leave
the minimum number of doctors here?
Isn't this what national universities
are supposed to do?
They can't pass the duty onto us,
can they?
We're one of the regional hospitals.
They're sending us because we excel.
I didn't know excelling
is something to be punished for.
Do we really have to go?
What about here?
It's not like we don't have
any patients here.
There are plenty of other hospitals.
In rural areas, they shut down ERs
because they lack staff.
You've already agreed
to accommodate their request,
haven't you?
What was I supposed to do?
How could I refuse?
If you have a problem, go and complain
yourselves. See if they would listen.
Why couldn't you?
If it were Director Lee, he would've
put his foot down and refused.
Did you say you went to the Ministry
of Health and Welfare on your way in?
Weren't you listening?
You can't just leave like this!
Then what? What do you want me to do?
We need to let the staff know of this.
Please go make an announcement about it.
Why don't we gather opinions
from each department?
We need a course of action.
Let's set a time and hold a mass meeting.
Whatever they call it,
they are basically expelling us.
How could they do this
without consulting us?
Winner tells the doctors,
the loser tells the nurses.
Chief, that's not…
What's up?
What are you talking about?
This is unacceptable.
I treat over 100 patients a day.
Even when I got hit by drunk patients
and molested, I hung in there.
Working in the ER was the toughest.
My legs felt like they'd break,
and patients screamed
about having to wait.
And this is what we get?
-Is it, doctor?
-Please say something.
I've heard of public universities
sending department chiefs to rural areas,
but how is this…
To be honest,
I feel like they just slapped me across
the face and knocked some sense into me.
We're part of the hospital staff anyway,
so we can just switch departments
or quit.
We can get a job elsewhere, but still--
Taking the patient to the ER.
He came in on Monday
as an outpatient for HCC.
-Okay.
-He also has hepatitis C.
He's in and out of consciousness,
but he responds to pain stimuli.
-Okay. Let me see his file.
-Okay.
This way.
-One, two, three.
BP is 100/60. HR is 100. Saturation is 95.
-Administer two liters of oxygen.
-Okay.
Sir, could you open your eyes?
Tell me if you feel pain.
Okay.
-Let's drain the abdominal fluid first.
-Okay.
-Did it go in?
-Yes.
You can get a job somewhere else, right?
Can he?
What about them?
Hundreds come in every night.
Where will they go?
Another hospital will take them in.
They won't end up on the street, right?
Then what will happen to us?
Should all of us go to another school
to finish our training?
Don't you know why patients prefer
university hospitals?
I get that we should improve access
to care in those areas,
but how could a university hospital
not have an ER?
Listen. They're not getting rid of it.
Why do you think we decided to train here?
Why would anyone apply
for an Emergency Medicine internship here?
Maybe we should go on strike.
It's not a maybe. We definitely should.
We should do much worse!
Are the higher-ups out of their minds?
How could they do this?
You haven't been home for days.
You're right.
One, two.
He can take care of himself.
He doesn't need me.
I know he can.
But that doesn't mean
he can be completely alone.
What if you really have to go
to Gangwon-do and leave Seon-woo alone?
What else?
We'll just live our own lives.
Seon-woo.
Did you go
to the director's funeral today?
I did.
You came to the hospital today?
You should've told me.
Why bother?
Why not?
Forget it.
You punk.
I saw No-eul.
She came down to the funeral hall.
I see. That's why she talked about you.
She did? What about me?
Forget it.
What did she say?
Hey!
Was I mistaken?
Director Lee would never do such a thing.
He's not someone
who would embezzle public funds.
There's no way.
Do you think
if I had not said anything to you,
Director Lee…
would not have…
died like that?
-What did we do?
-Not you. Me.
Why did he have a heart attack that night?
You were not mistaken.
He asked me how I found out
and who told me.
That was his first response
when I asked him about it.
What did you ask him?
I asked him how long he thought
he could hide it.
I asked him if he thought
no one would find out.
He should've asked me
what I was talking about.
He should've scolded me
for barging into his office
and being rude to him.
Just how long did you think
you could hide it?
How… How did you…
Who told you?
Hey. Jin-woo. That's not it.
It wasn't just me who tried to hide…
Jin-woo!
I've trusted you all my life.
And then?
What do you think?
I just yelled at him and left
before he could disappoint me more.
Did you say that to him?
That he disappointed you?
I need to look into it.
He would never do such a thing.
He admitted to it.
What is there to look into?
Don't waste your time on nonsense
and do your job.
I do my job just fine. Don't worry.
Should I close the door?
I'll do it myself!
Are there a lot of people?
Not yet.
Regarding Naksan Medical Center…
How are things there?
What do you mean?
Do they have any financial
or operational issues?
What nonsense is that? How would I know?
Why is that nonsense?
They wouldn't have sent
three of our departments there
without telling you about those things.
Then why did they call in
the acting director
first thing in the morning?
Yesterday morning,
you came straight to work from your home.
You did not stop by anywhere
on the way.
Why did you lie?
What bullshit is that?
How dare you suspect me?
If you keep this up,
I'll have to talk to the police.
What did you say?
If I keep what up?
You'll tell the police
that I came straight to work?
Then what would they say?
Do you think they'd even care?
A person died in your house.
You two had an argument.
But you told the police
that Director Lee went to your house
to have a drink with you that night.
If the police hear this,
would they really not care at all?
-We didn't have an argument.
-There was a witness.
I said we didn't.
It wasn't an argument. I just…
gave him a lesson.
Ye Jin-woo. Listen carefully.
The police?
Go ahead.
But if you do,
you'll have to expose
what the director was up to as well.
I've got nothing to lose.
But I bet what you are trying to do
will shatter the reputation
of Director Lee,
who was a well-respected man.
Just know that.
I'm trying hard to keep quiet
in honor of the deceased.
Ignorance is bliss.
If you care so much about his honor,
how could you destroy the hospital
he worked hard to protect
as soon as he passed away?
You asshole. Look who's talking.
You are not the one to blame me for that.
Your department is always in the red.
Don't you know who made it up for you?
The ER can accept any patient.
It ends there for you,
but other departments suffer so much loss
because of the patients you send up.
You count that…
as losses?
Why must I operate all day long
and hurt my back
to make up for your deficits?
Your department would've been long gone
if it weren't an essential department.
I know that you perform
a lot of surgeries.
And that you're popular.
What do you mean?
Why? Is there a problem with my saying
that the Chief of Orthopedics
performs a lot of surgeries?
You punk.
CHIEF OH
Hey. What's up?
Okay.
What?
Thank you all for coming
amidst your busy schedule.
I'm sure you know why we're here,
so I'll pass on that.
First, we need to discuss
how to resolve the situation nicely.
You can't look for something nice.
We should be raging a war.
This happened
because the school foundation
was sold to a corporation.
What's the point in bringing that up now?
You should've protested back then.
It's the Ministry's order. What can we do?
Public officials don't know
how to do anything
other than sit at their desks
and squeeze doctors dry.
Public officials aren't the problem.
Our management is the problem.
I knew it ever since they got rid of
the foundation chair
and appointed a president.
I heard he used to be the president
of a logistics company.
He may be an experienced businessman,
but he knows nothing
about how things work here.
He doesn't have a say
in the higher-ups' decisions.
He doesn't know this business or have
any connections in relevant offices.
I'm sure the Ministry of Health
and Welfare knew that.
"Hey. Sangkook University Hospital
got a clueless president.
Let's send them to the rural areas.
They're an easy target."
What does Naksan say?
They should be kissing our feet.
That's not what I heard.
Naksan only heard that we were going.
Other than that, they know nothing
about it.
As expected, Dr. Joo knows
a lot about rural hospitals.
That's irrelevant. Chief Lee is correct.
He didn't even go to medical school.
We should've fought back when they said
they'd send some expert CEO.
They appointed a CEO
because they consider us a department
within their corporation.
I ask you all.
Are we running a business here?
This is all because of
the current reimbursement standard.
Why are you bringing that up here?
If they paid more,
OB-GYN and Pediatrics
would've done fine there too.
They wouldn't have gotten rid of them.
Listen. No matter what we do,
the president won't even bat an eye.
Let me ask you this. Do you really think
a for-profit corporation
was so enthusiastic about education
that it had to acquire a university?
That's right. This is…
just the beginning.
Do you want one?
No, thank you.
I got this from abroad.
We all agree that there's a problem
with the standard,
but that problem
lies in the national policy.
What we--
Gosh. So many of you came.
Then who's tending to the patients?
We left enough on the floor.
I see.
Go on.
Aren't you here to discuss the surgery?
What surgery do you mean?
The surgery to heal Korea
from its illness.
I heard that our doctors,
who swore to set aside
race, religion, and social status
and to abide by
their duties toward patients,
had gathered to discuss their willingness
to go to the remote areas
of our country to help patients.
Why don't you begin?
How did they get this?
Could it be
that the late hospital director
gave the documents to someone here?
I'll do whatever it takes,
even if it means
that I have to appeal to the board
or get the media
and other organizations involved,
to let the world know that you see
this hospital only as a profit center.
If the structure affects profitability
negatively, we should change it.
"That's how it is"? That is not an answer.
Where do you get the authority
to send away 15,000 people
and disperse them...
to distant hospitals?
If the ER is gone,
there will be no patients.
You won't have to take in
the homeless patients
and non-paying patients anymore.
What did the hospital do
that made them volunteer
to relocate their doctors?
Do you know how things are
in other departments?
They're all calculating already.
Some say they should band together
and oppose the decision,
and others suggest giving in as it'd be
impossible to overturn the decision.
He wasn't here to listen.
He came to make an announcement.
What if we really end up going?
Let's do the best we can.
The young president is overly ambitious.
You are sure that you and I
are the only ones here
who know about it, right?
Yes. You and I are the only ones who know.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee