♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
♫ The break of dawn is full of longing ♫
♫ Anticipating your feelings ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, practicing love ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my darling ♫
♫ I can go away slowly when I think of you ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
♫ Your chest is warm and soft ♫
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
♫ I can't help smiling when I think of you ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
♫ When I think of you, I'll be energized ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so, so, sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
♫ Your chest is warm and soft ♫
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
♫ I smile when I think of you ♫
♫ I can't help ♫
I'm so stupid.
- Su Mu looked panicked when he found me.
- Tian Tiande!
He hugged me tightly.
He likes me, right?
His carefulness while bandaging for me.
The gentleness while blow drying my hair.
I feel like I can't leave him anymore.
The rain outside is getting heavier.
But... does it matter?
After the rain, it's sunny again.
Actually…
I want to tell you…
I like you.
Good morning.
I'll get up first.
You are up?
The scenery here is really good.
Very comfortable.
Did you sleep well yesterday?
Slept well.
Maybe because I was too tired.
I don't know what time I fell asleep.
Last night…
did you hear anything?
I heard it.
I heard the thunder!
It scared me!
Did you hear… other voices?
No… I didn't hear anything.
Did you hear others?
It was nothing.
Does your leg still hurt?
It doesn't hurt anymore, it's pretty good now.
I can even do a leg press.
Oh, right! Did you see Old Gao?
Old Gao? I really didn't see him when I woke up this morning.
Okay, let's pack up and go back.
Okay.
Give me your hand.
Feeling better?
Hey, Sister!
Why do you only come back now?
I went to Bai Sha Island last night.
There was no boat to come back due to the storm.
Why didn't you tell me before you went to see Old Gao?
Your phone couldn't be reached either.
There is no signal on Bai Sha Island.
You two went together?
Yes.
Ah, let me introduce you. This is Hui Zi.
She is a good friend of Su Mu's and mine.
She is Tian Tiande.
She is the little sister who lives opposite us.
Ah, hello.
I heard of your before.
Oh, really?
Uncle and Aunt, why is she not back yet?
Oh, wait for a few moments more.
Shall we call the police?
What police?
Stay calm.
Hey, isn't she back?
What happened? You're back so late.
I went out to have fun with my friend.
Where did you go?
Bai Sha Island.
Then, why couldn't I call you?
Don't you know there is no signal on Bai Sha Island?
Okay. Hey, right.
Hey, what happened to your leg?
Ah, I accidentally cut it while playing at the beach.
What did you do? Sit.
Well. You make a good match with your dad this time.
You deserve it!
I have asked you to not go around.
Talk to her nicely since she is back.
Does she listen if I speak nicely?
Why not, Mom?
When did I not listen to what you say?
I listen to you the most.
Stop it.
Li Di, send her to the second floor quickly.
And see if there are any problems.
Ah, sure. Brother,
let's go. I will check for you.
You!
Our girl is back.
Why are you still so angry?
You spoil her!
Hey, you are being unreasonable.
When did I spoil her?
Haven't I been spoiling you all the time?
Hey, enough. Go away.
I am pissed off!
Enough. Don't be angry.
Don't, don't.
Are you okay? Is it serious?
Oh, it's okay! It was a small cut.
Sit here.
This doesn't work, I'll bandage it up for you again.
Hey, no need. It has been treated.
The wrapping is so messy.
What doctor is that?
Not a doctor, Su Mu bandaged for me.
Su Mu?
You went there with Su Mu?
Why did you go with him?
Do you remember the uncle who edited the video for us?
He is a partner of Su Mu.
We went there for a vacation
and help him to negotiate a partnership.
What does his partnership have to do with you?
Doesn't he like me?
Who likes you?
The uncle, if not, who else?
Hey, why did you help Su Mu?
Neighbors, it's nothing.
It was a small matter.
Are you-u-u?
Why are you being womanish like my mom?
Womanish?
Don't I care about you?
The calls did not get through.
Okay. Isn't there no signal on Bai Sha Island?
Hey, hand me the yellow one.
Thanks! Why were you looking for me?
I looked for you…
- We just got Clayton's autographed ticket yesterday.
- Yeah..
He will come to our city later for another exhibition match.
- His ticket can only be exchanged with our signed ticket.
- Really?
Wow!
Where is your signed ticket?
My signed ticket? I'll look for it.
Look for me quickly! Hey, if you lost it, I can't forgive you.
- I'm sure I didn't lose it.
- Be careful.
Let me look… I remember…
Let me look for it.
What did Old Gao say?
Oh. Old Gao went through the blueprints and thinks that our idea is quite good.
But he made a few comments. If we can correct it,
there should be no problem with a cooperation.
Like I said, Old Gao will definitely appreciate your talent.
Thanks to you this time. Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to find Old Gao.
I just happened to know that he was on Bai Sha Island. But I didn't know where he was exactly.
How did you find him?
We… walked through almost the entire Bai Sha Island.
Finally, we found him.
Hey, you two stop the discussion.
Discuss it later when we go to the company in the afternoon.
Hurry up, go out and have some fun.
Bo Bo hasn't come to your place for a long time. He is excited.
Bo Bo, come.
Fortunately, you didn't lose my signed ticket.
If not...
How could I lose it?
Then, I'll grab the tickets later.
If I get it, let's go together.
Sure! Hey, our Clayton!
Hey, you have changed your outfit. Where are you going later?
I am asking you.
I'm going to the ice cream shop later.
Why do you still want to go with your injured leg?
Hey, if it wasn't for my mom nagging me, did you think I wanted to go?
Then I'll take you there.
Oh, isn't that Ms. Hui Zi?
Why? Do you know her?
Not really. I met her outside the swimming stadium yesterday.
It feels like they are close to each other.
I heard from Brother Yi that his sister Mia seems to want to match-make them.
Match-make?
How can match-making be better than natural development?
What natural development?
- Ah, nothing. Would you still send me to the ice cream shop?
- Of course.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
Are you feeling better now?
I am okay, much better now.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
What's wrong?
Ah, it's okay. Let's go.
- We are leaving.
- Okay.
Is my mother's cooking delicious?
Aunt's cooking is definitely delicious.
Yeah, I haven't eaten meals cooked by her for a long time.
- Su Mu, is that the ice cream shop you said? The one that is very delicious.
- Yeah.
Great, let's just buy one and try.
- Then, I'll go back to the company first, I am not going with you.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Here you go.
Which is the most delicious today?
All of them are delicious.
- Which is the most delicious?
- This is the most delicious one.
The chocolate one?
Hi.
You…
Oh, Sister Hui Zi.
Hey, aren't you Wang Yanyi's buddy? Li Di?
Yes, you still remember me!
Hey, you are here!
She made it for you a long time ago, wait.
Your ice cream.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What do you want to eat?
Old rules, separate into half.
- Can you give me a spoon?
- Okay.
- What about, you…
- Thank you.
Let's go.
Remember to use this.
Hey, Wang Chengfeng.
Play ball?
Forget it today.
Go. Go and play ball.
Isn't your foot still hurt?
Don't I have the medicine?
Okay, we will be there soon.
Let's go!
Come, take it!
Coming!
Take it!
Come!
Sure!
[Medical Alcohol Cotton Balls]
Come again! Be more precise!
Old rules, separate into half.
Brother Li, let me try again!
Senior, we'll leave first.
- Bye-bye!
Harder!
Okay!
- Let's ask sister De De to eat something.
- De De, let's go! Let's eat something.
Sure.
- Let's go!
Eat this, Brother Li.
- Senior.
- Yeah?
Are you very tired today?
Uh, no. I am fine.
Sister, what major did you study in school?
I studied interior design. I'm one year higher than Li Di,
but we joined the baseball team in the same year,
I used to listen to Brother Li complimenting you.
There are not many girls in the baseball circle.
As one of the few female players in our school,
you must carry forward my spirit.
Fight for three consecutive championships with your Brother Di.
I can't guarantee three consecutive wins. I just like playing baseball.
But I don't play very well.
As long as you are in the team, Wang Chengfeng and the others will play extremely hard.
So, your role is to boost the spirit.
Hey, why did I notice when I was on the team, why couldn't I boost your spirit?
Who said that? I was very spirited!
Hm, sure! Thank you, Junior!
- Come. Come.
- Xiao Yu!
- Hey!
- Where are you?
- We are drinking outside.
- With whom?
Me, Tian Tiande and Ding Xiaoyu.
- Ah? And Ding Xiaoyu?
- Yeah.
Wait for me, I'll be there soon!
Same place, we will wait for you.
Who's that, Brother Di?
Brother Yi, Wang Yanyi. He will be here soon.
Brother Yi…
Ah, enough. That's all for technical issues discussions.
This is the company's basic strategic deployment. Have a look.
If all goes well, they'll set up a division in Japan.
At that time, you and Su Mu will be in charge of it.
Sure, no problem.
Xiaoyu!
You are here, too? What a coincidence!
You are?
You don't remember me?
It's okay if you don't remember me.
Let me tell you.
We played baseball together.
Do you still remember?
Oh, it's you! I am sorry.
How could you say sorry?
It's my problem,
I didn't show up around you often.
I punish myself for a cup.
You are here, too!
- You are here!
- You two, stop quarreling!
Let's drink!
Come, bottom's up!
Don't drink too much.
You too. Drink less.
Brother Yi, why are you looking for me at this late hour?
What else can I have?
Su Mu and Hui Zi are doing academic research in the company.
I have nothing to do. So I sneaked out.
To drink with you.
Brother Yi, you are not in the meeting
and still wandering outside.
What do you do in the company?
Financial director.
That is… the one
who manages money.
I'm going to the washroom.
I'll go with you, Senior.
Brother Yi, you are being too obvious.
Was I?
I'm afraid she doesn't know.
You don't understand, right?
If you like someone, you must tell her.
If you hide it, no one knows you like her.
Aren't you afraid that she will reject you?
Then you must know why.
How could she know if you don't tell her?
Buddy, this time it's different.
Ding Xiaoyu is different from other girls.
She makes me want to settle down.
I think my previous days are wasted.
I really like Ding Xiaoyu this time.
I want to confess to Ding Xiaoyu.
Su Mu.
Okay.
Where's Wang Yanyi?
Xiaoyu, what do you usually like to do?
I usually like to play baseball.
No other activities?
I also like to go out to have fun.
Camping! Do you want to go camping?
I…
- Forget it, I'm too tired.
- Do you want to go?
Why not? Everyone can relax.
- Of course!
- I will go as well.
Sure, let's go camping. 12:00 tomorrow.
I have to answer a call.
Hello.
Ah, I'm answering a call downstairs.
I'll come back right now! I'll come back right now!
I… 12:00 tomorrow, it's a deal!
We have a deal!
Wait for me!
I am back. What happened?
- Where did you go?
- I was downstairs.
My brain hurts when you discuss technical issues.
About the Japanese company, it's better for you to explain.
We have a Japanese client who is keen on our technology.
They want to establish itself in the Japanese market.
The specific situation is like this.
Why are you still here?
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Do you want to go camping tomorrow?
I have no time.
No, I have asked Li Di and Tian Tiande.
And my little girlfriend.
Not going.
Why is he still the same?
I just met your girlfriend, Yang Hui.
Why are you here?
Drop me a message on WeChat.
Young people nowadays,
they become philanderers when they have some money.
Not as reliable as your dad.
Thank you for the compliment, Wifey.
Be sure to keep your eyes open when you find a boyfriend.
A person like this, you cannot choose them.
Not choosing. Not choosing.
Wifey, don't overturn a boat with one shot.
I think Li Di is a very good kid.
Ah, he is a good kid.
Li Di?
Mom and dad, I have to go camping with Li Di tomorrow.
I'll pack first.
You go then.
Hey, don't forget to bring the mosquito repellent.
Hey, Wifey.
Li Di and our girl have been together since high school.
Do you think they are more suitable?
I don't feel so.
Why?
Didn't I say?
Feeling.
Feeling, okay.
Hi, De De.
You must wear long-sleeved shirt and pants tomorrow.
Hey, you have to bring mosquito repellent even if you wear long-sleeved clothes.
- Okay.
- And sunscreen.
Since we are going camping tomorrow, don't put on heavy makeup, there's nowhere to remove it.
The most important thing is that you have to rest early.
You must have a good night's sleep.
Bye-bye.
Where are they?
Coming.
Everybody's here. Let's get into the car.
Wait! There is one more person.
Who?
Isn't he coming?
Everyone's here now. Get in the car.
Come on, let's start our camping trip.
Why are you all so dull? Get high!
We lack music.
This time it works!
The place I found is in the mountain and sheltered from the wind.
It's by the sea, super scenic.
With the tent set up and a barbecue.
Cozy!
How is it, Xiaoyu?
Xiaoyu?
Ah, what?
Nothing, nothing.
- I was asking you if you are thirsty, do you want to drink water?
- No. Thank you.
Tell me if you are thirsty.
- I have water here.
- Thank you.
Have one too, De De.
Thank you.
Ah, let me tell you. He has always been narcissistic.
In the past, he spent half an hour grooming his hair before going to the stadium.
It's so greasy.
As a result, after the game finished, he was like being licked by a donkey.
There were all guys at the stadium. I don't know who he wanted to show off to.
Who said they were all male?
- Weren't you there?
- I've seen you too much.
Do you need to do this? He made Wang Chengfeng stare at his hair non-stop.
He failed to catch the ball and it went straight to him.
Two of them looked at each other affectionately.
That scene…
Really?
No, it's not. Wang Chengfeng was not coming for my hair.
Why did you lower the window?
It's hot.
Okay, let me turn on the air conditioner.
Their teammate was a sore loser.
So I…
Didn't I turn on the air conditioner? Why did you lower the window again?
To see the scenery.
He's a sore loser, so he asked Wang Chengfeng to deliberately break the rules.
Isn't the wind too strong?
No.
Hey, let me take it for you.
- I will take it for you.
- No need.
No worries.
- Let's go.
Wow, it looks good.
Wow!
Of course, how could the place I choose be bad?
Hey, the scenery is really good!
- Sister De De, let's take pictures.
- Sure.
- Me too!
- Take a picture. Take a picture!
Su Mu, come here to take pictures together!
No, you guys go ahead.
It's okay, we'll go ahead.
Three, two, one, say cheese!
It's not working.
What's wrong?
Hey, it's fine. Let Su Mu take a picture for us.
He doesn't know how to take pictures.
The pictures he took for me were blurry.
I can't keep any of them.
It's true.
Who said I don't know how to take pictures?
Smile.
Hold.
- Can you hurry up? My face is numb!
- Almost there.
Is it so complicated to take a photo?
Done.
Let me have a look.
Come, have a look.
Su Mu, what did you do? Su Mu!
Let me see.
I told you he doesn't know how to take pictures.
- But you didn't believe me!
- Hey, where's Li Di?
- Hurry up, take it again.
- Let me hold it.
Let's take a photo with everyone.
Three. Two. One
Say cheese!
Look at this!
The place that I chose, isn't it amazing?
It's good.
Later, we'll set up the tent and the grill.
Looking up at the stars in the sky.
Looking down at the dolphins in the sea.
Eating barbecue and drinking beer. Cozy.
But there is nothing here. Where is the tent?
I've already prepared the tent.
Wait for me.
Xiaoyu, come here and take pictures.
Sure.
- One, two.
- Be careful. Don't fall.
Hey, have you prepared it?
Yes, it was done a long time ago.
That beef, mutton, and mutton leg.
I'm not saying these. I meant my fireworks!
Here, here. Take this.
Here it is.
- How many are they?
- Many, all of these.
- Can this be used?
- I guarantee you.
You may try it yourself if you don't believe it.
Sure, sure.
What should I try? Isn't it gone if I try?
Get the tent over first.
I'll go first. Thank you!
I know it, I know it.
Xiaoyu, let me help you!
I'm done.
You help me then.
All right.
You are so virtuous.
- Move away.
- Okay.
This tent will definitely be warm to sleep in today.
Very warm.
- Done!
- Thank you.
- No worries.
- This is set up so badly.
What is so bad?
This side is higher than this side.
Let me help you.
Don't do it.
It's all set.
I think it looks good.
You just let him do it.
He has obsessive-compulsive disorder.
Are you okay?
I said the bracket inside is broken.
I asked you not to do it. See, you broke it. Let me fix it.
I can fix it.
You do it then.
De De, let's go. Let him fix it.
Let's go look at the pictures.
Come on.
Sit here.
Hurry up.
Check this out.
Ah, what kind of expression is this?
Looks so good.
- Look at this.
- I am looking.
Delete this one for me, this one.
Oh, oh. Okay.
Why don't we choose it later? Let's catch fish.
Let's catch fish.
Xiaoyu, do you know what the biggest difference between you and other girls is?
I know.
I am not buying your tricks.
Quirky.
- Xiaoyu.
- Yeah?
- I have a dream.
- What?
Can you become my heart in the next life?
Why?
Because… I will die if you don't beat.
Then you will get a heart attack.
Quirky.
Let's go barbecue.
- Be careful.
- It's done.
- No problem.
- There seems to be a fish.
It's a fish!
Lend me a hand.
Slowly.
Wow, we have fish to eat.
You are amazing.
Are you going to catch fish?
- Yeah.
- Don't go.
The water is very cold when the tide is high.
Don't you know I like iced water?
Do whatever you want.
Lend me the fishing net.
Here.
Let's go and grill the fish.
Come on!
Let me do it. I am professional in this.
Oh, sure.
Grill me another chicken wing.
Turn it over, it's burned.
Yes.
Are you stupid?
- You are the stupid one.
It's good.
This…
This is honey!
Sure.
Hey, I caught a fish!
Thank you.
This is delicious. Thank you.
It smells so nice.
I caught a fish. Let me grill it.
Oh, that's great! You grill it. Let's play games.
Let's play games first, let's play the games.
Be careful. Watch out for the fire.
Fifteen, twenty-five.
- Fifteen, twenty-five.
- Fifteen, twenty.
Cheers!
This looks pretty spicy.
It's only tasty when it's spicy.
- You taste it.
- I won't eat it.
Come, let's play a game. The King game.
The person who picks the King can choose two persons to punish.
One card each.
Hey, I am the King.
Tell the punishment.
Um, the punishment is to eat these spicy skewers.
They are freshly grilled.
Choose two numbers.
Um, number one and number five.
Who is number one?
Did you inhibit me?
I am inhibiting you, eat it!
- Who is number five?
- Not me.
Who is number five?
You love spicy food anyway.
Let's cheers!
It's really spicy.
- Here.
- Come on, give me the cards.
It dropped.
Hey, I am the King this round.
It's you. What punishment?
Just say it, King. Make the punishment heavier. It's just a game.
A princess hug then.
Number three.
Number five, number five, number five.
Who is number five?
I am number five. Who is number three?
I'm number three. Good brother!
It's just a game. Come on.
One, two, three.
Just hug then.
Hugged.
Come on, pick a card.
I am the King.
What is the punishment?
How about two people...
two people walk around with their shoelaces tied together.
Tied shoelaces… Okay…
Number one and two.
One…
I am number two.
I'm number one.
- All right, sure.
- Come on, Brother.
Didn't we always play this before?
Come on, Brother.
Okay, okay. It's done.
- Come.
- Right… left. Right
Hey, hurry up.
Right, ah… Posture...
- Hurry up, it's almost there.
- Xiaoyu.
- Grab me.
- Grab me tight.
- Walk properly!
- I'm walking properly.
- Hurry up, don't be a slowpoke.
- We have telepathy.
It's almost done.
- Come, come, come. Start a new round.
- Sure.
Pick a card, hurry.
This…
I am…
Let's play an exciting one. Face-to-face push-up.
How to do push-ups face to face?
One on top and the other on the bottom.
- What are the numbers?
- Then...
Number two and four.
Uh, I am number four, you must be number two.
I am not.
Who is number two…
Sister De De, send me later through WeChat.
Sure.
Wow.
I'll go for a walk.
Hey, be careful.
♫ In the season I got to know you ♫
♫ Recalling the sea breeze brushing against our faces ♫
♫ Maybe it was the best part ♫
♫ Inadvertently ♫
♫ Dreams were not fulfilled at that time ♫
♫ You just barged into my sight ♫
♫ Can always protect you ♫
♫ But I miss you so much from the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ This is the most precious memory ♫
♫ Meeting you in the late summer ♫
♫ Fireworks raise their heads gorgeously in the night sky ♫
♫ Those innocence and helplessness are given
to this evening breeze ♫
♫ You must have faith that we can be together with a smile ♫
♫ You and I cannot live with goodbyes ♫