♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
♫ The break of dawn is full of longing ♫
♫ Anticipating your feelings ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, practicing love ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my darling ♫
♫ I can go away slowly when I think of you ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
♫ Your chest is warm and soft ♫
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
♫ I can't help smiling when I think of you ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
♫ When I think of you, I'll be energized ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so, so, sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
♫ Your chest is warm and soft ♫
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
♫ I smile when I think of you ♫
♫ I can't help ♫
I imagined watching the stars together.
The final ending is that Su Mu really went to the planetarium.
But the moment when he appeared in front of me riding a bicycle.
My heart still melted.
Compared to being with him, it's not important anymore.
We were so close on the bus.
I was so afraid that he heard my heartbeat.
Really not in love?
Mom's interrogation made me feel uncomfortable.
Not to the extent she has to follow me, right?
Where is she?
I blame God for ruining my plan.
Who else, if not him?
Taxi!
Sir, follow the car ahead.
Sir, stop.
Quick!
It's been a long time since I came to my alma-mater.
You park the car. I will wander around.
Sure.
Hey. Bye-bye.
What's this situation? Hey!
Wow!
Hey, boss. What kind of fish is this?
This is the king of goldfish from Japan, Ranchu.
How much are these two fish?
- Not expensive, 700 yuan.
- 700 yuan?
No way, it's too expensive! 400 yuan.
Girl, this is daylight robbery.
Last price, 600 yuan.
Well, I don't want it then.
I'm leaving, leaving.
- Is this Ranchu?
- Yes, they are from Japan?
- How much are these fish?
- 700 yuan.
- Okay, I want them.
- Hey, sure.
Aunt, you can't buy these fishes. They are not genuine.
Not really, I think they look good.
How can I lie to you? I would ask you to buy them if I were cheating you.
I'm not letting you buy them, how would I cheat you?
My family does the same business.
Really?
Thank you.
Boss, I am sorry.
I do not want them already.
Thank you.
She doesn't want them.
Sell ​​them to me at a cheaper price.
- 400 yuan.
- No way, no way.
- Well.
- We both take one step back, 500 yuan.
Sound okay?
All right! Take them, take them.
Thank you.
Where did he go?
Hey, little girl.
Didn't you say that these fish weren't genuine and shouldn't be bought?
He gave them to me for free.
I...
Hey, why are you only here now?
Come forward.
Why did you even bring two fish? Are they for me?
Not at all.
Do you remember the uncle who edited the video for us last time? Old Gao.
He helped us a lot.
So, this is a small gift for him.
- Oh... You are smart!
- Of course.
- Ticket.
- Thank you!
Clayton will be coming here very soon!
Great.
Captain, the coach is looking for you.
What's the matter?
I don't know. Do you want to go and take a look?
Then I'll go over and take a look.
- You queue up first, I'll be back soon.
- Okay.
Bye-bye.
Su Mu.
Hi, it's really you! I thought I saw the wrong person.
Why are you here?
I sent my mom here.
Your mom?
My mother has a lecture here.
Why did you come? With two fishes in hand.
Oh. I thought these two fish were very similar to Old Gao's.
I think he would like them. So, I bought them.
Where is your mom?
Over there.
That's your mom?
What's wrong?
Run, hurry up!
- Professor Shu, you are here.
- Oh.
- This way please.
- All right.
Quick!
Why did you drag me and run?
I had some misunderstandings with your mom.
Aunt wanted to buy these fish.
I also wanted to buy these fish for Old Gao.
Then, I cheated her that these fish were not genuine.
It's okay, just explain to her clearly.
No, the first impression is very important.
It's all wrong,no matter how I explain now.
Everything can only fade with time.
Hey, what are you doing in school?
Well, Li Di got two tickets for the baseball star's signing session.
Then, I came with him.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
What's wrong again?
My mom is here.
Why are you hiding from your mom?
She saw us together again yesterday.
If she sees us together again today, she will misunderstand.
Misunderstand?
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
Stop staring, let's go!
♫ is full of longing ♫
♫ Anticipating your feelings ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, practicing love ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my darling ♫
♫ I can go away slowly when I think of you ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
Oh my goodness!
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
Be quiet.
♫ I can't help smiling when I think of you ♫
♫ The scenery outside the window is changing ♫
♫ Change after change ♫
Let's go!
♫ Lovely memories, scene after scene ♫
♫ Wish to praise our love ♫
♫ It's so comfortable to be brushed by cold wind ♫
Su Mu!
♫ In the season, I got to know you ♫
♫ Recalling the sea breeze brushing against our faces ♫
♫ Maybe it was the best part ♫
♫ Inadvertently ♫
♫ Dreams were not fulfilled at that time ♫
♫ You just barged into my sight ♫
♫ Can always protect you ♫
♫ But I miss you so much from the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ This is the most precious memory ♫
♫ Meeting you in the late summer ♫
♫ Fireworks raise their heads gorgeously in the night sky ♫
♫ Those innocence and helplessness are given
to this evening breeze ♫
♫ You must have faith that we can be together with a smile ♫
♫ You and I cannot live with goodbyes ♫
♫ In the season, I got to know you ♫
♫ Recalling the sea breeze brushing against our faces ♫
♫ Maybe it was the best part ♫
♫ Inadvertently ♫
♫ Dreams were not fulfilled at that time ♫
Where have you been? I have been looking for you.
Oh, I have something on, so I'm leaving now.
Why were you with him?
Oh, Su Mu's mother is coming to give a speech today.
He sent his mom here. We met coincidentally.
What did both of you do?
Hiding from my mother.
My mother thinks we are in love.
Oh... You two should be innocent, open, and aboveboard.
Aunt must have misunderstood you.
I don't see them at all.
This is weird.
I'm exhausted.
Aunt.
Why are you here?
I— I—
I'm here to do something, and I am going home now.
- Su Mu, this is...
- Oh.
This is our neighbor.
Aunt, this is my mother.
- Hi.
- Are you going back?
- Oh, yes.
Let's go back together, we can drop you off.
Ah, sure, sure.
Thank you.
Ah, please, please.
Please, please get in.
Clayton! Clayton!
Yes, I finally got it!
- Thank you!
- No problem!
Do you have any plans later?
I can't accompany you anymore. I have something going on with the baseball team.
Okay. Get back to work. I'll find my mother.
Then I'll go first. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Wow!
I don't seem to have seen you before.
Ah! I usually live abroad.
I will only come back when I have matters.
Oh, that's right.
The children have grown up now.
Parents like us can't always follow them.
My son has been very independent since he was a child.
Independent?
It's good to be independent!
You are so handsome.
Have you found a girlfriend yet?
I heard him say that he seems to have found one, right?
Oh, really?
What kind of girlfriend is she?
This kid is embarrassed to say.
I haven't seen her.
But I heard him say that
she should be very pretty.
Pretty?
Okay. And cute.
Being naughty? Does that mean cute?
Ah! She woke up early in the morning to make him breakfast.
Early in the morning?
Isn't that... Oh, that's not.
What is that?
Oh, I said my daughter is not like this.
She sleeps until twelve noon every day.
Hey, wait.
I see.
Woke up early in the morning to make breakfast for others.
That's why I said, our daughter has separated from us.
She did not tell us when she fell in love.
Our daughter has grown up, give her some space.
She is back, stop saying. Gently, gently!
Dad, I'm back.
Our girl is back.
Where did you go?
I went to the baseball star's signing session, didn't I tell you?
Mom, what's wrong with your legs?
Oh, your mother today had been running up and down the whole day.
I was jogging in our neighborhood for just a while.
- My legs are a bit painful now.
- Jogging.
Mom, how long have you not been jogging? Why did you suddenly think of jogging?
None of your business.
Hey, what are you doing with these two goldfish?
I bought them for my friend. I need to send them to him later.
Don't send them. Your dad and I have been having a bit of leg pain for the past two days.
You don't go anywhere.
Make us breakfast.
Go, continue your activities.
Yes.
Put it down.
Hey, De De. Um?
Massage for me, Mom.
- Oh, mother, I...
- Hurry up!
Sure.
Is it comfortable?
Mom. Um?
What's wrong with your skin lately?
It's all dried up!
Ah? There are wrinkles.
Wrinkles? Ah...
What to do then?
Ah. It's okay. I have a new mask that works very well.
- I'll get it for you.
- Okay.
- Hey, Old Tian!
- Um?
Why didn't you tell me about my skin!
You are always perfect in my heart.
What did you say?
Are you downstairs now?
Morning, let's go to the island.
Now? No way, I'm tied with something now.
I'll be going over later.
Okay, I'll wait for you at the harbor.
Okay, see you later.
Mom, this mask is amazing.
After putting it on, get some beauty sleep.
When you wake up, all your skin cells will be instantly awakened.
Relax.
(Don't worry. Go on your way.)
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I was late, delayed by my mom.
It's okay, let's go.
Hey, aren't we going to look for Old Gao?
Why are you going to Bai Sha Island?
Oh, I went to the factory to find him yesterday. He was not there.
He lives on Bai Sha Island.
Then, are we going to take the boat?
Help!
Sir, drive slowly!
Are you all right?
I am okay, much better now.
Where is Old Gao?
I only know that he is on Bai Sha Island.
I don't know the exact location.
It's okay, let's find someone to ask.
Hello, Grandpa. Hello.
Do you know someone named Gao Bo?
Where is he?
Grandpa,
I'm asking if you know someone named Gao Bo?
Do you know where he is?
This grandpa seems to be unable to speak.
Same as you.
I mean, this island is not big.
We should be able to find him.
I'll look for him.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Wow!
♪ The stars in the sky don't speak ♪
♪ The doll on the ground misses mother ♪
Wow!
This place looks so good!
The sea blends with the sky.
Su Mu, come here and look.
This is so beautiful.
Take a picture.
Let me take it for you.
Do you know how?
Here. Take a pretty one, okay.
Are you done?
Yes.
Let me have a look.
Hey! Jogging?
Yes.
I just want to ask you if there is any market nearby.
Yes, but it's quite far away.
It's better for your son to drive you there.
He's not at home, he's out.
Hey, you can jog there.
- You can exercise as well.
- That's okay, no need.
There will be a storm later.
Hey! Hurry up and put your clothes in.
Will there be a storm with it being such good weather?
Do you have rheumatism?
I don't have rheumatism.
Oh, I study this.
Oh, you study rheumatism?
Oh, anyway.
Anyway, hurry up and put away your clothes.
It's going to rain soon.
Oh! Thank you!
Bye-bye!
People with rheumatism are quite accurate.
Let's get the clothes in.
Hey, De De! Let me tell you.
Your mask is really good!
De De! De De!
De De!
Oh my goodness.
I can still sneeze on such a hot day.
Someone is thinking of me.
Hey, my damn charm!
Ah, I mean why is this island so big!
We have been looking for it, but still to no avail.
I feel like I have finished walking the entire island.
It's too early to finish it.
We only finished 1/3 of the distance.
How do you know that?
There are latitude and longitude lines on the map.
The different latitude is 111 kilometers.
Every degree difference,
correspondingly, 111 is multiplied by three--
What are you talking about?
I'm saying that at different latitudes, every one-degree difference
makes the actual distance not equal.
So we need to calculate--
I mean how can we find Old Gao?
I feel that he shouldn't live here.
Because the residents here said they have never seen him before.
Let's go over there and see.
There... How far is it?
About... an hour.
One hour?
I'm so thirsty!
Anyone?
Hi, anyone?
Is there anyone?
Take this.
So comfortable.
What are you doing?
Didn't you say it was comfortable?
Hey, you try it too.
Two yuan per bottle.
Three yuan for two bottles.
Hey, Aunt. Do you know where the old man with gray hair who loves to drink is?
They all love to drink.
They just bought a few bottles of beer from me.
There! There they are!
He seems to be Old Gao.
Let's go and see!
Thank you!
Old Gao!
What's wrong with you!
Hey! I find that every time I'm with you, I feel very unlucky.
Do you inhibit me?
Who asks you to act like a little crab?
Pat someone's shoulder without seeing clearly.
If I didn't take you away, you'd have been beaten.
You save me every time, is it because you like me?
♫ In the season I got to know you ♫
♫ Recalling the sea breeze brushing against our faces ♫
♫ Maybe it was the best part ♫
♫ Inadvertently ♫
♫ Dreams were not fulfilled at that time ♫
♫ You just barged into my sight ♫
♫ Can always protect you ♫
♫ But I miss you so much from the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ This is the most precious memory ♫
♫ Meeting you in the late summer ♫
♫ Fireworks raise their heads gorgeously in the night sky ♫
♫ Those innocence and helplessness are given
to this evening breeze ♫
♫ You must have faith that we can be together with a smile ♫
♫ You and I cannot live with goodbyes ♫