♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
♫ The break of dawn is full of longing ♫
♫ Anticipating your feelings ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, practicing love ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my darling ♫
♫ I can go away slowly when I think of you ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
♫ Your chest is warm and soft ♫
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
♫ I can't help smiling when I think of you ♫
♫ Jasmine, Jasmine, my love ♫
♫ Jasmine, the air in Jasmine Day ♫
♫ When I think of you, I'll be energized ♫
♫ Little torturous pixie ♫
♫ How can you be so, so, sweet? ♫
♫ This long journey, step by step ♫
♫ Put you in the pocket, along the way ♫
♫ Your chest is warm and soft along the way ♫
♫ It's you in the heart ♫
♫ I smile when I think of you ♫
♫ I can't help ♫
We are finally adults who met the parents.
I cracked my brain to make myself another person.
Still, I was recognized by Su Mu's mother at first glance.
Aren't you the girl who bought the goldfish last time?
I am worried that aunt will misunderstand me because of the goldfish.
I'm sure your IQ is not low.
This is good for the next generation.
But it quickly made me relaxed.
My portfolio passed the preliminary test.
Everything is developing in the best direction.
But when I think that I'm going to Beijing for an interview,
I feel very reluctant.
It's all because of Su Mu's flirting.
I don't want to be separated from him even for a day.
Please come again.
Mu Mu, bring me another bowl.
Why are you here? Didn't your sister say you are quite busy these two days?
Yes, quite busy. I have a business trip tonight.
On a business trip? Where are you going?
Beijing. Beijing?
Ah, then how many days will you be there?
- Three days.
- Three days…
What time is your flight?
6:00 in the evening.
6:00? Hurry up then.
So, I have to rush over to accompany you.
Anything for me to help with?
- No, no…
- I'll help.
De De,
I finally understood the principle you said previously.
You said, it's okay to like someone.
But most importantly, that person has to like you.
Mu Mu, I didn't mean to intentionally display affection in front of you.
I really didn't notice you were beside me.
You're so cruel.
It was just a joke.
It's my first time falling in love, I don't know either.
Falling in love is not learned.
I have deleted all the official accounts.
I now feel that falling in love is based on feelings.
It's all based on feelings?
Then do you think I should go to Beijing for the interview?
This… um…
I really don't know.
[I reached Beijing.]
[Going for a meeting now.]
[Okay, good boy.]
Little crab, are you bored here today?
I think you are quite bored.
Why don't we go and play today?
Busy man, are you done busying to have time for me?
I just arrived at the hotel.
Do you miss me?
I waited for you the whole day.
I miss you so much.
Miss me but you won't let me go to Beijing with you.
I'm afraid I'll be too busy to keep you company. You'll be bored alone.
Won't you be back that night? Then it won't be boring.
What do you want to do at night?
What do you want to do?
W-W-What are you doing?
I'm taking a shower. Getting ready to sleep.
Oh, yes. You are so tired today.
It's time to take a bath and sleep.
Go ahead.
Hey, wait.
I haven't told you about something.
What's wrong?
Oh, I suddenly forgot what I have to say.
You go to bed now. I'm resting too.
Go to bed then. Goodnight.
Uh. Goodnight.
He definitely did it on purpose.
Did I get fooled because of this?
Isn't this…
just showing your upper body?
That's nothing.
The abs look quite good, isn't that so?
Mom.
I am going to Beijing today.
Isn't your interview tomorrow?
Su Mu is in Beijing.
This is a little inappropriate.
You both come and go at home, being together every day, that's fine.
After all, we adults are at home.
If it's outside, a boy and a girl alone in a room,
how can that be?
Mom, what are you thinking? We have lived together a long time ago.
Nothing happened.
When did you both live together?
When I didn't come home at night, I lived with him.
How can you both do this?
Su Mu is not that kind of person.
What about you?
I-I?
I am not that kind of person.
How could I be that kind of person?
Mom, would you let me go?
If Mom doesn't allow you to go, wouldn't you still go?
Mom just wanted to tell you.
You must know what you should do, and what
you shouldn't do.
I know. We are all grown-ups.
My point is… We adults know what to do and what not to do.
Okay, Mom, read your book. I'm going to pack up.
Youngsters nowadays.
Why did you call me so early? Aren't we meeting at night?
This blueprint, I've spent all night modifying it. After this, you will be responsible.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going back to Xing Yue City.
Why are you going back in such a hurry?
Ah, I got it. Hey, I can't do it alone.
Why are you like this every time?
Master, to the airport.
- Hello.
- Hello, little Su Su, where are you?
I… am in Beijing.
How about you?
I'm in… the ice cream shop.
Uh, I was so busy in the shop today.
How about you?
Um, I was quite busy today.
I won't be seeing you today, right?
You can see me if you want to.
Video doesn't count.
You can't touch it.
Then… what time are you going back to the hotel today?
Um… 6:00.
6:00? Just right!
What just right?
I mean it's great. You can go back to the hotel at 6:00.
I'll send you a video when you're back at the hotel.
Don't run around, I know where you are.
Okay.
See you at 6:00.
Master, please speed up a little.
Wow.
Ah, hello.
May I know what is the room number of Su Mu, Mr Su?
Sorry, our hotel has rules.
We cannot simply disclose our guests' room information.
I am his girlfriend.
We can't disclose too. How about you give him a call?
But I want to surprise him.
Wouldn't there be no surprises then?
- So, please…
- I am so sorry.
So sorry.
Okay.
Hello.
Hello. Where are you?
Hey, forget it, I'll tell you.
- I'm in Beijing for the interview.
- What?
- You are in Beijing?
- Yes.
I am at your… hotel.
Are you surprised?
I wanted to surprise you but I don't know your room number.
Where are you?
I'm at the ice cream shop.
W-Where?
Modern Sweet, Sweet Ice Cream ice cream shop.
Really?
Are you surprised?
I am… so shocked.
Stand where you are and don't move.
Okay.
Tian Tiande.
Why are you suddenly here?
I'm here to take the exam and to find him.
You two are really weird.
He spent the night modifying the blueprint so that he could go back to find you.
You still came to him? So dramatic.
Really?
It's fake.
It must be real.
This is where Su Mu usually stays.
All his things are inside.
Although he is not here, but it's full of his scent,
I believe you shouldn't feel lonely.
Enough.
I'll leave first if there is nothing else. Call me if there's anything.
It's better not to call.
Thank you.
Wow.
Doggie.
Sit here.
Work.
- Hello.
Have you made it in?
How is it? Are you still used to it?
- Not used to it.
- Not used to it?
Then… do you want me to change a room or a hotel for you?
I'm not used to being at your place without you.
I didn't expect you would come to me so suddenly.
I wanted to surprise you.
We just missed each other like that.
- What time do you wake up tomorrow?
- 8:00
All right, I'll wake you up.
- Don't need to. I'll set the alarm clock myself. I can get up.
- No!
- I'm calling you.
- Okay.
After finishing your exam, I'll pick you up at the airport.
Okay.
Sleep well.
I miss you.
Okay…
I miss you as well.
My doggie.
The above are all my works. Thank you.
Actually, this is not another recruitment.
You are not here to replace the spot.
But we noticed your work from many other works,
and decided to add a spot for you.
That means when you sent me the notice,
you already decided to accept me?
Yes, we appreciate your work a lot.
It can be seen that you have a solid foundation in painting.
We also want to see you in person and listen to your design concept.
I can see that you are a person full of imagination
to be able to design such a piece of dreamy work.
Our school needs such bold students.
Prepare a visa and report to school in a week's time.
A-A week?
Any problems?
Examiners, can I report to school later?
The enrollment time cannot be changed.
Can I take online lessons?
Are you kidding me?
Yes, just kidding.
You are so humorous.
♫ Summer night fireworks outline your silhouette ♫
Why are you here?
Didn't I say, I'll pick you up after you finish the exam?
I thought you'd pick me up at Xing Yue Airport.
How can that be?
♫ Love sneaks into the stars ♫
How's your exam?
♫ drawing close to your back ♫
♫ What is the color of scenery passing by? ♫
Not bad.
So smart.
♫ Let's go together in all seasons ♫
♫ Not separated in your embrace ♫
♫ Let's go together Traveling around the world,
or lazing in bed ♫
♫ Won't feel alone doing anything ♫
♫ Life is interesting because of you ♫
Sorry, sorry. The plane was late, so I was delayed.
The plane was delayed. I'm late.
If I knew you'd ask me out, I would definitely not have gone to Beijing.
It turned out to be late. I'm really sorry.
What's wrong with you?
I made an appointment with you all of a sudden today. I don't blame you.
No matter when you ask me out, I should be by your side immediately.
Why are you so nervous today?
Am I?
Actually… I don't know either.
Who I used to be… you knew it.
But after I met you,
I don't think I will.
Whatever I say and do becomes clumsy,
like a fool.
You are like a fool.
But I don't like the quirky ones.
I like fools.
What did you say?
You like fools?
Don't you like me?
She likes me! You like me?
Are you silly?
I'm really stupid.
So… kissing feels like this.
What did I do in the past?
I don't care about the past.
If you dare to mess around in the future, you are dead.
Why? You don't want me to control you?
No… The company asked me to take charge of the Japanese division.
I'm not afraid that you will control me. I'm afraid that you won't control me.
I am not going to Japan.
We haven't met in the past, but aren't we together now?
What's wrong? Are you afraid that we'll still be separated after being together?
Master, go to the restaurant.
Okay.
Do you think I look ugly today?
No, you look like a piglet.
How cute.
Aren't you worried about me getting fat?
Not worried.
You are already quite fat.
It's okay, I'll get fat with you.
You eat too.
Your son's career is so cool.
He has liked this since young.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
Do you know how they met?
I don't know.
It's because my daughter broke your son's aircraft.
Little Su actually threw my daughter into the mud pit.
Oh my goodness.
The two of them are really quarrelsome lovers.
I see them both getting more and more compatible anyway.
They are a match made in heaven.
Oh yes! Did you know they built a small house on Xing Yue Mountain?
Really? I didn't know.
Ah, I heard from Mia about it.
Mu Mu, based on De De's painting, built that small house.
Right, where's that painting?
This is the painting.
Have a look.
Ah, yes, yes, yes. I remember she painted this.
Right?
Unexpectedly, they even built a house!
The two of them built a house and lived together.
- No wonder…
- Mama Tian.
That…
I am very enlightened.
It's normal for children to be together.
I just hope they know how to protect themselves.
Ah, don't worry about this.
Our Mu Mu has been a responsible child since young.
I believe he will never do anything indiscriminately.
So is our De De.
She has been an opinionated child since young.
No matter what happens, she will be responsible.
Don't worry about this.
So, the two of them are really, really alike.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come and have coffee.
Okay, okay.
Come, come.
- We're home.
- Right.
Thank you for your hard work.
Mom. Aunt.
Why are you two back together?
Oh, Su Mu went to Beijing to pick me up.
You're not sensible at all.
Su Mu is already so busy and you let him go to Beijing to pick you up.
This is necessary. This is what boys should do.
How could you let your little girlfriend come back alone from such a far place?
Yes, the two of them are passionately in love.
Even if they get married in the future, you have to still be like this.
All right, Mom.
Tian Tiande has been tired the whole day.
Her stomach is a little uncomfortable.
So she came back first to rest.
Is your stomach better?
Yes… I walked and it digested, I feel better now.
You should eat less in the future.
Mom, let's go.
Ah, we'll leave first.
Oh! Okay, goodbye, goodbye.
Let's talk another day.
It's okay, we are going back.
We're leaving.
- Aunt, goodbye.
- Goodbye, Aunt.
- Bye-bye.
- Let's have tea together.
Okay, okay.
Stop watching. Let's go home.
You're back.
How was the exam?
Wow! Marvelous.
Sure enough, you didn't disappoint the expectations of a father.
Have a seat.
Look at your small mouth. Are you unhappy?
I've told you.
She is worried about being separated from Su Mu.
A long-distance relationship.
Girl, the most important thing in this life is to realize your dream.
Reflect one's own value.
But you can't live without love.
If you have sincere love for each other,
what is a long-distance relationship then?
Your dad is right.
Love and dreams are both important.
You can choose, and you can cope with both.
It's up to you.
Don't worry, Mom and Dad. I will think about it.
Girl, don't be anxious about this.
Isn't it said here?
There are still a few days before reporting.
You can consider.
Your dad and I, again,
you've made your own decisions since young.
No matter what your decision is, you always have our support.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Mom.
It's so good having you both.
Are we really going to be apart?
How am I going to spend these few years?
Why are you here?
Can't I come?
Of course, you can. You are welcome any time.
Just nice, have a drink with me.
Why are you here suddenly?
Is there anything important to announce?
Of course.
I announce, I, Li Di,
formally joined Di Cheng Company today.
Wow, isn't that your dad's company?
What is there to announce?
Hey, this is different from what you think.
I didn't join as a young master.
I passed the interview and got in decently.
So, I, now have become Di Cheng Company's
outstanding intern.
Come, cheers for being an outstanding intern.
Hey. Don't look down on interns.
I believe that through my unremitting effort for a year,
I can be an excellent full-time employee.
I believe in you.
I see that you have been in a good mood recently.
If you have never experienced hurdles, how would you see the rainbow?
What hurdles have you gone through?
I…
From a boy… became a man.
You are in love, too?
What?
I just… figured out some things.
What's that?
Just some things I didn't understand before.
Being so full of myself…
Just those things.
You now understand more and more.
I'm getting more and more confused.
What can you be confused about?
You and Su Mu quarreled?
No. Didn't I pass the interview?
I'm going to study in the UK for a few years.
Isn't this a good thing?
It's a good thing.
But this means…
I have to be separated from Su Mu for a few years.
So you are worried about a long-distance relationship with Su Mu.
Yes.
It's okay.
People who will be together... will always be together.
People who won't be together,
even if they're together, will also be separated.
You really grew up, to be able to say such things.
Did I?
Yeah, just like us.
We will always be together.
Hey, do you still remember?
When we were in high school, once you came,
we became the best brothers.
We go to play and did various fun things together.
Went through everything.
In the end, we were still together in university.
This shows that we will always be together.
Right.
Thank you.
Enough. Don't you know your tolerance?
Stop drinking.
Yes.
You said it before, when it comes to drinking,
I'm just your little brother.
In my heart, you're always my good little brother.
So no matter what you go through, if you need my help,
just look for me.
I will definitely be the same as before.
I will stand up for you for everything.
Always standing up for you.
Yes, promise!
- Promise!
♫ In the season I got to know you ♫
♫ Recalling the sea breeze brushing against our faces ♫
♫ Maybe it was the best part ♫
♫ Inadvertently ♫
♫ Dreams were not fulfilled at that time ♫
♫ You just barged into my sight ♫
♫ Can always protect you ♫
♫ But I miss you so much from the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ This is the most precious memory ♫
♫ Meeting you in the late summer ♫
♫ Fireworks raise their heads gorgeously in the night sky ♫
♫ Those innocence and helplessness are given
to this evening breeze ♫
♫ You must have faith that we can be together with a smile ♫
♫ You and I cannot live with goodbyes ♫