=The Queen of Attack=
=Episode 6=
These are all His Highness' belongings.
Please take a look.
Which items should be sealed?
And which
should be buried?
This was what His Highness wore
during his final days.
When I look at it,
it's as if I see His Highness
from those days.
A bellyband?
This is absurd!
Something's wrong.
All these years, apart from me,
His Highness had no other women.
But this...
But...
But this doesn't belong to me.
Stop.
(Linlang)
Linlang?
I see.
His Highness only ever
listened to my songs.
Why suddenly
would he want some young musician?
Wait.
The physician said
His Highness' condition had improved.
But then it suddenly
took a turn for the worse.
Now that I think about it,
could he have done something
beyond his capacity
that harmed his health?
Bring her in.
Yes.
Do you think it looks nice?
Ziyi?
You're back.
Exquisite.
Attending palace events
is truly tiresome.
I really don't want to
attend these social obligations.
Young lady!
Don't drink that water!
I know.
But these things can't be avoided.
Though it's not publicly announced,
you're Prince Rui's only nephew
and the sole male heir of his line.
Now that he is gone,
these people will surely flock
to befriend you.
There's no escaping this.
Why do you keep staring at me?
You spring-drinking country girl
have truly changed.
You're mastering these
tedious protocols too well.
You're speaking like that again.
Alright.
It's all my fault.
You only became like this because of me.
You've suffered hardship.
I feel for you.
I know you care about me.
Lady Hong is still here.
Lady Hong.
I'll take my leave.
Lady Hong,
why leave as soon as he arrives?
Seems I've become unwelcome.
My lady,
the Princess sent for you.
Oh, yes.
I should go pay respects to my aunt.
No.
Her Highness requested Lady Hong.
What?
At this hour,
what could it be about?
Go with her to keep watch.
No need.
Lady Hong.
Go.
Lady Hong,
why do you dislike me so?
Your Highness, you jest.
Look up.
Look at me.
Okay.
Let's go.
No need to accompany me.
I don't want to,
but you're Ziyi's friend.
I must ensure your safety.
Your relationship with her
is truly remarkable.
Have you ever felt
instant affection for someone?
Let's go.
Prince Xian, why are you here?
I'm here to pay respects to my aunt.
Your Highness.
This doesn't concern you.
Leave us now.
Lady Hong is Ziyi's guest.
So she's my guest too.
I'm afraid she doesn't know
the rules here.
It's better for me to stay here.
We need to discuss
women's private matters.
It concerns Lady Hong's reputation.
Would you like to listen?
These two normally patrol
the front courtyard, right?
Why are they serving
the County Princess today?
With these two present,
why aren't you concerned
about Lady Hong's reputation?
Did you select the toughest enforcers
among the guards
to bully a defenseless woman?
How dare you!
Aunt,
I've been bold since childhood.
You know me well.
Either humor me,
or
I'll take my people and leave.
Forget it.
Listen if you must.
Bring the item.
Yes.
Speak.
Is this yours?
These harem tricks again?
Speak!
What are you doing?
Confess honestly.
Confess what?
These are just your despicable
underhanded schemes.
Let's go!
(Linlang)
It's mine.
With me protecting you,
no need to admit it.
This was a love token
between Prince Rui and me.
Shameless!
Drag her out and beat her to death.
Who dares?
You're right.
I do despise you.
After finally securing
Prince Rui's favor,
I thought I'd rise to greatness.
Who'd know he'd die?
Now the title falls to you.
I really
hate you utterly!
Your Highness.
What are you waiting for?
Take her away.
You shameless woman!
What act are you putting on now?
Your Highness,
don't let them torture me.
You'll regret this.
What do you mean?
I...
I'm carrying
Prince Rui's child.
♪Fate begins and ends, I sip the past♪
♪Love and hatred flow endlessly♪
♪When spring comes, I see the truth♪
♪We've changed through the years♪
♪Cold lamps reflect pear blossom dew♪
♪Worlds change as streams run west♪
♪Rains veil hills, gathering sorrows♪
♪In deep courtyards, hands drift apart♪