=The Queen of Attack=
=Episode 5=
(Prince Rui's Mansion)
My lady,
hasn't everything
already been taken care of?
I thought
back then, Lin Hong'er
didn't tell Xiao Xian
about her family background.
So I could fabricate a new identity.
But now,
I've gained an extraneous relative,
one
that doesn't belong to the Xu family.
The County Princess might not
investigate this matter.
Write to my father.
Tell him to arrange for someone
to drive the Luo family
out of the capital.
My lady,
doesn't this strike you as odd?
How is Lady Hong's enemy Mr. Sun?
Master,
Sun Qi is dead.
But complications arose.
Uncle Luo from Hong Linlang's blacklist
suddenly appeared
and disrupted our plan.
All plans have variables.
This might not be a bad thing.
But what if Uncle Luo's interference
ruins everything?
I guided him there.
I found Xu Ziyi inherently suspicious.
If things go too smoothly,
it'll feel unnatural.
Moreover, our acquaintance
is behind this.
You mean Princess Ruihua?
Return and keep Linlang company.
Master.
I truly understand you less.
I want to help you.
Remember.
Helping Linlang is helping me.
I...
Linlang, are you here?
Is that Ziyi?
Yes.
Open the door.
Are you alright?
I've been worried sick.
I'm fine.
Last night,
I heard you brought people there,
so I slipped away as planned.
After getting back,
there was no news from you.
How was everything?
It was okay.
I took people
to teach that fool a lesson.
He won't dare show his face again.
That's wonderful news!
Not only do you play music,
but you also paint?
I paint all my enemies.
What could've happened to you
to have so many enemies?
Look.
This is the man you captured last night.
His surname is Sun,
the Registrar of Lai County.
What's your actual grievance with him?
He's greedy and lustful.
My family's enemy bribed him with money,
so he distorted the truth
to help her escape charges.
There's a woman in your paintings?
She's no ordinary woman.
No one knows her true identity.
She's meticulous
and exceptionally skilled in deception.
Linlang,
such people are the hardest
to deal with.
Indeed.
Defeating her
will be extremely difficult.
That's why
you must help me.
Don't worry, Linlang.
I'll assist you for sure.
It's good you're here.
I'm relieved to see you safe.
I'll take my leave now.
(Xu Ziyi,)
(it's your turn.)
That night,
I thought Sun
would implicate Xu Ziyi too.
Unexpectedly, she foiled it.
However,
like in chess,
blocking one path
might open new possibilities elsewhere.
(Xu Ziyi...)
Master already investigated.
That Sun Qi
truly acted lawlessly.
He took bribes and caused injustices.
He has many enemies.
This time, it might genuinely be
a coincidence.
Behind every coincidence
lies cause and effect.
Keeping Hong Linlang in the mansion
will eventually bring disaster.
Why did the County Princess
insist on keeping her?
Just to show gratitude
for playing for Prince Rui?
His Highness has a weakness for beauty.
Lady Hong is exceptionally beautiful.
His Highness remained ill,
but kept demanding her performances.
Rumors spread through the mansion.
Their private affairs
were vividly described among the maids.
The County Princess
must have heard the gossip.
Fearing she might spread tales,
she's protecting the reputation.
The bribed maid revealed
Concubine Dou gained His Highness' favor
through a magical flower.
Flower...
Its fragrance stirs desire.
(I'll use this
to pit them against each other.)
Concubine Dou.
What a rare visitor!
I've heard
this mansion's
rarest treasures reside
in your courtyard.
I came to broaden my horizons.
Apologies for intruding.
These
are mere tokens of Prince Rui's favor.
He showered my chambers with luxuries.
The whole mansion knows this.
Curious visitors come frequently.
Though a bit annoying,
after all, we're all family here.
It's okay.
So this is
the flower?
It actually exists.
What?
Lady Hong mentioned
His Highness planned to
gift her these flowers
after recovering from illness.
He wanted her chamber
overflowing with their fragrance.
Pity...
His Highness never regained his health.
So I am really curious
what's so special
about these flowers
that captivated him so much?
Concubine Dou,
why are your hands trembling?
Are you unwell?
Yes...
I'm suddenly feeling unwell.
His Highness gave Lady Hong flowers...
I need rest.
Please, leave.
I'll take my leave then.
Well...
Could they...
Need to ask?
What are these flowers for?
They were meant for us...
I always wondered
why that random musician appeared
and His Highness
insisted on sleeping to her music.
Night after night.
This was never about music.
She was seducing His Highness.
No.
I need proof.
Proof?
♪Fate begins and ends, I sip the past♪
♪Love and hatred flow endlessly♪
♪When spring comes, I see the truth♪
♪We've changed through the years♪
♪Cold lamps reflect pear blossom dew♪
♪Worlds change as streams run west♪
♪Rains veil hills, gathering sorrows♪
♪In deep courtyards, hands drift apart♪