Lin Hao,
did you break up with me
because of Lan Xiaochuan?
No.
Then why?
Lin Hao,
even if it's fake,
you still rushed in.
Groom, please put the ring on the bride's finger.
Remember the temperature of her fingertips at this moment.
In the days to come,
protect her light in her eyes
as you protect this ring.
And the bride, please put the ring on the groom's finger.
Hold his hand through thick and thin,
as if holding the whole world's stability.
Groom, you may now kiss the bride.
Auntie,
shall we call it a day?
Okay.
Let's call it a day.
His speech
is too pretentious.
I don't like it.
I need to make some changes.
Auntie,
why don't you rehearse with my dad?
After all, you two are getting married, right?
That won't do.
Your dad and I both believe in old customs.
We can't meet before the wedding.
During this time,
you two will be our little pigeons.
We two...
It's the ninth.
What ninth?
What number nine?
Number nine.
I'll go get my dad's suit.
What are you doing?
Isn't it the ninth today?
Today?
I'll go now.
Yunfei, see him off.
No need.
Okay, no need.
Your dad's wedding clothes are pretty nice.
It must be expensive.
It's okay. Let's go.
Hello.
Are you done?
What do you want to do?
Xiaochuan,
I'm in the wedding dress store.
Look at this mess.
Your dad is getting married,
but he didn't tell me.
Did you get the money
for this month?
Get out of here.
I got the money,
but it's not enough.
Xiaochuan,
is that all the money for a life?
Shame on you!
How do you feel?
My arm has been numb
since I got pregnant.
If you weren't here for acupuncture,
no one could cure it.
Thank you, Dr. Xiaochuan.
You're welcome.
It's unnecessary.
Liu, Liu.
She is my niece.
You can treat her as your niece.
You don't have to be polite.
Next time,
I'll give you a discount.
What are you doing?
You killed my baby.
You must pay for it.
Liu.
This...
What's going on?
You shameless quack!
You fraud!
My wife had a miscarriage
after getting acupuncture from you!
You owe me my son's life!
You murderer!
What...
Impossible!
You...
Liu, Liu,
just say it.
-I'll beat you to death today. -Just say it.
Don't beat me, don't beat me.
My son is dead, don't beat me.
Don't beat me.
You are really rich.
Okay, okay, okay.
Lan Jianhua,
you are really rich.
Don't move.
Xiaochuan,
Why didn't you tell me
your dad got married?
Lan Jianhua is such a shameless jerk.
He killed my sister,
and now he's gonna kill someone else?
Well,
he has money
to hold a wedding,
but he doesn't have money
to help his own brother-in-law?
My dad earned the money
for his wedding himself.
What does it have to do with you?
He has supported you for years.
I also send you money every now and then.
Isn't that enough?
Come on,
why are you so rude?
Honestly, the money you gave
wasn't for me.
It was all for the victim.
Over the years,
if I hadn't mediated,
you would have been ruined.
You're my niece.
If I don't care about you,
who will?
Don't use this to shut me up.
After that incident,
you've been stopping me from seeing that pregnant woman.
If you're so sure, let me ask her face to face.
You want to see them?
You still want to see them?
She miscarried.
She hates you so much.
She's tormented by her in-laws every day.
You know how hard her life is now?
She just wants some compensation.
What do you want
to meet her for?
To make things worse?
There are proper procedures for compensation.
Why would she need you to pass messages?
Did you
give her the money?
Who knows, right?
She said
if she gets 500,000 within three days,
and then it's done.
500,000?
Why don't you just rob someone?
Why are you yelling at me?
By the way,
that guy,
Yun Fei,
I thought he looked familiar.
Then I remembered.
He's
your ex-boyfriend, isn't he?
I remember
he works for the government.
Now he's your family.
It's really hard to avoid disasters.
I feel sorry for his future.
You see,
if he gets involved in something shady,
how will he
hold his head up in the future?
To make a long story short,
I can gather the 500,000.
I have only one request:
I want to meet his family.
Listen,
I can give you the money,
or I can give it to them.
I can find them myself if I want to.
If I find them,
will you still get your share?
If you take me to them,
I'll make sure you get your cut.
Otherwise,
you'll be begging on the streets.
You've really crossed the line!
You're nothing!
Hello.
You didn't contact Lan Xiaochuan, did you?
I'm doing this for your own good.
If you contact her,
then our cover will be blown.
How can we ask her for money in the future?
Where are you?
Still at the plaza internet cafe.
Okay, okay.
Good, good.
There's food, drink, and fun there.
Pretty good.
Fine.
You play there.
I'll come to you in a few days.
Okay, okay.
Idiot.
The plaza internet cafe.
Turns out to be hiding there.
Beauty.
You've been with us all the way.
What do you mean?
Liu.
Don't you remember me?
It's you!
What do you want from me?
I'm here to talk about money.
Didn't you want money?
I'll give you money.
Give me all the reports
of your wife from the maternity hospital.
Ultrasound reports,
progesterone test results,
and any documents proving the fetus's condition.
You still have the nerve to ask?
Haven't I already told you?
I burned all those documents
when I performed a ritual
for my child.
You have no evidence.
How can you prove the miscarriage was my fault?
I used the outer gate acupoint on her wrist.
How could it
cause a miscarriage?
You killed my child and you're still lying.
I don't understand your traditional Chinese medicine.
When you stuck that needle in,
did some bad energy go into her belly
and killed my son?
You're just making things up.
You're the one making things up!
Do you know the law?
You killed my son
with your acupuncture.
You killed him!
I'm telling you,
you could be in prison for over a decade.
I'm giving you a chance to repent,
and it's only because of my kindness
that I'm settling this privately.
I'm saving you here.
Do you understand?
Put it down.