Shengxiutang.
What does it mean?
Why is the clinic named like this?
Be benevolent and virtuous.
Improve yourself and help others.
It also requires us doctors
to be compassionate
and improve our moral cultivation.
This is the name given by my great-grandfather.
Great-grandfather?
That must be many years ago.
Yes.
My writing isn't good.
Jin,
if you don't mind,
I'll give it to you.
I don't mind at all, uncle.
Thank you, uncle.
I should be thanking you for your help.
It's nothing,
just a small thing, Lin Hao.
How about we add some acupuncture cases
to this storyboard?
What do you think?
Sounds good.
Many people are interested in acupoints,
but it's too obscure.
Animation can make it more accessible.
Sure.
Here, take this.
I made chicken soup for everyone.
To boost your health.
Thank you, Auntie Du.
Did you burn your hand?
Fei,
thank you for coming.
You finally got a break,
and you've been busy all day.
When are you going back?
When I become a part of this family,
I'll go back.
It won't be long.
The wedding date is set.
We'll be a family soon.
Lin,
what's wrong with you?
I'm fine, uncle.
I just stayed up late these days
and caught a bit of a cold.
You've been working hard.
Must be from working on the promotional video.
Xiaochuan,
get some ginseng for Lin.
Here, have this.
Here you go.
Thank you, Xiaochuan.
No problem.
Jin,
what's wrong with you?
I'm fine, uncle.
I'm having a bit of a headache.
Must be the water and food.
Let me check on you.
Could you grab a bowl for me?
Lin Hao,
could you look after Caien?
Right,
just here.
That's the spot.
Feels great.
Right here.
So good.
Xiao Chuan,
see, Xiao Fei
is a real gentleman.
Come on, another sip.
Brother,
I'll do it myself.
It's okay.
So good.
Brother,
wipe your mouth, it's all over your lips.
What are you doing?
Brother,
come here.
I have something to tell you.
Dad,
I'll talk to my brother for a moment.
Okay.
What exactly do you want to do?
What did I do?
My dad is here.
You're touching me.
Taking care of my sister
How can it be inappropriate?
Who is your sister?
Then what are you to me?
I'm warning you for the last time.
The last time.
If you do this again, I'll beat you up.
Your bangs are showing.
You're over the line.
I think it's just right.
You don't let go after breaking up.
It's not a gentleman's behavior.
Yunfei
Lin Hao said
you were still bothering her after breaking up.
You are a
bad guy.
He just misses her.
I think he is a good guy.
There's nothing wrong.
See?
They are a team.
Don't be self-righteous.
What are you doing here?
You drank?
I missed you.
Where are you going?
To bed.
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
But let's get this straight,
I didn't touch you at all.
Is there a problem?
My hand...
I... I need to tell you something.
I...
still like you.
What are you doing?
Don't get drunk and make a mess.
Lin Hao,
did you break up with me
because of Lan Xiaochuan?