I should have known when we broke up three years ago.
Some people are like chronic allergies.
You think you're cured,
but as soon as you meet again,
all the symptoms come back.
Next, let's welcome...
For example, now,
when I look at him through the camera,
my heart beats like a drum in my ear.
Leading figure in youth aviation technology,
core engineer,
Yun Fei.
What's worse,
we're about to become
brother and sister.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're so meddlesome.
If you don't want to wear it, take it off.
No one's forcing you.
If you don't want to talk nicely, don't follow me.
No one's forcing you either.
We broke up three years ago.
You still have the habit of
not losing out in words.
You've changed a lot.
You're so considerate.
Thank you for your shirt.
But back then,
when I was unconscious from a fever,
you didn't even answer the phone.
I've never seen you so thoughtful.
What are you doing?
Applying medicine.
No, I can do it myself.
You don't think I still like you, do you?
When we broke up,
you said the kiss at the bar
was because you were drunk.
Was it?
Yes.
I was just going along with you
at that time.
Here, give you back.
That's fine.
We're even now.
That way,
I didn't take advantage of you for nothing, right?
What do you mean?
Don't get me wrong. The shirt money.
Xiaochuan,
are you in there?
are you okay?
I'm fine.
Who is that?
My boyfriend.
Do you want to meet him?
Let's go.
Sorry about that.
I shouldn't have said you're my boyfriend.
I thought you weren't joking.
Anyway, thank you for inviting me to the exhibition.
If your video needs editing next time,
just let me know.
But there's one thing I need to make clear to you.
Don't fall for me.
You're great,
but we're not right for each other.
Doctor Lan,
do you have to be so blunt?
Yes, I do.
Anyway, just to be clear,
you'll promote my family's clinic next time.
I'll send you the contract once it's drafted.
It'll be three percent more than a regular deal.
Looking forward to a smooth cooperation.
Me too.
Hello, Auntie.
[Xiao Fei,]
[I need to remind you of something.]
[Your mom has been]
[acting all secretive lately,]
[making calls in private,]
[and always heading to the TCM clinic.]
TCM clinic?
Morning, Chuan.
Morning.
What's the issue?
Doctor Lan, my heart
keeps fluttering.
Now that I see you,
I feel at ease.
Chinese medicine emphasizes inspection, auscultation, inquiry, and palpation.
Your inspection is impressive.
Roses given,
hands
leave fragrance behind.
You're healthy, just a bit of internal heat.
Heartburn.
It's quite fiery.
Wrist bone acupoint connects to the heart meridian,
which clears heat.
No, it's sore.
That's normal, just hold on.
Flowers again?
Trash.
Old man,
you've waxed your head.
Even mosquitoes have to do splits to land.
What do you know?
I'm doing this for the clinic's image.
Everyone,
put your work aside.
It's lunch break.
Order something tasty.
I'll treat you today.
What?
Why do we have a lunch break so often recently?
Last month, we just talked about increasing the number of patients.
This is called work-life balance.
Here.
Take it.
Go order your favorite sweet and sour pork.
Remember,
add more sweet and sour sauce.
Go.
Xiao Fei,
I'm afraid that if your mom got sick,
she wouldn't tell you.
Pay attention to her when you come back.
Are you stalking me?
What do you mean?
Who's stalking you?
This is my clinic.
You're sneaking around like a burglar.
It can't be a coincidence, can it?
Your clinic?
Blood pressure is 120 over 80.
Very healthy.
That's good.
[Why is my heart]
[beating so fast?]
[Annoying.]
I didn't eat this morning.
Maybe you have low blood sugar.
I'll give you some sugar.
Who is this old rascal?
My dad.