I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No letters written criminal or offense in writings.
Somewhere in a corner,
A white-skinned young man
He courageously defends his country,
The country had failed and fallen into the well.
Episode 14
The Heavens are in danger
and the Heavens are fighting
and the Earth is fighting
and the demons are fighting
Congratulations to all of you for passing the Immortal Riding Path
Next,
is the Immortal Riding Platform Battle
Whoever can grab the immortal ball
and stand on the Immortal Riding Platform
until the end
will be the winner
Okay, let's go
The winner can get two treasures
The first one is the elixir of peace
This is the elixir that the Gold Elixir Master made
It can help to break the impurities and get into the peace
The second one is the best weapon
It's the best weapon
Don't talk about the new disciples
Even the core disciples of Su Yan Li
I'm afraid there's only one
When the immortal ball falls
the battle will begin
I want to play with you
I'm not good enough for you
Go
Kill them
How good are you
Little flower pillow
You're a despicable person
Who do you want to trick
The way of battle
is not easy
I only talk about winning
no matter what
Welcome the snake cloth
Wuyi, good job
This is a big deal
It's a five-level battle
It's a big deal
It seems that Wuyi has at least
a battle of the five-level battle
As long as you help me defeat Wuyi
I'll give you two treasures
after you get the elixir
Really
I, Zhao Dan Long, will keep my word
I won't let you go
I don't believe you
Everyone, as long as you help me defeat Wuyi
and get the first one
I'm willing to give you the elixir
as a revenge
You mean the elixir
Take the money
and work hard
You're a despicable person
Four times the elixir
plus five times the elixir
Wuyi only has four times the elixir
Even if he has six times the elixir
I'm afraid he's going to lose
Zhao Dan Long has a lot of tricks
I think he's a lot of tricks
I think Wuyi has a lot of potential
Wuyi, are you going down the stage by yourself?
Or should we invite you down?
One more to one
Let's go together
If you have the courage, don't blame us
for being cruel
Zhao Shi's thirteen arrows
One sword is a cloud
Be careful
The feeling of being angry
is not good
Go down the stage and be naughty
Otherwise, your five organs and six organs
will be crushed
If you have the guts
I'll take you down
and see you die
Despicable
Please
You really want to fight us
I just can't stand you bullying people
Then let's see if your king is capable
to solve it
You don't have to help me
You saved me on the mountain
My king doesn't like to owe people
Cloudy sky
Three arrows fall into the clouds
Wuyi
Finally
What a bad weapon
It's in my ear
Wuyi
You pushed the weapon out of the body
You can't live
These arrows want to kill me
I'm far worse
Five-fold
He used the arrow to break the five organs and six organs
to the fifth part of the body
The extreme pain of the ten thousand arrows
can be tolerated
Wuyi is not a problem
Let go, stop him
You are a bunch of useless
You have been fighting me for so many years
You didn't even hurt Wuyi
You are useless
Money is not enough
You are a bunch of useless
Wuyi is empty
Open fire
Congratulations to Wuyi
You are the first
Great
I have my own style
In a year
Wuyi has finally entered the immortal gate
Don't worry
I will make them pay
Where are you going
at this time
I prepared a small gift for him
You are idle
Wuyi got the first place
This is a big news
Congratulations
You are good
I have a special weapon
I use a stick
From today
You are my disciple
Come with me
I will watch an old man from Yanli
Can I send him home first
Yes
Where is Sun Daojiu
It seems that Situ Jin took him back to the immortal garden
Old man
Sun Daojiu
You still drink after you die
You are really a good person
Old man
I am back
Situ Jin
You are really despicable
That little bastard should be very angry now
The more angry the better
I'm afraid that little bastard has no blood
What do you mean
I hope he makes me angry
It's better to kill a few more people
Then we can make a fair and just move on
Defend the rules of the clan
Situ Jin
I want you to blood and blood
Eternal place trial
Immediately open
Today, the tea will not fly
Brother Luo, you lure them over
We kill them all together
Nie Kai
Five swords are combined
God sword broken
Meng Yi, Zi Yan
One does not stay
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
I'm he
I'm not