I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
equals
total
Singney
I want to go to the bathroom, but I can't do it.
I was about to leave.
Shouldn't have gone.
The wind blew it away our carAh uhm
the wind blew it away our carAh uhm
at your耶
д
I do well.
A place where we can't see or feel you
Engraved in the memories of nights
For our love and effort
This hotel looks like nothing to me
Episode 16
Get off! Get off!
Immortal Sun,
have a taste of this Monkey-Ear Wine.
You bold monkey!
Somebody!
I'll break his nose!
Get off!
You bad monkey!
I won't let you get away with this!
This Monkey-Ear Wine
is a gift from my dear guest, Dongyue.
His Majesty was careless
and offended the Immortal's favor.
Somebody!
What is the purpose of
removing these treasures
from the Heavenly Palace?
Since you don't like Monkey-Ear Wine,
this gift
may be a gift from you.
It seems that you don't like it either.
Since you don't like it,
I'll pick some other things
and send them to the Heavenly Mountain.
Your Majesty, you're too kind.
I heard that Monkey-Ear Wine is the national wine of Dongsheng.
Your Majesty, the guest you mentioned
is from Dongsheng.
You're right.
The King of Dongsheng
is going to marry Princess Wu You.
These are the best wine
that the King personally picked.
It's a pity that you don't drink it.
Qi.
Are you suspicious?
The people of Dongsheng are evil
and cruel.
Dongyue has always been righteous.
How could he have an affair with such evil monsters?
You...
Don't worry about him.
The people of Dongsheng
are so cruel to us.
If we don't marry Princess Wu You...
If we don't marry Princess Wu You,
the Nine-Sixth Army will not retreat.
I see.
It's late.
I'll leave now.
Why are you leaving?
Immortal.
I'm lonely in the mountain.
How about
I send some beauties to serve you?
He is not a passer-by.
Chen, keep an eye on him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Dongsheng and Dongyue are in a relationship.
There must be something wrong with it.
The monster is...
Go.
Little Fox.
Do you want to play with me?
What do you want to play?
I'll accompany you.
You said it.
Yes.
Uncle Zhong, is the wine awake?
It's awake.
But those who framed the Crown Prince
are so mean.
You can't get rid of them.
You followed Ayu.
You can understand if you can't swallow it.
But Ayu's case is very serious.
You'd better be careful.
How is everyone?
Thanks to you,
everyone is much better.
But that child is still not well.
I'll think of a way
to go to a few more pharmacies and ask.
Thank you for taking us in.
But don't worry, Miss.
When you see the Immortals,
the child will be saved.
Immortals?
Miss.
It's almost time.
Uncle Zhong,
I'll leave the medical thing to you.
Yes, Miss.
My little princess.
Didn't you say you'd put a lantern in the lily box
and pray for your dead brother?
Why did you come to this shabby temple again?
Could it be that
there's a dog man
who can make you happy?
I just need to be polite to the princess.
You have the nerve to talk.
Mi Chang.
I heard that there are a group of refugees in the southeast.
There's no one in the capital.
Did they hide you in there?
My good sister.
Tell me.
I promise I won't report to the Empress Dowager.
You make me...
disgusting.
Let go of the sword.
I'll show you.
Uncle Zhong.
No.
You're so bold.
It's okay to go out of the palace.
You're still taking the name of the southeast behind the Empress Dowager.
Tonight I'll teach you a good lesson for the Empress Dowager.
Who?
The... the late emperor.
You're the late emperor of the Heavenly Sword Sect.
You're a traitor.
You deserve to die.
I think you're handsome.
You're in good shape.
But the face under the mask is more handsome.
I'll play with you first.
Then I'll eat you.
You're so annoying.
He wants to play with you.
Impossible.
You're a broken-hearted man.
How dare you play with me in front of my own people?
You deserve to die.
Be careful.
You're a rotten monkey.
You deserve to die.
The mother of Yin and Yang.
The first name of the world.
Long Yue.
Don't kill me.
I'd rather be your maid.
I'll serve you forever.
You don't deserve to beg for mercy.
Who are you?
It's you.
I can't beat them with you.
It's not a rare brush.
Heaven has changed.
Oh my god.
I didn't expect such a monster in the capital.
Thanks to that Sun.
Otherwise, the snake demon would kill people in the dark.
Mi Chang.
You can't die.
Who?
We can't fight them.
Today, we'll never fight them.
Luo, you lure them here.
We'll kill them all together.
Nie Kai, the great dragon.
Five swords are in one.
The sword of god breaks the heaven.
Meng Yi, Lian.
We can't leave them.
I'm sorry.