I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ta train
immigrant
The moon is full of stars, the mountains are lonely
The road ahead is not smooth, the wind is laughing, I'm too crazy
The mountain is still hanging, the heart is beating
Only one side is as old as the old
I dare to break through the night
The wind, the snow, the moon, the people are all running away
I'm afraid you'll be here in winter
The evening sunset in the middle of the fall
Love is hard to bear, hatred is hard to bear
In the night, the soul is lost
The broken heart is broken
You look back, the world is so beautiful
A Yi, you're a dog
A Qi
This is the ancient murderer of the second level of the soul, the Tien Tien Fae
Fu Yue, you're dead this time
Tien Tien Fae, kill him
The god of death
Everyone, run
Don't cry, kid
When I finish solving these problems
I'll take you to eat sweet and spicy
Golden
You!
It's you!
Today is different from the past.
If you dare to disobey His Majesty again,
I'll catch you.
What the hell, Your Majesty?
I only know one His Majesty.
Shut up!
Let's get out of here.
Leave it to us soldiers.
What about the people?
I used to be
a soldier too.
How can you stop me
from guarding the family?
Dad, you're too old.
I always
practice a skill of running knives.
I have no place to use it.
Today, I'll try it with these beasts.
You talk more than me, old woman.
You...
Are you all so fierce?
Let's go.
We can't be weak as soldiers.
Kill them.
Yes.
Come on.
I'm still alive.
Don't you dare to make trouble in my Eastern Courtyard.
The beasts with three spirit energy and two-time mirror
are no match for him.
He's too strong.
Ayu, are you okay?
It's okay.
Let's get rid of this devil first.
You think you're a kid?
I'll kill you.
Three second and four minutes.
ormal strength results in
Hong yet.
ginseng
OH ohh
oh
MLJ
мор
I'm not afraid
You bastard
The firepower of this fire is not weaker than the three-dimensional fire
You can instantly turn into ashes
Quickly look at the star
I'll teach you a trick
Hang this fire
Nian Fan brain
You live and die
One hit
The big skill is strong
The moon is full of bones
The star is stuck in the body
A little boy who doesn't know how to count
What to fight with this fairy
It's killing me
That's right
Father is a three-dimensional mirror
Just rely on his physical ten times
How can it be a father's opponent
This time he is forced to die
Nian Fan brain
You live and die
One hit
The big skill is strong
The moon is full of bones
The star is stuck in the body
Nian Fan brain
You live and die
So strong power
The star is full of bones
The fire is full of bones
The star is stuck in the body
One hit
father
It's not good
That kid blocked the eye
Messy formation
Father, are you okay?
As long as you get the power of the sky
Everything can break the system
Only with the right path
You are also dead
You all love me
Haotian
I don't know how to read
You even killed your own child
You are so cruel
Poison
Isn't it called revenge?
I'll show you
You pay the price
Heaven's book
Don't want to get
Let the world feel the power of the spring
Catch me
Little Su
You think you can force the level to the west
Can you beat me?
Dream
The god of death
Thanks for watching!