I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Huge
B Era
Oh!
He's gone!
Hey!
Hohohoho!
quite obvious
So I have a power over enough
I hope nothing will go wrong
Kiki
Such an absent Courts
only one thing can stop you
What's that?
I cannot go
No
Snot
I'm sorry.
Young Master.
Brother,
you don't have to worry about making me happy.
I'm fine by myself.
Young Master,
just look at her.
Brother, I'm fine.
You don't have to...
Brother!
Brother,
you're dressed up to make me happy.
You're my real brother.
Young Master,
because...
Brother!
There's another one.
Brother, help!
She's a demon!
I can't move.
There's no man in this world
who can escape from me.
Brother, let's go!
You're lucky today.
You two are the only ones
who can escape from me.
You brat!
You don't know if you're hit by a spell!
Protect your health!
Watch your heart!
She can get rid of my control of the power of the soul,
but she has a few abilities.
Unlike this little fatty,
she doesn't carry any burdens.
She's in the West City, cursing the heavens!
Let her go!
You're so young and handsome,
yet you dare to show off in front of me.
Brother,
you're really not afraid of death?
You can still climb up?
I'll have to show you something amazing.
I'll take you to the sky!
Brother,
just give up.
You're no match for me.
It's...
so heavy...
Little Thing,
I'm...
You brat,
I've been practicing the Golden Armor for days.
You've got me a big favor to do.
What?
Golden Armor, change to the second form!
I'll use the Golden Armor!
This brat is so smart.
After he's done with his treasure hunt,
he might be able to break through the Seven Wings of the Nying Qi today.
He might be able to destroy the deep-seated old man
and make your dream come true!
He's got me a life.
Get out if you don't want to die!
You brat sure has a sharp tongue.
I didn't expect you to suffer so much.
You don't know how good my sister is.
I'll take you to the sky!
I'll use the Golden Armor!
You brat is quite capable.
Cut the crap!
I'll take your life!
I'll use the Golden Armor!
Blood Moon Sting!
How come?
You're the only one I have.
You can't kill me.
Hongyi!
As long as the demon is strong,
no matter how strong the demon is,
you're nothing but a poor wooden object.
That's right.
And he can't kill us.
I'll kill him with my sword!
How dare you humiliate me in the Golden Pavilion?
I'll teach you a lesson!
Blood Moon Sting!
I'll use the Golden Armor!
You old bastard!
One day,
I'll make sure you die in a place where you can't be buried!
Since I can't kill you,
I'll cut your hands and feet
and make you suffer for the rest of your life!
No!
What's going on?
Zishi!
Hongyi!
Red Flame!
He's so skilled.
I'm afraid he has some kind of a legend.
If he can get his hands on it,
I'm afraid he can get his hands on it.
Dragon Slash!
Ren Qianchi!
You bastard!
You're lucky this time.
If I see you again next time,
I'll suck your oxygen!
I thought you were so good.
I knew you'd get away,
I just hate that you saved me
and you still don't admit it.
Whatever you think.
Idiot, wake up.
Big brother, where's the fox demon?
It ran away.
Damn Wu Yu, how dare you defame me!
Next time, I will pull out your sword and skin!
Killing your peers is a big crime.
Shui Yue, are you really going to kill him?
You idiot.
No one will think you're dumb if you don't tell me.
I will tear your mouth apart sooner or later.
Chase!
These Martial Souls are all replaced by the beast.
I'll give them to you.
You can't live without the fox demon.
What Martial Soul is this?
Why is the power so powerful?
I'm very interested in your new Martial Soul.
This Martial Soul is interesting.
I'm sorry.