"Don't Let Me Go" by Arthur Chen, Sabrina Zhuang
♫  My affection for you lies quietly in my heart  ♫
♫  And you just happened to pass by there  ♫
♫  So effortlessly  ♫
♫  Awaken the feelings with just one smile  ♫
♫  Oh, I once tucked my true heart away  ♫
♫  But your quiet intuition found its hidden path  ♫
♫  How lucky  ♫
♫  That person turned out to be you  ♫
♫  Our tightly-held hearts folded the distance between us  ♫
♫  Every heartbeat writes the words of our daily life  ♫
♫  And just for now I want to hold you tight  ♫
♫  Come let me see you in the morning light  ♫
♫  If our eyes can't hold back love  ♫
♫  Then let it pour in like a flood  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫
♫  Eye to eye  ♫
♫  Come feel my heart  ♫
♫  Burning bright  ♫
♫  Our hearts beat in perfect sync  ♫
♫  It's obvious because I'm thinking of you  ♫
♫  So don't let me go  ♫
Today is Tuesday, April 9, 2024.
It’s a clear, sunny day in Shanghai,
with highs of 23°C (74°F) and a low of 15°C (59°F).
The air quality is excellent.
A light long-sleeved T-shirt or jacket
would be perfect to wear.
Another beautiful morning
to all our listeners out there.
Have you gone for a jog and enjoyed a meal with your loved ones?
You've just run 10 kilometers (6.2miles).
Congratulations, you've reached today's exercise goal.
I've boarded.
See you later.
Ladies and Gentlemen, your attention, please.
Flight ZX366 from Hong Kong
arrived at 2:10 p.m.
Ladies and Gentlemen, may I have your attention, please?
Flight ZX366 from Hong Kong
arrived at 2:10 p.m. Thank you.
See you in 2E.
Meet you soon.
- I'm picking up the coffee.
- Sure, just a moment.
I've landed. Grab me a coffee.
­Your attention, please.
Go ahead.
Let me.
Thanks.
- Hello, here's your coffee.
- Thank you.
Data...
I'll organize it and send it to you at once.
- Hi. A latte, please.
- Sure.
You can scan to pay.
All right.
Hello?
- Hello, here's your latte.
- Thanks.
Okay, I'm coming out now.
Excuse me. Have you seen a book around here?
Is this it?
Yes, thanks.
No problem.
Sister Tong, it's time to meet Training Box's CEO Yuan.
We will make it. There is no traffic now.
I've already revised Training Box's funding proposal
and sent it to your inbox.
I have read it on the plane.
You did a good job.
Once this deal closes,
you'll be promoted to Managing Director, won't you?
With so many competitors, how could I even hope for it?
Among all the candidates,
you joined the company the latest,
but you've landed many big deals.
And the Training Box client specifically requested you.
Don't get too excited yet.
Last time we met,
Yuan Chao seemed less enthusiastic about the funding.
I think their side is divided.
But he initiated today's meeting.
That's just my guess.
We will see his intent in our meeting.
Hello?
Gan Yang, I'm at the café.
Where are you?
Sorry?
I said I'm at the café.
I'm heading to the parking lot now.
Let's go to Training Box.
All right.
♫  The time and time  ♫
♫  For life and life  ♫
♫  I had it once. I lost it though  ♫
She's back.
Weren’t we meeting at the cafe?
Why are you at the parking lot?
Where's my coffee?
I forgot.
Let's grab it on the way back.
My car's parked across the street.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I ran ten kilometers today.
I'm a bit tired.
Did you try on your new shoes? How do they feel?
They're okay.
What do you mean by that?
- That's not the attitude I'm seeking.
- Fine.
In the data, let’s show a 5% increase in the rebound rate.
Gosh, do you realize 5%
means many all-nighters for me?
You're our Chief R&amp;D Officer at LT Capital.
I believe nothing can stop you, Dr. Wang.
Go for it.
Then I won't go to the office. I'll head straight to the lab.
CEO Yuan, it's been a while.
Likewise, Director Ding.
Sorry to make you come all the way from Hong Kong.
Please, have a seat.
You're too kind, CEO Yuan.
Providing excellent service to our users is what we should do.
Here is the revised proposal incorporating your feedback.
Please take a look. If you've any questions, we can answer right away.
Director Ding, I'm really sorry.
After the board meeting,
we decided to hold off the funding for now.
Here's the thing.
Although I'm the company's CEO,
I have to consider the shareholders' opinions.
The second-largest shareholder is firmly opposed to this.
It puts me in a tough spot.
CEO Yuan, I understand fully.
Since LT Capital is Training Box's second-largest shareholder,
why don't we invite LT Capital's CEO for a chat?
What do you think?
Brother, I'm telling you,
Yuan Chao is staging a mutiny.
What happened?
We already agreed in the last meeting to reject more funds.
Yet today, he’s meeting with Gutong Securities at his office.
- No way.
- They're in his office right now.
Although LT is our second-largest shareholder,
they did invest when we were struggling.
His influence rivals mine.
I have to consider his stance.
Most importantly, he assured me that
LT Capital will provide further funding
if we need money.
Let's go.
We need to catch him red-handed.
LT Capital said they would provide funds now.
But have you discussed how the equity will change?
With your capabilities,
you could absolutely build a high-value company in this field.
However, do you think their capital alone
can make that happen?
CEO Yuan, CEO Gan is here.
I thought he wasn't coming in today.
I have no idea why he's back.
Director Ding, my apologies.
Something unexpected came up.
Shall we discuss the funding another time?
- CEO Yuan, but...
- I understand, CEO Yuan.
We will leave then.
Feel free to reach out anytime.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Xiao He, see them out.
This way, please.
Take care.
CEO Yuan.
What brings you here? Please, have a seat.
Brother Yang, I just want to update you.
CEO Yuan, during the last shareholders' meeting,
I believe we made it clear
that we wouldn't accept funding.
Then why did you meet with people from Gutong behind our backs?
"Behind your back"?
Since when do I report my meetings to you?
- Hey, you...
- Sun Hao, we're not here to argue.
Sit down.
CEO Yuan,
it's just us three now.
Why not share your real thoughts?
I'm considering the company's long-term development.
Our competitors are already developing intelligent hardware
and expanding the gym studios.
I'm worried Training Box will miss this opportunity.
True.
But have you considered
that while expansion can bring us huge funds and short term profits,
it also includes enormous risks?
The second-largest shareholder of Training Box
should be in Yuan Chao's office now.
- Let's go back.
- All right.
Director Ding, what are you doing?
I left something inside. I'll go get it.
Please don't, Director Ding.
I'm sorry, but CEO Yuan is in a meeting.
You can't go in right now.
If you're in a hurry, you can leave,
and I'll have it delivered when the meeting ends.
It’s fine.
I'll just wait here.
Carry on with your work.
All right, suit yourself.
Sister Tong, will we just wait?
Let's wait for now.
All right.
At this stage, I think our priority
is to focus on Training Box's profitability.
Let's build solid revenue,
not just pursue inflated valuations.
CEO Yuan, we need to be responsible to our investors.
Yes, I think CEO Gan is right.
Even as a minority shareholder,
I've watched Training Box grow from the start.
I firmly trust CEO Gan's judgment.
CEO Yuan, we need to maintain a long-term perspective.
Jia Xin, it's time for my video meeting.
- Let me know when someone comes out.
- Understood.
CEO Yuan, please think it over.
We will leave now.
Are they gone?
Sorry, Sister Tong.
I missed them.
It's okay. Let's figure something out.
Shall we eat?
The convenience store's instant noodle combo
before my flight was really delicious.
You're so easy to please.
Let's go to the one near my place.
All right.
Sister Tong, are you from Shanghai?
No. Why?
You're based in Hong Kong and travel all over the world.
You come to Shanghai maybe twice a year.
Why did you buy a home here?
After we make money, let's buy a house here.
All right, let's buy one here.
Gan Yang.
Sister Tong.
Sister Tong, what's wrong?
I’m fine.
♫  I miss you  ♫
Hao Chen, park at the convenience store ahead.
Got it, CEO Gan.
♫  I love you  ♫
Sister Tong, it's been ages since you made paper cranes.
Really?
I'm full, Sister Tong.
Nothing beats these noodles. Totally hits the spot.
Get some rest. Don't stay up late.
Yes, Sister Tong.
- Hello.
- Hi
Do you still have Laoshan Water?
Yes, how many bottles do you need?
Five or six, please.
Sure, just a moment.
Thanks.
So many paper cranes.
We used to have strings of these at home.
I hung them by the window.
When the wind blew, they looked like real flying cranes.
How beautiful.
It's her.
Well, Ding Zhi Tong,
you didn't even tell me you were back in Shanghai.
We're on the same wavelength.
I was just about to call you.
Enough chitchat.
Come to my place for dinner.
Too late. I already ate.
I’ll see you tomorrow.
And I need a favor.
What is it?
Help me find who the CEO of LT Capital is.
See you at the office tomorrow.
All right.
♫  I wish I could spend every  ♫
♫  Dusk and dawn with you  ♫
♫  Like a world with just us  ♫
♫  And a clock without hands  ♫
♫  I wish I could stay with you  ♫
♫  To feel the lingering warmth of love  ♫
♫  How can I seal away these feelings in my heart?  ♫
♫  When it comes to love  ♫
♫  I hide but speak from the heart  ♫
♫  Listen, the night sighs softly  ♫
♫  The rain clouds are approaching  ♫
♫  I can’t bear to part  ♫
♫  Yet still hold back  ♫
♫  And let you stand in the rain with me  ♫
♫  Wind delivers the messages of my heart  ♫
♫  Which line should I send?  ♫
♫  Can let our story continue  ♫
♫  I wish I could spend  ♫
♫  Every dusk and dawn with you  ♫
♫  Like a world with just us  ♫
♫  And a clock without hands  ♫
♫  I wish I could stay with you  ♫
♫  To feel the lingering warmth of love  ♫
♫  How can I seal away these feelings in my heart?  ♫
♫  I hide but speak from the heart  ♫
♫  Please don’t wake me  ♫
♫  Let me hold you  ♫
♫  From the ashes of my dream  ♫
♫  Even for just one more second  ♫
♫  Please let me chase the lonely star  ♫
If she's happy, that's all that matters.
♫  Through this unaligned universe  ♫
Why are you marrying him?
♫  Only for you  ♫
♫  I wish I could spend  ♫
♫  Every dusk and dawn with you  ♫
Because I love him.
♫  Like a world with just us  ♫
♫  And a clock without hands  ♫
Goodbye.
♫  To feel the lingering warmth of love  ♫
♫  My longing keeps knocking on the door  ♫
♫  When it comes to love  ♫
♫  I hide but speak from the heart  ♫
♫  Let us remain forever in this moment  ♫
Yu Lin, look who's here.
Mommy Ding, I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
Look what I brought you.
What is this?
A doll!
- And this?
- KFC! I haven't had it for so long.
Right, let's see what we've got here.
Mom, can I have it?
Sure.
You always feed her snacks.
Once in a while won't hurt.
Right?
You spoil her too much.
Our little princess deserves to be spoiled.
Go ahead. Have it at the table, okay?
Take your doll with you.
Nanny, please help me out.
Leave it to me.
Yu Lin's getting cuter every day.
If you like children so much, have your own!
I don't have the time.
Besides, it takes two to make a baby.
Come on. Haven't you had any romantic encounters in Hong Kong?
No, just clients and colleagues.
That ring on your finger scares everyone off.
What about that rich guy from your last project?
He seemed nice.
Why not give it a try?
I promised my boss I wouldn't date clients or colleagues.
You're something else.
No clients, no colleagues.
How long has it been since you dated anyone?
I don't remember.
That's why I'm saying you should meet more people.
Maybe you'll really meet someone—
Let's discuss business.
I said to inquire about LT Capital.
What's the deal with them?
I did some digging.
Their official head is Old Chen.
He's very low-key and is an overseas Chinese.
But they said the actual controller is called "Forrest."
He's the one managing all of the company's affairs.
Oh, and I heard they're participating in that sports charity fund,
CrossFit Challenge.
Haven’t you been training lately?
Why don't you give it a try?
Maybe you'll meet them.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
I'll sign up, have a casual talk,
and find out why he's against the funding.
Don't play dumb with me.
Gan Yang's English name is also Forrest in Matching.
Could it be the same person?
No way.
So many people have the same English names.
It can't be that coincidental.
It's better not to be him.
If, I mean, hypothetically,
if you were to meet Gan Yang again, what would you do?
Kill him.
It's been years.
Don't dwell on the past.
You'll be the only one suffering.
I'm not dwelling on the past.
I just can't forgive him,
never in this lifetime.
Why are you marrying him?
Do you love him?
Or is it because you hate me?
Why would you think I'd gamble with my own happiness
just because I hate you?
♫  The long-lost memories suddenly resurfaced  ♫
♫  That was when we were searching for a crack in love  ♫
♫  The one who ran back then just wanted to stop  ♫
If you really love him...
♫  Even brushing past, we couldn't help but look back  ♫
♫  But we failed to hold on to that tenderness in time  ♫
then I wish you happiness.
♫  Hidden in plain sight, yet too hard to say aloud  ♫
I love him.
♫  Someone stayed by your side without reservation  ♫
Thanks for the blessing.
♫  Someone lost all the warmth those moments once held  ♫
And please...
don't show up in front of me again.
♫  It took every ounce of courage to let go of all the pain  ♫
♫  So I could fulfill all your future  ♫
♫  Someone once said, "Please forget me"  ♫
♫  And every time I think of it  ♫
Sister Tong, I've never formally trained for CrossFit.
I just viewed the challenges,
and my brain is fried.
We're not here to actually compete,
but mainly to connect with folks from LT Capital.
Where are they?
I asked the staff.
That empty tenth lane is reserved for LT Capital.
They should be here soon.
You'll be wearing heart rate monitors
throughout the event.
The data will be displayed in real-time on that big screen.
If any of you have a heart rate
exceeding 180 beats per minute,
the red light will beep,
then you must pause and adjust.
Sister Tong, they're here.
It's Wang Yi.
Why is it so high?
What's going on?
Sister Tong, is your monitor malfunctioning?
I'm fine.
Well, this is awkward.
Can you still compete?
That guy in black looks like their boss.
Should we go over and say hello?
Not yet. Let's finish the challenge.
Understood.
All right. All the team members have assembled.
The competition officially begins.
♫  Sunrise covers everywhere I ran through  ♫
♫  Feeling the morning breeze  ♫
♫  The sweat on my forehead is the morning dew  ♫
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Let me handle this.
♫  It lets me release all my worries  ♫
♫  Remember to keep up with my pace in one go  ♫
♫  Immediately alleviate all the burdens  ♫
♫  For the brighter future, we must keep going  ♫
♫  Creating everything we're longing for  ♫
♫  Day and night  ♫
♫  Wait until I can reach my dreams  ♫
♫  Gather enough courage to embrace the thorns  ♫
♫  Let the global starlight shine over me  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫
♫  I appreciate you've been there for me  ♫
♫  Staying with me through the thick and thin of life  ♫
♫  Because of you, I have more courage  ♫
♫  Every place we've been became a beautiful memory  ♫
♫  The encounters along the journey  ♫
♫  It's the blessings of all my dreams  ♫
♫  Be okay  ♫
♫  Please hold me tight once again  ♫
Are you okay?
If you ran into an ex you once loved deeply,
would your heart still flutter?
A) Show up deliberately to embarrass him.
B) Try to get back together.
C) Pass by silently and wish him well.
D) Explore other possibilities.
I choose D. Explore other possibilities.
Wait.
Why?
I'm busy; no time for dating.
- No current relationship means no exes.
- Whatever.
Are you done yet? Give me my phone.
I'm leaving.
Hold on. The result will be out soon.
Soulmates!
Are you saying some quiz found my soulmate?
Is this how you scam users?
Don't say it like that. It sounds so bad.
Listen, out of 10,000 users,
this is the first time I've seen a 100% compatibility score.
Most only score 50% to 60%.
You know what, I have to take a picture
and send it to Deng Bo Ting for promotion.
Hurry, I'm going to my part-time job.
Aren't you curious what this "Forrest" looks like?
He's your soulmate.
I believe in soulmates,
but not ones decided by a quiz.
And only 10,000 users, those are the odds?
Doesn't that just prove you two are more destined?
Trust me.
Deng Bo Ting's algorithm is definitely reliable.
If you won't look, I will.
I'll see what he looks like.
You're hopeless.
Seriously, Missy.
Your phone is too slow.
With your First-class Scholarship,
National Scholarship, and all those part-time jobs,
you're getting at least ¥20,000-30,000 ($2,700-4,100) a year.
Can't you get a decent phone?
Imagine someone failed to inform you for a job  interview.
How embarrassing would that be?
I'll just delete a few apps.
It's loaded.
Maybe he's a cute guy.
Cute guys don't post their back view.
Since you're not interested, I'll chat with him on your behalf.
I'm leaving.
Chat, yes, right.
Are you sure you won't chat with him?
Move the chair there.
Be careful; the floor is slippery.
Ding Zhi Tong, off to work again?
- Come back early.
- Tong Tong!
- What are you doing?
- Uninstalling the "Matching" app.
Why?
Takes up too much storage.
- I'm leaving.
- Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Tong Tong, are you heading out?
I've got class. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
- Off to work?
- Yes.
- Bye bye.
I'm leaving.
♫  Since the first time we met  ♫
♫  My heart lost its balance  ♫
♫  I open my arms wide trying to take it all in  ♫
♫  Don’t miss out on your life again  ♫
♫  Let me fill in the empty spaces  ♫
♫  That moment you looked at me and said I love you  ♫
♫  Since the first time we met  ♫
♫  My heart lost its balance  ♫
♫  I open my arms wide trying  ♫
♫  To take it all in  ♫
Brother, wait for me.
Who's that?
I'm asking you, who's that?
- I don't know.
- Then why are you staring?
Oh, love at first sight?
It found your soulmate.
What soulmate?
Look at your phone.
On the Matching app, you two are the only perfect match
in our entire school.
Really?
It's 100%?
You answered "no exes" on the last question.
And someone gave the same answer?
I think everyone has a soulmate,
but it's impossible to find one through some quiz.
But "Forrest" and "Get Rich" matched 100%.
What are the odds?
You seem to have a lot of free time.
Aren't you nervous about the competition this afternoon?
Not at all.
Then don't drop the ball onstage.
Relax. I won't hold you back.
I'll go prepare now.
Do you believe in soulmates?
I didn't in the past,
until I met her.
"Someone" by Tia Ray
♫  The long-lost memories suddenly resurfaced  ♫
♫  That was when we were searching for a crack in love  ♫
♫  The one who ran back then just wanted to stop  ♫
♫  Even brushing past, we couldn't help but look back  ♫
♫  But we failed to hold on to that tenderness in time  ♫
♫  Hidden in plain sight, yet too hard to say aloud  ♫
♫  Someone stayed by your side without reservation  ♫
♫  Someone lost all the warmth those moments once held  ♫
♫  It took every ounce of courage to let go of all the pain  ♫
♫  So I could fulfill all your future  ♫
♫  Someone once said, "Please forget me"  ♫
♫  And every time I think of it  ♫
♫  Someone stood behind me with no reservation  ♫
♫  Someone held my hand against all odds  ♫
♫  Now I’m left alone, piecing together the memories we once had  ♫
♫  Along the road we used to run through  ♫
♫  There is always the someone I never once forgot  ♫