"Don't Let Me Go" by Arthur Chen, Sabrina Zhuang
♫  My affection for you lies quietly in my heart  ♫
♫  And you just happened to pass by there  ♫
♫  So effortlessly  ♫
♫  Awaken the feelings with just one smile  ♫
♫  Oh, I once tucked my true heart away  ♫
♫  But your quiet intuition found its hidden path  ♫
♫  How lucky  ♫
♫  That person turned out to be you  ♫
♫  Our tightly-held hearts folded the distance between us  ♫
♫  Every heartbeat writes the words of our daily life  ♫
♫  And just for now I want to hold you tight  ♫
♫  Come let me see you in the morning light  ♫
♫  If our eyes can't hold back love  ♫
♫  Then let it pour in like a flood  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫
♫  Eye to eye  ♫
♫  Come feel my heart  ♫
♫  Burning bright  ♫
♫  Our hearts beat in perfect sync  ♫
♫  It's obvious because I'm thinking of you  ♫
♫  So don't let me go  ♫
Director Qi, why did you put an idle person under my charge?
Am I in charge of idle employees?
She asked to come to your team.
It's the pressure from the higher-ups.
I can't help it, either.
The regular meeting is over, but she didn't arrive yet.
What is Xu Chen Xi's background?
­
As long as you tear her disguise in front of Gan Yang,
and use that opportunity,
Gan Yang will be all yours.
As long as she stays within the lines, I can let her stay.
But if she crosses my bottom line,
you know my temper.
I understand.
But don't be too tough on her.
She must have connections among higher-ups.
So we should cover her a bit to answer to the higher-ups.
You can flatter the higher-ups while I suffer.
You sure know how to play your cards right.
Hi, Guan Guan—
I...
Xu Chen Xi?
Why are you here?
Why can't I be here if you are?
What a jinx.
A new analyst will come soon.
Help her get familiar with our project
and help her start as soon as possible.
Okay.
Come in.
Hello, Director Dai.
I am Ding Zhi Tong, the new junior analyst.
Hello, Director Dai. I am the new intern, Xu Chen Xi.
I heard you are this year's outstanding graduate from Qingbei University?
Yes.
I was also an outstanding graduate of Qingbei University.
I graduated ten years ago.
Ten years have passed.
Qingbei's teaching quality should have improved greatly.
Rest assured, Director Dai.
I'll surely work hard and live up to Qingbei's good name.
As expected of a Qingbei University graduate.
Director Dai, I'm—
Why I asked you two to report in so urgently
is because one of my accounts, a natural gas public company,
is doing private placement financing, and we are short a junior analyst.
Since you joined the team suddenly,
I won't arrange too much work for you.
Focus on this project first.
Jia Fan, assign the work.
This is all the information
about Guanghua Energy's natural gas private placement (investment).
Get familiar with it soon.
There's so much...
Is there any problem?
No.
It's impressive, isn't it?
The rebound rate is unparalleled.
There is still room for improvement.
Stop pretending to be unimpressed.
A rebound rate of 80% is maxed.
But I think the cost is still too high.
Just a small piece of it cost us ¥10,000.
It's hard to have mass production.
Then let's make it a special-order product.
I believe as soon as it is released...
- countless...
- Wang Yi.
Did you forget our goal of making shoes?
Hello?
What's wrong? Did anything happen?
It's from Shuchi.
He made an appointment and was waiting for three hours.
Okay, I understand.
Director Zhan! You're back.
Please give me ten minutes.
I'd like to know why Shuchi suddenly stopped
funding our research and development.
Your R and D cost is too high.
It's impossible for mass production.
It's good for youth to have ideas.
But you are not professional enough.
We're already working on the cost issue.
I believe we can resolve it soon.
Please spare us some time.
"Resolve it"?
Yes.
How will you resolve it?
Do you really think you are a genius?
Without the investment from Shuchi, you are nobody. Understand?
Since you don't believe in us, why buy our design?
As a responsible enterprise,
maintaining a good public image is also important.
Do you think after we bought your design, we should manufacture it?
Do you know that adding a new product line
requires countless evaluations?
It's not child's play.
I've seen many college students like you!
Slogans are all you've got.
Have you really devised a realistic plan?
You publicly breached the contract,
yet you still want to maintain a good image?
You haven't made any research progress so as the investor,
I have the right to stop funding, understand?
Security! See him out.
I hope you won't regret it.
I've read the information about Guanghua Energy.
So fast? You took only two days.
I'm a fast reader.
Then read it again and check for any typos.
If there are, correct them.
All the typos have been corrected and tagged.
This is the latest version. Please review.
This version of the Private Placement Memorandum (PPM)
has the reporting date of December 30 last year.
All the financial and business data in it have expired.
Update all the financial and business information of Guanghua Energy.
I believe you know how to find data, right?
Get to it.
Hello.
Tong Tong, where are you?
I'm at home.
I was about to freshen up and go to bed.
Are the lights in your bathroom so bright?
You have such sharp eyes.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
I'm still at work doing overtime.
I'm afraid you might worry.
Why are you so busy?
Hetai uses the last-place elimination system.
They rate employees every week.
It lasts six months.
My boss, Dai Bo La, is very strict.
I heard if our rating isn't four stars,
we get kicked out of the project team.
I heard that's why the previous junior analyst got fired.
Tong Tong, you are great at studying.
Over the four years in college,
you were among the top three students.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
But I joined late.
The private placement project is faster than a stock launch.
Before I came, they already finished due diligence on the project,
and it was established.
Now it's the second stage.
If I can't get the project core at this stage, my work will be in vain.
I don't want to just stay at the project sidelines.
In that case,
have you considered changing project teams?
That won't do. I've already inquired.
My boss, Dai Bo La,
has many projects, high performance, and many bonuses.
So I must follow such a leader to make good money
on a good career path.
So money-minded.
I don't work so late every day. Today is an exception.
I've been going home on time so far.
Tong Tong, I disagree with your work style.
It's really tough.
And it's so late now.
It's not safe for you to go home alone.
Well, I just started this job.
I'll ease up when my boss sees my value.
Are you sure you won't get busier by then?
Wouldn't the bonus also get bigger?
Before you make money, care for your health.
Good health is required for any revolution.
- Got it?
- Okay, I'll run whenever I have time.
Keep up the good work, Tong Tong.
Don't stay up all night.
You, too. I miss you.
Remember to miss me, too. Good night.
Bye bye.
What time is it?
It's past 11 p.m.
Are you running this late?
I'll go and run a few laps.
If you want to sleep, go to the bedroom.
You might catch a cold here.
I'm so stressed.
If we don't receive new funding, our research has to stop again.
Don't worry.
It's useless to worry.
Your idea is on the right track.
It's just on the verge of success.
Besides, Shuchi is not China's only shoe manufacturer.
We will find a way.
I'll go run a few laps.
Don't wait for me.
It's so late already, and she's still working overtime.
Just putting on a show, I reckon.
If you catch a cold, Gan Yang will feel sorry for you.
No such luck!
Good evening.
Professor Qin, what would you like today?
Professor Qin!
What a coincidence.
I ordered many dishes.
Why don't you sit and eat with me?
Do you wait for me on purpose?
I didn't!
I just wanted to try out your extremely spicy set.
Have a seat!
I don't know if you like them.
Try them.
Professor Qin.
Actually, there is a question I wanted to ask you long ago.
Go ahead.
You were doing really well in the financial world.
You're at your career peak. Why did you choose
to teach at our college?
I can't figure it out no matter what.
My father got sick the year before last.
He feared it would affect my job,
and he hid it from me.
It wasn't until his condition worsened
that he finally told me.
So I quit my job and returned to Beijing.
How about now?
Is he cured?
That's good.
But Professor Qin, have you ever considered this?
Even if you didn't come back,
your father may still have recovered.
Isn't it a pity to give up your bright future?
Not everything can be measured by money.
I really envy you.
You have a more important goal in life than money.
Here. Eat up.
Okay.
Yes, I'll give you feedback after reading it.
I'll contact you later.
Sister Qin Yu, my database
is missing an industry research report for the natural gas industry.
Can I ask the Industry Research Department for it?
It's not there?
I remember I saw it days ago.
It's not there.
Industry Research Department should have backups.
You can report to Compliance.
Then go see Han Tao from Financing.
But he is a bit hard to deal with.
Be careful when talking to him.
Got it.
Go there in the afternoon.
Their department has meetings in the morning.
Thank you, Sister Qin Yu.
You are welcome.
Have you finished updating the memorandum?
I just need the industry research report to finish it.
Impressive.
I just collected the information.
No technical expertise is required.
How about you? Have you finished investigating the investors' turnover?
I've completed my part for three investors, reviewed it,
and uploaded it to the database.
Then can I see the information?
Sure. You are also a project team member.
I'll send it to you now.
I've given you all the information for this project.
But the database lacks an industry research report.
Could you give me a copy?
That's your problem!
If everyone in the company is sloppy like you,
and come ask me for another copy,
then I don't need to do anything else today,
and just help you?
Brother Tao!
Angry isn't good for your health. Have some coffee.
Don't scare our new colleagues.
Have a drink.
I've sent the information to your email.
Thanks.
Why did you join Hetai Securities suddenly?
Did something happen at Wendao Capital?
I just go into the industry for more experience.
Hetai is one of China's largest investment banks.
The people and things I can experience here are unmatched elsewhere.
I thought you always wanted to join Investment Banking Department?
Industry Research is also good.
Imran Khan from Credit Suisse
also switched from Industry Research to Investment Banking.
How about you? Is it going well in Investment Banking?
I'm doing well.
I'm just a little busy.
I heard you work under Jia Fan.
Jia Fan joined the company at 27 years old.
This year marks his third year as a project manager.
It's quite critical to him.
What do you mean?
He can't get promoted further,
and his salary is higher than the new analyst.
If the company, in this year's second half
or next year's start, conducts a layoff,
he might be on the list.
So he worries most
that once he trains you, it will harm him.
Some time ago, an employee was kicked out of Dai Bo La's team.
He was behind it.
So be wary of his tricks.
Thank you for helping me.
We are old classmates, no need to thank me.
Maybe at times, I'll need your help.
Get back to work now, or he might bother you.
Then I'll leave first. Keep up the good work!
Okay.
Ding Zhi Tong!
We're still friends, right?
Of course.
That's good.
Feng Sheng.
You didn't come for a few days.
Here you are, the handouts and notes from each subject.
Are these for me?
- Thank you.
- It's fine. We are friends, right?
- Hurry and take a look.
- Zhi Tong.
Please help me solve this problem.
But I don't know which to use first.
You can follow this.
Use this first, right?
Hello.
Now?
I'll have an online meeting in 20 minutes. I can't make it over there.
Can I come tomorrow?
I'll check my time.
If this won't work, it'll have to be the day after tomorrow.
Bye bye.
What's wrong, Sister Qin Yu?
The bank asked me for a document.
But I'm too busy to go.
Can you let others fetch it for you?
Forget it.
Jia Fan will make a scene if he doesn't see you here later.
I've finished all he assigned me.
And he will also go out later.
He will sign a subscription agreement with Directors Dai and Zhang.
It's fine if I get back before he returns.
Then I'll leave it to you.
Ask for Xiao Li at the bank on Zhaohui Road.
I'll tell her about it in advance.
Okay.
Thank you, Zhi Tong.
No worries.
Sister Qin Yu, I'm here.
I'll wait for her in the lounge for a bit.
Thank you for your help.
Doesn't it look nice? I just bought it yesterday from Hong Kong.
You had such a wonderful annual vacation.
You went to Macao and Hong Kong.
You can also go there on your annual vacation. It was really fun.
Then I'll give you a guide. You can just follow it and have fun.
By the way, I brought you a local specialty. Come to my desk later for it.
What is it?
You'll know when you come get it.
- You're so mysterious.
- This accent and this person...
This information is very important. You must keep it safe.
The video was provided the day before yesterday.
But the bank staff who provided the video was on annual vacation.
Thus, bank statements provided by Director Zhang may be fake.
Hello?
Sister Qin Yu, are Director Dai and the others still at the office?
They already set out to Director Zhang's Company.
Judging by time, they might arrive soon.
Is there any way to contact them?
I kept calling, but no one answered.
When they sign contracts with the investor,
Director Dai usually asks them to mute their phones.
What's wrong?
Director Zhang's bank statement may have problems.
Mister, is there a traffic jam?
Yes, look at the congestion.
I fear we can't go within 20 minutes.
Please let me out.
How much is it? I'll pay you.
Okay. It's 38 yuan.
Director Zhang, this is our agreement.
We sent you the electronic version for confirmation before.
You can check it again.
If there is no problem, we can sign the contract.
All right.
Director Dai!
You can't sign it.
Fake bank statements?
It's a serious charge.
Do you have any evidence?
I heard it with my own ears.
The staff in Director Zhang's video of bank statements
just returned from her annual vacation in Hong Kong.
And she just came back yesterday.
We can confirm that by checking with the bank.
So she couldn't have pulled the statements the day before yesterday.
The video is surely not from the day before yesterday.
Is this your first day at work?
You let the investor make such important bank statements himself?
Have you lost your mind?
Director Dai, I'm sorry.
I had too much work
so I didn't have time to go there.
I gave you an assistant. Why didn't you let her help?
Don't think I don't know what's on your mind.
If this happens again, you get lost immediately.
Ding Zhi Tong.
Go on a business trip with me tomorrow.
I'll see you at 10 a.m. at the airport.
Is there any problem?
No. I'll arrive on time.
Go out.
I've received a five-star rating.
Sister Qin Yu said this is the first time that Director Dai
rated a new employee five stars in the first week.
You saved her project and her reputation.
Surely she would give you five stars.
And I can go on a business trip with them this week.
Do you know what this means?
It means you've entered the core project.
Tong Tong.
You've said it 800 times.
I'm just happy.
I'm also happy for you.
This means your efforts are worth it.
But Tong Tong, I still have to say this.
Before doing your job well,
you should care well for your health.
It took you only 30 minutes
to cover a 45 minutes distance to run.
You are sacrificing your health.
But I'm all safe and sound.
Even if I get injured, this result is worth it too.
You don't take your body seriously.
Let's skip this topic.
Gan Yang.
Thank you.
If you hadn't given me shoes and taught me how to run,
it wouldn't have gone well.
So you can have half my credit.
Okay.
Tong Tong,
why did you believe
you could do the journey in 30 minutes?
I'll never know if it's possible unless I try.
My life creed is never giving up until the last moment.
Gan Yang.
Gan Yang. What are you thinking of?
You are right.
Until the last moment,
we should never give up.
Tong Tong,
thank you.
Why is it broken?
Is Ms. Ding Zhi Tong at home?
Coming.
- Hello.
- Are you Ms. Ding Zhi Tong?
- Yes.
- Please sign for this luggage.
I didn't buy luggage.
Mr. Gan Yang asked me to send this.
- Thanks.
- Welcome.
You want me to wear your shoes to run the College Marathon League?
- Right.
- I know your family produces shoes.
But I can't wear just any shoes for the competition.
It may affect my performance.
Anyway, I already brought my shoes here.
You can start wearing it while training today.
If you are dissatisfied within the period,
you can terminate our contract anytime.
I'm not a seeded player.
I don't even have a team behind me.
I don't think I'll get any good results.
You won't benefit from it much, right?
I know you are not a seeded player.
But if a non-seeded player can wear our shoes,
and win the competition, doesn't that show how good our shoes are?
You wear my shoes.
I'll help you improve your performance.
We benefit mutually.
Isn't this good?
Okay, I believe you.
The meeting is at 3 p.m. Qin Yu will do the presentation.
Before the meeting, you three read all the information.
- Yes.
- Okay.
♫  Feeling the morning breeze  ♫
♫  The sweat on my forehead is the morning dew  ♫
♫  It lets me release all my worries  ♫
It doesn't quench the thirst like spring water.
I'm about to fly to the next city.
Our competition was a big success.
My exam results are also very good.
Hope to see you soon.
You still have time to enjoy your relationship?
Because Wu Xun won the championship, it even brought Shuchi back to us.
But you rejected them. What's on your mind actually?
What do you mean, Brother?
We're short of money now.
We shouldn't be so demanding, okay?
Can you please calm down?
Now these brands are all rushing in.
If we encounter any problems then,
will they run away altogether like Shuchi did?
Good things are worth the wait.
Be patient.
Where are you going?
I'm going for a run.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Why are you following me?
Mister. You misunderstood.
I'm just looking at the rare shoes you're wearing.
I wondered what brand it is.
I wanted to see.
What do you mean?
There is a shovel-shaped carbon plate underneath your shoes.
But when you run,
it doesn't conform to the shovel-shaped carbon plate.
I'm just curious.
Young Man, you sure know much about it.
You flatter me.
Can we discuss your shoes?
Sure.
Where have you been?
Why did you return so late?
I met someone.
Do you remember Dr. Chen?
- He specializes in researching running—
- Stop, listen to me first.
Do you know who came to see me today?
No.
What's going on?
The beauty in your major finally likes you?
Be serious.
Okay, go ahead.
Gan Yang. One of the world's best sports brands,
Didi Sports, came to our place
and said they would invest in us!
For real?
But I've just solved the investment problem.
What? When did it happen?
Just when I was running.
Y-You must have met a fraud.
No way.
Do you know Dr. Chen?
Dr. Chen? Which Dr. Chen?
Do you mean the judge of the Running Shoe Design Competition, Dr. Chen Hai Chuan?
Yes. That's him!
- Unbelievable.
- I just met him.
How can you be so lucky?
Did you meet such a big investor while running?
I just met him in the park.
At first, I noticed only his shoes.
Then we quickly chatted.
But as I talked, I felt he was familiar.
Unexpectedly, it was Dr. Chen himself.
When I found out, I purposely talked about R and D.
As we talked, he...
- Invested?
- He invested.
I never thought it would be so smooth.
What about Didi Sports?
Will we consider them?
I think for us...
Dr. Chen is more suitable as our investor.
He loves shoes very much.
Besides,
when we were talking,
he actually said our heartfelt creed.
He said, in his opinion, the best running shoes
should be made for all to wear.
Tong Tong,
it's our Day 27 of being long-distance.
I'm missing you again.
[Ding Zhi Tong: It's Day 39 of being long-distance.
Dr. Chen, this is your awaited guest.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Dr. Chen.
- Please, have a seat.
- Okay, thanks.
This one is our business plan.
Please take a look.
Director Dai, your flight ticket.
After going to Hefei, Jia Fan and I will go to Guangzhou.
Qin Yu, Ding Zhi Tong, you two go to Suzhou to visit Director Huang.
You performed well these days.
You do the presentation for Director Huang's project.
It's about your rating this week. Don't take it lightly.
Thank you, Director Dai.
Help get me a cup of coffee.
Okay.
Same.
- Matcha latte.
- Okay.
Two iced Americanos and two matcha lattes.
Okay, please wait a moment.
It scanned through.
Tong Tong. I knew you'd see it.
That's why I especially left it for you.
But I'm not there now.
I transferred from Shanghai Airport three days ago.
I thought you were in Shanghai.
We will see each other soon.
I'll finish what I'm doing promptly.
All right.
Aren't you having exams soon?
Why did you come to Shanghai days ago?
I haven't told you the Shuchi matter.
They breached the contract.
But it doesn't matter. I found a new investor.
I'll buy some new equipment with them now.
I'll also poach some talent to establish a new laboratory.
So in these two months, I'll travel around the country.
I also applied for the online courses.
My instructor has approved it.
I'm sorry.
I advised you to sign with Shuchi.
See?
I knew you would blame yourself. So I never told you.
It's not your fault.
Well, then you can go do your work.
I'm waiting for coffee.
Go ahead, Tong Tong.
Hey, Tong Tong!
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay. Then you hang up first.
Bye bye.
Hello, your coffee is ready.
Coming.
Gan Yang, do you think this cloud looks like a puppy?
After we arrive, we might need to see Director Chen first,
then check the machines.
Okay.
It's almost time. We...
Tong Tong, are you also at Suzhou Station?
Where are you going?
Which platform are you on?
Yes, are you also here?
The train is about to depart.
Passengers, please board the train quickly.
Tong Tong, which platform are you on?
Platform 5.
I'm on Platform 7.
What carriage are you in?
I'm at Carriage 2 right now.
Go toward Carriage 1.
Walk to the front of the train.
I'm right there.
I got there.
Tong Tong!
Tong Tong, I-I'll come to you now.
Don't come here.
My train is departing.
I'll just watch you for a while.
Tong Tong,
I miss you so much.
I miss you as well.
I want to hug you now.
I want to hug you, too.
♫  Which line should I send?  ♫
♫  Can let our story continue  ♫
♫  I wish I could spend every  ♫
♫  Dusk and dawn with you  ♫
♫  Like a world with just us  ♫
♫  And a clock without hands  ♫
♫  I wish I could stay with you  ♫
The train is about to depart.
My train is leaving.
Take good care of yourself.
Bye bye.
"Someone" by Tia Ray
♫  The long-lost memories suddenly resurfaced  ♫
♫  That was when we were searching for a crack in love  ♫
♫  The one who ran back then just wanted to stop  ♫
♫  Even brushing past, we couldn't help but look back  ♫
♫  But we failed to hold on to that tenderness in time  ♫
♫  Hidden in plain sight, yet too hard to say aloud  ♫
♫  Someone stayed by your side without reservation  ♫
♫  Someone lost all the warmth those moments once held  ♫
♫  It took every ounce of courage to let go of all the pain  ♫
♫  So I could fulfill all your future  ♫
♫  Someone once said, "Please forget me"  ♫
♫  And every time I think of it  ♫
♫  Someone stood behind me with no reservation  ♫
♫  Someone held my hand against all odds  ♫
♫  Now I’m left alone, piecing together the memories we once had  ♫
♫  Along the road we used to run through  ♫
♫  There is always the someone I never once forgot  ♫