"Don't Let Me Go" by Arthur Chen, Sabrina Zhuang
♫  My affection for you lies quietly in my heart  ♫
♫  And you just happened to pass by there  ♫
♫  So effortlessly  ♫
♫  Awaken the feelings with just one smile  ♫
♫  Oh, I once tucked my true heart away  ♫
♫  But your quiet intuition found its hidden path  ♫
♫  How lucky  ♫
♫  That person turned out to be you  ♫
♫  Our tightly-held hearts folded the distance between us  ♫
♫  Every heartbeat writes the words of our daily life  ♫
♫  And just for now I want to hold you tight  ♫
♫  Come let me see you in the morning light  ♫
♫  If our eyes can't hold back love  ♫
♫  Then let it pour in like a flood  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫
♫  Eye to eye  ♫
♫  Come feel my heart  ♫
♫  Burning bright  ♫
♫  Our hearts beat in perfect sync  ♫
♫  It's obvious because I'm thinking of you  ♫
♫  So don't let me go  ♫
We've arrived at the final stop.
The doors are opening.
Please watch your steps.
Please board at the front and exit at the back.
Thank you.
♫  I wish that moment could last forever  ♫
Girl, are you riding again to clear your head?
All right, sit tight.
♫  I’m burning with anticipation  ♫
♫  Counting the days like years  ♫
♫  I’ve fallen for you without even realizing it  ♫
♫  Our tangled headphone cable  ♫
♫  Carried my longing to you for me  ♫
♫  I’ve kept everything in me  ♫
♫  Since the first time we met  ♫
♫  My heart lost its balance  ♫
♫  I open my arms wide trying to take it all in  ♫
♫  Don’t miss out on your life again  ♫
♫  Let me fill in the empty spaces  ♫
♫  That moment you looked at me and said I love you  ♫
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting so long.
No problem. I just got here, too.
Sit.
Here, have some water.
Thanks.
Why did you go to the final stop?
- Do you have a part-time job there?
- No.
Sometimes, I like taking the bus to the final stop and back,
watching the scenery along the way.
Do you also like the feeling of watching the city pass by?
Does watching people bustling around give you a sense of peace?
How did you know?
Because I enjoy the same thing.
I don't like running on a treadmill.
I prefer running by the river or on the street and watching people.
I think it's a great way to relieve stress.
Then we're quite in sync.
Of course, we are.
Oh, I almost forgot this.
This...
I got it at a flower shop near HKEX.
I figured it soaked up plenty of good luck for making money; I brought it for you.
Good luck for making money? Thanks.
Let's go.
What a huge plum orchard.
Right.
As a child, I loved plum jam.
Hello?
Ding Zhi Tong, return and submit your paper.
I'm sorry. I totally forgot it.
I'll go back now. Give me 30 minutes.
I'm so sorry. My assignment is due today.
I forgot it. I must rush back to school.
It's fine.
My car is nearby. I'll drive you.
- Then...
- This time, you can't pay me for gas.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm back!
I smell gossip.
- What's this?
- Who gave you the flowers?
- Gan Yang.
- They smell amazing.
"Gan Yang"?
It's not what you guys think.
Do you really feel nothing for Gan Yang?
You tell me, how many years would I have to work to live like him,
flying wherever he wants?
You're so smart.
I say five years is enough.
Then let's talk again in five years.
See if he brings me flowers then.
Look, all that is just material stuff.
You can also have that via hard work.
But what you two really share are your souls.
Exactly. Such a bond is rare.
You two are 100% in sync.
You guys are meant to be.
That's right.
You two have time for that kind of talk.
Soulmates are not as common as you think.
She says we're nagging. Fine.
Leave her alone.
Eat this.
Look at mine.
They're so fresh.
- That one is ours.
-  Gan Yang? Why is he here, too?
Auntie, Auntie. Please let me pick more.
I came here first.
- Let me pick some.
- I saw them first.
- How could you?
Why are you fighting with the elderly for it?
You're unreasonable.
Let's just pick ours.
Ding Zhi Tong, why did you come?
I got a bunch of plums.
Let me see.
- You got so much?
- Yes.
Then let's keep picking.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
♫  Welcome to  ♫
♫  My world  ♫
♫  Each cloud is brushed with color  ♫
Maybe, just like Song Ming Mei said,
although Gan Yang and I live in different worlds,
we truly are similar.
♫  The warmth causes a flower to bloom  ♫
♫  Waiting for you to appear  ♫
♫  I lie awake  ♫
♫  I’ve been missing you for 1,001 nights   ♫
♫  I just want to greet the sunrise in your embrace  ♫
♫  And never say goodbye  ♫
♫  You and I  ♫
- What the heck?
- Li Fei, be careful. Those are all brand-new shoes.
If you ruin them, how can we explain to Director Gan?
Gan Yang's not even here right now.
Stop calling him Director Gan, Director Gan.
You just love currying favor with him.
No one would take such junk even if they were thrown on the street.
He fusses over those rotten shoes daily for data testing in R&amp;D,
as if he can make something good.
Watch what you say. Don't let him hear that.
Relax. I'm just venting.
I just don't like him,
acting like some famous brand doing R&amp;D?
Does he even know what a real brand is?
Like this.
Nice. That brand is expensive, isn't it?
It's from the flagship (prime) store. Good, right?
Oops, I'm so sorry.
Let me wipe that off for you.
Why is the label coming off?
It really is.
Wasn't that from a flagship store?
I used to work at that store.
Those logos are stitched, not glued.
- You might have bought a fake.
- Don't talk nonsense.
Are you okay?
Director Gan, do you know her?
She's my friend.
Li Fei,
apologize to her.
Director Gan, I've seen plenty of girls like her.
She's clearly after your money.
I'll give you a kind reminder; stay away from her.
I know her better than you do.
Apologize.
Hey, we're all friends.
I'll talk to him.
Apologize.
Right now.
Apologize to her.
I'm sorry. I was wrong just then.
I'm not the one you owe an apology to.
What were you guys saying just now?
Nothing.
Ding Zhi Tong.
Don't be angry.
We just know each other well.
Sometimes, they speak without thinking.
Don't take it to heart. I'll scold them later.
You still defend them after all they did?
They act nice to your face, but do you know what they say behind your back?
They say you'll never make good shoes.
Really?
Yes.
Why are you still smiling?
Ding Zhi Tong.
What?
Are you concerned about me?
You're crazy.
Ding Zhi Tong, thank you.
Professor Qin, this is for you.
Your voice sounds a little hoarse.
This is good for soothing your throat.
Are you openly bribing me?
Of course not.
You still teach us even while you're sick.
I'm just showing my concern.
Go ahead, what do you want?
Then I'll be straight.
I'd like you to take me
to the finance networking event coming up.
It's a large-scale event. Attendees need a plus-one.
Well, I'm well-versed in finance, stocks, funds, trusts,
and whatever else you can name.
Besides, I'm great at socializing.
I swear... I swear I won't embarrass you.
That actually does makes sense.
Moreover, we have a teacher-student relationship.
Even if people find out, they'll only praise you
for being a kind, selfless teacher.
No one will overthink it,
and it'll avoid any unnecessary gossip.
Given all that, you might actually be the best choice.
So... are you agreeing?
I'll consider it.
Thank you, Professor Qin!
Please think it over.
Yes!
I have to admit,
this feels so good.
It does feel nice.
It's all thanks to Gan Yang.
He will come later. We'd better watch our words.
You mean Director Gan, right?
Honestly, his cold face this morning scared me.
I really feared he'd break with us.
He pays a lot when we try his shoes.
We can't afford to offend him.
He won't.
If he does cut ties with us, who will test all that junk of his?
Buddy, keep your voice down.
Did you forget we almost got in trouble this morning?
He's not even here yet. Relax, all right?
Rotten shoes are rotten shoes.
Why can't we say that?
You still defend them after all they did?
They act nice to your face, but do you know what they say behind your back?
They say you'll never make good shoes.
We've been here awhile.
Gan Yang still hasn't arrived.
True. What's taking him so long?
Here he is.
- Director Gan.
You're finally here.
We've been waiting quite a while.
Go get changed.
Director Gan, the new batch of shoes are really good.
When the next version comes out, we're happy to test them.
That's not necessary.
I won't trouble you with such small things anymore.
Come on, we're buddies.
We're more than willing to help you.
Director Gan, what's that in your hands?
This?
Shoes.
No.
More accurately,
it's the junk you were just talking about.
Since you clearly disdain the shoes,
I won't have you try them anymore.
I'll take the shoes back.
Wait, if you take them, what will we wear?
That's your problem.
- Come on, hurry.
- Gan Yang,
did that girl say anything to you?
She has nothing to do with this.
- Gan Yang!
- Don't go after him.
Hello?
Ding Zhi Tong,
thank you for helping me truly see those guys.
Do you mean those guys on the track team?
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
They're not worth feeling bad over.
Exactly. I'm glad you think so.
Gan Yang?
Gan Yang? Why aren't you saying anything?
Ding Zhi Tong.
Thank you.
You've already thanked me once.
Don't mention it.
I've made comments on yesterday's assignment.
Can someone help hand it out?
I will.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
There's a finance networking event soon.
All the attendees are major players in the industry.
It's a great chance to gain insight at this event.
And you can make connections to help with future job prospects.
I happen to have an invitation here.
And I can take one person with me.
To keep things fair, I've decided that
whoever ranks first in the upcoming due diligence simulation
can go with me.
Professor, can guys participate, too?
- Gender doesn't matter.
- Professor Qin.
Do you disagree with my decision?
Not at all.
In that case, move a bit more quickly, please.
Professor Qin.
Don't you have something to say to me?
Now that you mention it, I do.
I had been struggling to find someone to take with me.
Thanks for reminding me I can take a student.
You tricked me?
If you didn't want to take me, you could have just told me.
Maybe you misunderstood.
First, I agreed that I'd consider it,
but I never promised you anything.
Second, you made valid points,
but you're not my only student.
And last, the simulation hasn't even started yet.
Are you saying you will eventually lose?
Are you provoking me?
I swear I will win.
Watch and see!
Hurry and wash a few more.
Okay. Are you sure you know how to make it?
Of course. You've tasted my cooking before.
Since I can cook, I can make jam.
Are cooking and jam-making the same?
You'll see when you taste it.
It will be good too.
Delicious.
- Add more sugar.
- Okay.
I like sweet stuff.
- Try it.
- You go first.
- You've worked hard.
- I go first?
Yes, you get the first bite.
All right.
Well, how is it? Is it good?
No.
It's terrible.
No way.
- Let me try it.
- It's awful.
- You'd better not.
Trust me, Pal. You'd better not.
I don't believe you. Let me try.
It's really bad.
Just one small spoonful, okay?
Fine, one small spoonful.
Use this spoon.
W-Wait. This is also a spoon.
Who's there? Come out!
That darned Qin Chang.
Old fashioned.
I went out of my way to impress him.
Seriously, when have I ever been so humiliated?
You rotten man.
Tong Tong, perfect timing.
I say that Qin Chang has really gone too far!
Ming Mei.
Wait, what happened to your hand?
I was so clumsy.
I tripped on the way back.
It should be okay.
Does it hurt?
- I'll take you to the clinic. Come on.
- No need for that.
It's so late. Let's just disinfect it.
- Do you have iodine?
- I do.
Come on. Sit down.
Gan Yang.
Gan Yang?
I can eat this delicious jam myself.
Gan Yang!
Why are you here?
I made some plum jam and brought you some.
I'll take this call.
Hello? What do you want?
Where did you hide the jam?
- Do you even have a conscience?
- Shut up.
Wrong number.
You changed your ringtone?
I thought that song was nice so I changed it.
I can't believe you know archery, surfing,
skiing, shoe design, and you can make jam.
How did you know I ski, surf, and do archery?
I found out by accident.
Here, take the jam.
Thanks.
What happened to your hand?
Nothing.
The light didn't work on the path back to the dorm. I tripped and fell.
It's fine.
Thanks.
Oh, be sure to keep it in the fridge.
It tastes even better cold.
Okay. I'll try that.
- I'm going.
- Bye bye.
Bye bye.
The light doesn't work?
Gan Yang, where did you hide the jam?
- I ate it.
- I'm not talking to you anymore.
I didn't even get one bite.
Stop.
Let's go ghost hunting tonight.
What ghost?
It's okay.
It's just stray cats and dogs.
- Shut up.
- Be quiet.
Who's there?
I see you. Come out!
Say something.
Don't move.
Keep your voice down.
We don't want anyone to see.
Speak louder. Say it louder.
You're so bad. So annoying.
Don't touch me.
Others will see.
- What are you trying?
- What are you guys doing?
Why are you following Ding Zhi Tong?
I don't know what you're saying.
You don't know what I'm saying?
- Wang Yi.
- We knew you wouldn't admit it.
We already set up security cameras here.
If I send this video to your coach,
your career is over.
Don't, Director Gan.
I was wrong. Aren't we buddies?
I just wanted to scare her. That's all.
"Scare her"?
Li Fei, we can keep the video a secret.
But stalking won't just be forgiven.
What are you going to do?
No.
Stop. I was wrong.
Director Gan, I'm sorry.
I thought someone was stalking me,
but it was just a couple.
"A couple"?
Did you see who they were?
It was so awkward. Why would I stay to find out?
But it was right before dorm curfew.
Were they still on a date?
Don't they fear getting locked out?
Isn't this situation resolved? Why are we still here?
Look, the whole road is empty.
Ding Zhi Tong will surely feel scared when she passes by.
If someone's talking nearby, she won't fear.
But we can't keep doing this forever.
How long are we staying here?
Shouldn't be too long. I already reported it to the school.
Once they fix the streetlight, our job's done.
You care about her so much.
Why not just walk her back yourself?
You think I don't want to?
I don't want to appear too obvious and pressure her.
Like that, no wonder you're still single.
She's coming. Be ready.
Say something.
- About what?
- Like what you said before.
Come on.
I'm angry.
- Don't hug me.
- Louder.
Even louder.
You scoundrel.
- No, please.
- She's coming.
- She's here.
- Don't kiss me.
- She's right here.
- No.
What are you two doing?
Weren't you supposed to go that way?
Who said I would come that way.
So it was you two last night, too?
- No.
- Yes.
Your girlfriend is quite unique.
It's so embarrassing.
Your dorm is about to lock down, right?
I'll walk you back.
Okay.
So why did you ask the track team guys to test your shoes?
It's hard to run an OEM business now.
I told my mom we should transform
to develop our own R&amp;D.
But she thinks OEM is already good enough.
So I started experimenting on my own.
I got them to try the shoes
to collect performance data.
But I never thought
they'd be so mean.
That's not your fault.
Don't overthink it.
So did you tear apart the shoes
for research data too?
Did you watch videos I posted online?
In the future, I want to create my own sports shoe brand
and build a sports science lab.
Wang Yi? Wang Yi is a Ph.D. student in material science here.
He is my research partner.
You know what midsole material is?
It's actually the core of a running shoe.
That's what we are working on.
Whether the brand works or not actually depends on that.
Have you ever considered
your main customer target group?
For investment in a product or a company,
the first detail is its target group.
I've thought about that.
Our brand mainly targets two groups:
First are athletes.
Second are running enthusiasts.
But our focus is tech-driven running shoes.
It helps athletes improve speed
while keeping them safe.
So you make shoes for people who love running.
But have you ever thought,
what if someone who doesn't like running
puts on your shoes and enjoys it?
You're right.
If someone who hates running starts to love it
after wearing the shoes I make,
that's very meaningful.
Exactly. That means your market gets wider.
You'll make way more money.
That's true.
Then would you help me test the shoes?
Me?
Yes.
Can I even do that?
Why can't you?
I'll take that as a yes then.
When I finish my first pair of shoes,
you'll be the very first one to test them.
Deal.
Ding Zhi Tong,
you must look amazing when you run.
I'll wait for the day...
you truly want to run with me.
Come on, I'll walk you back.
Thanks for walking me back.
Okay. I've arrived.
I'm going in.
Okay.
- Bye bye.
By the way,
I've got a mock interview at the café tomorrow afternoon.
Okay.
I see.
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
All right, see you tomorrow.
I'm leaving.
Bye bye.
Why are you still here?
Why don't you go back?
See you tomorrow.
I'm leaving now. See you tomorrow.
Which department are you from?
Why are you yelling so late?
Running off?
Hello. I'm Ding Zhi Tong.
Hello. Welcome to the interview.
Please, have a seat.
That's not quite right.
Press palms together.
Align the thumb webs, firm and steady.
Hold for a second without shaking.
Most importantly, look the person in the eye with confidence and sincerity.
And don't forget to smile.
It's just a handshake.
I didn't know there was so much to it.
It's actually the most important part of business etiquette.
It sets the tone for your first impression.
You really know your stuff.
When it's my turn to interview, I definitely need your advice.
Anytime.
Can I take a look?
Here's your lemon water. Enjoy.
- Thanks.
What's wrong? It won't turn on?
Yes. It happens a lot lately. I don't know what's wrong.
I might really need to get it repaired.
Let me see. I know how to fix it.
Can you fix computers?
Then take a look for me.
- Sure.
- I really hope it can be fixed.
I'd rather not replace it.
Well?
Is it fixable?
What's the issue?
Looks like it may have a hard drive problem.
"Hard drive problem"?
Are my files still there?
Yes. But I might need to open it up to fix it.
How... how about this?
If you don't need to use it right now,
I can take it home tonight, fix and return it tomorrow.
Then I will have to trouble you with this.
Thank you.
No problem.
Gan Yang, what happened that's so important?
Finally, you're back.
Thanks for your effort. Give me your bag.
Sit.
You must be thirsty. Have some water.
Here.
Don't you love meat?
I made you a steak, medium rare.
All right, get to the point.
Do you know how to fix a laptop?
Take a look.
Whose is this? It's so old.
It's been used for ages.
It's Ding Zhi Tong's.
I guessed that.
Buddy, other people chase girls with flowers and jewelry.
You always do such stuff.
Shut up. Can you fix it or not?
Did you try rebooting or reinstalling the system?
I can't even get it to reboot, let alone reinstall anything.
Then I can't help you.
Aren't you an engineering student? Why can't you fix a laptop?
Who told you engineering students can fix laptops?
I knew you couldn't.
I won't waste time with you.
Hold on.
I can't fix it, but I know someone who can.
All right, give it a try.
He is a professional.
Thanks, Boss. Thank you.
No problem, but look, this laptop is ancient.
The system runs fine now, but it will only get slower.
It might crash completely one day.
Better replace it soon.
So, Boss, I want to ask this question. If I keep the same outer shell
but replace all the internal parts with the latest parts,
how much would that cost?
Seriously?
Boss, ignore him. Just do your work.
Boss, don't listen to him.
How much would it cost?
Well, it won't be cheap. Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
All right, I'll calculate it for you.
Brother, you're seriously devoted.
Is this really my laptop?
Yes.
It boots up so fast now.
All the software runs smoothly. It feels like a brand-new one.
Thank you.
Just some minor issues.
What do you want to eat? Pick anything from the cafeteria, my treat.
Ding Zhi Tong, can you be a little more creative?
Who treats others in the cafeteria every time?
Then what do you want to eat?
Let me see. But it can't be too expensive.
Actually, a movie is showing.
It's called, "I Like You."
I heard it's quite good.
Why don't we watch it together?
I've already checked.
Twenty-five yuan per ticket. Half price for us.
"Us"?
I m-mean student discount.
That sounds like a deal.
Okay, then it's on me.
- I'll go get the tickets.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
One large popcorn, please.
That'll be ¥56. You can scan here.
Hello, Advisor? What's going on?
A court document addressed to you has arrived at my office.
It looks like a court summons.
Come pick it up.
"A court summons"?
That must be a mistake.
Do you know Zhao Hai?
He's my uncle.
You'd better come now.
If this isn't handled properly, it could affect your graduation.
I understand.
- Ready to go?
- Gan Yang, I'm really sorry.
I can't watch the movie with you. I need to go back.
I'm leaving now.
Ding Zhi Tong.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by 💖 Heart's Journey 💖 Team @Viki.com
"Someone" by Tia Ray
♫  The long-lost memories suddenly resurfaced  ♫
♫  That was when we were searching for a crack in love  ♫
♫  The one who ran back then just wanted to stop  ♫
♫  Even brushing past, we couldn't help but look back  ♫
♫  But we failed to hold on to that tenderness in time  ♫
♫  Hidden in plain sight, yet too hard to say aloud  ♫
♫  Someone stayed by your side without reservation  ♫
♫  Someone lost all the warmth those moments once held  ♫
♫  It took every ounce of courage to let go of all the pain  ♫
♫  So I could fulfill all your future  ♫
♫  Someone once said, "Please forget me"  ♫
♫  And every time I think of it  ♫
♫  Someone stood behind me with no reservation  ♫
♫  Someone held my hand against all odds  ♫
♫  Now I’m left alone, piecing together the memories we once had  ♫
♫  Along the road we used to run through  ♫
♫  There is always the someone I never once forgot  ♫