"Don't Let Me Go" by Arthur Chen, Sabrina Zhuang
♫  My affection for you lies quietly in my heart  ♫
♫  And you just happened to pass by there  ♫
♫  So effortlessly  ♫
♫  Awaken the feelings with just one smile  ♫
♫  Oh, I once tucked my true heart away  ♫
♫  But your quiet intuition found its hidden path  ♫
♫  How lucky  ♫
♫  That person turned out to be you  ♫
♫  Our tightly-held hearts folded the distance between us  ♫
♫  Every heartbeat writes the words of our daily life  ♫
♫  And just for now I want to hold you tight  ♫
♫  Come let me see you in the morning light  ♫
♫  If our eyes can't hold back love  ♫
♫  Then let it pour in like a flood  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫
♫  Eye to eye  ♫
♫  Come feel my heart  ♫
♫  Burning bright  ♫
♫  Our hearts beat in perfect sync  ♫
♫  It's obvious because I'm thinking of you  ♫
♫  So don't let me go  ♫
Bro.
I'm out, too.
It's no fun being in Training Box without you.
I'll wait for you guys in Shanghai.
We will be back in Shanghai soon.
Let's fight together again then.
I believe that day will come soon.
Don't be upset.
We will come back.
Wang Yi is right.
We will return soon.
As long as we stick together,
we don't fear anything.
Okay.
It's getting late.
Let's go.
Gan Yang isn't easily defeated.
He will definitely come back.
It's not that easy to return.
All right.
Hello.
Gan Yang, tickets are ready.
Let's go then.
Okay.
♫  The time and time  ♫
Ding Zhi Tong.
Goodbye.
♫  Life and life  ♫
♫  I had it once. I lost it though  ♫
Goodbye.
Gan Yang.
What's your bed number and name?
Song Ming Mei. Bed 6.
All right.
All done. The chemo meds are in.
Let us know if you feel any discomfort.
Please tell me your bed number and name again.
Song Ming Mei. Bed 6.
All right.
Am I done with the IV?
How do you feel?
Any discomfort?
It's not as scary as they say online.
Chemotherapy isn't that terrifying.
Look, I'm fine.
Can you pass me the mirror?
Do I look beautiful?
Gorgeous.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Nurse!
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Just messing with you.
You're sure you're okay?
Just joking.
I'm hungry.
Please don't joke like that again, okay?
What do you want to eat?
Hey, don't be angry.
I'm craving wontons from across the street.
Wait here. I'll go get them.
Are you all right?
I didn't want you to see me like this.
It's okay.
- You were promoted to S.A.
- What are you guys looking at?
Sister Tong.
Sister Tong, have you read the company document?
- I've been promoted to S.A.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations to you, too, Sister Tong.
- To me?
- Yes. You've been promoted to MD.
Didn't you read the company email?
See, I didn't lie to you.
How so?
I quit Training Box.
You did.
But when you quit,
the project was almost finished.
Both sides were satisfied with your valuation.
The signing went smoothly too.
So we unanimously agreed you should be M.D. You earned the promotion.
Congratulations, Ding Zhi Tong.
Congratulations, Sister Tong.
Thank you, all. Thank you, Director Zhang.
Let's celebrate tonight.
Sure.
Back to work.
Excuse me, who's Ding Zhi Tong?
- It's me.
- There's a delivery for you.
Ding Zhi Tong, right? Here you go.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
♫  Only after the burning, the fireworks come  ♫
♫  Beauty always comes with its cost  ♫
♫  Every fall brings scars but also gives me  ♫
♫  A strong armor  ♫
Tong Tong.
Congratulations.
Gan Yang.
You know,
becoming M.D. has always been my dream.
But now that I've achieved it,
I can't seem to be happy about it.
Why aren't you happy?
♫  Joy and sorrow will eventually become  ♫
♫  A moment of memory  ♫
♫  But I want too much  ♫
♫  How can I stop?  ♫
Gan Yang.
♫  I accept  ♫
How have you been?
♫  The gap of losing after every gain  ♫
♫  The story twists and turns, but it isn't a fairy tale  ♫
♫  I matter most, and everything else comes behind  ♫
♫  I'm glad flowers once bloomed on my path  ♫
♫  But they are not worth looking back  ♫
♫  I allow moments of weakness, pain and struggle  ♫
♫  If I can't forget, just let it be  ♫
♫  After taking some wrong turns  ♫
♫  Then I know where to go  ♫
Gan Yang, I miss you so much.
♫  I'll arrive by myself  ♫
You're here early.
Morning.
- What's wrong?
- You're trying to scald me?
I'm really sorry.
You know, it's too cruel to show affection in front of him.
Let's tone it down a bit.
Have some water.
Didn't you say he fell asleep only at 7 a.m.?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you need sleep?
I dozed off a bit last night but couldn't really sleep.
I didn't want to waste time so I came back.
You still need rest then.
Take some melatonin.
No, thanks. I have a meeting with Design at 9 a.m.
Don't worry about me.
I'm in good shape.
I can't stop thinking of the design, R&amp;D, and the production line.
I'm just too hyped to sleep.
I'll have Luo Hao Chen reschedule the meeting to afternoon.
Take the melatonin and go to sleep now.
Really, no need.
You know the serious result of disobeying Xi.
I advise you to listen to her.
Go to sleep now.
All right.
I can't win against you two.
I'll take one and nap on the couch.
Wake me up before the meeting.
Come in.
The Zhongya new energy project needs your signature.
Sure.
Didn't sleep well again last night?
I heard sour dates help with sleep.
Why don't you try them?
I've tried all kinds of sleeping pills.
They only let me sleep for two hours.
I dare not take too many.
With all that coffee during the day, no wonder you can't sleep at night.
This vicious cycle can't continue.
Maybe you should try traditional Chinese medicine?
I've seen both TCM and Western doctors.
It's okay. It's a mental thing.
It'll get better.
Go ahead with your work.
I'll be leaving.
Let's talk.
Do you have feelings for me?
Yes.
But I don't feel that way.
I know you don't like me now.
But that doesn't mean you never will.
Hello, Ma'am.
Here's your coffee.
Enjoy, Sir.
This is the very coffee you ordered last time.
I still remembered.
Actually, I never liked coffee before.
I found it too bitter.
It seemed useless except for keeping me awake.
I started drinking it
because Gan Yang once prepared a surprise for me at a café.
I started to like coffee because of him.
So...
If I give you enough time,
maybe you will start to like something else
and replace coffee.
Not just coffee,
the breathing technique I taught you when we first met,
running, the food I like, and learning to live well,
Gan Yang taught me all these.
So I think a relationship isn't just about memories,
but becoming more like that person.
But those memories are in the past, aren't they?
Even so,
I still like Gan Yang now.
And I'll always like him.
Have I made myself clear?
Thanks for the coffee.
But I won't have it.
Even so,
I still like Gan Yang now.
And I'll always like him.
Have I made myself clear?
Chairman.
Ask Director Zhan from Shuchi to come see me later.
Got it.
Ding Zhi Tong, I've got a foolproof life hack.
Do you want to try it?
What is it?
Feet slightly apart.
Hands on hips.
Take a deep breath.
What are you trying to do?
Head up.
Lastly, you shout,
"Ding Zhi Tong, come on!"
Ding Zhi Tong, come on!
♫  I wish I could spend every  ♫
♫  Dusk and dawn with you  ♫
♫  Like a world with just us  ♫
♫  And a clock without hands  ♫
♫  I wish I could stay with you  ♫
♫  To feel the lingering warmth of love  ♫
♫  My longing keeps knocking on the door  ♫
♫  When it comes to love  ♫
♫  I hide but speak from the heart  ♫
Gan Yang, look at this.
♫  Let us remain forever in this moment  ♫
Don't throw your back out. Take it easy.
Come on, let's go.
Let me help you.
Sun Hao. Why are you here?
Bro, is LT really struggling this much?
The CEO and the R&amp;D director are doing this themselves.
Yes, it's tough.
How about you invest more?
And I'll give you another 5% stake.
There you go again with the sarcasm.
Don't listen to him. He suffers from insomnia.
I make him work hard so he can sleep better at night.
Is insomnia that easy to cure?
Your insomnia is especially hard to treat.
Go away.
So why are you here?
I came to see you.
I've missed you all so much after such a long time.
It's obvious he's all talk.
- How can you come empty-handed?
- Hey...
- Wang Yi, you...
- You couldn't even bring a cold drink.
- In this heat?
- You punk...
Not good!
- Watch out.
- Shuchi just launched new shoes
and promoted them on Training Box.
Take a look.
Yuan Chao actually partnered with Shuchi?
It must be Wang Sen's doing.
And Shuchi is directly targeting our product line
at one-third our prices.
They're after blood.
Bro, what should we do next?
They can't keep up the price war for long.
But our cash flow is tight right now.
Let's avoid head-on collisions with them in the domestic market.
Chen Xi, keep the marketing going.
We keep highlighting our shoes' advantages.
Also, clear the inventory.
- See how long this price war can last.
- All right.
Wang Yi, at this stage, R&amp;D is all on you now.
Don't worry.
When 7.0 comes out, I'll slap them in the face again.
Bro, I've saved some money over the years.
I'm also part of LT.
Take it for now.
Thanks, Buddy.
- Come on.
Keep moving.
Let me help you.
- Then I'll go.
- Okay.
Fighting!
That one is heavy.
Be careful.
Sister, what do you want to eat? I'll order.
Anything is fine.
All right.
Hello, Ming Mei, can you do me a favor?
What's up? Just tell me.
The user profiles of Matching and Gan Yang's shoes overlap perfectly.
I want you to do a marketing promotion for him.
Can you give me a friendly rate?
You're this worried about Gan Yang?
Why don't you just be with him? Stop struggling.
Worrying is one thing.
You know we can't be together.
You haven't moved on, and he still likes you.
How is that impossible?
Besides, your mother hoped you two will be together.
Why do you act like it's a drama and you ship us?
Anyway, you can't blame me for what I say or do now.
Why not?
Because I have cancer.
What are you saying?
Don't say such things. Knock on wood!
Stage 3 breast cancer.
I'm undergoing chemo for a while now.
The surgery was booked for next week.
I wasn't going to tell you.
But what if the surgery fails?
Then you wouldn't get to see me a last time.
Which hospital are you in?
I'll come back today.
Don't joke around.
Aren't you making money?
Don't you dare disturb me.
I'm perfectly happy here with Qin Chang, just us two.
Stop that.
Send me the hospital address, now.
I'm not at the hospital now.
Just focus on your work, okay?
Right now I just want to enjoy life.
I'm hanging up.
Jia Xin, book me a flight back to Shanghai.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Director Zhang, may I take two weeks off?
My friend is sick and needs care.
Don't worry. I'll make sure all my work is covered and not delayed.
Have some soup.
- Here.
- Mom, I want more of this.
It's okay, you guys eat. I'll get the door.
- Ms. Ding.
- Ma'am.
- Careful, it's hot.
- Professor Qin.
Long time, no see.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It's okay.
Stop crying.
If you keep being like this, I'll feel bad, too.
The doctor said I can't have many emotional fluctuations.
I've searched about your illness on Internet.
The cure rate is quite high.
Let's treat it as a chronic disease.
You'll surely get better.
You can't even say the word "cancer."
I've fully accepted it.
Yu Lin doesn't know yet, does she?
No.
I want to protect her.
But if the surgery fails,
I'm expecting you to raise her.
What are you talking about?
How would the surgery fail? It can only succeed.
Ming Mei, no matter what happens, I'll face it with you.
Well, it's all right now.
Why are you taking photos of the medical records?
For insurance claims.
Peel me another apple, will you?
Sure. Cut down on screen time.
Excuse me. Where's Ward 12, Bed 6?
The second one on the right.
You got here fast.
Shouldn't a pre-op patient focus on herself, not meddling?
Hey, you. Okay, stop looking.
I'm the patient here.
Song Ming Mei, I wish you a successful surgery.
The doctor just called me for an examination.
You two chat.
Don't. I can manage on my own.
Have a good talk.
Did you just cry?
I'm going downstairs.
Ming Mei has been acting up lately.
Don't mind her.
I thought it was you who was sick.
You scared me to death.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm fine.
She had some tests a few days ago and dragged me along.
All my indicators are normal.
That's good.
Has your insomnia improved recently?
Much better.
I don't even need to take sleeping pills.
How about you?
Has Shuchi's new shoes launch impacted you?
You wouldn't believe me if I said no.
But it's fine.
We can handle it.
Ming Mei's surgery is day after tomorrow.
Let's talk after that.
All right.
I'm leaving.
Take care of yourself.
You, too.
- Keep running.
- Eat properly.
Don't worry.
I'll keep running, and I'll keep waiting for you, always waiting.
I'm leaving.
Bye bye.
Where's Gan Yang?
He left.
Don't do that again. It makes me feel really bad.
Your mother wouldn't want you to stay like this.
I know.
I still don't feel right about it.
Give me some time. I'll get there.
All right.
I won't push you.
I was actually thinking of asking you and Gan Yang to take wedding photos with me.
"Wedding photos"?
Downstairs, I was just thinking
that if the surgery fails,
these two days would be when I'm at my best.
Qin Chang and I never took proper photos together.
We want to have wedding photos as a keepsake.
The surgery won't fail.
You two are both so confident.
All right. If it fails or not,
I want photos.
I want to do it right here.
Come on.
Don't worry. I'll be waiting outside.
Don't worry. It'll surely go smoothly.
It's done.
Doctor, how did it go?
Don't worry. The surgery was a success.
The tumor has been completely removed.
It'll probably take another half hour for her to fully wake from anesthesia.
Okay, thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
You can go to the ward and wait.
- Great!
- Okay.
Qin Chang.
How are you feeling?
I'm falling for you again.
The doctor said yesterday's surgery took a full eight hours.
How was it?
Were you scared?
I was worried sick.
But when the doctor came out and said it was successful,
it felt like getting a second chance.
Watching you hold Professor Qin's hand made me wonder
whom I'd want to see first if I woke from surgery.
Knock on wood.
Don't curse yourself like that.
The new version of Matching is live.
You promised to help me test it.
You've just had surgery and already think of work?
Just log in and give me some feedback.
Okay. I'm logging in now.
It's been years since I last logged in.
Let me think. I need to remember my password. Bye bye.
Tong Tong, Old Chen agreed to lend me the money.
All the effort finally paid off.
I wish you were here with me.
Tong Tong.
I got drunk again last night.
Sitting on the office floor,
I felt like you were by my side.
You touched my face
and said to me,
"Since when"
"does this small thing scare you?"
I just feel so absurd.
I promised to protect you,
but it turns out I'm the coward here.
Tong Tong, I know you deleted your Matching account.
But every time I miss you,
I still log in to look.
Tong Tong.
My stomach acts up again.
I ran into a high school classmate at the hospital.
He was shocked to see me.
He asked me why I was so frail
and if I still ran.
I dreamed of you again last night.
In the dream, you said to me,
"Gan Yang, promise me."
"You'll keep running."
Gan Yang, you have a really big appetite.
It's three times of mine.
If you eat like this, won't you become a plump middle-aged man?
With all my exercise, what I eat turns into muscle.
Feel it.
All right. Then promise me you'll never stop running.
You keep running.
All right, I promise I'll keep running.
I promise you I'll keep running,
and running
until no distance is left between us.
Tong Tong, we live only once.
I hope you can let go of the past
and love the one you're meant to love.
Ding Zhi Tong,
it's time for you to run once more for Gan Yang.
"Someone" by Tia Ray
♫  The long-lost memories suddenly resurfaced  ♫
♫  That was when we were searching for a crack in love  ♫
♫  The one who ran back then just wanted to stop  ♫
♫  Even brushing past, we couldn't help but look back  ♫
♫  But we failed to hold on to that tenderness in time  ♫
♫  Hidden in plain sight, yet too hard to say aloud  ♫
♫  Someone stayed by your side without reservation  ♫
♫  Someone lost all the warmth those moments once held  ♫
♫  It took every ounce of courage to let go of all the pain  ♫
♫  So I could fulfill all your future  ♫
♫  Someone once said, "Please forget me"  ♫
♫  And every time I think of it  ♫
♫  Someone stood behind me with no reservation  ♫
♫  Someone held my hand against all odds  ♫
♫  Now I’m left alone, piecing together the memories we once had  ♫
♫  Along the road we used to run through  ♫
♫  There is always the someone I never once forgot  ♫