=Love's Little Delicacies=
=Episode 9=
You go ahead with your work.
I need to record more footage.
I told you to simply fix anything
to eat.
What are you doing?
Eating to be full is just
an animal instinct.
Enjoying gourmet food is human nature.
A corporate slave like you
wouldn't understand.
Where did you hear that phrase?
My first love.
Oh, your first love.
I see, I see.
(Daoli Little Panda.
Animals eat to live, humans live to eat.)
Do you know your first love's last name?
The last name is Dao.
No, that's not it.
I don't know either.
Have you met them?
No.
You don't know if it's a man or a woman.
You don't even know her last name,
and you call that your first love.
It's a feeling,
a taste.
Strange.
Why does this taste feel so familiar?
(Didn't you teach me this?)
I think
to own
those delicate hands,
she must be a petite and exquisite girl.
Someone who can write such healing words
must be a gentle,
quiet, and delicate girl.
What kind of guy do you like?
You haven't answered my question yet.
This taste is really familiar.
What kind of guy do you like?
Can't you just tell me?
You're so persistent, young man.
Fine.
I'll tell you.
A guy who's 165 cm tall,
has tanned skin,
likes RnB,
has tattoos,
and curly hair.
So? Can you imagine what he looks like?
How can you like that kind of person?
Am I not good enough?
Are you okay?
Move aside. Stop taking advantage of me.
Hi, we meet again, Shi Guang.
What's up?
Hey, Linda.
(I asked you to sabotage
Ji Yu and Shi Guang's collaboration,)
not to go on vacation.
If you mess up again,
you'll be the next to get fired.
How am I supposed to sabotage it?
Aren't you good at being a "green tea"?
[*conniving behavior]
Do I have to teach you?
Shi Guang has
five million followers now.
With that fan base,
it would easily be seen
as the work of anti-fans
if we start attacking him.
We need to find a way
to generate negative publicity for him,
like
a scandal or a romance.
(How to be a perfect "green tea"?)
Shi Guang,
will your girlfriend be mad
if I do this?
Shi Guang is on his way
to Laifuping right now.
Looks like I'll have
to sacrifice myself a bit.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
If I said my skills are rusty
because I haven't driven in a long time,
do you believe me?
The rear light is damaged.
We need to find a repair shop to fix it.
I'll make a phone call.
Okay.
You better behave yourself.
Shi Guang,
there's smoke coming out from my car.
Can you help me fix it?
I'm really scared being here
in the middle of nowhere.
Open the hood.
If you help me fix the car,
won't your girlfriend be mad at you?
Don't speak nonsense.
Okay.
But the person you like
doesn't seem to like you.
Yes, our is now at...
Are you done?
I finished the call.
They said there's a repair shop nearby.
We can just drive the car over there.
It's getting late.
Why don't we find a place to stay?
We don't have the budget.
I have money.
As compensation,
I'll pay for your stay.
No thanks.
I don't want to stay
with someone like you.
Here you go.
I've booked the rooms for you.
Thanks.
I'm hungry. Go make some food.
I have to thank you for fixing my car.
Otherwise,
I would have had to squeeze
into a tent with you guys tonight.
No need to be polite.
We should help each other out.
It's cold.
Ms. Linda,
why don't you put on an extra layer?
Young people are full of energy.
We're not afraid of the cold.
But someone old like you
should dress warmly.
Shi Guang,
I want to eat spicy broad noodles.
Can you make it for me?
Sure, go ahead and make it for her.
By the way, use less red oil.
I remember Ms. Linda saying
she was on a diet
during her live stream.
Shi Guang's cooking is really good,
especially these spicy broad noodles.
You must have worked so hard.
Have more meat.
Too much meat is greasy.
Eating vegetables is healthy.
If you want to eat,
you should eat
the spicy broad noodles you made.
Eating such greasy noodles late
at night,
aren't you afraid
of getting pimples the next day?
I'm full.
I'll go and get my beauty sleep.
All right, bye.
I'm done eating.
You can eat by yourself.
Fine.
Don't eat then.
I thought you said
you were going to get your beauty sleep.
I can't sleep.
So I want to enjoy the moonlight.
Can't I do that?
Here's
a bowl of Saozi noodles made
from a special secret recipe
just for you.
Thanks. But I'm already full.
Full?
Full from what?
Is it jealousy?
Jealousy? Jealous of what?
Jealous of you and Linda?
Or
is it him?
Tanned skin,
someone who's 165 cm tall,
and curly hair.
Get lost.
You like me, don't you?
Come on.
Have a bite.
Otherwise, the noodles will get soggy.
You can let me down.
But don't let the food go to waste.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just suddenly thought
of my mom.
Ji Yu,
then
let me make delicious food for you
on your mom's behalf from now on.
Okay.
♪I'm drenched under the heavy rain♪
♪But I remain silent♪
♪Who can tolerate
my eccentric personality?♪
♪I care too much about right and wrong♪
♪Like complex polarized colours♪
♪I can't sketch out
the original network♪
♪Am I your first choice?♪
♪I put out the fire in your gaze♪
♪Let's give each other
our last blessing♪
♪You've said countless times
that we're not right for each other♪
♪But I still struggle for an outcome♪
♪Is there medicine
that can heal my new wound?♪
♪Releasing our passion
to quench our thirst♪
♪The deeper we immerse,
the lonelier we become♪
♪Let's say it's all my fault♪
♪I want more than just a companion♪
♪I stubbornly need
a partner who fits perfectly♪
♪I will take all the blame♪
♪What can I do with you?♪