=Love's Little Delicacies=
=Episode 14=
Say that again.
Where did the money we earned
from the live stream last night go?
To commemorate our first time,
I bought a meteorite.
It was a good deal.
There's also
(50 yuan Voucher)
a 50 yuan voucher for Rolls Royce.
That was the money
for our hotel stay tonight.
Can't you make things easier for me?
Where will we stay now
without money?
Uh...
I don't know.
(Management Office)
(Free for Couple)
We'll stay here.
This is the place you found?
Free for couples?
For people like us
who are trying to become a couple,
it should be free too.
Are you here to participate
in the event?
Couples have to kiss for a minute
and post a photo on their social media.
If you get more than twenty likes
and tag our location,
you can stay for free.
Did you do this on purpose?
Give me your phone.
I'll take the picture for you.
Hurry up and kiss. I'm recording.
Recording a video too?
You have a lot of tricks, huh?
Only tricks for you.
Are you a dog?
Don't rush.
We still have 30 seconds left.
Okay, your one minute is up.
Dude, you're quite professional.
Looks like you've never been
in a relationship.
How did you know?
The timing
should be changed to five minutes.
A fan asked,
"Why do you want
to become a food blogger?"
I remember back in high school,
I stayed in the dorms.
The cafeteria food was terrible
and the portions were small.
So every time I got hungry at night,
I would watch food videos.
I remember following a blogger
named Daoli Little Panda.
I'm not sure if any
of you have heard of her.
Daoli Little Panda?
She's the one I mentioned before,
who said,
"Eating to fill up is just
an animal instinct,
but enjoying food is human nature".
Her food videos kept me company
(Daoli Little Panda)
through every hungry night.
Since then,
I wanted to become a food blogger.
If you had the chance,
would you want to meet her?
You know her?
I said, if.
If I could meet her,
of course, I'd love to.
Where's my chili powder?
Didn't you bring it?
It should be in the car.
I'll get it.
It's okay.
I'll go and get it myself.
At the same time, I can...
Be careful.
It's okay.
Ji Yu.
Xia Mu?
I forbid you from being with him.
I made you who you are.
- It was me.
- Let me go.
You can only be with me.
It's over between us. So let me go.
Go to Beijing with me, okay?
After we get back,
I'll announce
that you're my girlfriend.
We've worked together for eight years
and dated for five years.
You can't just leave like this.
I don't want to hear all of these.
- Please.
-  let me go.
Let her go!
Shi Guang.
Are you okay?
Xia Mu,
I really hate
the way you are now.
Didn't you say I am important to you
and you'll never leave me?
Why didn't you say that
when you fired her?
That was to teach her a lesson,
to correct her mistakes.
Do you still not understand
who is in the wrong, Xia Mu?
Do you remember the you who loved food?
You've long forgotten.
That person
can ruthlessly harm his peers
for a bit of resources
and roles now.
To gain more benefits,
he can easily
abandon quality content.
You even...
You even
repeatedly hurt me.
Girlfriend?
Don't you think it's a joke?
Ji Yu, I...
I remember you once said,
whether in poverty or wealth,
we would always be together.
Only now do I realize
what you meant by "together"
wasn't the same.
What you want is a submissive lover
who doesn't fight or argue.
I accompany you
when you need
and I'm kicked aside when you don't.
Am I something to cover up?
You want the warmth of a girlfriend
while maintaining your boyfriend image
in front of your fans.
Why do you dare to act
but not take responsibility?
Have you ever considered me
over all these years?
Ji Yu,
I'm sorry.
Can you give me another chance?
Come back with me.
♪You've said countless times
that we're not right for each other♪
♪But I still struggle for an outcome♪
Hello?
Mr. Xia, come back now.
Mr. Xu wants to terminate
the contract with you.
Okay, I'll be right over.
♪Releasing our passion
to quench our thirst♪
♪The deeper we immerse,
the lonelier we become♪
♪Let's say it's all my fault♪
Ji Yu,
I'll wait for you in Beijing, okay?
Get lost.
♪I will take all the blame♪
♪What can I do with you?♪
♪Like complex polarized colors♪
♪I can't sketch out
the original network♪
♪Am I your first choice?♪
♪I put out the fire in your gaze♪
♪Let's give each other
our last blessing♪
Today is our first anniversary.
Make a wish.
Then
I wish
that no matter whether we are rich
or poor in the future,
we will grow old together
and stay together for a lifetime.
I wish
that not only will we be together
for a lifetime,
but also work together for a lifetime
and make our account
the company's number one.
Once an agreement is made...
Nothing can stop us.
♪I will take all the blame♪
♪What can I do with you?♪
What's that smell?
Is something on fire?
On fire?
The lamb leg.
I'm roasting lamb leg in the back.
What lamb leg?
It's the car! Put out the fire quickly!
After growing up,
I rarely have the time
to sit down like this
and look at the starry sky.
Yes.
Ji Yu.
Yes?
Actually...
Actually, not all men are jerks.
At least I'm not that kind of person.
If you're willing to trust me,
I'm willing to prove it to you.
Why are you silent?
Instead of thinking
about such boring questions,
why not think about
what we should do next?
The show is not finished yet.
(Flavors of Shaanxi)
We can't give up halfway, can we?
Can't you be a bit more romantic?
Mr. Shi Guang,
if you can get a vehicle
to take us to the city right now,
I'll talk poetry and literature
with you.
You two really know
how to give me trouble.
(Is a broken car not still a car?)
(The repair costs will be deducted
from your salaries.)
(I'm hanging up.)
How are we getting to the final stop?
Isn't our ride here now?
♪I ride across the world,
armed to my teeth♪
Mister, we're going to the food alley.
Okay!
Mister, drive faster.
♪I'm drenched under the heavy rain♪
♪But I remain silent♪
♪Who can tolerate
my eccentric personality?♪
♪I care too much about right and wrong♪
♪Like complex polarized colors♪
♪I can't sketch out
the original network♪
♪Am I your first choice?♪
♪I put out the fire in your gaze♪
♪Let's give each other
our last blessing♪
♪You've said countless times
that we're not right for each other♪
♪But I still struggle for an outcome♪
♪Is there medicine
that can heal my new wound?♪
♪Releasing our passion
to quench our thirst♪
♪The deeper we immerse,
the lonelier we become♪
♪Let's say it's all my fault♪
♪I want more than just a companion♪
♪I stubbornly need
a partner who fits perfectly♪
♪I will take all the blame♪
♪What can I do with you?♪