You gave that USB drive
to me on purpose,
right?
=Half-awake=
=Episode 19=
You hired someone
to kidnap me, didn't you?
Stop trying to frame me.
Your guy got beaten half to death by me
and confessed to everything.
All of this
was planned by you.
Isn't that so?
Then go tell Gu Yixiao
and see if he believes you
or me.
Chu Muzhi,
I wouldn't call it framing you.
Even if I hadn't done this,
you'd still make a move.
I just played along with your game
and completed your plan for you
in advance.
I really underestimated you.
Never thought you'd be this ruthless,
even willing to use yourself.
If not,
how can I survive
among people this shrewd?
That brotherhood you treasure
means nothing when love comes into play.
You've worked for Gu Yixiao,
risking your life for over ten years.
You handled all those dirty deals,
and shouldered the dangers for him.
But you got nothing in return.
And me,
someone he once hated most,
now he follows my every word.
Doesn't that burn you up inside?
Do you really understand
our brotherhood?
Who do you think you are?
Alright.
Let's see then
how strong your brotherhood really is.
I'll be watching closely.
Why are you coming to see me again?
He was willing to risk his life for you.
And you still refuse to let him go?
You've been at Gu Group
for so many years.
You must've gathered
quite a bit from him.
Can you hand it over to me?
Back then,
to get revenge on Yixiao's dad,
I didn't hesitate to use myself
to reach that goal.
But you've seen it.
What did I really gain?
My only son
ends up despising me.
Do you
only have hatred towards Gu Yixiao?
I... I never thought about it.
So, it's not entirely absent.
Right?
Ye...
Miss Ye,
you still have time to step back now.
Maybe
both you and Yixiao
could live a peaceful life.
No matter what you say,
my answer will stay the same.
Gu Yixiao broke the law.
He deserves the consequences.
Are you really trying
to have him killed?
Have you ever considered
that letting Gu Yixiao face justice
might be the best way to save him?
If you really want to help him,
then hand me what you're holding.
By the way,
I've got one last question for you.
Back then,
who was really behind hurting Gu Yixiao?
That's all of it.
This client list seems pretty important.
If they actually use these accounts
to do anything illegal,
this list becomes the clearest proof.
I pulled this out of the shredder.
The list should be in here.
It's impossible to piece back together.
Maybe I could check Mr. Wu's computer.
That's way too risky.
Don't act on impulse.
Let me think of another way.
What other way do you have?
Are you still going
to keep getting involved with him?
Let me help you.
Ye Xingwan,
I like you.
I can't just stand by
and watch the woman I like
being tormented by a monster.
I've dreamt of bringing him to justice,
so you could finally live a normal life.
Xiao Yinan,
I don't like you.
We're not from the same world.
There's no way back for me.
Why did you let her join the project?
It's been so many years.
I've always listened to you.
But I can't just stand by and watch you
being sent to prison by that woman!
I simply can't stand by
and watch Gu Group,
our hard-earned efforts,
be destroyed completely
because of her.
So,
you had someone kidnap her.
You think I did it?
Do you really not trust me at all?
I know
everything you've done.
Chu Muzhi,
I don't want to fight you.
But Ye Xingwan is my bottom line.
You keep hurting her again and again,
and my patience
has its limits too.
I know
your mother betrayed you,
so you trust no one.
But what about me?
We've fought side by side for 15 years.
Chu Muzhi,
through all this time,
I've always trusted you.
Whatever you wanted to do,
I never questioned it.
But this time,
you've crossed my line.
You can go now.
I'll make sure
you get what you deserve.
But I can't let you meddle
in my life anymore.
Alright.
I'll show you
who's actually wrong.
- Dr. Chen.
- Hello.
(Mr. Chu?)
(It's so late at night.)
(Why is he at the hospital?)
♪The fragility stripped away by you♪
♪Keeps dragging me down endlessly♪
♪If not once devoured by blazing flames♪
♪Who would ever understand
this baptism by fire♪
♪You betrayed me so decisively♪
♪With indifference laid bare♪
♪It taught me to stay silent first♪
♪So the explosion would be deafening♪
♪A burning soul tears off
its own shackles♪
♪The stubborn pain♪
♪Hardens into the hottest flame♪
♪Taste the fruit you planted,
don't ask me for mercy♪
♪Just enjoy this searing pain♪
♪See whether blood or tears flow first♪
♪Your screams sound like regret to me♪
♪Greed caused the chaos,
none can run away♪
♪The karma you sowed by your own hands♪
♪Watered to maturity
with blood and tears♪
♪Then ignite the anger forged by hatred♪
♪I'll burn it all down♪