=Half-awake=
=Episode 24=
Pack your things.
We're leaving now.
You rushed back just for this photo?
Chu Muzhi was right.
You're really pitiful.
No.
What Chu Muzhi said isn't true.
Don't believe him.
He... he... he...
He said that just to provoke me.
But it's fine.
I still have you.
You'll stay with me, right?
No way.
No.
None of this is real.
You're lying to me, aren't you?
I am lying to you.
I've been lying to you all along,
Gu Yixiao.
I never loved you.
I could never love you.
Every day I spent with you,
it was all an act.
I forced myself to get close to you,
just to get the evidence against you,
so I could bring you down for good.
No.
That's not true.
You're lying to me, aren't you?
I've already handed the evidence
to the police.
They'll be here any minute.
No matter where you run,
it won't help.
Xingwan.
You said it yourself.
You said you'd always be mine.
You even promised
to marry me.
You can't break your promise.
Gu Yixiao,
how desperate are you for love?
I don't like you.
I never like you at all.
Stop talking.
I even dislike you.
- Stop it.
- I despise you.
Every single day with you,
I'm thinking how to make you disappear.
Stop talking!
I'm giving you two choices now.
Either come with me,
or stay with me till the end.
Which will it be?
I'm not choosing.
Gu Yixiao,
you should turn yourself in
and face the judgment of the law.
Think about what you did to me before.
How do you even have the nerve
to bargain with me now?
You
don't deserve to have love.
I truly wanted to love everyone.
My family.
My brothers, my love.
You must be dying to know
the answer to that question, right?
Why did your mom leave you back then?
Because
she simply didn't love you.
I have one last question for you.
Back then,
who was really trying to hurt Gu Yixiao?
It was me.
He should never have been born.
His very existence was a mistake.
Did you hear that?
No one needs you.
You gave it everything you had,
and still ended up with nothing.
Your whole life,
from start to finish,
has been a complete joke.
You say things like that
because you want to avenge your family?
No, Gu Yixiao.
I only just realized now
that revenge
isn't the only way to fix things.
But you
still have to pay
for the wrongs you've done.
Go ahead.
Turn yourself in.
Confess to what you've done.
Just leave.
Here come the Longevity Noodles.
Xiao, it's your birthday.
You have to eat Longevity Noodles.
That's how you'll grow up
healthy and strong,
and live a long, long life.
A long, long life.
♪If not once devoured by blazing flames♪
♪Who would ever understand
this baptism by fire♪
♪You betrayed me so decisively♪
♪With indifference laid bare♪
♪It taught me to stay silent first♪
♪So the explosion would be deafening♪
Dad.
♪A burning soul tears off
its own shackles♪
♪The stubborn pain
hardens into the hottest flame♪
From the day I met you,
my life completely fell apart.
It was you.
Your appearance
turned me into who I am now.
I don't want to fight you.
But Ye Xingwan is my bottom line.
♪Your screams sound like regret to me♪
♪Greed caused the chaos,
none can run away♪
You believe me now, right?
I do.
But it's already too late.
How could you be this naive?
(Two unread messages)
(Gu Yixiao)
(Xingwan,)
(I want to love you wholeheartedly.)
(I think,)
(from the very beginning,)
(I've always loved you.)
(If)
(we could start over,)
(I wish)
(you hadn't saved me back then.)
♪A burning soul tears off
its own shackles♪
♪The stubborn pain♪
♪Hardens into the hottest flame♪
♪Taste the fruit you planted,
don't ask me for mercy♪
♪Just enjoy this searing pain♪
♪See whether blood or tears flow first♪
♪Your screams sound like regret to me♪
♪Greed caused the chaos,
none can run away♪
♪The karma you sowed by your own hands♪
♪Watered to maturity
with blood and tears♪
♪I pick it myself, for you to taste♪
♪Face the bitter fruit you made♪
♪Taste the fruit you planted,
don't ask me for mercy♪
♪Just enjoy this searing pain♪
♪See whether blood or tears flow first♪
♪Your screams sound like regret to me♪
♪Greed caused the chaos,
none can run away♪
♪The karma you sowed by your own hands♪
♪Watered to maturity
with blood and tears♪
♪Then ignite the anger forged by hatred♪
♪I'll burn it all down♪
(Thanks to timely rescue, Gu Yixiao
survived and turned himself in.)
(He received a fair trial
according to law.)
(The police launched
a full-scale operation.)
(They completely dismantled
the criminal gang.)
(All core members were arrested.)
(Ye Xingwan received lenient treatment
for turning herself in.)
(All remaining illegal activities
of the group were fully uncovered.)
(What awaits them now
is the full weight of the law.)
Back on campus again,
are you getting used to it?
What brings you here?
This photo was sent to me by Xingyue.
She asked me to give it to you.
This one
was taken on my birthday last year.
Make a wish.
What did you wish for?
The first wish.
Gu Yixiao gives me a white dress.
The second wish.
Gu Yixiao takes me
to the amusement park.
The third wish.
Gu Yixiao says he loves me.
But he doesn't know
I was lying to him.
There's something I've always
wanted to ask you.
When Gu Yixiao pointed a gun
at you back then,
why didn't you run?
What if he lost control
and ended up killing you?
He would never kill me.
Because his right hand
couldn't pull the trigger.
Anyway, it's all behind us now.
The future will get better for sure.
The good thing is,
I never gave up hope.
Go to class.
Alright.
Xingwan.
(If hatred is a cage,)
(revenge)
(only forges stronger chains.)
(Only letting go)
(is the key to unlocking the cage)
(to free the self
that's been imprisoned.)
♪The fragility stripped away by you♪
♪Keeps dragging me down endlessly♪
♪If not once devoured by blazing flames♪
♪Who would ever understand
this baptism by fire♪
♪You betrayed me so decisively♪
♪With indifference laid bare♪
♪It taught me to stay silent first♪
♪So the explosion would be deafening♪
♪A burning soul tears off
its own shackles♪
♪The stubborn pain♪
♪Hardens into the hottest flame♪
♪Taste the fruit you planted,
don't ask me for mercy♪
♪Just enjoy this searing pain♪
♪See whether blood or tears flow first♪
♪Your screams sound like regret to me♪
♪Greed caused the chaos,
none can run away♪
♪The karma you sowed by your own hands♪
♪Watered to maturity
with blood and tears♪
♪Then ignite the anger forged by hatred♪
♪I'll burn it all down♪