P seen
The Long Ballad
I'm taking him away now.
If you have any problem, just tell me.
I've given you my face.
You don't want it.
Go.
Hold me tight.
Close your eyes.
What are you waiting for?
Kill them all.
OK.
You'll regret it.
You're awake.
Don't worry.
I asked aunt to change your clothes.
I didn't tell them anything.
Can you help me solve this?
I don't want to be a prisoner.
You...
What do you mean?
You're not a prisoner.
You're a prisoner.
This is a locator.
You lied to me.
The problem with Kun hasn't been solved yet.
There will be danger later.
As long as you're willing,
I'll come to save you.
Locator.
How can I run?
Don't think about running.
If you don't run,
I can help you.
If you run,
you'll die a long time.
Understand?
What if I want to
bet on the life of that man who died of alcohol?
No one can run out of this island.
Including me.
It seems that I can only leave
with him.
I can't use this medicine.
You're so nice to me all of a sudden.
What are you planning?
Save me.
The medicine is a reward for you.
As the medicine is poison,
it's stillPal upstairs.
OK, I accept it.
Jun Chen
Do me the favor,
please.
You'll die covertly if you hurt Dieci.
Stop.
I haven't finished.
I don't want anyone to touch me.
Why can't I see that man?
We're on the same boat now.
You have to trust me at least.
I won't run away again.
I won't tell anyone about you.
But I hope you can protect me.
Aren't you afraid that I'll help you sell it?
I believe you're different from them.
I'm determined to wander.
What's the difference?
I want to cover up those sorrows.
How long will regret last?
You're so fat.
Are you familiar with it?
The loneliness of memories.
No.
But time is growing.
I'm not afraid now.
It will make me and the stars.
Why?
There's a little bit of wind on the skin.
At least you haven't hurt me.
I miss the past.
I'm depressed to see your eyes.
Okay.
I'll give you a chance.
We debut tonight.
I'll help you get rid of A'Kun.
You're really willing to help me?
But if you fail to escape,
I'll get rid of you.
Can you help me?
Have you forgotten A'Kun?
Yes.
Brotherkr cash!
Boss will be back soon.
Will it really kill us?
Zheng Wen is definitely watching K事情.
Can he save her?
Which means he's being guilty.
Hahaha, K.
What?
You are so angry at me.
I was impulsive today.
It's my fault to be your brother.
Dr. Gu, I apologize to you.
What?
Why are you so mean?
We are brothers.
We should share good things.
I bring you a gift today.
What?
The most beautiful woman in Taichung,
Benita.
Play with me tonight.
Brother K, I want to learn Taichi too.
How?
I want you to teach me.
Okay.
Don't forget we have something to do tonight.
What?
Can you give way?
Don't disturb us.
Where?
Take it.
Me?
Brother K, don't you want to teach me?
Watch carefully.
Put your hand here.
Relax your right hand.
Relax your shoulder.
And then breathe in.
Exhale.
And release the root.
Do you learn it?
Play by yourself.
The gift you gave is too valuable.
You can keep it for yourself.
Boss, why did you come back early?
I have to go to the hospital.
Why did you come back early?
Boss.
Is this the woman you like?
I gave you so many women but you don't want them.
So you like this kind of woman.
I think I've seen you somewhere.
Sorry.
I need to go to the bathroom.
The man I've been looking for is a drug dealer.
Why did he kill my mom?
So you two are fighting for this woman?
Boss, no.
We are good.
I'm sorry.
Brother Ke.
Drink.
Come on, brother.
You drank this cup of wine.
You forgot today.
Come on.
I don't drink the wine that others gave me.
Chung Chang.
dire
Is the task that I left you done?
Yes.
I don't want to make a mistake.
You'll see, I kill you.
I will be noticed here sooner or later.
Don't follow so slowly.
Doesn't she hear you entirely?
That's why I thought she's good- Gross too.
Why do I have to follow so slowly.
Gu Nian.
I think you don't need to leave.
My men will take care of you.
What did you say?
Brother K.
I'll be faster than that woman.
I'll treat you well.
And
I'm shocked by what happened.
I must beat them.
then how many maids should we be?
Where are you going?
I'm sorry.