The Long Ballad
Episode 18
Nian, I found out that Song Qian
was in the workplace three years ago.
She has never been to Taicheng
since she was in the local province.
A month ago,
she officially took over the Wei family
after she got engaged to Wei Qing.
She has become the new executive director.
It seems that
she has been promoted.
Could it be that
she really isn't her?
Qian,
the female doctor today
is your friend?
How could I know her?
Could it be that you forgot her
after you lost your job?
I'm afraid that
she really knows that
you are in Taicheng
and she will threaten you.
It's better to deal with her as soon as possible.
She is a doctor.
She can't threaten me.
Then don't see her anymore.
She looks like
an unruly woman.
Okay.
It's too late.
I'll ask Zhao to send you back.
I won't go back.
I won't go back tonight.
I'm your fiancee.
You haven't even touched me yet.
I was injured before.
You know that
I haven't recovered yet.
I don't care.
I'm going to be here tonight.
Be good.
I have something to deal with with your brother.
Haozheng,
send Miss Wei back first.
Yes.
Miss,
the secretary who got the certificate
must be dealt with immediately.
Miss Wei,
I've unlocked the phone of the dean.
Wei's Drugstore?
These photos are all confidential.
Could it be
that the dean's death
is related to Wei's Drugstore?
Guiyun,
I'm sorry.
Dr. Gu,
please wait here for a while.
The representatives of our cooperation
will be here soon.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
What's in the photo?
Judging from the background,
it should be the warehouse of Wei's Drugstore.
But how can I find it?
Dr. Gu,
I didn't expect that.
Mr. Song?
We met again.
You're the person in charge of the cooperation?
Is it an accident?
I hope we can cooperate happily.
Let's cooperate happily.
Let's stop here for the morning plan.
Let's call it a day.
Okay, Mr. Song.
Okay.
Dr. Gu,
let's have lunch together.
Mr. Song, I'm sorry.
I've made an appointment with someone.
It's late.
I'll leave first.
Okay.
Am I that scary?
Dr. Gu,
you were bothering me two days ago.
Now you're so impatient.
Mr. Song,
I think you've misunderstood.
We're just cooperating.
Why are you bothering me?
An Nian.
Senior.
Dr. Gu,
this gentleman is looking for you.
Why are you here?
I'm here to pick you up for lunch.
Okay, I can leave now.
Mr. Song, we'll leave first.
Won't you introduce yourself?
This is the psychologist in our hospital,
Dr. Zhou.
This is Mr. Song from Wei's Drugstore.
Hello, Mr. Song.
Are you going to have lunch?
Mr. Song, we'll leave first.
Okay, let's have lunch together.
I happen to have something
to ask Dr. Zhou.
Okay.
Hello.
What would you like to eat?
Help me order.
How about
trying our couple meal?
We're three people.
Three people can also order couple meal.
I want to order couple meal.
Two servings.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Where's Mr. Song?
He...
He went out for lunch with Dr. Gu.
Dr. Gu?
Gu Nian?
Miss,
I'll leave first.
Song Qian,
how dare you lie to me?
Nian,
have a shrimp.
It's good for your health.
You two seem to be in a good relationship.
Of course we're in a good relationship.
Nian's mother gave it to me.
Of course I have to take care of her for the rest of my life.
By the way, Mr. Song,
aren't you going to ask me a favor?
I want to ask you
how to treat me
if I have amnesia.
Amnesia?
Then you need to
go to the hospital for a checkup first.
Then I'll give you a treatment plan.
Then I'll trouble Dr. Zhou.
Are you Nian's friend?
No trouble.
I still want to thank you.
Eat more.
It's good for your eyes.
Mr. Song,
you don't like mango?
I'm allergic to mango.
You eat it.
Nian,
what's wrong with you?
I'm leaving first.
I have to organize the materials.
Nian,
I'll go with you.
No need.
What a coincidence.
I don't like mango either.
Is it a coincidence?
He's also allergic to mango.
I want to ask you
how to treat me
if I have amnesia.
He has amnesia?
But his shoulder is not injured.
He hasn't been to the hospital either.
Which floor are you going?
The warehouse.
I know the place.
I'll try.
Let's go together.
The warehouse.
Where are the boxes in the photos?
Why is it out of power?
Who?
Your words are too hard for me to describe.
What song is it?
Just for a second,
it disappears without a trace.
Hands in the air,
break free from the gorgeous cage.
No need to say it,
a pain is gone,
it's gone.
The endless night,
the empty wind,
the next is the murderer.
Who is so unruly?
Maybe it's empty,
but it's empty again.
Let me disappear in the darkness.
I can't see who is hiding behind.
The wound still hurts,
the memories are still in danger.
There are two endings,
whether you understand or not.
Let me disappear in the darkness.
I can't see who is hiding behind.
The heart still beats,
a blood-red in front of me.
There are two endings,
whether you understand or not.
Let me disappear in the darkness.