Episode 6
Who is it?
You guys... Who are you guys?
Hey!
If you don't talk, I'll call for help!
Mr. Song, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Get out.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sorry to bother you, Mr. Song.
You guys continue, continue, continue.
Dr. Gu, why did you come to the country?
I'm lost.
Lost?
Do you think I'll believe you?
Believe or not, it's up to you.
I told you to leave.
Let me go.
Don't move.
It's you.
The person who was in the dean's office that night, it's you.
What are you talking about?
He's the one who killed the dean.
Let me go.
Don't move.
I won't hear wrong.
It's this sound.
Hello, I've arrived.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I advise you to leave quickly.
My friend has called the police.
Don't talk nonsense with him.
Let's catch him first.
Let me disappear in the darkness.
Why don't you get off the car?
How did you find me?
Just passing by.
Passing by?
Or you had a plan?
What?
You suspect me of being with them?
Song Qian, who are you?
Are you still suspecting me of that K?
I said I'm not.
I know the person who was in the dean's office that night, it's you.
I advise you to go to the police station and explain everything.
I don't care what the reason is.
You think I killed the dean.
If you have evidence, you can go directly to the police.
Song Qian, what are you doing?
Dr. Gu, I don't know who you offended.
But I advise you to not ask for anything.
Otherwise, tonight is your best chance.
It's not every time you meet danger,
you will be able to get out of it.
I'm not afraid of danger.
Someone will come to save you.
With his identity, he can't do it himself.
Then why did he appear on the scene?
But anyway, tonight I was attacked.
It proves that someone doesn't want me to investigate anymore.
If the dean was really killed by Song Qian,
I'm a witness.
Why did he save me?
Boss, in his phone,
except for a few photos of the drug drug,
there are no other suspicious ones.
Destroy the phone.
And you have to keep an eye on Gu Nian.
Yes, boss.
But if he really starts to suspect you,
what should I do?
Then get rid of him.
Dr. Gu,
look what you did.
From yesterday,
the drugs that were not yet listed
from the Wei family
have been sold in the market.
Impossible.
I'm the one who is watching the drug products.
It's impossible to leak it out.
The problem is not with me.
The nurse can help me testify.
Dr. Gu,
I was there at the time.
But I really don't know if the drugs are leaked.
I'm only responsible for tracking the car.
I can't take the responsibility.
You...
Dr. Gu,
you stop working and take the punishment.
Director,
do you think I'm selling drugs?
From the beginning,
you were in charge of this project.
Now something happened.
You must be responsible for it.
I haven't done anything.
I won't admit it.
But I will find out the truth.
Director,
please give me three days.
If I can't find out,
I will resign automatically.
Hello.
I want to confirm
when Mr. Song can see me.
Dr. Gu,
we have informed you.
But I'm sorry.
Mr. Song said
it's not convenient to see you for the time being.
Ah-Qian.
Let's go to eat.
Okay.
Don't worry, Miss Wei.
She can't find any evidence.
Soon,
she will be punished and expelled from the hospital.
She will even go to jail.
I tried to enter the drug factory
and the hospital's surveillance system.
There is no trace of the surveillance video
of the hospital.
But the video of the drug factory...
Look.
The truck is in a blind spot.
There is no way to prove your innocence.
It seems that the problem is in the stomach.
Ah-Nian,
this is very serious.
You might go to jail.
This is the same as
the way to frame my mother.
The same.
There is no witness.
There is no surveillance.
Is the death of aunt
related to the drug factory?
And the death of the dean.
It may also be related to the drug factory.
I know they were killed.
But I have no evidence.
One day,
we will find the truth.
Look.
Look at this.
This truck has no fire extinguisher.
Its traffic record
should record everything.
This license plate
looks familiar.
It should be of the highest level.
But this parking lot
needs a certificate to enter.
How can I get a certificate?
Niannian,
there is no way to prove innocence.
I just have to
sell my beauty.
Brother.
Miss, what's wrong?
Please help me.
My ankle is twisted.
Are you okay?
How could it be?
There is a license plate.
It's there.
Hey, who are you?
Sorry, let me hide for a while.
Dr. Gu,
you broke into my private property.
I can call the police to arrest you.
Gu Nian,
you're crazy.
Gu Nian.
Is it...
is it Ago?
What is this spring season behind Eunuch Gu?
Yes.
능
What song is it?
Just for a second
Disappearing without a trace
Hands in the air
Stuck in the gorgeous cage
No words are needed
A knife cuts through pain and breaks through the sky
The endless night is floating
The next is the murderer
How to continue to be empty and empty
Let me disappear in the darkness
See who is hiding behind
There are still pains in the wound
Memory is still in fear
There are two endings, no matter if you understand
Let me disappear in the darkness
See who is hiding behind
There are still pains in the wound
A blood-red eye in front
The ending is still a kind of unimportant
Let me disappear in the darkness
Thanks for watching!