♪I really like you
but I can't explain why♪
♪Maybe this is how love works♪
♪The scenery I see♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪I just want to be with you every day♪
♪Is that OK♪
=Crush on My Ex-husband=
=Episode 22=
- You are awake.
- Qi Shuli, what do you want?
Don't move.
Qi Shuli, let me go!
What are you doing?
You can't get out of this.
Qi Shuli, you are shameless.
Let go of me!
Haven't you always missed your dad?
I will send you to his side later.
Qi Shuli, you are destroying yourself.
Let's do some negotiation, OK?
Negotiation?
He came pretty fast.
Don't move.
Junye.
Calm down, my dear nephew.
Where is the stuff?
Throw it over.
I know you hate the Qi family's guts.
It's impossible
for you to escape unscathed now.
I only have one request.
You can have Jun Yue
and the whole Qi family.
I
will stay here and that's OK.
But Jiang Shishi is innocent.
Let her go.
Junye.
No matter what happens tonight,
we'll forget about everything.
You can have all the evidence.
Beg me, beg me!
Junye.
Unexpectedly,
you are such an affectionate person.
My brother and sister-in-law
carefully cultivated you
for so many years,
yet you're actually doing this for a woman.
Throw it over.
Throw it over!
Step back.
Step back!
- Shishi!
- Junye!
Qi Junye, I can't let it go like this!
Back then, to take the family property,
your parents ruined my life
so that I can never be a father.
I also want you to know what it's like
to have no descendants at all!
Junye, leave me and just go!
- Just leave me!
- I said
I would be with you forever.
I won't let you slip away again.
Junye.
Shishi, are you OK?
Junye!
Junye! Junye!
Help!
Junye!
Boss!
Boss! boss!
(Police)
Zhao, change his dressing later.
OK.
Doctor,
how are they?
The male patient
still needs observation.
The female patient
just breathed in some smoke.
She will wake up soon.
Thank you, doctor.
Now
I don't hate that scumbag
as much anymore.
Me too.
I even kind of hope
they can reconcile.
Me too.
Shishi, you're awake.
How do you feel?
Junye... Junye...
Don't worry, he is still alive.
Qi Shuli has been arrested.
Easy.
Junye.
Junye, will you marry me?
Will you?
Qi Junye,
let's get married, OK?
(Several days later)
Here comes the groom.
Junye is so handsome today.
Congratulations!
Shishi.
During the time of divorce,
I have been thinking about something.
Was I too used to your existence
because we were too close?
Maybe that's why
I ignored the shining points on you.
This month of cooling-off period
gave me a chance
to reexamine myself carefully.
It turns out that
in my world,
love is just an added value.
It's more like a silent transaction.
Your generosity,
sincerity,
persistence,
kindness
and courage
taught me what love is.
That is a kind of love
that only the two of us understand.
But at that time,
I was so arrogant
and narrow-minded
that I didn't know how to cherish you.
I hope
it's not too late now.
Shishi,
are you willing to
become my Mrs. Qi again?
- Marry him!
Marry him!
Qi Junye,
thanks to you,
I understand
that love is not a one-sided thing.
It requires mutual effort and hard work.
We can only love each other better
by becoming a better self.
Although love has made us
a little crazy,
it has also
made us happy.
Qi Junye,
are you still willing to be my husband?
Yes, I am.
- Kiss!
Kiss!
♪The sun melted the ice cream♪
♪And you melted my heart♪
♪When I wasn't paying attention♪
♪I didn't have time to respond♪
♪I like every look of you♪
♪I care a lot about them♪
Are you so happy to get married?
Of course.
I thought I would be marrying
some vulgar returnee.
Unexpectedly, it's Qi Junye!
I'm so lucky!
♪My mood is all determined by you♪
♪I really like you
but I can't explain why♪
(Marry this girl after you graduate.)
(OK.)
♪Maybe this is how love works♪
Thank you, Dad.
♪The scenery I see♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪I just want to be with you every day♪
♪Is that OK♪
I have an idea.
How about we elope?