♪I really like you
but I can't explain why♪
♪Maybe this is how love works♪
♪The scenery I see♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪I just want to be with you every day♪
♪Is that OK♪
=Crush on My Ex-husband=
=Episode 5=
The beautiful Ms. Jiang Shishi.
Would you do me an honor
to let me give you a ride?
Why are you here?
The filming ended early today,
so I came here to pick you up.
My superstar is always so reliable.
Of course.
Get in the car.
Come on.
Surprise.
It's really a surprise!
Mom, why are you still up?
Explain this to me.
What are you busy with all day long?
You really think
you are a great designer?
(Divorce Agreement)
It's such an important matter,
why didn't you discuss it with me?
But this is really a good thing.
Back then,
I didn't agree
with your marriage at all.
She shouldn't live
in this house anymore.
I have packed her stuff.
She can move out tonight.
Mom, where can she go
at this late hour?
You also know it's late.
She still hasn't come back yet.
Who knows what she's doing out there.
I don't wanna see her again anyway.
Mom.
Thank you for this morning.
No problem,
call me when you need it again.
- OK. Thank you.
- Take care.
Since you're not happy in his house,
why don't you just move out?
Anyway, you are divorced.
Could it be
that you still like him?
I like him? Come on!
Good for you,
you have found
a new boyfriend already.
That being the case,
take your trash
and get out of our house.
Mom!
Junye.
Let go.
I said let go!
Give it to me.
(Assistant Mo)
Hello.
Hello, Boss.
I have already sent all the information
about Liu Shi to you.
Why are you suddenly
interested in him?
He's super popular now,
especially among girls.
For our company, he's...
He is not even as handsome as me.
(Personal Information)
What do they see in him?
Welcome to Shishi's
single party!
Come on.
Have a drink!
Sorry, I don't drink.
You're acting strange today.
Drink it up!
- Come on.
- Sorry, I really don't drink.
I really can't drink.
I'll drink with you guys.
Cheers. Have fun.
OK, come on.
Cheers.
Shall we continue?
Of course. Come on.
Let's drink.
OK, come on.
Let's have a drink.
Here.
Sorry, I really don't drink.
It's non-alcoholic.
OK. Thank you.
Cheers.
I didn't expect that
President Qi would come
to my single party.
Come on.
This drink is on me.
Come back with me.
I won't.
Do you want to take me back
to the Qi family?
I remember I was just kicked out.
That's not what I meant.
I don't care.
It's not work time now,
please stay out of
my personal life, President Qi.
Hey, you wanna take her away like this?
I don't think it's appropriate.
Mind your own business.
Don't forget about our agreement.
There cannot be
any negative news within a month.
Are you threatening me?
You did that to me first.
The party is not over yet,
but the protagonist is leaving?
Don't you think it's inappropriate?
She's not single.
Shishi,
you can refuse
if you don't want to leave.
You are wearing sunglasses
in such a dark place,
aren't you afraid you might fall?
Unexpectedly, Liu Shi, the superstar,
actually has time for a party.
You have become a has-been so soon?
Don't worry about it, Mr. Qi.
My new drama just premiered.
I'm still popular.
Shishi.
- Liu Shi!
Have a drink.
Let go! What are you doing?
What do you want?
Get in the car.
Your car?
You want me to get in your car?
How would I dare
to get in the great President Qi's car?
Oh my god!
Cut it out.
What are you doing? Put me down.
Put me down.
♪The sun melted the ice cream♪
Wait a moment.
Are you trying to
help me fasten my seat belt?
This kind of sweet move
doesn't suit you.
You'd better continue being
a scumbag ex-husband.
♪I care a lot about them♪
♪Maybe this is how love works♪
I will.
♪It's all about you♪
♪I just want to be with you every day♪
♪Is that OK♪
(He actually took me here.)
You can live here from now on.
Jiang Shishi? What are you doing here?