♪I really like you
but I can't explain why♪
♪Maybe this is how love works♪
♪The scenery I see♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪I just want to be with you every day♪
♪Is that OK♪
=Crush on My Ex-husband=
=Episode 8=
Hello everyone, I'm now at
the new product launch event
of Jun Yue Group.
At this event here...
Dear guests and media friends,
welcome to our event.
Our new product launch
is about to start.
- Sit down please.
- Are you two reconciled?
I am not sure
about my feeling for him.
Think about Mr. Jiang!
He admitted it himself
that he's responsible for
Mr. Jiang's death.
Maybe it is also a misunderstanding!
After all, I have worked
in the company for so long,
but found nothing suspicious at all.
In my opinion,
you have fallen for him again!
Let me tell you.
You must remember a sentence,
"Clever people will never fall in love."
Can't you focus on your career?
Come on.
Let's go.
Hello, everyone.
I am Qi Junye.
Thank you very much for coming
to the new product launch event
of Jun Yue Jewelry.
Now, Jiang Shishi, our design director
will explain
her design concept for us.
Applause, please.
You can do it.
Hello everyone, I am Designer Jiang Shishi.
Originality and tranquility
are two stages in my life.
Originality was the old me,
when I was
surrounded by fatherly love
and living in anticipation
of a better life.
And the present me
can feel the tranquility.
I can follow my heart,
do what I like
and shine like a diamond.
- Bravo!
- Junye, thank you so much.
- My mom and little brother?
What are you doing here?
This is not the first time, right?
Shishi, you know we need money.
There's nothing wrong with asking
my brother-in-law for some money.
You need money?
OK, take my card.
Don't come to Junye for money again.
Why not? He's my son-in-law.
Take it
or leave it.
Let's go.
It's OK.
We got the money anyway.
You have been giving them money
since we got married?
I'm sorry.
So you refused when I tried to
borrow money from you
to help Jiang Group
because...
Because I had done this
many times.
And I think Jiang Group's problem
can't be solved just with money.
Your younger brother
is really not suitable
for running a company.
That's why I didn't tell you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
It's OK.
We are family.
I'll be here for you in the future.
OK, stop crying.
I don't think
I can pay you back in this life
for what my family owes you
with my current salary.
Then do it in the next life
and the next one after that.
Silly girl.
You are my wife,
you don't need to pay me back.
But we have already divorced.
You don't love me.
Our marriage
is just a transaction.
Jiang family is going downhill,
so I am useless now.
If there is another marriage,
I hope
it's a marriage of love.
Love.
People like us
don't have the qualification
to talk about love.
Let me tell you
a little secret.
Actually, since I was little,
I have never made friends.
And I...
I never had any hobbies.
Even my only marriage
was arranged by my mother.
The reason is simple.
Just because I was born
in the Qi family,
every day,
I have to
be cautious and careful.
Because I have to become
the pride of everyone.
I can only do
the right things.
This is my fate.
My parents have always told me
since I was young
that love,
friendship, and things like that
are all meaningless.
Only money and interests
are the most solid stuff.
Those who claim that
they love you
will often hurt you the most.
To be honest, I...
I don't even know what love is.
But I just
really, really, really want
to see you again.
I don't want you to leave.
Qi Junye.
Honey, I need your shoulder now.
Don't leave me.
OK. I will never leave you, alright?
Don't ever leave me.
I will never leave you if you behave.
I will behave.
You will?
Really?
I will.
I'll do whatever you ask me to do.
Really?
What about your family?
I don't care.
Look,
I'll tie us together.
Like this.
Again.
♪You are like the weather in my heart♪
♪Will it rain tomorrow♪
So we will never be apart.
Never.
Then...
Give me a hug.
Then let's
go to bed now, OK?
No.
You just want to leave me.
I won't.
Please don't leave me.
OK.
I'll hate you
if I can't see you tomorrow morning.
I promise you.
OK.