=The Reincarnated Lovers=
=Episode 9=
♪Swaying on the boat♪
♪Rocking to and fro♪
Your Highness.
What are you doing?
I was just bored,
so
I entertained myself by humming.
What?
Your Highness.
I'm sorry.
I left something out just now,
so
I came back.
You were already humming a song
for Her Highness
to chase away her nightmares.
I stood outside,
not daring to disturb you two.
Chase nightmares away?
Yes.
I suggested it to His Highness.
His Highness
even said that it was a superstition.
But he started singing
and got invested in it.
Get out.
Yes, Your Highness.
Don't listen
to his nonsense.
It must've been hard for you
to believe in a superstition.
Were you even
going to get a sorcerer
to read my fortune?
(Should I give her this hairpin?)
(Am I being too proactive by doing so?)
Hey, lad.
You are extraordinary.
You are the Nine-Tailed Immortal Fox
who has nine lives.
The woman you met recently
must be
your true love.
My destined one?
You have nine lifetimes,
and in every lifetime,
both of your fates
are closely intertwined.
Your Highness.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Anyway,
how's Mother?
And also,
the sick people in the city?
The miracle physician
has prescribed medicine for Mother.
I've also delivered the drugs
to the people's home.
But the physician
said that the medicine
only addresses the symptoms.
To solve the root cause,
we must find the source.
Unconscious
and foaming at the mouth
with no cause?
Your Highness.
I might
have a solution.
Your Highness.
Investigation on the poisoning case
in Jiangling has not made any progress.
The perpetrator is a cunning person.
For now, it is important for us
to treat the people.
Gather all the physicians in Jiangling
to come up with a solution
and deploy personnel for investigation.
We must find out the perpetrator.
Yes, Your Highness.
Slow down.
Tang Wanwan.
Can't you hurry up?
Wait, Wan.
Why did you summon me
so early in the morning?
You have to work on your stamina.
Anyway,
I heard that the arrow poison leaf
is a unique plant in Xiliang.
As powder,
it is tasteless and colorless,
and it burns in fire but boils in water.
If one drinks it,
they will fall into a coma
and foam at the mouth.
It's incredibly difficult
to seek the cause of sickness.
You're right.
But what does that have to do with me?
Aren't you from Xiliang?
I'm sure you're very familiar
with the arrow poison leaves.
That's why I sought your help
to help me find the Perescia plant
that counters arrow poison leaves.
I think the sickness Her Highness
and the people suffer from
is related to arrow poison leaves.
Let's go.
(Wan Pavilion)
Why didn't you tell me Her Highness
is at Tianjing Mountain for herbs?
I thought you knew.
Moreover, she had set off
way before dawn.
If something happens to her,
I'll be questioning you.
Don't worry.
Her Highness
is accompanied by Mr. Hua.
She's safe.
What did you say?
Are you actually
trying to trick a good-looking man
like me
into the deep mountain forest?
So that you can
do something indecent to me?
Let me tell you.
Don't even think about it.
My admirers
has lined up from Jiangling to Xiliang,
while I
try my best
to satisfy every one of them.
In your dreams.
You missed.
I'm so...
unlucky.
Come on. You're on top of me.
Get up.
Your Highness.
Is this your solution to the problem?
Anyway.
How did you...
How did you know
about the arrow poison leaf?
After developing a suspicion,
I met the sorcerer in the dungeon.
With so many people in Jiangling
falling ill,
don't you think
it's related to the arrow poison leaves?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Will you
stop pretending?
Your disciple has confessed.
I advise you
to spill the beans
and avoid punishment.
Ungrateful brat.
Your Highness.
It's none of my business.
I was forced too, you know.
That day,
a man wearing a straw hat
knocked me out.
He forcibly fed me arrow poison leaves
and made me follow his orders,
or else he would take my life.
Are you sure it was a man
with a straw hat?
Yes.
The sorcerer
and a man with the straw hat.
Yes.
He threatened the sorcerer,
ground the arrow poison leaves
into powder,
and poured it into the well
that everyone in Jiangling uses.
Who's that man in a straw?
He's so cruel.
Luckily, when I was young,
Qing'an told me about the Perescia plant
and the arrow poison leaves.
Your Highness.
Your memory is great.
How do you remember
what Qing'an told you?
Zhu Que.
Less talking,
more working.
Look.
Perescia plants.
Don't.
Perescia plants have deadly thorns,
silly.
Stand back.
You're in no position
to look after my queen.
I'm free anyway.
It's nice to visit you, Your Highness.
You're the sweetest.
Where's Zhu Que?
I ordered him
to send Perescia plants
to the homes with sick families.
Anyway,
we have this too.
Let's give Mother this.
I'm sure
she'll heal soon.
Mother.
How did you...
Jingyue's Perescia plant
saved my life.
I just happened to see them.
On my way back to Tian Capital
with Father,
I heard about the illness in Jiangling,
so I sought Father's permission
to come back
and see if I could be of help.
Jingyue's medical skills
are truly remarkable.
Anyone who has her as a daughter-in-law
must've been blessed
from their previous life.
I'm just an amateur.
I just happen
to have read some books.
Mother.
My queen has also
brought Perescia plants
for you and the people.
Mother.
No, thank you.
I can't take it.
♪Before the storm♪
♪The air is stifling♪
♪Clinging to every breath♪
♪Who holds the secrets of whom♪
♪Transcending expectations?♪
♪In the days after parting♪
♪Shedding the innocence♪
♪Never realizing that you and I♪
♪Are born adversaries♪
♪He once invaded in every possible way♪
♪Claiming my territory♪
♪Easily giving promises♪
♪Treated as optional questions♪
♪In this age not favored by fortune♪
♪A moment of joy♪
♪Yet repeating the same old habits♪
♪Twisted and tangled
interpersonal relationships♪
♪Hidden melodies♪
♪Stories, as tradition goes♪
♪Rise and fall in sequence♪
♪I wait for you♪
♪Endless anticipation♪
♪Till the latest trend
grows out of season♪
♪Who gathers the shattered heart♪
♪Becoming an undisclosed ailment?♪
♪The kiss that I tasted a thousand times
still enchants me♪
♪Fantasizing each day♪
♪About various ways to meet my demise♪
♪I am sick♪
♪To the point of silence♪
♪To the point
of overwhelmed by myriad emotions♪
♪Repeatedly dreaming
of raindrops against the current♪
♪And the wounded you♪
♪He once invaded in every possible way♪
♪Claiming my territory♪
♪Easily giving promises♪
♪Treated as optional questions♪
♪In this age not favored by fortune♪
♪A moment of joy♪
♪Yet repeating the same old habits♪
♪Twisted and tangled
interpersonal relationships♪
♪Hidden melodies♪
♪Stories, as tradition goes♪
♪Rise and fall in sequence♪
♪I wait for you♪
♪Endless anticipation♪
♪Till the latest trend
grows out of season♪
♪Who gathers the shattered heart♪
♪Becoming an undisclosed ailment?♪
♪The kiss that I tasted a thousand times
still enchants me♪
♪Fantasizing each day♪
♪About various ways to meet my demise♪
♪I am sick♪
♪To the point of silence♪
♪To the point
of overwhelmed by myriad emotions♪
♪Repeatedly dreaming
of raindrops against the current♪
♪And the wounded you♪