=The Reincarnated Lovers=
=Episode 6=
(Tablet of Xiao Qing'an)
Qing'an.
Poor Qing'an.
There's nothing left of him.
All we have to bury are his clothes.
Qing'an.
Leave.
I don't want to see you.
You don't deserve to be here.
Your Highness.
Let me send Qing'an off.
I beg you.
Your Highness.
Am I really cursed?
Be it in my past life or this life,
those close to me
never have happy endings.
You're still injured.
You might catch a cold,
making things worse.
♪Time passes, yet memories linger♪
Back then,
could you really not save him?
You think
I did it on purpose?
Tang Wanwan.
You're not thinking straight.
I won't blame you.
Still, I want you to know
I'm not as awful as you think.
♪If I were to see you again♪
I'm also upset
about my brother's death.
♪You're right before my eyes♪
♪Yet why pretend not to see♪
I'll head to Tian Capital tomorrow.
Take care of yourself.
♪Hesitant to continue
at the same moment♪
♪Must I forget you once more♪
All you do is cry and cry.
He's already dead. Why are you crying?
Look at Tang Wanwan.
Xiao Qing'an just died,
and she's already seducing Xiao Xuanyi.
Qing'an was great to her.
How could she do that?
Not everyone's like you.
It has been years,
and you keep clinging onto one person.
Your focus
must now shift.
I've told you,
Xiao Xuanyi is a legitimate prince.
He's much better than Xiao Qing'an.
Mother.
What are you saying?
I only like Qing'an.
I only want Qing'an.
Enough.
Right now,
we still need to get rid
of that troublesome Tang Wanwan.
We can't let her
be the Queen of Jiangling.
I don't agree with shaving Wanwan's head
to mourn Qing'an for three years.
Age is very important to young women.
How can we waste her years?
I won't let my own daughter
fall for that trap.
It's what the Princess Dowager wants.
We are in the wrong.
How so?
No one wanted Qing'an to die.
Anyway,
it can't be blamed on Wanwan.
Father.
I'll do it.
Stop.
Xuanyi.
How are you back so soon?
If I were any slower,
it will be too late.
Your Highness.
You came just in time.
The sorcerer
is starting Wanwan's shaving ceremony.
For Young Master Qing'an, she...
Tang Wanwan cannot shave her head
because
I'm going to marry her.
Xuanyi.
Do you know what you're saying?
Of course.
This marriage
is impossible.
She has already killed one of my sons.
I can't let her kill you too.
I'm afraid
that's not your choice.
His Majesty, the Emperor.
Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
(Emperor of Great Yuan)
Who
here
is Tang Wanwan?
Good.
Jingyue.
Announce it.
(Lin Jingyue, Princess of Great Yuan)
Tang Wanwan,
beautiful and gracious daughter
to Minister of Jiangling,
the Prince of Jiangling is ready to wed
a virtuous woman of choice.
The daughter of Tang
and the Prince of Jiangling
are a perfect match.
We will grant this wish
and permit these two
to join in sacred matrimony.
I and my wife
thank Your Majesty.
You are now the future Queen of Jiangling.
You don't need to kneel all the time.
What if I don't want
to be the Queen of Jiangling?
It's an imperial decree.
We can do nothing.
Tang Wanwan.
Is marrying me
really that bad?
I am cursed.
I am no match for you.
Is it because of that
or because you think little of me?
You jest.
I'm the cursed woman
who just killed her husband.
You are an outstanding man.
This marriage is not a good match.
I'll tell His Majesty
I
will never marry again.
Never marry again?
Are you going to mourn Xiao Qing'an
for the rest of your life?
Yes.
Xiao Qing'an is the only husband
I'll have in this lifetime.
♪Before the storm♪
♪The air is stifling♪
♪Clinging to every breath♪
♪Who holds the secrets of whom♪
♪Transcending expectations?♪
♪In the days after parting♪
♪Shedding the innocence♪
♪Never realizing that you and I♪
♪Are born adversaries♪
♪He once invaded in every possible way♪
♪Claiming my territory♪
♪Easily giving promises♪
♪Treated as optional questions♪
♪In this age not favored by fortune♪
♪A moment of joy♪
♪Yet repeating the same old habits♪
♪Twisted and tangled
interpersonal relationships♪
♪Hidden melodies♪
♪Stories, as tradition goes♪
♪Rise and fall in sequence♪
♪I wait for you♪
♪Endless anticipation♪
♪Till the latest trend
grows out of season♪
♪Who gathers the shattered heart♪
♪Becoming an undisclosed ailment?♪
♪The kiss that I tasted a thousand times
still enchants me♪
♪Fantasizing each day♪
♪About various ways to meet my demise♪
♪I am sick♪
♪To the point of silence♪
♪To the point
of overwhelmed by myriad emotions♪
♪Repeatedly dreaming
of raindrops against the current♪
♪And the wounded you♪
♪He once invaded in every possible way♪
♪Claiming my territory♪
♪Easily giving promises♪
♪Treated as optional questions♪
♪In this age not favored by fortune♪
♪A moment of joy♪
♪Yet repeating the same old habits♪
♪Twisted and tangled
interpersonal relationships♪
♪Hidden melodies♪
♪Stories, as tradition goes♪
♪Rise and fall in sequence♪
♪I wait for you♪
♪Endless anticipation♪
♪Till the latest trend
grows out of season♪
♪Who gathers the shattered heart♪
♪Becoming an undisclosed ailment?♪
♪The kiss that I tasted a thousand times
still enchants me♪
♪Fantasizing each day♪
♪About various ways to meet my demise♪
♪I am sick♪
♪To the point of silence♪
♪To the point
of overwhelmed by myriad emotions♪
♪Repeatedly dreaming
of raindrops against the current♪
♪And the wounded you♪