It’s okay, we gotta introduce you to Mom and Dad
sooner or later anyway
Mom, Dad, this is Bao, the guy I told you about
Nice to meet you
I brought a little gift for you guys today
Oh, how thoughtful! Thank you!
Bao, where are you from?
I’m from Thanh Hoa
Khanh
Come down here!
Your sister brought her boyfriend home!
Bao, this is Khanh, my little brother
And Khánh, this is Bao
your soon-to-be brother-in-law!
Hi Khanh, I’m Bao, Huyen’s boyfriend
So Bao, what do you do?
Right now I’m just focusing on school
Oh, still young!
Where do you study?
I…
I study at the University of Economics.
Oh, that’s where Khanh works!
Khanh
KHANH
Yeah?
Do you know Bao?
Yeah… we’ve met before
Let me introduce the main teaching assistant for this class
Mr Khanh
Hey everyone, I’m Khánh. I’ll be your main TA…
I’m so sorry, I’m late!
AH
Thanks
Everyone, listen up
from now on, no being late to class
Alright, let’s get into the lesson
Hey, let’s go grab snacks at the canteen
What were you just doing?
Just texting a friend
If you were recording or taking pictures of me
delete them now
I told you, I was just texting!
You realize that’s violating privacy, right?
Hand me your phone!
No way, why should I?
If there’s no photo of me, I’ll publicly apologize.
But if there is
I’m keeping your phone until the end of class.
OMG! He is f**king hot! Total mlem vibes!
Damn, go for it, b!tch
If I catch you filming or snapping pics again
I’m reporting you to the school
Okay! I’m sorry!
You again!
Hey there, fancy seeing you again, Mr. TA
Getting this much attention from the TA on your first day?
Not a good sign.
I thought getting noticed was a good thing?
If it weren’t the first day
I’d already report you to the department office.
Come on!
Just punish me privately, don’t get me kicked out.
Poor me!
If I punish you, your legs won’t be able to walk after!
I thought it’d just be copying lines
or something…
How would I know what you’re imagining?
Come in, sir
What are you doing?
Huh?
I don’t kiss anyone unless they’re my boyfriend!
Really?
How about this then?
A  sine graph, huh?
Wanna taste??
Let me teach you a little lesson
Wow, right on time!
A perfect 45-minute session with TA Khánh
Hello?
Yeah, I’ve got everything ready
see you!
What’s going on? You seem serious.
I’m getting married, Mr. TA.
Married?
Yep
Congrats then!
I’m serious!
I said congrats, didn’t I
Anyway, I’m heading out
Why so quick?
Scared someone will get jealous?
So we’re just a one-night stand, huh?
Can’t we have night two, three, four, five, six, seven?
Poor student like you needs lots of extra tutoring, huh?
All in your hands, sir!
What a small world!
Turns out Bao is a student in Khanh’s class!
How’s Khanh as a TA?
Pretty strict
But he’s always happy to answer student questions
Khanh’s always been a top student.
Even in college, they kept him on as a lecturer
Now he even teaches master’s classes
Yeah, Mr. Khanh is pretty famous
So, Bao, what do your parents do?
Um…
I’m an orphan.
Yeah, Bao’s really hardworking.
He paid his own way through university
even bought his own place
and he’s doing his master’s too
Wow, so young and already owns a home.
I got lucky with some stock investments.
I’m taking a break now to focus on studying.
So young and already so driven
Huyen really picked the right guy
Let me check what’s going on
Khanh
Khanh!
You really embarrassed me!
You can’t marry this guy.
Why
He’s like 5 or 6 years younger than you!
Oh come on
age gaps of 10, 20 years are common these days!
But he doesn’t even have a stable job!
Bao’s got ambition.
You don’t need to worry
That’s right
No need to stress, Mr. Khanh!
At school, he’s Mr. Khánh.
At home, he’s your brother-in-law!
Got it, got it
Huh? Why’s everyone out here?
Tra
This is my fiancé!
I heard you were coming today
but I got stuck at work
No worries at all!
Bao, this is Tra.
MY WIFE
They got married early last year
right before our grandma passed away
Don’t we make a cute couple?
Yeah