[English subtitles are available]
[Let's Meet Now]
[Episode 11]
If I bring the team assistant,
will she think I'm finicky?
I think she will.
What are you talking about?
Are you talking to me?
Yes.
Zhou Ziqian.
When are we leaving tomorrow?
Actually,
you don't have to go with me.
How about I go talk to the coach?
No.
I wanted to go.
I've watched many of your games
and I think you're amazing.
I really wanted to know you.
The coach is calling me.
I'm leaving.
So soon?
He works so hard.
I'm sure
Xu Wang raises it better than this.
What's wrong?
The printer is broken again.
Chen tried hard today but couldn't fix it.
I went to the company next door to print it.
It's broken again?
Xu Wang is good at physics.
He should be able to fix it fast if he's here.
Does this have anything to do with physics?
Who is Xu Wang anyway?
Oh, right.
A friend of mine.
By the way,
I just bought many.
Thank you.
I don't think Xu Wang has tasted
this kind of candy produced in Jiangyi.
You've been talking about him all day.
Who is this Xu Wang?
Your boyfriend?
No.
Don't joke about this.
Well, if I may say,
at your age,
you should have a boyfriend.
Hey, are you free tonight?
Go somewhere with me.
Tonight?
Where?
Is it fun?
Trust me.
It'll be fun.
Not bad. You can drink a lot.
This is not fun at all.
This is a blind date organized by my friends.
Don't worry.
These boys are quite decent.
You can start by getting to know each other.
But I don't want to.
Try some meat.
Xu Wang.
Why Xu Wang again?
How many times
have you called his name today?
I saw him.
Oh no.
If he knows I'm on a blind date,
he will misunderstand me, won't he?
What should I do?
Who is this girl?
I've never seen her before.
Her name is Song Rongrong.
She came with me today.
No wonder you're so pretty.
I wouldn't have forgotten if I had seen her.
Since you're here,
make some friends.
You have to drink.
That's right.
How can you not drink?
Bottom up.
Come on, Ding Ding.
Cheers.
Well, Ding Ding,
I have something to do.
How about I...
Rongrong, right?
Did anyone say you look like a celebrity?
No.
The one with short hair.
The one who likes wearing tank tops, right?
Yes, that one.
Her waist is so thin, and her legs are so long that I feel...
Excuse us, Rongrong.
We are all quite straightforward.
Please don't mind.
The girl called Rongrong doesn't look smart.
Isn't that what you want?
Don't think I didn't see it.
You couldn't take your eyes off of her.
That kind of girl.
If you talk to her more, she will think you like her.
They're easy to fool.
But in terms of the length of legs,
Susu has the longest legs.
Did you see Xia, over there?
Her waist is also very thin. You must haven't noticed.
And that Ding Ding.
She must have had many boyfriends.
But I don't know what tricks will work on her.
You should get that fool first.
That's easy.
Just a matter of two more bottles of wine.
Remember to order more wine later.
Where were you?
Keep drinking.
Come on.
Song Rongrong.
Let me send you back.
Xu Wang.
Xu Wang?
So Xu Wang is a real person.
Who are you?
Why are you leaving at will?
Rongrong, sit down.
You're going to...
Let go. It hurts.
If you touch her again,
what hurts won't only be your hands.
What do you mean?
Right.
What's wrong with my friend?
You want to fight?
Don't fight.
We're all good people.
Let's talk.
Talk?
About what?
About who has the longest legs,
or whose waist is the thinnest?
Or who seems to have had the most boyfriends?
Didn't you two talk enough in the men's room?
Really?
Can't you tell?
They were heard.
What's wrong with you?
Don't talk nonsense.
I never said that.
He's talking nonsense.
Did you come here together?
Can I take her home first?
Okay. No problem.
Rongrong said she wanted to go home early.
Right?
Hurry up.
Go.
You're leaving already?
If I see you again,
I...
I'll call the police.
Call the police?
We should call the police.
Did you look in the mirror before you went outside?
♫I haven't written to others since October♫
Why are you here today?
An old friend is here.
♫I'm just a little composer♫
We had a dinner date.
Can you just leave like this?
It's okay. He's gone already.
♫Never mind these bad things and put them in the corner♫
Why were you so angry just now?
Although we haven't known each other for long，
♫Just think about what it's worth♫
I never saw you like this.
Like this?
♫Focus on the things that will make you feel better♫
Like what?
Just...different from usual.
You're usually patient and attentive.
You don't seem to care about anything.
♫It will make you happier♫
But this is the first time I've seen you like this.
♫I've been thinking about you lately♫
They bullied my friend.
♫You know I'm happy to hear you talk and you are happy to share♫
If you haven't come over today,
I might sit until the end.
♫The way you look at me I can't help getting close to you♫
I think I can make do with it.
There are things you don't have to make do with.
♫No one loves you as much as I do♫
And don't drink
when you are out with unfamiliar people.
I don't want to go on blind dates anymore.
Blind date?
No.
I wasn't here for a blind date.
I didn't want to come here for a blind date.
I'm not looking for a boyfriend.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Qiu is working overtime anyway.
No hurry.
What?
Nothing. Let's go.
Qiu, you know what...
She's not back yet.
Hello, Ding Ding?
I'm home.
How many people?
Only me.
I was looking forward to the follow-up between you two.
Why did you go home alone?
I was going home anyway.
Are you still there?
I left a long time ago.
Those two scumbags pissed me off.
Susu exposed them in the company WeChat group.
They are probably condemned by all the girls in the company right now.
Don't change the subject.
Listen to me.
Since you like your friend,
you should hurry up.
There are only few boys like him now.
I like him?
I saw it.
I saw sparkles in your eyes
when you looked at him.
Don't you like him?
Who said that?
Nonsense.
How come?
How come what?
How about this?
Imagine
if he picks you up from work every day,
will you be happy?
Yes.
If he asks you out,
will you go?
Yes.
If he tells you you are pretty,
will you be excited?
Of course.
That's it.
You must like him.
No.
Enough.
When girls fall in love,
they like to lie to themselves.
Think about it on your own.
Bye.
It's so hot.
It seems that...
I'm in love with him.
Everything is ready.
Let's go through the process.
OK.
Have you confirmed the order of the guests coming tomorrow?
Yes.
The first one to go up is Lin Xiao.
She is lively and cute.
She'll be able to warm up the stage if she's the first.
Next is Xiao Chen.
As a member of the most popular boy group FEEL,
he has a very large fan base.
We must get the security ready in advance.
Next, Zhou Ziqian and Fu Qile.
Because neither of them is from the entertainment industry,
and they know each other,
we arranged them together.
Ye Qiao will be the last.
She usually only gets off the car
after all the guests are here.
So we may have to wait for a few minutes.
We need to rehearse
what may happen on site in advance.
I will be
Zhou Ziqian and Xiao Chen.
Tianyang, then you are Fu Qile.
Miss Ji is Ye Qiao.
C will be Lin Xiao.
I'll start first.
Zhou Ziqian and Fu Qile
are very familiar with each other.
At this time, the tacit understanding between men
must be shown by them.
Isn't this Mr. Fu?
Isn't this Mr. Zhou?
Brother, I missed you so much.
I really missed you, bro.
Miss Ji, should it be like this?
Probably.
I heard you two knew each other from before.
You must be very close.
Just so-so.
Not at all.
To be exact,
I don't know him.
Let's continue.
Although Ye Qiao is distant,
Lin Xiao's nickname is Little Sun.
She can definitely melt her.
Great work, Miss Ye.
Miss Ye.
Miss Lin Xiao is over there.
Do you want to say hello to her?
I can, but it's not necessary.
The last one, Xiao Chen.
Although he's young,
he debuted early.
He must be good at dealing with relationships.
And he's always been a considerate guy.
He must be good at getting along with girls.
Nervous?
No, I'm not.
They are all my older brothers and sisters.
I think I can learn a lot from them.
I think I'm one year younger than you.
Really?
I can't tell.
Maybe I look younger.
Five totally different young people get to know each other
in a variety show with no restrictions.
With totally different personalities,
there will be all kinds of sparkles among them.
Five kinds of completely different professional experiences.
There will never be awkward silence on the stage.
Long time no see.
Your skin looks nice too.
He's very popular online.
Let's take a photo.
OK.
Stand still. Ready.
One, two, three.
The most important thing is the atmosphere.
It will be very entertaining,
friendly,
and harmonious.
This is quite different
from what we imagined.
What's wrong?
Why did everyone stop talking
after self-introduction?
Ji Qiu,
try to communicate with the guests
to liven up the atmosphere.
No problem.
Good work.
You two, say something to liven up the atmosphere.
The director's eyes are killing me out there.
What's there to say?
Anything.
Good work.
Did you all have breakfast?
Well...
I did.
Really? Me too. What a coincidence.
Miss Ji,
given this situation,
do you remember
what we predicted about the first part?
The first part
is drawing lots to decide
who will act alone in this show.
The other four
will be divided into two groups
based on the props
we took from their houses.
Two teams of two.
Before they start,
they need to be connected with an elasticity rope.
And the one who acts alone
doesn't have any restriction
to be fair.
I'm suddenly worried about
the one to be chosen to act alone.
He must be very sad
to be left alone.
How sad would it be?
It must be sad
to step out alone.
But it can't be helped.
Xiao Chen.
[Xiao Chen]
It's really...
What a...
What a pity.
Xiao Chen, as the guest
who'll be acting alone for the recording today,
can get going to the next venue first.
Well,
my friends,
I'm leaving.
Well,
the four of you left
will be divided into two groups of two.
I won't team up with you.
What a coincidence. I won't either.
Here's the travel fee
to the next venue, Xiaolanshan Mountain.
It's all here.
Keep it well.
Fifty yuan?
Are you sure?
We tested it ourselves.
This is the minimum travel expense
to the next venue.
I have a small suggestion.
Let's split the money
and take care of our own half.
What a coincidence. I think so too.
Can you walk properly?
The road is wide. I'm not walking abnormally.
What are you doing?
The road is so wide.
I also want to walk on this side.
A famous shooting athlete
and a psychology lecturer.
Why are they like my Bai and Yuan?
Your kids?
My two shibainu dogs.
How about this?
Let's be friendly during the drive.
What do you mean by that?
For example, let go of your hand now.
Are you sure you want to talk like this?
Just like that.
I saw you brought an assistant this morning.
Where is she now?
Right.
Where is she?
Don't forget to bring the props.
Okay, Miss Ji.
Everyone is moving to the next venue.
Why are you still here?
I...I'm looking for someone.
Looking for someone?
Which team is he on?
Zhou Ziqian's team.
Zhou Ziqian?
I'm the new assistant of Jiangyi Shooting Team.
The coach asked me to come with him
to this shooting
and see if I can help.
I can take care of him.
Don't worry.
I won't disturb your shooting.
I'll just stand there and watch.
It's okay.
Everything's ready, Miss Ji. Let's go.
OK.
Zhou Ziqian and others have left.
Would you like to go to the next venue
with me and wait there?
Is that okay?
Sure.
Okay, thank you.
The car is over there.
You go first.
Okay.
Thank you.
Assistant?
Why didn't Zhou Ziqian tell me about it?
Xiao Chen disguised himself
to avoid being recognized by the fans
and got on a taxi.
It's like I'm watching a scene
from a drama about the Qing Dynasty.
[Ji Qiu]
Is there a conflict between the guests?
The problem is not the conflict,
but it's a bit too harmonious.
Ye Qiao,
look over there.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes.
Ye Qiao, is your stuff heavy?
Do you need my help?
No need. Your stuff is heavy too.
I'll carry it myself.
It's okay. I can handle it.
Excuse me.
I'll change a card.
Please take a rest.
OK.
The camera was recording.
You said you'd carry my stuff.
Are you afraid that I won't be scolded after it's aired?
I was just afraid that you can't carry it.
It's not recording now.
You don't need to laugh.
You made quite a lot of mistakes
due to confidential issues.
It won't happen this time, right?
Ah.
What is it? A bug?
Take it away.
It's okay.
I got it for you.
You...
Aren't you afraid of this?
When I was little, I lived with my grandparents.
No one played with me then.
I was so happy when I saw them.
Because they could play with me for a long time.
It's okay.
I'll help you catch them all along the way.
Thank you.
Ye Qiao,
why are you afraid of bugs?
Are you afraid of all kinds of bugs?
Are you afraid of butterflies then?
You talk so much.
I do talk a lot.
Do you need any help from me?
Just talk less.
Mr. Fu.
Let's play a game.
No.
Are you afraid of losing?
It's just rock, paper, scissors.
Whoever loses
will carry a piece of the other's luggage.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Mr. Zhou.
Thank you.
Again.
The one who loses this time
will carry all luggage for the other one
for half an hour.
Are you sure?
Rock, paper, scissors.
It's getting late.
Let's go.
No.
Again.
For one hour this time.
Rock, paper, scissors.
One more.
Rock.
Scissors.
Paper.
I quit.
You have to carry it for
eight hours in total.
Let's play again.
No.
Come on. Last round.
Mr. Zhou, try it.
You have a chance.
Just once.
Why are you so talkative?
It's almost ready.
We need to confirm with the guests again.
Miss Ji.
They are coming.
Am I seeing it right?
Ye Qiao is able to smile?
Miss Ye Qiao,
let's take this time to record a promotion video.
Let's go.
Ye Qiao.
Water with brown sugar.
Drink this. It won't take long.
Zheng Hui.
Miss Ji.
Why are you so tired?
Are Zhou Ziqian and Fu Qile back?
Just arrived.
We're the last to arrive today.
Mr. Zhou and Mr. Fu are quite exhausted today.
They didn't even have dinner.
There's no food left?
I just went to have a look.
The food is all cold.
The night recording is about to start.
We don't have time to buy food now.
I thought I'd find something for them
for a quick bite.
You take a rest.
I'll go find something for them.
Okay, thank you, Miss Ji.
Are you feeding pigs?
You didn't eat, right?
I specially prepared
sushi, fruit, and sandwich for you.
And drinks.
I don't know which one you like,
so I bought them all.
How did Coach Zhang trick you here?
With you.
Forget it. Stop talking.
I'll stop then.
Eat up.
He already had food.
Ji Qiu.
Why are you here?
Zhou Hui told me you didn't have dinner.
So I brought you some food.
Good. I'm hungry.
That's all I have.
It's okay.
This is enough.
Have a seat.
There's so much left.
Are you done eating?
I have a friend who hasn't eaten yet.
He's still in the tent.
Thank you.
After you eat,
get some rest.
Or after the recording starts,
you won't be able to sleep even if you want to.
There won't be
any strange games tonight, right?
This is a serious show.
As far as I know,
when you give me this look,
it won't be serious.
Nonsense.
Aren't you saving it for your friend?
He's not hungry.
Here.
Try this. This is pretty good.
Just eat it like this.
It tastes okay, right?
So Miss Ji and Mr. Fu are a couple.
No wonder they look so good together.
I'm done eating.
Miss Ji. Miss Ji.
Emergency!
What is it?
My hand carried too much weight today.
I can't hold chopsticks.
Since I can't hold chopsticks,
I haven't even had dinner.
What should I do?
You didn't have dinner?
Just a little.
I don't care.
I want this bread.
The same one as this.
Take it if you want.
I said I can't move my hands.
You can't move them?
It seems to be better.
Learn from me.
This is acting.
I'm leaving. Get ready.
The recording will start soon.
Before tonight is over,
we have a little game in the end.
The rule of this game is very simple.
Say something that you've never done before.
If a guest has done it,
he/she needs to fold one finger.
If you haven't done it, you don't need to fold it.
The first person who gets ten fingers folded will lose.
As usual,
the loser will be punished. Right?
Exactly.
Your crew is so good at tricks.
Let's talk about the punishment first.
We can talk about the reward first.
The one
with the most fingers left
can ask any of you
a question.
I like it.
Okay, I'll go first.
I've never driven a car.
Neither have I.
I've never sworn.
I've never worn tight pants.
I've never taught students.
Except Mr. Fu,
no one has done that, right?
I've never participated in a shooting competition.
Except Mr. Zhou,
no one has done that either, right?
I've never had a lecture.
I've never won a gold medal.
I've never had a sister.
I've never had a younger brother.
I've never written on the blackboard.
I've never walked with anyone at night.
I've never bought midnight snacks for anyone.
I've never gone shopping with anyone.
I've never done my homework.
I've never shot anyone else's target.
I've never asked for an autograph.
I've never been locked up in the bathroom.
Well...
According to the current situation,
Ye Qiao still has nine chances.
Xiao Chen has eight more chances.
Lin Xiao has
seven chances.
Fu Qile and Zhou Ziqian
each have one chance left.
So Ye Qiao will be the final match point.
OK, I'll go.
I've never fallen in love with anyone.
But what's the standard of "falling in love"?
If I think someone is good-looking,
and I'm happy to see him,
does this count?
Right, Mr. Fu.
In psychology,
what counts as "falling in love"?
♫I've finally got ready to see you♫
♫My heart is pounding with all kinds of feelings♫
If you are in love with someone,
you'll think of her right away when this topic is brought up.
♫How should I hold the flowers so I don't look nervous♫
When you are in love with someone,
when you see her,
♫Your city is so big♫
you can't help laughing.
You want to keep in touch with her all the time.
Every second you can't see her
♫I'm about to see you♫
feels longer than two or three seconds.
As long as you are with her,
♫I must act more natural than you♫
no matter how long it is,
you won't feel bored.
When you see her with another guy,
♫The eyes that can push my tears away♫
you can't help getting angry.
When you are in love with someone, you become a different self.
But everything about her
♫Why are they avoiding me♫
will become very meaningful.
♫I won't let you be afraid♫
♫I've finally got ready to see you♫
♫My heart is pounding with all kinds of feelings♫
Now Zhou Ziqian also folded a finger.
There are two losers now.
Fu Qile and Zhou Ziqian.
As the final winner, Ye Qiao,
you can ask any of them a question.
I'm curious about
Mr. Zhou's performance in the last round.
So this question is for you.
I have a question.
If you can call the one you love
on the spot of a shooting competition,
what would you say first?
I think what
I would say first is,
are you watching my game?
What's wrong?
Why does it sound so familiar?
Miss Ji, you didn't realize
this sentence has no information at all.
Mr. Zhou
was obviously joking.
Is that so?
Because we lost the game,
we have to stay in the same tent.
Are you that happy about it?
Let me correct it.
Even sharing a tent with you
didn't affect my mood.
Why are you
so happy today?
Aren't you a psychology teacher?
Take a guess.
No.
Are you asleep?
Why is the moon so round tonight?
No way.
I'm hallucinating because I've been thinking about it too much.
Zhou Ziqian.
Why are you here?
I'm getting a jacket from the car.
What are you doing here?
I came out to get some fresh air.
You worked hard for the recording today.
Go back and rest early.
I'm off.
Hey, Ji Qiu.
Look.
The weather is so nice today.
Why don't you come with me to see the stars
and enjoy the moon?
You must be tired from shooting today.
I heard from Zhou Hui that you almost walked back.
It's alright. The thing is...
The thing is...
We encountered a few games on the way, right?
We barely played any.
We didn't succeed,
so we didn't get to ride the vehicle.
How come?
The games we picked are all very simple.
How is it simple?
There was a game of
throwing stones.
I played it for more than 20 times,
but I never succeeded.
My hand almost cramped.
This game requires skills.
Skills?
Of course.
When you play this game,
you need to stretch your hands
but relax your fingers.
Like this? Like this?
Like this.
No.
It's like this.
Why is a shooter's hand so stiff?
♫I've thought about it many times♫
♫I have thrown away this charming and empty thing in vain♫
What are you looking at?
♫I pick up the pen and only remember your wish♫
I'm thinking.
♫But my mother said boys can't be too sweet♫
I haven't got it yet.
♫I want to experience so many things with you♫
You don't want to teach anymore?
♫I wish I could have all the good and bad sides of you♫
I don't think it's about the game.
It's about the person who plays.
♫I hope we can be the only light♫
♫That we can see in each other's eyes♫
♫I'll learn to be a fool♫
By the way,
your shooting team hired an assistant.
♫Learn to be soft-hearted even if you turn a blind eye♫
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't know until Li Tianyang told me.
♫Clumsy with words but brave for you♫
I didn't want to bring her.
I'm a boy.
If you...
♫Plain and daily but romantic for life♫
If others think I'm finicky, it won't be cool.
I'll learn to be a fool.
It's rare.
You care about what others think.
♫Reckless and anticipated at the same time♫
Of course.
You made a fool of yourself
quite a lot of times in our show.
After the show is aired,
♫There will be a silent arrangement tomorrow♫
other people's thoughts can't be...
Can I bribe the staff then?
♫No sorrow, no joy, I'm so touched♫
It depends on how you bribe her.
Ji Qiu.
♫I've loved so many people♫
How could you be like this?
♫I know I will go through♫
♫All kinds of scenary with you♫
♫Hold me cause I'm drunk in you♫
♫I'll learn to be a fool♫
♫Learn to be soft-hearted even if you turn a blind eye♫
♫Clumsy with words but brave for you♫
♫Plain and daily but romantic for life♫
♫I'll learn to be a bad boy♫
♫Being playful and cute at the same time♫
Surprise.
Ji Qiu.
I have a very serious question for you.
Go ahead.
From a girl's point of view,
between Zhou Ziqian and I,
which one is better?
[Let's Meet Now]