♪ I walk across the mountains
with elegant footsteps ♪
♪ How much time has passed unknowingly ♪
♪ There's loneliness hidden behind your smile ♪
♪ I'm unable to guess the fire in the water ♪
♪ I'm afraid my youth fades with the wind ♪
♪ Searching the cause and ignoring the results ♪
♪ Asked where I'm from and where I'll be going ♪
♪ I can't say nor can I escape
from myself that I don't know about ♪
♪ Who am I in the past ♪
♪ Who will recognise my face ♪
♪ The person that you know ♪
♪ Is it even me and who am I living for ♪
=Maiden Holmes=
(Episode 25)
We found those maids
upon arriving at the temple.
After checking their pulse,
I realized that
they weren't expelled from the palace
because they were sick.
We got it right.
Brother Xie,
what's wrong with you?
You're so weird.
Are you all right, Brother Xie?
He's fine.
Rushuang, do you find out
what poisoned them?
It's a chronic poison.
The palms of these maids
got swollen all of a sudden and
failed to be cured.
So they were expelled from the palace.
Seven years later,
most of their palms
have deformed.
They only got palms deformed
after being poisoned.
But the late emperor
died of a sudden death.
It's different from the chronic
poisoning symptoms of
those maids.
So I think
someone must have
used some catalytic agent.
So it speeded up the poisoning.
Can you be sure of that?
I need a little bit more time.
As long as I can find out the poison,
I'll find the catalytic agent.
That's great!
Brother Xie,
what's wrong with you today?
Two days ago, you looked sad and gloomy.
And you're laughing happily today.
Has something good happened?
Tell us.
Little Fei Yuan,
nothing good happened.
I don't know why
I just can't help laughing.
You looked so gloomy recently,
and I wanted to make you happy.
So I gave you a little bit
of laughing medicine.
Laughing medicine?
Sister Rushuang, you're awesome.
You can even make such rare drug.
Rushuang,
give me the antidote.
I laugh too much
that my belly hurts right now.
Okay.
I can give you the antidote.
But you must promise me that
you won't be sad and gloomy again.
You must be happy like you always do.
Rushuang, I promise you.
Please give me the antidote now.
All right. I'll give it to you.
The antidote is on the desk in my room.
It's in a white bottle.
Drink it and you'll be fine.
Okay.
Keep chatting and I'll get the antidote.
It's been a long time since
we heard him laughing open-heartedly.
Brother Pei, Sister Su,
has he spoken to you
about anything recently?
What's wrong?
I'm not sure what's wrong with him.
I just feel that
he's been avoiding me recently.
It seems like something is bothering him.
Did you talk to him about it?
I did.
But he didn't answer my questions.
I don't know why he is avoiding me.
It seems like he doesn't want me
to know about it.
Rushuang,
everyone has their own secret.
Just like me. I had a secret too.
You should give him some time.
I know.
So I'm not forcing him to tell me.
I just want to be by his side
and make him happy.
When he gets over,
he'll tell me.
The maids were poisoned by
something called
Fei Yue, a rare chronic poison.
It can be catalyzed by Bletilla.
We normally use Bletilla with the herbs
that help invigorate blood.
I've asked Imperial Physician Zhang to
list the prescriptions
that the late emperor
took when he's alive.
Bletilla wasn't in this list.
Are there any other catalytic agents?
Let me look into all these herbs.
You're not coming with me?
I've got other things to do.
Bletilla should be the catalyst.
But why it was not included
in the prescriptions?
Ms. Rushuang,
Hi, Sir.
what kind of herbs
are you looking for today?
Are there any new herbs lately?
Yes. We've just got a new batch.
Please come and take a look.
See.
Let me have a look.
Help yourself.
Just let me know if you want anything,
I'll pack it for you.
-Thank you.
Sir,
I need two taels of Magnolia Ginseng.
All right. Please wait for a second.
-Sir.
-Yes.
That's not what this gentleman asked for.
Yes, it is.
He asked for some Bletilla.
Didn't he say Magnolia Ginseng?
Magnolia Ginseng is Bletilla.
How can they be the same?
Magnolia Ginseng looks like ginseng.
Besides that, it belongs to Magnoliaceae.
The elderly
used to call it Magnolia Ginseng.
But the name has changed.
Here you go.
Right. Magnolia Ginseng is Bletilla.
It's the catalyst.
Yes.
It's Bletilla.
Bletilla is harmless itself.
But the late emperor
had got chronic poison.
So...
Who gave this tonic to the late emperor?
The Empress Dowager.
Her Highness was very closed
to the late emperor.
I knew it.
So
it can't be her
who poisoned the late emperor.
Well then,
could it be that
someone took advantage of her
to present the tonic?
Don't worry.
I'll find what she might know.
Maybe I'll get the answer.
You want some tonics?
Yes.
I got many injuries
in the battles years ago.
So I thought
to take some tonics to be stronger.
Yeah.
You're not young anymore.
You should take care of your body,
and get your own children.
I remember
when the late emperor was still alive,
he often took tonics.
So I thought you might knew about it.
The tonic your father took
was indeed recommended by me.
But it was presented
by the imperial physicians.
But I can't recall
the details of the prescription now.
I remember father once told me that
the tonic he took
three times a day was really effective.
He felt so energetic after having it.
And he felt he was getting younger.
But who knew that
he was poisoned to death
not long after that.
Yeah.
Speaking of the tonic, Princess Consort Yun
did make a lot of efforts in finding it.
It's Princess Consort Yun
who presented the tonic.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna to report the grievance
to His Majesty.
It was Prince Yun.
He was the one
who ordered to poison the clothing,
and took advantage of his wife
to present the tonic.
It's he who killed the late emperor,
and framed the entire Bai Liang Clan.
Calm down.
With his power and authority
in the court,
we can't bring him down
mere with the letters
and our inference on the case.
So we're just letting him break
the law with impunity.
The late emperor,
my parents,
the entire Bai Liang Clan,
as well as
the warriors sacrificed
in the Battle of Honggu
could not die for nothing.
Instead of acting recklessly
and making him alert,
we should try to get the solid evidence
and expose his conspiracy to the public.
Do you have any ideas?
I'll figure it out.
Rushuang,
what are you doing?
I'm doing an experiment.
What experiment?
What kind of experiment that needs
to use so many pieces of cloth?
That's all thanks to
the idot Xie Beiming.
I told him that
I just needed only one type.
Yet he got so many.
I was thinking that after the experiment,
the rest could be used to make
new clothes for Rushuang.
I bought them
from the best cloth store in the capital.
That's great.
We can make some new clothes.
Sister Su,
pick one for yourself.
I think this one suits you.
Right?
Brother Xie, do I look good in this?
Awesome.
You look good in everything.
By the way.
They told me that's the best.
It's the closest to Bai Liang brocade.
Brother Su,
I can get you some
if you like it.
It's Bai Liang brocade.
Are you sure?
Bai Liang Clan would never teach outsiders
about their brocade weaving technique.
Could it be...
Where did you get this?
(Jinxiu Silk Shop)
Sir, please take a look at this.
Is this brocade from your store?
I imported it from somewhere else.
You've got quite good taste.
The brocade in your hand
is the last piece in my store.
Where did you get it?
Miss,
are you trying to compete with me?
It's hard to get brocade
with such quality.
And they don't produce much
or at stable frequency.
I can't tell you for nothing.
Where exactly did you get the brocade?
Tell us.
I got it from the Xu family in Nanxun.
(Tea house)
Here's the tea.
The steamed bun will be served shortly.
(Nanxun Town)
You may leave us.
There's quite a number of
people left the town today.
Yeah.
I'd leave too
if we don't own
a huge mulberry orchard.
Hey, guys.
Why are there so many people
leaving the town?
There's an outbreak of plague in the town.
An outbreak of plague?
Will we get infected?
Little Fei Yuan, I'm here.
What are you afraid of?
It's the Xu family.
They got cursed by the silkworm empress.
And now everyone in town has to suffer.
I agree.
The Xu Family...
Hey, guys.
Are you talking about the Xu
Family, the silk merchant?
Yes.
Are you here to buy some silk?
You'd better not.
Have you guys heard about this?
The silkworm empress statue caught fire
in the celebration two days ago.
The next day,
one of the staff in the Xu family
was found dead in the silkworm house
with his head being wrapped in
white cloth just like a cocoon.
The murderer was so cold-blooded.
He wrapped the victim into a cocoon.
Bill, please.
No one murdered the staff.
That was the punishment
from silkworm empress.
Why was the Xu family
punished by the silkworm empress?
That's a long story.
In Nanxun Town,
almost every household is involved
in silk reeling business.
Some of us even produce brocade.
We all are blessed
by the silkworm empress.
The rich families will compete to
hold a celebration
for the silkworm empress
in the town every year.
Praying that they'll have a great
and prosperous year ahead.
The Xu family finally got the chance to
hold that celebration this year.
But the tragedy happened.
They're so unlucky.
The Xu family
has prospered for seven years.
It's about time.
Seven years?
You siad the Xu family has
prospered for seven years.
What happened seven years ago
leaving you such deep impression?
Seven years ago,
the Xu family mastered a very complicated
brocade weaving technique out of nowhere.
Ever since then,
they beat the Sun family
and became the biggest
silk merchant in town.
Sir,
do you know who in the Xu family
mastered this brocade weaving technique?
Lady Xu.
We all suspect that
Lady Xu
must have traded with the silkworm empress
to learn such great technique.
Otherwise,
why did she die
when the Xu family was in the prime?
She is dead?
A trade is a trade.
They'd have to
pay it one day.
You guys are talking nonsense.
It's true.
After Lady Xu passed away,
the Xu family could still hold up.
But none of their staff
could produce high-quality
brocade like Lady Xu.
And their business went downhill.
But some people said that
she was killed by the concubine.
Who knows.
Did she marry Master Xu seven years ago?
No.
She came from Nanxun Town.
Brother Pei, look at the woman over there.
Is she going to jump into the river?
Oh no!
Somebody was jumping into the river.
(Nanxun Hotel)
Miss, you're finally awake.
How do you feel?
Am I...
Am I dead?
If you're dead,
then we're all ghosts.
We wouldn't sit and see
you kill yourself, would we?
Why did you save me?
Miss,
is there something bad happened to you
that makes you want to commit suicide?
My father forced me to marry Sun Bo.
I didn't want it.
They wouldn't listen to me.
They forced me.
Although marriage is supposed to be
arranged by our parents,
our will is important too.
How could he force you to marry someone?
Sun Bo is after
my family's wealth.
He kept coming to my house to trouble us.
If he's after your family's wealth,
Why would your father
force you to marry him?
My family
held a celebration few days ago.
Something went wrong in that celebration.
Sun Bo took this chance
to stir up the hatred among
the people in the town
to fight against my father.
My dad had no choice.
You're the daughter of the Xu Family?
Yes.
I'm the eldest daughter.
Ms. Xu,
can you tell us what happened
during the celebration?
It's our turn this year to
hold the celebration
for the silkworm empress.
My father paid so much attention to this.
We prepared for
the celebration months ago.
My father told me that
it's one of the biggest celebrations
in town.
It has to be a success.
My father booked the entire tea house
this morning,
so that we can
watch the celebration from here.
We can see everything clearly,
in this quiet environment.
Your father is so good to you.
Look, it's the silkworm empress.
It's the silkworm empress.
Let's go and take a look.
It catches fire.
It catches fire. Why is this happening?
Help! Be careful!
Move!
You...
What do you want to do?
Everyone in town knows that
your family have screwed up the celebration.
That's right.
And now there's an outbreak
of plague in town.
Yeah.
What are you going to do to stop all these?
What are you going to do?
-Tell us!
How could you say that
we brought all these to the town?
Maybe one of you
insulted the silkworm empress.
Xu Mengchang,
if it's not you,
how come one of your staff, He Da
was killed in the silkworm house?
Yeah.
That's enough.
Or else,
I'll sue you.
How dare you?
We shouldn't let him off the hook.
Stop it.
Give us an explanation.
Calm down, everyone.
Master Sun is coming.
-Master Sun.
-Calm down.
Master Sun, please say something.
Master Xu,
come with me.
Come with me.
Please calm down, everyone.
Master Sun is here to help us.
Master Xu,
have you thought about the suggestion
that I gave you the other day?
If I can marry Qingmei,
you'll be my father-in-law and
I'll definitely help you.
Sun Bo,
I know that you're after
our silkworm rearing technique
for a long time.
Tell me.
Did you kill my staff?
Master Xu,
please don't make any accusations
when you have no proof.
I'm here to help you.
I can't stop them
from making a big fuss
if you don't give me your daughter.
Besides,
Xu Qingmei is the daughter
of your late wife.
And you don't like her.
Give her to me.
And you won't have to see her again.
And we'll be a family.
Master Xu,
it's win-win.
Your father is so cruel.
No parents will harm their child.
And he forced you to marry Sun
Bo just to settle the riot.
My mother...
My mother passed away a long time ago.
No wonder your father favors
your younger sister
and pushes you to hell.
They've been treating
me like this
for so many years.
I'm used to it.
Ms. Xu,
you said the statue caught
fire out of nowhere.
What happened?
I don't know.
It happened in a flash.
It caught fire when everyone was watching.
It's like magic.
That staff who was killed...
He Da.
Yes.
When did he die?
How did he die?
He died on the day
when the celebration was held.
His body looked very strange.
Everyone in the town said that
he was punished by the silkworm empress.
Did he
have any enemies?
I don't think so.
What were your family doing
when He Da was killed?
I was with madam during the celebration.
After the fire incident,
something happened on our way home.
So we got home late.
It was already afternoon when we're home.
My father and the others got home
earlier than me and madam.
Ms. Xu, take a good rest.
Don't think about this anymore.
Here you go, Sir.
(Morgue)
The piece of silver is for you.
All right. Please follow me.
Sir,
do you know about the details
on He Da's murder?
You'd better
not to look into the case.
He's not killed by human being.
On the 10th day of the 9th
month in lunar calendar,
we found his body
at the silkworm house in
the Xu family's residence.
His head was wrapped into a cocoon.
No wound was on his body.
It's strange, isn't it?
It must be the punishment
from the silkworm empress.
That day
was also celebration day, right?
You're right.
He had been staying in the
silkworm house for half a month
to look after the silkworm larvae.
This is one of the rules here.
And that date
was the third hibernation
period of the silkworms.
The date can't be wronged.
It's stated on He Da's record.
What do you mean
by third hibernation period?
All of silkworms in our town
produce cocoons only after
the 4th hibernation period.
The time is fixed.
Have any officers looked
into the suspects?
Yes.
But,
it's really not like done by human.
He Da had no family.
They simply processed his body
and sent it to the morgue.
His body is in this coffin.
You guys can come and take a look.
How's it?
Did you see anything strange?
His face had turned purple.
No physical wound was on his body.
He was suffocated to death.
Sir,
who sent his body here?
Mr. and Master Xu
reported to the government.
But I'm not sure who found the body.
By the way.
What's left
of the burnt silkworm empress statue?
It was burnt to ashes.
Nothing was left.
We couldn't find any clues on the body.
Let's pay a visit to the Xu family.
Sister Su,
I'm not going with you all.
I want to find the source of the plague
so that I could find a cure for it
as soon as possible.
All right.
See you.
I'll...
You must stay by my side.
Please be careful.
Let's go.
It's urgent.
Let's go to the Xu family.
Are you planning to go wearing this?
What's wrong with my outfit?
Goodbye.
Please come again.
Sure.
How can I help you?
Dear,
just take a look around.
See if there's anything that you like.
We come from the capital.
We've heard that Nanxun Town
is known for its silk.
So we thought to buy some shops here
for our satin business.
Do you have any recommendation?
The Xu family is one of the
biggest satin stores here.
They own some shops and property too.
I think they're putting their business
on sale now.
Why's that?
Master Xu was interested in
a high-quality Hetian Jade in my store.
He even paid the down payment for it.
But he didn't come
to get it for so many days.
And they got into troubles recently.
I think they've got some
problems with their cash flow.
Can I have a look at the Hetian jade?
Sure.
Sir,
here is the jade.
It's as white as snow.
It's refined.
And the structure looks good.
It's pretty good.
Do you like it?
What do you think?
I've never given you any gifts before.
I'll buy this jade for you.
How much is this jade?
It's cheap.
Only 100 taels.
100 taels!
And you say it's cheap?!
Sir,
It's fine, dear.
What...
You can keep your savings
to buy some make-up.
It's too expensive.
It's good enough you're thinking
of buying me gifts.
Welcome.
Hi.
Why did you buy the jade?
Dear,
you can buy what you like in the future.
I can afford it.
No.
It's too expensive.
Sir.
All right. I'm just joking with you.
I need this to solve the case.
To solve the case?
Come on.
We need to get some new clothes.
Hold on.
Why do we have to get new clothes?
We're going to visit the
Xu family, right?
Those are our props.
Why we need props?
Please queue up and wait.
Everyone has a chance.
Rushuang, everything is ready.
I've spoken to the shopkeeper.
He agreed to let me
use all the herbs in the store for free.
All I have to do is
to examine their symptoms and
find the similarities among them.
Then I should be able
to find the solutions.
All right.
Let me do it, Rushuang.
Let me get you a bandage.
Rushuang,
I'm fine. It's just a minor cut.
I'm fine.
No.
We don't know how the disease spread?
We must be careful.
Rushuang,
I'm
not afraid to die.
Stop talking nonsense.
How do I survive if you die?
Rushuang,
You're so good.
I'm not worth it.
Later, let me talking with them.
You observe and see if there's
anything strange.
Okay.
(Xu Mansion)
Here we are.
Let's go.
Go.
Master,
What's it?
A gentleman is waiting to see you.
He told me that...
I'm not going to meet anyone.
This is a critical time.
How can you let strangers
come in to our mansion?
The man comes with his wife.
And it seems like they're rich.
He told me that he's here
to do business with us.
Really?
Hurry up.
Invite them to the living room.
Please drink some tea.
I come from the capital.
I heard that you're selling your property.
So I thought I should come
and talk to you about it.
I'm getting old.
And I don't have a son.
Our family owns a lot of property.
I can't pass all these
to my daughter, can I?
So I thought it's better to
sell it to someone else.
How much property do you own?
We have 2 shops,
57 acres of mulberry orchard
and 3 silkworm houses.
To be frank,
my family owns a few shops in the capital,
doing trades with the Purchasing
Bureau in the palace.
We've been supplying satin to
the palace all these years.
But we cannot always get high-quality satin.
So the elderly have decided
to acquire a satin company.
So we don't have to
travel around for good satin.
That's why
we're here.
You've come to the right place.
To be honest.
our technique in silkworm breeding,
silk reeling and brocade weaving is unique.
Unique?
Well.
How about the Sun family?
Their brocade
is nowhere near ours.
My late wife mastered
a unique brocade weaving technique
seven years ago.
No one in Nanxun knew the
technique except her.
Well, you've got me
curious about it.
Can we take a look at the brocade
that you produce?
Sure.
Is anybody there?
Master.
Get our high-quality brocade.
You can leave us now.
All right.
It's the Bai Liang brocade.
The brocade is indeed of good quality.
But...
Master Xu,
the brocade weaving technique that you used
is similar to Bai Liang's brocade
weaving technique.
Well...
Sir,
that's nonsense.
Dear,
the Bai Liang Clan broke the law,
and the entire clan was given
the death-sentence.
Anyone related was questioned.
Your wild guess
will put Master Xu in danger.
That's right.
You're right.
I'm sorry for all that, Master Xu.
That's fine.
I was too excited just now.
I've been supplying brocade
to the palace these few years.
I can't help but
to compare your brocade
with Bai Ling brocade
because they're very similar.
I've heard the Bai Liang Clan
never gave out their technique.
And the entire clan
was sentenced to death.
It doesn't make sense
if they're the same.
You're right.
I'm curious that
how you've got such unique technique.
Where did your late wife learn
this technique from?
Well...
I really don't know about this.
My late wife locked herself up
for half a month.
And after that,
she mastered it all of a sudden.
Did your late wife have contact with
anyone before she locked herself up?
Master, the celebration has
turned into a disaster.
Is...
Is the silkworm empress punishing us?
What are you afraid of?
Look at how He Da died.
Shut up.
There's an outbreak of plague in the town.
Everyone is blaming us for it.
How are we going to live in this town.
It's all because of Sun Bo.
Sun Bo took this chance
to stir up the hatred
He did all that because
he's after my family's wealth.
And Qing Mei is so stubborn.
What she has to do is marry Sun Bo
and all would get over.
And now she has gone missing.
What should we do
if Sun Bo comes to cause trouble?
Yes.
We should find a solution.
No.
Master,
are you going to let Sun Bo marry Bingjie?
Father, Mother,
I'm still young.
I don't want to leave you.
No.
How could I let Sun Bo marry you.
Now,
if someone can acquire our property,
we'll leave this place.
That's a good option.
Look at our situation.
Who else will acquire our property
besides Sun Bo who is after our wealth?
♪ Feeling lonely and left out ♪
♪ The whimpering of the flute
and the faraway star ♪
♪ I don't know when I'll return
as long as my travel goes on ♪
♪ I dream of coming back every night ♪
♪ Through the rain and dust ♪
♪ A deep love I feel for you ♪
♪ Looking at the vast lands
and sighing out of loneliness ♪
♪ Where can I go to find you ♪
♪ A promise for life from both of us ♪
♪ After many separations and gatherings ♪
♪ I will never disappoint you
when we meet again ♪
♪ For life ♪