♪ I walk across the mountains
with elegant footsteps ♪
♪ How much time has passed unknowingly ♪
♪ There's loneliness hidden behind your smile ♪
♪ I'm unable to guess the fire in the water ♪
♪ I'm afraid my youth fades with the wind ♪
♪ Searching the cause and ignoring the results ♪
♪ Asked where I'm from and where I'll be going ♪
♪ I can't say nor can I escape
from myself that I don't know about ♪
♪ Who am I in the past ♪
♪ Who will recognise my face ♪
♪ The person that you know ♪
♪ Is it even me and who am I living for ♪
=Maiden Holmes=
(Episode 7)
Young master, this way.
This is
your study and bedroom.
Let's go, I'll show you.
Fei Yuan.
Where is the guest room?
The guest room...
The guest rooms are in the side and back yards.
This way.
Lead the way.
Here, young master.
Look.
At your command,
I have converted the largest master room
into a guest room.
Not bad.
Right, over here.
Young master.
This is what you asked me
to prepare for Detective Su.
The folklore about Prince Qi.
Young master.
Why don't you just tell him that
you are Prince Qi.
It's not a good timing.
All right.
I'll show you the other rooms.
Okay.
Let's go.
Such a nice house.
I thought that Brother Pei was the kind of
childe's aesthetic.
It seems that I still don't know him well.
What kind of childe's aesthetic would that be?
It's the type of aesthetics
like Xie Beiming has.
All the houses he showed me recently
were magnificent,
with carved beams and painted buildings,
as if he wishes to be inlaid with gold
at all the corners.
I'm just an errand boy,
I can't afford that.
From what I see, Brother Pei
could definitely afford it.
Why would you say that?
Here is in a downtown
with convenient transportation.
The land value and rent
are among the top in the capital.
Although there is no gold
or jade inlaid in this mansion,
the design is charming and unique,
and the furnishings
are exquisite and meticulous.
It is by no means
ordinary residential building.
I had a rough look at it just now.
There are about 20 servants in the mansion.
If we calculate
on the basis of one tael of silver
per person per month,
Brother Pei would have to pay
more than 20 tael of silver
as for the monthly salary.
Not to mention some experienced servants,
the monthly salary will be higher.
Brother Pei.
I'm afraid your identity
is not as simple as you said.
This is the villa of my ancestors,
no rent is required.
Also, my family has been running some business
which makes a lot of money every month,
and I just rely on them,
otherwise I can't afford it
with my own salary.
Let's go over there.
Okay.
Here, this way.
Brother Pei, it's just an average house.
Actually, I can pay for it.
And you can make it more gorgeous.
What do you think?
Gorgeous?
The houses he looked for me
were indeed much more gorgeous.
Rushuang...
You've just arrived in the capital,
I just hope that you can live more comfortably.
My eyes nearly got blind
seeing the houses inlaid with gold and jade.
And you said it was comfortable?
What's over there?
There's a garden there.
I'll show you.
Okay.
Let's go.
This way.
Brother Pei.
Are the rooms of me and Rushuang
close to each other?
Sorry,
I didn't arrange a room for you.
Then...
Didn't Fei Yuan say that
there are three guest rooms?
I think my house is too dull and not a match
for the childe's aesthetic standard
in which inlaid with gold and jade.
Brother Pei.
I have thought about it.
I think
my style matches this simple and elegant style
very well.
But the room is too small,
I'm afraid it would be uncomfortable for you.
It's not small at all.
It's better to have a bunch of people together.
Am I right?
Look! Maple leaves.
Yeah.
The maple leaves are so beautiful.
Try it.
This brush...
I've seen this before
when I was working in the palace.
But where did you get it?
I got this from the Prince Qi,
I don't need it myself.
I'll give it to you.
It's too expensive.
Just take it.
I'm just a rough man,
I could carry knives and guns,
but not this.
The folklore about Prince Qi!
Brother Pei.
Why do you have so much
of the folklore about Prince Qi?
I got them for you.
For me?
I know you like them.
Does that make you so happy?
Brother Pei.
Come in.
Little Su.
Brother Pei.
Thank you for arranging a room for us.
I know I shouldn't
bother you again,
but I think it's better
to make something clear.
Have a seat.
You should first have a look at this.
(Lease Agreement)
(Lessee: Su Ci, Lessor: Pei Zhao)
Lease agreement?
Sit down.
I should pay the rent
as I live here.
You can set a price.
No, Little Su. I just want to...
I can understand.
Which is why
I can't take this kindness
for granted,
and that's not a gentleman should do.
If I don't collect the rent,
Little Su would definitely
refuse for a long stay.
Okay.
Then five tael of silver per month.
Five tael of silver...
Then I couldn't have enough to buy the folklore.
But it's reasonable,
it's worth the price.
We made a deal.
I'll add it in the agreement later.
Besides that...
Given to our circumstance,
I also drafted additional terms.
Here they are.
Keep it a secret for the lessee,
and shall not use it to blackmail...
Physical contact?
And other non-compliance actions.
During the contract period,
the same-sex intercourse
must be strictly observed.
If there is any violation,
the lessee has the right
to demand compensation,
the compensation details are as follows.
Here.
If there is a clear intention of verbal offense
or physical contact,
a fine of one tael,
if committed again, then...
Wait.
I feel that your contract is just for
binding me.
In return,
under the reasonable
and ethical circumstances,
I will also provide assistance
such as investigating cases.
It sounds like you're going to help me
deal with my affairs after an accident.
No.
That's not what I mean.
I have to think about it.
Since the owner doesn't agree,
I'll move out tomorrow.
The room rate tonight,
just calculate
based on the market price of the inn.
Thank you, Brother Pei.
Wait, Little Su.
Okay, I'll sign it.
It's effective now, here you go.
I'm going back now.
Okay.
Goodbye.
I'm such a pity landlord.
Lease agreement?
Young master, so mean of you.
This...
Ain't both of you are friends?
How could you collect the rental fees?
Little Su insists.
He's such a principled person.
Five tael?
Young master, you're
such a blackhearted landlord.
What...
Detective Su's monthly salary
was only seven tael,
and you collect five tael from her?
This...
How do you want Detective Su to live?
What?
Little Su's monthly salary was only seven tael?
I heard it from Detective Su
last time when we chatted.
It seems that I should find a way
to raise the salary of Mingjing Office.
(Lessee: Su Ci, Lessor: Pei Zhao)
The legal codes of Liang
are divided into six parts.
They are theft and robbery law,
treason law, prisoner law,
law of arrest, miscellaneous law,
and criminal law.
The basic content is roughly
divided into three parts.
The first part is...
The most beautiful moment...
Keep it.
Don't you have breakfast
with the homeowner?
I still have unfinished tasks
in Mingjing office,
I'm not going to eat.
Brother Pei, do as you wish.
No physical contact.
We've already written it in the contract,
the one who breaks the rules
will be fined one tael of silver.
Does it count?
Young master.
What are you guys talking about?
The young officer is trying hard
to make me reduce my rent.
Yes, you should.
One more tael of silver
will be added for verbal teasing.
Ain't we are friends?
Since we are friends,
why can't we do it
like before?
Before?
Little Su.
Don't you want the pieces of silver?
Weird, so weird.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-This way, please.
-Welcome.
-Congratulations.
Childe, this way please.
-Welcome.
-This way, please.
Your Highness.
(Fu Mansion)
Officer Fu.
It's the greatest honor
for Your Highness's presence.
Officer Fu, you're welcome.
Ziyou and I are like brothers,
of course I have to be here
to celebrate his big day.
Where is the groom?
Ziyou?
He went out early in the morning
to pick up the bride.
I can tell that he was in a hurry.
Getting married is a significant event in life,
the etiquette can't be neglected.
Your Highness, please.
Right, did Zizhuo go with him?
I'm so busy
that I've forgotten about him.
Probably.
Officer Su.
Officer Shen.
I've heard Ministry of Personnel
just informed us
we're going to have a pay raise.
Really?
Why so sudden?
Are you serious?
Our daily work is so risky,
we deserved a raise long ago.
You are right.
Great, I can buy the folklore.
Your Highness, please.
Young master,
why hasn't the bride come yet?
Welcoming the bride would not be easy.
Everyone makes it difficult for the groom,
so that they can ask for more money.
Master!
Master, something bad happened.
Su Ci.
(Case File)
A body was found under the city walls this morning.
It has been proved to be
the daughter of the Du family.
The one going to marry
Commander Fu today?
This case involves the courtiers,
Mayor of Capital City
has transferred the case to us.
You are now in charge of this.
Yes, My Lord.
I've recorded all the evidence
and the process of handling the case
in this booklet.
Keep it.
Brother Su, are you heading to the crime scene?
Why are you here?
I can't go into the Mingjing Office.
So I can only wait here.
Rushuang, I'm in a hurry.
I should go now.
I know.
(Mingjing Office)
I'm here to help you.
I have all the autopsy tools ready.
Miss Du died miserably.
All right, stop looking.
Never thought she would leave
at such a young age.
Stop gather around. Step out of the way.
Detective Su.
Could it be that ghost bride?
She has come back to haunt.
Stop it. It's so creepy.
Miss Du
looks so horrible.
Yeah, so bad.
Joint dislocation,
obvious fracture of the scapula,
fatal injury is the neck fracture,
showing death form of
falling from high altitude.
Is this Su Ci, Detective Su?
Indeed, never heard of him?
He is the great detective Su Ci.
It's true that she jumped down.
Brother Su, where are we going now?
Rushuang, don't follow me.
Let me follow you.
I promise not to make trouble.
You're not a member of the government,
you will be criticized for this.
But...
I have followed you
since we were investigating
a case in Qingshui County.
But this case involves
the daughter of a courtier,
it's not appropriate.
You should go back.
Then...
Then I should just go back.
I'll go back.
Be careful on your way home.
The government is gathering
information from witnesses.
Whoever saw the girl
in the portrait last night,
with any clues
can report to the government,
and will be rewarded once verified.
Rumors say that it was Miss Du who found dead.
A wedding that became a funeral.
(Collecting Witness Clue)
She is the apple of Master Du's eye,
getting married to the
eldest son of the Fu family,
why did she die?
What do you mean by this?
The Mingjing Office
would like to ask you a few questions.
What questions?
Did you meet Miss Du yesterday?
Miss Du?
Do you mean my sister-in-law?
She was dead.
Someone had witnessed
two of you were together last night,
so we would like to know
what actually happened last night.
What? Who have died?
Ms. Du Lan.
She was found dead under the city walls.
Xiao Lan?
The young lady got along better
with the second son of the Fu family
since she was a child.
I think they've agreed on eloping
last night.
Go ahead.
But the young lady came back
right after they met,
and said
she had made up her mind.
Made up her mind?
What was that about?
She'd decided to get married.
She said that
the elder son of the Fu family is nice.
She would live a life
for the reputation of the two families.
Did anything else happen last night?
No.
I didn't leave until I had served
the young lady to sleep.
No one else saw your young lady
when she went out in the middle of the night?
Does this baggage belong to your young lady?
Can I open it?
Did she bring this yesterday when she went out?
No, she didn't.
Ms. Xiao Qing, think carefully.
What's unusual about your young lady
besides seeing the second son of the Fu family?
Unusual?
Yeah.
Like
some unusual acts.
You can tell me.
My young lady...
My young lady would hear
the raindrops for no reason.
Raindrops?
That day she looked out of the window in a daze,
and suddenly asked me
to listen to the rain with her,
saying that
the sound of rain was good.
But when I looked out the window,
it wasn't raining.
Did she act like this before?
Never before.
Listen to the raindrops on a sunny day,
that was really weird.
Detective Su.
We've caught Fu Zizhuo.
Detective Su,
he hadn't sobered up
when he was caught,
and he refused to say a word.
Okay.
-Little Su.
-We'll go now.
Okay.
Brother Pei.
I've heard about it.
So I came to you
and wanted to help you with the case.
We don't need your help.
Little Su.
The Fu brothers are my friends,
I should do something for them.
I hope you can understand.
All right, you may follow us.
We've caught
the second son of the Fu family.
What?
Fu Zizhuo is not a prisoner,
why did you lock him up?
I guess you don't know that
he has gone mad
when hearing about the death of Miss Du,
and none of us could catch him.
It was hard to get him here.
After bringing him back,
he didn't say a word
like he have lost his soul.
We had no choice
but to lock him up.
This way, please.
He must be emotionally unstable
after the tragedy,
so let me talk to him first.
Okay.
Zizhuo.
Your Highness.
They said Xiao Lan was dead.
Is it true?
It's true.
How could it be?
How would she...
Zizhuo, listen to me.
Detective Su
from the Mingjing Office investigates it.
She is fair and intelligent,
she can definitely find out the truth
and won't let Miss Du died for nothing.
You must cooperate with her.
Make sure you tell her everything you know.
Okay.
Detective Su doesn't know my identity yet,
so...
Detective Su, you may come in now.
Master Fu, I'm Su Ci from Mingjing Office.
Detective Su, please find out the truth.
That's what I should do.
Master Fu, I hope you
don't hide anything from me.
For the sake of Xiao Lan,
I will tell everything I know.
You are accused of meeting with Miss Du
outside the capital gate last night.
Is that real?
Yes.
Why did you meet each other?
Xiao Lan and I promised each other
to elope to the borders,
and stay together anonymously.
Xiao Lan?
I've been worried that you won't come.
The carriage is just
outside the capital, let's go.
No, Zizhuo.
I can't go.
Neither can you.
Xiao Lan, what's wrong?
I'm here
to tell you that
we're done.
No.
Why?
Didn't we agree to leave together?
If we leave,
we'll be unfaithful to our elder brother
and unfilial to our parents.
Even if we live on the borders,
we won't feel at ease.
I don't want to make
the elders of the two families
become the laughing stock of the capital
because of us.
Have you made up your mind?
It's our fate.
I sent Xiao Lan back to Du Mansion,
then I went to buy some drink.
Then I left the capital.
You were out of the capital last night?
Yeah.
I was drunk.
I returned to the capital after dawn.
Then I found a tavern and continued to drink.
Why were you out of the capital?
Xiao Lan and elder brother were going to marry,
I didn't know how to face them.
I just wanted to find a place and hide up.
Does anyone can be your alibi?
Why would you ask me that?
Zizhuo.
At present,
your suspicion is indeed the biggest.
You suspect me?
It's impossible that I would kill Xiao Lan.
Young master, please calm down.
As far as the situation is concerned,
you seem to have the intention to do so.
So,
please think carefully.
Does anyone can be your alibi
when you left the capital?
I got drunk and went out of the capital,
continued to drink,
and then I fell asleep.
Have you returned on half way?
No.
Were you wearing the same clothes
since last night?
Can you take them off and let me have a look?
We may find traces on his clothes,
while he was outside the capital,
to prove his innocence.
I know him well.
Even if elopement fails,
he will not kill.
We have to find the evidence
to prove his innocence.
The death of Miss Du
can only reveal
until we find the truth.
Since he said that
he left the capital in the middle of the night,
then I'll go
to restore the scene tonight.
I'll go with you.
I don't feel safe
if letting you handle the case alone
late at night.
Besides,
I have to do my part
as a friend.
All right.
For friends.
Let's go.
Right,
you should go back first and wait for me.
I have another place to go.
Mansion of Fu?
I used to think that
you're the most dull to emotions,
but I didn't expect that
you're the most attentive in this case.
Put heart to heart,
the sudden loss of the beloved,
Ziyou is the most innocent
and painful person.
You should comfort him.
Ziyou.
Your Highness.
Why didn't I get apprised?
Have a seat.
I'm just here to pay you a visit.
I asked them to do so,
so as not to disturb others.
Thank you for your concern.
Have a seat.
I didn't get to show her
the painting.
Ziyou.
I've met Zizhuo.
Actually, Zizhuo...
I already know.
You knew it?
Xiao Lan and I are engaged.
But in fact, Zizhuo has been closer to her
than I since childhood.
Two days ago,
I accidentally saw a letter of Zizhuo,
in which he said that
he was willing to give up everything
and leave the capital with Xiao Lan.
You knew they were about to elope?
Yeah.
And you...
Didn't stop them?
One is my brother,
and the other is my lover.
If Xiao Lan chose to go with Zizhuo,
I would be willing to help her.
But if Xiao Lan chose to stay,
I'd be good to her for the rest of my life
and prove that she had made a right decision.
But who knows...
Ziyou.
Do you think Zizhuo would kill people?
I don't know.
The truth is all I want.
If she killed herself,
I want to know the reason.
But if it's a homicide,
I'll let the killer pay for it.
Goodbye, Prince Qi.
Now I realize that if you like someone,
you give
without expecting anything in return.
Love should be selfless,
not selfish.
Little Su.
No matter what you choose,
I'll be there to protect you.
Little Su.
Brother Pei.
I was going to read while waiting for you,
but I fell asleep.
That's okay.
You can rest for a while
if you're tired.
No, I've had enough sleep.
What time is it now?
Just after 7 p.m..
Let's move now before it's too late.
Okay.
Zizhuo leaves the city from here.
Where would he head for next?
Many dyeing workshops
are on the west of capital suburb,
people who passing by
will leave some traces of dye
on the clothes and shoes.
Look here.
I guess
he must've been heading to the west.
What now? Where are we going?
Fu Zizhuo said he had walked for a while,
then stopped to drink
and fell asleep.
Look.
The green marks on this
should be the juice from the grass,
and the wrinkle on his back
should be left after
the clothes were wet with dew
and dried.
So now
we should look for a grassy area
and there should be a big tree next to it.
Look here.
This is...
Bird's dropping?
He should have been lying down,
the bird droppings on his body,
then he wiped it with his hands.
Let's go over there.
Look at this.
This wine jar belonged to Zizhuo?
Probably.
It means that
Zizhuo was outside the capital last night.
But it's just the route we speculated.
Give me the clothes.
I mean the evidence.
I want to see
if there are any other clues.
Thank you.
Why you sigh?
I'm just lamenting that
love doesn't always end well.
Little Su.
Miss Du's death would be a painful
and a lifelong grief for Zizhuo.
Although
I can't help him out,
I hope I'm able to find out the truth.
I'll be with you.
Little Su, thank you.
From now on, we could enjoy the food
made by Little Fei Yuan as we live together.
Look, this is the kitchen.
Brother Pei, you have a bed in the kitchen?
Fei Yuan, why didn't anyone tell me that
the kitchen had moved to another place?
I haven't had the chance to tell you...
Young master.
Are you named...
Xiao Yao?
Young Master, my name is Xiao Xue.
From now on, you will be called Xiao Yao.
All right.
Let's go. Let's move to the backyard.
Brother Pei.
You recognize neither the people nor the house.
Is this your house for real?
I don't pay much attention to them.
There are too many maids here,
it's normal to remember wrongly.
No, there are just two or three women here.
Look, the rest are all men.
All right.
Go and see the rooms.
Let's go and see the rooms!
I've told you to remember the people well.
Let's move.
♪ After many separations and gatherings ♪
♪ I will not disappoint you when we meet again ♪
♪ I will never disappoint you for life ♪
♪ Feeling lonely and left out ♪
♪ The whimpering of the flute
and the faraway star ♪
♪ I don't know when I'll return
as long as my travel goes on ♪
♪ I dream of coming back every night ♪
♪ Through the rain and dust ♪
♪ A deep love I feel for you ♪
♪ Looking at the vast lands
and sighing out of loneliness ♪
♪ Where can I go to find you ♪
♪ A promise for life from both of us ♪
♪ After many separations and gatherings ♪
♪ I will never disappoint you
when we meet again ♪
♪ For life ♪