♪ I walk across the mountains
with elegant footsteps ♪
♪ How much time has passed unknowingly ♪
♪ There's loneliness hidden behind your smile ♪
♪ I'm unable to guess the fire in the water ♪
♪ I'm afraid my youth fades with the wind ♪
♪ Searching the cause and ignoring the results ♪
♪ Asked where I'm from and where I'll be going ♪
♪ I can't say nor can I escape
from myself that I don't know about ♪
♪ Who am I in the past ♪
♪ Who will recognise my face ♪
♪ The person that you know ♪
♪ Is it even me and who am I living for ♪
=Maiden Holmes=
(Episode 9)
Father.
Zhi.
Come here.
Take a seat.
Father.
I know about the list of candidates
for Prince Qi's Princess Consort.
Did you tell her about it?
Sorry, my Lord.
It's my fault.
Father, don't be mad.
That's what I want.
Don't blame Ying Ying.
You're dismissed.
Yes.
Here. Take a seat.
Zhi.
You should be able to tell
there's something fishy
behind the list, right?
I know.
No young aristocratic ladies are chosen.
It's obvious
who's behind it.
Since you know,
why do you want to risk it
and insist on marrying
none other than Prince Qi?
I once said
that my husband
must be like you.
Loyal, brave, unyielding,
smart and bold.
A real gentleman.
Prince Qi
is that kind of man.
Wait for me!
This place is so beautiful.
The view is really good.
Miss, pick a wishing lamp.
(Puhua Temple)
Brother Su.
Is this your first time here
like me?
Rushuang.
There are so many fun places
in the capital.
I can go with you.
I...
You...
Toss higher.
(Miraculous Fortune-telling)
It's so lively.
How did the murderer choose his victim?
And how did he get their information?
Why are all the worshippers girls?
Rushuang, here's the thing.
Puhua Temple is famous
for people praying for marriage.
I've heard that the prayers
are often answered.
Really?
You can pray for marriage
right over there.
Did you see that tree?
That tree is called the marriage tree.
You have to write your name
and the person you like on a board
and toss it on the tree.
Then, you can stay together forever.
Young Master.
Seize the opportunity
to pray for your marriage.
It just so happens that recently...
What is it?
It just so happens
that Young Master's family
has arranged a marriage for him.
Brother Su.
I would like to pray for marriage too.
Why don't you come with me?
It should be
right there!
What about me?
Brother Xie.
It looks like you're the one
who should be worried.
Little Su.
I'll surely help you
so that you can be yourself in the public.
Fang, are you here
to pray for marriage too?
What brings you here?
What are they doing over there?
If you can throw the copper coin
into the lotus flower,
your wish will come true.
Really?
I'll give it a try.
Throw gently.
I hope Brother Su and me...
Rushuang, this is awesome!
Your wish is going to come true.
I'm counting on that, Little Fei Yuan.
Let's check out the marriage tree.
Let's go.
(Meditation Room)
Not bad.
Take a look.
Young man.
You're ruining other people's destiny.
-You should be kind.
-Keep your voice down.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm leaving.
This is an auspicious oracle.
The names are written on it.
Why didn't you go
and join them for fun?
This wooden board seller
comes in contact
with many girls every day.
Little Su.
I hope
you can cut loose once in a while.
She's destined to be a lone star
who causes the death of her family and friends
and lead a lonely life.
How can she cut loose?
If you say another word,
I'm going to make you
the star of loneliness.
It's the trick that they use.
Don't mind him.
Let's go.
Sir.
You two have a similar fate.
Your parents have passed away.
One is the Solitary Star
and the other is the Widow Lodge.
But
if both of you can make a pair,
the propitious star governing marriage
will ascend.
The Solitary Star will find its partner.
You two Solitary Stars
can supplement each other.
You'll have a blissful life
and stay loving and grow old together.
Both of us are men.
Don't spew nonsense!
About that.
Only God knows.
You know, and I know.
Wait, Sir.
Why don't you buy a love lock?
You'll be locked together
for a lifetime
and no one can tear you apart.
Indeed, both of us
become acquainted because of a lock.
It's just
some tricks
to fool the ignorant girls.
Rushuang.
What did you write?
It's better for kids like you not to know.
What's the big deal?
(Fei Yuan, Young Master)
You can see mine.
Little Fei Yuan.
This is to pray for marriage.
You wrote your name
and your young master's.
What is this? Do you want to get married?
What's wrong?
Fei Yuan, ignore him.
Let's toss our tablet.
This is...
(Su Ci, Dong Rushuang)
Rushuang.
Don't force yourself to toss it
if you can't do it.
No way.
I must find a way to get it up there.
It's up there now!
Fei Yuan.
Let's go and find Brother Su.
Let's go.
Xie Beiming.
(Xie Beiming, Dong Rushuang)
Let's go home now.
Mom, this is tasty.
I'm not eating.
Brother Pei,
why do you keep looking at me?
You jumped up and down earlier.
But you don't seem exhausted.
You've got quite good at kung fu.
Brother Pei.
Don't ever tell Rushuang about it.
Is it obvious
for me to do this?
Not at all.
I'm relieved to hear that.
It's extremely obvious.
Brother Pei.
I've made it so obvious now.
But Rushuang...
Does it mean I don't stand a chance?
Brother Xie.
Don't worry.
It's impossible
for Little Su and Rushuang to be together.
That's right!
Why did I forget that?
Yes, it's impossible.
I'm relieved now.
Yan Zhi.
Xu Zhi?
I almost couldn't recognize you.
Where's Brother Pei?
Brother Pei?
He's...
I didn't expect to run into you here.
Brother Su, what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
I...
I have a stomach ache.
A stomach ache?
But you're holding your chest.
Why would you
get a stomach ache all of a sudden?
I...
I feel sick in my stomach
from time to time these days.
It's not a big deal.
I'm surprised you still remember.
(Pei Mansion)
Here, Young Master.
How do you feel?
Young Master.
Have you seen the candidates list
for Princess Consort?
Ms. Xu Zhi is also on the list.
Xu Zhi?
That's right.
I heard from Brother Jiang
that her name was suddenly added
to the list.
Young Master.
I think Ms. Xu is pretty good.
You've known each other
since youth, right?
I think
she must really like you.
That's why she made efforts to be on the list.
Was it her that you met
at Puhua Temple?
Young Master.
What did you say?
Why don't you seem to care?
It's selecting your consort.
I'm aware of that.
Come on.
(Name-list of the candidates)
He said he's not interested.
But he secretly looked at the portrait.
Why does this girl
look so familiar?
(Su)
Su?
Detective Su?
Does the young master
like...
men?
Miss, congrats.
You've got your wish fulfilled.
It's just the beginning.
My wish hasn't come true yet.
It's obvious that in terms
of family background and looks,
Prince Qi and you make a perfect match.
Look at you.
You honey-lipped girl.
Someone is too happy to notice
my presence.
-Father.
-Master.
It's been tough on you
in the past few days.
Zhi.
The official list has been announced.
Don't worry now.
Here.
Zhi.
I'm going away tonight
and won't be back for some time.
After I leave,
you must take good care of yourself
especially after you enter the palace.
You need to be careful
in everything you do.
Is this how
the Imperial Astronomer works?
Calm down, Your Highness.
Marquis Zhenyuan
probably pulled some strings
and got Xu Zhi on the candidate list.
Marquis Zhenyuan
guards the Northern Xinjiang.
He commands a massive military force.
I can't let him
form a marriage alliance with Prince Qi.
But this list has already been sent out.
I'm afraid Prince Qi has received it.
So what if he gets the list?
They delivered themselves
right on the chopping block.
All right.
Don't blame me for not showing you mercy.
Ms. Xu.
Other candidates have already
entered the palace.
They live next door.
This is your room.
Ms. Xu.
Here we are.
I'm Xiao Yun.
I'm in charge of your daily necessities.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
Thank you.
It's my job.
Miss.
What are they doing?
They are betting on
Prince Qi's consort candidates.
Miss, are you interested to place a bet?
If you win, you can make a fortune.
The names on the plates
are the candidates
for Prince Qi's consort?
That's right.
It looks like Ms. Xu is quite popular.
Rushuang.
Brother Xie.
Here.
Take a seat.
Why did you ask me here?
You've been working so hard
to do investigation lately.
I asked you out
so that you can relax.
Here. Drink some water.
You Feiyun Manor are quite good businessmen.
You're using Prince Qi
to make money.
Well, we're expanding the business.
Young Master.
We discovered
several wedding dress suicide cases.
We've sorted out the details.
Please have a look.
Give them to me.
(Case File)
Rushuang, there you go.
Well done.
Keep searching.
Search the cases in all the nearby counties.
Yes.
Not bad, Brother Xie.
You're getting better at it now.
These are the ones
that we have found so far.
There are many coincidences among these cases.
It's most likely a serial murder.
The murderer looks for designated targets
in a designated place.
But
I still can't confirm
his pattern of murders.
If that's the case,
the murder must be very smart
with odd behaviour.
Arrest him as soon as possible.
Got it.
It's time to eat.
What a sumptuous meal.
Here.
Why are you looking at me?
Where's Brother Pei?
Young Master went for a matchmaking session.
He won't be back for dinner.
Eat up.
What did you say?
Brother Pei went for a matchmaking session?
That's right.
My young master is so outstanding.
I'm sure all of you know that.
Many people got in line waiting for him
as soon as he returned to the capital.
Can't help it though.
That's no big deal.
Let me tell you.
Those coming Feiyun Manor
to propose marriage every year...
Rushuang.
Not a single one comes.
So,
Brother Pei is really outstanding.
I'm so impressed.
Little Fei Yuan.
Which lady is on the blind date
with your young master?
How does she look like?
Do you have her portrait?
There are six of them.
I won't be able to finish
telling you the whole story.
But they are all gentle
and virtuous ladies
with suitable background.
I think none of them
strikes Brother Pei's fancy.
That's impossible.
They all have been screened.
He'll surely find one
that strikes his fancy.
Besides,
he has reached the age of marriage.
He'll get married for sure.
I'm full already.
Enjoy yourselves.
I'm going to rest.
Brother Su, you...
He didn't even take a single bite.
Why would he be full?
That's so weird.
(Legal Code of Liang Dynasty)
He can marry anyone he wants.
What does it have to do with me?
Brother Su.
Are you asleep?
Come in.
Rushuang.
You didn't eat much just now.
Is something troubling you?
I'm fine.
I've made you some dessert.
Give it a try.
Thank you, Rushuang.
It's fine. Try it.
Is it good?
Not bad.
Brother Su.
Actually, I know what's on your mind.
You're only a few years
younger than Brother Pei.
Actually, you've also reached
the age of marriage
I'll be frank with you.
Since I was a child, I swore to myself
that I didn't want
to see the people suffer injustice.
If this wish is not fulfilled,
I won't think about a romantic relationship.
But a man can live and work better
if he has a wife and a family.
Only then can the world be in peace.
I have no home, no job,
no property, no land.
I don't want to be a drag on any Miss
living a hard life with me.
What if there is a girl
who doesn't care
about your pay and wealth
and wants to be with you
and to take care of you?
This...
When it comes to marriage,
it's better if both agree to it.
But if it's unrequited love,
I'm afraid it's going to be tough.
My father once told me
that it's not easy
to meet someone we like in our lives.
So we have to cherish it
and don't let go.
Rushuang.
I...
Little Su.
Brother Pei, come on in.
Rushuang.
I'll make you some pastries.
Brother Pei.
Were you
standing at the door?
I just came back.
I heard you had an upset stomach.
Are you feeling better now?
I'm fine.
If there's nothing else,
you should head back and rest earlier.
I've been at Mansion of Prince Qi all day long.
I'm indeed exhausted.
Mansion of Prince Qi?
But didn't Fei Yuan say that you were...
What did Fei Yuan tell you
that I was doing?
Nothing.
If there's nothing else,
I'm going to read some book later.
All right.
I'll get going then.
Little Su.
Will you marry someone you don't like?
No.
What a coincidence.
Neither will I.
Miss.
I've heard from the others
that Prince Qi and you
were childhood sweethearts?
We met at a very young age.
All these years
he hasn't changed at all.
You're so outstanding.
I'm sure you'll become
Princess Consort Qi.
All right now.
The Empress Dowager will summon us tomorrow.
Serve me to bed.
All right.
Miss.
Miss?
I'm here to serve you wash up.
Somebody help me!
Is anyone there?
Brother Pei.
Why are you here?
This is my residence.
Where shall I be if I'm not here?
As for you,
how long
are you going to be here?
Rushuang is staying here, right?
Wherever Rushuang is,
that's where my home will be.
Brother Pei.
Why are you so relaxed?
Have you finished
of the princess consort selection?
Are you really
going to pick one of the candidates?
I heard
that Feiyun Manor opened a gambling business.
Are you here
to worm it out of me?
Brother Pei.
I'm really concerned about you.
I hope you can marry someone you like.
Of course, at the same time
to gain profits for Feiyun Manor.
If that's the case,
I earnestly thank you
for your concern.
Don't mention it.
Brother Pei.
Judging from your expression,
it looks like you have found a solution?
The selection of princess consort
isn't just my private affair.
Many people in the government
are trying to pry into it.
They are wary of it.
So the person that I choose
has to be someone to their liking.
Well, Brother Pei.
Who do they want you to choose?
Actually, the six finalists
are to their likings
except for Xu Zhi.
Except for Xu Zhi?
I get it now.
Except for Xu Zhi,
the remaining five
are from families with weaker influence
who are of no help to you.
So
whoever you pick,
they'll be happy with it.
This is...
Are you really going to choose Xu Zhi?
I'll choose Ms. Jiang.
Ms. Jiang's mother
has been in poor health in recent years.
She's recuperating at home.
Recently, her condition got worse.
I'm afraid her days are numbered.
I get it again.
If Ms. Jiang's mother died,
she would have to mourn
not getting married in three years.
Given your tricks,
this marriage will get past
in less than three years.
Brother Pei, there's one thing though.
You can run, but you can't hide.
What about next time?
His Majesty and the Empress Dowager
aren't so open-minded as me.
If they know about Brother Su and you...
Even they gave you the nod,
the officials and people
wouldn't agree to it.
After all, you're Prince Qi.
You need to have your children.
If I were you,
my adoptive father
would break my leg.
Not to mention you...
Your Highness.
Xiwen.
Didn't I tell you
not to come here?
It's fine. Go on.
Your Highness.
Xu Zhi was dead.
What?
The shoes print.
Drag marks.
How come there is powder here?
The decorative pattern.
The shoes wear out at the heels.
Why don't the footprints match?
Come here.
Take them back.
Yes.
Detective Su.
I've checked.
Ms. Xu came into contact
with very few people
after entering the palace.
Besides her maid, Xiao Yun,
she merely had connections
with a few candidates.
The selection is rather complicated.
Many people are involved.
Have you checked everything out?
I've cross-examined all
but one person.
It's Qu Linjiang, the painter
who drew her portrait
because he's not usually in the palace.
All right.
Let's start the investigation
from her maid, Xiao Yun.
My Lord.
(Mingjing Office)
It's all my fault.
I knew the palace is a dangerous place.
Yet, I let you have it your way.
That kind of place
isn't meant for a naive girl like you.
Had I known this would happen,
I shouldn't have brought you back here!
My Lord.
My condolences.
Who did this?
We have launched
a full-scale investigation into it.
Liu Xuan.
We both know
that my daughter
did not die in the hands of one person.
If you can get to the bottom of things,
I hope
that truth will come to light.
I'll surely do my best.
I'm full already.
Enjoy yourselves.
I'm going to rest.
Brother Su, you...
He didn't even
take a single bite.
Why would he be full?
He did so whenever
hearing Brother Pei's matchmaking.
That's just so weird.
Do you think
Detective Su is envious that my young master
went to a matchmaking session?
You won't get it.
Eat up.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
Not bad.
Brother Su.
Actually, I know what's on your mind.
You're only a few years
younger than Brother Pei.
Actually, you've also reached
the age of marriage.
♪ I dream of coming back every night ♪
♪ Through the rain and dust ♪
♪ A deep love I feel for you ♪
♪ Looking at the vast lands
and sighing out of loneliness ♪
♪ Waiting for you to return every day ♪
♪ A promise for life from both of us ♪
♪ After many separations and gatherings ♪
♪ I will not disappoint you when we meet again ♪
♪ I will never disappoint you for life ♪
♪ Feeling lonely and left out ♪
♪ The whimpering of the flute
and the faraway star ♪
♪ I don't know when I'll return
as long as my travel goes on ♪
♪ I dream of coming back every night ♪
♪ Through the rain and dust ♪
♪ A deep love I feel for you ♪
♪ Looking at the vast lands
and sighing out of loneliness ♪
♪ Where can I go to find you ♪
♪ A promise for life from both of us ♪
♪ After many separations and gatherings ♪
♪ I will never disappoint you
when we meet again ♪
♪ For life ♪