We were so incredibly naive.
How the hell could we believe
everything would end without bloodshed?
Victor’s life
was crucified like a worthless pawn.
Bastards!
They orchestrated every bit of it.
I was wrong.
Don’t blame yourself, Tiva.
No one saw this coming.
I KNEW it was gonna happen!
I knew the military...
was gonna crush us without mercy.
And they fucking did it!
I never thought they could be this cold-blooded...
Since when did you know about it?
Before he went up on that stage.
I've heard some very bad news about tonight.
From where?
Extremely bad news
about the safety.
You should avoid it at all cost.
Don't throw meat to a lion.
Why didn't you say anything!?
cause we couldn’t postpone it any longer!
And you damn well knew it!
This isn't how it should be.
Victor's death...
will not be in vain!
His death...
will ignite millions to rise up and fight!
But Victor didn't need to die!
You used him
like bait!?
Didn't he choose to risk it himself?
How the hell could I have stopped him?
Fucking bastard!
Coward!
How could you do this!
That cost someone’s life!
And that very person
was Victor!
Our friend!
If you were me,
wouldn't you do the same?
You’ve lost your goddamn mind!
You were so blinded you couldn’t even see
the worth of a human life!
Tiva, people like you—
are no different from those blood-soaked juntas!
How dare you call
this shit a revolution?
I've had enough.
Scumbag!
Don’t get involved with those hardliner students.
Don't go out
Stay with him.
Don't let him go there.
He doesn't need to know about this.
Since when did you know about this?
Promise me you won't go out tonight.
Can you promise me?
Fuck you! How could you let him walk to his death like that?
Fuck it!
Fucking idiot!
Get out!
Chief, are you sure you're going to publish this?!
Just write the students are communists!
There is no evidence!
How the hell could you come here?
You’re suspended!
Get out!
These are the only pieces of evidence
I could gather from foreign reporters last night.
I swear the student murdered last night
wasn’t a communist like the news claimed.
I'm begging you, chief.
Just do the right thing for once!
Is this the picture of the murdered student?
You got a picture of the shooter?
No, chief.
These are from the protest.
And these... are when the chaos broke out.
The student
was dragged into a nearby alley and executed.
It had to be the state’s doing.
- It was staged. / - Wait.
Why the hell were you even there!?
- I did order / - Just fuckin' listen!
- I ordered your suspension / - Fuckin’ listen, damn it!
Everyone fucking knows!
Last night wasn’t a riot — it was cold-blooded murder!
What they said in the news was a lie!
He wasn't a fucking commie. If the press won't tell the truth,
then who the hell is gonna stand up
- and do what’s right!? / - Ran!
You're fucking out of line.
You know that?
I quit!
Go!
Move you ass out of here!
Guys, write this down.
These kids are communists!
No questions!
As for the violent incident that happened,
it has been reported in the news that
this was caused by the communists,
I—
am reiterating publicly that—
the report
was not true.
What actually happend was an operation staged
by the army
under the direct order of the commander,
General Pracha Suttisakol.
Colonel, stop it!
And I, Colonel Krailert Suwannapas
took part in this operation
by carrying out his command.
Hello, this is Dhevi Dechanara Suwannapas.
May I speak with Air Vice Marshal Tadthep Detnara?
Today,
I've decided
to reveal the truth
because I can no longer remain silent
while wrongdoing continues in this country.
We cannot allow our nation
to continue down this unlawful path.
I will let the people
be the judge of my actions.
Thank you.
Colonel!
You're destroying the army's image!
What you said will bring all of us down!
Please allow me, sir.
Take him.
I know Krailert made the confession himself.
But please, my brother.
No.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm his wife.
Can you please speak to him on Krailert's behalf?
Trin,
can you drive for me? There's somewhere I need to go.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much, sir.
Prepare a public statement
saying Colonel Krailert
acted outside the army’s command
and defamed the army.
The military investigation department will immediately appoint a committee of inquiry.
Leak the news
about Colonel Krailert and how he is linked
to students activists
through his nephew.
The voice that no one has heard...
is the voice that does not exist.
Here... crispy fried duck egg
with madan fish sauce on rice.
Victor's and your favorite, Tiva.
You two fought over it since you were kids.
Eat it, son.
Auntie,
I'm so sorry, Auntie.
I knew they were going to crush us so badly...
but I never thought they would be this ruthless.
It's my fault. I let Victor die, Auntie!
I'm so sorry I let him die.
I want to take his place so badly.
I’m so sorry...
No one deserves to die.
That's what happened to him.
And I ask you, son.
Live on for him!
Auntie... I’m so sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Please... take my life for his, Auntie.
I really didn't mean it.
How are you?
Not bad.
I never imagined this would happen.
Really?
But I always knew
this day would come.
The order’s come from above.
We must end this fast.
It’s starting to spiral out of control.
I'll order a lockdown of the area
so we can contain the protest site
and prevent...
No,
I’ll send in an SS team to sabotage from inside.
They could be some opportunists
lurking for a chance to stir up chaos,
or
communists.
they won’t even know
who’s killing whom.
But sir, we don't need to go that far.
There are ways to maintain peace and order
without killing innocent people.
Those hardliners aren't innocent!
But they are just students!
Aunt Dhevi,
How did you know Ms. Moira kept a video recording?
I don't know.
Perhaps... instinct.
Only women know what each of us is capable of,
and how far we can go.
Ms. Moira once said that at Grand Paradiso,
there was no secret she didn’t know.
Apart from the video evidence showing
General Pracha
as the one who commanded the murder of the student,
today we have received another video tape concerning
the death of the Huay Kham Saeng village chief.
Now the villagers are starting to ask
if what happened was really an accident.
Then do what you must.
Or would you rather this leak to the press?
Those who can’t keep their mouths shut
will never use them again!
Or
do you think
there are other options, Colonel?
With all due respect, I must say
that I disagree
with the way this problem is handled.
Maintaining stability
should not mean controlling people through fear.
As a military—
Colonel,
you're too inexprienced for this game.
Don't be so sure
your wife's family
can always protect you.
It's me, General Pracha.
I wish to speak to the Prime Minister.
I'm sorry.
His Excellency is not available.
Just tell him!
I need to talk to him!
He said he does not wish to talk to you.
Wait!
Leak these pictures.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
The Army Commander-in-Chief has ordered
General Pracha Suttisakol,
to be summoned for a committee hearing
on the unlawful abuse of power.
You must report yourself immediately
for the military disciplinary investigation
and interrogation process.
Please follow us.
I must thank you so very much, Ms. Mondira
I had no ideas who I could turn to for help.
I also must thank you, Mrs. Dhevi.
The whole drama has just made my life so colorful.
But for other matters,
they are truly beyond our control.
This is all we can do for you, Veera.
You installed video cameras
like the CIA?
Of course.
I need to know who and what’s going on in my premises.
You're
something else.
Because I'm Moira, Colonel.
But then, who would dare strike a hidden deal
at Grand Paradiso?
Actually, it’s better things turned out this way.
I'm bored
of those old scheming scumbags
plotting secret deals in my hotel.
Not funny.
Grand Paradiso must be a fun
and safe place for everyone.
Thank you, Moira,
for everything.
About that—
are you sure?
I won't be a coward anymore.
Now you're talking!
Here he comes!
How have you been, sir?
Colonel Krailert,
what do you think about what just happened?
(Let's fly beyond the clouds)
(where tomorrow awaits)
(and we'll be free)
(Sarasawadee's last letter)
Dear readers,
I am well aware
that this day would come, no matter what—
The day I must
say good bye
and finally face what I have always been avoiding:
myself.
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
That's enough.
I'll take it off myself.
What do you want to say?
I must go,
Dhevi.
Where to?
Where I should have been
a long time ago.
America?
Europe,
or the moon?
Trin.
Can I come in?
You're going back to France?
Yes.
Tanakom's father
has arranged for the Ministry of Foreign Affairs
to manage my secondment
to work at the Thai embassy in Paris.
It won't disrupt my civil service pathway.
So you’re all leaving.
What do you mean, Aunt Dhevi?
Say it.
We don't need to hide anything from each other anymore.
Aren't we the same family?
At least...
we are right now.
What is it, Krailert?
Say it.
I...
love someone else.
Right...
That reporter, Naran.
You knew?
I knew.
And I also know
this isn’t going to end
with you eloping with that man.
I can say for certain—
you won't even make it to the airport.
You should know...
this will not be easy.
Pracha got arrested and you think it’s over?
They won’t let you walk away that easily—
not if my three brothers don’t intervene.
Aunt—
Let me finish, since finally I get to speak.
That reporter, does he even understand
the risk he's about to take to be with you?
And Trin too.
Aunt, I—
I know you won’t hurt Trin.
Right.
Trin is my nephew.
But my three brothers
they won’t think the same.
Do you remember this ring?
Asawin Wiswa.
Do you remember what happened to him?
Asawin Wiswa...
You really think my father chose you?
It was me who chose you—
because I love you.
And you had chosen me—
the moment you put on that halo diamond ring.
So you're not going
to take responsibility for what you've chosen?
Give me the air ticket, Krailert.
Tell Trin to deliver it to him.
Tell him to leave as fast as he can,
if he doesn't want to end up like that movie star.
Although I disagreed with what my father did,
but I can't guarantee nothing will happen.
And you, Krailert.
It's high time
you play the role of my husband to the fullest extent.
We will have a perfectly happy family life together.
(Air ticket)
How could I ever think
it was going to be possible?
(Air ticket)
(Sarasawadee)
Sarasawadee
Bro,
you should go to sleep.
Come on. Can you get up?
Tanwa, don't stay here alone.
Get the hell out!
Just leave me.
(Sarasawadee)
Trin, you should go.
Uncle, you don't need to do this.
Isn’t there any other way?
Each one of us
must be responsible for our own choices.
I have already made mine,
and now I’m ready
to accept its outcome.
But Trin, you still have a chance.
I want you
to choose the life you want
and live it on my behalf.
That room was so charming, Uncle.
Mr. Klai Rung.
Yes.
It was charming.
(Sarasawadee)
Both Klai Rung
and I
know well
that some things
in life
will never change.
Klai Rung—
my stubborn rival,
so annoyingly unyielding.
He is the only one
I have ever fought with, all the way through.
And yet,
from the quiet depths of my soul,
I still find myself wishing to remain by his side.
My dear readers,
Do you have that one person in your life—
the one you wish to keep arguing with until your very last day?
Someone who, even in the heat of an argument,
you still hope will never stop speaking?
Someone who,
even in the throes of passion,
still makes you feel
that a million touches would never be enough?
I have never believed
there must be a single answer
to every single question in life.
But if I must give just one answer
to just one question,
I will
choose that person.
And I already know—
that person will choose me too.
Some things
do not need to be spoken aloud.
Some answers
are better left quiet, unannounced,
because we already know them,
deep down.
I believe our listeners must have heard
that Klai Rung
has announced his retirement from the column
following Sarasawadee.
Tonight,
let me bid farewell
to our dear rivals who have long graced
the newspaper pages—
with this song from a mysterious songwriter.
This is for love,
whether it be a joyful one or a sorrowful one.
Beyond the Clouds
(Victor Salenko)
Trin.
I heard from Tanakom that you would be here.
Could you at least go see Tanwa?
This is something he has to face on his own.
Please take care of Tanwa.
I have to go now.
(Draft: Education Policies,
submitted for consideration, by Dr. Trin Suwannapas)
We have received a report this morning
that General Pracha Suttisakol,
the former Army Commander-in-Chief,
was found dead inside his prison cell.
The body was discovered in a seated position,
with his neck tied to the cell grille.
At the time of the incident, no guards were present nearby.
The matter is now under further investigation.
That's enough, Tanwa.
How long are you going to keep folding paper stars?
The night is full of stars...
but why is it so dark in here?
Tanwa.
The sky is so damn lonely.
The moon is gone.
Stop it, Tanwa.
The moon isn’t gone!
Go!
Stop burying yourself under this pile of paper!
Tanwa.
That is the moon!
The real moon!
Come out and see the real thing!
What's wrong with you?
I'm so disappointed in you.
Wake up!
I used to believe
we must choose to stand on only one side.
But when everything collapsed,
I realized
there aren’t just two sides to everything.
Still, I couldn’t decide which path to take.
Then I met the Rector,
and listened to his words.
My conscience seemed to return.
He said,
"Don't let failure stop us."
As long as we stand firm in what we believe,
we will always find the way.
I crossed to the other side.
I took a risk.
I loved.
I failed.
I learned.
I saw what the far side of the moon looked like.
I used to be afraid of the outcome of my own choice.
But today,
I finally understand—that choosing, in itself,
is what truly matters.
Regardless of the outcome.
It’s still better than not choosing at all.
Mom...
What is it, Dad?
Try reading it.
It's your mother's last novel.
She never finished it.
Why did you give it to me?
Night fell,
the indigo moon floated vividly in the sky,
I sat at the old spot
on the cruel, cold bed.
Every night was always too long—
stretching on with no end in sight.
The clock
kept ticking on the wall.
But I did not move with it.
Just read on.
I used to keep my hope in that small box.
I used to believe that if at the right time,
I opened it,
I would find something inside
that could keep me going.
But tonight, I opened it,
but it was empty.
I wasn’t surprised.
I was just...
too tired.
When the moon slips past the horizon,
it would be a blessing if I could disappear with it.
You finished the book?
Dad, would you mind
if I continue writing Mom's novel?
I want to write it in my own way,
but the ending
will be different.
Of course not, Go on.
I'll be waiting to read it.
Bet on your words.
(2 years later, 1971)
Hi!
Hello, Ms. Moira!
Please come back again, Ms. Moira!
You're no longer partying?
Sorry, Moira.
I’m tied up at the moment.
It seems my hotel needs to recruit a new musical band.
You don't need to.
I'm still playing in the band.
Let me know your plan then.
I have handsome young men
queuing up for a job with me.
Let them wait.
Bye-bye.
Can I have the autograph of the future famous author?
(For Mondira, my best friend — Chanya)
Thank you,
Rimtara.
- Bye / - Bye-bye.
Dear Prof. Trin,
I hope this letter finds you in good spirits.
I’ve been stationed in Nadon
as Deputy District Chief for a while now.
I've also started a co-operative project
for education here,
following the method you once proposed.
I received a letter from Nuch,
Auntie Num
and Uncle Ivan.
They are doing well in America.
Nuch has been taking care of them.
She has even received a green card
after being legally adopted by Uncle and Auntie.
She will finish community college this year.
Nuch said that once she gets a job,
she would repay you
for the tuition fees
and air tickets you supported her with.
I still meet my old friends from time to time.
Narong opened his own tailor shop,
an extension of his father's fabric shop in Phahurat.
These days,
everyone goes to Narong Tailor to have their suits made.
Tiva
is still working with his juniors on student protests.
After the November 17 coup d’état,
various groups of students have come together.
It seems
the current situation is building toward a major revolution.
I just hope
Tiva
will lead them
there successfully.
(Community Development Volunteer Club)
We've been through so much together.
Although in the end
we chose different paths,
our friendship
has never faded.
Whenever we visit Victor’s relic stupa,
we always see the fried dough
that M.L. Tanakom placed on the altar.
He said you told him
to place one there every Buddhist Sabbath.
Lastly,
I'd like to thank you
for initiating the village co-operative project
for education,
and Colonel Krailert for providing the funding.
I once doubted
whether we could truly bring about change—
but now I know
it is possible.
I will do my best to keep it alive.
Wut, December 12, 1971
(Victor Salenko)
Monsieur!
Yes?
I need your signature,
but.. it’s really urgent, just a quick one.
That’s it —
It always ends up happening at moments like this.
I’ll also confirm it with the Austrian embassy.
No problem.
Oh, I almost forgot —
there’s a small collection going around.
Thank you.
Moira.
Trin, you should read this.
This book is a great read,
especially for you.
You won’t be able to put it down.
Miss you,
Moira.
(Indigo Moon, by Rimtara)
Tonight,
the indigo moon floated vividly in the sky,
I decided to open the small box
where I had kept my hope.
I used to believe
keeping promises
and keeping silent
were the best things I could do.
That day,
when, out of nowhere, that young man confronted me,
he asked,
Do you really love him?
I love him.
Can you promise me
that you'll take care of him as best as you can?
I promise.
Wait.
Don't tell Phi Trin.
Don't let him know about this.
Stay with him.
Don't let him go there.
He doesn't need to know about this.
Take care of Phi Trin.
Can you promise?
I promise.
(Victor Salenko)
And that was
why I made that decision
on that fateful day.
I’m sorry
I couldn’t keep any of the promises you asked of me.
I have watched people walk away from me.
I respected all their decisions.
But today,
I choose to respect my own freedom.
I choose to live,
to stand up,
and to love.
I won't let everything
fade away in silence,
and I hope that someone
is still waiting to hear my voice.
I still believe
there won't always be
only nights of darkness.
The moon always shines.
I need to go back to Thailand urgently.
Please arrange my air tickets.
(written by the small window in a quiet room, by Rimtara)
(Indigo Moon, written by Rimtara)
Vanilla sky from beneath the Pont Neuf bridge
is truly stunning.
Want me to sign it for you?
No.
I don't want scribbles in my book.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Trin.
I'm Tanwa.
Rimtara.
Life
never tells us
what lies on the far side of the moon.
But crossing to that side on your own
is the truest beauty
of living.
Hua Hin, September 2025
Sometimes,
the audacity to risk
brings us the most
unexpected happiness.
And such
is life.
C'est la vie.