The more you order, the more you get a discount.
Taobao Shangkou invites you to watch
the five-night detective of Zhao Xue Lu.
In 1936,
the fog of Huangpu River hasn't been cleared.
I'm a lover, not a lover.
How did you prove
you're not with him?
Take out my fucking friendships部分 le j forehead!
Has anyone worked for someone's life all this life?
There is a spy in it, isn't there?
Tar die inculcated
Kill her
Warl divides just like bodies
Wanna the killer
The case was not as planned.
A strange theft case
made them suspicious.
The first-in-law Chen's family's heirloom
was not easy to get.
And the suspect was among the six of them.
In this city of crime,
everyone has their own secrets.
The first-in-law Chen's family's heirloom
Do you want to find it?
I don't know.
I really don't know where it is.
The second-in-law Chen's family's heirloom
Do you know this?
You have no way out.
You broke into the place without a door.
Chen's family's heirloom
You also stole the double jade.
What?
You're back?
No.
Come on.
Come here.
Sorry.
Foreigners just came back from abroad.
I don't understand.
My name is Yan Lei.
Hello.
Liu Yang came back.
Come on.
Say a few words in Niu.
Niu.
Hello.
I'm a little sick.
What does it mean?
Say you're handsome.
You choose it yourself.
Handsome.
What does it mean?
Warm you with a smile.
What's wrong?
Do you want me to jump up and stick my ears to your mouth?
I don't know.
Squat down and talk.
Come on.
What does it mean?
Warm you with a smile.
You've seen the end of the next door.
The person who stole things
must be among you.
The hardest is useless.
Stealing things.
Someone stole things.
What is stealing?
What does it mean?
Aren't you French?
Why do you learn to be like a Japanese?
I have the rules of the police station.
I have the strength and means.
Let me think about
how to beat you.
Who will start first?
Learn the bird language first.
Come on.
Help me.
No.
I'm not afraid of you.
Come on.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Everyone,
one of you
has been protected for 24 hours.
One of you?
Who?
Well...
It's you. Come here.
There are two people
you trust.
Get back to work.
OMG!
Kevin.
Curious talked
정 fame
Beethoven
Part II
uição
then
Goodbye.
Choose another one.
Who?
Choose...
Let them each show their talents.
No.
We don't know
if this is a good thing or a bad thing.
Rock-paper-scissors.
We two.
No.
Never leave.
Never separate.
No.
We never leave.
Yes.
You never leave.
You go.
I'll bring my dowry.
Goodbye.
I'm the dowry.
Okay.
We've made our choice.
They may not be good players.
It's okay.
We're teammates.
We're teammates now.
Come and hug.
Okay.
Bye.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Bye.
Where are we going now?
Let's find the fortune teller first.
Fortune teller?
Where can we find the fortune teller?
Let's take a walk.
Let's find it.
Let's go this way.
This way.
The Mushroom religions are the collective
of thoseBuddha and Mahayana.
I miss tasty foods.
I miss tasty foods in the Hard Valley.
I miss tasty food in the Hard Valley.
But I need.
A נorenko.
Put some oil on it.
Put it on.
Sit.
Come closer.
I'll change it.
It's on.
Try it.
It's not that one.
It's on.
It's not washing.
It's washing the air.
This air
represents that you two are like a pair of cogs.
You can gather wealth,
you can walk in a big circle,
you can be rich.
Do you know that?
I know.
Among you three,
there seems to be a line
that is drawn here.
I don't know.
Come on.
Stand here.
I'll close it.
This is a red line.
It seems to be between you three.
Which two are they?
I think
you must know it.
Who doesn't know that?
The weather is not to be revealed.
I know
why you came here.
But
I just said
the weather
can't be revealed.
Unless
you give me sea turtle soup.
Sea turtle soup.
I like it the most.
Come on.
I will only answer you
yes or no.
If you answer wrongly,
I have a sacred oil here
to guarantee your wisdom.
If you answer the soup
in ten sentences,
I will give you
what you want.
Search here.
I'll search.
Search.
There is a woman
who bought a pair of high heels
and wore them to work.
But she died.
Why?
The high heels broke.
No.
Are high heels from someone else?
She is...
She killed herself.
No.
If you answer wrongly,
I'll give you a sip.
Come on.
The wisdom is great.
Oh, no.
It must be very sour.
It's chestnut flavor.
It's not sour at all.
I can't.
It's delicious.
Yours must be sweet.
Why are you like this?
It's a kind of love.
From now on, they are the same.
OK.
You can ask the question.
Someone in the company
was jealous of her beauty
and killed herself with high heels.
No.
It's not that.
Come on.
You are still not clear.
What are you eating?
You are waiting for the monkey to cut off the heel.
Eat.
You two are wrong.
Wrong.
Hello, I'm Zai Zai.
I haven't asked.
It's not that you two
are going to fight with each other.
I want to ask you.
I can't think of it.
Do you need help?
We got it.
We have got the clue.
Can we leave now?
No one is stopping you.
We won't let you go.
We are leaving, too.
You go to find the boss of the study.
There is a dice in turn.
If the number of dice you three
have counted is 13,
you will pass the game.
Six.
Eleven.
Two.
It's OK.
Let's do it again.
Come on.
OK.
I wish you a good trip.
What are you?
A woman.
She wore high heels.
She died when she arrived at the company.
The sea turtle soup, right?
Yes, the soup.
OK.
The sea turtle soup.
I'm good at it.
Come on.
Let me ask you the first question.
She killed him.
The man killed her.
The sea turtle soup.
Is it related to the man?
Is the man her boss?
No, it's her colleague.
Come on.
OK.
It's her colleague.
She said it.
Come on.
I'll eat for her.
Thank you.
Why did she wear high heels
and kill her colleague?
She killed her.
I think it's strange.
Is there a mental problem with that man?
No.
Come on.
What's wrong?
It's too sour.
Teacher, please give me some hints.
Is it a normal reason
or a very ridiculous reason?
A normal reason.
The reason why the man killed her
is because
she wore high heels.
Yes.
The woman wore high heels
and killed her
because she was taller than her.
Half.
I know.
I guess
the man killed her by mistake.
He might have killed someone taller than her.
But the woman wore high heels
and killed her.
It's possible.
Is it a mistake?
Yes.
Look.
OK, the last question.
A mistake.
It means that she wore high heels
and killed someone taller than her.
OK, it's a colleague.
She killed her.
Then the man killed her.
Maybe it's a mistake.
Is it possible?
Is it possible that
the man is a magician?
And then she...
And then this woman
suddenly wore high heels
and the height was different.
So her organs
and everything was different.
Is it possible?
OK.
Correct.
Congratulations.
So cool.
Can I follow
my sister-in-law and brother to investigate the case?
An Xin Suo.
The fate is in the hands of fate.
Xiao You.
Please keep it.
Let's see.
Let's see first.
And you can also see first.
Let's exchange it.
Yes.
So we're going to Bai Le Men.
We seem to go to Bai Le Men.
Don't push me to微 cordial for a moment.
Sister, I have a feeling
Her own
beautiful
Those who are noisy
That's what she meant
Teacher Liang
I just felt something
Mr. Chen
This not
It's
Excuse me, are you Mr. Chen
Amazing
How can you close in
collaboration
What's it
Cheers
Hello, handsome men and beautiful women.
We, Bailu Men,
are recruiting men and women.
Are you interested in trying it?
Where are you holding your hands?
Come on, Peng.
Please step up.
I see that you all have some basics.
Don't hide it.
Is there any trick?
I can do popping.
Then you can do popping.
Come on.
I can do popping with my fingers.
Popping.
Then...
How to do this?
Isn't it like this?
If we all know it,
it's not popping.
Yes.
We two can do it now.
Is it called popping?
You...
OK.
I'll do that.
I don't believe it.
Is there any popping?
Who has it?
I can do the chorus.
Can I?
Yes.
It's so smooth.
It's amazing.
Any male can do this.
I can't.
Now, let's welcome
Mr. Chen Hongsheng
to come up to the stage and say a few words.
OK?
Come on, let's welcome him.
It's been a long time.
Come on, be careful.
It's been a long time, Boss Liu.
These are
our new dancers.
I'm Chen Hongsheng.
Welcome to the stage.
Tonight,
I'll be the one who gives you the treasure.
Double jade.
The thief is inside the stage.
The thief's jewelry is very special.
The jewelry is very special.
It's his.
Your jewelry.
Oh my god.
That night, my security
was hit by a shield
and I was knocked out on the spot.
Tonight,
I just want to show you the secret sword.
Let's see who is the most suspicious.
Boss, don't do this again.
It's Yu.
I got it.