The Long Ballad
According to the news,
Wang Xin's trace was found in the southeast of the city.
From today,
all the wooden houses in this area
will be completely inspected.
The patrols will guard all the traffic lights
in the southeast of the city.
The government will also take the initiative.
Yongci and Princess Yongning
will assist the government to distract the traffic.
Yes, Your Majesty.
In addition to the teeth and teeth
What a handsome man.
He is a rich man.
Indeed?
That̶
that̶
is my matsudou.
Hmm?
Yes.
A tormentosed senile spirit
has probably been
armored
with the first incident of Polish Kemper Oucha.
There should be no problem.
According to the condition of the corpse
and the blood liver,
he was killed before we searched the tomb.
The assassin set up a trap here.
The position inside the tomb is not clear.
There are no signs of fighting or dragging around.
From this point of view,
the victim should have taken the initiative to go to this position.
He didn't resist or try to escape.
It means that the victim not only knew the assassin,
but also trusted him.
The crime was at midnight.
The assassin had set up a trap in advance
and drew a pattern
to wait for the victim to arrive.
The victim walked into the warehouse from the yard.
It's hard to see the pattern on the ground
and the pattern that fell off.
The assassin had another attention of the victim.
The victim didn't realize it at all
and was walking on the dead end.
Judging from the traces on the grain,
the person who cut the rope
should have been hiding on the grain.
Judging from the opening of the rope,
it was cut twice.
The assassin was afraid that the rope would be cut off
at the end of the tunnel,
so he cut it in half in advance.
But the flat end of the rope
was cut off with one knife.
It seems to have been changed by the saw.
But the marks on the saw
are much smaller than that of a regular saw.
I got it.
It was changed by the shameless saw of the jade carving master.
It can accurately control the depth of the cut.
You mean
the killer is still Wang Xian?
It can only be confirmed
after the face is restored.
Well.
Kill him.
Transfer my orders.
Please forgive me.
The face of the deceased
is really cruel.
I understand.
It's hard for you to draw.
Please draw an image for the deceased.
Painter Ning,
with your painting skills,
based on the face of the deceased,
you can draw a complete image.
It should be fine, right?
I will do my best.
Oh.
You drew only half of the face
of the deceased.
It's a pity that
your painting is so sad.
I'm flattered.
I'm not as good as my name.
I'll leave now.
Please.
When Ning Buyi was vomiting,
I saw that he didn't vomit.
It's just the sound of liver cancer.
I also felt that
when Ning Buyi first met Wu Qianhua,
he also had a bad liver cancer.
He had a big hand,
a strong hand,
and a strong body.
But the one who vomited
should have used his hand
to hold his chest and chest.
He didn't use his stomach to relieve his discomfort.
After I finished painting,
my face and eyes
would turn red because of the pressure.
My eyes would cry.
That day,
he looked as normal as usual.
His eyes were clean.
He was not afraid,
but he was a warning.
Ning Buyi
is suspicious.
It seems that
Ning Buyi is likely to be the murderer of this case.
How can you use a suspicious portrait
to infer that Ning Buyi is the murderer?
Because the victim of this case
is Wang Xin,
the sculptor who has been running away for many days.
This muddler
was made by me
as the victim's mother.
It was the first time that Ning Buyi
and I met.
I was very worried.
I was worried that
Ning Buyi
would be the murderer of this case.
I was worried that
Ning Buyi
looked like me
when it was done by Wang Xin.
It was thanks to him
that he wanted us to get Wang Xin.
The portrait was not false.
The late cut of the industries'aws
cuiork out with Wang Xin.
The profile
of Ning Buyi
can never find that person.
He realizes the reason
why he tried to turn Wang Xin into a person,
so that he knew his secret is out there.
and used the shamelessness of the general to change the fate.
He deliberately made us think
Wang Xin was the murderer.
Ning Buyi deliberately drew the face of the victim
to cover up the crime
in a different way from Wang Xin.
It's the same as the muddied picture I made.
It can prove
that he already knew the real identity of the victim.
Only those who are very familiar with Wang Xin
can know how to adjust
to make the effect of the two sides
of the same size.
If he is not the murderer,
how can he know that the victim is Wang Xin?
He even had to cover his eyes.
But what if Ning Buyi
doesn't admit that he deliberately drew the face of the victim?
So we still need evidence.
The painting table is not like the God temple.
Isn't this the son of the one I think of every day?
This girl is...
His Highness just left me for a few days.
He pretended not to know me.
You haven't seen me for a few days.
You're pretty again.
I'll go get you some wine.
Yanli.
You're so mean.
You let me down.
I'm going to smash the door of the Prince of Yi's Mansion.
What... What's going on?
You don't listen to me.
You hit me right after you came up.
What are you doing?
Keep playing.
Your Highness.
I'll be waiting for you.
Why don't you go after the princess?
You still think I'm not good enough?
You hit me when I was chasing you.
I think the princess really cares about you.
If you really care about her...
I really care about her?
I don't have that much of a heart.
I think you have a lot of fun stuff here.
Pick one and give it to her.
Just let her know.
What a coincidence.
A few days ago, I received a small dagger.
It's a good thing that I was able to get it.
The princess will like it.
All right. I'll save it.
I put it in the study room at home.
I have some work to do in the afternoon.
If you don't mind,
why don't you go to the Han's House after dinner?
Go to the Han's House.
Okay. It's a deal.
Bai Feng went there for me? Why?
After all, you are a noble person.
It's too risky.
Yes.
And I'm familiar with you.
You're kind and trustworthy.
No.
I'd rather not be blind.
I'm so handsome.
Can you pretend to be handsome?
I...
I'm not handsome.
What do you want?
It's all for your own good.
I want to go there myself.
I know what to do.
As for the danger, who is not dangerous?
You don't let me go there
because you're afraid that I'll steal the head of the palace?
Or you're like those people in the capital.
You look down on me.
If you're really afraid that I'll get into trouble,
Zheng Fu Yan, send more people
to surround that bastard's house.
Bai Feng, Zhan Yang,
you have to give me more strength.
Pull me out earlier.
Ning Bu Yi is cold-hearted.
He's very anxious.
If he finds out that we're suspecting him,
he'll be even more brutal.
You must be careful.
The poison is small.
The big one is an external wound.
You must be careful.
Ying Shao?
No.
This is for you to protect yourself.
I can't take it.
Take it.
As long as you're alive,
no matter how serious the wound is,
I can cure it for you.
Wan Er,
I'm sure you're a good wife.
I love only you.
Ning Sacrifices...
Don't say a word.
You sound like a discount.
Just take it as a reminder.
As long as we
are good brothers forever, that's it.
Let's go.
Please.
It's good.
The tea is not bad.
Please wait, Your Highness.
I'll get the dagger now.
Go ahead.
Why is it wet?
Calm down.
It's just a small wound.
It's not a big deal.
Your Highness,
you can't lose the eagle hand again.
Your Highness.
Let's go.
Go.
Ning Buye.
If you keep coughing,
I won't be able to pretend to be dizzy.
Stop.
You can kill me if you want.
But you can't steal my beauty.
You're waking up so fast.
How big of a deal can you have
with your small body?
I'm just pretending to play with you.
I really thought I'd succeed.
Stupid.
You thought you could die
with a little bit of anger?
Don't worry.
I'll avoid the poison.
I'll use this dagger
to cut your body
into two halves
bit by bit.
Let you see
your five organs.
Your Highness,
I've never had such a weak death.
It's so satisfying.
You like a man who's powerful.
How can I help you?
How about...
Ning Buye.
Kill me now if you have the guts.
Brother Qi.
Where did Yan Li go?
We're trapped.
Ning Buye can leave a fake secret passage.
But he can't leave this yard.
Bai Feng, keep searching.
Zhan Yang, search.
Yes.
Yan Chi, look.
There's a secret passage.
Smells disgusting.
It smells unpleasant.
Ning Buye,
put down the dagger and kill him.
He'd better go to hell.
Ning Buye.
근 rigid combo
This time for sure.
JavaScript
is about love.
The Heaven's
Daoist Society.
You know about the Heaven's Daoist Society?
Very good!
Very good?
Then you should know.
You...
You are a piece of cotton.
You deceived Princess Yong Ning.
You deserve to be punished!
I'm innocent!
I'm still a pure...
pure, pure man.
I just went to the Flower Pavilion every day
because I was afraid of sleeping alone.
I have a deep love for Little Ning Ning.
We've been in love for three lives.
We spent the spring nights together at the Fengqi Pavilion.
You dare to talk nonsense again.
Believe it or not, I'll tear your mouth off!
Your Highness.
Your Highness, are you all right?
Yan Li!
Oh.
Where is Yan Li?
Here.
I'll chop you into pieces!
Stop!
Come here!
It's good that His Highness is alive.
It's not easy for him to live.
Why aren't youACrest wasnalis?
since when did you start to suspect me?
It doesn't matter when I suspected you.
If you didn't kill Wang Xin
for your smartness,
my suspicion would be only suspicion.
에는
He
committed suicide.
I must kill him.
They are both very λ哈哈
and game of throwback.
The case of Guanyin Town was also did by you?
It was not done clear enough at that time.
I should have YouTube more about many things.
But you started the Heavenly Professor?
It's all handled.
This must be heaven.
If you were going to kill me,
kill me.
But if I can survive for a few more years,
I will definitely kill you
for하기 apathy!
What crime did I commit?
The lives I have
are far more precious than the souls of His Highness
who died in the battle.
How dare you argue with the soldiers who defended the country?
The winner is the king, the loser is the leader.
From now on, you can be in the same group.
It's a pity.
He is also
a traitor.
Don't ruin his life.
You wanna be in my charge?
As the leader,
you have to
take the punishment.
I'm afraid I'll die for no reason.
Let's
I can see your dog's eyes clearly
I am the heir of the first king
Open the door
Your Highness, please forgive me
Yang Li, stop
That person pretends to be Princess Yonglin
Stop him
Yes
Don't hurt him
What do you dare to say
Help
I kill you
It's him
The skin is covered with blood
Even if he doesn't shoot himself
He won't live for a few days
It seems that this is the mark of the Swordless Flower
No wonder Zhang Nengxuan was rejected
To play the trick
Just to cover up the existence of the Swordless Flower
I know I have no time
And I have to work hard to harm the lives of several people
This is the so-called
The so-called
The mask is made of wood
White
It was carefully made according to Ning Buyi's face
The wood is hard
Unless the fat and thin wheels are exactly the same as Ning Buyi
Otherwise, others can't wear it
And the white is also dark yellow
It can be seen that it has been made for a long time
It seems that you lost this mask
Only the owner of the white mask is qualified to wear
The other owner of the negative owner wears a silver mask
So to speak
Ning Buyi is the owner of the Tian Dao Club
The real murderer of the Qingcheng murder case
It's a dead end
But there are other parties who haven't been cleared
Ning Buyi is dead
We can only strengthen the defense
Governor
Please send more people from the city
To catch the murderer of the Tian Dao Club
Yes
Master, princess
Ning Buyi's identity has been found
Minjiang and Qinghe are all in trouble
The court is worried about the disaster relief
Prince Yu personally escorted to Huzhou
But the Huzhou Ministry of Justice
Secretly investigated the vice minister and Ning Shoude
The corruption of the disaster relief fund
To the point of being unfavorable
Ning Shoude did not repent
Never admit his crime
Rejected the execution
The family property of the Famao
Three generations of descendants
Can't be discussed
Ning Shoude
Is Ning Buyi's father
He is a little rich man
How dare he talk about it
It's just because Prince Yu is the emperor's uncle
Dare not investigate him
His father is just a scapegoat
For the crime of corruption
Father and mother
No wonder he is innocent
Mother
Lan'er
I have something to tell you
What's wrong
Are you glad to remember
Duke Shen's Manuel
Yes
After thinking about the court
Is there a father same as
Ning Buyi's father is different to Duke Shen
Although he is not therag
But there are indeed obstacles
Yes.
Ning Buyi wanted to pursue justice.
He should have found a way to make Prince Yu confess his crime.
He shouldn't have used the lives of ordinary people to make a few mistakes.
I was wrong.
You weren't wrong. You were just too kind.
You were just a strange person.
It's wrong. You don't have to comfort me.
When I was pushing the case, I was drunk and tried to escape.
I didn't finish reading the case file and then I made a decision.
I even leaked my own heart to the public.
It was wrong.
Zheng Fuying and Zhan Yang are not talkative.
But in the future, you should be careful when you talk to them.
Thank you for your words.
I'm honored to have you as my husband.
I heard that the murderer has been arrested.
You did a good job in this case.
Very good.
Your Majesty, this case was successfully solved.
Princess Yongci's credit is not enough.
Zheng Fuying and Zheng Baishi also cooperated.
Yongci's credit is not enough.
Your crime should also be punished.
Please explain, Your Majesty.
The criminal who was corrupt has been in the capital for several days.
He is still not released.
I wonder if you are ignoring my order and showing off your colors
or because the internal situation of the Shuoxi Army is not good enough
and you can't do anything about it.
Your Majesty, I have found out that
there are indeed some bugs in the Shuoxi Army.
They are very strong.
They didn't go to court because they were searching for evidence.
But I can guarantee with my life
that the bugs in the Shuoxi Army are hard to find.
There are indeed some holes in the father's jade.
There are holes in the father's jade.
But the soldiers in the family are not loyal to the emperor.
They dare not deceive Your Majesty.
Please investigate it, Your Majesty.
Come on.
Come up.
Light this lamp for me.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please take back the fire book.
Are you angry with me?
I dare not.
Then why do you want to return the fire book to me?
This book is yours.
Of course, you have to return it to me.
I just gave you the responsibility to light the lamp.
I didn't give the fire book to them.
But someone doesn't understand such a simple reason.
Your father and I are brothers,
but we are also military officials.
If he can't get rid of the bugs in the Shuoxi Army,
I'm afraid I can't be at ease again.
The land under the sky is not the land of the king.
The soldiers in charge are not the ministers of the king.
I hope Your Majesty can go to Shuoxi with me
to save that corrupt person.
To support the emperor's power to defend the holy star.
Okay.
Then go.
Don't let outsiders know about this.
As long as you and your father are of the same mind,
I will be at ease.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Master, a letter from the other tribes.
It says the crown prince has sent the army provisions.
When we were on the border,
the commander found us checking the accounts in private.
He punished the soldiers and locked them up.
Father is really muddled.
He is so protective of those Shuoxi officials.
Everyone would think he considered the Shuoxi Army as a police.
His Majesty was not satisfied with this.
If he doesn't hand over those corrupt officials,
His Majesty will definitely take advantage of this
to take over the whole Shuoxi Army.
I will go to Shuoxi to negotiate with Father.
You stay in the capital to take care of Waner.
If there is any mistake, you can come to me.
Yes.
If Princess Yongci asks about this...
Tell her I will go to investigate the military provisions.
I will be back soon.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Is it certain that the murderer is Ning Buyi?
Ning Buyi was caught by Prince Rui
during the case.
He confessed to the case of the crime.
The evidence is clear.
Since the evidence is clear,
he was arrested and executed on the spot.
Why did Zheng point out
that the case was not cleared at the end of the case?
Because the witness Zhang Dongxuan pointed out
that there are other people in Tiandao who are not Ning Buyi.
And the vice chief is another person.
Then, Zheng, do you have any clues
to find the vice chief?
Not yet.
Do you have any evidence to prove
that the vice chief is the one who ordered Ning Buyi to kill?
Ning Buyi is the chief.
Who can order him?
Zheng,
the case documents should be solved in one case.
Since the case is solved,
it should be considered a trial.
Never make any more troubles
and make any more mysterious claims.
If His Majesty asks about it,
how do you want me to answer him?
Do you want me to tell His Majesty
that there are still some mistakes to be made?
What do you mean, Zheng?
I mean,
there are still some mistakes to be made.
What do you mean, Zheng?
This case is a very important case.
It's a good thing for His Majesty and the people.
Moreover,
His Majesty cares about Prince Yi very much.
If he knows that you are willing to set a trap
for the investigation,
if His Majesty blames you,
I'm afraid that
even Prince Rui and Princess Yongci
will be punished.
So in my opinion,
it's better to solve this case earlier
and be more stable to all parties.
Well,
thank you for your advice.
I will re-write the documents
and submit them to His Majesty.
Then I wish you two
to make new contributions in advance.
Brother Li,
wait a minute.
Xiaowan,
come with me to the palace.
Brother Ze will be here soon.
Who is your brother?
Prince Xie.
We haven't seen each other for almost ten years.
He is the third-best among the brothers.
He was the best to me when I was a kid.
The mother of the late Princess Consort and the seventh brother
was a handkerchief.
He also had a good relationship with the seventh brother.
Okay, let's go.
Prince Xie is here.
Your Highness.
I greet you, grandmother.
Okay,
no need to do these formalities.
Ning,
help your third brother to sit down.
Your Highness.
Ze,
you have been looking for a doctor outside for years.
Why haven't you recovered yet?
Grandmother,
don't worry.
I have recovered.
But my eyes
can't stand the strong light.
I have to use medicine to keep them.
Let Wan'er see it.
I can't ask for it.
It's because I heard that the doctor is wise
that I hurried back to the capital.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Princess,
no need to be so formal.
Thank you.
Your Highness,
don't worry.
I will ask Princess Yongci
to come to the palace to see you.
Yes.
Wan'er,
how is it?
Your Highness, don't worry.
I will go to see her.
Yes.
I am worried
that the crown prince's old disease is cured.
He is only concerned about the liver and liver
to be cured.
He is also concerned about the liver and kidney
He only needs to use acupuncture
and medicine to recover.
I can rest assured
with your words.
Don't leave today.
Stay in the palace for dinner.
Where is Xiaoqi?
When he came back,
he didn't come to the palace to see me.
Bai Feng said
that His Highness went out to work.
He will be back in a few days.
Sister Yang Si will be here soon.
Don't waste your time.
By then,
you will have fun
with me.
Yes, Your Highness.
Brother Ze, have some tea.
Brother Ze.
Ning,
you don't have to be so careful.
I have been used to it for so many years.
I can take care of myself.
Come here, Ning.
My herbal tea
can help you sleep well.
Drink it every day.
You can sleep well after drinking it today.
I can't sleep well.
Your Highness,
what's wrong with you today?
You have been unhappy.
If you are bored,
you can go to see Mr. Li.
What does it have to do with him?
Why do I have to go to him?
Then why are you so worried?
Since you met the new prince today,
you have been in a bad shape.
I...
Let me tell you.
Don't tell anyone.
That's the thing
I regret the most in my life.
I was six years old.
I participated in the first cave hunting.
Because the crown prince and Brother Chen were both cruel,
they didn't want to take me to ride a horse.
I was angry
and went to the horse farm alone.
It was very windy that day.
I was lost on the way.
Brother Zhou Ze found me missing.
I was afraid of shame.
I didn't want others to see my mess.
Brother Zhe
had to take the risk
to carry me back to the manor.
But he was hurt by the snow.
That year,
he was still a child.
What happened next?
Then,
Brother Zhe's eyes
were blind.
This prince
is a good man with feelings.
Did his eyes gradually become blind?
Or since that day,
he couldn't see anything?
He should have become blind since that day.
There's nothing he can do.
In recent years,
Brother Zhe has changed his name.
It seems that he hasn't recovered.
Did his eyes get hurt before?
No.
Did he have eyes before?
I don't think so.
But Brother Zhe has been weak since he was a child.
He has been watching things for a long time.
His eyes hurt.
If I hadn't been so willful,
how could he be so sick?
I'll pay for my own sins.
I want to marry him
and take good care of him for the rest of my life.
Why?
That's your fault for being so young.
Why do you want to pay it back with your life?
Because no noble girl in the capital
would be willing to marry a disabled nun.
Since it's my willfulness
that has caused Brother Zhe to lose his happiness for the rest of his life,
I can't just ignore it.
I have to take responsibility for him.
But marriage should be a two-way relationship.
You can't be together forever just because of a momentary sympathy.
I...
I'm willing to do it.
What about Yan Li?
That's right.
I don't know.
I think
if it weren't for me,
he would be very happy.
What else did Fulin say?
He also said that
Princess You Ning has already given up.
If you still don't get your strength back,
no one can help you.
I was almost killed by someone.
How can I get my strength back?
I'm a simple and innocent girl.
She has seen it and hugged me.
Now I'm sick and cold.
I don't even know where I am.
She is so cruel.
She has seen it and hugged me.
When did this happen?
It doesn't matter.
That's right.
It really doesn't matter.
What matters is that
Princess You Ning doesn't want to hug you anymore.
Bai Feng.
But Princess Yong Ci said
that you should be dead when you're sick and cold.
You'd better take the medicine.
If you really die,
not only will you trouble Princess Yong Ci to come and check on you,
Princess You Ning will be more at ease
and run with Prince Xin.
Where are you going?
She's not dead yet. She's thinking of remarrying.
Take the medicine first.
Look at her.
She's pretty.
I heard that
you've been sick since you were a child.
Can you tell me the cause of your illness?
If you want to keep your eyes on the patient,
you can't hide anything from the doctor.
Otherwise, even if you have a temporary relief,
it will recur in a few days.
What do you mean?
This internal medicine
is aimed at the symptoms of the disease
in your organs.
But from the pulse,
there is another cause of the disease.
I have a guess
that can explain your pulse
and why you have an incurable disease.
It just needs your usual disease diagnosis.
I've forgotten about my childhood.
I can't tell you.
So,
you've known that
you've been poisoned since you were a child.
You're really a great doctor.
But let bygones be bygones.
If you really know that I have a double vision,
you can only say that fate is so cruel.
I just hope that you can try your best.
Your Highness, since you've answered my question,
I'll do as you wish.
Your Highness,
you should rest early.
Bai Feng?
Your Highness.
Why hasn't His Highness come back yet?
His Majesty is in the military.
He has some misunderstandings with His Highness.
He can only go back to Shuoqi and deal with it.
Then why don't you follow him
and follow him on the way?
Your Highness, don't worry.
From Shuoqi to the capital,
you're very familiar with it.
It's absolutely fine.
You left me here
to protect you.
You'll be fine when you're safe.
What are you doing here so late at night?
There's been a commotion in Prince Jin's mansion.
Why does the day and night turn around
But still
I still see your light
Like a flower
floating in the snow
So cold
I still see your face
So warm
If a love
falls into the haze
The snow falls
and my body is white
If a love
falls into my heart
The pain will also
be the same
Open your heart
Love is not about the deep sea
Please grant me courage
Let fate be in the way
Don't be afraid of the starlight
Being covered by the moonlight
The stars will shine
beyond the sky
It's like dust in the dark
But it's the color of the stars
The sky is blue
The moon is bright