[Final day
Confession]
[Only boys who choose each other
can shoot the final script]
I want to choose the one that makes me feel the most comfortable.
[Previously]
And I think the most interesting and funny...
[Adson already has someone in his heart]
I think we get along very well and we are really a match.
Robert makes me feel that
I can change my role.
[Chien Yu chose Robert]
I've always been the one taking care of others,
always the one giving,
which makes me feel like
I can find some warmth and care from him.
Actually, I'm considering
between Adson and Pink.
[Love Casting]
Guei just said
[Auntie Squad: Aben]
he has two choices.
[Auntie Squad: Poom]
[Auntie Squad: Qiao Qiao, Kimi Hsia]
[Auntie Squad: Chu, Ernie Chu]
One is Pink and the other is Adson.
[Auntie Squad: Queen of BL, Niki]
So he officially said goodbye to Chris.
[Auntie Squad's expected couple pairing, Chris & Guei
becomes impossible]
It's over.
Poom. What do you think?
Guei and Pink.
Yes, Guei and Pink.
Yes, yes, yes.
Why?
Because when they performed together,
their fingers were tightly intertwined, and they exchanged glances.
[Poom supports the hand-holding couple Guei and Pink]
I know. When they were tightly holding hands.
Yes, tightly holding hands.
You need to fully trust each other
to show that kind of feeling.
Okay, deep down, we hope that...
Guei and Pink.
Guei chooses Pink.
Chien Yu is obvious
because he wants to choose Robert.
And Adson.
Adson will definitely choose Yi.
I'm very happy that
our show, Love Casting,
was meant to see if fake feelings can turn into real ones.
It’s really about whether real feelings develop
during the process.
Actually, at this point,
you can already tell from the night before
they made
their decision and confession
that they have developed a deep bond.
Yes. And I believe this deep bond
will make their acting improve significantly
if it really becomes a series.
Acting based on true emotions is truly different.
Yes, let's look forward to it together!
The confession of the last episode.
Who will pair up to form the perfect couple?
I'm still thinking about who to choose.
[Chris can't make a decision,
so he chooses to seek help from tarot card reading]
He also went there.
Who? Who? Who?
Overall, this gives me a better feeling.
Okay, let's see A first.
So for A's situation, here we see a Flirting Star.
It has a lot of tails, very similar to a nine-tailed fox, right?
It is also pink.
This card is like your feelings toward him.
You think he’s charming and attractive,
but you feel like he's not entirely in your control.
Also, as you noticed with the knife,
it's similar to an utility knife.
It won't give you a fatal blow,
but it can still cause some damage.
[Chris's person of interest, A,
often leads to conflicts when they interact]
It might not bring the best outcome
in the dynamic between the two of you.
Let's see B.
The three cards of B are all upright.
This person gives you a sense of reassurance,
warmth, and thoughtfulness.
He's like the moon.
The moon gives us a feeling similar to that of a mother,
who takes care of you and makes you feel at home.
He's smiling, which shows that he agrees.
This card, the treasure bowl, has a lot of money.
Yes.
It's not that he'll bring you wealth,
but he will bring you a lot of good relationships.
If you choose him,
you two will get along very well.
[Chris's person of interest, B,
provides provides abundant emotional support]
And that sense of mutual support
can actually bring a lot of opportunities to both of you.
Okay, I think
you can draw one from this stack.
I think you can communicate with your soul
and see if it has anything to remind you.
Come on, Chris. Who will your soul choose?
Okay.
It's so accurate.
What did it say?
It says go with the flow.
He might have an answer in his heart already.
[Let's go with the flow]
He's just being indecisive.
I am shocked.
Although we don't spend a lot of time together,
I've observed how he interacts
with everyone from the side.
And...
[Pink has decided to whom he is going to confess]
I think that, in the end,
our personalities might actually be a good match.
When I am with him,
I won't feel uncomfortable or stressed.
I feel very happy.
I think the reason I'm most hesitant is
because I know he won't choose me.
The person I want to choose...
Although I know he won't choose me,
I've decided to
[Fumi is ready to face the possibility of failure]
follow my feelings
and be brave for once.
So I am struggling a bit,
wondering whether I should be honest with myself
and bravely face the feeling of
being rejected.
I still don't know who to choose.
Because...
I'm thinking about many different reasons,
like who could help me improve further.
[Yi decided to get a fortune reading after struggling to decide]
What do you want to ask today?
I'm not sure who to choose today.
Will he have three choices, or just two?
His tarot cards will be fully laid out on the table.
Fully laid out.
Two.
There are two people in your heart.
Yes.
Now please close your eyes.
Just think to yourself
whether it's better to choose A or B.
I want to know who it is.
My gosh, this tarot card reading is really intense.
From a development perspective, it actually looks quite good.
And you can see here that
there is a bathtub with lots of flowers.
Many flowers represent popularity with the audience and people in general,
which is a positive effect.
So, if you choose him,
your interactions with each other
will be very comfortable and happy.
However, with this card, you should also be cautious.
It indicates that you might have a few points
where disagreements could easily happen.
[Yi's choice for Person A
has great appeal to others, but they may occasionally argue]
This is what you should pay attention to.
The three cards for B seem more calm,
because, unlike A, which has a lot of flowers,
B's three cards look yellow and dark.
Overall, it doesn't seem like a very comfortable relationship.
And we have a card in the middle
with a sun in it.
This card is actually a nobleman card,
but it's upside down here.
You two might
have your own ideas and opinions,
so it may not be easy for you to communicate with each other.
And then, you might not be able to help each other.
So the third card doesn’t look good.
[Person B in Yi's heart
is hard to communicate with, and they can't help each other]
It's a skull-like situation.
Although it's upside down,
I think if we are talking about long-term interaction,
B's card
doesn't look as comfortable.
Now I think
you can communicate with your soul
and see if it wants to remind you of anything.
Okay.
Okay, you want this one.
Okay. What does it say?
Lying on you.
Actually, I think deep down,
you already have
some ideas in mind by now.
Very reassured.
Yes, it's Adson.
It's Adson.
Nice.
Nice. He said nice.
He thinks it's accurate.
[Final script
What decision will the boys make?]
It's coming.
Just like this?
Get us two.
At least two scripts.
I'm going to cry.
[Adson wrote down his choice
without hesitation]
It must be hard to write.
Yes.
[Thinking again and again
Chris wrote down his final decision]
Yi, don't write the wrong name.
Yi, you need to write the name of the person you care about correctly.
Robert!
[Guei seems to be hesitating between Adson and Pink]
I think Pink will choose Yi.
He has figured out what to write it.
[Pink, without hesitation,
wrote down the final confession choice]
Fumi, I can’t guess who it is.
[Fumi gathers the courage
to write down his choice from the heart]
I think Fumi feels more sorrowful.
I already feel like crying.
Is it too early?
I think so too.
You’re on the verge of tears.
No.
I was not about to cry.
But don't you think watching them walk up
and seriously...
I think they are...
They moved you, didn't they?
It moved me.
Also, aren't you feeling more sentimental about Fumi?
A little.
It's obvious that Adson is going to choose Yi.
Personally, I believe in tarot card reading.
In the end, he got the card and said lying on you.
That's Adson.
Because being with him just feels really reassuring and comfortable.
Will you cry if Yi didn't choose Adson in the end?
Then that's his fault. He jinxed it.
[Master of the jinx]
Come on, the master of Yi and our master of the jinx.
Do you think Yi will choose Adson?
After watching the teacher's tarot card reading, I feel...
Yi must choose Adson.
Okay. Poom.
I think Yi will choose Pink.
[Poom has a different opinion
he thinks Yi will choose Pink]
Really?
So do you think Person A and B in the tarot reading
are Adson and Pink?
Yes.
He thinks it's Adson and Pink.
It makes sense.
Adson and Pink didn't hesitate at all.
They are very direct.
But Chris did a tarot reading.
He did one as well.
But I really don't know his choices.
The first one is someone who is charming,
but gettin along with him
might come with some barriers and challenges.
I immediately thought of Yi.
Do you remember when Yi hurt him?
When they finally ended up
[The fourth day
Yi replaced Chris, who was going to sleep in the same room, with Adson]
in the same room,
Chris was happy.
But Yi replaced him.
He was very disappointed during the interview.
He said he had no chance to stay in the same room with Yi.
[The boy is heading to the final confession spot
Will the one he chose appear?]
There will be a confession spot,
and the other person will go find him.
Pink.
[Pink's determined steps
will lead to who?]
Pink will go to Yi.
Who? Who? Who?
Guei.
Impossible.
I still really hope for this pair.
Pink and Guei.
I think Pink is going to Yi.
Look, he really goes to Yi.
Impossible.
He's really determined.
Poom is amazing.
[Spot on]
[Guei is still waiting]
Who will he choose?
Pink.
Yes, Pink.
[Guei didn’t wait for Pink to arrive]
I think maybe the time we spent together was too short.
Well,
we talked for a long time.
I thought we were quite close.
We also had great chemistry
in terms of coordinating with the storyline.
I think Pink's gaze
really helped me immerse myself in the story.
It reminds me of this.
No, this is my favorite scene.
Maybe he has his own favorite person
who he likes and feels comfortable with,
someone he can easily work with.
That's fine. I wish him the best.
They will definitely be able to work better together.
That's it.
He's hurt.
Don't be sad, Guei.
He's acting tough.
Gosh.
[Chien Yu walks bravely
towards Robert?]
Robert.
Okay. Okay.
We meet again.
I think I care about Fumi.
Yeah, who will Fumi choose?
[Fumi's final confession is to...]
It's Yi.
[Everyone in the Auntie Squad is shocked]
We were all wrong.
[Adson hasn't made a choice yet]
[Will he choose Chris, whom he dotes on like a younger brother?
Or the childish companion Yi?]
Adson will choose Yi.
Oh no, Yi.
Yi. That's a lot of people.
Why?
[The person Chris chose didn't show up]
So, who did Chris choose?
I'm a little sad.
But...
[Fumi]
Because I feel that my connects with him
is on a spiritual level.
I can respect his choice.
Tarot reading is very accurate.
I feel that with Fumi,
I don't have to do anything special.
We just get along so well,
[Chris chose Fumi
but Fumi chose Yi]
and I feel secure.
Oh, my. Yi really messed things up.
I didn't expect three people to choose him.
Really. I really didn't expect that.
He's really the king of popularity.
But Fumi and Yi...
Yeah.
Why did Fumi choose Yi?
Or maybe he really got into the character?
Because the scene he played with them was,
Chris gave Yi a love letter,
and later Yi gave it to Fumi.
[Sounds reasonable]
Didn't they hug each other?
So when Fumi was acting in that scene,
we thought it was an act,
but it actually seemed like he was expressing his true feelings.
It's not me.
I've liked you for a long time.
I think he might have picked up
on the emotions Yi was giving him.
Now that we know his thoughts,
looking back at that expression, we are able to notice something.
There must have been a lot of complicated emotions.
How could we not see that?
We missed it.
Because yesterday at the bonfire party,
[Is there a possibility that Chien Yu and Robert both feel the same way?]
we talk about how I feel that, for me,
being brave is something I hope to learn.
I think during the course of this show,
it feels like I can use this opportunity
to make some changes in myself.
I think you give me a sense of being cared for,
a feeling of dependence,
which makes me feel warm.
I want to tell you this.
I don't think you need to feel pressured.
Because I think this has helped me
become a different version of myself.
Whether it's being brave
or expressing my true feelings
to a stranger,
I think you, out of these seven people,
have given me the most energy and ability to make changes.
That's all.
Thank you.
You also brought me a lot of good energy.
We can still maintain a friendly relationship in private.
Of course.
Because I really like you.
Okay.
Good luck.
Give me a hug.
A hug?
Yes.
You don't have to get up.
Thank you.
Okay.
No.
Can I hug Chien Yu?
I want to know more about Robert.
Because we don't seem familiar with you.
Since you're new, I thought we should "collide" a little...
Maybe have a little misunderstanding.
Yes, a misunderstanding.
You want to sleep on the left or on the right?
I'm fine with anything.
[The Auntie Squad is heartbroken]
My baby.
Don't touch him. He's mine.
Go, baby.
Yeah.
So bad.
Oh my god.
Look.
Didn't you say you want to sleep over for another night?
Robert!
[Tears pouring out]
What song is this?
What you want is not me?
That's too much.
I thought they could at least be together.
My gosh.
Give me Chien Yu's number right now.
[Robert refused Chien Yu's confession
They are not able to form a couple]
Let's give him a hug in the air.
Come on, everybody.
Let's give Chien Yu a hug.
[Let's give brave Chien Yu a hug]
Poom, you supported them from start to finish.
Comfort Chien Yu.
Give Chien Yu a hug.
Give him a hug.
I think that Chien Yu's speech
was sincere, thoughtful,
and full of courage.
And you can see that Chien Yu has transformed
into a completely different person from the beginning until now.
You know it takes a lot of courage to confess.
I've done that.
Yes.
You can hear the heartbeat.
You will be scared of any look
or reaction the other person might give you.
Confessing is very difficult.
He was so brave.
But in the end, he has to watch...
But I'm curious now.
Who is Robert going to choose?
Maybe no one.
He has to choose.
He might just put a big 'X' on it.
A big 'X' that he is not choosing anyone.
That's possible.
It really is just that there are no feelings, or...
Don't hit my face.
Hit my face!
Getting slapped in the face directly.
Okay, I feel...
Can we take five days off?
No.
I want to continue watching.
I am watching while bleeding.
This vest was supposed to be white.
It has already turned red.
My heart is bleeding.
The first thing I did when I got on the boat was talk to you.
[Pink was the first to express his feelings]
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Pink.
Pink?
You make me feel warm and comfortable.
Although your Chinese is not so good,
and my English is not so good.
Today is handsome.
You too.
You look like Kenny.
This is big.
In the past few days,
although I'm not the one you spend the most time with,
I've been observing you and others.
I feel like
you are the person I think is the most suitable choice.
From the beginning on the boat,
it was anime that gave us common topics to talk about.
Then we both did
similar work related to modeling.
Later on, I acted with you.
We chatted a lot when we lived in the same room.
At that time,
I felt like I really wanted to
continue doing things together with you.
Can we be together?
Yi.
Just, you know, first day we met, we, like the same room.
And second day we acted drama together.
Nice.
Nice?
Nice to hear.
So...we share the same zodiac.
And our sense of humor is pretty much the same too.
Paper, scissors, stone.
What's that?
My face.
I feel like we just get along really well, we’re a match.
So I'm very happy that I can
play with you from the first day to the last day.
So, yeah, follow your heart, you know.
No.
What are you doing?
This is the most important part.
Aren't we...
Yeah, aren't we going to watch Yi's choice?
You showed us a bunch and then turned into this...
Auntie is angry.
Yes, I want to see who he will choose.
I just want to know the ending.
When I was watching this group, I realized
we only have one last chance left.
This is the last group.
I want Yi and Adson.
At least.
We have to protect our couple.
Okay, that's it. Come on.
Thank you for choosing me.
Fumi.
When we didn't know each other at first,
I knew you read anime.
Then I think we have a lot in common to communicate.
We can talk about anime.
Because I didn't know other people,
but I know a lot about anime.
So I'm very happy
to see a otaku here.
So we can
watch more anime together in the future.
And Pink,
I know it's hard for us to communicate
because my Chinese is not good,
we didn't communicate much on this show.
But I'm still very happy to know you.
We both like playing basketball.
Although I can't play it well,
you can carry me.
You said you want to go to Thailand,
so you can send me a message.
You can come and live at my place at any time.
We can eat and play basketball together.
And Adson,
we were
not that familiar with each other at first.
But you told me a lot when we were on the boat.
You spoke in English and translated for me.
The first day we lived together, and there was no door.
It was awkward.
So we knew each other very fast.
The next day, we filmed that drama.
That was my first time.
You're very experienced.
I think you've helped me a lot.
I also feel the most comfortable when I'm with you.
So I want to say thank you for choosing me.
If I can choose,
I want to choose all of you guys.
When his hand was like this,
I thought he was choosing Adson.
Then it got back here.
Yeah, and it came that way.
You know, I just heard a keyword.
He said if I could you all.
Didn't he say that?
Yeah.
So he did say "you" for all, right?
Did that mean
he is not choosing any of the three?
[Impossible]
No way. No way.
I heard that too.
Maybe it just means,
"if I can choose all of you".
He just doesn't want to offend anyone.
Translate it with Yi's level of Chinese.
[Tired]
So he said he is most comfortable with Adson.
Yeah.
The most comfortable and secure.
That actually aligns well with the tarot.
Yeah, and with Pink...
Although they didn't communicate very much,
there's a Bangkok Date.
For Fumi, they share the same hobbies, so they enjoy their conversations.
They both like anime.
Yeah.
I am thinking if he might end up not choosing any of the three
and go for Guei instead?
Gosh, I'm going crazy.
And Guei thought nobody would choose him at the very beginning.
If he chose Guei, I would really...
run out naked.
Okay, you said it.
You said that, don't...
But that'll be amazing to watch as well.
Keep that for now.
I'm literally going crazy.
Poom, Poom, what do you think?
[His expression explains everything]
He's really struggling.
Thank you for choosing me.
If I can choose,
I want to choose all of you guys.
But today,
I need to...
I still need to follow my heart.
[Yi’s final love confession choice is]
Then I choose...
Adson.
Our...
At least we have secured a pair.
Pink.
Actually, the result is...
just as I expected.
I'm happy that they can form a CP
and continue to develop.
At the very least, I think
I gathered my courage
and was able to express my feelings to him.
I think
that's what matters the most.
I think Fumi is really…
Pink.
But I really think Pink
stayed true to himself all the way through, right?
It turned out that Pink cared about him from the moment he got on the boat.
Some happy, some sad.
Such a conflicted feeling.
When I look at them, I will feel very happy.
But that two people’s backs looked so disappointed.
All the choices are over.
But I really admire Fumi and Pink
because Fumi already knew the answer.
Yeah.
And throughout this process,
he cared more and more about Yi and also his every move.
He even knew what Yi's final choice would be,
But in the end, he still decided
to tell him what he wanted to say.
Fumi was just trying to... How to put this...
Pretending to be strong.
Yeah.
You know, because Fumi knows
[Fumi is mentally prepared for a failure in the love confession round earlier]
how to protect himself well.
He already told himself
the day before the selection that
Yi definitely wouldn't choose him.
Get mentally prepared.
Yeah, he had already prepared himself mentally.
So he has already sealed himself.
And Pink...
I feel so sorry for Pink.
I think Pink cried so saddly because
he was looking forward to it.
When Yi was talking about everyone,
did he already know a bit about it?
Yeah, I feel before he had announced his final choice,
he already felt that Yi would choose Adson.
So his tears dropped.
And Pink and Adson,
neither of them has ever hesitated at all.
So I think with two people who didn't hesitate at all,
one ended up heartbroken,
while the other found happiness.
And I just didn't expect that he had already
made up his mind the first day he got on the boat.
I didn't expect that!
Me neither.
That's right, the moment he stepped on the boat.
So he's the type of person who believes in "love at first sight."
This is really...
We really need to watch it again from season 1.
He actually made up his mind from the moment he got on the boat in the first episode...
[First day
first meeting]
What's your name?
I'm Pink.
Pink?
When we first met at the very beginning,
[Day 3: Pre-sleep interview
Pink talks about the most memorable thing about Yi]
he gave me the feeling of being really approachable,
like he's pretty cute,
and his Chinese is not very good.
We're getting separated soon.
[Day 3: Pink and Yi, who were originally supposed to shoot together, are suddenly separated]
I'm really reluctant. We slept so well together last night.
Yeah.
He just gives off this very happy vibe.
[Day 5 Pre-sleep interview: Pink already wants to choose Yi as his CP]
No matter what we do,
I just feel like we click,
and I also want to try acting with him.
Poom. When you see Pink crying, you feel...
Very sad.
I also feel he is very sad when I see him crying.
It seems that he knew he wouldn't be chosen,
so he started to cry and feel sad.
So I think this is really very interesting.
I think this is really the most valuable part
of our Love Casting.
When I was watching, I was in a mixed mood.
On one hand, I was expecting,
and on the other, I was very worried about them.
At last, I also felt they're heartbroken.
Actually, this is where our fake drama becomes real.
What sounds like a
made-up story is all fiction.
Yeah.
And many BL dramas are built on an imagination.
But their emotions are real,
[BL world is fictional
the boys' feelings are real]
so Pink can cry like this.
And it can be conveyed to the audience and into the hearts of those who watch.
It’s all ups and downs, and you just go along with it.
But at least we formed a CP at last,
and it's a happy CP.
Yeah, the strongest CP vibe. They're like a perfect mix of enemies turned lovers  all the time.
[Adson and Yi's love confession is about to unfold]
Yeah, their plots are really fascinating.
Alright, actually, our production team
really put a lot of effort into completing this project —
Energy Running Low — let's watch it together!
[Energy Running Low]
Give me.
Give me energy.
Naked man.
Sir. Sir.
Hello.
Are you okay?
You're awake.
Sir. Sir.
Are you okay?
Do you need me to take you to the hospital?
I'll make the call.
Sir. Sir.
Stop joking, okay?
Pranks are not funny.
Don't let go.
Just consider it me doing a good deed for the day.
Why do I have this?
You'll be naked if you're not wearing it.
That's too crazy.
So you came on a spaceship?
How did you end up on Earth then?
I don't know.
So holding hands can give you energy?
Yeah.
How long do you need to get fully charged
before you can return to your planet?
Holding hands for about
ten thousand years.
Ten thousand years?
That's too long.
Or you want to hug me, which can be faster.
Hug you?
Okay.
No, not like this. This is useless.
Take off your clothes.
Only skin contact can work.
No.
We can hold hands.
Hold hands?
So what about your friends?
I don't have enough energy,
so I can't reach them.
I'll get you some clothes. Let's go.
You want to stay in my house?
Sure.
You want my energy?
Of course.
But from now on,
you will be my slave.
Carry me upstairs.
Did you hurt your foot?
Do you still want energy?
Okay.
Go!
Here.
Give me a massage.
Is this okay?
Harder.
You need to eat, so do I.
Let me help you.
What's that?
Are you stealing electricity?
Keep massaging. Hurry up.
I'm not full yet.
You're always trying to steal electricity.
How much have I given you already?
You stole my electricity.
Go home.
I want to go home.
Stand straight.
Hands up.
Higher.
What are you doing?
You'll know later.
Thank you for the energy you give me.
I'm willing to give you more.
They're so cute.
So cute.
[Great Shock]
Gosh.
Shocked?
Very shocked.
That kiss...
For that kiss, you could feel the energy even through the screen!
Because it used to be some funny plots,
I thought it would be just like that.
When it came to the end, it turned out to be this.
It gives you something real.
Full of energy!
That kiss requires a lot of trust in each other,
and it’s something that comes from having feelings that have been nurtured,
so they can kiss like that.
Really.
That’s something they can't fake. It really can’t be acted out.
To be honest,
since the first performance, Yi has improved a lot.
He has improved a lot. Yeah.
He showed his cuteness in front of the camera.
And the key point is, don’t you think
they play their roles so perfectly that
no one else could pull it off like they do?
Poom.
Is that kiss real?
That kiss was clearly very real.
Especially when they kissed, I felt very shy.
From the moment they started getting to know each other until now,
watching them perform together,
I feel they’re just so cute.
Really.
That's called being an Auntie, okay?
Yeah, that's an auntie's heart.
Congratulations to Poom on becoming our senior member.
A senior member of Auntie Squad.
He's in.
From the beginning, we gathered these eight boys,
these new actors together,
to train them and have them live together.
I actually think BL, to me, is kind of like this:
no matter your gender or age,
we've all probably imagined
having a perfect love story at some point.
What's that image? What're those pink bubbles?
[BL brings a perfect love story to the audience, regardless of gender]
It doesn't have to be like a fairy tale where
two people are destined to be together.
But it can be very free and natural,
allowing you to feel the bitterness and sweetness of love.
I think that's what makes BL so beautiful.
It really feels like I've accompanied them
through what feels like a summer.
Yeah.
As for my own feelings,
because it's actually been a while since I've been in a relationship,
I mean it,
I'd forget about love and excitement,
[The real love stories of the 8 boys strike directly at the hearts of Auntie Squad]
or my heart racing because of love.
When I saw everyone confessing their love,
it'd remind me of the way I confessed mine before.
So I'm very grateful to Love Casting.
Thank you, these eight boys.
You remind me of
he fluttering feeling in love
[The fluttering feeling of love and the feeling of youth]
and the feeling of youth.
Really, thank you.
I want to congratulate you.
Although some were not chosen,
at least you can have a beautiful experience
and made some good friends.
Congratulations.
Really.
Before coming to the show, I thought it would be
all about youth,
and just fun and happiness, full of joy,
but I didn't expect that
they'd have so many real stories.
Whether it was through the process of filming the acting scenes
or truly having heart-to-heart conversations to understand each other,
I feel like the unexpected surprises actually
came from them.
For these eight boys,
this is a very precious memory,
and it also includes your dream--
to film a very good production.
This is already a very, very good production.
Even though in the end, it’s Adson and Yi who are filming together,
the other boys, you all did a great job.
This is the biggest encouragement I want to give you all.
Really, thank you
for letting us see such youthful, passionate,
and touching moments. Thank you!
As you said,
these eight boys brought us their true emotions.
I'm also looking forward to seeing them
in different fields,
and appreciating their different products.
Most importantly, that "Energy Running Low", isn't it too short?
Right? I'll be pounding the table for more.
They can show us 12 episodes for that.
Yeah, because the characters are well set.
Thank you, Love Casting,
for bringing us passion for life.
We'll see you next season.
Bye.