♪The wind sways,
trembling the moonlight♪
♪Spreading over the Xingdou forest♪
♪Your image imprinted on my heart♪
♪No matter where I go♪
♪If fate stirs up waves♪
♪I will stand before you to shield you♪
♪Without retreating♪
♪Even if my soul disperses♪
♪For you, I renounce my dreams♪
♪With unwavering love
and profound devotion♪
♪I'll use a lifetime of courage♪
♪I will protect your peace
for a lifetime♪
♪Enduring immense suffering
does not matter♪
♪I'll face endless suffering
without regret♪
♪Even if I turn into drifting dust♪
♪I must♪
♪Run into your arms♪
=The Land of Warriors=
(Adapted from Tangjia Sanshao's novel
"Soul Land")
=Episode 23=
I have a few words to say.
Five years have passed.
You little devils
have all grown up.
Five years ago,
you parted ways in chaos.
Now, five years later,
you reunite amid the turmoil.
The seven of you
are destined to face
extraordinary challenges
and responsibilities.
As the dean,
I have only one thing to say,
Shrek Academy
will always be your strongest support.
To the Shrek Seven Devils!
Thank you, Dean!
Cheers!
Since Ao is back,
the dean has spent
a fortune on this meal.
So, you guys must eat and drink
to your heart's content.
Don't try to save him money!
No problem!
How naughty you are!
Alright.
Let's dig in!
Let's eat!
Here.
Boss Dai.
Come on!
Cheers!
Rongrong, Zhuqing.
Don't hold back with the dean.
Try this.
It's delicious.
This is hot. Let me blow it for you.
I wish I could eat
and drink with everyone.
Here, have some more food.
You guys enjoy the meal.
I leave here for a while.
San.
Mubai!
If you want to drink,
I'll drink with you.
When you come back,
we'll drink together with everyone else.
But, if you come out alone,
they'll worry about you.
I can't feel genuinely happy.
But I don't want
to ruin their mood either.
It's better to stay here.
At least I can drink with you.
You were advising Ao earlier.
But, now you're the one
overthinking things.
A doctor struggles to treat themselves.
All I'm thinking about now
is how to grow the Tang Clan quickly,
strengthen myself,
revive you,
and overthrow Martial Soul Hall.
San,
achieving those goals
doesn't conflict with being happy.
The journey ahead is long,
so you must travel light.
Don't let your body and mind suffer.
Sometimes, I feel like you're not just
a figment of my imagination.
You
and your words
feel so real to me.
♪If I love you♪
♪Embracing you in every life♪
♪Once you smile, my world♪
♪Clears up♪
San.
Sir.
You received a huge hidden weapon order
from Chief Ning today.
But, the Tang Clan
only has Ao and Fatty.
How are you planning to fulfill it?
I've already thought about it.
Recruiting new members
is our top priority now.
I've already set my sights on a target,
which is the four affiliated tribes
of the Haotian Sect.
Back then, because of the grudges
between Martial Soul Hall
and the Haotian Sect,
they were implicated
and severed ties with the clan.
I want to gather them back together,
partly as an explanation to my father.
But, their resentment
toward the clan runs deep,
so this won't be easy.
That's fine.
Even if you can't persuade them,
Shrek Academy is here for you.
Don't forget,
you have many outstanding juniors
without any affiliation to the clans.
You don't have to stand
on ceremony with me.
Thank you for your support, Dean.
San,
you still have us.
Regarding the four tribes you mentioned,
does that include the Tribe of Strength?
Hmm,
what's their leader's name again?
Titan!
Oh, I remember.
You even sparred
with him at the academy.
You guys have good memories.
But, the Tribe of Strength led by Titan
is only one of the
four single attribute tribes.
As for the other three tribes,
I'm not as familiar.
We'll definitely overcome all obstacles
and stop at nothing to achieve the goal.
San,
just let us know
what you need.
Yeah!
We'll help grow the Tang Clan
into something powerful!
Martial Soul Hall didn't get enough
to harm my second brother,
now they even forced you and Wu
to suffer the same fate.
Their cruelty knows no bounds.
They’ll get their just deserts someday.
I don't expect the divine punishment.
Together with the
righteous people of the world,
I'll make sure Martial Soul Hall pays!
Since your last parting
with the Haotian Sect,
you've become even more composed,
San.
You establish the Tang Clan
and fight against the Martial Soul Hall.
I'll fully support you.
As for the Haotian Sect,
you don't have to worry too much.
The elders are looking for
someone capable of leading
the Haotian Sect.
Strengthening the Tang Clan
will only prove to them
that they chose the right person.
But,
apart from the Tribe of Strength,
your intention to ally
with the other
three single attribute tribes
is nearly impossible.
So I suggest you
recruit other capable individuals
to expand the sect.
I can help you with that.
I know
it's difficult to convince them,
which is why I came to you for help.
I'm a disciple of the Haotian Sect,
and also Tang Hao's younger sister.
I'm afraid I'd be chased away
the moment I showed up at their doors.
The four tribes' resentment
toward the Haotian Sect
runs deeper than you imagine.
I don't want you to visit them directly.
I need your help understanding them.
As the saying goes, "Know your enemy
and know yourself,
and you'll never lose."
The four single attribute tribes
include the Tribe of Strength,
the Tribe of Defense,
the Tribe of Agility,
and the Tribe of Destruction.
Individually, their strength
isn't top-tier,
but each tribe
has its own unique skills.
The Tribe of Strength
is known for its immense power
and mastery of forging,
which brought
great wealth to the tribe.
Their martial soul
is the Supreme Orangutan.
The tribe leader, Titan,
is a vice president
of the Blacksmiths Guild,
a Divine Craftsman,
and a Great Soul Master
of the Storm Attack Branch.
Blacksmiths aren't highly regarded
across the continent,
but your father deeply admired
Elder Titan's forging skills.
In return,
Titan greatly respects your father.
If you're determined
to convince the four tribes,
the Tribe of Strength
should be your first choice.
The Tribe of Defense
is renowned for its
incredible defensive capabilities
and expertise in construction.
Many of the
defensive structures in the sect
were built by the Tribe of Defense.
In terms of defense,
they are definitely
not worse than the Elephant
Armored Tribe among the Seven Clans.
Their martial soul
is the Plate Armor Rhino.
Their leader, Niu Gao is a Great
Soul Master of the Defense Branch.
Elder Niu
is a warm-hearted,
and outspoken person,
a very lovely old man.
But,
he's very clear about
his likes and dislikes.
Because of past events
involving the Haotian Sect,
he holds a grudge against your father.
You must be careful.
The Tribe of Agility
is famous for its incredible speed
and reconnaissance skills.
Their martial soul is the
Sharp-tailed Swallow.
The pure speed-type soul masters
are the best scouts.
Their tribe leader, Bai He,
is a Great Soul Master
of the Agility Branch.
Apart from that,
he's also your father's and my uncle.
You should address him as a grand uncle.
(Grand uncle?)
However, regarding this relationship,
you'd best not mention it
when you meet him.
Ever since the
Haotian Sect secluded itself,
we've had no contact with them.
I've heard that in recent years,
their tribe hasn't
been doing well either.
Lastly,
the Tribe of Destruction.
Their martial soul
is Soul Breaking Spear,
focused on attack.
The Tribe of Destruction specializes
in secret medicinal techniques,
so they are skilled in making medicine.
Whether life-saving remedies
or deadly poisons,
they are very good at it.
Their tribe leader, Yang Wudi is a Great
Soul Master of Storm Attack Branch.
It can be said that he has
tried all kinds of herbs
and is obsessed with it.
Specializing in making medicine...
Actually, the Tribe of Destruction
suffered the most under the
suppression of the Martial Soul Hall.
Back then, the Martial Soul Hall
wanted to locate the
Haotian Sect's whereabouts,
and besieged the Tribe of Destruction.
During that,
Elder Yang's brother
was taken hostage.
He's most likely
killed.
I didn't expect them
to have endured so much.
No wonder my father feels so guilty.
If I truly manage to bring the
four single attribute tribes together,
I will do everything
to make it up to them
and ensure they are
never oppressed by the
Martial Soul Hall again.
San,
that's all I know
about the four single attribute tribes.
I hope it's helpful to you.
Of course, it is.
But,
I have one last question.
(The Mansion of the Tribe of Strength)
(Strength)
(Apprentice Fee: 2000 silver soul coins,
debited from Divine Hornet Clan)
(Ledger)
As per routine,
today is the day to distribute funds
to each household in the tribe.
However, the current situation is chaos.
We've long lost contact
with all the clans
we've had dealings with.
Only a few balances remain unsettled.
So,
please, everyone
bear with us a little longer.
Senior Brother,
don't worry.
We'll get through
this tough time together.
Senior Brother.
How is it going?
The Seven Clans reorganized.
The Divine Hornet Clan was attacked
and annexed by other clans.
Their leader was killed.
The clan no longer exists,
and the debt is unrecoverable.
The leader of the Divine Hornet Clan
was always righteous,
but he meets such a cruel end.
We shall pay our respects
to him another day.
Did someone bully you?
Senior Brother,
I...
I was driven out of the Gale Clan.
What happened?
The Gale Clan has surrendered
to the Martial Soul Hall.
They claimed the clan
has changed its leader,
and they won't
acknowledge the past debts.
They even said,
if you're dissatisfied,
go ahead and settle it in person.
They are waiting for you.
All useless men!
Senior Brother,
don't act rashly!
Let go of me!
Senior Brother!
Senior Brother.
What are you doing?
I know the tribe is
short on funds right now
and this may not be the best
time for me to say this.
But, my child is falling ill,
and I need to get a doctor
urgently for some herbs.
Could you spare me a little,
just enough to cover
the medical expenses?
Come on.
Get up.
Hurry up.
Take your child to see the doctor.
It's not much.
If it's not enough,
I'll figure something out.
No, no, Senior Brother.
I can't take your money.
Just let me withdraw a bit
from the tribe's funds.
There's no fund
in the tribe's account now.
Take it.
Don't delay the treatment.
Thank you, Senior Brother.
I'll figure out the money issue later.
Don't tell the tribe leader.
He's getting older,
don't let him worry.
Understood.
Nonsense!
Do you think I'm blind?
Father!
Leader!
I, Titan,
am ashamed to face all of you.
Back when we,
the Tribe of Strength
left the Haotian Sect,
although we lived in poverty,
we could still sustain ourselves.
But now, given the current chaos,
the tribe
is struggling just to make ends meet.
Here are all my personal savings
from over the years.
A portion is left for the elderly
to spend their old age at ease.
The rest can be equally
distributed among all of you.
For those who want to seek a new path,
take the money
and leave the Tribe of Strength.
Don't trap yourselves here.
No, leader!
We won't leave.
Leader,
whatever challenges arise,
we will face them together.
We're young and strong.
We have our hands and feet.
We won't be starve to death.
This is
all my fault.
If it weren't for the rule I set
forbidding certain businesses,
the Tribe of Strength
wouldn't be in this dire state today.
Father,
how can this be your fault?
Back then, the entire tribe
agreed to the rule you set.
Senior Brother is right.
We all supported
the rule you established.
Even if we must beg on the streets,
the Tribe of Strength
will never earn that kind of money.
Father,
our tribe must not fall apart like this.
If we can't find suitable work,
I'll take everyone
outside to look for jobs
or participate in the Martial
Soul Competition to earn prize money.
No matter what, we'll find
a way to support the clan.
Good men of the tribe!
Since you are all so resolute today,
we will surely get through this.
The Tribe of Strength
is quite impressive.
I'm satisfied.
As the Deputy Head of the Tang Clan,
I propose
we make this the Tang Clan's mansion.
You truly are
a good student of Mr. Flander.
Is your martial soul an abacus?
San,
regarding the matters
you asked me about,
I've already sent disciples
from the Qibao Amber Sect
to investigate it.
The Tribe of Strength's business
has been struggling ever since
they left the Haotian Sect.
With the recent chaos caused
by the Martial Soul Hall,
things have gotten even worse for them.
I have one last question.
What are the weaknesses
of these four tribe leaders?
This is what you truly wanted
to know from me, isn't it?
Elder Titan
is loyal
and values promises.
He holds deep affection for your father.
Among the four tribes, he's the only one
who voluntarily left the sect
out of the resentment
for how your father was treated.
So, I believe
Elder Titan's weakness
must be your father.
San,
will we get kicked out later?
The other three tribes, maybe.
But, the Tribe of Strength won't.
If we're kicked out this time,
we'll just come back next time.
Either way, we'll be with you.
Please inform Elder Titan
that an old acquaintance
has come to visit.
Thank you.
Elder Titan,
it's been so long,
and you're still as robust as ever.
Brother Tai Nuo,
I hope you've been well.
Young Master,
is it really you?
The old servant, Titan
pays respects to the Young Master!
Senior,
please get up.
I never expected that after such
a brief meeting at Shrek back then,
you would still recognize me.
You've grown.
You look more and more
like a master now.
You are our Young Master.
You should sit in the master's seat.
Hmm...
Serve the tea!
Thank you.
Young Master,
I heard that after the
final match of the
Continental Advanced Soul Master
Academy Elite Tournament,
you were taken away by the master.
How is
the master now?
My father...
has decided to retire.
Retire?
Why is the leader
of the Tribe of Strength
meeting San alone?
Could something have happened?
Fatty, stop walking around.
You're making us dizzy.
Are we just going to wait for him here?
We should set a time limit.
For instance, if we don't
meet up within half an hour,
we'll charge in.
Agreed.
San has his own plans.
I trust him to be able
to handle things smoothly.
I've waited all these years
for the master's return.
Honestly, for those two soul bones,
what if they were never returned?
It wasn't his fault.
It was all the Martial Soul Hall.
Yet the Haotian Sect
blamed him for it all.
You don't have to worry about this.
My father is now staying
by my mother's side,
and is unaffected
by those outside rumors.
As for the unfinished matters
my father left behind,
I will take care of them for him.
Senior Titan,
I've come
to discuss something with you.
Young Master,
feel free to say anything.
As long as it's within my power,
I will not refuse.
I plan
to establish a clan
called the Tang Clan.
I'd like to invite the
Tribe of Strength to join us.
Establishing a clan?
The elders of the Haotian Sect allowed
you to reclaim your heritage.
Why do you establish a new clan?
I have a ten-year agreement
with the elders.
Within ten years,
if I can obtain
a Hectomillennium Soul Ring,
reach level 80 in cultivation,
and defeat a Grand Soul Master
from the Martial Soul Hall,
my father will be allowed
to return to the sect
and pay respects to my late grandfather.
Those stubborn old fools!
What kind of conditions are these?
There are all impossible conditions.
Clearly, they just don't want
the master to return.
Father,
others may not be able to do it,
but the Young Master
has extraordinary talent,
that he might succeed in it.
For the sake of my father's wish,
I will achieve it.
Not only will
I fulfill these conditions,
but I will also establish a new clan
to gain strength
over the next ten years.
This way, we'll be in a better position
to fight against Martial Soul Hall
in the future.
I believe
this is what my father
would want to see.
I see.
Young Master,
you truly have great foresight.
Our Tribe of Strength once
swore loyalty to your father,
taking his will as our mission.
Whatever you need,
I will fully support you.
But,
I only have one request.
Senior, please go ahead.
If the Haotian Sect re-emerges one day
and you decide to merge with it,
please allow the Tribe of Strength
to withdraw from the Tang Clan.
That will never happen.
The Tang Clan is the Tang Clan.
It will not belong to any other clan,
nor will it merge with the Haotian Sect.
From today onward,
the Tribe of Strength
will join the Tang Clan
and follow the Young Master's commands.
Elder Titan,
please get up.
From today onward,
you are the chief elder
of the Tang Clan.
Master,
the clan has just been established,
and you must haven't
chosen a location yet.
What about establishing it
at my mansion?
After all, what's mine
is the Young Master's.
Alright.
However, I heard
that the Tribe of Strength
is in the midst of hardship.
If there are any funding issues,
you must tell me.
Our Tang Clan
recently accepted an order
from the Qibao Amber Sect,
and we'll need the full support
of the Tribe of Strength.
Qibao Amber Sect?
What kind of items do they want?
Tang Clan's exclusive secret weapon.
This is the Soundless Arrow,
one of the Tang Clan's secret weapons
and one of the many custom orders
from the Qibao Amber Sect.
Ingenious!
Absolutely ingenious!
Master,
we, the Tribe of Strength
cannot craft such items.
Why is he taking so long
with no progress?
Elder Titan,
let me introduce them.
Alright.
This is Ma Hongjun,
Dai Mubai,
Zhu Zhuqing,
Ning Rongrong,
and Ao,
they are my close friends.
I've long heard
of the Shrek Seven Devils.
I apologize for the earlier neglect.
Please forgive me.
Tai Nuo,
quickly prepare guest rooms for everyone
so they can rest well.
Alright.
Elder Titan,
there's no need
to go through all that trouble.
Please, if you have
matters to attend to,
don't worry about us.
Alright,
then I'll excuse myself.
Thank you, Elder Titan.
Thank you.
Did you secretly learn
communication skills from the dean?
You settled this so quickly.
Elder Titan has agreed
to join the Tang Clan,
but he refused to craft weapons.
No crafting weapons?
After the Tribe of Strength
separated from the Haotian Sect,
we suffered repeated oppression
from the Martial Soul Hall.
Not only did they interrogate me
about the Haotian Sect's whereabouts,
but they also tried to force
the Tribe of Strength to serve them
by crafting weapons.
They used both coercion
and deception.
At one point,
for the survival of my clan,
I was compelled to create
some experimental weapons.
They used those weapons
to annihilate countless minor sects,
just to test the power of the weapons.
Those sects had a legacy
of over a hundred years,
yet they were easily
destroyed in an instant.
I became an accomplice.
I was the knife of the
Martial Soul Hall used to kill.
Since then, I established a rule
of not crafting weapons anymore,
to atone for our sins.
Who would have thought
that the renowned Tribe of Strength
in the blacksmithing world
would refuse to craft weapons?
No wonder they're struggling so much.
Please allow me to speak frankly,
this tribe was taken in,
but not entirely.
How could Elder Titan
abandon his crafting skills?
As a Divine Craftsman,
how could he not want
to create masterpieces on the forge?
But, because he carries
a compassionate heart,
he's willing to let go of his pursuits.
This is righteousness.
I originally thought
convincing the Tribe of Strength
would help me unite the other tribes.
But, I didn't expect the first hurdle
to be so challenging.
The rules mentioned by Elder Titan
seem to have been made out of necessity.
Now, things have changed with time.
Maybe we can figure out a way
to change his mind.
We'd like to train with Elder Titan.
Great!
You're welcome to join.
Amazing!
This is incredible!
These arrowheads are so sharp!
Fatty,
look at all these
broken stones on the ground.
The floor is covered in pieces.
Maybe we should find something
to clean this up.
This is made of refined iron essence.
It's evenly textured
and highly durable.
It seems to have been tempered
using the Haotian Sect's
Random Air Hammer Skill.
This is truly impressive!
But, what is it called?
It's called the Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
Don't underestimate its small size.
It can hold up to
48 bolts at a time.
You just need to simply adjust
the trigger mechanism before use
and it can release 16 bolts in one go.
16 bolts!
Moreover, it can easily pierce through
the defenses of a
soul master below level 40.
Its firing speed is extremely fast.
Elder, please consider
to own this for the Tribe of Strength.
This Godly Zhuge Crossbow
is indeed divine.
Keep it safe
and don't leave it
lying around carelessly.
Why is this old man so stubborn?
No rush.
(Strength)
Elder Titan,
please come along with us
to the Qibao Amber Sect.
I've taken on another order.
Master,
please don't trouble me with this.
Don't worry.
It's not weapons.
Rongrong's carriage
is already waiting outside.
Let's head out now.
These are the disciples severely injured
during our last battle
with the Martial Soul Hall.
This time, we invited the Tang Clan here
because San thought
we might be able to use prosthetics
to help restore their broken bodies.
What are prosthetics?
Elder,
take a look at this.
This is the drawing I drafted.
We're here
to measure the body of the disciples
and make sure the exact sizes,
so that the prosthetic limbs we made
can fit them perfectly.
Rongrong.
Come on.
Thank you, Elder.
The Soundless Arrow.
You recognize it, Elder?
If not for it protecting me,
I might have lost more than just a leg.
I heard the master has ordered
another batch of hidden weapons.
I hope I can use them
to continue protecting the sect.
I'll take the measurements for you.
Thank you.
Master,
for this order,
the Tribe of Strength
won't accept payment.
I'm willing to craft prosthetic limbs
for the Qibao Amber Sect for free.
Elder,
I appreciate your generosity,
but I understand the
Tribe of Strength's current situation.
How could I let you work for free?
No,
prosthetic limbs will be free.
But, we'll charge
for the hidden weapons.
You've changed your mind.
I am an old man
with one foot in the grave,
and I thought I have
made clear of everything.
But today, you've taught me
an important lesson.
I understand your intentions.
Weapons are inanimate,
and are neither good nor evil.
It all depends on
whose hands wield them.
Such a simple truth,
yet I was blinded by my stubbornness.
Abandoning the craft due to fear
is indeed an unwise option.
Your reluctance to sacrifice more lives
stems from your compassion.
That is no fault of yours.
But, the Martial Soul Hall
is now being so rampant,
and no one dares to oppose them.
My initial intention
of establishing the Tang Clan
is to fight against
the Martial Soul Hall.
If one day
the armies of Tiandou and Xingluo
are equipped with the
Tang Clan's secret weapons,
what advantage would
the Martial Soul Hall have left?
The number of soul masters
in the Martial Soul Hall
is enough to crush both Tiandou
and Xingluo empires.
If we can use the equipment
to close the gap between
ordinary people and soul masters,
then soul masters won't have
an absolute advantage anymore.
Especially for the
low-level soul masters,
while facing armies
with highly destructive weapons,
they will inevitably suffer losses.
The Qibao Amber Sect placed an order
because they witnessed
how Tang Clan's secret weapons
can help for the lack of combat strength
among the support branch soul masters.
But, to produce such
a large quantity of secret weapons,
we'll need not only
the Tribe of Strength,
but also more blacksmiths
to join the Tang Clan.
Master,
I'll lead my tribes and give it our all.
With our own strength,
we will severely strike
the Martial Soul Hall in the future.
Master,
the tribe has limited metal supplies.
We can manage the prosthetics,
but for the secret weapons,
we'll need to go to the
Capital of Metal, Gengxin City,
to buy materials.
The secret weapons are not urgent.
Our primary goal right now
is to convince the other
three single attribute tribes.
I'll leave the other three tribe leaders
to your efforts, Elder.
Regarding the antidote
Xue Beng asked you to create,
are you confident about it?
This complex poison is indeed tricky.
Without knowing how it was made,
it's hard to formulate an antidote.
But, since I've promised Xue Beng,
I'll do my best.
Moreover, the fate of Emperor Xue Ye
is tied to the well-being of the people.
If even you and the
Grand Venom Master are stumped,
who else could solve this poison?
If we can convince the
other three single attribute tribes,
there might be one person
who can do this.
It seems
that convincing the
remaining three tribes
will be incredibly difficult.
Why do you say so?
If someone in the four tribes
can create an antidote,
but you haven't given up yet
and are still trying,
there's only one possibility.
You're not completely confident
about persuading the other tribes.
What's your next plan?
Take them down one by one.
There's an opportunity soon.
The four tribes meet every two years.
This time, the gathering is in Longxing
Town, at the Tribe of Defense's place.
The date is drawing near,
and I plan to take everyone there.
This rare item was acquired by the
master of the Elephant Armored Tribe
through an auction.
Its attacking power is incredible,
and I presented it as a gift
for Your Holiness's enjoyment.
Interesting.
But against the absolute power,
this thing is worthless.
What does Hu Yanzhen want in return?
The Elephant Armored Tribe hit a wall
with the Tribe of Defense,
so they're asking for our help.
Na,
what do you think
the Martial Soul Hall currently lacks?
Soul masters.
We've lost too many
people to the Operation Clan Hunt.
For our future ambitions,
we need more soul masters to join us.
Great!
What about the Elephant Armored Tribe?
The Elephant Armored Tribe was
the first of the original Four Clans
to pledge allegiance to us.
They've always sought to claim
the top spot among the new Seven Clans.
Obviously, they want
to expand their power
and gain new support.
Their strength represents
the Martial Soul Hall's
new force in the
reformation of the Seven Clans.
See?
No matter how strong the weapons are,
it's incomparable to
the powerful soul masters.
So, only soul masters
are our most valuable assets.
Which do you think is stronger,
the Elephant Armored Tribe
or the Tribe of Defense?
Of course, it's the
Elephant Armored Tribe.
Does that mean the
Elephant Armored Tribe
doesn't want to
sacrifice their disciples
and is borrowing our strength instead?
I may have
underestimated Hu Yanzhen.
That means
the internal affairs
of the Martial Soul Hall
are as complex as a nation's.
Everyone has their own agenda.
Na,
you need to learn how
to control people's hearts.
Taking advantage of people's
hearts is the best way.
Understood, Your Holiness.
I'll extend the grace of the Holy Lady
and first investigate the situation
of the Elephant Armored Tribe
before making any decisions.
This way, we won't appear indifferent
and hurt their loyalty,
nor will we deplete
the Martial Soul Hall's resources.
At the same time, this will show them
the fierce competition
among the new Seven Clans,
prompting the Elephant Armored Tribe
to give their all
to expand our influence.
It's a triple win.
Take Yan with you.
There are some things
you don't need to say it yourself.
You need to learn this as well.
Thank you for your guidance,
Your Holiness.
Stop!
If you want to pass through here,
pay 100 gold soul coins.
I've never heard of such
a rule in Longxing Town.
The Elephant Armored Tribe.
Who gave you the authority
to set up a toll here?
If you don't pay, then scram!
Who dares
speak to me like that?
If you have the guts,
step forward and let me see who you are!
How dare you
challenge the Elephant Armored Tribe?
You're leaving your life here today.
Elder,
let me handle this.
I have some old scores
to settle with these guys.
Bu Le,
do you still remember me?
You brat!
I'll take your life today!
Inescapable Double Shield!
Don't worry.
Fatty can handle this.
Let him have some workouts.
Let's fight together!
♪The young man's journey
of dreams has begun♪
♪Breaking through the uncharted storms♪
♪The twin martial soul
shapes the destiny ahead♪
Thanks for letting me win.
♪Waiting for the moment
to shift the tides of fate♪
♪The trained body
is surging with growth♪
Haotian Hammer!
Bu Le!
It's never too late to take revenge.
Let's escape first.
We haven't settled yet.
Run!
Let go of me.
Master,
your friends
are truly remarkable young talents!
♪The battle of youth
drawn to the brink of battle♪
♪Marching forward
with dreams blazing like fire♪
♪The tale of blood
and battle scars of heroes♪
♪Earning glory in the face of adversity♪
Everybody!
Longxing Town,
I know this place.
This town
is very small,
but since it is located on the border,
there are many merchants
who travel back and forth here.
There are lots of good food, too.
It's just that the security is not good.
Those guys at the gate
were just too arrogant.
Yeah, that's right.
Mubai.
Zhuqing.
Who governs the Longxing Town now?
The Elephant Armored Tribe
is the strongest force here.
They've been managing the town,
but the report of Longxing Town
about the Elephant Armored Tribe
doesn't match what we saw today.
That's right.
The prosperity here is just a facade.
The Tribe of Defense
moved here two years ago.
They told me
that the business here is hard to do.
Plus, they've been
subjected to bullying
by the Martial Soul Hall.
The four tribes hold
a gathering every two years
to support one another, right?
Yes.
Without the protection of a clan,
we can only band together for warmth.
We're all oppressed
by the Martial Soul Hall.
Only by uniting can we resist them.
The scope of the Martial Soul Hall's
persecution is growing wider.
It has even expanded to
the Xingluo's border now.
This shows how Bi Bi Dong
has been laying her plans for years.
That's why her influence is so vast.
Master.
Elder.
San might be talking to Wu.
Hmm,
this is a long story.
How about we head to a bun shop
and talk while we eat?
Sure.
Let's go.
On the way, I'll tell you
about my romantic encounter
in Longxin Town.
No need.
We still need to look around
and see if there’s anything unusual.
Let’s go.
That story about your girl in white,
I’ve heard it so many times
my ears are growing calluses!
We’ll also go take a look around.
They don't have the chance to taste it.
Let's go.
Let's enjoy some meat.
What's that sound?
San.
Hurry!
Let’s go take a look!
Good! Good! Good!
Excuse me.
Good! Good!
We can actually make
money performing here.
We could do performances
in the future too.
I'll play this part,
and you can your Blue Silver Emperor
to do a "thousand-hand
plate spinning" act!
You are indeed a business genius.
Great!
Thank you.
San,
ordinary people have it tough
trying to make a living.
You should give them some support too.
Thank you.
Alright, thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you all.
♪Ending the despair of suffering♪
♪Justice runs deep in our veins♪
♪The humble but powerful♪
♪Will break open the world of darkness♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪Consumed and engulfed by fate♪
♪The flame within burns
with unwavering passion♪
♪The broken darkness♪
♪Will eventually break into daylight♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪