♪The blood within me ignites
with a fierce desire♪
♪Exposing the lies
that fate has written♪
♪No more hiding♪
♪My martial soul has awakened
in its full strength♪
♪Even countless of trials can't stop me♪
♪The searing heat
that surges within my chest♪
♪I want the world♪
♪To remember me♪
♪Yes or no, right or wrong♪
♪To defeat or to be defeated♪
♪Giving my all with no regrets♪
♪Breaking through the encirclement♪
♪It doesn't matter who my opponent is♪
♪To shine as the new star
of Douluo Continent♪
♪The fleeting dream of life is
easily shattered♪
♪So why not face it boldly,
just this once♪
♪Fierce storms and raging thunder♪
♪Burn me, yet refine my determination♪
♪No matter how battered,
I smile and refuse to retreat♪
♪A so-called hero, covered in dust♪
♪Scarred and worn♪
♪Can still sever the cycle of fate♪
=The Land of Warriors=
(Adapted from
Tangjia Sanshao's novel "Soul Land")
=Episode 14=
Master.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to collect a debt.
Such audacity!
Don't forget.
I'm the leader of Martial Soul Hall!
I am your master!
And I am your...
What did you say?
You were already nothing to me
ever since the day you hurt me.
So, I can boost my power
by absorbing the soul power
of other soul masters, huh?
Thank you,
my master.
Thank you for your last lesson.
(Qian Xunji,)
(your death)
(gave me a reason
to drive off the Haotian Sect.)
(It also helped me to unlock
the Rakshasa Secret Realm.)
(Now, I face its challenge.)
(The Martial Soul Hall
will rise gloriously.)
(I suppose this is the last bit of value
you can provide to us.)
Unlock it.
I need you to do two things for me.
First,
I owed our sect these two soul bones.
I've failed to meet
the expectations of Haotian Sect.
Bring them back for me.
Second,
help me pay respect to your grandfather.
Send my regards to your uncle as well.
Father,
why aren't you willing
to visit Uncle yourself?
I'll spend the rest of my life
to keep your mother company here.
San,
I have placed such heavy burdens
on your shoulders.
Are the burdens too heavy for you?
As a son,
I only hate myself
for not being able to share your burdens
with you earlier.
You've grown up.
Father,
you're wounded.
You need to rest and recuperate.
This Dragon Leaf can help you
to consolidate your foundation.
You may consume this once per month.
By the way,
I know of a place
that can boost
the growth of plants 1000 times.
That place
may help Mother to recover
from her wounds quicker.
1000 times?
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
That place is known as
one of the Three Treasures.
It's called Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
I harvested these Dragon Leaves
from that place.
Yin,
did you hear that?
Everyone else is undergoing training.
Why did you guys disobey our order?
We're applying
for the teaching position.
We won't join
Martial Soul Hall Army.
Release us now!
That's right! Release us!
You want me to release you?
Sure.
But that'll depend on your capabilities.
Who's there?
Your Holiness, please pardon me!
- Your Holiness.
Take them away.
Hu Liena shall remain here.
Yes, Your Holiness.
Na,
come to me.
remember this.
Although one's killing intent
is important,
it'll backfire on you
if you don't know how to control it.
Those who see through you
can manipulate you,
do you understand?
I understand.
I'll surely undergo training
to strengthen my mental fortitude.
Ao,
I don't think the flower crackers
are as good as they used to be.
This is Tiandou City.
This is Qibao Amber Sect.
It turns out that Douluo Continent
is gigantic.
I heard that the environment here
is very harsh.
It can hone one's determination,
body, and mind to the highest degree.
(Extreme North)
If I can endure the trial here,
I'll definitely be able to protect you.
I can't just let other people
protect me forever.
Ao,
I'm working just as hard as you.
Eight steeds! Seven coincidences!
Ten out of ten!
Who opened the door?
Shut the door. Hurry.
It's so cold.
Our party of Level 60 War Soul Masters
lacks a support soul master.
We'll be harvesting soul bones.
And we'll be departing tonight.
This is the deposit.
I'm a Level 53 War Soul Master.
Do you need me?
I'm a Level 49 War Soul Master.
I'll go with you
if you pay me half of it.
I'm a Level 58 Support Soul Master.
Give me two times the deposit.
Twice my reward if we manage
to harvest soul bones.
Even the soul masters of
Qibao Amber Sect
aren't as greedy as you.
Seems like you're itching for a fight.
Don't get so agitated.
Here.
This is a treat for you all.
Try it.
Are you a Food Branch Soul Master?
Boss, look! My wound has healed!
His food can cure people.
Yeah.
I'm fair to all, and you won't
incur losses when you invest in me.
I feed you when you starve
and save you when you're in danger.
You're reliable.
I, Wang Kui, the Tempest Wolf,
will have you in our party.
Tempest Wolf?
He's actually Tempest Wolf?
Tempest Wolf,
I've long heard of his name.
This is my partner,
a Seven-Ring War Soul Master.
If you want me,
you have to take him as well.
I'll say this first.
One can only enter
the mountains if they're capable enough.
However, one's life or death
will be determined by fate.
Don't worry.
I know the rules.
Our party is full.
Let's enter the mountains.
Youngsters prefer to seek wealth
than ensure their own survival.
You're right. Cheers.
Tempest Wolf is notorious in
the soul beast hunting circle.
He plays dirty.
Many soul masters who followed him
into the mountains
have gone missing.
No one knows whether
they're dead or alive.
Are you sure you want to
follow him?
I've heard of him.
This man is great
at hunting soul beasts.
I'm almost Level 60.
I can find better soul rings
if I follow his lead.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
But...
You may leave if you're afraid.
I'm not afraid.
I'm just worried about you.
I gave the lady my promise.
I have to fulfill it
and head back as soon as possible.
We're men.
We need to keep our promises.
(Martial Soul Hall Academy)
Generous benefits!
Honorable services!
This is a rare opportunity!
Don't miss out on it...
Who did that?
These boys!
Capture them!
Yes, sir!
I didn't mean it.
Stop!
You want to escape?
Darned lass,
seems like you have a death wish.
How dare you hit me?
She's quick.
Not bad.
Lass,
there's no escape.
You look quite pretty.
I'll make you suffer less
if you stay obedient.
(People often think that escaping
is a sign of cowardice.)
(Little do they know that the art of
movement is a part of the Great Dao.)
(During the evasion process,)
(one can lure foes, set up traps,
and set up formations.)
(Most importantly, they can stay alive.)
I didn't expect you
to be a powerful War Soul Master.
I'm sure you hold an important position
in the Martial Soul Hall.
Mister,
sorry for failing
to recognize your greatness.
Seems like the training
I provided to you wasn't in vain.
Grandpa Sword!
Grandpa Sword,
what are you doing here?
Just look at you.
You ran out all by yourself.
Your father was worried about you.
He told me to find you.
Grandpa,
did you see that?
He's a Five-Ring War Soul Master.
Don't you think I'm amazing?
Of course I saw that.
How dare he try to hurt
the princess of Qibao Amber Sect?
This won't end well for him.
(Sunset Forest, Ice Fire Mouth Spring)
This place is magical indeed.
This is the Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
The eye of the spring is highly toxic.
Soul masters and soul beasts dare not
approach this place easily.
It's safest for Mother to grow up here.
San,
you have to be careful.
Do not let the environment here
harm your mother.
Mother.
Father,
seems like
this is the best spot for Mother.
This may seem like a beautiful place.
However, these two springs
are fatal to humans.
It's because I've consumed
the Octa Dark Frost
and the Fiery Soft Apricot.
And, I've undergone
the Ice Fire Body Training.
Therefore, my martial soul and body
are immune to both water and fire now.
Immune to both water and fire?
This place is great indeed.
How did you discover it?
Dugu Bo abducted me and
brought me to this place
to make me neutralize
the poison in his body.
I even made a bet with him.
A bet?
That's right.
As long as I pass his three
poison-neutralizing tests,
he'll promise me three things.
First, it was
the Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom.
I neutralized it easily.
The second was the Bamboo Emerald.
It was highly toxic.
It can turn the victim
into a pool of pus
after a short period.
However,
I neutralized it with the pollen
of Fragrant Silk Woven Flower.
As for the third test,
it was more troublesome.
The third test
should be neutralizing the Jade Phosphor
Serpent King Venom in your body.
I can't bear to kill you now.
If you lose, you can stay here
and serve me as my apprentice.
You can plan how to exploit me
all you want after I lose the bet.
You have a Beast Martial Soul.
That's why the poison
merged with your body.
If you wish to retain
the lethal toxin in your body
without letting it damage you,
you have to find a vessel
to store the toxin.
Do you intend to seal the toxin
in my body
in my soul bone?
That's right.
It's possible to use medicine
to guide the toxins
in your meridians and bones,
gradually filtering them and
concentrating them entirely
into the soul bone.
Just like me.
The toxins in my body
are kept in Blue Silver Plant
and my attached soul bone.
Therefore, my life isn't in danger.
There are not many people
I admire in the world.
Now, you're one of them.
All right.
I'll heed your instructions.
Consume this.
You just spit this out.
Now, you want me to consume it?
This...
I...
Weren't you worried
that I was trying to harm you?
Didn't you make me take that
in order to keep me in check?
This is the inner core
of my Jade Phosphor Serpent
after I evolved it
into the Jade Phosphor Serpent King.
If you fail to treat me,
it'll explode in your body.
Forget about you.
Even a Grand Soul Master
won't be able to survive this.
I'll suffer a terrible death
if I fail to treat you, huh?
So, if I manage to treat you,
I guess there are plenty
of benefits for me, right?
You annoying boy.
This inner core contains
half of my power.
As long as you don't try anything funny,
it'll only be beneficial
to your cultivation.
You better return it to me
once I'm cured.
Fine.
Old Freak,
I have one more condition.
Do you know
that you're the only person
in the last few decades who dares
to negotiate a deal with me?
It's simple.
Every single plant here is a rare herb.
I wish to take some with me
so that I can give them to my friends.
Forget about the plants.
If you can cure me,
you can own
the entire Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
After that, I neutralized
his poison using the methods found
in the Xuan Tian Records.
And, I became the owner of this place.
We became friends
after our hostile encounter.
In the end, we became best friends.
Grand Venom Master is known
for his eccentric personality.
It's kind of magical for you two
to become friends.
Indeed.
After that, I brought these herbs
back to Shrek Academy.
I gave them to my friends
to aid them in their cultivation.
I suppose this is our shared destiny.
San,
I'm truly happy for you.
Friends, brothers, and lovers,
those are
the reasons we live in this world.
You have plenty of friends,
and have found the love of your life.
You're truly lucky.
This is a type
of responsibility as well.
Father,
do you miss Uncle?
It's been more than
two decades since we met.
He should be as old as me now.
(Wu, I finally saw Mother.)
(I'm sure you would
be happy for me as well)
(if you were still around.)
How's Father doing?
Fourth Prince,
His Majesty still needs
to rest and recuperate.
Get out of my way.
I'll serve Father.
His Majesty must take his medicine
without any accidents.
I should do it.
I'm fulfilling my filial duties here.
Can you replace me for that?
Go now.
Get us some snacks and tea.
I have to look after His Majesty
under Crown Prince's order.
I dare not leave without permission.
Crown Prince?
What?
Aren't I one of the princes too?
Xue Beng.
Why are you raising your voice?
Father,
I heard that your condition
has worsened.
That's why I came here
to look after you.
But that scum tried to stop me.
It's time for you
to be sensible.
You should learn from Crown Prince.
I'll feed you the medicine.
Hurry and get us some water.
Your Highness.
What are you doing here?
I escorted Fourth Prince here
to visit His Majesty.
Why are you still standing there?
Hurry and feed Father some water.
Your Highness, I dare not obstruct you
from fulfilling your filial duties.
You were never here usually.
Why are you being a filial son today?
You know that it's your duty
to look after Father, huh?
Although I'm a terrible son,
I still have to fulfill
my filial duties.
Moreover, I have something
to discuss with Father.
Father needs to rest.
You may discuss it with me.
You...
What trouble have you
gotten yourself into again?
Father,
a few days ago,
I wanted Grand Venom Master
to give me a venomous serpent for fun.
He wasn't willing to do so.
He said he lost the serpent.
He tried to deceive me
like I was a three-year-old kid.
Therefore, I came here to find you
so that you could issue an edict to him.
Your Majesty,
my serpent did go missing
a few days ago.
It wasn't my intention to brush him off.
However, I've found another serpent
that can replace it.
I wish to invite Fourth Prince
to check it out with me.
Hurry!
Show it to me!
You...
You came here to visit me
just so you could get yourself
a venomous serpent?
Scram!
Father, please be appeased.
Don't be angry.
I'll scram right now.
Get out!
Let's go.
This time, you mustn't lose
the serpent again.
Father, don't be angry.
Please mind your health.
Water.
Here. Have some water.
This is the medicine I swapped out.
Luckily, you appeared
in the nick of time.
Is this the pill?
This contains the toxin
of my Jade Phosphor
Serpent King's Martial Soul.
This pill is highly toxic.
Are you sure
it can fight off the toxin
in Father's body?
I've been crafting poisons for decades.
This is the only solution.
Father is deeply poisoned.
I can't afford to delay it any longer.
I have to take the risk.
Do I need to test the potency myself
before I feed it to him?
Although I like playing dirty,
I won't joke around
with His Majesty's life.
Don't worry.
This pill can stabilize His Majesty's
heart meridians.
You can swap Imperial Physician Yang's
prescription with this
so that I can keep researching
the antidote.
You have to be careful.
Hopefully,
Crown Prince didn't notice it.
If we wish to suppress
the toxin in His Majesty's body,
we have to take the risk by swapping
his prescriptions multiple times.
I don't think we can suppress it
if we only do it once.
Now, there's no turning back.
Let's take it one step at a time.
Luckily, we've obtained the poison
that Imperial Physician Yang
had fed him with.
I'll leave the antidote research to you.
Your Holiness,
I think we should head back.
Head Flamen and other flamens
won't support us.
I don't need their support.
I just need them to know about this.
Yes, Your Holiness.
Head Flamen and the other flamens
have vital positions
in the Martial Soul Hall.
If we don't notify them before we act,
we'll be criticized when they find out.
Elder Golden Alligator.
Where's Head Flamen?
(Grand Golden Alligator Master)
(Second Flamen)
Head Flamen is on a retreat.
He will not see anyone.
Please hand this to Head Flamen.
What does that mean?
Since they're not objecting to it,
I'll take it as a yes, then.
If so,
they should send flamens
to support Her Holiness's operation.
It'll make
things way easier.
It's because they aren't agreeing
to it wholeheartedly.
And,
I don't expect the Elder Hall
to support me either.
Relay my order.
Summon the chiefs of Martial Soul Halls
from all cities and continents
to Martial Soul City.
I have an announcement to make.
Yes, Your Holiness.
This is an item handed to you
by Her Holiness.
The engravings on the Elder Token
represent the Upper Three Clans
of the Seven Great Clans,
Her Holiness, and Martial Soul Hall.
Is she...
(Qian Dao Liu, Head Flamen)
She only retained the crown.
Isn't this obvious enough?
She's too ambitious.
However, we cannot deny the fact
that the Martial Soul Hall
has achieved such glorious results
all thanks to her lofty ambitions.
(Grand Sacred Dragon Master, Elder)
So what?
She no longer has any regards
for Martial Soul Hall.
She forgot
that the Elder Hall was the core
of Martial Soul Hall.
Only we and Head Flamen
are able to dictate the future
of Martial Soul Hall.
If we can let her manage
the Martial Soul Hall,
we can make her step down
from her throne.
That was possible 20 years ago.
But now,
I'm not sure about that.
She's recruiting plenty of soul masters
and accumulating her forces in secret.
Her forces have spread across
the continents.
She's no longer someone
we can deal with easily.
It's been many years.
She never gave up on her plan.
However, if she succeeds,
it'll be even harder for the Elder Hall
to keep her in check.
It doesn't matter.
Once the chosen one appears,
she'll naturally be constrained.
Could it be
that you've received a prophecy
from the divine oracle?
I believe
that my expectations
will not be in vain.
(The Xuan Tian Records are right.)
(The Ice Fire Mouth Spring)
(is indeed a Treasure.)
(My soul power has received)
(a tremendous boost
after just one night.)
(I've already exceeded Level 59.)
Father.
Look.
It's only been one night.
However, your mother's body
is already twice its original size.
Father,
you're poisoned.
Poison fills the air due
to the Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
I thought you would be fine
after consuming Dragon Leaf
since you had
a huge amount of soul power.
I never expected...
I'm fine.
Father,
please calm down and regulate your qi.
I'll neutralize your poison.
How could this be?
Father,
you mustn't stay here.
I'll take you somewhere else
and neutralize your poison.
No.
I promised Yin
that I wouldn't leave her again
when I see her.
But it'll be too late if the poison
seeps into your heart meridians.
With my cultivation,
such poison is nothing to me.
What about this?
You should consume these two Dragon Leaves
and regulate your body.
I'll go and concoct a pill.
You won't be affected
by the air here upon consuming it.
Don't waste your cultivation on me.
Your father isn't that fragile.
Father, there's no need
to worry about me.
I could neutralize the poison
crafted by Grand Venom Master.
I'm sure I can neutralize yours as well.
And,
I can only leave you guys in peace
if you can keep Mother company
in a healthy state.
Father,
you have to promise me this
for Mother's sake.
San,
come here.
What are you doing?
Is this the so-called "pill"
you mentioned?
Father, you don't need
to worry about me.
Did you forget?
The soul bone skill
that Mother had left behind for me
has regenerative properties.
This kind of minor wound
is nothing to me.
That doesn't mean
you can mutilate yourself!
You shouldn't do it
even if it's for my sake
or your mother's sake!
I'm not trying to act tough
because of my soul bone skill.
I only wish for you
to stay by Mother's side healthily.
I've consumed
the Octa Dark Frost
and the Fiery Soft Apricot.
These two herbs are highly toxic.
Your poison can only be neutralized
if you consume
a pill made from
the catalyst using my heart's blood.
The pill is completed.
Please let me
fulfill my filial duties.
This is the map to Haotian Sect.
Depart immediately.
Your aunt
should be waiting for you
back at the sect.
Your soul power should reach
Level 60 soon.
Once you're done
with the sect's affairs,
you can head to Xingdou Forest
and look for Wu.
She should be entering
her mature phase soon.
People won't be able to recognize her
as long as she puts on a disguise.
Yes, Father.
I will remember that.
You know that I have
high expectations of you.
But you better remember this.
You're the only son
in our family.
Remember to prioritize your safety.
Father, Mother,
please don't worry about me.
I know what to do.
All right now.
Go and do the things
you're supposed to do.
Don't worry about me.
Your mother is here with me.
This place is my best refuge.
Go now.
Father,
Mother,
please take care.
Daming, Wu is...
Be quiet.
(Wu,)
(the things you've been
experiencing all this while,)
(I'm able to experience them too.)
Enough! Don't do it again!
Enough!
(Don't be afraid.)
(I'm here.)
San?
Wu!
It's time to wake up.
San, please save my mother!
She will die!
The Martial Soul Hall will kill her!
Why can't I save her?
Wu,
she has already passed away.
There's no way to change the past
even if you dwell
on it.
We have to look forward.
Look forward?
Wu.
Come with me,
okay?
No.
I cannot leave this place.
I'll go through the same experience
over and over again.
When I open my eyes, Mother will...
♪You will understand♪
♪If I love you♪
Wait, San.
If there's no way to exit this place,
how did you manage to come in, then?
Are you here to rescue me?
I cannot rescue you.
You were doing everything
you could to rescue yourself.
You caused an opening to appear,
allowing me to enter this place.
Wu,
let go of the past.
Move forward.
Live on.
Create your empire
using your mother's body.
Mother.
♪If I love you♪
♪If I need you♪
Okay.
Let's go.
♪You will understand♪
♪If I love you♪
♪Your heartbeat resonates in my heart♪
♪Once you cry, wind starts blowing♪
♪In my world♪
♪Memories will ignite like sparks♪
♪Igniting the corner you existed in♪
Wu actually succeeded!
♪If I love you♪
(Congratulations,)
(Wu.)
(You've conquered another challenge.)
(I need to prepare a gift for you.)
(I can't just see you)
(empty-handed, right?)
♪Ending the despair of suffering♪
♪Justice runs deep in our veins♪
♪The humble but powerful♪
♪Will break open the world of darkness♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪Consumed and engulfed by fate♪
♪The flame within burns
with unwavering passion♪
♪The broken darkness♪
♪Will eventually break into daylight♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪