♪Ending the despair of suffering♪
♪Justice runs deep in our veins♪
♪The humble but powerful♪
♪Will break open the world of darkness♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over destiny♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪
=The Land of Warriors=
(Adapted from
Tangjia Sanshao's novel "Soul Land")
=Episode 7=
- Kill him!
You knocked him out?
What are you doing?
Just kill him!
Don't you know the rules?
This isn't child's play.
Kill him!
- Kill him!
(Do not drink the Netherland Shot
when entering the city.)
(Abstain from killing strangers
in the arena.)
(This Haotian Sect disciple)
(is quite the extraordinaire.)
My great king.
Looks like this new warrior
who's come to the Netherworld City
has a kind heart.
He won't be for long.
Will you continue fighting?
(He is being controlled.)
- Kill him!
- Good!
- That's right!
There's one more alive.
- Kill him!
Please, don't kill me.
I'm begging you, don't kill me.
All nine must die
for you to be named the winner.
The state he is in now
is no different from a dead man.
According to the rules,
they must be truly dead.
If he doesn't die
and leaves that door,
The Netherworld King
will sentence you to death.
Please...
That should've been the way.
Yeah.
Congratulations to No. 9528 for winning.
- Nice!
- Good!
You should've just killed him.
Good work.
Good!
He is really skilled.
- Kill him!
The third soul skill, teleportation.
Stop it. You're stepping out of line.
Wu.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's alright. Again.
No, you almost got hurt.
I feel like I'm about to break through
the level 50 bottleneck.
The normal training is no longer
of much use to me.
Thank goodness for Erming.
He used his gravity control field
to pressure me.
That helped me
to concentrate my soul power.
It's the push I need
to finally reach level 50.
But...
San.
(I don't know what you've been through,)
(nor what I could do for you.)
But whenever I was powerless,
I would think of a children's song
my mother used to sing
for me in the past.
♪If you're afraid♪
♪Look up at the stars♪
♪The stars shine bright♪
♪For they're calling out your name♪
♪If you're afraid♪
♪Look up at the stars♪
♪The stars shine bright♪
♪For they're calling out your name♪
Your Majesty.
Evildoers move in the darkness of night.
So,
I propose a curfew.
When night falls, all soul masters
are forbidden from going out.
If there's a need, five or more people
are required to travel.
Apart from that,
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Clan
and Qibao Amber Sect
will send their disciples
to go to the other sects
to provide one-on-one assistance.
That's a good plan.
But, do Chief Ning and
the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Clan
agree to cooperate?
It will be done.
(Yu Tianheng,
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Clan)
I will write a letter
to inform our chief.
Come on, welcome.
Here. You have to try this.
Here.
Strawberries?
And tofu?
Uncle, can this be delicious?
You bet.
Listen.
Your Aunt Erlong's cooking skills
are second to none.
Only she would be able to create
such a delicious dish
using strawberries and mapo tofu.
Go on and try it.
I'll have you know.
This is my special recipe.
It's your uncle's favorite.
You won't find it anywhere else.
You're lucky to be able to eat it today.
So make sure you eat a lot.
Anyway,
how is your grandfather?
He's good.
Sometimes,
he'd go and sit in your room
and no one's allowed to disturb him.
Uncle,
when this matter is resolved,
perhaps you and Aunt
could go back and visit.
I am a disgrace of the family.
If I go back, it will only put
your grandfather in a difficult position.
I know he misses me.
But that doesn't mean
he'd want me to go back.
I don't get it.
Your martial soul mutated as it evolved
and turned into Luo Sanpao.
It wasn't your fault.
Why were you kicked out of the sect?
Tianheng,
move your chopsticks.
Don't be shy.
Eat more.
It's fine if you don't want to tell me.
But the Blue Lightning
Tyrant Dragon Clan is your home.
Nothing wrong in going home, right?
I no longer had a home
when I was kicked out.
Tianheng.
Come on.
Eat more and talk less.
Eat.
Okay.
Is it good?
Yes.
Oh, right.
Grandfather asked me to give this
to you before I left.
Isn't this the clan's mugwort cake?
Xiaogang,
I remember
this used to be your favorite.
Excuse me for a minute.
You two eat.
I've disappointed you.
(Young Yu Xiaogang)
Sorry for embarrassing you.
Please take care of yourself
when I'm gone.
Take these.
It's your favorite snack.
Leaving home,
it'd be hard to find these again.
Xiaogang,
the old grandmaster's
intention is clear.
It's about time you return.
Not yet.
In this world,
no son wouldn't want
to make his father proud.
Same goes for me.
My martial soul
shamed him.
Perhaps my martial soul's
accomplishments
could make up for its flaw.
Do you mean...
The day San and the others
stand at the pinnacle
of the continent's masters,
the people would see
that my beliefs on the martial soul
are not unfounded.
When that happens,
that would be the day I return to
the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Clan.
Showing mercy to the opponent
is being cruel to yourself.
Mubai, Zhuqing, what do you think?
I agree.
The ancestral teachings taught us
that kindness without principles
shows ignorance toward evil.
I will take it to heart
and not forget the limits for mercy.
Principles and limits are clearly
written in the ancestral teachings.
Do you abide by them?
- We dare not disobey.
Showing the slightest bit of kindness
could very well
put yourself in an unfavorable position.
It's the survival of the fittest.
Have I not taught you?
I understand.
I don't think you do!
The one who lives
is the one who gets to rule.
What are you two waiting for?
I thought you guys have left Xingluo.
We were too naive.
We though we could hide the truth,
but we failed to escape Father's grasp.
Do we have any other choice right now?
The ancestral system is not a knife,
but it's forced us
to turn against one another.
See?
The person you saved could very well
betray you.
The ancestral system exists
to prevent a backstab.
What are you people doing?
Father,
I do not regret what I did.
If I could choose one more time,
I still would not kill my brethren.
Insolence!
A benevolent person
will never assume the seat of the king.
Real power
is not annihilating others.
It's to become indestructible,
able to not only protect yourself
but also other people.
Your Majesty,
I solemnly vow
to reach level 60 before I turn 25.
If I succeed, I implore you to let
Zhu Zhuyun and Dai Weisi go.
You should ask
your father, Duke Lingmao,
how long it took him to reach level 60.
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
They don't know
what they're talking about.
What if I manage to do it?
There is no way.
Father,
I too promise you.
I will reach level 60
together with Zhuqing.
We'll become unprecedented warriors
of Xingluo.
Please spare their lives.
Your Majesty.
Are you bargaining with me?
I wouldn't dare.
But if we succeed,
we will become the pride
of Xingluo Empire.
And Xingluo will look down
on the entire continent.
The Martial Soul Hall is unhinged.
And Tiandou has its sight
set on Xingluo.
For Xingluo's future,
we will do everything we can
to become stronger.
I dare ask Your Majesty
to spare them when the time comes.
You can speak to me again
when you actually reach level 60.
Rongrong,
are you angry with me?
Yes.
I'm angry because
you put yourself in harm's way.
Don't ever step in front of me again.
It didn't do any good anyway.
I wasn't able to protect you.
Ao,
you're an amazing support soul master.
You don't have to console me.
This isn't consoling.
If the war soul master
hadn't shown up today,
things could've ended terribly.
That's not true.
Ao.
I have a weird feeling
about what happened today.
The two soul masters who attacked us
clearly knew about our backgrounds.
And that war soul master
named Wang Zheng.
He showed up just at the right time.
Rongrong, the chief asked for you
and Ao to greet guests in the study.
I'm tired and would like to rest.
The chief said it's an important guest,
so it's imperative
that you two be there.
What important guest?
What does it have to do with me?
Okay.
We will be there.
Shouldn't you be resting?
I'm fine. It's not hurting.
The chief never invited me
to the study before.
Who knows I'm in for something good?
Father, we're here.
Come over, Rongrong.
Let me introduce you.
You.
So you are Ms. Rongrong.
You two know each other?
Ao and I were in trouble today.
He was the one who saved us.
I see.
That means
I should properly thank you.
They are not very good at offense.
Thank goodness you got here in time.
You're too kind, sir.
Rongrong should really thank you.
Anyway, Rongrong,
Wang Zheng is
Grand Bone Master's nephew.
He is the most outstanding disciple
among the younger generation.
You flatter me, Mr. Ning.
Not at all.
Please, sit.
Ms. Rongrong, take a seat.
Ao,
you too.
Rongrong,
didn't I tell you
to properly thank the young master?
Thank you for your help today.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
It was nothing, really.
I happened to pass by
and stepped in to help.
I guess we share
an affinity, Ms. Rongrong.
Sure we do.
Tiandou City is massive,
and yet you happened to show up
right when Ao and I were in trouble.
I don't suppose I accrued the good luck
in my previous life?
Two youngsters of similar age,
brought together serendipitously.
There could be good things in store.
Indeed, I am five years older than Rongrong.
My Bazi is in the Shen branch,
of the Fire element.
I wonder what Rongrong's Bazi is.
I feel like we are quite a good match.
Really?
I don't think so.
The two ruffians today seemed ruthless,
but they didn't go overboard.
It looked precarious,
but none of the moves were fatal.
Don't you find it odd?
Father,
I am not feeling well
and can't stand it any longer.
I am going to rest.
Rongrong,
we have a guest here.
Mind your manners.
It's alright, Mr. Ning.
Rongrong must have gotten a scare today.
It's better to rest early.
Thank you.
I shall take my leave then.
Let's go, Ao.
You're still up.
Rongrong,
you can be frank with me.
Why don't you go first?
What was that about?
Trying to arrange my marriage?
Wang Zheng has a lot of potential
among the younger masters.
But do you know
what he did today?
I know Wang Zheng's ways.
It's underhanded and deplorable.
Hence why I won't force you to continue
to keep in contact.
Why did you invite him if you knew?
You even asked Ao to be there.
Were you purposely
trying to embarrass him?
I did not intend to embarrass anyone,
nor deliberately oppose anything.
I just wanted you two to see the truth.
Wang Zheng today could be taken
as a mock obstacle
for you and Ao.
But it represents a very real future
you two must face.
After what happened today,
you should know better.
As a support soul master,
your offensive skills
are no match for a war soul master.
We have secret weapons.
We have the means to protect ourselves.
If Wang Zheng hadn't done his homework
and sussed out our background,
Ao has the ability to fly.
He couldn't have so easily subdued us.
What if his ability was blocked
and you used up your secret weapons?
No matter how strong the weapons are,
they cannot beat physically
possessing fighting power.
The marriage
can be put aside for now.
But Rongrong,
do you remember
the sect's rule?
The spouse of a direct sect disciple
has to be a war soul master.
Master Gurong.
But when I was in danger today,
Ao stepped in to protect me.
Based on this one sacrificial act alone,
tell me which war soul master
is better than him?
You took Ao in as a personal disciple.
I thought...
I accepted him as a private disciple
because he possesses the talent.
But Ao won't be able to change the fact
that as a support soul master,
his fighting power is not as strong.
He is destined
never to be my son-in-law.
Neither of you has the ability
to protect yourself without help.
So I have to make the choice for you
to ensure not just your future safety,
but Ao's too.
Over the centuries, the Qibao Amber Sect
is considered on equal footing
with Haotian Sect
and Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Clan
despite us following the support branch.
That's because we've always collaborated
with the war soul masters.
For centuries?
Despite centuries gone,
no one has been able
to reach Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
That... That's also
to support the war soul master.
There's Ao.
He's more talented than me.
Today,
I had to be the bad person
and embarrassed Ao.
I know you and him
share deep affection for each other.
But...
But Rongrong,
you are Qibao Amber Sect's successor.
You have the duty
to protect the sect.
Take this.
This
will be useful for treating your wounds.
Thank you.
But I care about now
is not these skin-deep wounds.
Do you know why Qibao Amber Sect
has been able to stay away
from outside influences?
It's because of me
and the Grand Sword Master.
As war soul masters,
we have to work in tandem
with support branch soul masters
to ensure that Qibao Amber Sect
has no interference
from the outside world.
I will do everything I can
to protect Rongrong
and Qibao Amber Sect.
If the outcome is unsatisfactory,
what's the use of giving it your all?
I will use 10 percent of my power
and not use my martial soul.
Do as you see fit.
Oscar, you are a talented person.
I know your feelings
for Rongrong are sincere.
As a support branch soul master,
your innate talent is much greater
than my nephew
who is a attack branch soul master.
But right now, he's the one
who can protect Rongrong.
Not you.
I can do it!
If you truly love Rongrong,
I doubt you'd want her
to get hurt, do you?
I get it.
Thank you for your advice.
(If I don't become stronger,)
(I have no right
to stay by Rongrong's side.)
You are dead.
You can't hurt me.
My lady.
Enter.
My lady, a group of the soul masters
among the entourage
sent to Xingdou Forest
encountered beast-eating flowers.
They were almost wiped out.
Give their families compensation.
In the future, there's no need
to bother me
with such matters.
Yes, my lady.
One soul master escaped.
They claimed to have seen
the 100,000-year-old soul beast.
However,
it got away.
Send more men.
Yes, my lady.
This is the Supreme's order.
Capture the 100,000 year-old
soft-boned rabbit alive.
Yes, sir!
Set out!
The third soul technique.
Teleportation.
Wu,
you're improving so quickly.
With the help of your gravity field, my soul power
has become more concentrated.
Erming,
don't hurt it.
How did you get here?
The way is full of fierce beasts.
It's dangerous to come here.
This is me.
Where did you find this?
Did you come looking for me on purpose?
It previously helped me locate the traps
the Martial Soul Hall set up.
It must have a reason
for coming.
I'll go take a look.
Looks like Bi Bi Dong won't quit
if she doesn't capture me.
Wu,
I'll go and teach them a lesson.
No, Erming.
Although they can't take you on even in a group,
if a fight breaks out now,
it will surely cause a commotion
within Xingdou Forest
and make other soul beasts feel uneasy.
Got it, Wu.
I'll do as you say.
(San,)
(what should I do?)
No. 9528, 41 wins.
- Nice one!
- Great!
No. 9528, 65 wins!
Good!
No. 9528, 79 wins!
Great!
(Aside from Tang San,)
(you are the most talented
soul master I've come across.)
No. 9528's winning streak
has caught up to that
of the Emissary of Hell's.
I heard
some people are secretly calling him
King Asura.
People are scared to meet him
in the Hell's Training Ground.
However many are scared of him,
means they are as many
who wish him dead.
Looks like you want him
out of the picture.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have matched him
against a level 80 Great Soul Master.
King Asura,
you may begin your performance.
♪The fleeting dream of life
is easily shattered♪
♪So why not face it boldly,
just this once♪
♪Fierce storms and raging thunder♪
♪Burn me, yet refine my determination♪
♪No matter how battered,
I smile and refuse to retreat♪
♪A so-called hero, covered in dust♪
♪Scarred and worn♪
♪Can still sever the cycle of fate♪
- Kill him!
You want to suck my soul power dry?
Dream on.
(Haotian Sect Random Air!)
All things come together!
That concludes the match.
No. 9528,
95 wins.
(When he used the Haotian Hammer,)
(he was even stronger than Tang San.)
(With such formidable power,)
(he will surely break 100 wins.)
(I should plan ahead.)
He... He won again.
Look, he's injured.
I never want to meet him
in Hell's Training Ground.
Don't let him onto the Ground again.
We should kill him right now.
Kill him!
King... King Asura.
You did not disappoint.
(Only when you're at the brink of death)
(will you be able to obtain)
(the power to turn the tide.)
(This power)
(is hard-won)
(and extremely risky.)
(Mastering it)
(is a true test of one's will.)
Father,
I will not let you down.
He's come.
Anyone who successfully escapes
Hell's Road
is free to leave
and enter Netherworld City.
No one can stop him.
That King Asura...
I mean, 9528.
What do you plan to do with him?
He and the girl from Martial Soul Hall
are indeed troublesome.
I'll have to think about it.
(It's not just the Netherland Shot.)
(Even the air here)
(causes confusion in people.)
(Who knows how much the pellet I made)
(could withstand the poison.)
What's the matter?
What's happened?
San is in a lot of pain right now.
That's his own problem.
You are at the bottleneck
of reaching level 50.
Focus on transforming the soul ring.
If you help him now,
who's going to help you?
The Martial Soul Hall
won't give you any more time.
I know what I'm doing.
Between us,
if one party needs the other,
the other
would not sit idly by.
Wu...
♪Sprinkling it on the starry forest
and grassy fields♪
♪Your image is etched in my heart♪
♪No matter where we go♪
♪If fate stirs up waves♪
(Soul ring conversion
is not complicated.)
(But one must remain calm
and clear-minded.)
(San,)
(remember.)
(Only when you're safe)
(can I be at ease.)
♪For you, I renounce my dreams♪
♪With unwavering love
and profound devotion♪
♪I'll use a lifetime of courage♪
Wu.
♪Enduring immense suffering
does not matter♪
♪I'll face endless suffering
without regret♪
♪Even if I turn into drifting dust♪
♪I must♪
♪Run into your arms♪
♪Hair like clouds,
sideburns delicate as cicada wings♪
♪Combing through a lifetime
of entwined moments♪
♪How I wish,
in all our joys and sorrows♪
♪You'd be by my side♪
♪The promises made
will not be forgotten♪
♪The martial soul burns with hope♪
Wu.
♪Holding your hand♪
Thank you.
♪For you, I renounce my dreams♪
♪With unwavering love
and profound devotion♪
♪Willing to spend a lifetime of courage♪
I will begin the level 50
soul ring conversion immediately.
I can only stop the calamity
brought upon by the Martial Soul Hall
if I leave Xingdou Forest.
♪To descend into eternal depths
without regret♪
San,
when I reach level 60,
I will go to you.
♪Running into your embrace♪
♪Ending the despair of suffering♪
♪Justice runs deep in our veins♪
♪The humble but powerful♪
♪Will break open the world of darkness♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪Consumed and engulfed by fate♪
♪The flame within burns
with unwavering passion♪
♪The broken darkness♪
♪Will eventually break into daylight♪
♪Engraving the words of good and evil♪
♪Into the pages of history♪
♪The remains of courage
on the shoulders♪
♪Still shine with light♪
♪Burn♪
♪The hidden and mysterious soul♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪
♪Take on the future♪
♪And triumph over fate♪
♪Together, we forge a new era♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Protecting the light of justice♪
♪With unwavering resolve,
marching forward without fear♪
♪The only me who stands guard♪
♪Firm, tenacious, and resolute♪
♪The me who chases the light♪
♪Firmly believing
that justice will never fall♪