=The Land of Warriors=
(Adapted from Tangjia Sanshao's novel
"Soul Land")
=Episode 32=
♪The wind sways,
trembling the moonlight♪
♪Spreading over the Xingdou forest♪
♪Your image imprinted on my heart♪
♪No matter where I go♪
San.
Wu.
You two can die together!
Wu, let go!
You won't survive her Light Slash!
♪For you, I renounce my dreams♪
Wu,
are you alright?
Don't worry.
I'm wearing the Peerless Flexible Armor.
Good.
You survived a hit from my Sacred Blade?
You want to kill him?
You'll have to get through me first.
No, Wu!
Come back!
The realm is broken.
That means you're weakened.
San.
Wu.
Young Master!
Chief,
sorry we're late.
It's all good.
Retreat.
Old Rhino.
Wu.
This time, it's not a soul skill.
Wu,
are you really back?
(I'm alright.)
(I'm just exhausted)
(and need to sleep.)
Wu...
Did Wu's consciousness and body
manifested into one?
How is she now?
She told me
she needed to sleep.
She said not to worry.
Did you all receive
the clan's signal I sent?
Yes.
(Tang Clan)
We bumped into Oscar and Prince Xue Beng
on the way here.
We learned of your predicament
and proceeded to enter by force.
Old White Bird led the disciples
in blocking the Imperial Guards.
That allowed us to get to you.
Go on the offensive immediately.
Back to the academy!
I never thought you'd hunt me down.
But as the commander,
infiltrating the back-line
isn't the wisest decision.
If I could get through your defenses,
I'd be able to capture you alive.
A battle between two armies
to kill the commander
and capture its flag.
Without its leader,
the Tiandou Soul Master Legion
will crumble without a fight.
My brother and I
are pleased to entertain you.
To be able to capture Tiandou's
Imperial Chaplain and Chief Ning alive,
I suppose the outcome
of this fight is set.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Xiaogang!
Farting like thunder.
Blasting Luo Sanpao!
Xieyue!
Oh no.
Their Martial Soul Fusion Skill
is much stronger than before.
Is this your martial soul?
It's no wonder
why you are the Blue Lightning
Tyrant Dragon Clan's disgrace.
What a joke indeed.
Chief Ning,
assist me!
Qibao, reinforced with Amber!
Grandmaster!
Grandmaster.
Such a weakling.
Alright.
I guess I'll give you a swift ending.
Why bother with
this meaningless struggle?
You could surrender.
Take the Tiandou Soul Master Legion
and abdicate to the Martial Soul Hall.
I'd be willing to spare your lives.
On the battlefield, you die fighting.
There's no pleading for mercy.
The Tiandou Soul Master Legion
will never surrender even if
only one person remains.
Then go ahead and perish.
Xiaogang!
Xiaogang, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Chief Ning.
Full Moon.
Sun and Moon shine golden!
Xue Qinghe.
No, I should call him Qian Renxue.
He's been defeated.
Also, the Martial Soul Hall army
is surrounded by
the Tang Clan's five schools.
If you wish to continue,
I'll be obliged.
No.
There's no way!
Grandpa Chrysanthemum!
Grandpa Ghost!
Grandpa Ghost.
My Holiness,
we're cornered.
We should retreat.
Retreat.
Mr. Yu!
Father.
Mr. Yu.
Xiaogang.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
His Majesty has been brought
to Flander's study.
Xiaogang.
We won.
We failed.
The Tiandou Soul Master Legion,
under the Yu Xiaogang's leadership,
is much stronger than anticipated.
Plus, they have support
from Qibao Amber Sect and Tang Clan.
Our attempt to suppress them failed.
Tang Clan.
Tang San recruited
the four single attribute tribes
of Haotian Sect
have merged into Tang Clan.
A single blunder.
We didn't expect
a variable like Tang San.
At last, it led to failure.
Young Master,
we still have control over the palace.
Although they managed
to rescue Emperor Xue Ye,
he is gravely poisoned.
His death is imminent.
We only need to announce
that Xue Beng assassinated the emperor.
Once we take over the throne,
we can then deal with those people.
We failed to eliminate
the Tiandou Soul Master Legion.
I could've reassured the officials
as the Crown Prince
and stabilize the situation.
But now that I've lost Xue Ye
and Xue Beng,
I no longer have an edge.
Xue Ye may be at the brink of death,
but so long as they find a way
to awaken him briefly,
he'd be able to leave a will.
Then I won't be able
to gain the throne by force.
Young Master,
does that mean we're giving up?
Not stopping when you have to
will only cause more trouble.
Tang San,
we shall meet again.
How is it?
This poison is known
as the Seven-colored Poison.
Based on the pellet the chief gave me,
I've been able to decipher
six of the poisons.
This needle has absorbed the poison
in His Majesty's blood.
With this,
I'll be able
to ascertain the last remaining poison.
However,
His Majesty is barely
clinging on to life.
I think someone must have used a drug
to keep His Majesty alive
to lure Xue Beng out.
If I'm unable to come up an antidote
in the next 24 hours,
I'm afraid not even God
could save His Majesty.
Senior Yang...
I will do my best.
Your Highness.
Your Highness?
Bone Erosion Poison.
Who gave you this poison?
The culprit
is Qian Renxue's
trusted imperial physician, Yang.
Father's poison is his creation.
Physician Yang?
Where is he?
When I rescued Father,
I took him too.
He's being held
in the academy's firewood room.
No matter how much I press him,
he refused to hand over the antidote.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I can get rid of the poison for you.
So it is you.
Big brother.
Long time no see.
Yang Wushuang.
You traitorous rat working
for the Martial Soul Hall!
How could you use Tribe of Destruction's
banned drug on the Emperor?
Because I want
the Tribe of Destruction
to be buried alongside me.
Once Xue Qinghe succeeds,
they'd think I was with Xue Beng
and sentenced to death together.
Is poisoning the Emperor to death
good enough a reason?
You...
You want to kill me?
Go ahead.
Did you forget, brother?
Back then, when Tribe of Destruction
was attacked by the Martial Soul Hall,
you left me behind
to protect the tribespeople.
As a result,
I was taken by the Martial Soul Hall.
I should've died then.
But I somehow managed to survive.
Take a guess.
Guess what I've had to endure.
You were abandoned by your people.
You're about to die.
Will you still not tell us
where Haotian Sect is?
Only big brother knows
where the sect is located.
I've never been there.
Quite the stubborn guy.
Guess you're asking to try
my collection of trinkets.
Spit it out!
Clean him up and tend to his wounds.
I have use for him.
(Since then,)
I made a vow to myself.
I will live again.
And I'll do whatever it takes
to destroy the Tribe of Destruction.
The day Emperor Xue Ye dies
is the day I reveal
my identity as a member of the Tribe.
What made you become like this?
The men of my tribe
are people with heart.
If I had been the one taken that day,
I would've felt relieved.
You didn't abandon the tribespeople
in order to save me.
That's how you and I differ.
If it were me,
I would never leave you behind.
Because...
you are my most cherished big brother.
Wushuang.
Enough.
You're here
because you want
the antidote
for the Seven-colored Poison.
You can forget about it.
I live in humiliation,
all for the sake
of this one day.
Xue Qinghe may have failed,
but with Xue Beng's smarts,
he would've likely guessed
our relationship.
Once the Emperor is dead,
the Tribe of Destruction
will go down with him.
My days are numbered.
But to be able to see your face again
before I die
is well worth it.
Everything is worthwhile.
You are my younger brother.
No one knows you better than I do.
You cultivate poison with your own body.
Your blood must be the seventh poison used
to make the Seven-colored Poison.
And thus it has to be the antidote.
He can't save him.
He... He has to die.
I will not only save him,
I will save you too.
I'm beyond saving.
And there's no need to.
Even if the poison
has reached your bone marrow,
I will still try my best to save you.
All these years...
you must have suffered.
If the Emperor wants accountability,
I will bear it for you.
This time,
big brother
isn't going to give you up again.
Brother.
This time...
can you...
can you
take me back home?
Brother,
go on
and take my blood.
Wushuang!
Sorry I let you down.
(Wu.)
(You've been asleep for a long time.)
(Are you not going to wake up?)
(You said you're alright.)
(You weren't lying to me, were you?)
(Please,)
(can you quiet down?)
(I just want to sleep in peace.)
Wu.
You're up?
Where are you?
You're too noisy,
how could I not wake up?
But I wasn't talking.
You were calling out
for me in your mind.
Did you forget?
This is your Spiritual Sea.
I'm sorry.
No, stop.
My body is really weak right now.
If you touch me,
it will disintegrate.
Did Qian Renxue's attack
damage your consciousness?
Yes.
But don't worry.
I just need to have a good sleep
and I'll recover.
Wu...
Stop.
I know what you're going to say.
Remember what I told you?
Your life is my life now.
I would never allow
Qian Renxue to harm you
and not do anything.
It's because I'm too weak.
Sorry I made you worry.
You're too humble.
This is our tacit understanding.
If you hadn't gone all out and destroyed
Qian Renxue's Angel Domain,
causing him to stumble,
I couldn't have had
the chance to strike.
Qian Renxue, as strong as she is,
wouldn't have guessed
that she'd be fighting
two persons instead of one.
However,
forcing my body and mind to coalesce
was indeed a little hard.
The fight was underwhelming.
Don't worry.
One day,
I'll let you have fight
to your heart's content.
Okay.
We can leave it
for next time.
Now I need to recuperate.
I need to sleep undisturbed.
Would you mind making sure it's quiet
in the Spiritual Sea?
You have my word.
What's the matter?
Let me remind you.
You better stay away
from that Qian Renxue.
I saw the way she looked at you.
There's something there.
Don't act surprised.
My intuition is always right.
Go and self-reflect.
I...
How is it?
Father.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Please rise.
Stand up.
You've done your best.
Thank you, Your Majesty,
for your pardon.
Senior Yang,
how is the treatment
of my father's poison?
I managed
to get rid of the poison.
But His Majesty
had been poisoned for too long.
His body
suffered greatly.
Despite using herbs
coupled with Grand Venom Master's
soul power
to strengthen his foundation,
it is still...
Still, I will only have
three years to live.
Plus, I'll be bed-ridden
for the remaining days.
Is there no other way?
Help me up.
Dugu Bo has told me
about everything.
Chaplain,
what's the legion's casualties?
More than half are dead.
But we managed to cause a huge loss
to the enemy too.
What about Qian Renxue?
Your Majesty, after Qian Renxue led the Martial
Soul Hall's remaining forces
to slaughter Tiandou's palace guards,
she's gone into hiding.
Qian Renxue!
Father.
Your Majesty.
You just recovered.
You need to recuperate.
Tiandou is awaiting your command.
In my current state,
I am not fit to command.
You may all go.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Chief Ning.
You stay.
Go on.
Where is Father?
Rongrong,
His Majesty said
no one should go inside
without his permission.
Why did His Majesty want Father
to stay behind?
Could it be that...
Sorry, I cannot oblige.
Qibao Amber Sect's secret technique
may be able
to temporarily restore your past vigor,
but if you over-exert yourself,
you could very well be...
It will shorten my life further, huh?
So be it.
But before I pass,
I must clear up the mess first.
I can't leave the dilapidation
to Xue Beng.
Right now, my body
cannot bear this huge responsibility.
There is no point in staying alive
for three more years.
So I'm asking you for this favor.
Your Majesty...
As the ruler of the nation,
I was too blind to notice
the enemy in my midst.
The fault lies with me.
Help me quickly recover my strength
by using my remaining life force.
It's the consequence I have to bear.
You...
are the chief of a clan,
as well as a father.
You should understand.
But this method is high risk.
And the process will be painful.
With your current condition,
your body might not make it.
I just want to know,
if I go through with it,
will I
have two years to live?
One year?
Your Majesty.
Once you use the secret technique,
if Your Majesty
could hang on for half a year,
it would already be considered
a miracle.
I suppose this is what it means
to bargain with God.
That's enough.
Do it then.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'm ready.
Congratulations on getting healthy,
Your Majesty.
Congratulations on getting healthy.
I'm glad you're alright, Father.
You may rise.
You are all Tiandou's
accomplished subjects.
Once the matter is settled,
you will surely be rewarded.
Chaplain.
Present.
Gather the other subjects
and the Tiandou Soul Master Legion.
We are returning to the palace.
The Martial Soul Hall
tried to unseat us Tiandou.
First, Qian Renxue was ordered
to annihilate my royal kin.
Then, they sent their soul master legion
to exhaust Tiandou's strength.
Their actions deserve to be punished.
Today, as the ruler of the nation,
I, Xue Ye,
declare war on the Martial Soul Hall
as Tiandou's emperor.
Their wicked plans will not succeed.
Their greed
will be shattered by the iron cavalry
of Tiandou.
Xue Beng,
if I do not survive this,
I hope you'll be able to fulfill
my promise to the people
on my behalf.
I will, Father.
To battle!
To battle! To battle!
You made the wise choice, Young Master.
But,
they managed to get Emperor Xue Ye
back to his old self so soon.
How did they do it?
This only proves
that our enemy is much stronger
than we thought.
So be it.
It's more interesting
when they put up a fight.
The battle has only just begun.
There's one more mystery.
Why do you treat Tang San differently?
He managed to get away this time
due only to luck.
He isn't worthy to be your match.
He...
I have my own reasoning.
Tang San and his friends
could very well become
the Martial Soul Hall's
biggest threats in the future.
Back to Martial Soul City.
Yes, Young Master.
(Tang Clan)
How many were killed?
Thirty.
All disciples that stayed
to protect the clan.
The rest went to support
Tiandou's soul master legion.
They weren't here.
Otherwise...
(Tang San, you win this time.
We shall meet again. Qian Renxue)
Qian Renxue.
I will make you pay with blood.
To ensure the security of the palace,
I have reorganized
the palace inner guards
from a selection
of the legion's elites.
Prince Xue Beng personally picked
the people who will be assisting you.
Everything is in order.
Tang Clan has sent Hall of Agility
members to scout the situation.
They haven't found any signs
of Qian Renxue's subordinates.
I'm guessing they've returned
to Martial Soul City.
After the recent battle,
half of our forces were lost.
But the greater danger lies ahead.
We have to hasten and replenish
the soul master legion's numbers.
Chaplain,
Chief Ning.
I'm assigning this task to you two.
To capture the king,
Tang Clan was ambushed
and suffered casualties.
Tiandou will not forget your sacrifices.
This time, you played a big part
in the battle against Martial Soul Hall.
You showcased your capabilities.
You are certainly a pillar of strength
that Tiandou can rely on.
I fully support your wish
to expand Tang Clan.
Whatever you need,
you can let me know.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I do have a favor to ask.
Speak.
Tang Clan's Hall of Medicine's elder,
Yang Wudi's younger brother,
is Qian Renxue's trusted confidant,
Imperial Physician Yang.
He was working for the Martial Soul Hall
as a result of the grudge
with Haotian Sect
back in the day.
Now, he had died for his sins.
Yang Wudi is willing to pay the price
with his own life.
I'm pleading for Your Majesty's mercy,
to spare his tribespeople.
I don't see that as asking for a favor.
Yang Wushuang carried out the order
to harm me,
whereas Yang Wudi
did his best to save me.
The two brothers' actions
offset any merits.
Now, Yang Wudi is an elder
of Tang Clan.
He still has more to contribute
to the nation.
Consider the matter settled.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
After the recent attack,
things are in chaos.
Everyone,
I ask for your help
in stabilizing the situation.
Especially Tang San.
The challenge from Qian Renxue
means an impending battle for you.
I am waiting for it.
♪The young man's journey
of dreams has begun♪
♪Breaking through the uncharted storms♪
♪The twin martial soul
shapes the destiny ahead♪
♪The power hidden
within the food branch♪
♪Protecting the battlefield of youth♪
♪Waiting for the moment
to shift the tides of fate♪
♪The tempered grows wildly♪
♪Some things can only
be understood through action♪
♪Moving together in perfect harmony♪
♪Together, we push forward
to overcome darkness♪
♪Fighting with mutual support
is unwavering faith in victory♪
♪The confusion and collisions
along the way♪
♪Fighting across the world
because you're by my side♪
♪A new victory will make
a splendid entrance♪
♪Nirvana is the light in the darkness♪
♪Wings soaring in the flames♪
♪Standing shoulder to shoulder
in the arena where we first shine♪
♪A tempered body growing wildly strong♪
♪Some truths need fists to be explained♪
♪The ignorant and arrogant ridicule♪
♪Has never shared a common goal♪
♪Fully supporting
releasing a critical signal♪
♪Though not good
at sharing through words♪
♪My speed is
an unpredictable trajectory♪
♪Change the direction decided by fate♪
♪There is no turning back in this game♪
♪The battle of youth
drawn to the brink of battle♪
♪Marching forward
with dreams blazing like fire♪
♪The tale of blood
and battle scars of heroes♪
♪Earning glory in the face of adversity♪
(No animals were harmed
during the filming)