The Prefect’s Mansion is on fire.
Take me there.
Once Li Zhang was into trouble,
then the people who dressed like
soldiers of the Military Commissioner
set the Prefect’s Mansion on fire.
Jing Yi got poisoned and went crazy
the night he entered the military camp.
I assume Duke Chang is related to it.
Your Highness, it’s datura flower.
Is there something hiding
about General Leng’s illness?
Chu Chu, do you still remember
the two people who tried to
kill Xu Rugui?
Yes.
I remember you said after the autopsy
that they were both soldiers.
Your Highness, why do you mention this?
These people are also soldiers.
Jinli found out
that before we went into
the mountain with Li Zhang,
more than 20 soldiers left the camp
to buy supplies
under Wu Chen’s order.
This is exactly the number of soldiers
who showed up in the Prefect’s Mansion.
But Wu Chen doesn’t have
the power to dispatch troops.
Therefore, it must be someone
very powerful behind this.
What’s more,
from the traces of the scene
in the wood house that day,
except for the Shence Army who
came to kill Xu Rugui,
there was another group of people
who wanted to capture Xu Rugui alive.
Your Highness, why do you think
it’s General Leng who sent people
to arrest Xu Rugui?
It’s just my speculation.
At this point,
if they want Xu Rugui,
it must be for his value
as a bargaining chip
instead of his identity,
I shouldn’t say
these things to bore you.
It’s late. Go to bed.
I want to stay with you.
=The Imperial Coroner=
=Episode 29=
Jinyu, I’ve found out
that it was Hou Bin
who sent those people out
to buy herbs.
They used to be bandits and they were
incorporated into the army.
Take me to him.
This one.
My child... my child...!
Hou Bin!
Hou Bin! Hou Bin!
Get a doctor now!
Yes!
-Hou Bin. Hou Bin!
-My child...
Hang in there.
My child...
Hou Bin! Hou Bin!
Hou Bin!
What happened?
I’m late.
He stabbed himself.
If I had come earlier,
I could have stopped him.
Chu Chu.
Can you find out what he just ate?
There is no food residue in his mouth.
I can’t tell now.
Have you two been guarding here?
Yes, Your Highness.
Has anyone been here
after General Hou came back?
No.
After General Hou came back
from the infirmary,
he has been staying
in the barracks by himself.
The two of us are keeping watch outside.
We never left.
What’s going on here?
General Hou got poisoned.
Poisoned?
Chu Chu.
Examine his body carefully
and find the source of his toxins
as soon as possible.
Your Highness.
General Hou’s belly
has been cut open by himself.
The evidence
may disappear in a while.
Can I perform an autopsy on him now?
Autopsy?
How can you cut him
while his remains are scarcely cold yet?
What are you yelling about?
Don’t you know the military rules?
How dare you obstruct
Commandery Prince An’s investigation?
Get out and take fifty floggings!
Yes.
Hold on.
General Leng, they are not
obstructing the investigation.
No relatives or friends of the deceased
are willing to let anyone perform
an autopsy on the deceased.
But General Hou was murdered.
I promise I will restore his body
after the autopsy.
We’ve known our mistakes.
We are willing to be punished.
Take General Hou to the mortuary first,
then take your punishment.
Yes.
Miss Chu, please.
Hou, how is your injury now?
When did you get injured again?
Just a flesh wound.
It doesn’t matter.
How does it not matter?
Isn’t it your flesh?
It doesn’t matter?
I heard from Wu Chen
that your injury hasn’t healed yet.
You are even having malignant sores.
You don’t even apply the ointment
Doctor Qi gave you on time.
Are you trying to show how tough you are
or are you just stupid?
All right.
You two big men are even
more nagging than my wife.
It doesn’t look like an arrow
made by the Tang armies.
No, this is used by the bandits.
I was young and aggressive
when I just joined the army.
I followed Hou Bin
to suppress the bandits once.
I was eager to make achievements
and I fell for their trick.
Hou Bin got shot by many arrows
on saving me.
This arrow was so close to his heart
that he missed death by an inch.
I wanted to keep this arrow
to remind myself.
But he insisted on keeping it.
He said if I get impulsive again,
he will remind me with it.
Now I get impulsive again,
but he is gone.
General Leng valued him a lot
during the past year.
Last year, the Vice Military Commissioner
stepped down due to illness.
Zhao Jie should have been
promoted by seniority.
But Hou Bin got promoted in the end.
And I found out
it was him who sent those people out
to buy herbs.
Also it was him who took the bandits in.
So I started to suspect him.
Before General Hou died...
My child... my child...!
He seemed to be saying
something about his child.
Do you know what that is about?
He should be talking about
his wife and son.
About three or four years ago,
his wife died in childbirth.
He lost his wife and his son.
He and his wife
loved each other very much.
It hit him quite hard.
Does it have anything
to do with his death?
Maybe it does.
Jinli.
Does General Hou also play dung beetles?
It’s a folk prescription
in the southwest.
Dung beetles in honey
with some vinegar.
It’s for treating malignant sores.
We use it a lot in the army.
Is there anything wrong with it?
General Zhao.
There is blood on your hand.
It’s fine.
I guess I got it from General Zhao
when we were standing together.
Prepare some water. I’ll take a bath.
Yes.
Your Highness.
The new wound on
General Hou’s abdomen was the one
(Autopsy Report)
that he cut from left to right
with his right hand holding a knife.
But that wound
is different from a normal one.
What’s the difference?
Whether it’s cut by others
or by oneself,
that person will feel pain
when his flesh is cut.
And he will dodge
when he feels pain.
The wound will vary in depth.
Especially when you cut yourself.
No matter how tough you are,
you will use less strength
because of the pain.
The wound is deep when you insert the
sword but shallow when you draw it out.
Bur General Hou’s wound is different.
There is almost no change
in the depth of his wound.
As if he couldn’t feel pain.
Yes.
Did he do something else
after he cut open his abdomen,
as if he was looking for
something in his abdomen
and trying to take it out?
Your Highness, how do you know that?
I couldn’t believe it at first.
But I checked it many times.
His viscera are in a mess.
He reached in and pulled them around.
Chu Chu, does General Hou
have malignant sores?
Yes.
There are many marks
of old wounds on his body.
Especially the one
that runs through his chest.
It hasn’t fully healed.
Looks like he relapsed many times.
There are two malignant sores
at his back
around the perforating wound.
It was treated sloppily.
There was a sour smell on the surface
with some fine powder.
I guess he used a folk prescription
in Qianzhou.
The prescription of
dung beetles in honey?
You even know the folk prescription
in the southwest?
You are so good.
It’s just my speculation.
Chu Chu, did the three dead soldiers
also have malignant sores on them?
I can’t tell from the man
who burned himself.
But there are malignant sores on the men
who were drowned and strangled to death.
Did they also use this prescription?
The drowned soldier was submerged.
I can’t tell if he used it.
But the strangled soldier’s wound
is broken.
Obviously he used it.
Your Highness, what’s wrong?
Is there any problem?
No, that’s right.
I know how they were poisoned.
You’d better stay quiet.
Something happened tonight.
No one has time to take care of you.
You are not like
Xiao Jinyu’s people at all.
I did it for your own good.
After everything is over,
I will release you.
You are a rebel!
You know nothing about it.
Did you see that?
My life is coming to an end.
What I went through these troubles for?
I did it all for you,
for the Leng clan!
Bah!
The Leng clan has been guarding
the Southwest for Tang
for generations and we are
brave and loyal.
If it wasn’t for your greed for power,
how would the Emperor grant
a marriage to me and Xiao Jinli?
All these years I’ve been
trying to escape from such a fate.
Now you are saying you did it for me
and for the Leng clan.
I will never believe you.
The Leng clan will never believe you!
You can kill me now,
or after I untie the ropes,
I will kill you by myself
even to be blamed as
the black sheep of our family!
Fine.
I’ll give you what you want!
General Leng!
What are you doing?
Your Highness.
Chu Chu.
Get up.
This is my family affair.
It’s none of your concern.
There is no family affair between us.
Commandery Prince An,
do you need anything?
I didn’t see Leng Yue
and I was a little worried.
I was going to see Wu Chen,
the secretary
in charge of military supplies,
and ask him a few questions.
I passed by
and vaguely heard Leng Yue’s voice.
So I came here to have a look.
Your Highness.
I asked him why he concealed
his illness from the court.
He knocked me out with his hand
and tied me up.
He said he will release me
after everything is over.
Your Highness.
General Leng, it’s your family affair
and it’s about your military business,
I shouldn’t ask too much.
But considering what happened tonight,
to avoid misunderstanding,
I want to ask you one question.
Did you really not
report your illness to the court?
What do you mean?
You may not know
that the Minister of War,
Feng Jie, was murdered
when he arrived in Chang’an.
There was a special volume
of inspection notes missing.
What?
After I learned about your condition,
I asked Jinli about it
and he remembered
that you once talked
to Minister Feng alone
for half a day during his inspection.
That’s right.
I did tell my condition
to Feng Jie on that day.
It concerns
the military power in the Southwest
and the future of the Leng family
after my death.
It also concerns the safety
of the Southwest border in Tang.
I know how important it is.
I’ve discussed with Feng Jie
that I would keep my condition a secret
so as to stabilize the military spirit
and prevent the bandits from
creating a disturbance in the Southwest.
Feng Jie would write down my condition
and present it to His Majesty in person
to come up with a good solution.
I didn’t know Feng Jie died so suddenly
as he arrived in Chang’an.
I didn’t receive any imperial edict.
I thought His Majesty
would appoint a new Minister of War
and that’s why Xue Rucheng
came to Qianzhou.
But he didn’t set foot in my camp.
He just returned to Chang’an like that.
So there were several
mysterious deaths in the camp
when I asked Leng Yue to send you
a letter and greet you.
It was such a coincidence.
No wonder you got suspicious.
Then you sent me a letter
and invite me to investigate the case
to find out if I’m up to other things
and to make sure
Leng Yue is safe, right?
You want me to find out the fact,
but you don’t trust me that much.
So you are not going to
tell me the truth.
But Leng Yue acted impulsively
and had a fight with you.
You had no choice
but to keep her in your barracks
to keep her safe
after everything becomes clear.
Am I right?
You are smart indeed.
General Leng, is the moxa stick yours?
Yes.
I had rheumatism once.
Nothing worked.
The doctor asked me to burn moxa stick
and keep using it.
Although the rheumatism
can’t be totally cured,
at least it can alleviate the pain.
Your Highness,
there is something wrong with the moxie.
What’s wrong?
This moxa is a little darker
than the normal moxa.
And there is a strange smell.
Let me take a look.
There is cinnabar in it.
Cinnabar?
This moxa is mixed with cinnabar.
The burning cinnabar is poisonous.
It’s hard to be noticed
while being mixed in the moxa.
Grandpa, there is a reason
that you became ill.
It’s because of the moxa.
Where did you get the moxa?
Wu Chen.
It’s still warm. He just left.
Soldiers.
Yes.
Pass down my order.
Guard all the entrances and the exits.
Search every corner of the camp.
You must find Wu Chen out.
Yes.
General Leng.
Are you sure that Wu Chen
gave the moxa to you?
Yes.
Are you looking for the evidence
that he tried to kill me?
I’m here to find the evidence
that he poisoned the soldiers.
He poisoned the soldiers?
Did he kill Hou Bin?
I’m afraid he is responsible for
the recent events in the army.
What a bold bastard!
If I get him,
I will skin him alive.
Jinyu.
I’ve found it out.
Feng Li who strangled himself
has someone in his family
who also hanged himself.
Wang Chi, who drowned himself,
has some relatives drowned
in a flood in his hometown.
And General Xu who rushed into the fire,
his old house caught fire
and his mother died in flames.
The three of them
are just like General Hou.
They were away from home when something
happened to their loved ones.
They had been feeling guilty.
Your Highness, this was found
in the ashes of the incense burner.
Show it to me.
Your Highness, this is the powder
made from the seeds of datura flower.
General Leng.
This is what makes
the soldiers in the camp
go crazy for no reason.
Wu Chen used it as a drug enhancer
which can make the victims
see illusions.
These illusions are associated with
the long suppressed painful
experiences of the victims.
As long as the murderer knows enough
about these people’s experiences,
he can guess what kind of illusions
they will see when the poison
starts to work.
Then he can design
the way they kill themselves.
How did he do it?
I thought about it at first
that maybe someone used poison.
We used a lot of methods
to ensure the safety of food
and drinking water in the army.
Where else could he put the poison in?
He mixed the datura flower powder
in the medicine for
treating malignant sores.
(Sterculia lychnophora)
Those who have malignant sores
will be poisoned when they apply it.
Commandery Prince An
and I have checked it.
All the soldiers who have gone crazy
all had malignant sores
and they all used the same prescription
to treat the malignant sore.
But Jing...
But Dog doesn’t have
any malignant sores.
How did he get poisoned?
He doesn’t have malignant sores.
But he touched
the most critical ingredient
for treating malignant sores.
What?
The living dung beetles
raised in the infirmary.
Dung beetles?
Chu Chu and I have
checked the infirmary.
I think Wu Chen
mixed the datura powder
into the baked dung beetle powder
when he counted the crude drugs.
Because the jar of dung beetle powder
was next to the jar of
living dung beetles,
some powder floated into
the jar of the living dung beetles.
Dog accidentally got
some powder on his hand
during the dung beetle race
with the wounded soldiers
without knowing it.
I guess he got excited and then
he just took the water and drank it.
That’s how he got poisoned.
The seeds of datura flower
are hard to get.
There are tight restrictions on
entering and leaving the camp.
I asked Jinli to check the records.
The only person who touched
the jar of dung beetle powder
and is able to
bring the datura flower powder
back to the camp
is Wu Chen in charge of
military supplies.
Your Highness, please check this out.
Your Highness, this is the kind of
moxa used by my grandpa.
The moxa should be
brought here in a whole box.
The moxa sticks
in General Leng’s barracks
can only cover three or four days.
Yes.
These moxa sticks
are not enough to replenish a whole box.
According to Jinli,
those who left to buy supplies
won’t be back in ten days,
which means
Wu Chen didn’t plan to
keep poisoning you.
Did he stop because he knew
we were coming here?
No.
General Leng, I was taking
a bath in my barracks.
Sorry I’m late.
Take your men to search for Wu Chen.
You must find him out
before dawn.
Search for Wu Chen? What’s wrong?
Hurry up!
Yes.
Hold on.
General Zhao, please remind the soldiers
that he might dress up as a soldier
and blend in the search team.
Got it.
All these soldiers
even can’t find a civil official.
Can he fly or go under the ground?
General Leng, one night has been passed.
I think they have searched
all the places in the camp
where he can hide himself.
General Leng,
please order your men
to pay attention to the places
where only the dead can stay.
You mean
Wu Chen is dead?
If he hasn’t escaped from the army,
and he isn’t among the soldiers,
then there is only one possibility left.
General Leng, Commandery Prince An.
We have found Wu Chen.
These two cooks found
Wu Chen’s body in the well
when they went to
draw water this morning.
Has anyone been here before?
I have asked them.
They were searching all night.
Countless people
passed here.
The footprints are messy.
The bottoms of their shoes are the same.
We can’t tell anything.
The deceased male is over 30.
His mouth and eyes are slightly open.
There is a swelling on his abdomen.
There are bruises caused by struggling.
There is foam in his nose and mouth.
(Nasal cavity Oral cavity)
He was drowned.
But his body has been soaked in water,
it’s hard to determine
the exact time of his death.
I assume
he died between one to five a.m.
Between one and five?
That’s when Hou Bin died
and we were searching for him.
Could he jump into the well
in desperation
when we were looking for him?
He might be holding this rope
and hiding in the well.
He didn’t expect that we would
search for him all night.
He lost his strength gradually.
So he fell into the well
and got drowned.
This place is not close to the three
entrances and exits of the camp.
And it’s not on the way
from his barracks to the exit.
Even when he was fleeing from us,
he shouldn’t hide here.
Are you suspecting
that Wu Chen was murdered?
Chu Chu.
Perform a thorough autopsy on him.
Go ahead and do what you need to do.
I’ll sign the approval paper for you.
Okay.
But, Your Highness.
I need something first.
Miss Chu, just tell us what you need.
As long as we have it,
we will give it to you.
Thank you, General Leng.
I need green onion, pepper, salt,
white plum, lees, vinegar.
one garlic mortar and two mats.
Please find an open space
in the camp for me.
I need to dig a two-meter pit
and burn some firewood in the pit.
Are you going to cook?
I want to braise him.
Chu Chu, are you going to eat him?
No, no.
I’m not going to eat him.
Braising him
with my method
can let us know
if he jumped into the well by himself.
General Leng, Chu Chu
is from a family of coroners.
She often uses some unusual
but really useful methods.
I think you should let her try it.
Cooks.
Yes!
Bring the stuff Miss Chu needs.
Yes.
Thank you. General Leng.
Zhao Jie. Jinli.
Yes.
Do whatever Miss Chu says.
Leng Yue, stay here and help Chu Chu.
Okay.
Commandery Prince An.
Can we talk in your room?
General Leng, please.
Please.
(Jiangshan Hall)
You’ve read the memorial of
Commandery Prince An.
The Prefect of Qianzhou, Li Zhang,
has been brought to justice.
But Commandery Prince An thinks
Li Zhang is not the main culprit
behind the illegal minting of coins.
What do you think?
(Memorial)
I think what Commandery Prince An
said is reasonable.
Minister Wang.
What Commandery Prince An
wrote in the memorial,
except for the arrest of Li Zhang,
the evidence of the rest of the events
has all been destroyed.
It can just be his side of story.
How is it reasonable?
Your Majesty, I think
Commandery Prince An
is putting himself off
and fooling you.
Now he went to the camp of
the Military Commissioner of Qianzhou
in the name of investigating the case.
He is meddling in military affairs
and acting beyond his authority.
Minister Han.
When I went to the Southwest,
Commandery Prince An
mentioned this case to me.
The case of illegal minting
of coins is really complicated.
It’s understandable
that Commandery Prince An
couldn’t make it clear for the moment.
Minister Xue, you two
are really interesting.
You are his teacher
and the head of the Ministry of War.
You were ordered to go to the Southwest
to inspect military affairs.
You found out nothing
about the military affairs.
But now you are meddling in the affairs
of the Three Judicial Offices.
Commandery Prince An is the head
There is no end of his investigation
of the illegal minting of coins.
Now he is meddling in
the military affairs of the Southwest.
The both of you acted beyond
your authority.
Does Commandery Prince An
have a bad influence on
his noble teacher
or do you mislead your clever student?
Commandery Prince An only mentioned
a few words about the illegal minting
when we were chatting.
As for why he went to
General Leng’s army,
I believe he will give us
an explanation.
General Leng has always
ruled his army rigorously.
He won’t let others lay a hand on
the military affairs that easily.
You are so interested in the affairs
of the Three Judicial Offices,
then you should bring back
the survived rebels.
But you didn’t bring back
the person you should bring back,
you even lost the person
you shouldn’t bring back.
Commandery Prince An was ordered to
investigate the illegal minting case.
Now it turns out like this.
Shouldn’t he thank his teacher for that?
The illegal minting of coins
has always been a major case.
Commandery Prince An has
the right to act at his discretion,
but he went to the Southwest this time
to look for his father.
He didn’t take much luggage
and many attendants.
Maybe he just needs some help.
Ask the Military Commissioner for help?
What does he want to do?
The Commandery Prince entered the camp
of the Military Commissioner in private.
Minister Xue, you’ve taught
a wonderful student.
Minister Xue is the teacher
of Commandery Prince An.
It’s normal that they
mentioned a few words
about official business
when they were chatting.
But what Minister Han said
is true.
There is no solid evidence
in the memorial.
No matter what,
Li Zhang is still a prefect of a state.
Even he wants to arrest him,
he should have irrefutable proof.
Right now,
Commandery Prince An
couldn’t find out the truth.
So he claimed that there is
someone else behind Li Zhang.
He is smart indeed.
Minister Xue, am I right?
Your Majesty.
Commandery Prince An failed in his task,
made decisions without authorization,
deceived his superior and subordinates,
intervened in military affairs
and acted beyond his authority.
He should be taken back
to Chang’an and be punished.
Minister Jing.
What do you think?
I think
there is another possibility that why
Commandery Prince An only
mentioned his speculation
but not any solid evidence.
It’s not because
there is no real evidence.
Commandery Prince An worries
that some treacherous men
might take the letter away
and it will cause unnecessary troubles.
Commandery Prince An has always been
thoughtful and cautious.
Your Majesty, I think you can
order him to come back first.
After Commandery Prince An
returns to Chang’an,
if there is no real evidence
to prove his speculation
in this memorial,
you can punish him at that time.
Yes, Senior Jing has a point.
Your Majesty, I think
what Senior Jing said is reasonable.
If you are going to punish
Commandery Prince An,
you should punish him
after he returns to Chang’an.
Your Majesty, I also agree with
what Senior Jing said.
All right, let me think about it.
You can leave now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
♪Nothing can♪
♪Stop me♪
♪From missing you♪
♪All the time♪
♪It’s cold at night♪
♪Everything changes in the world♪
♪I have affection for nothing♪
♪But your hug♪
♪Close the eyes♪
♪Meet again♪
♪By your side♪
♪I brush your hair gently♪
♪Life is long but love isn’t♪
♪There’s regret in the world♪
♪Only with you around♪
♪We’ll never lose contact♪
♪The moment♪
♪You smile♪
♪Let me cherish it for good♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I care about my life♪
♪I’m not old yet♪
♪I still love you♪
♪At last I settle down for you♪
♪I can rely on you all my life♪
♪Hope we’ll spend our lives sweetly♪