I’m Chu Chu.
I came to Chang’an to become a coroner,
who can work for the Handsome Judge,
Chief of Six Gates.
(Court of Judicial Review)
Kind Lord Jing helped me to take part
in the Coroner Qualification Test.
(Two Merits Hall)
But I mistook Commandery Prince An
as the testing body
who takes care of all criminal cases.
(Three Judicial Offices)
His Highness is smart and kind.
I think he’s Handsome Judge
that I’m looking for.
But...
He looks very curious about my pendant.
Greetings, Your Highness,
Vice Minister Jing.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Miss,
you must be the coroner
Commandery Prince An picked
in today’s selection test.
Congratulations.
No. No. The result hasn’t come out yet.
I just...
General Zhou,
did His Majesty send you here
for any mission?
Here’s the thing.
(Three Judicial Offices)
When I was patrolling in the Palace,
I picked up a bunch of keys.
I guess some official lost them
when he left the Palace.
I’m then asking in all departments.
General Zhou,
where did you find the keys?
In the corridor outside Xuanzheng Hall.
Don’t bother, then.
Even if you visit
all departments in Chang’an,
no one will claim them.
What do you mean, Vice Minister Jing?
In the way
you’re looking for the owner,
soon all officials will know that
someone lost a bunch of keys.
It’s no problem if they’re normal keys.
If they’re keys
to archives, storerooms or cells,
the owner will be in big trouble.
If I lost the keys,
I would never admit that.
You’re right.
Thank you for your instruction.
I’ll leave you alone.
(Three Judicial Offices)
Qin Luan’s Imperial Armies go
where they heard of anything,
just like dogs.
Don’t they fear to be battered?
Your Highness,
may I
have my pendant back?
Now that it matters so much to you,
keep it carefully.
Don’t leave it to others again.
I see.
(Princess Xiping, Emperor Wenzong’s daughter)
Heng, are you still alive?
Do you know I’m still waiting for you?
=The Imperial Coroner=
=Episode 2=
Come and have a look!
He’s perspicacious.
He punishes evil-doers.
He really looks like the Handsome Judge.
Are you still inspecting me?
By the way,
it’s the ointment to remove blood clots.
My grandfather made it.
It’s very effective.
Apply it.
Thank you.
Don’t bother.
I know
you think coroners bring bad luck.
But this is new.
I haven’t used it before.
It’s not dirty.
What? Regret so soon?
No, no.
You don’t think
what I touched is filthy?
You also touched me, didn’t you?
Angelica and peony
for improving blood circulation.
Ligusticum and cattail
for removing blood clots.
Boswellia for pain relief
and peach kernel for dissolving lumps.
They work for my symptoms.
You can even recognize it?
I know a little.
Is there anything you don’t know?
Who gave you the pendant
you left in the inn?
Why did he ask about my pendant?
I can’t tell anyone else.
You can’t tell me
or you don’t want to tell me?
Come and have a look!
Baked cake.
Hot baked cake!
Baked cake!
Stop.
Jing Yi,
go buy a piece of baked cake.
Come and have a look!
Don’t bother.
I...
I’m not hungry. Don’t buy it.
Hot baked cake.
I’m hungry.
Xiao Jinyu is heading for Yan’s Mansion?
Yes.
Besides Jing Yi,
he also took a female coroner
who took part in the test.
Female coroner?
A girl even wants to be a coroner?
I asked about her.
When she first came to the capital,
she met Jing Yi privately.
She also took part in the test,
for Jing Yi’s sake.
A female coroner?
Make an issue of female...
Sounds like what the Jing Family do.
Not only Jing Yi works for Xiao Jinyu,
but also a female coroner.
Jing Zhi thinks so highly of Xiao Jinyu.
Jing Yi is smart,
but he’s a playboy
who enjoys wealth and honor.
In case of corpses,
he can’t help feeling terrified.
It makes sense
when Jing Zhi plants a female coroner
to spy on Xiao Jinyu.
I failed to figure out who she is.
But I find something fishy.
What is it?
When I saw Xiao Jinyu today,
he was holding a stone pendant.
As soon as he saw me,
he hid it right away.
When he stared at the pendant,
I felt that
he cared a lot about it.
The female coroner said
it was her pendant.
Stone pendant?
What does it look like?
It’s flat,
with carved patterns.
Looks like one of two halves.
It has...
A blue tassel.
Eunuch Qin, you know that?
Did you see it clearly?
I’m sure I did.
Looks like the blue tassel isn’t
from any ordinary family.
I looked at it a few more times
and I was quite impressive.
Why does a female coroner
have the love token
of Princess Xiping and Xiao Heng?
Don’t worry.
I’ll take her back.
Go. Go ahead.
Is Xiao Heng...?
I must send someone to get some intel
from Princess Xiping.
According to the first witness,
when he arrived here,
he found the dead man.
Did the witness move anything
in this place?
He claimed he didn’t.
Come on, Your Highness.
What do you mean claim?
I didn’t!
Lord Jing, you found the dead man?
Yes.
Lord Jing, how did you find him?
I heard the scream.
That night, Yan Ming held a banquet
in the foreyard,
to show off his valuable calligraphy.
Unexpectedly, he didn’t come back
after a long while.
Later, his scream came
from the study.
Then came the scream of a dancing girl.
I rushed here immediately.
As soon as the dancing girl
pushed the door open,
she saw what happened in the study
and slumped on the ground out of fear.
Before she recovered from the shock,
Jing Yi arrived.
So, he was the first
to get into the study
and checked on Yan Ming.
Didn’t the dancing girl or Lord Jing
see the murderer?
Not to mention the murderer,
there wasn’t even a suspect.
Look, here’s much blood.
There must have been blood
on the murderer.
I asked to seal the mansion
for a thorough search immediately.
No one was missing.
No extra men were here, either.
But we found no one
who had blood on him.
Wasn’t it strange?
The bloodstain looks smooth.
I think Yan Ming took the box out
and put it here.
When he was dead,
the calligraphy wasn’t in the box.
Did he take it out
and show it to the murderer?
Where’s the calligraphy now?
Now that
Yan Ming showed it to the murderer
and it’s missing now,
it means the murderer
wanted the calligraphy,
killed Yan Ming
and ran away with it?
I don’t think the murderer
wanted the calligraphy.
How do you know he hid it
in this place?
When something is hidden
among similar things,
people can’t easily see it.
Now that the murderer
didn’t want the calligraphy,
the stain on it didn’t matter.
Why did he hide it?
If he hadn’t hidden it,
would you think
he was a thief who killed Yan Ming
so as to get the calligraphy?
I heard that the calligraphy was missing
after Yan Ming was killed.
Did Commandery Prince An find any clue?
He hasn’t told me about it.
Yan Ming was killed
because of the calligraphy.
It’s not appropriate to say this,
but what a pity
when the calligraphy is missing!
In my humble opinion,
Yan Ming may not be killed
because of the calligraphy.
Then why was he killed?
If the murderer only wanted
to steal the calligraphy,
he didn’t have to kill Yan Ming.
It makes sense.
You checked the crime scene.
What else did you see from the corpse?
You can tell me now, can’t you?
I want a try.
How?
Could you pretend to be the murderer?
Just show me
how you think
the murderer killed Yan Ming.
I’ll show you
how I think Yan Ming died.
All right.
What’s in your hand?
The weapon.
It’s a meter long
and as thick as wheat straw.
Anything wrong?
Someone’s dead!
Help!
What are you doing?
I’m pretending to be Yan Ming.
I’m showing you the calligraphy,
but you hold a weapon.
I’ll certainly yell for help.
You’re right.
I wasn’t thinking
in the murderer’s position.
Let’s try again.
Look.
Something’s wrong.
It doesn’t make sense.
There’s really a hole.
That’s how he protected himself
from Yan Ming’s blood.
In this way,
people without the bloodstain
are also suspectable.
You said something wrong. What’s that?
I mean
there’s no trace of bumping
on Yan Ming’s back.
He shouldn’t have fallen down like this.
But according to the bloodstain,
he did.
Then the murderer held him
before he bumped into the desk,
like you just did.
The murderer killed him.
Would he even worry
if he would be wounded?
Then why did you hold me?
You’re the murderer.
Miss Chu,
if you wanted to be serious,
you didn’t scream
like Yan Ming did.
I don’t know what you heard.
But Yan Ming didn’t scream
before he died.
Why?
Judged from the blood on the ground,
the upper part of his heart was stabbed.
It’s the connection part
between heart and blood vessels.
When it was stabbed immediately,
Yan Ming would be out of breath
because of the huge blood loss.
He couldn’t scream at all.
Jing Yi, are you sure
you heard Yan Ming’s scream?
The murderer screamed?
If so,
the murderer would stop Yan Ming
from bumping into the desk.
Why?
In case he made a noise
and others would notice.
Would you like to try again with me?
Yes.
To fool others,
the murderer faked the crime scene.
Someone’s dead!
What are you doing?
You’re the murderer and Yan Ming,
aren’t you?
There should be a dancing girl.
I would pretend to be her.
It was what happened that night.
Now that you pretend
to be the dancing girl,
don’t you realize
something wrong with her?
What’s wrong with her?
It took her a while to find Yan Ming
after she came.
The was a short interval
between the two screams.
When the murderer screamed,
the dancing girl must have been
in the yard.
No matter how fast the murderer left,
she must have seen him.
But why did she stay and do so much,
instead of leaving immediately?
Yeah.
(Jiangshan Hall)
Your Majesty, I wonder
if I should say something
about Yan Ming’s case.
Go ahead.
Yan Ming is a vice six-rank official,
but he’s at least a minister.
His case has been suspended
for half a month.
After you gave a time limit,
Commandery Prince An
used Yan Ming’s corpse
for the Coroner Test,
instead of solving the case quickly.
He’s absolutely disrespecting you.
He’s so careless and arrogant!
No wonder other officials impeach him.
I shouldn’t have spoilt him.
If he doesn’t find out the murderer
before sunset,
I’ll dismiss him from office!
Did you search
the dancing girl’s body immediately?
I did.
But that wasn’t very necessary.
She wore such a thin dancing dress.
How could she hide
a one-meter-long weapon?
So, she left the weapon here.
It’s the weapon.
He can even find this?
I think the dancing girl learned
from some ventriloquists
in the Dancing Service.
It’s hard to imitate a man’s voice,
but it wasn’t very hard to scream only.
She didn’t hold the weapon
or had the blood on her.
She could have left directly.
Why did she scream twice?
According to her confession,
she wanted to steal something
in the yard
on her way to the latrine.
As checked,
she greeted other dancing girls
who came with her
before she left.
She also met a maid and asked the way.
But she couldn’t be vindicated
with such simple evidence.
She couldn’t assure her safety
unless she made herself the witness.
A girl tricked me?
Wait. What did she steal?
Go catch her in the Dancing Service
and ask her.
She must have run away
after she stole the thing.
You’d better issue a warrant.
What if she’s still there?
Why did Lord Jing leave
through the window?
That’s his bad habit.
You’re awesome, Your Highness.
You’re even smarter
than the Handsome Judge.
Your Highness,
may I still work for you?
You must answer all my questions, then.
All right.
Tell me about your pendant.
Pendant?
Are you...
Are you really not the Handsome Judge?
I’m not.
What does he have to do
with the pendant?
I can’t tell you
unless you’re the Handsome Judge.
Yan Ming’s case isn’t closed yet.
I need you to give evidence
in the court.
You can’t leave Chang’an before that.
And you must come
whenever you’re needed.
Your Highness.
Miss Chu,
is this yours?
I don’t even know where I lost it.
Where did you find it?
You silly girl,
you don’t even know
your package was stolen.
Stolen?
Who stole it?
Just now.
The waiter who asked for the bill.
But he doesn’t look like a thief.
Didn’t you realize
your package smelled like that waiter?
What smell?
The smell of honey locust
and atractylodes
that coroners have.
He’s a waiter in an inn.
He doesn’t use that.
You keep holding the package
in your arms.
It must be very important to you.
When you checked in,
you wouldn’t give it to the waiter.
So, it’s very likely that
he searched your package secretly.
You really know everything.
Wait.
This isn’t my purse.
No. I mean this is my purse.
But the coins are not.
They’re yours, too.
It’s your pay.
Keep them carefully.
So many coins for such a short time?
Isn’t it great to work for you?
What?
Your Highness, please give these coins
back to Lord Jing.
All right.
Send some men to follow her.
Check where she goes
and who she meets.
Yes.
Also,
exchange her own coins.
Amazing whip, Your Grace!
What are you scared of?
You don’t deserve
to be killed by my whip.
I don’t. I don’t!
What are you coming for?
For your information, Your Grace,
these are grapes,
from the Western Regions.
My master asked me to bring them...
Get out!
Your Grace,
my master truly cares for you.
Get out!
Go, go, go.
Go back and tell Qin Luan.
Don’t think I don’t know
he always complains to His Majesty.
How dared he slander
Commandery Prince An!
What does he think he is!
Get out with your grapes!
Yes. Yes, Your Grace.
Get out!
Let’s go. Go.
Be quick!
Leave us.
What happened?
Didn’t I ask you to get some intel
from Princess Xiping?
Look what a mess you’re in!
I got nothing, Master.
Princess Xiping has such a big temper.
Before I finished,
she lashed me!
Master, it doesn’t matter
when I’m aggrieved.
But Master, I work for you.
When she lashed my hips,
she was exactly slapping your face!
What did you say?
Don’t get angry, Master.
I don’t mean that.
What a loser!
Master, you asked me
to ask about the female coroner.
Do you suspect
she has something to do
with Prince Consort Xiao Heng?
Does she have something to do
with Xiao Heng
or does someone else want Xiao Jinyu
to think so?
Anyway,
someone must have seen Xiao Heng
and known where he is.
As long as we know
who the female coroner is,
all problem will be solved.
Master, you care about the pendant.
Does it have a special meaning?
(Princess Xiping’s Mansion)
Your Grace, it takes trouble to blend.
Have some rest.
When did I ever do such a thing?
If my husband comes back someday,
he’ll laugh at me
when he sees me.
Your Grace.
You all want me to believe that
he’s dead.
But in his grave,
there’s nothing but a set of clothes.
I won’t believe he’s dead
until I see his body.
Your Grace, I also wish him
to come back.
But it’s been so many years.
If he were still alive,
why didn’t he come to see you,
considering your deep love?
Stop. I don’t want to listen.
Don’t let my children
know about the cenotaph.
Yes.
Especially Jinyu.
If he knows,
he’ll look for his father,
regardless of anything.
We mustn’t tell my children about it.
He’s handsome,
and kind.
He solves cases,
and wants to hire a female coroner.
The Handsome Judge
-is perspicacious
-Perspicacious
-and kind.
He has an abhorrence of sin
and a handsome appearance
so that people like him at first sight.
Isn’t he the Handsome Judge?
Why doesn’t he admit that?
(Notice)
How is that possible?
Sir.
Sir?
What happened?
Something surprising.
Three Judicial Offices
solved a criminal case
where a man was struck by lightning.
Look, here’s a notice,
telling us how to protect ourselves
from lightening.
Oh my God!
People can even die like that?
Yes. I saw that today.
You saw the lightning?
No.
I mean I helped to solve the case.
I checked the dead man
who was struck by lightning.
You’re a coroner?
What bad luck!
Sir, are you alright?
Why didn’t you watch your steps?
Miss, are you trying to hit me to death?
I’m sorry. Are you alright?
Let me check on you.
Don’t touch me.
Sir, I think you’re hurt.
Let me take you to see a doctor.
It’s kind of you.
Don’t bother, Miss.
I have medicine at home.
I live near here.
Let me get you back home, then.
All right. Thank you.
Come on. Stand up.
Be careful.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
She’s the dancing girl?
Yes.
She ran quickly.
I’ve never been so tired before
when chasing girls.
Take her away.
You’re right again.
She was still practicing dancing
in the Dancing Service.
I lose whenever we make a bet.
How boring!
Others give good things
to beautiful girls.
But everything His Majesty awards me
goes to you.
But you’re wrong about one thing.
What is it?
You said she had stolen something
from Yan Ming.
I searched her residence
in the Dancing Service,
but didn’t find anything.
What exactly did she steal
from Yan Ming?
Besides,
I personally searched her body
that night.
Even her shoes were taken off.
What could she have stolen?
(Year of Jia, Yi, Bing, Ding,
Wu, Ji, Geng, Xin...)
(Year of Renchen)
That’s what she stole.
What?
A volume of book.
Interrogate her and find it out.
She really stole something?
All right, then.
I won’t decline a job
to deal with a beautiful girl.
After interrogating her,
ask the three grave robbers in prison.
According to them,
they know very well
about all nearby grave robbers.
Grave robbers?
Why do you want to ask about them?
Isn’t it Miss Chu’s pendant?
I asked Wu Jiang to borrow it
from my mother.
It’s Princess Xiping’s pendant? Then...
I haven’t seen
my father’s pendant before.
But Chu Chu’s pendant
has the same pattern
and the same tassel.
You think someone robbed
Prince Consort’s grave,
got the pendant out,
and gave it
to a female coroner
so that you would be attracted
and more likely to hire her?
I asked the three grave robbers.
They said that
no one had robbed my father’s grave.
So, she didn’t get this pendant
from his grave.
Do you think
she looks like a spy?
She came from the Southwest.
Prince Consort was also killed
by rebels
in the Southwest.
He might have lost it somewhere
and someone picked it up
before giving it to her.
If this is the truth,
why doesn’t she admit?
Miss, it’s right ahead.
Be careful.
What do you want?
Miss, go with me
and I won’t kill you.
I... I don’t have money.
I’m... I’m ugly, too.
I even eat a lot.
Shut up!
I work for Commandery Prince An!
Stop nagging and give me the pendant!
Pendant?
Give the pendant to me!
Give it to me!
Go!
Miss Chu, shall we go back
to Three Judicial Offices?
All right.
This way, please.
Master, you’re back?
Madam said you wouldn’t have dinner
if you didn’t come back.
Has Jing Yi come back?
He can’t come back very soon.
The Coroner Test was over.
Where has he gone?
According to his servant,
he has gone to the Dancing Service
to catch the murderer
who killed Yan Ming.
He found out the murderer?
Yeah.
Your Highness.
-Your Highness.
What happened?
Stop crying.
Explain to me
before you cry again.
Or...
Or keep crying for a minute.
Wu Jiang, what happened?
A gang of villains
tried to kidnap Miss Chu.
Who are they?
I’m sorry,
but I failed to catch anyone alive.
I only bring back a corpse.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
Don’t. Don’t punish him.
I didn’t know they were bad men.
It was all my fault.
And they didn’t kill those kidnappers.
A villain did.
All right.
I won’t punish them.
Are you hurt?
Then what are you crying for?
I feel like I had a nightmare.
I didn’t wake up until I saw you.
Then I couldn’t help crying.
What do you mean?
Your Highness,
you asked General Wu
to save me, didn’t you?
You helped me again.
You helped me several times today.
I…
Shall I...
Shall I kowtow to you again?
There’s no such rule with me.
Don’t bother to be so courteous.
You don’t be courteous, either.
Stop calling me Miss Chu.
Call me Chu Chu.
All right.
Chu Chu.
You took back the corpse?
Yes.
Go get us a coroner.
Don’t bother. I’m a coroner.
Your Highness, you saved me.
I don’t know how to pay you back.
All I can do is to perform an autopsy.
I can do it on anyone.
Let me do it for you.
I want an autopsy on the kidnapper.
Are you still willing to?
Yes.
His heart was stabbed
by something sharp.
The cut is neat.
He died with one stab.
Thick calluses between his right thumb
and the index finger.
He’s sound in limbs.
Your Highness,
in her purse,
there’re 23 copper coins
with Qian Printing.
I checked in the Minister of Revenue.
19 of the coins are illegal coins.
They’re the same
as what the merchants from Qianzhou used
you saw in the West Market.
You didn’t say much, did you?
Don’t worry. I know what I should say.
But I think there’s something fishy
with Miss Chu.
She gave this to me today.
It’s poisonous?
No.
If she poisoned it,
she would be someone
I unintentionally offended
during a case
and she simply came to take revenge.
That would be simple.
But this isn’t poisonous
and she flatters me all the time.
She’s more eager to be admitted
than ordinary coroners.
If someone is behind her,
the pendant she holds
must be the bait.
But she prefers to give up the chance
of getting a job,
rather than tell me
how she got the pendant.
With all due respect, Your Highness,
Jing Yi found that girl.
Get to the point and then leave!
Your Highness, there’s no restriction
for tomorrow’s selection test,
is there?
I met a genius coroner today!
But she’s a bit special
and she can’t be admitted
to Three Judicial Offices
unless you help her.
I promise you,
she’ll impress you!
Then you come to annoy me first?
I’m serious, Your Highness.
No way.
You know what?
If you miss her,
you’ll regret all your life!
I mean
even if someone helps her,
it can’t be me.
Otherwise, when people know about it,
there’ll be trouble.
I’ll help her, then.
I’ll be the invigilator tomorrow.
Jing Yi grew up with me.
I know him very well.
He won’t do this to me.
He doesn’t need to do so, either.
Wu Jiang, have you heard about
the Handsome Judge
she just mentioned?
I haven’t.
Now that you want to know
about her pendant
and obviously Miss Chu hasn’t met
the Handsome Judge before,
why don’t you pretend to be him?
What if she wants a code
or to check about some birthmark
or nevus?
You’re right.
Even if I can pretend to be someone,
I need to know
what this man looks like.
Yes. Yes.
You’re right, Your Highness.
We can’t figure out
if there’s such a man
in the martial world.
Send a letter to Leng Yue.
We should ask her
what she knows most.
Yes.
By the way,
who kidnapped her?
They’re martial artists.
But they deliberately concealed
their martial arts.
I can’t tell who they are.
As far as I see,
they came for Miss Chu on purpose.
Also, they don’t want
to kill her.
They don’t want to kill her?
Yes.
I heard them say...
Go with me
and I won’t kill you.
♪Nothing can♪
♪Stop me♪
♪From missing you♪
♪All the time♪
♪It’s cold at night♪
♪Everything changes in the world♪
♪I have affection for nothing♪
♪But your hug♪
♪Close the eyes♪
♪Meet again♪
♪By your side♪
♪I brush your hair gently♪
♪Life is long but love isn’t♪
♪There’s regret in the world♪
♪Only with you around♪
♪We’ll never lose contact♪
♪The moment♪
♪You smile♪
♪Let me cherish it for good♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I care about my life♪
♪I’m not old yet♪
♪I still love you♪
♪At last I settle down for you♪
♪I can rely on you all my life♪
♪Hope we’ll spend our lives sweetly♪