Feng’s Mansion’s mourning hall
suddenly caught fire.
His Highness disregarded the danger
and rushed in the fire to rescue me.
And he spoke up for me
before Minister Han.
Thankfully, I didn’t betray
His Highness’s trust.
I found out that
the ministers who seemingly
died because of accidents
were all killed by the same method
at Rugui House.
I also found
His Highness’s little secret.
However,
I’ll keep it for him.
(Xiao Jinli)
Shelves with categorized files.
(Princess Xiping)
(Yan Ming)
(Xiao Heng)
These are monitoring records.
How daring!
This is...?
(25th, Princess Xiping’s Mansion Banquet)
Princess’s Mansion.
(Jing Yi)
(Xiao Jinyu)
His Highness.
Your Highness, what are you doing?
I’m drawing Xu Rugui’s portrait.
So we can issue the writ of arrest.
But wasn’t today the first time
you saw Manager Xu?
You can draw his portrait
when you’ve only met him once?
=The Imperial Coroner=
=Episode 6=
Qin Luan.
Your Majesty, here I am.
I’m here.
Bastard! What’s your problem?
Your Majesty.
Who taught this new guy?
He can’t even pour
a cup of tea properly.
Your Majesty, don’t be mad.
He didn’t learn the manners well.
It’s all my fault.
Why are you still here?
You’re so annoying. Go away!
Your Majesty, don’t be mad.
I’ll clean this place right now.
(Qianzhou)
Qin Luan,
where were you just now?
There are strands of beard
stuck under your shoes.
Beard?
Your Majesty, these are not beard.
These are my strands of hair.
Your Majesty,
when you demanded my presence,
I was trimming the hair on my temples.
I guess mistakenly stepped on it
when I changed my clothes in a hurry.
I’m sorry for the annoyance.
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
Forget it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, it’s late.
The palace will host
a tea gathering tomorrow.
The tea gathering.
I’d forget it if you didn’t bring it up.
Go to Three Judicial Offices
yourself tomorrow.
Pass on my order.
Xiao Jinyu must be present
no matter how busy he is with work.
If he doesn’t come,
you can kidnap him there.
If I don’t find him a chance to
mediate his relations
with the ministers,
I’m worried that he may
get swallowed alive one day.
Yes.
It’s exactly the same.
Your Highness, you’re amazing.
But.
But what?
But I still find
Manager Xu looks a bit weird.
Weird?
How?
I can’t describe it.
But I had such feelings
when I say him today.
I just find him a bit odd.
Don’t rush.
Think carefully. Why is he odd?
What?
I knew!
His look is odd
because it’s like something
that’s pieced together.
Something that’s pieced together?
Yes.
People look different from each other.
But people born in the same regions
share similarities in looks.
It’s like there’s a mould.
People from the Western Regions
have a mould.
People from Lingnan Regions
People from Chang’an
also have a mould.
But Manager Xu’s face isn’t shaped
by any of those moulds.
His face looks as if
someone shattered many moulds
and took parts from those moulds
to piece together.
On my journey from Qianzhou to Chang’an,
I’ve seen people from every region,
but I’ve never seen a man
who looks like this.
This is so weird.
What if his parents or ancestors
are descendants from other regions?
That’s not the case either.
For example, Mules are born from
donkeys and horses.
Mules don’t look exactly like donkeys,
nor horses.
However, in every parts of mules,
you can find features of
both donkeys and horses.
It seems that
the eyes of Lingnan people,
the mouth of the Northern barbarians,
the forehead of Jiangnan people,
and the chin of Goryeo people
are all assembled on a face from
people who’re inside Shanhai Pass.
Xu Rugui might have disguised his look.
Disguise?
Leave the city at dawn.
There will be people waiting
for you outside the city.
You’d better be smart.
You know what are the consequences
if Xiao Jinyu catches you.
General Zhou, don’t worry.
Today is the only time I met Xiao Jinyu.
Even if he has miraculous
drawing techniques,
he can only draw my falsified look.
When my natural face
was hidden,
Xiao Jinyu was still
an infant in the cradle.
He definitely can’t recognize me
even if I stand right before him.
Cut it out.
Can you not boast about yourself?
It’s late. Hurry up.
What are the other orders
from Eunuch Qin?
He ordered you to hide for a while.
If he has more orders,
someone will contact you.
I’m at Eunuch Qin’s service.
Xu Rugui is right-handed.
Yes.
Look at the way he walks.
He’s trained in martial arts.
Martial arts?
I’ve never heard that
our manager knows martial arts.
Your manager is used to putting keys
in his left sleeve?
Yes.
I always see him
take out keys from his left sleeve.
Then what does he often store
in his right sleeve?
Right sleeve?
I don’t know that for sure.
I’ve never seen him
take out anything from the right sleeve.
Lord Jing,
why did you come back
from the outside?
Xu Rugui
is just like a rabbit.
He has dug up several exits
to the dark chamber.
Wu Jiang and I have tried all of them.
They all lead to the outside.
And this.
What’s that?
You’ll know when you see it.
Xu Rugui isn’t inside.
But there’s indeed a stove.
This was left next to the stove.
There are also many shelves.
Each section of the shelves
has names on it.
There are my name, your name,
and the names of many ministers.
And the things you’re holding now.
You’re worried that someone killed
Xu Rugui to keep him silent.
But it seems more likely that
he fled when he knew
we’d search this place.
And he tried to burn the evidences,
but didn’t put everything in the stove
before he fled
because he was in a hurry.
And I dug this out of
(25th, Princess Xiping’s Mansion Banquet)
the stove.
Wu Jiang.
Yes.
Go back to Three Judicial Offices
immediately.
Bring enough people to
Princess Xiping’s Mansion.
Ensure her safety.
Don’t leave before I come.
Yes.
Your Highness, what’s the problem?
It’s fine.
Jing Yi.
Does the chamber have a place
that requires keys?
No.
It’s just a dark chamber.
There’s nothing more besides the exits.
Xu Rugui has a chain of keys that
he habitually stores
in his right sleeve.
If those are not for the dark chamber,
he must have another residence
as a hiding place.
Another residence?
Where is it?
I don’t know.
I’ve never heard that
our manager has another house.
This is the map of Chang’an.
(The Map of Chang’an)
Squares represent neighborhoods.
This is Rugui House.
(The Map of Chang’an)
Jing Yi.
Identify the objects in this room.
Find out from which store
the items were bought.
Manager.
Think carefully about
Xu Rugui’s daily habits.
Mark the places he visits regularly
on this board with chess pieces.
Yes.
This is Huaiyuan Residence.
This is the East Market.
(Pingkang Yiyang Qinren the East Market
Anyi Daozheng Changle Jinggong)
(Jiahui Yanfu Huaizhen Yonghe
Yongping...)
(Yong’an)
He’s active in this neighborhood,
except this region.
This should be the place.
Your Highness,
this place seems to be a small square
on the chessboard,
but, in reality,
it spreads across over 20 hectares.
Over 100 hundred families live there.
There was mud and rice paste mixture
at the bottom of his shoes.
There must be a residence
that’s under construction
next to his secret house.
Take this portrait and
ask the neighborhood.
I’ll look for his secret residence.
Handle things here.
Yes.
And,
send people to each city gate.
Tell each guard leader in my name.
Tell them that
there’s an important suspect
on the loose.
Ask them to carefully
interrogate every person
who enters or exits the city.
Those without an ID or
with a suspicious one
mustn’t exit the city
no matter what seals, letters,
or certificates they hold,
particularly those dressed
as Shence Army members.
I got it.
Chu Chu, come with me.
General Zhou, once I leave the capital,
please take care of my family.
Sure.
But how I take care of them
depends on you.
I get it.
Oh.
Have you taken care of those
who killed Feng Jie and the others?
I’ve taken care of them the old way.
General, don’t worry about it.
General, please take this to Eunuch Qin.
Let’s go.
(Serene Spirits)
General Wu.
Aunt Banxia.
What’s going on?
I’ll tell you the details later.
Where’s Princess?
This is the place. Search!
Yes.
Your Highness, no one’s inside.
They haven’t left for long.
We’re one step behind.
Your Highness, we found no one.
Your Highness, no one’s here.
This smell.
Your Highness, check this out.
What?
Look.
What is that?
Pickled cabbages.
Pickled cabbages?
Yes, pickled cabbages from Qianzhou.
People from Qianzhou all like sourness.
At our place,
every household knows
how to make such pickled cabbages.
A special ingredient is needed
to make them.
It’s something like a broth.
Without it, we can’t make
good pickled cabbages.
Your Highness, don’t you think
that Manager Xu and I might
come from the same place?
It’s possible.
Rugui House has cooks
who’re from Qianzhou.
They hoard fish mints regularly.
And there are Qianzhou
pickled cabbages in this house.
Even if Xu Rugui isn’t from Qianzhou,
he must have some ties with it.
General Zhou.
Open the door.
Why are you exiting the city
when it’s so late?
It’s none of your business.
Just open the door when I tell you to.
Someone died of pestilence
in my battalion.
I’ll burn his body outside the city.
Wait.
Haven’t you heard me?
General Zhou, any passing vehicle needs
to be examined after the gate is closed.
Hurry. We can’t handle the consequences
if we let Xu Rugui slip away.
Hyah!
This man had pestilence.
If he spreads it across Chang’an,
you’ll assume the responsibilities?
The city gate has its rules.
General Zhou, if I let you exit the city
without permit,
when the superiors look for
the ones accountable,
me and my brothers will be executed.
Who?
Let him inspect.
General Zhou, excuse me.
Open the door. Let them leave.
Master.
How is it going?
Master, don’t worry.
Everything is going well.
Great. Great.
Go to rest.
Yes.
The stove is covered by dust.
It hasn’t been used for a long time.
But the storage jars are
clean and organized.
They’re often moved around.
Master, what’s inside?
Black beans.
I’m sorry. I slipped.
Don’t move.
These beans seem to have been
smashed regularly
by hard objects.
Something was hidden in the jars before.
Grains can absorb moisture.
Only house owners touch these.
When valuables are hidden inside,
they’re hardly noticed by others.
This color and texture are familiar.
Yes.
It’s Ruyi Pawnshop’s unique tassel.
The killers of Rugui House
conduct their transactions
(Ruyi Pawnshop)
through Ruyi Pawnshop.
Xu Rugui rented pawnshop’s lockers
(Rented the lockers)
and shared them with the killers.
(Depositing...)
They each hold a half of the tally.
They complete their transactions
without having to meet.
I hope we can catch the killers in time.
Vice Minister Jing.
Where’s His Highness?
Your Highness.
Lord Jing, how did you find us?
I can’t find Xu Rugui’s house.
But I can find His Highness.
Your Highness,
I’ve taken care of the things
at Rugui House.
The officers who headed to Tonghua Gate
were intercepted halfway
by men in black.
They didn’t intend to kill
and retreated soon
after hearing the whistle.
The officers arrived at the gate
only to find that Zhou Han,
from Shence Army,
just led a group of people and
left the city thirty minutes ago.
Did the guards search them
before letting them leave?
They did.
But they found nothing suspicious.
Such a coincidence.
These men in black seem to be there
just to buy Zhou Han more time.
I’ll go and check it.
Bring people to catch
the killer who murdered
Feng Jie and the others.
You must catch him alive.
Where is he?
This?
Ruyi Pawnshop.
Xu Rugui must have a tally
which is from Ruyi Pawnshop.
Currently, the tally isn’t kept
at the place it’s usually stored.
Xu Rugui might have just gone to
Ruyi Pawnshop to pay the killers today.
Rugui House was closed down today.
Once the killer got the news,
he will retrieve the money
immediately before he flees for life.
Take Xu Rugui’s portrait with you.
Interrogate the owner of Ruyi Pawnshop.
And you’ll know
the number of their locker.
Keep an eye on it.
Whoever goes to retrieve money
is the killer.
Don’t worry.
(To Commandery Prince An)
And this.
Wu Jiang asked someone to deliver this.
I’ll go ahead with my work.
Let’s go.
The weather is dry.
Things are flammable.
Chu Chu’s birth date has been confirmed.
Her father’s wife has been deceased
for years.
The neighborhood knew Chu Chu as
Chu Ping’s daughter out of wedlock.
The identity of her
birth mother is unclear.
Chu Family led a simple life
in the neighborhood.
They only had close ties
with a lonely witch doctor,
who left the region five years ago,
and is still missing to this day.
A witch doctor?
That’s the one
who told her stories about Six Gates?
Your Highness, we’ve arrived.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Rise.
Have Zhou Han and his team returned yet?
No, Your Highness.
They have five riders
and a carriage.
Yes.
One of them rode a flat wagon?
Six people in total?
I know all of them.
They’re indeed from Shence Army.
There was one corpse on the flat wagon.
The dead was dressed in
Shence Army’s uniform.
But his face looked unfamiliar.
It’s said that he died of pestilence.
They were in a hurry to burn him
outside the city.
Just one dead man?
Yes, just one.
No.
I mean there was only one corpse
on the flat wagon?
Yes, indeed.
A flat wagon,
a rider, and a corpse.
How can the tracks be so deep?
Have you checked under the wagon?
No.
My attention was caught by
the corpse on the wagon.
This is a cover-up.
I’m afraid there was another person
under the wagon.
Let them exit.
Your Highness, I’m sorry...
It’s okay.
This happened too quickly.
It’s not your fault.
Examine more carefully in the future.
I believe Zhou Han will come back soon.
Just let them get back to the city.
Don’t say a thing.
Just pretend you know nothing.
I’ll send someone to
handle the rest.
Yes.
He even figured that out?
It’s midnight already. What happened?
Where’s Jinyu?
His Highness is all right.
It’s just...
His Highness is so busy with work that
he hasn’t had a chance
to see Your Grace.
His Highness misses Your Grace.
So he ordered me to come
and strengthen the defense
at Princess’s Mansion
to express his filial piety.
Why should he strengthen guard
if everything is going well?
I know martial arts and I have guards.
Why do you come to my place
when you should be protecting him?
I heard that the mourning hall
of Feng’s Mansion was on fire tonight.
Did Jinyu ignore His Majesty’s orders
and again make a scene
at Feng’s Mansion?
I’ll go and find him now!
Your Grace, don’t be angry.
Your Grace,
Scholar Xue has told you that
you mustn’t intervene with
His Highness’s work.
That’s harmful to His Highness’s
reputation in the office.
His Highness has been always discreet
since childhood.
Your Grace, you should trust him.
How can I trust him
when he’s caused so much trouble?
Your Grace, His Highness promised to
come here after work.
Just wait a bit longer.
Your Grace, His Highness is
a man of his words.
He promised to come here later.
Then he will.
Why don’t you sit down and
think about how you’ll scold him later?
Otherwise, it’ll be like the usual days.
Before you can give a good talking,
His Highness will have already
changed the subject.
Then, you’ll blame me instead.
Fine. Just leave.
You!
You’re always on his side.
Master, you finally came out.
His Majesty.
It’s fine.
How are things doing out there?
Master, don’t worry.
Everything is going well.
He has left the city.
It’s finally dawn.
This night is too long.
His Majesty said that
he was afraid that
someone may devour Xiao Jinyu alive.
Who do you think should be that person?
Devour Xiao Jinyu.
Devour?
Who?
(Tonghua Gate)
Commandery Prince An is right.
Chu Chu.
Go back and take some rest.
You’ve been busy working
with me all night.
You must be tired.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Are you coming or not?
I have other matters.
Then when will you come back?
Why are you asking?
I just find you rather pale.
Come back to rest
when you’re done with work.
Okay.
Wait.
I didn’t have the chance
to ask you earlier.
What’s the embroidery
on your handkerchief?
It’s a bone.
The fifth rib bone on left chest.
Rib bone?
Why that?
Because it’s the closest place
to a person’s heart.
When you put your hand
on the bone’s position,
you can feel your heart pond.
That’s my favorite bone.
Do you find it beautiful?
Yes.
Go.
You embroidered this?
If you don’t like it...
Your Highness, there you are!
Where’s Her Grace?
She’s inside.
Jinyu,
where have you been all night?
Come closer. Let me see if you’re hurt.
No. Mother, don’t worry.
You caused so much disturbance
in the middle of the night.
Everyone was worried because of you.
If you don’t explain everything
clearly today,
I’ll greet His Majesty and ask him to
remove you from Three Judicial Offices.
Mother, calm down.
You can interrogate me today.
I’ll tell you everything honestly.
Wu Jiang, take the guards and leave.
Yes.
I’ve been busy all night.
I didn’t even have water.
Can I beg for a cup of tea?
Tea?
You won’t even get cold water.
Miss Chu,
let me help you change the medicine.
No. No need.
I can do it myself.
These are just minor wounds.
When I made baskets at home,
my hands always got scratched.
I never whined because of pain.
You’re so brave.
No, I’m not.
I’m nothing
compared with His Highness.
Chu Chu. Chu Chu.
Chu Chu.
Oh!
Can I ask you for something?
What is it, Miss Chu?
His Highness has given us the order.
You can have whatever you want
so long as it’s not livestock
or growable seeds or seedlings.
I want a spoon.
A spoon?
Miss Chu, if you want to eat something,
you can ask the kitchen to cook it.
You don’t have to do it yourself.
No. I’m not trying to cook.
I just want a spoon.
A spoon of this size.
This size?
Fine. Mother.
I’m already full.
Eat more.
Look at how pale you are!
You must have stayed up late for days.
Banxia, go to the kitchen.
Bring out hasma if it’s cooked.
Your Grace, didn’t you just say
you won’t even give
His Highness cold water?
Of course, I won’t.
How can he drink cold water
in such a freezing day?
Go and check it.
Bring out hasma if it’s cooked.
Yes.
Mother.
I’m here today because
I want to ask you something.
You promised to let me
interrogate you today.
You are to break the promise
after lunch?
Now, you’ll interrogate me?
Don’t you want to know
what happened last night?
Take a look at this first.
(Xiao Jinyu...)
(Lynched the remaining members
of Chen Ying’s party...)
(Xiao Heng escaped luckily...)
Mother.
Banxia.
Guard the door.
Don’t let anyone enter
without my permission.
Yes.
Where are these from?
A tavern named Rugui House in the city.
A tavern?
Why would a tavern
investigate your father?
That’s why I want to ask you.
Ask me?
How can I know?
The man who made
these investigation records
has fled upon sensing danger.
My men are still hunting him.
These are what he has left behind
in a sealed chamber at Rugui House.
There were more records
about other people.
They were destroyed by fire.
Among the few scrolls remained,
there’s one that’s about father.
If I’m not mistaken,
that man left this intentionally to me.
He left this to you on purpose?
Why would he do that?
(25th, Princess Xiping’s Mansion Banquet)
On last month’s 25th,
did you throw a banquet at the mansion?
I invited Madam Jing.
Someone is spying on us.
So, I didn’t allow Wu Jiang to
explain everything clearly
to you last night.
Mother, please forgive me.
The audacity!
Mother, don’t be mad.
Tell me.
What do they spy on me for?
They want to find out
something from you.
What do they want to know?
Mother, I’m wishing you to tell me.
How can I know?
Mother,
father passed away years ago.
His remains are buried under Chang’an.
Why are they going through
all this trouble
to spy on you,
me,
and those who had ties with father?
It seems...
It seems that they’re searching for
his whereabouts.
Nonsense.
A few days ago,
I saw the other half of this pendant.
Where did you see it?
It’s in the hands of
a girl from Qianzhou.
A girl from Qianzhou.
Is that the coroner you brought to
Feng’s Mansion to send your condolence?
Yes.
Then, she...
Mother, don’t rush.
It’s still under investigation.
No.
Ask your men to fall back.
Order them to come back.
Kick that coroner out of
Three Judicial Offices.
No, kick her out of Chang’an.
You can’t keep investigating this case.
Why?
Mother, about father,
are you keeping secrets?
Now, the enemies are hiding in the dark.
We’re exposed.
This is unfavorable to us.
Mother, please tell me
everything truthfully.
Master.
Mingde is here.
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Put them down carefully.
Put them down.
You two. Leave. Go.
Yes.
-Close the door.
-Go ahead with your work.
Master.
Look. Everything is here.
Except those we’ve burned
and those you ordered to be left
to Xiao Jinyu,
every other scroll
is here.
Has Xiao Jinyu taken actions?
Just as you’ve expected,
Xiao Jinyu ordered his Chief Guardsman,
Wu Jiang, to lead a team of guards
and stand by at
Princess Xiping’s Mansion.
They only left
when Xiao Jinyu himself arrived.
I guess
our wise and assertive
Commandery Prince An
is now shaking Princess Xiping’s sleeves
and begging for his father.
Prince Consort secretly reported
the treason of Chen Ying,
the Military Commissioner of Jiannan,
to the imperial court.
Prince Consort was tragically
murdered by Chen Ying.
When I led Shence Army
to suppress the rebellion
at His Majesty’s behest.
It was too late.
These are what I can bring back.
I’m sorry, Your Grace.
His Majesty is impressed
by Prince Consort’s loyalty.
His Majesty has decreed the conferment.
Your Grace, please take it.
I’ve never imagined that
-you father would disappear
-No.
-like that.
No.
So, father’s current grave in Chang’an
is a cenotaph.
Besides accepting it,
what else can I do?
The Imperial Court at that time
was so different from the current one.
The conflict between ministers
and eunuchs were so heated.
When we heard your father’s
death in Chang’an,
Chang’an was caught in Ganlu Incident.
The North Yamen led by eunuchs
were on a killing spree.
The South Yamen led by Prime Minister
were slaughtered.
Even my father was
confined in the imperial palace.
The conferment decree for your dad
was already ordered.
Leng Family, from the Southwest,
supports me.
But if I insist to seek justice
from the Imperial Court,
considering the situation,
I would’ve already brought calamities
on you and your brother
before the justice could be upheld.
Mother,
it seems that
father might still be alive.
♪Nothing can♪
♪Stop me♪
♪From missing you♪
♪All the time♪
♪It’s cold at night♪
♪Everything changes in the world♪
♪I have affection for nothing♪
♪But your hug♪
♪Close the eyes♪
♪Meet again♪
♪By your side♪
♪I brush your hair gently♪
♪Life is long but love isn’t♪
♪There’s regret in the world♪
♪Only with you around♪
♪We’ll never lose contact♪
♪The moment♪
♪You smile♪
♪Let me cherish it for good♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I care about my life♪
♪I’m not old yet♪
♪I still love you♪
♪At last I settle down for you♪
♪I can rely on you all my life♪
♪Hope we’ll spend our lives sweetly♪