Xu Rugui used Lady Xu’s hairpin
to lead me to discover the identities
of Chu Chu’s biological parents,
trying to damage the trust
between Chu Chu and I.
Whatever happens,
I will find out the truth.
My mother was killed by
the housekeeper of the Xu family
and Xu Rugui is my uncle.
Your Majesty,
I’ve found out
that the rumor about
Duke Chang these days
came from a brat doing chores
in the Imperial Garden.
He was new in the Palace
and hasn’t changed his vulgar habit
he developed when he was out there.
Somehow he got the nerve
and made up some shadowy stories
about the late Duke Chang.
I’ve severely reprimanded his supervisor
who teaches him about the rules.
Is it really a new minion
who spread the rumors about
the son of the Emperor Wuzong
in the capital?
Yes.
He is bold indeed.
He had a few drinks
and dared to talk nonsense in the Palace
which was heard by the boring servants
and spread outside the Palace.
And everyone is talking about it.
But he is also
timid indeed.
He was so scared
that he had a heart attack and died
before I bring him to you.
He died of fear?
Yes.
Rumors...
Are these just rumors?
Your Majesty, you know
that the offspring of Emperor Wuzong
has been dead for a long time.
These words are just rumors.
If you want to stop these rumors
as soon as possible,
I have a solution.
Bur I’m afraid you need to
sacrifice a little bit.
I don’t know whether I should say it.
Just go ahead.
I think
these people can be incited
by the rumors
because they have forgotten the fact
that the Emperor Wuzong’s sons
died a long time ago.
You only need to remind them
and the rumors will naturally disappear.
Tell me
how I should remind them.
Your Majesty, you can choose
an auspicious day
and give posthumous names to
the sons of the Emperor Wuzong.
Posthumous names?
Good.
Only the dead will be
given posthumous names.
You are showing your benevolence.
I believe no minister will object it.
Those who are discussing Duke Chang
in the court and the commonalty
will also deeply admire your generosity
and become more loyal to serve you.
Good.
Order the academician
to draft an edict now and ask
the Ministry of Rites and the Imperial
Astronomer to get on it immediately.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Order Wu Jiang to
enter the Palace tomorrow.
I have something to ask him.
It has been a while since
Commandery Prince An left Chang’an.
Why is there no news from him at all?
If Xiao Heng is really in the Southwest,
there is no way he would
avoid his biological son.
Yes, Your Majesty.
=The Imperial Coroner=
=Episode 17=
Why did you ask about Duke Chang?
Do you still remember Yan Ming?
Yan Ming?
You found a scroll at Yan Ming’s place.
I told you that Yan Ming was
looking for someone.
Was he looking for Duke Chang?
It’s possible.
When Yan Ming was repairing a book,
he had a habit
that an official would have.
When he met a deceased person
whose year of death
or whereabouts are unknown,
he would try to
find it out through
the clues from the old scrolls.
The ink on his scroll is still new.
It can be seen that he got interested in
the late emperor’s young son
whose year of death is unknown.
Did he suspect
that Duke Chang is still alive?
Before I left Chang’an, I ask Wu Jiang
to secretly verity
what’s written in his manuscript.
Hold on.
A nerd scribbled a few words
and you took it seriously?
You even verified it?
Yan Ming’s deduction
is not rigorous enough,
but it’s not all unreasonable.
The three people Xu Rugui
was ordered to kill in Chang’an
are Lu Chuansheng, the Capital Liaison
Representative in Qianzhou
responsible for the communication
between Chang’an and Qianzhou,
Liu Yue, the head of
the Ministry of Revenue
in charge coins minting
in the Southwest,
and Feng Jie, the Minister of War
who just finished the inspection
of the military affairs
in the Southwest before he was killed.
He hadn’t had time to
report on the military inspection.
All of them are related to Qianzhou.
And Qianzhou was also granted to
Duke Chang at that time.
At such a point,
Yan Ming was murdered
because of a scroll about
looking into the whereabouts
of Duke Chang.
So you are suspecting
that Duke Chang is behind
these things related to Qianzhou?
He killed Yan Ming
because he is afraid
that someone would know he is alive.
It doesn’t make sense.
If he is behind it,
the dancing girl should
destroy the scroll
when she killed Yan Ming.
Why would she hide it?
There is another possibility.
What possibility?
He killed Yan Ming
no because he is afraid
that people will know he is alive,
but because he wants people
to know that he is alive.
Master.
There is one thing I can’t figure out.
Why are you protecting
that brat who took poison
and committed suicide?
You think I’m protecting him?
Of course.
He must have committed suicide
by taking poison
and there is someone behind it.
This Antique Store might be the clue.
But you didn’t mention
a word about it to the Emperor.
Aren’t you protecting him?
You are short-sighted.
I’m not protecting him.
I’m protecting us.
I’m foolish, please enlighten me.
The Emperor asked us to look into this,
do you think he really
wants to know the truth?
He was just testing us.
When the son of
the late emperor was dying,
we were by his side.
He suspects that we are behind it.
I have to solve it in this way
to finish our job.
Master, you are wise indeed.
Mingde, let me
tell you something from my heart.
Stop being that glib.
Try to be cleverer.
The channels of communication between
Qianzhou and Chang’an court was cut off.
A large amount of
copper coins were minted.
The news about military affairs
in the Southwest
was strictly prevented from
being reported to the court.
If there is one person
behind all these things,
what do you think this person is up to?
What?
To plot a rebellion!
That’s right.
Rebels of all dynasties
want to be the ruler in the end.
But a dead person
can’t ascend the throne.
No one will support a dead man
to be an emperor.
Therefore, if he wants to
ascend to the throne
in the name of Duke Chang,
he must bring Duke Chang
back to life first.
You mean he killed Yan Ming
because he wanted you to
discover the scroll
and find out Yan Ming was killed
because of his conclusion
that Duke Chang is still alive,
so as to whip up public opinion
and then he can rebel
in the name of Duke Chang.
That’s why I’ve been
trying to contain the news.
But I got news from Wu Jiang
that there are rumors
in Chang’an about
Duke Chang being alive.
I guess he realized
that I’m not used by him,
that’s why he has to use the dumbest way
to spread rumors.
There is no evidence but rumors.
He can’t make any waves.
I’m not worried about that he can
make any waves with the rumors.
But I’m afraid he is so eager
to spread the rumors
because everything is ready
and he only needs a chance to do it.
If that’s the case,
we have to find him out quickly.
He caused so many messes
in Qianzhou.
Maybe he is hiding in Qianzhou.
This is too important to rush into.
Right now, Qianzhou is in such a mess.
A lot of things happened.
But these things
are connected
and interlocked.
If we can pull a thread from it,
everything will be clear then.
Duke Chang is the trueborn son
of the late emperor.
The Emperor now is the uncle
If Duke Chang is still alive
and you find him out,
it’s fine if he is behind these things.
But if he is innocent,
how should the Emperor deal with it?
That’s exactly why
I didn’t tell you about it.
Weren’t you blaming me for
not taking you to handle
those dangerous affairs?
I do have a selfish motive.
What?
If anything happens to me,
you are the only one I can entrust
with the posthumous affairs.
And only you
can coax my mother and my brother.
Your Highness.
My original intention of coming to
the Three Judicial Offices
is to be a rakish young master
with my father and my brother’s
official authority.
How does it turn out like this?
You worked for it.
Fine, I deserve it.
What should we do to Xu Rugui?
Bring him back to the county office
or send him to Prefect’s Mansion?
Keep him here for now.
Keep him here?
He just killed the father of
the Deputy Magistrate, Tan Gui.
Keeping him in the county office
may cause trouble.
But if we skip the magistrate
and send him to Li Zhang,
it will also bring troubles
if Li Zhang looks into it.
Your Highness, you are afraid
that Xu Rugui
will tell others about
Chu Chu’s background, right?
It has been our speculation
and Xu Rugui’s side of story so far.
Before we have any conclusive evidence,
don’t bring this up to anyone.
Your Highness, you are going to suffer.
What?
You have someone inside of you.
All the prisoners who have not
been arrested in Tang
are all here.
Of course I have people inside.
Cut it out.
Your enemies in the court
include the discontented officials
of the Three Judicial Offices,
the incompetent magistrates,
and those eunuchs like Qin Luan.
Do they ever stop
picking on you together?
Have you ever been
so pissed off by them?
It’s not the time
that I brought trouble to you,
when have you been so angry with me?
It’s such an important clue.
You must consider it carefully.
By the way,
I brought this for you.
If you won’t use it as evidence,
then give it to Chu Chu as a keepsake.
Father, I want to ask you something.
What are you panic about?
When Chu Chu’s mother died,
did she die at the place
of Chu Chu’s uncle?
Yes.
Her brother
is Chu Chu’s uncle.
Have you met Chu Chu’s uncle?
Yes.
Can you recognize he now?
Now? Where?
Maybe...
Did he come back to Guanling County?
Father.
Maybe he is locked inside our woodshed.
What?
The man locked inside the woodshed
is Chu Chu’s uncle?
When they brought him here,
his head was covered.
I was worried about Chu Chu
and didn’t pay much attention
to that man.
Yeah. They also said
that there is one thing
concerning Chu Chu’s life.
Concerning her life?
What is it?
They spoke vaguely
and I didn’t hear clearly.
Father, what should we do?
Do what?
You are not sure about anything yet.
Don’t be in such a hurry.
I mean, Father.
Are you going to
let her die just because
she is not your biological daughter?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I’m telling the truth.
Xu Zongfang?
Thank you.
Mr. Chu, why are you still up so late?
I worked late.
I saw the light here
and I’m here to bring you a pot of tea.
Give me the tea.
Thank you, Mr. Chu
The dew is heavy in the late night.
Please go back and rest earlier.
I want to go inside and get something.
Mr. Chu, please.
Thanks.
Is he the bandit who kidnapped Chu Chu?
Yes, Mr. Chu.
He is very dangerous.
You’d better go back to your room.
Okay.
Father, how is it?
They covered his face
and gagged his mouth.
I can’t tell.
All right, let’s leave it to tomorrow.
Father...
That’s it.
Everyone in this world
will be unable to speak or move one day.
Our Chu family
is to say out loud
what they want to say but cannot say.
Grandpa, can you hear the dead?
I don’t hear them
I see them.
Why can’t I see them?
Do you also want to see them?
Yes.
Good.
Grandpa.
I’m here to see
if you are getting better.
What are you busy with
early in the morning?
The room is too messy.
I’m tidying it up.
Father always said
the room is too messy
to be a girl’s room.
How does it not look like a girl’s room?
If it’s neat and clean,
it won’t be my Chu Chu’s style.
Grandpa, have a seat.
Grandpa, it was my fault yesterday.
I made you worry about me.
You are like a coroner
working for a high official now.
You speak like a grown up
and you know the etiquette now.
When you were at home before,
I always saw you as a kid.
I thought a girl
won’t get into the county office.
So I didn’t give you
any serious lessons.
Now it turns out
that I was short-sighted.
Grandpa, why are you
saying this suddenly?
You will always be a member of
the Chu family.
I promise you.
Tell me the truth.
Don’t you trust me anymore?
Of course I trust you.
Even you trust me,
you still can’t feel at ease.
I understand.
A verbal promise doesn’t count.
A coroner needs to
write a report for the autopsy.
An official needs the case file
to settle a lawsuit.
And it also needs evidence
to prove that you are
the daughter of the Chu family.
This is the genealogy of the Chu family.
By the ordinary rules,
women can’t be written on it.
But I’ll make the decision this time.
If you are willing to be the child
of the Chu family,
I’ll write you in the genealogy.
In the future,
no one can say that you are not
a child of the Chu family.
Grandpa.
What are you doing? Get up.
Grandpa, I’m ungrateful.
I have a favor to ask you.
Promise me you will say yes.
Get up first before you tell me.
Grandpa, just let me finish it.
Otherwise you will think
I’m being childish even I say it.
Fine.
I promise you. You can tell me now.
I don’t expect my name
to be written in the genealogy.
I only need you to promise me
that no matter who my father is,
you must bury me beside my mother
if I die one day.
When you have time,
remember to visit me
with my father and my brother.
What silly words are you talking about?
Grandpa, I’m serious.
Jinyu, do you hear that?
Please don’t despise me
because of my background at that time.
If it’s inconvenient for you,
I don’t need any offering or joss stick.
Just come and visit me.
I want to know if you are doing well.
I’m afraid...
I’m afraid I won’t be able to
see you again.
Why do I feel like
Miss Chu is preparing for her death?
Are you still thinking about Father?
Did you tell Jing Yi about
what happened in your father’s mansion?
No.
But he is clever enough.
I think he probably knows what happened.
I’m not worried
whether he knows it or not.
I’m just worried
he will tell the people
in the Palace about Chu Chu.
About Miss Chu?
Chu Chu.
Your Highness?
Have a seat.
Why did you get up so early?
You should sleep more.
I...
I can’t sleep.
Your Highness, is there
anything you want to say
but you can’t say?
Yes.
Is it about the case?
Kind of.
How about you?
Me, too.
That’s why
you are here washing the stones?
No, I’m going to grill the mushrooms.
When there was something
I wanted to say but couldn’t say,
I would put it in the vegetables
and eat the dish after I cook it.
Then I don’t need to think about it.
I don’t know if it will work this time.
Well, I’ll eat with you
after you cook it.
It’s better than eating alone.
Your Highness, it’s nice
to be your coroner.
I...
What’s this?
Your Highness, what’s wrong?
These stones seem to be glowing.
These are just ordinary stones.
There are a lot of stones like this
right here.
I remember the witch doctor said
that there is something like spar
inside these stones.
I don’t quite understand.
Anyway, these stones seem to glow
when being illuminated
by the light. It’s very beautiful.
Light?
Lord!
Damn! You scared me.
Can’t you keep your voice down?
I almost ruined the koi sculpture.
What’s the fuss about?
There is a letter from Guanling County
that they found the traces of
a fugitive wanted by the court,
Xu Rugui.
Give the order immediately
and catch the wanted the criminal now!
Yes!
Hold on.
Is Commandery Prince An
still in Pingle Town?
Yes.
I also heard that he dug
a woman’s grave.
Dug...?
Didn’t he come to find his father?
Why did he dig a woman’s grave?
Does he want to get a dead stepmother
for his dead father?
That’s funny, My Lord.
By the way, My Lord.
You don’t need to worry about
the investigation into
minting coins privately.
Why is that?
The man drinking with you
and Magistrate Zheng in the County
Office of Guanling on that day
is not Commandery Prince An.
Who is that person then?
That’s the Vice Minister of
the Court of Judicial Review, Jing Yi.
Jing Yi?
Vice Minister Jing is just an idle
young master.
He rarely does anything serious.
When you had drinks on that day,
I guess he was just making fun of
you and Magistrate Zheng.
What do you know?
There must be a plan.
The Jing family is a family of foxes.
They are best at
finding out the truth through
expressions and voices.
I dealt with Jing Yi in the way
I should deal with Commandery Prince An.
It’s wrong.
It’s all wrong.
It’s all wrong!
They messed with me
must because they want to
step in the coin minting thing.
Keep an eye on Guanling County.
Let me know if you have any news!
Yes!
(Princess Xiping’s Mansion)
Greetings to Your Grace.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Grace.
You came early this morning.
Did anything happen to Jinyu?
Your Grace, rest assured.
Commandery Prince An
and General Xiao are doing well.
There is something
His Highness asked me to show you.
He is in a hurry
so I came in early in the morning.
Please forgive me for
disturbing your rest.
What is it? Bring it to me.
Yes.
(To Mother)
His Highness is investigating a case.
This hairpin belongs to
a person involved in the case.
His Highness hopes that he can find out
who this person involved is
through this hairpin.
He said
the owner of this hairpin
should be a person of high status.
Maybe you can recognize it.
It looks familiar.
I got it.
This was a gift from my mother
to Madam Jing.
You mean the wife of Senior Jing?
Yes, it’s her.
Master.
Come in.
There is an urgent letter from Qianzhou.
(To Father)
Well...
Is it a hairpin?
It looks so familiar.
I have an exact same hairpin.
Really?
Yes.
I remember it.
When we got married,
Princess Xiping’s mother
gave me a pair of hairpins.
I kept one by myself
and gave the other one to someone else.
Wait
Look, does them look the same?
This is the style of young people.
I haven’t worn it for years.
Do you remember
whom you gave this hairpin to?
It’s been a long time.
I can’t remember it.
But,
I have a record of the things
I gave away.
I’ll tell you after I check it.
Go to find the housekeeper
and tell him
that I got slightly sick last night
and I’ll ask for leave
for the morning court.
You are not going to the court today?
Where are you going?
We have something to do.
We will be back soon.
No, you can go anywhere as you want.
But Chu Chu must stay.
Missy, you haven’t recovered yet.
Take the medicine
and take a good rest at home.
Brother, I’m recovered. I’m fine.
No, I said no.
Stay at home.
You are not allowed to go anywhere.
We have a very important thing to do.
I don’t care how important it is.
Go back with me.
Let her off!
She is my sister...!
She is a coroner of
the Three Judicial Offices!
I’m going to take her out
to handle a case.
You are also a public servant.
You should know what the crime is
to obstruct your superior’s work.
It’s very cloudy now.
What if it rains?
Well,
does the coroner In Guanling County
only go out to work
in sunny days?
You...!
Brother, I said I’m fine.
Just let me go.
I’m just like you.
We are both coroners
working for the government.
When you were working,
no matter what happened,
as long as Magistrate Zheng
asked you to go to the county office,
you never hesitated.
Why are you stopping me now?
I am also a coroner just like you.
Commandery Prince An asked me to work,
I will go no matter what happens.
Rest assured.
Since she is leaving with me,
I will take good care of her.
What happened yesterday
won’t happen again.
I can’t rest assured.
It will be too late if
what happened yesterday
happens again!
Let me ask you.
Where exactly are you taking Chu Chu to?
Why didn’t I hear
that there is a homicide in the county?
The homicide in the county
should be handled by the county office.
My work
is beyond the control
of the county office.
Don’t follow us secretly.
Otherwise I will handle it according to
the official principles.
You can try it if you are not afraid of
losing the qualification as a coroner.
Let’s go.
Brother, I’ll be back in a while.
Your Highness, don’t be angry.
Don’t harm your health because of it.
I’m not angry.
My brother isn’t usually like that.
I don’t know what’s wrong
with him today.
I guess he was scared by
what happened yesterday.
Don’t worry.
I’m not angry.
I said those words
because I don’t want him to follow up.
Didn’t you promise my father
that you will keep the secret for him?
If he follows us,
it will be inconvenient for us to talk.
He is not angry...
General Xiao, is he really not angry?
Since he said it, just take it.
All right.
What a stubborn man.
Grandpa, are you going to
send food to Xu...
Send food to that bandit?
Your father went to
the county office to work.
It’s time for a meal.
I’ll send the food to him.
Although he is a bad person
and he hurt Chu,
we still can’t starve him.
He committed a crime
and he will be punished
according to the law.
Grandpa, let me do it.
He is dangerous.
I can handle such a small thing.
Go to do what you should do.
Grandpa.
I also need to go there
and pick up a few things.
Let me do it.
Tell the two guards
that their meal is on the table.
Ask them to eat it when they have time.
Don’t let the food get cold.
Got it, go back to your room.
Sirs, it has been hard for you.
I’m here to bring him some food.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
Your meal is also ready.
It’s in the kitchen.
Hurry up and have a bite.
We can’t.
This person is really dangerous.
We can take turns to eat.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
I won’t untie him.
He can’t run away.
What’s more,
this kitchen is so close to here.
I’ll call you if he runs away.
Commandery Prince An
just left with Chu Chu
and that general
to investigate some case.
I’m afraid they will send someone back
and ask you to go with them.
It’s hard to do your job well
when you are starving.
I can’t afford the punishment
if they blame me.
I’m a little hungry.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
We will be back soon.
Okay.
Mr. Chu, be careful.
Got it, go ahead.
Please.
I want to ask you something.
I’ll take out the cloth from your mouth.
Don’t shout.
Let me ask you.
Are you Xu Zongfang?
You must be Chu He.
How do you know that?
Don’t worry about how I know that.
Hurry, untie the rope for me.
Chu Chu will be dead later.
What are you saying?
You just said
that Xiao Jinyu and his brother
took Chu Chu away.
They are going to kill Chu Chu.
But you are the one
who almost killed Chu Chu yesterday!
You are killing me.
Since you came here to ask me
if I am Xu Zongfang,
it means you know
that I am Chu Chu’s uncle,
right?
I was trying to take her away
to save her.
Don’t talk nonsense.
No one would...
No one would save a person in that way.
Didn’t Chu Chu tell you
that her biological father, Yun Yi,
is a criminal who rebelled with
the Military Commissioner of Jiannan
and killed the father of
Xiao Jinyu and Xiao Jinli?
Yesterday they opened the coffin of
Chu Chu’s biological mother,
which is my sister.
They must have known
the identity of Chu Chu’s
biological father.
I think they are going to
retaliate against Chu Chu
and kill her!
Well, I’ll go to find them.
Don’t!
Chu He, these two brothers are
highly powerful
and they have soldiers in hand.
If you go now,
you are taking down
the whole Chu family!
I’ll do it. Let me go now.
I’m Chu Chu’s uncle.
I failed Chu Chu
and her mother at that time.
But right now,
I will protect her with my life.
What are you waiting for?
It will be too late
if you don’t untie me now.
Let’s take the food back and eat
lest anything should happen.
I’ll go back, too.
Are you sure you can save Chu Chu?
Of course.
Hurry up.
Well...
You two finished your meal so fast.
I think we should eat here.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
You can leave him to us now.
Okay, I’ll leave.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
General! Your Highness!
Has anyone been here?
No one has been here.
Brother, give it to me.
Keep watch at the door.
Don’t let anyone approach.
Rest assured.
Chu Chu, close the door.
Okay.
Your Highness.
Why do you only place
these four chess pieces?
I played twice with my elder brother
and I played once with Jing Yi.
Every time at the end of the game,
there would always be
these four chess pieces
in these four positions.
Is there anything special about
these four positions?
I haven’t figured it out yet.
But when I saw those illuminated stones,
these chess pieces,
and the layout of this room,
I still feel that something is missing,
The layout of this room?
These are painted by the witch doctor.
Does he like painting a lot?
He didn’t like painting
that much before.
But during the time before he left,
he just somehow
started to like painting.
He didn’t paint anything else
but mountains and trees.
These paintings are all scenes
of Guanling County
The mountain is Phoenix Mountain.
The water is Yong’an River.
Light...
♪Nothing can♪
♪Stop me♪
♪From missing you♪
♪All the time♪
♪It’s cold at night♪
♪Everything changes in the world♪
♪I have affection for nothing♪
♪But your hug♪
♪Close the eyes♪
♪Meet again♪
♪By your side♪
♪I brush your hair gently♪
♪Life is long but love isn’t♪
♪There’s regret in the world♪
♪Only with you around♪
♪We’ll never lose contact♪
♪The moment♪
♪You smile♪
♪Let me cherish it for good♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I care about my life♪
♪I’m not old yet♪
♪I still love you♪
♪At last I settle down for you♪
♪I can rely on you all my life♪
♪Hope we’ll spend our lives sweetly♪