Wu Chen poisoned soldiers
and fabricated the strange things.
He also poisoned General Leng
with cinnabar.
You traitor!
Hou Bin was murdered.
Wu Chen was killed and silenced.
Duke Chang is ending his plot.
He poisoned Leng Peishan
with noxious mugwort stick,
murdered Feng Jie
and kept Leng Peishan’s condition
from His Majesty
to stall for time.
I’m sure he uses such a plan
because he wants big trouble
in Leng Peishan’s army.
General Leng, you think
Wu Chen was the only murderer?
What do you mean? I’m all my ears.
Wu Chen is a civil official
who isn’t your enemy at all.
Why did he take so much trouble
to poison you?
And why did he poison soldiers
at this moment
to make such a big trouble?
Even if he finished his plan,
you died,
your soldiers fell into chaos,
what benefits could he get
for himself?
You think someone wants
to take over my troop?
Behind Wu Chen,
there must be
a long and thorough plan.
I’m afraid
the plan is coming to an end.
So, he doesn’t need
to poison you anymore.
Coming to an end?
You mean
they’ll take over my troop soon?
General Leng, have you heard of a case
about illegal copper coins in Qianzhou?
Illegal copper coins?
We seldom need copper coins
in the army
and there’s been much trouble lately.
I haven’t heard about
what happened in Qianzhou.
Before coming here,
we crashed a hideout
for illegal copper coins
and arrested Prefect Li Zhang.
Hardly had we arrested him
when some of your soldiers
set fire to his mansion?
What?
I didn’t send any soldiers.
Oh,
Hou Bin sent some soldiers to Qianzhou
for material purchase.
But Hou Bin died.
What exactly happened?
General Leng,
do you recognize them?
I do.
Hou Bin recruited them from bandits
six months ago.
The other day, they escaped
during the training outside the camp
because they couldn’t bear
the hardship.
You met them?
Prefect Li’s neighbors identified that
your soldiers set fire
to Prefect Li’s mansion.
They’re two of the soldiers.
I guess they escaped
because they didn’t want me
to recognize them
after I came here.
If I guess correctly,
someone must have coordinated with them.
General Leng,
there’s another man hiding in your army
who’s about to make trouble at any time.
Are you interested in catching him
with me?
=The Imperial Coroner=
=Episode 30=
Turn him over.
Yes.
Come on, Chu Chu.
Newly cooked ﻿white plum cakes.
They’re still hot.
Perfect timing.
Put the cakes on him.
All right.
Done.
After the cakes on put on him,
we need to wait for a while.
I’ll guard here.
Miss Leng, go have some rest.
How can I rest when you don’t?
Besides,
His Highness urged me
to keep you company.
Your Highness. General.
How’s it going? Have you got anything?
Don’t be anxious. It’ll be done soon.
Bruises?
He didn’t have bruises
when he was taken out of the well.
He was drowned in the well.
The water is cold.
And he just died.
Bruises on his corpse
can hardly appear directly.
Normally,
they appear in one or two days.
But if we want
to see the bruises earlier,
we can steam the corpse
on the newly burned pit for a while,
put some paper bathed in wine vinegar
where there might be bruises,
and put the hot white plum cakes.
If there’re real bruises,
they’ll appear.
(Bruises on the back and neck)
Your Highness, this bruise proves that
someone knocked him out
and drowned him in the well.
(Drowned in the well)
He’s the only man who could do it.
Who?
What an easy and effective way
to recognize friends and enemies
with the red ribbon!
You’re awesome, Your Highness.
You even predicted that
rebels would get changed
before the fight.
It’s not hard to predict.
When two groups of men fight
in the same clothes,
they’ll get accidentally injured
without some striking changes
on their clothes.
Go.
Your Highness, how did you know
Zhao Jie was the murderer?
Time.
Time?
The time when he killed Wu Chen.
Last night when we searched for Wu Chen,
Zhao Jie came very late.
General Leng, I was having a bath
and I’m late.
We thought he was late
because he was having a bath.
But after Chu Chu found something fishy
on Wu Chen’s corpse,
I asked Zhao Jie’s guard
outside his camp.
The guard told me that
he was having a bath for one hour.
During that,
he didn’t ask for more hot water.
Last night, I noticed his hands.
After being bathed in water
for one hour,
(Bathed in water)
(Skin on hands)
his hands should have looked pale
or had winkles.
That’s it.
When he said he was having a bath,
he was finding an excuse.
In fact, it was when
he killed Wu Chen.
That was the time.
Kill him!
End the fight.
If we want to catch them all,
we must let Zhao Jie leave first.
Only when they think they can win,
they’ll come out together.
Upon hearing the horn,
General Leng’s closest soldiers
will fight back and besiege them,
so that none of the rebels can escape.
Zhao Jie!
You traitor! Surrender yourself!
This room looks neat
and nothing seems special.
What are we looking for?
As the supreme commander
of the rebel plan,
(The Book of Songs)
Zhao Jie must have chances
to contact his superior directly.
We may find some clues here
about his superior.
Your Highness,
are you sure Duke Chang is his superior?
Anyway,
Zhao Jie isn’t the man
who manipulates the whole plan.
He doesn’t have ability or chance
to make Li Zhang work for him.
He isn’t able to make trouble
in Chang’an, either.
So far,
we’ve only arrested chess pieces.
We still don’t know
where the chess player is.
After Hou Bin died,
Zhao Jie is the only man
who’s experienced and powerful enough
to take his place.
Once General Leng let him
be the Vice Military Commissioner,
he will tell people
General Leng is badly sick
and then he can take over the army.
Taking over the army forcibly
is Zhao Jie’s backup plan.
He didn’t expect us to find out Wu Chen.
So, he had to kill Wu Chen hastily.
Before that,
he might have written a letter
to his master
about the changes.
He...
He hasn’t sent the letter yet.
Let’s look for it, then.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
It’s the letter
Zhao Jie hasn’t sent yet?
Yes.
There’re ten patterns on it.
Some patterns are duplicate.
(4 7 3 1 5 10 8 6 2 9 8 10 7)
I think it’s a cipher letter
where patterns are used
to represent one to ten.
When there’re numbers,
there should be a decoding book.
It’s not as easy as the cipher letter
Prince Consort left us.
Expecting someone to decode it,
Prince Consort left us enough clues.
With it,
people will decode it
unless they’re idiots.
But Zhao Jie doesn’t want anyone
to decode it.
If he puts the decoding book
in his mind,
how can we decode it?
Even if Zhao Jie has a great memory,
he won’t remember
such an important thing
only with his mind.
He can only remember the patterns
representing ten numbers.
He must have a decoding book
to translate the numbers into words.
(The Book of Songs)
This is the decoding book.
The Book of Songs?
Other books of his
are mainly about military
or national policies.
They haven’t been read for a long time.
He often read the Book of Songs.
There’re over 300 poems in it,
concerning astronomy, geography,
phenology and folk custom.
(Sundial, compass)
(Sweet Green Rice Ball, lion dance)
The words are abundant enough
for basic communication.
Your Highness, other books on the shelf
also look clean.
How do you know
they haven’t been read for a long time?
They look clean,
because Zhao Jie is
a senior military officer.
Cleaners come often.
But cleaners
only dust the cover of the books,
instead of inside pages.
The weather is damp in the Southwest.
After a long time,
an unopened book will be musty.
If it’s not opened for years,
there’ll be mildews.
Three volumes of the Book of Songs
aren’t musty.
Their edges are worn out, too.
(Often read with worn-out edges)
So, he must have often read them.
Your Highness, you have a sharp nose.
It smells really musty.
We’ve found the decoding book.
But we don’t know
how the patterns match the numbers.
Ten patterns represent ten numbers.
There should be...
3.6288 million types of permutations.
Ye... yes.
(4 7 3 1 5 10 8 6 2 9 8 10 7)
(Wu failed, I killed him. Won’t join you
in Chang’an as scheduled.)
But only one permutation
can translate the numbers
into relevant words.
If we keep trying,
when can we find the right permutation?
(Wu...)
Your Highness, you’re awesome!
As long as you can
thoroughly recite the Book of Songs,
you’ll figure out the words, too.
(Wu failed, I killed him. Won’t join you
in Chang’an as scheduled.)
I’m too old to move quickly.
Be careful.
Grandfather, have some water.
All right.
Grandfather, are you alright?
It should be me.
What?
It should be me who died.
Grandfather,
after the problem is solved,
let’s go back home.
Let’s go back to Chang’an.
There’re the best doctors in Chang’an.
They’ll cure you.
My silly granddaughter,
don’t take the doctor’s words seriously.
Can I really live
as long as the doctor says?
Can’t you just listen to me once?
All right. All right.
Yue,
something in this world matters more
than keeping us alive.
Or Commandery Prince An
wouldn’t have come here.
You wouldn’t have come here
with him, either.
It’s unrelated at all.
What does it have anything to do
with your disease?
All right, Yue.
Just take care of yourself.
Don’t bother about me.
General.
How’s it going, Jinyu?
Have you found something?
It’s what Zhao Jie said
in the letter to his superior.
Wu failed. I killed him.
Won’t join you in Chang’an as scheduled.
It meant Wu Chen failed and was killed.
Join you in Chang’an? Join?
I’m afraid
there’s another group of rebels.
They picked a date
to join each other in Chang’an.
We’d better find the detailed list.
Even if we can’t,
we should estimate a number.
Otherwise, people in Chang’an
can hardly deal with them.
Our priority is
to interrogate the captured rebels.
Jing Yi, go interrogate them.
He doesn’t need to go.
They were all executed.
What?
They were bandits.
General Leng didn’t kill them,
because he had pity on them
who did bad things for a living.
In case they hurt common people,
he recruited them.
About this,
soldiers have a lot of criticism.
They made trouble again.
If General Leng didn’t
kill them immediately,
he could hardly
convince his subordinates.
All right. I have no job now.
None of them is alive.
Your Highness, let me have a try.
What do you mean?
Let me do the autopsy.
Now that they’re dead,
you should let me find clues
from their corpses.
They look like soldiers
who have received training for years,
but we may find traces of old lives
in their internal organs or skeletons.
If I can do the autopsy,
I may find some clues.
All right. Do the autopsy.
In whatever way you want.
Brother, take her there immediately.
All right.
(Antique Store)
It’s a pleasure to see you, Eunuch Qin.
Sorry I haven’t welcomed you.
I’m sorry.
Are you an idiot?
I told you this is...
My subordinates bothered you
the other day.
Please kindly forgive them.
Search the place carefully!
Yes!
You! What...?
-Go.
-Yes. Yes.
Show me all your purchasing lists
of this year.
(Account Book)
These things look like imperial stuff.
I’ll take them back for inspection.
If they’re not, I’ll return them to you.
This one looks like
an imperial thing, too.
It doesn’t matter, Eunuch Qin.
The Ruyi you gave me...
I had it discerned very carefully.
It’s quite a precious thing. Thank you.
It’s just a little gift.
It’s quite my honor
that you accept it.
The words carved on the copper Ruyi
look quite interesting.
Yeah.
I’m interested in that.
May I have a word with you?
Sure. Sure.
It’s my honor.
Come, please.
Please stay, Eunuch Sun.
Come this way, please.
I...
Come, please.
Tell me. Where’s Xu Rugui?
Don’t worry, Eunuch Qin.
When Xu Rugui first
came back to Chang’an,
he was dying.
Luckily, he struggled to live.
After a period of treatment,
he can talk now.
Just get to the point.
I’m quite busy with palace business
and I don’t have time
for a useless talk!
You served three emperors
and you investigated it a few times.
Then you should know
what Duke Chang suffered
in Qianzhou, right?
Duke Chang?
It’s said that a group of bandits
attacked his mansion in Qianzhou.
His family were slaughtered.
Everyone in his mansion was killed.
No one stayed alive.
Not bandits.
What did you say?
They weren’t bandits?
It wasn’t bandits
who slaughtered Duke Chang’s family,
but an official army from the Palace?
Official army?
How did you know that?
Duke Chang witnessed that.
His Highness exchanged clothes
with his study companion
and hid among corpses
so that he survived.
He never forgets such a miserable scene.
I see.
But what does it concern me?
Eunuch Qin,
His Highness knows that
you’re caring for him.
He also wants to talk to you
about old affairs.
But it’s not convenient for him
to come now.
So, I’m asked to entertain you
to resolve the misunderstanding
that we sold imperial objects
and also to reassure you.
When His Highness
takes care of Xu Rugui,
it’ll do no harm to you.
You’re threatening me?
I don’t dare to.
Eunuch Qin,
His Highness wants to cooperate with you
to kill the tyrant,
take back the throne belonging to him
and restore our nation.
We rely on you to do such a great thing!
Cheers.
Now that His Highness wants cooperation,
shouldn’t I meet him first?
He’s been waiting for you.
He’s in Chang’an?
Who’s that?
It’s me, Master. I’m Mingde.
Master.
Aren’t you on duty today?
Why are you coming here,
instead of serving His Majesty?
Don’t get angry, Master.
Last night, His Majesty had a cold.
When he got up this morning,
he felt sick
and he was angry.
He kicked me out
when he didn’t want to see me.
Master,
we’re going to make Duke Chang
the emperor.
Why don’t you do away
with the present emperor?
What do you need your head for?
To make you look like a human?
Please enlighten me, Master.
The present emperor
is quite a tough man.
He pretended to be insane
and fooled everyone.
Now, he’s trying
to suppress our division.
He sounded us out from time to time.
Cunning Jing Zhi is also making trouble
with the other officials.
Do you think
we can dethrone him so easily?
If we don’t act carefully
and make him realize something,
we’ll be killed first!
Serve His Majesty carefully.
Our priority is
to kill Xiao Jinyu and his men
in case he ruins the big plan
Duke Chang and I have.
Don’t worry, Master.
I’ll make careful arrangements.
I won’t let Xiao Jinyu come back alive.
All right. Go get it done.
Yes.
Today, I come to you,
for a clear answer.
The soldier from Qianzhou...
Who’s he?
Don’t worry, General Leng.
He isn’t a bad man.
I certainly know he isn’t.
My granddaughter looks at him
in the exact way
her mother looked at her father.
Could he be Vice Minister Jing Yi,
the son of Senior Jing?
You have sharp eyes, General Leng.
So, he really is.
I hear that
Jing Yi is good at identifying lies.
Do you disguise him like that
and put him in my military clinic
so that he can get more intel?
It’s an expedient.
No offence, General Leng.
Please understand.
Your Highness.
Chu Chu, what have you got?
Your Highness, it’s so weird.
What have you got?
General Xiao, are you sure
they’re recruited bandits?
Yes. I’m quite sure.
No way.
Not all of them are bandits.
Not all of them?
What are they, then?
Soldiers.
Soldiers who had been trained for years.
No way!
I picked ten corpses
of different batches of recruitments.
Then I found that
four of them were trained in the army.
They never lived as bandits.
They used to be bandits
many years ago.
It’s normal
when you can’t find such traces.
It’s not.
His Highness said that
there would be traces of any action.
There would be traces with bodies, too.
No one can easily hide
what a life he used to live.
His body would record everything.
If they’re real bandits,
what traces should be recorded?
Bandits run about in the mountain.
(Leg)
So, they have strong shanks
(Heart)
and a strong heart.
Their patellae are usually worn out
with frequent injuries and sprains.
There’re traces of recovery
on their skeletal muscles
(Fractures on arms and legs)
after they have fractures.
But among the ten men,
only six have such features.
They were obviously bandits
for a long time.
The other four men
(Unknown)
have some features
like Military Commissioner’s soldiers.
No way!
They were definitely recruited
from the den of bandits.
Brother, I remember you said that
bandits in Qianzhou
not only caused trouble
to Military Commissioner’s army,
but also disturbed the battalion
of Qianzhou Army.
Is that so?
Yes.
Qianzhou Army isn’t like us.
They never fight hard with the bandits.
When they robbed Qianzhou Army,
they snatched money and food.
Did they also snatch soldiers?
Snatch soldiers?
They did, as I heard.
Maybe soldiers were taken away
to do labor work.
When failing to defeat them,
did Qianzhou Army keep recruiting
more soldiers?
I’m not sure about that.
Your Highness, you mean...?
Brother, go get the recruitment record
of Qianzhou Army
with my official seal.
All right. I’ll be on my way.
Eunuch Qin.
Go. Go.
Minister Han.
Eunuch Qin.
His Majesty forgot to tell you something
when he talked to you.
He asked me to wait here for you
so that I would bring you the message.
Minister Han,
may I have a word with you?
Eunuch Qin, just get to the point.
Minister Han,
I told on Princess Xiping to you
the other day.
Do you not remember it at all?
I’m still checking on that.
What?
With two witnesses,
you still doubt that?
Eunuch Qin,
I’ve verified
the two ladies.
They did work for Princess Xiping.
But you want to tell on Princess Xiping
with some useless words
from two ladies?
Even if you report to His Majesty,
Princess Xiping will defend herself
with a clever talk.
It’s a big crime to deceive His Majesty.
I can’t be too careful.
You mean there isn’t enough evidence
to close the case?
Well, please take care of the case
and make further investigation.
But I’m telling you.
What’s faked can’t be true.
You’ll find out something.
Minister Han,
His Majesty has drafted a decree
to get Commandery Prince An back
to Chang’an.
You must hurry up.
Let me remind you.
To do something big,
you must be daring and ruthless!
Don’t show petty kindness!
Trying to fob me off?
♪Nothing can♪
♪Stop me♪
♪From missing you♪
♪All the time♪
♪It’s cold at night♪
♪Everything changes in the world♪
♪I have affection for nothing♪
♪But your hug♪
♪Close the eyes♪
♪Meet again♪
♪By your side♪
♪I brush your hair gently♪
♪Life is long but love isn’t♪
♪There’s regret in the world♪
♪Only with you around♪
♪We’ll never lose contact♪
♪The moment♪
♪You smile♪
♪Let me cherish it for good♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I care about my life♪
♪I’m not old yet♪
♪I still love you♪
♪At last I settle down for you♪
♪I can rely on you all my life♪
♪Hope we’ll spend our lives sweetly♪