Xu Rugui used Chu Chu’s identity
and induced Chu He to
help him escape.
I don’t know if he is alive now.
I am a survivor of the rebellious party.
But Commandery Prince An
jumped into the river to save me
without hesitation.
I didn’t realize how special
Chu Chu is for me.
But Chu He is also...
You must go home when I ask you to.
If you really see yourself as
the coroner of Three Judicial Offices,
you must follow my orders.
If you think of my words
as unworthy of your attention,
you shouldn’t keep working for me.
Three Judicial Offices will be fine
with one less coroner.
Come on, Miss Chu.
Let’s go, come on.
Three Judicial Offices will be fine
with one less coroner?
You too. Out.
=The Imperial Coroner=
=Episode 19=
Take it.
Come again.
I won’t charge you if it’s not tasty.
General Xiao, what’s wrong
with His Highness?
He...
Is he angry with me
because I jumped into the water
to save my brother?
-I’m good at swimming.
-Take a look.
He saw it.
Do you only see Chu He as your brother?
Of course.
What about Commandery Prince An?
What do you think of him?
I think of him as a prince.
Umbrella!
General Xiao, what do you want to say?
Forget it, it’s too complicated
to be explained in a few words.
Miss Chu!
Deputy Magistrate Tan.
Is my brother awake?
General Xiao.
Miss Chu, don’t worry.
It’s not about Chu He.
Miss Chu, I don’t know
if it is convenient for you
to have a few words with me.
Deputy Magistrate Tan,
what’s the matter?
Delicious rice noodles!
Since that thing happened
in Xu’s Mansion,
I always want to talk to you
but never get the chance.
Deputy Magistrate Tan,
you can just tell me.
When Xu Zongfang took you
to Xu’s Mansion,
there were only my father,
Xu Zongfang and you
in that room.
Now my father is gone.
Xu Zongfang is missing.
I can only ask you
about what happened on that day.
Well...
Miss Chu, my father died a tragic death.
As his son,
I don’t even know the cause.
I’ve been anxious during these days
and I don’t know how to face my mother.
Please let me know what happened.
Deputy Magistrate Tan, get up.
Xu Zongfang said that day
that he wanted to avenge my mother.
If you want to avenge your mother,
I can do it for you.
Then he killed Butler Tan.
My mother died an unfair death.
But I never wanted to
avenge her in such a way.
Miss Chu, don’t worry.
I don’t blame you at all.
Thank you for telling me the truth.
I hope you can do me another favor.
Please don’t tell
Commandery Prince An about
our conversation today.
Why?
I’m the Deputy Magistrate
and the son of the deceased.
It’s nothing wrong with asking that.
But for the sake of my career,
I think I should avoid
arousing suspicion.
Okay.
Thank you, Miss Chu.
Vice Minister Jing.
Are you going home?
Yes.
From the County Office to Xu’s Mansion,
you shouldn’t take this way.
Vice Minister Jing, do you have
any instructions?
I asked you to send out the message.
Why haven’t I gotten any news from you?
Vice Minister Jing,
I’ll let you know immediately
if I have any news.
Deputy Magistrate Tan, you should know
that I can tell if you are lying.
I... I dare not.
You got some news. But it’s not for me.
It’s for you, right?
Have you verified Chu Chu’s identity?
Senior Jing doesn’t
want to get you involved.
Please don’t waste his good intention.
What kind of things
that I can’t get involved in?
Are you going to...
Vice Minister Jing.
I’ve handled such matters many times.
Please don’t worry about it.
My family is preparing for the funeral
and there are a lot of things to do.
I should leave.
Your Grace.
Today I got a very interesting
endgame by chance.
I thought that you are
a master of chess,
so I’m here to consult you.
Have you ever seen such an endgame?
No, I haven’t.
Please, Senior Jing.
Please, Your Grace.
Senior Jing.
I remember when you
and your wife got married,
my mother
gave you a pair of lily hairpins
as the wedding gift.
I wonder if that pair of hairpins
is still in your mansion.
Your Grace, that’s
a hard question for me.
You know my wife well.
She bought a handful of
hairpins every time.
There are more hairpins in my mansion
than the chopsticks in the kitchen.
They all look the same.
How can I recognize it?
Why do you suddenly ask about that?
A few days ago
when I was at the flower market,
I saw someone wearing a similar one.
It just occurred to me.
I guess maybe Madam Jing
gave it to someone else.
I’m just curious.
I’ll ask her when I get back.
Then I’ll let you know.
I know you are quite
worried about
the marriage of General Xiao
and Leng Peishan’s daughter.
I want to give you a piece of advice.
I hope you can make this marriage
happen as soon as possible.
A good marriage is fated.
Why should we rush it?
A good relationship is fated.
But human effort is the decisive factor.
This matter should be decided
sooner than later.
Thank you for your concern.
I’ll find a master and see
if their dates of birth
and eight characters match.
Then I’ll discuss this with the Emperor.
Your Grace, you are superb in chess.
I’m truly impressed.
You are flattering me.
Stop looking.
You are in Guanling Yamen now.
Why am I in Guanling Yamen?
Chu Chu?
Where’s Chu Chu?
I want to see Chu Chu.
I want to see my sister!
Where is my sister?
Do you still see her as your sister?
Of course she is my sister.
Could it be...
Didn’t Chu Chu tell you
that her biological father, Yun Yi,
killed Xiao Jinyu
and Xiao Jinli’s father?
They must want to take revenge on her.
You killed my sister?
Listen,
if you dare do anything to my sister,
I will fight you with my life!
Fight me with your life?
Fight me
with this?
You...
You keep saying
that Chu Chu is your sister.
That’s how you
put your sister in danger?
Listen,
Chu Chu is at home now,
telling your family
that you are safe.
She is fine.
But she almost got killed in the river
because of you.
Commandery Prince An.
I did this all by myself.
It has nothing to do with Chu Chu.
It has nothing to do with my family.
What did you do?
I...
I heard
the man who kidnapped Chu Chu
is her uncle, Xu Zongfang.
I wanted to ask him
if he is Chu Chu’s family
and who else there is
in Chu Chu’s family.
But...
He told me
Chu Chu’s father
is the rebel who killed your father.
You two took Chu Chu out
to kill Chu Chu.
You just took that bandit’s words?
I didn’t.
But I worried...
I worried
that you would imprison Chu Chu
and interrogate her
if you know it.
It happened many years ago.
What can you find out?
His words were clear and logical.
If you take his words
and believe that Chu Chu
is the child of your enemy,
she will be wronged.
That’s why you gave him
this filing blade
and help him escape?
Chu Chu is my sister.
She is innocent.
I have to save her.
You are putting her in danger!
Chu He, even you don’t trust my conduct,
you should have considered
the possibility
that the bandit was lying
and inducing you to untie him.
What you did is putting Chu Chu
in the position of being disloyal!
If what the bandit said is true
and you helped him take away Chu Chu,
then Chu Chu will be doubly guilty.
Everyone in the Chu family
will be punished.
If that bandit managed to escape,
killed everyone in the Chu family
and killed innocent people,
can you afford such a result?
Can Chu Chu afford it?
I...
As a coroner working
in the County Office,
you are also a public servant.
But you acted recklessly,
you don’t deserve to be called
a faithful and upright subject
as Chu Chu said.
You kept saying
that what you did is for Chu Chu.
Do you have the nerve
to say it again in front of Chu Chu?
Commandery Prince An.
I was too worried to think clearly.
You can punish me
as you want.
Please don’t punish Chu Chu
and my family.
I’m glad you know your mistake.
As a matter of fact,
Chu Chu knows
what that bandit said
and she told me everything.
What did Chu Chu tell you?
Chu Chu and I are both public servants.
Chu Chu trusts me
and I trust her.
I will handle it impartially
and clarify the truth.
I won’t wrong Chu Chu.
You can rest assured.
You must also remember
not to do such stupid things again.
Otherwise you won’t be
the only one to be punished.
I won’t.
I won’t do it again.
Let me ask you,
how did you fall into the river?
After I gave the filing blade
to Xu Rugui,
I kept an eye on the coffin shop.
I found Xu Rugui
escaped after killing people.
There were also two bandits chasing him.
Did you fight with them?
No, no.
I followed them from a distance.
They were particularly cautious
and I was almost spotted.
Then I slipped
and fell into the river.
Did you see
where they were heading for?
The northeast.
It seemed to be the direction
of Phoenix Mountain.
Get up first.
Thank you, Commandery Prince An.
What you did is ridiculous,
but you sincerely regretted
and almost got killed in the river,
I think you have learned your lesson.
I won’t give you any serious punishment.
Let me ask you one thing.
You must answer me truthfully.
Please go ahead, I’ll be honest.
I heard from Magistrate Zheng earlier
that the bridge between
Guanling County and the outside
was built five years ago.
Before that,
it was very difficult to get in
or leave Guanling County.
Is it true?
Yes, it’s true.
The Prefect granted the money
to build the bridge.
It was a great thing that benefited
everyone in the county.
Do you still remember
whether the bridge was finished
when the witch doctor
living in the back of your house left?
Not yet.
I remember it clearly.
My family also found it strange.
The witch doctor’s legs
didn’t work well.
He couldn’t leave
Guanling County at all.
How did he disappear suddenly?
Your Grace.
You must be tired after playing chess
with Senior Jing for so long.
I’ve asked someone
to prepare some hot water
and give you a bath later
to relieve your fatigue.
I’m afraid
that Jing Zhi came here
not just to play chess with me.
I can’t help but feel worried.
I think
Senior Jing came to urge you
to promote Miss Leng’s marriage.
The more he urges me,
the more it means
this marriage won’t work.
I hope Mr. Xue can
talk the Emperor out of this idea
during their trip to Qianzhou.
Your Grace, are you worried
that it will involve
General Leng’s military power
if General Xiao and Miss Leng
get married?
Not all because of this.
If we only consider the interests
involved in this marriage,
it’s safer to let Leng Yue marry Jinyu.
It won’t involve the military power
of the Leng clan
and can make the Leng clan
continue to support Jinyu in the court.
What I care about is still Yue.
She has been following Jinyu
since she was a child.
She does everything
Jinyu tells her to do.
I guess she has fallen for Jinyu
for a long time.
It’s just Jinyu cares about nothing else
but the official affairs.
I always wanted to find a chance
and talk to Jinyu about it.
Tell him not to fail Yue.
Unexpectedly, such a thing happened
before I get the chance.
Now Yue is going to be
Jinyu’s sister-in-law.
Your Grace, relax.
We have Mr. Xue’s full support
in this matter.
Besides, Commandery Prince An
is also in Qianzhou.
He has been thoughtful
since he was young.
If he knows it,
he will figure out a way
to solve all the problems.
Have you asked Wu Jiang?
Is there any news about Jinyu recently?
Yes.
Wu Jiang said that His Highness
is at Miss Chu’s house in Guanling.
Who?
The female coroner.
Coroner?
Have you met that coroner?
What does she look like?
She...
She is delicate.
What if compare her with Leng Yue?
How can they be compared?
Miss Leng is one of the most
beautiful girls in Chang’an.
That girl is cuter than Miss Leng.
But in terms of appearance,
she is just delicate.
There is no way to
compare her with Leng Yue.
Cute?
I mean, could it be that Jinyu
just likes cute girls?
Chu Chu.
His Highness always protects me.
He said I’m the best coroner.
But why did he say that to me?
You must go home when I ask you to.
If you really see yourself as
the coroner of Three Judicial Offices,
you must follow my orders.
If you think of my words
as unworthy of your attention,
you shouldn’t keep working for me.
Three Judicial Offices will be fine
with one less coroner.
Chu Chu.
Father.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I’m just thinking
where that man
could escape to.
Chu Chu.
You know who that person is, right?
Yes.
That man is my uncle.
You also know it, right?
Your brother accidentally
heard a few words said by the people
around that lord.
When I sent water to them last night,
I took a look at that person.
Although his eyes were covered
and his mouth gagged,
I can still recognize him.
That’s Master Xu.
I didn’t dare to tell your brother
because I was afraid that he couldn’t
hold back his temper
and make a big deal out of it.
I only told your grandpa.
Chu Chu, don’t think too much about it.
Xu Zongfang is Xu Zongfang. You are you.
No matter what he did,
it has nothing to do with you.
Do you know it?
Yes, I do.
Father, don’t worry.
I won’t bring shame on the Chu clan.
Of course you won’t.
You are Commandery Prince An’s
coroner now.
You make the Chu clan proud,
right?
Don’t think too much about it.
Your Highness, Miss Leng
and Magistrate Zheng are here.
Your Highness.
Magistrate Zheng,
please wait inside for a while.
Yes.
What’s wrong?
How do you know something is wrong?
If there is nothing wrong,
you should send the medicine
to the kitchen first.
You wouldn’t come here to stop me.
What is it?
There is a little thing
I’m curious about.
I want to ask you casually.
Then I will listen casually.
Your Highness.
Does the Deputy Magistrate Tan Gui
have any relation with you?
What relation?
Like
is he your confidant or your spy?
Why do you ask that?
Answer my question first.
No.
Really?
If he is my confidant,
how come I didn’t know
Xu Rugui is Xu Zongfang until now?
Alright, you just casually asked me.
And I’ve casually heard you.
Just take the medicine to the kitchen
and ask someone to decoct it for Chu He.
Get him some food.
Let him go home
after he gets better
lest the Chu family should worry.
Your Highness.
Don’t you ask me why I asked you that?
You will tell me when you figure it out.
You already know it?
Know what?
Know that Jing Yi has been stalking me
and sending message to Chang’an
behind my back?
Or know
that you found out the person Jing Yi
has been meeting behind my back
is Tan Gui?
You know it.
It’s nothing strange that I know it.
Jing Yi has been around me
for almost 20 years.
It’s too obvious for me what he did
and what he didn’t do.
He also knows if I know
what he did.
Your Highness, there must be
some misunderstanding here.
You know that Jing Yi
will never hurt you.
I know.
The strange thing is how you know it?
Have you been stalking him?
I...
When I was keeping an eye on Chu Chu,
I saw Jing Yi stalking you and Chu Chu.
I thought
Jing Yi was after Chu Chu.
I’m worried that the Jing family
would do something to Chu Chu,
so I stalked him a few times.
Earlier, I found out by chance
that he met someone alone.
I didn’t see that person’s face,
but I saw the footprints.
When I saw Tan Gui’s just now,
I realized that he was
the person Jing Yi met.
Your Highness, what is Jing Yi doing?
Don’t worry.
What Jing Yi needs to do in his life
is not only the work I give him.
It’s just like I won’t let him do
all the work.
It’s the same.
When it’s necessary.
he will give me an explanation.
Your Highness, thank you.
For what?
Thank you for trusting Jing Yi.
Why should you thank me?
Your Highness, you...
Your Highness.
Forgive me for interrupting you.
Just say it.
Something weird happened.
I don’t know what to do.
So I’m here to ask you for advice.
Chu He asked me for
flogging.
Ask you for what?
Flogging…
He wants to get beaten.
He asked me to beat him.
Why does he want to get beaten?
I don’t know.
I asked him why,
but he wouldn’t tell me.
He said he deserves it.
Your Highness,
what should I do?
Just give him what he wants.
What kind of thing is that
to give him flogging?
He asked for it.
Flog him as many times
as he asks.
Don’t beat him too hard.
Just let him suffer a little bit.
Remember not to hurt his bones.
Yes.
Also remember,
don’t let others know
what I just said to you.
What are you waiting for?
You’ve never been here.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I think I understand. I understand.
I understand.
Your Highness, does the medicine
for Chu He need to be decocted?
(Shangyang Gate)
Minister Han is perceptive indeed.
That female coroner
only took an exam
in the Three Judicial Offices,
and you found out her identity
as a survivor of the rebellious party
through the details.
Yeah.
Minister Han is great indeed.
Be careful of your words.
She is suspected of
being the daughter of a rebel.
We still need the Emperor
to make the final decision.
However,
as public servants,
we should always remember the teachings
of Commandery Prince An.
We can’t make any mistake
in this matter.
Otherwise,
he has a lot of ways
to teach us a lesson.
Yeah.
Commandery Prince An hasn’t realized
he opened the door to a dangerous person.
If it wasn’t for you to find out
who she is,
I’m afraid he can’t go back to
Chang’an being alive.
Commandery Prince An hired
the daughter of a rebel.
After he returns to Chang’an,
he should punish himself
for hiring a wrong person.
Yeah.
It’s just Xue Rucheng took the credit.
If he wasn’t ordered to
handle affairs in Qianzhou,
how would the Emperor ask him to
investigate it
and catch the rebels by the way?
He took the credit for nothing.
All right, no big deal.
A person points at the rabbit.
A dog catches the rabbit.
The Emperor
knows who makes what contributions.
We don’t need to take this credit.
Moreover,
the daughter of a rebel threatens
Commandery Prince An’s life.
Xue Rucheng
dares not neglect it.
It’s a good thing for us.
We don’t need to confront
the Commandery Prince An
and he saved us from
the hardship of the trip.
Why shouldn’t we feel happy about it?
Brilliant.
Yeah.
Hurry. Hurry up.
Set the meal.
Don’t delay the meal.
Minister Han.
Eunuch Qin.
Congratulations, you’ve found out
the survivor of the rebellious party.
This is what I should do.
Yeah.
What is this?
How can we eat this?
Eunuch Qin, did you
serve the wrong dishes?
Yeah.
That’s what you are going to eat today.
The Emperor said
it’s not easy for Tang to be peaceful.
You are the pillars of the country.
You should be prepared for danger
in times of peace.
Don’t forget His Majesty’s grace
and your responsibility
when you get cocky.
Minister Han, am I right?
Yeah.
All right, enjoy your meal.
Enjoy your meal.
It isn’t so much about
Han Ji taking the credit.
It’s about Han Ji
finishing this tricky matter for us.
You are right, Master.
Ever since the female coroner
came to Chang’an,
there hasn’t been one day
that is not troublesome.
After I get something useful out of her,
I’m going to vent all of my anger.
I won’t let her die easily.
Then you need to hurry up
and think about
how to kill her.
Listen,
it won’t take us long
to get her.
That’s great.
Xiao Jinli?
Leng Yue?
Why are you here?
I found him strange
when he stopped Miss Chu on the street
and asked her some questions.
A moment ago, I saw him
sneak out from the County Office.
I’m afraid he will do harm to you.
So I’ve been following him.
Then I saw him lying in ambush
near Chu’s house.
He followed Miss Chu all the way here
and tried to attack Miss Chu.
But I didn’t expect her to be Leng Yue.
Say it, what do you want to do?
I want to kill Chu Chu
to avenge my father!
No wonder.
You asked Miss Chu
how your father died.
She told me.
Then I told Commandery Prince An.
Miss Chu is clever.
She said it’s only when bad people
want to do bad things
that they don’t want
Commandery Prince An to know it.
You are really up to no good.
Jinyu, we’re on the same page this time.
You asked Leng Yue to dress as Chu Chu
in order to catch him, right?
Despicable. Shameless.
What did you say?
I’ll chop your head off.
Xiao Jinli, it has nothing
to do with you.
You’d better leave.
Why does it have nothing to do with me?
I just saved you.
Did I ask you to save me?
I...
All right.
We don’t need to keep it from him.
Keep me from what?
Tan Gui, you should know
why I got someone to dress as Chu Chu.
This method isn’t above-board.
But this is the only way
to get you out
and make things clear for you.
I don’t understand what you are saying.
You don’t understand?
You went to see Chu Chu
in front of Jinli on purpose,
and asked her mysteriously
about your father’s death.
You even told her
not to tell me about it
to make sure I would know it.
You asked about your father’s death.
In this way, whether you will
make it or not,
it can be the most powerful testimony
to explain why you want to kill Chu Chu.
What do you mean?
I don’t understand.
Enough!
Stop lying
at this point.
What you did is really shameful.
My family asked him to kill Chu Chu.
Vice Minister Jing, you can’t...!
Brother, no!
Xiao Jinli, are you crazy?
I’m sick of your Jing family’s
sneaky tactics.
Say it, what are you up to?
It has nothing to do
with Vice Minister Jing.
Shut up.
Say it, why do you want to
kill Miss Chu?
Say it! Why?
Commandery Prince An, General Xiao.
Chu Chu is the daughter of
the person who killed your father.
What?
Vice Minister Jing.
Do you still remember
the hairpin we rubbed?
The one Chu Chu’s mother gave to her.
Your mother recognized
the pattern on it.
She gave this hairpin
to a general’s wife as a wedding gift.
That general is Yun Yi, a subordinate of
the Military Commissioner of Jiannan.
Chu Chu is Yun Yi’s daughter,
which means she is
a survivor of the rebellious party.
After I passed the Imperial Examination,
I took Senior Jing as my master.
Then I went back to Qianzhou
to look for and get rid of
these fugitives
to avenge the Prince Consort.
Why are you stopping me?
Vice Minister Jing.
How should you explain to Senior Jing?
I don’t need to explain to him.
He wants to kill Chu Chu for someone
who was like a real brother to him.
I won’t let him kill Chu Chu
also for someone
who is like a real brother to me.
These are two different things.
But the feelings are the same.
My father knew I would do this.
That’s why he kept it from me
and asked you to do these things.
No need to say much. I trust you.
Commandery Prince An.
What Senior Jing did
is for avenging your father.
That’s your father!
Why are you protecting
your enemy’s daughter?
You can only protect her for a while.
Even I won’t say it,
and they won’t say it,
but someone else will
reveal her identity one day.
At that time,
you will be convicted of covering up
the survivor of the rebellious party.
What’s in that for you?
How should you face Prince Consort
and Princess Xiping?
General Xiao.
Are you also going to
let her get away with it?
Even she is a survivor
of the rebellious party,
it’s the County Office’s bushiness
to punish her.
Senior Jing can’t use lynching.
Deputy Magistrate Tan.
Since you work for Senior Jing,
you should know why I came to
the Southwest this time.
Senior Jing wants you to kill Chu Chu
to avenge my father.
But if my father wants you to
let her go,
are you willing to
put off killing Chu Chu
and tell Senior Jing about
the situation first?
You mean Prince Consort is still...?
♪Nothing can♪
♪Stop me♪
♪From missing you♪
♪All the time♪
♪It’s cold at night♪
♪Everything changes in the world♪
♪I have affection for nothing♪
♪But your hug♪
♪Close the eyes♪
♪Meet again♪
♪By your side♪
♪I brush your hair gently♪
♪Life is long but love isn’t♪
♪There’s regret in the world♪
♪Only with you around♪
♪We’ll never lose contact♪
♪The moment♪
♪You smile♪
♪Let me cherish it for good♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I care about my life♪
♪I’m not old yet♪
♪I still love you♪
♪At last I settle down for you♪
♪I can rely on you all my life♪
♪Hope we’ll spend our lives sweetly♪