(This drama series is fictional,
and the places, persons, organizations,)
(settings, and events depicted
have been fictionally created.)
(7 years ago)
It's you.
What was this doing in my car?
What's your excuse this time?
It's just what my mom did to my dad.
Why do you get upset over nothing?
I did it out of love.
You understand me, right?
Yoo Ji An.
There's nothing to understand.
This is a crime.
I'm going to the police tomorrow.
I can't overlook this...
even for your sake.
You can never report me.
Do you want to hear a secret?
(Episode 11, The Way I Love)
Are you sure about this?
You can't trust me?
How amazing.
(Yoo Ji An)
- What is it this time?
- Surprise.
Park Jun and now Jun Hyuk?
Impressive.
Tomorrow, she'll be a woman
of double scandal.
Are you prepared for that?
I don't care about anything,
but don't mess with Jun Hyuk.
I won't tolerate that.
(Jun Hyuk)
The person you have reached is
not available.
Please leave a message after the beep.
- What?
- Ma'am, have you seen this?
It's all over the social media.
What now?
(Is that the trainee next to Daniel?)
(Do we have a good-looking couple?)
What on earth is he doing?
("Who's Emily's Man in Scandal?")
("Emily, Love Triangle
with Daniel and Park Jun?")
(UNIS CEO Daniel
Emergency Press Conference)
You said Emily and Park Jun were...
old friends.
What does that say
about your relationship with her?
A rookie singer's double scandal.
And one of them is with her agency boss.
It's enough to get sued
by your investors, isn't it?
Do I look like...
someone that foolish and irresponsible
to you?
I'm not here to explain,
but to publicize the damage.
These two scandals are false,
and the person who fabricated
and leaked them is...
A who was wrongly known to be my ex.
Are you saying A wasn't your girlfriend
but a stalker?
That's right.
You even retired to remain silent.
Why are you revealing it now?
It's the same reason...
I remained silent seven years ago.
I have someone to protect.
How will you explain this picture?
I will show you...
a video to explain that.
You're here.
Isn't this awesome?
- Hello, CEO Han.
- Hey.
- Hurry up.
What took you so long?
We've been waiting for you forever.
To be honest, this is my first time.
Wait up.
Let's take it together.
Be careful.
Ho Yi, you look like a bird.
Nice weather.
Watch out or you'll fall.
Did you see this?
You scared me.
O Du Ri. Don't be distracted.
You must have fun.
What are you doing?
Girls, let's take a picture.
Ho Yi, join us.
Okay. Let's all take a picture together.
Everyone.
Soo Jin, can you get closer? Okay.
Hurry.
It's okay. I'm okay.
Again.
Here we go.
Ready.
V.
- Done?
- Done.
My goodness.
Come here, you.
It's nice to see them happy.
Get back here, you.
Thank you for helping me with this plan.
I wouldn't have dared to do it alone.
What's your plan now?
I'll help her accomplish what she wants.
And?
Just that for now.
Happy debut to you
Happy debut dear Element
Blow out on the count of three.
One, two, three.
(Congratulations on your debut
as Element.)
We recorded that recently...
That's our voice, right?
I knew you'd like it.
So I brought it
as soon as it was done mixing.
Don't be so happy yet.
We have one more thing to celebrate.
You're scheduled for a shoot.
Really?
Soo Jin.
- Why are you crying?
- Don't cry.
("Paper" by Lapillus)
Like paper paper
Give up on your emotions
Stale love, cut it out
This is our last page in pain
Give me the mic.
Get a seat.
Just tell me the number.
What? Press 8807.
Eight eight zero seven?
I'll liven up the mood.
("You're Of A Frugal Mind")
- What was that?
- Stop.
Give it to me.
What?
People who were bad at school
don't know how to have fun either.
Chan Mi?
Do you have to make us liven up the mood?
Jun Hee?
This is bad. Let's help him.
Seriously.
Let's go.
Ola
Say ola
Everybody say...
one, two, three, four.
Don't judge a book
By its cover
The look isn't everything
Don't judge me
By my appearance
Don't fall in love
Trust me
Get down get down
Come party wit uptown
Yes.
Get down get down
Come party wit uptown
Come out.
Come on.
- Seriously.
- No...
Ola
(A stalker who stalked the member
of UNIS' new girl group...)
(turns out to be Daniel's ex?)
(Complaint)
(Plaintiff Han Jun Hyuk)
What are you doing?
Do everything you can
to make him withdraw.
Why are you dragging me into your crime?
If there's anything you did wrong,
pay for your price.
- The same goes for you.
- What?
We're accomplices at least to Jun Hyuk.
Don't you get it?
CEO Han.
You can stop.
How can we stop?
Bothering you all these years
wasn't enough,
she's now going after our artists...
Can't you read the room?
- Who's the one tying him down here?
- You!
Stop it, Mother!
Is that what you're talking about?
That she's my mom?
You've used it once already.
Look who's talking.
What's so good
about what's already happened in the past?
It's over already.
Right.
If I gave up on my career to cover you up,
you should've stopped.
That's not how my heart works.
At first,
I was going to return to the US
after seeing your face.
But...
Anyway, I only wanted...
to get rid of that weird wench
next to you.
You better get Chairwoman Kim
out of your plan.
If you disclose it,
that will only be added to your crime.
I have nothing more to say.
- Jun Hyuk...
- If I call the police here,
it'll only worsen your situation.
Jun Hyuk...
You...
Did you...
No, right?
So you...
When did you know?
Jun Hyuk, when you...
When you retired...
Was that...
Was that because of me?
Don't worry.
Yoo Ji An can't disclose it.
She's not stupid.
No.
No, I will...
I will say it.
I will...
hold the press conference and confess it.
I will say everything,
so she has nothing on...
No.
I'll protect myself.
As I have always done.
No, Jun Hyuk...
I...
Is everything okay?
Thanks.
Don't forget.
If it's a mountain, you can climb it.
If it's a river, just cross it.
Life is not a big deal.
Okay. I'll follow you with trust.
You won't tell me what it's about, do you?
Right. I also have so many secrets
I haven't told you yet.
We're even now.
See you tomorrow.
Right. If you can't sleep,
drink jujube tea.
- I'll get going.
- Bye.
The person you have reached is
not available.
Please leave a message after the beep.
You may hang up after the message.
(Ms. O)
She can't be with him after what happened.
What are you doing?
That's harsh on your stomach.
For your information, I'm on your side.
What?
You're fighting with Daniel over Du Ri.
I know everything.
My motto is the winner by my side.
But this time, I'm on your side.
What?
Do I resemble your father or something?
Why do you keep talking about my father?
I miss him.
Do you miss your dad?
You said he only nagged at you
and blamed you.
It's better without him, isn't it?
I'm scared
that I might never see him again.
The only person who'd like me
as long as I eat well...
and stay out of trouble.
Who else is there other than my dad?
Even I consider myself weird.
He may have nagged at me,
but he never criticized me for once.
I've seen him wiping his tears
without showing me.
Gosh.
I only gave him a hard time.
What if I never get to see him again?
Why are you worried?
A parent would never leave his child.
A man shouldn't weep.
Don't hesitate. Just go for it.
My dad says...
if you do nothing,
nothing's going to happen.
You have to do something.
More than Daniel.
Do everything you want, Jun.
What are you doing?
Go see your dad.
How do you feel about being famous
even before the debut?
I'm not famous.
Noise marketing is still marketing.
Now that people know our names,
it's time to show them our skills.
Anyway, CEO Daniel is amazing.
Our trip was all planned.
A trap to catch the stalker.
I'm not sure about this.
It wasn't solely for us.
Did he take advantage of us?
Come on.
Are you saying
you don't want to go next time?
- Hello.
Wait.
Part A looks too plain.
Is there a way to make them stand out?
Let's reduce the movement...
and come up with a new theme.
Got it.
Let's start over.
("The Way I Love")
Okay.
Good.
You know what's nice?
That you all look different...
yet you have good teamwork.
Let's keep it up.
Yes.
Du Ri and Min A.
You were offbeat twice.
Okay.
I've never seen so many stars before.
The stars look closer and brighter...
when it's cold.
You know everything like a granny.
My father loved stars.
He dragged his body to the balcony...
when he could barely move...
and stared at the stars for a long time.
That's first.
Telling me about yourself.
Is that right?
What about you?
You never told me...
about your parents or siblings.
Not even about your dog.
It's not that I didn't. I couldn't.
Because I have none.
What do you mean?
What about your aunt?
She cares about you so much.
Care about me so much?
That's interesting.
I didn't know you could be wrong.
You know Chairwoman Kim...
doesn't care about anything...
other than singing.
Even if I were her son...
not a nephew,
things wouldn't have been any different.
You must be disappointed in your aunt.
I know what she's like.
I mean, I think I understand.
My biggest strength is... Well...
That I'm a loner.
I have no one to protect me...
or that I have to protect.
I was able to say I'd quit and leave...
for that reason.
Because I have no regrets in this country.
Don't pity me.
It's not time for that yet.
You must be cold.
If you give me your jacket,
what about you?
I'm okay.
You wish.
You're already going pale.
See? You're cold as ice.
Wait.
Good now?
Let's go.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Right. Did you not tell my mom?
She was worried
that you suddenly disappeared.
What brings you back here at this hour?
I thought you moved back to the dorm.
I left in a rush.
I'm going back tomorrow.
I see.
I saw it on the way.
You love the ones with red...
bean...
Ha Na told me.
Yes. Thanks.
I was actually hungry. Thanks.
Bye now.
I saw them getting out of
the car together before.
I know.
Now that his mother-in-law's gone,
he doesn't even try to hide it.
One more bottle of soju, please.
It's not a meeting. It's torture.
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
That sounds tough.
Still, hot rice soup and soju with you...
makes up for it.
Mi Jin.
I...
can't help you with your work anymore.
What do you mean?
I appreciate your help,
but...
I need to do my job.
Did I upset you?
- Are they Romeo and Juliet or what?
- No. Wait.
The finance team manager position is
vacant. Do you want that spot?
If you just say it, I will...
I'll work for you
until you find someone new.
Thank you...
for everything.
I really appreciate it, Mi Jin.
Min Seok.
Why are you acting like this?
I have to save this restaurant.
This is my family business.
And it's going down
because of the new owner.
Of course.
This is the best spot.
You know everyone's eyes are on it.
Come on.
If it weren't for my other business,
I would've kept it.
Is this the rice soup restaurant that
tastes different after the owner changed?
Yes.
After the owner changed,
they lost all their customers...
and ruined the neighborhood too.
What a pity.
They're crazy...
It's ruined!
You're done for.
The end.
Are you out of your minds?
Why are you making a fuss
in my restaurant?
All because of this.
Contract Clause 13 Special Agreement.
"If any problem occurs regarding
the quality in less than a year,"
"the contract will be terminated..."
"for violating
the quality maintenance issue."
It means you're doomed.
I released everything Yoo Ji An did
to the press...
and sent it to the prosecutors too.
We'll have to wait for the result,
but this time, even with her dad's help,
she won't be able to avoid prison time.
Thank you for everything.
Whatever.
Can't you at least try to hide it?
What do you mean?
You'll soon pierce Emily.
Unless you want to tell everyone,
stop gazing at her like that.
What's wrong with my gaze?
Are you crazy?
What are you doing here?
What if a scandal breaks again?
Hey, the whole country acknowledges...
I'm your official male friend.
Besides,
as long as you cover your eyes,
no one will recognize you.
- What are you saying?
- Whatever.
Today, I have no tomorrow.
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
(New Seoul Record)
I didn't know a place like this
still existed.
This place is popular among kids
these days.
Really?
Kids these days listen to turntables?
Yes.
It's working.
Stop dragging me.
What is this place?
- Hold on.
- What?
I know. Press this.
Wait. Our faces are on here.
What's this?
What?
I think it started already.
- Time's up.
- It started.
Get in the pose. It's taking pictures.
Ms. O.
Let's go there.
(Spring Hanbok)
You look pretty.
Let's go.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Don't just eat everything alone.
Give me some too.
Ae Sim.
Did you book the surgery?
I don't need a fake document like this.
I'm keeping the baby.
Are you crazy?
I'll be 40 soon.
It's a miracle that I got pregnant.
Look.
The nation's favorite graceful singer...
Kim Ae Sim got pregnant?
Without anyone knowing
before getting married?
Gossip won't last long.
I'll rise again.
Do you know how much debt we have?
What?
Every time the boys got in trouble,
I had to settle with the victims.
And that darn Mr. Park who promised
to build your own concert hall...
took off with the budget, so
the interest costs 10,000 dollars a month.
You don't have time to be distracted...
for the next few years.
What the hell have you been doing?
Whatever. I'm having the baby.
Ae Sim.
If you go to a hospital,
people might spread the word.
I'll look for a midwife...
Son of a gun.
Unless you have a death wish,
don't ever appear in front of me again.
You know I do what I say.
Sis.
Ae Sim.
Aunt Ae Sim?
Jun Hyuk, it's okay.
Want a glass?
Just say it.
The happiest time of my life.
Yes, it was Emily's age.
I spent most of my time...
in Royal Salon.
People who dreamed of becoming a singer.
Obscure singers.
We sang, laughed, cried,
and talked together.
I idled so much
that I was even on academic probation.
There was a time...
when singing meant everything to me.
And that continued until now.
Singing meant everything to you,
and it still does.
I understand what you mean exactly.
Yes.
So it was tough for me...
to regret that life and retrieve it.
I couldn't ask...
for your understanding...
No.
For your forgiveness.
It sounds terrible.
What kind of excuse is that?
Nothing's going to change.
Just keep the life you had until now.
But that doesn't mean...
that you meant nothing to me.
Don't...
take that wrong.
There's a timing for everything.
To get mad.
To hear an excuse.
And to expect...
with slight hope.
I'm really sorry.
How can I make it up to you?
No, don't do anything.
Now I finally feel relieved.
Let's not shake up each other's life...
and root for each other with respect...
like now.
(Owl Cabin)
Here.
Cheers.
It's good.
I heard kids these days love retro.
This place is real retro.
This is amazing.
What? What is?
Just until recently,
we had no place to go...
other than the senior center or a park.
It's amazing that we're hanging out...
like young people in the city.
And it's amazing that it was so much fun.
Right.
How did we survive
our boring and dull lives until now?
Perhaps...
we were sad because of our hearts
that didn't age,
not our aged bodies.
So what?
What matters is that we can be together
in young bodies again.
By the way, is the scandal resolved now?
Can you debut?
I'm okay,
but I'm worried about him.
Him?
As much as I am...
No.
He turned out to be lonelier than I was.
He was pretending to be okay.
But...
his eyes keep bothering me.
No.
You're not in love with that young boy,
are you?
Can I?
Come on. What a lame joke.
How can you fall for him?
That's what I thought at first.
No.
Just until recently.
- But...
- Ms. O.
I can't fool myself.
You know it's not going to work out.
Why are you taking the hard way?
I don't care even if it doesn't work out.
I'm okay as long as I can like someone.
Do you like that man that much?
When you think about him,
does he cheer you up?
Sure. That's all that matters.
You're young again. What stops you?
Sing and love...
all you want.
Okay?
(O Mal Soon Beef Head Meat and Rice Soup)
What the?
What are you doing here?
Du Ri.
I thought you went back to the dorm.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Park... No.
I met Jun. I'm going back...
That's not the point.
What are you doing here alone?
They got rid of the recipe.
My mother-in-law lost her memories
and went off the grid.
I can't...
What am I going to do
about our restaurant?
Get up.
How do you know...
I've seen my cooking before.
I learned it from her just in case.
You learned it?
What matters the most?
The ratio between ox head broth
and leg bone broth.
What's the ratio?
Three...
Three to seven.
Okay.
Boil the head for 5 hours,
and 2 days for the leg.
If you boil more than that, it'll stink.
- Make sure to keep track of time.
- Yes.
Scoop the meat separately in parts...
to keep it tender and delicious.
And what matters the most?
Remove the grease in the leg broth...
every five hours.
Yes! Remove the grease every five hours.
Thanks, Du Ri.
The scoop is dented.
Did you call the contractors?
- I'm sorry.
- "I'm sorry?"
- The exhibition is around the corner.
- Ms. Kang.
The windows and system are delayed.
I'll finish it up.
Then we couldn't appreciate...
No, we'll take care of it.
You're busy working on the proposal.
I don't plan to steal your career.
I just want to end it on a good note.
Don't worry.
Even if you haven't eaten anything
for three days,
you shouldn't eye on other's food.
I learned that from my mom.
Look at the time.
Are you still up?
How can I sleep when you aren't home?
Look at your face.
The deadline is near.
I have a lot of work. Goodnight.
Even if you die tomorrow,
do you think your work will cry for you?
They'll find someone new to replace you.
But I will die...
and follow you.
Die? How can you say...
Unless I say that, you never listen.
Take care of yourself, will you?
Why are you going so hard on yourself...
for what?
Honey. You're home.
Come here for a second.
What's the matter?
Why are you so hyper? I'm getting nervous.
No. Come here. Hurry.
Don't say anything.
And try this.
What do you think?
It tastes just like Mother's rice soup,
right?
Did you make this?
How can I do that alone?
Du Ri...
gave me the recipe.
Isn't it amazing?
- Du Ri told you?
- Yes.
She asked Mother.
My gosh.
She's so shrewd and smart, right?
He's trying so hard.
I'm proud of him.
Look at the time.
Did I push myself too far?
When the moon is full, it declines.
And the flower that blooms first
withers first.
The moon is so bright.
Why the long face? Something happened?
Nothing.
I think I pushed myself too far
these days. I'm just tired.
Right.
What about you? Are you not feeling well?
I'm on my period.
I took the medicine, but it's not
getting any better. What about you?
That reminds me.
My period is due, but there's no sign.
What's wrong with me?
Are you that tired?
Your skin looks dry.
You need to take care of yourself.
Okay.
Hello.
Thank you.
What's this?
Again?
It happened to you before.
You suddenly got spots like a granny.
It happened to me before?
It happened to you for a while,
then you soon recovered.
Don't worry too much.
Excuse me.
Tell me what you know about Emily.
Everything.
No.
That can't be true.
Hello. I'm Ha Na from Element.
We're here...
to film our first music video.
I will introduce you to...
my members...
and UNIS teachers...
who are beautiful enough to be mistaken
as my members.
Min A, Jay, Olla, and Soo Jin. Say hi.
- Hello.
Everyone.
Our Du Ri.
No, Emily is busy getting ready.
The Strange Sisters' main vocalist's
flashy transformation.
What do you think?
Are you surprised?
You look beautiful, Du... I mean, Emily.
You're shining like a diamond.
- Sorry.
- Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
- Let's do this.
Soo Jin, say something as a leader.
We can do it.
Olla? Say hi.
- Hello.
Did you get into an accident or something?
Is that it?
Did you lose your memories? Let me see.
If you lost your memories,
we'll find them.
Even if you can't,
we'll force them to come back.
Or just live as the person
I'm looking for.
How did you recognize me?
Mr. Park.
Yes. Mr. Park told me.
Leave hopeless O Mal Soon to me.
Cherish your time.
And enjoy it.
Don't look at anything.
Don't think about anyone.
Just do as your heart says.
Especially for your last choice.
Cut.
- Hey.
- Du Ri.
Du Ri.
- What's wrong?
- Are you okay?
If Janet was Emily,
am I going to get old again?
Emily, are you okay?
Hey.
Mom.
(The last episode
will be aired tomorrow at 9:50 p.m.)
(Who Is She!)
Did you enjoy the spring?
I have to choose?
If I return, is there a place for me?
Tell me what's going on.
I will finish up...
what you started.
Don't forget me.
Or I will be really sad.
- It's time.
- Let's do this.
Have you made up your mind?
So I...