Song Ji Hyo
Nam Ji Hyun
Chae Jong Hyeop
Ha Do Kwon
So Hee Jung
The Witch's Diner
♬  This crazy love  ♬
♬  I think I'm the only one saying this  ♬
♬  Like a lie  ♬
I'm sorry, but can you take a picture for us?
♬  Oh won’t you hold my hand  ♬
I'll take the photo now.
One, two, three.
♬  Both on a sleepless night  ♬
♬  and when you toss and turn tomorrow comes  ♬
♬  Everything is gonna be alright  ♬
Hui Ra.
♬  I’ve been waiting  ♬
♬  my whole life for love  ♬
♬  Nothing is easy  ♬
♬  Sometimes it’s heavy  ♬
Let's be together forever.
♬  Why do I feel this way  ♬
♬  It’s just another day  ♬
I want revenge.
There's a cost for the wish.
The cost is for you to be a witch.
I don't care if it's a witch or whatever.
My wish is for the man's child
to be as unhappy as I am.
I hope they get hurt like me, in a miserable way.
So I hope that man is in agony.
The Witch's Diner
EP. 07 Mom's Kimchi Bean Sprout Porridge
1st Birthday
Noona.
But is that him? The person you're dating?
He doesn't seem that great. You deserve better.
Let's go.
I'm sorry. Can I borrow your phone please?
I missed you.
I have an urgent film shoot tomorrow, so I don't think I will be able to come.
I think I'll have to prepare for a recording next week.
How could you not notice all those excuses, like an idiot?
Everything was a lie.
Gil Yong.
I'm so
sorry about today. I shouldn't have bothered you.
I'm fine now. You should go.
You're not okay.
Why do you always say you're okay?
Yeah.
I'm not okay.
But I don't know what to say
or what to think.
I don't know anything right now.
Don't think about anything and go in and rest well today.
Okay. Be careful going home.
Noona!
I want you to be happy.
They say it's good to cry when you're sad.
If you're having a hard time, don't hold it in today.
Okay.
Thanks.
♬  You don’t need to say anything  ♬
♬  What reason do we need?  ♬
♬  Would the meaning of love be deeper than this?  ♬
♬  My dear  ♬
♬  A person who will feel sorry for everything  ♬
♬  Even after dying  ♬
♬  I live because of you  ♬
♬  A person who said it was a fine day  ♬
♬  You say that my sadness is your sadness  ♬
♬  My deepness is your smile  ♬
Love as if you've never been hurt.
♬  Would the meaning of love be deeper than this?  ♬
♬  My dear  ♬
Someone said that
the reason why people are fooled by lies is simple.
The belief that the other person won't lie to me now.
Because of that belief,
I'm not lying to the other person.
♬  I live because of you  ♬
♬  A person who said it was a fine day  ♬
The weather is cold.
Can I get you a blanket? Wait here. I'll be right back.
It's been a while.
Are you here because of Jin?
Yes. I came because of her.
Are you going to do something to my Jin—
Jin has been cursed.
Cursed?
She will become unhappy.
No. No. Not my Jin.
I'll take the curse.
Sorry.
She is the  person who must receive the curse.
What are you doing now? Get out immediately.
Why aren't you picking up my calls?
Go. I have nothing to say to you anymore, and I don't want to see you either.
Let's talk.
Let go. Let go of me!
You are married and even have a child. You hid all of that from me.
How could you think of coming here shamelessly?
Married man? What are you saying? I think there is a misunderstanding.
We locked eyes at the ceremonial hall today.
So that was what you were talking about.
I didn't see you though. Did you see me in the Dol (child's first birthday celebration)?
How long will you continue to lie to me?
I couldn't help but take the role of the dad today instead of my friend because he requested that of me.
I should have told you in advance.
Why are we doing this now?
Friend's request?
Did you think I would believe that? Get out!
I'm telling you it is a misunderstanding!
Why don't you believe me?
I have no intention of breaking up with you or letting you go.
So just know that.
Crazy b*stard.
Okay. Let's say I made a mistake,
so I came here immediately to apologize and comfort you.
Comfort me?
I don't need that, so get lost from my sight immediately.
You speak very harshly.
I didn't know you were like this.
I thought you were kind.
So you weren't sincere with me.
Yes. There is no way you would do this if you were sincere with me.
You... You have gone crazy.
I came here and lied to you to comfort you and apologize!
Is this possible if I don't love you?
I'm working this hard. What are you?
Who are you to make me a bad guy?!
I told you I love you.
What are you!?
Crazy b*stard!
Jerk!
What are you?! Don't you dare lay your hands on her!
Crazy jerk. Move. Get off me!
Police, please help us! Please help us.
Please save us.
Tell us your name and your ID number.
It isn't a big deal.
I was just arguing with my girlfriend.
But that guy came in suddenly and there was a misunderstanding.
I'm not his girlfriend.
I saw him assaulting her.
You can check the CCTV to see that he entered her home forcefully.
We ended up fighting because he was hitting her.
What is your relationship?
I'm her guardian.
Guardian.
- Don't joke.
- He is my guardian.
He is my guardian, and you were the one who assaulted me.
I told you it's a misunderstanding!
Why don't you believe me?
I am trying so hard.
What are you? Who are you to make me a bad guy?
There is no need to hear any more.
You have evidence and an eyewitness. Legal action can be taken.
Would you like to file a complaint right away?
Yes, Hyung.
I have a problem, so help me out.
Yes, this is Kangbu Police Station.
Yes, thank you.
I would like to call my lawyer here.
You can call your lawyer,
because they also have.
From now on, please talk to me about all law-related problems.
You think you won just because you have a recording?
Now that I think of it, did you target me from the beginning because I am a public figure?
I won't stay quiet if you spread this matter to the media or the internet.
Just go if you really don't want to make the issue bigger.
If you have anything else to say, please say it through your lawyer.
You guys have messed with the wrong person.
I will decide whether we end it or not.
That trash-like b*stard.
Yes, PD. How have you been?
Are you really not going to sue him, Noona?
It is because I need some time to think.
If we leave him out, what if he does something to you?
He won't be able to move impulsively.
He said it himself. He's a public figure.
You aren't doing this because you are worried about him, right?
No.
It's because I want to confirm what is happening to me.
- Noona—
- Jin.
Would you have a word with me?
You must be  shocked. Drink this first.
Uh...
I ate the leftover chocolate before, without realizing it.
The witch told me never eat it.
It might become an irreversible poison.
Is it because of that?
Because of that chocolate?
Do you really think that?
If there's a cost, then there is also a side effect.
I was wondering if I were cursed.
It's possible.
But
didn't you ever think that
you might not be able to see the real problem because you think it's the chocolate?
- Excuse me?
- Think about it again.
There may be an answer in your memory,
from the question that you avoided the most.
Seoul to Gangreung
Jin, your dad recovered a lot and was discharged from the hospital.
Do you remember the house we lived in when you were young? I guess he was still living there.
Do you want to come over here?
I didn't keep up with reality.
The truth that what I suppressed to avoid is like Pandora's box.
I've never tried to look at it properly.
Mom!
Oh! My daughter, you're early.
I came quickly because I miss you.
But did you stay up all night? What's wrong with your face?
No, I didn't. I'm just a little tired.
Your dad's still asleep.
Oh, don't wake him. I'll greet him later.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Your daughter is also a little sleepy.
Oh, okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go in. Let's go in.
I've prepared all the ingredients you mentioned.
This time, what kind of guest is this food for?
Take a seat here.
You've been through a lot.
You don't have to come anymore starting tomorrow.
- Excuse me?
- This restaurant is going to close now.
Is there something wrong? Then what about Noona Jin?
I'll talk to Jin separately.
Miss Witch, what the hell is going on with Noona?
I made a wish that I wanted to be by her side, but
even beside her, I couldn't help her.
What
would you do if you could make a wish again?
If I could make the wish again,
I'd protect her rather than be by her side,
or change it to make her happy.
How long did I sleep?
Oh, did you wake up?
I was very accurate.
I thought my daughter was going to sleep for another 20 hours and was just getting ready.
Oh, wow, I'm amazing.
Yes, my mom is really amazing.
You must have been really tired.
Yes, a little.
- Kimchi bean sprout porridge?
- Yes.
You looked for this every time you were sick.
After you finished one bowl, you got better in no time.
My Jin.
I made your favorite, kimchi bean sprout porridge. Try to eat a little.
- There you go. Are you not sick anymore?
- No!
Did you get sick because you wanted to eat this?
When I was young, I used to fake it whenever I wanted to eat this.
But I'm not sick.
Are you only sick when your body is sick? Heartbreaks are pain too.
I hope you get all better after eating a bowl of this.
- What are you thinking about?
- Huh?
Eat before it gets cold.
Thank you for the meal.
It's really good.
- Hey, Mom.
- What?
Don't you hate Dad?
I hate him. I hate him, so that's why I'm here harassing him.
It's so much fun to scold your dad.
But Jin, I don't know if it's because my brain is bad,
but as time goes by, the hatred is erased bit by bit.
Oh, but I shouldn't keep forgetting.
Mom.
I...
I remember everything.
She keeps... Why are you setting this mood?
What? What did you remember?
What happened when I lost you when I was young.
That it wasn't a dream.
Actually,
I know everything.
That Dad brought me from outside (adopted her).
When I was five years old, I heard you and Aunt talking.
Did Brother-in-law drink and make a fuss again?
And you're still going to live with her?
Why would you suffer like that?
You need to live too.
Quickly divorce him, and just leave the kid at the orphanage.
Watch what you say. Jin will hear you.
You know, the kid Brother-in-law brought from outside...
What makes her so pretty that you would go through all this trouble?
You can't keep your mouth shut?
Why didn't you tell me?
Did you not tell me because you were afraid you'd hurt me?
Jin, no matter what anyone says, you're my one and only daughter.
I know.
Of course, I know.
So... thank you so much
for letting me live as your daughter.
Don't mention it.
That is why I
can't forgive Dad.
He hurt you.
I only... wished that you wouldn't get hurt.
But Jin,
if we are alive, we can't live without getting hurt.
There are no wounds that don't heal.
I was still extremely happy because of you.
Where else would I get such a pretty daughter?
Thanks a lot.
It's been a while.
Jin,
you hate me a lot, right?
I have made mistakes all my life.
I regret it every time, but I still made the wrong decisions.
I only thought of running away.
I was selfish.
Back then, I couldn't see anything except myself.
I know I can't get forgiveness
from anyone.
But...
I at least wanted to apologize.
I am really,
really sorry, Jin.
But...
I thought
I should give this to you myself.
Go if you aren't interested.
Excuse me.
About that contract... Let's make it clear.
It's not everything to just say, "This store is now mine."
There's loan interest, electricity bills, water bills, cost of materials.
You have a drinking habit.
Whether it's big or small, that's for him to bear. It is not like you are going to live for his sake.
- I mean, it's because I'm not going to live for him that I'm—
That is why I should be more serious.
Witch. Witch.
But at least the last of my life has been fun with her.
If you were to make a wish again...
You would disappear without leaving a trace.
That order has brought me up to here.
The results are obvious.
Do I have to see you dying?
Therefore, right now, I will face up to reality..
Only the reality.
The Witch's Diner
I met my dad and came.
So you must have heard anything. It is something that can be forgotten.
Erase it.
The preparations are all done.
You can curse him so that he won't be able to mess
with you ever again if you just eat this.
How big of a price must I pay...
for that curse?
You don't need to know.
I'm going to eat it anyway.
Stop. Stop it.
If it's revenge that has a price, then I will do it myself.
Now I know...
I can't give you both.
Red or blue?
You choose.
Ahjumma, you choose first.
Who the woman who gave me that candy was.
Mom.
My mom will worry, so I have to go now.
Let's go to your mom.
If you fall again later, I will hold your hands then too.
Who the woman who gave me the candy was.
You have been by my side always, right?
Mom.
♬  Even after giving everything  ♬
♬  A person who feels sorry  ♬
♬  I live because of you  ♬
♬  A person who said it was a fine day  ♬
♬  Suddenly, you’ve grown so small as you’re leaving  ♬
♬  Why am I feeling so endlessly sad?  ♬
The Witch's Diner
Epilogue
I wanted to say goodbye.
It's a shame, but we can't do anything about it.