[The Awakening of Housewives]
[Episode 10]
Senior.
Hello?
Wang Yan.
Are you crazy?
Where's my money?
What money?
What are you talking about?
Get out of here!
The voice-changing call,
the anonymous letter
and the garbage truck.
Li Zhiqing.
Nice performance.
Do you mean
the money you've transferred from my account?
Let me tell you.
I have all the bank evidence in my hands.
I want you to return all that money
to me completely.
Take one more step forward and you'll regret it!
Li Zhiqing.
We're not divorced yet, are we?
You've already given him the keys?
He'll stay in my house tonight.
He'll protect me.
He'll protect you?
Are you leaving or not?
If you don't leave, I'll call the police.
Then you had better protect her well.
At night, she can be
quite hard to deal with.
I'm sorry.
I used you
just now.
It's okay.
Why are you here?
We got the money back.
I was worried that he might come here to give you a hard time,
so I stayed downstairs all this time.
Let's go.
Let's have a drink.
Mr. Wang.
I've figured out everything for you.
I asked a professional to check it.
That picture was photoshoped.
Although
you've been deceived,
there's at least one piece of good news.
Your wife doesn't have
any real evidence.
From now on, if I don't ask you anything,
just keep your mouth shut.
Alright.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Wang.
There are so many termination agreements
and a pile of legal claim letters.
What do you think we should do?
What do you mean?
Are you trying to hold me accountable now?
I won't take the blame for this.
Who's responsible for the company's current state?
When you're in this position,
don't you feel guilty?
That's right.
I can't even pay salaries now.
If it's really not okay,
just disband our team.
That's great.
I was just thinking the same thing. Leave the company now.
Don't let me see you tomorrow.
I have no problem with that,
as long as Ms. Li agrees.
Everyone, calm down first.
You've all been with my father
through thick and thin.
I won't let the company collapse.
I'll definitely
pay the salaries as usual.
If there's a deficit in the accounts,
I'll cover it personally.
Count me in.
-Count me in.
Ms. Li.
If you're trying to win people over,
you should at least come up with a better lie.
Right?
Are you treating us all as fools?
Anyone can brag.
Do you have a better solution
to help Dongqing get rid of this predicament?
The person who has put the company in this situation
is the one treating us all as fools.
Jintai.
As long as we make Jintai become our client,
we'll be able to save the company.
Mr. Zhao and I will come up with a new proposal.
We'll do our best
to make Jintai become our client.
Where's Li Zhiqing?
Come out here!
Are you afraid to come out because you've done
something shameful?
Ms. Li
is in a meeting right now.
Please wait here for a moment.
On what grounds can you stop me?
I'm her mother-in-law.
You first made trouble at home, and now you're causing trouble in the company.
You really won't stop it, huh?
Is this how an elderly person should behave?
Are you behaving well like a daughter-in-law?
Her son is already behaving like that,
and she even has the nerve to criticize others?
Well, Zhao Ninghao...
Zhao Ninghao, come out here!
I'm here.
Why do you want to see me?
So you're already trying to protect him?
My son is still sitting in the company.
You two are doing such dirty things
right under his nose.
Don't you know that spreading rumors
can lead to legal consequences?
I'm spreading rumors?
In front of everyone in the company, will you say that
you don't have any other intentions towards my daughter-in-law?
Do you dare to say it?
Do you dare?
Alright.
You're feeling guilty, aren't you?
If you want to make a scene,
then go ahead and do it.
If you leave now, I'll lose all respect for you.
Why would I leave?
I want everyone in the company to know
what kind of person you really are.
Has Wang Yan's client arrived?
He's in the lobby.
Don't go.
This way, please.
Let me tell you.
This person
always seems decent.
She's actually quite despicable.
Mr. Wang.
Who is this?
As for this kind of person,
if you don't expose her,
she'll never know what shamelessness means.
Guys, just remember that
she's quite revolting.
Now that you have such a leader,
I even feel sick for all of you.
She's like a shrew.
Recently, your company's atmosphere
has been quite lively.
That person...
is...
Don't you think it's such a disgrace?
She's our company's cleaning lady.
I thought so.
How could your company have someone like this?
That's right.
She always pretends to be decent.
Zhou Ran.
Take Mr. Fang to the office to rest first.
She acts as if she were awesome.
I'll just wait for you right here.
So you're not coming out?
I just won't leave.
What are you looking at?
Don't you have work to do?
Son.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
I'm here to teach Li Zhiqing a lesson for you.
I have an important client there.
Leave now.
Don't embarrass me.
Son.
Go!
Well...
We happen to need a cleaning lady here.
Would you like to consider it?
Mr. Fang.
Take care.
Alright. It's good to collaborate with you.
Bye.
Hello, what is it now?
Hello, Mr. Chen.
Has Ms. Bai read the proposal I gave you
last time?
Ms. Bai is still angry about that matter of yours.
If she doesn't make a decision on this,
it'll be useless for you to talk to anyone else.
I understand.
We've been old friends for so many years.
Stop mentioning that we're old friends.
Solve the problem as soon as possible.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm wondering
whether you can
put in a good word for me in front of Ms. Bai.
If this works out, I'll have to...
I didn't read my horoscope before coming out.
I'll stop playing it.
Mr. Xiao.
Don't leave.
You haven't paid the money yet.
Can't you see that?
I don't have any money now!
Since you've won so much, I'll pay next time.
There is no such a usual practice.
Then what do you want?
If you don't have money, pay with your fingers.
Each finger is worth 2,000 yuan!
Is this enough now?
You can let him go now, huh?
Let me make this clear first.
I have no money to repay you.
I didn't expect you to return the money, either.
So you are
making a sacrifice for love?
But there's one thing
you need to help me with.
I knew it.
Tell me.
What is it?
You paid for me, and I have to help you.
Help me kidnap Li Zhiqing's daughter.
You want me to do such an inhuman thing?
Alright.
You've come to the right person.
[Inpatient Department]
Ms. Li!
What's wrong?
Why are you here so late?
Your father is critically ill.
We couldn't reach you by phone.
Fortunately, your husband is here.
My husband?
Wang Yan?
He's in the ward.
Go take a look now.
Okay.
The patient has been resuscitated now.
His condition is basically stable.
Thank you, Doctor.
Don't worry too much.
Zhiqing.
Actually, you should thank your husband.
He basically
comes here to visit your father every night.
If he hadn't discovered it in time this time,
the consequences would have been unimaginable.
Thank you, Ninghao.
There's no need to thank me.
This is what I should do.
Previously, the chairman
and you took such good care of me.
Then I'll go out first.
Son, look.
Let me tell you. This color really suits you.
Look.
Mom.
Is this why you've asked me to come here?
This outfit
really
suits you so much.
Go try it on.
You'll surely look so handsome in it.
Mom,
could you please not come to my company again?
I have so many important clients.
Don't cause any trouble for me. Okay?
Alright.
I won't
go to your company again. Okay?
Go try on this outfit now.
Go try it on.
Just go.
Why are you here?
So you used my mother?
I'm sorry.
I missed you,
so I came to see you.
While there are few people outside,
leave at once.
Don't blame me for being disrespectful to you.
I'll apologize to you.
About the pregnancy,
I lied to you.
Have you finished speaking?
If you've finished, leave at once.
I can help you get Jintai's project.
Do you think there's a chance of winning for you to get Jintai's project?
I won't lose.
You've caused so much trouble.
I'm sure you're quite clear about Ms. Bai's attitude
towards you now.
If you can't get Jintai's project,
you'll be kicked out of the company.
Do you want to lose to Li Zhiqing?
Then do you have a better solution?
Qian Xiaoxuan.
You've gone too far.
But I like it.
You always know exactly what I want.
Take her down
while she's vulnerable.
I'm willing to
do anything for you.
It was my fault to deceive you.
However,
I really want to have a child with you.
Then you can
just have one with me.
What's that sound?
How shameless!
Ms. Li.
It's not appropriate to watch this, is it?