[The Awakening of Housewives]
[Episode 7]
As you expected,
he's very nervous.
Have you made up your mind?
Revenge is nothing easy.
Even with just one wrong move,
you might end up ruining yourself.
For my father,
the company he dedicated his life to,
and Jia,
I can't let this scumbag
ruin everything.
But...
it will be very difficult for you.
Compared to betrayal,
difficulty means nothing.
Count me in.
Let's take down Wang Yan together.
So boring.
Why are you so distracted today?
Someone's onto us.
They know about the fake accounts.
If this person really has solid evidence,
he wouldn't have played a trick like this.
Could it just be a prank?
What if he does have something?
We'll both end up in jail.
We need to destroy those accounts now.
Could it be Li Zhiqing, that old hag?
Her?
Does she even have the brains for this?
Whether it's her or not,
I'll
settle a score with her tomorrow.
Are you blind? Do you even know how to drive?
I'm sorry.
Did I hit the child?
This is a school zone!
Don't you know you should slow down?
People like you should have their licenses revoked!
Isn't this Jia's mother?
Yes,
Jia is in the same class as your child.
No wonder.
Today's my unlucky day.
Let's go, baby. We're going home.
Baby,
from now on, if you see this woman,
stay away from her.
And
don't play with Jia anymore, understand?
Why, Mom?
Their family is dirty.
Let's go.
Madam,
where's Jia?
I don't see her.
Wasn't she picked up by someone you sent?
What?
Here.
Bye bye.
See you tomorrow.
Right here.
Goodbye, Madam.
Sorry.
The number you have dialed is currently unavailable.
Please try again...
Sorry.
The number you have dialed...
Jia,
do you want some candy?
Tell me if you want some.
Oops.
How could I forget?
Jia can't speak.
-Little mute!
You kids,
how could you say that to Jia?
It's okay, Jia.
Come on.
Come on, Jia, have some candy.
It's okay, Jia.
Take a bite.
Jia!
Jia,
are you alright?
Do you feel unwell anywhere?
Qian Xiaoxuan,
you know Jia is allergic
to peanuts.
She almost died last time.
You tried to harm a child.
Are you even human?
I'm not human?
Li Zhiqing,
when you came to my house yesterday,
didn't you do the same to me?
Best friends
should return favors, right?
Good.
Return favors, right?
Jia,
watch cartoons for a while.
It won't take long.
How dare you slap me!
Qian Xiaoxuan,
listen,
stay away from my daughter.
I was already kind enough at your place that day.
You can come at me.
If you dare to lay a finger on my daughter,
there'll be consequences!
Stop filming!
Isn't that Jia's mother,
the one who cheated on her husband?
The one
caught with a young guy at midnight.
Yes. Yes.
Li Zhiqing,
be careful with your daughter.
If you don't divorce him,
I'll keep feeding your daughter candy.
Don't worry.
The child is fine now.
Thank you, doctor.
But Jia still can't speak.
What could be the reason?
Based on the examination results,
there's nothing physically wrong.
I believe
it's more of a psychological issue.
What can I do to help?
Spend more time with the child.
Oh, right.
What's also important is
you must ensure
she's in a peaceful environment
to recover gradually.
Everyone's here now.
Let's stick to the plan then.
I'm ready too.
Good.
Mr. Wang,
you've done a good job.
The company will be yours soon.
It's all thanks to you, Mr. Gu.
However,
there's still one obstacle in our way.
That kind of person
is no threat at all.
At the meeting later,
you just watch.
Mr. Wang,
there's a call for you.
It's been patched through.
Hello?
Mr. Wang,
why didn't you answer your phone?
Did you receive the package
last night?
Who are you?
What do you want?
I know all your little secrets.
Prepare two million yuan by 5 p.m. today.
Otherwise,
you'll get a surprise.
Do you think I'm a three-year-old boy?
Trying to trick me?
Believe it or not.
Hello?
Mr. Zhao,
do you know how big of a blow it is
to our company to lose Hongming?
What's there left to say?
Mr. Zhao,
we gave you a chance, but you blew it.
Mr. Wang,
the Hongming project was a ticking time bomb,
yet you hid it from everyone.
It was obviously a trap you set.
Zhao Ninghao!
You failed to secure the project,
but you're blaming Mr. Wang!
You've gone too far!
Everyone,
for the long-term development of the company,
if you agree to dismiss Zhao Ninghao,
please raise your hand.
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhao.
It's the majority's will.
You're fired.
I'll never forgive anyone who causes losses
to the company.
Previously, Ms. Li
was embroiled in a scandal.
I hope that everyone
can prioritize the interests of the company.
In this regard,
we should learn
from Qian Xiaoxuan.
Holy crap!
Look at this, everyone!
Come and take a look!
Isn't this Mr. Wang?
Right?
This...
This is not your daughter-in-law, right?
Who...
Who is she?
Stop looking! Stop looking!
Stop looking!
Mr. Wang,
your nightlife is quite wild.
Stop looking!
Who did this?
Turn it off!
Stop looking!
Which one of you is Wang Yan?
Me.
It's me.
Someone reported you misappropriated company funds.
Come with us.
I am Zhao Ninghao,
Vice President of Dongqing Group.
[Authentication documents]
I accuse
Wang Yan, the acting chairman of the company,
of illegally misappropriating company funds.
How did it go?
I managed to fob them off for now,
but they're onto me.
What about us?
Issue a statement first.
Say the videos and photos are fake,
and we'll take legal action.
Netizens
don't believe that anymore.
Then what do you suggest we do?
How about
saying Li Zhiqing cheated first,
there has been no love
between you and your wife for a long time,
and we are true love?
This way, we can minimize the negative impact.
That's nonsense.
That's admitting to the affair.
Jintai hates anything that damages the image the most.
The most important thing now is to secure Jintai's deal.
Otherwise, the company will be finished.
And we'll be finished too!
I think
Li Zhiqing did this.
I think it's her too.
I'll have my mother keep a close eye on her.
Just keeping an eye on her is not enough.
We need to find her weakness.
Your daughter,
Jia.