I'm afraid I can't protect you from the danger of death.
Gang Master
Episode 48
— disturbing my husband's home? — That's right.
His past was expatriate of the 31 of the Great Valor.
I wanted to ask him to leave the mountain
and write Xiyuan's story into the Great Valor.
But you also know that his past is already closed.
Mr. Liu and I are old friends.
No matter what,
as long as you like it,
we'll try it.
The weather is beautiful,
the world is beautiful.
This is also the rumor
about us running away.
Let's go.
Come on.
It's cold at night.
You should dress more.
No need to see me off.
Brother,
we'll leave now.
Mr. Liu,
you should go back to your work.
Okay.
Take care.
Yes.
See you.
It seems that many families are clear-minded
and know that Mr. Liu will be back to the official family sooner or later.
Congratulations, Mr. Liu.
You've made a great achievement.
I'm afraid that
people outside the door can understand it.
People in the door are still confused.
Recently,
have those people said anything?
That night,
when Mr. Liu heard the news,
he was so angry that he couldn't get up.
The fourth room stood in the yard
and scolded him.
But
I got a news.
Tell me.
Madam killed Master.
What did you say?
Mr. Liu,
please forgive me.
Madam wants you
to extinguish this same lamp
to warm her sweat.
I've lost weight.
Nana,
take good care of yourself.
I promise.
Brother 했iang
will ask for a help soon.
It's something important.
Recently,
you have dust on your face.
You're not home.
I see you've lost weight.
I'm back.
I'm leaving the city.
I heard that Lingquan Temple is in a good mood
and is in a good mood.
Qingqing.
Peiqin.
Mr. Cheng.
We are brothers-in-law.
You should be careful of your health.
Don't make it too hard for me.
Peiqin.
You can't be so cold to me.
Mr. Cheng.
The total price of the gift is 21...
Get out!
The new play of Mu Ling has been written.
When are you going to go back?
Not now.
Xingkai.
Whether it's chess or the form,
you always like to play the game.
But this time,
you are facing your uncle.
You should
be careful.
You are born to be a man of your word.
Mr. Liao.
You lost.
Good.
I'm glad you know it.
I was careless.
I'm sorry.
Young Master.
Okay, Young Master.
What's wrong?
Has anything changed?
Nothing.
The official family is under
my uncle's control.
I'm afraid...
Mu Ling.
From now on,
all the promises we made
are not valid.
You can choose again.
But no matter what,
I won't blame you.
What to do?
If you have any decision,
show me.
Okay.
It doesn't matter.
When I go back,
if you are questioned,
I will say I have been released...
I've packed my things.
Let's go.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Do you know where we are?
It's early in the morning.
Why are you making a fuss here?
Madam,
I don't know what they are doing.
They are coming to our mansion.
What are you doing?
Madam.
Mr. Cheng.
Mr. Cheng, you are so cunning.
What are you doing?
Madam,
you don't know, right?
Recently,
we lost several goods in the warehouse.
Xing Kai is not at home.
He called me.
I was thinking
there must be a mole in the house.
Madam,
we need to investigate it.
Keep an eye on the yard.
No one is allowed to go out.
Yes.
Qingyang, what are you doing?
Mr. Cheng,
the official is doing his job.
Xing Kai is not at home.
Someone has to do it.
What do you think, Mr. Cheng?
It's a good idea.
I think you want to take advantage of Xing Kai's absence
and take over the power.
You are so selfish.
Don't talk nonsense.
I don't mean that.
I'll see who dares to enter from me.
Sister-in-law,
don't you feel hot
holding this tablet?
Don't worry.
No matter who takes the position of the master,
your position will not change.
Come on, do it.
Uncle Cheng.
Well...
You still can't get rid of
your heart disease.
Xing Kai.
Mother,
sorry.
Guan Xing Kai.
Where have you been these days?
Your mother was worried about you.
You came back at the right time.
Fine.
Since you are back,
you will take care of the mole
today.
Okay.
Mr. Cheng,
the people below said that Guan Xing Kai is back.
Just keep watching.
Okay.
Where are you going?
I heard that Xing Kai is back.
I'll go to him.
Wait a minute.
Take him back to his room.
Why don't you let me go?
Miss.
No.
Xu Yanshu, why do you...
Miss.
Xu Yanshu.
Miss, let's go.
Why doesn't he let me go?
Miss.
Just listen to your brother.
Go back to your room.
Just listen to what he says.
I don't listen to your brother.
Who else?
Miss, just don't listen to him.
He doesn't want to be punished.
You should tell me why.
Just stay in your room.
Okay.
Mr. Cheng.
Uncle.
You still remember?
When Mr. Cheng sent someone to kill me,
I don't think it would happen today.
Xing Kai.
What's going on?
Isn't Liang Man dead?
My senior died to escape.
Otherwise, how could she stand here
and expose your true face?
Kill him.
Mr. Cheng, you have to kill me.
Senior sister, listen to me.
Listen to me.
If you want to kill me,
I'll find a way to help you.
You may not know that
this handsome and kind-hearted
Mr. Cheng
is actually a cruel and ruthless
murderer.
Bullshit!
You are all pretending to be gods
and playing well.
Where is the evidence?
Chun Shang.
Here comes the young master.
Uncle.
Do you recognize this?
You are so stubborn.
Mr. Cheng.
I'm loyal to you.
You can just use me.
But you sent someone to kill my brother.
Not only that,
he also burned Lan Yu to death
in order to find the master's seal.
And,
you killed
my uncle.
Me?
Fine.
So what if it's me?
He deserves to die.
What has he done for the Guan family
all these years?
I'm the one who has developed the Guan family
to this point.
Without me, who are you?
Who do you think you are?
You are still a noble family.
You are dreaming.
You keep saying that it's for the Guan family.
Then look at what these are.
A seal?
How dare you put a seal in the Guan family's medicine?
How could you do this?
Guan Xingkai.
You are so cruel.
Uncle.
Do you have anything else to say?
Why don't you go to the police station
and explain it to Xingchu?
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Let me go.
Guan Xingkai.
You are a good singer.
You have done enough.
I have developed the Guan family.
If you send me in now,
you will be the one to take the throne.
Don't forget that I'm your second uncle.
I'm the second master of the Guan family.
Second master of the Guan family?
Don't forget that
if you betray the interests of the Guan family
and get rid of your reputation in the family history,
I'm afraid that
the Guan family will never protect you again.
Guan Xingkai.
Let me go.
You are blocking Guan Xingkai.
Wait for me.
Guan Xingkai.
Come on.
You are so thin.
Eat more meat.
Thank you, mother.
Qingqing.
Come on.
Eat meat too.
Thank you, aunt.
Qingqing has been with me
the whole time you were away.
I discussed with the Xu family
about the marriage a while ago.
You should be more careful
about the marriage.
The marriage is at stake.
You should be more careful
about the marriage.
I'll take it as your agreement.
Mother.
I can get married.
Good.
Come on.
But not with the Xu family.
Brother Xingkai.
What do you mean?
You can't get married with anyone
if you don't marry me.
I want to marry Shen Muling.
You...
Xingkai.
You are so stupid.
How can you find a playboy?
It will ruin our family's reputation.
You...
Sister-in-law.
Help me.
Shen Muli.
But I...
I'm still pregnant.
I can't keep a baby.
What are you talking about?
Make up.
aplicative,
and make-up,
please take it slowly.
I'll leave soon,
okay?
The flower of love is like you, inseparable, the face in the ruins is clear