My mind is still Guardian
I didn'tные even care wherest youping
Death courses
Episode 16
Hong Ning, you're back!
You've been out for so many years.
You must have suffered a lot.
You've lost weight. You...
I'm Mu Xian, not Hong Ning.
You're not Hong Ning?
I'm the main teacher of Qingyue State, Mu Xian.
Fine.
Let's go.
How could it be?
Xingguan, did something happen to Zhong Tian?
I don't know.
How could you not know?
Don't say it's me.
No one in Zhong Tian knows.
The Heaven and Earth Stars are in a state of
8-level skin, even if they don't die.
And the Heaven and Earth Lord
never wakes up after returning to his position.
I think he hurt his body
and his vitality when he was in a state of
9-level skin.
He hurt his body? Is it that serious?
No, don't think about it.
Look, do you remember that place?
Although it's been thousands of years,
I can still remember it.
I was sitting there at that time.
I was sitting there and taking you to class.
These flowers are...
The immortals also know that the God is missing.
They pray for him.
It's a kind of flower festival.
But the flowers in the Flower Forest are so mysterious.
The flower god hasn't returned, and the flowers are not in place.
Of course, there is no new flower.
I don't think so.
There is no sign of a sign on the Life and Death Road.
The ancient book of Xingyun Pavilion has changed again.
In the Heaven and Earth,
everywhere has been searched, but no trace of the God has been found.
I'm just worried that the God is not so good.
Oh.
You said that he hasn't returned.
Is it because I hurt his God root?
Don't think like that.
The affairs of the God are over.
If you don't do those things,
how can you save the people of Wuzhang?
How can you have merit?
And you can't light up the Star of Heaven and Earth.
The Star of Heaven and Earth hasn't been extinguished.
Maybe it's the God and Wei Du's misfortune.
Don't cry.
Let's go.
Magistrate Ju.
Magistrate Ziteng.
Magistrate Ziteng is currently in charge of the affairs of HuaZhao Palace.
This is Magistrate MuXian who just became the Magistrate of the Flower Garden.
That's right.
There was a little red tea monster in the palace.
He looks a bit like you.
Really?
That's too coincidental.
But this red tea is rough, rough and playful.
He doesn't know the rules.
I think Magistrate MuXian is not that kind of person.
Magistrate Ziteng is too worried.
Since I hurt the God, I will follow the rules.
It's good that you know the rules.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.
Ignore him.
He looks similar, but he is very soft.
Magistrate Ziteng is really too much.
Just follow the rules.
Why bother with him?
HuaZhao Palace is no longer the head of the family.
It has become like this.
Look, it's not as good as before.
Are you Magistrate MuXian?
I am.
Magistrate Ziteng just told me that these flowers need to be planted before the flower gathering.
Thank you.
Wait, so many flowers?
You should know that Magistrate MuXian just got the divine power.
His power is weak.
To take care of so many flowers, he needs a lot of spiritual power.
How can he cultivate himself with so much spiritual power?
How can he cultivate himself?
Magistrate Ziteng said that the things in the garden are already old.
If Magistrate MuXian can't finish it, he can ask the Goddess for permission.
There are other powers in the heaven.
Fine.
I will go to Magistrate Ziteng and talk to him.
I will see if I can repair these flowers before the flower gathering.
Magistrate Ziteng has given me hope.
I will do my best to let these flowers bloom again.
Thank you, Magistrate.
I'm going to the garden.
Isn't it because the Magistrate is not here?
They are busy with Magistrate Ziteng and the Goddess.
They came to our HuaZhao Palace to do nothing.
I just went to the heaven.
I should do more things.
He doesn't ask you to do more things.
He...
He is just bullying you.
If the Magistrate is here, how can he make you angry?
I will go to the garden.
It is time, Brother.
I just came back from the temple.
The mist runs through my hair and hairs.
I said, the spiky 오 indeed.
It is something, I do not know.
I know the OL T blooming of the Licorice.
What is it?
That is enough, what is it?
Hum?
I don't understand.
What is diubing the conch of Goddess,
wearing such a loud voice?
If you have any doubts,
I have something to tell you.
When did you become so stubborn?
After experiencing the incident of Wuzhang,
and the moment of life and death,
I finally understand what I want.
I was a pervert before.
I clearly liked and cared about you,
but I didn't dare to face and admit it.
Listen to me first.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm done.
Lu Yao.
When you were going to marry my brother,
I always deliberately teased you
and made you angry.
But afterwards, I was also very angry.
I even thought that
I was sick.
I don't know why I did that.
Until later, I realized
that it was because I was unwilling.
I wanted you to see me
and feel me.
I didn't want to see anyone else.
But I didn't know what to do.
I could only use this stupid method
to get a little bit of your attention.
I'm not afraid.
After experiencing this incident,
I finally saw the truth.
I like you.
I love you.
I want to be with you.
When the flowers bloom,
the flowers fall.
When the time
comes,
the love will be broken.
The world is full of twists and turns.
Who will come to meet me?
Who will fall into the dust
and become a moon?
I don't care about the past,
even if I'm in this life,
I don't regret it.
The wind is blowing in my mind,
I'm lost in my heart.
I don't want to see the flowers bloom.
Kunlun Jun,
now you're back to Zhong Tian.
You're back to Zhong Tian.
No matter how I change,
I'm either the Bai Ling of the ice,
the son of the Prime Minister,
or the Kunlun Jun of the past.
I've never changed my love for you.
Do you know what kind of person I am?
The North Fairy Realm is very powerful.
So I need to marry your brother
to rebuild the North Fairy Realm.
You don't remember the past.
I just think you're a bad guy.
But you're forced to follow the Heavenly Lake.
I have to stay with you.
I wanted to use you
as my beloved son
to get the help of West Sea.
That's why I approached you
and helped you.
This is me.
You're so close to me.
I'm so desperate.
So?
You're so annoying and use me.
Have you ever loved me
at all?
So what if I have?
So what if I don't?
Now I've got what I want.
These useless love affairs
are just half-truths to me.
Okay.
I'm being too kind.
I'll leave now.
Goodbye.
I shouldn't use you anymore.
Please rise.
Lu Yao failed to light up Kunlun's
sky and earth.
Father asked me to do it.
I came to apologize.
Alright.
Since Jinxiu hasn't appeared yet,
we still have hope for Kunlun.
Did Zhong Tianwang really disappear?
What's wrong?
The whole Zhong Tian has been searched
There is no clue
Heavenly daughter
You were sacrificed by Kunlun Jun in Wuzhang Kingdom
I see it all
Now, the doctor still needs your help
Don't worry
The conditions we agreed on will not change
After the matter is done, I will definitely go with the Western Sea soldiers
Help you to take back the Northern Heavenly Realm
Your Majesty
I have decided to go back to the Northern Heavenly Realm alone
Tian Hu's ceremony is about to start
You are alone and have no soldiers
If you go back, you will die
I see Kunlun Jun has been living and dying for two generations
I feel something
Now
He can take the Heavenly Star
But I
I can't even return to my hometown
I can only hide in the Western Sea
I can only live in this way
Besides
I don't want my relationship with Kunlun
to have any conditions
I don't want to stand by him in this way
But I'minaudible
In fact, Kunlun has done something similar
Tian Hu from the North tourists
Gave him the research
with Tan Wushuang
I will visit this advisory
and try to prove his responsibility
I've thought it through.
I'll take back the Northern Immortal Realm
and enter the Middle Heaven.
I'll take my leave.
Your Majesty, His Majesty is here.
Finally, it's this far.
Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Kunlun has awoken.
Although he has not fully recovered,
but when can Your Majesty go and see him?
Now,
Jinxiu's Star of Heaven and Earth is bright,
but the whereabouts are unknown.
This is my hidden trouble.
I've also thought
whether Jinxiu's ceremony is not completed yet.
Is this the scene of the Star of Heaven and Earth?
The Goddess understands me.
Then why did His Majesty give him the fairy flag today?
If he is not the tea demon,
why do you care?
I don't know if he is the tea demon.
It's just a lowly person.
But he saved the people of Wuzhang.
If I don't give him the fairy flag,
how will the immortals think of me?
But,
if he interferes with the Star of Heaven and Earth,
it will be a disaster.
It's really His Majesty.
I understand.
Whether he is a human or a demon,
he is not worthy of being killed by the gods.
He is a chess piece under heaven and earth.
Please, Goddess,
please give us the eye of the West Sea
and watch the three stars.
Find Jinxiu as soon as possible.
The whereabouts of the King of Heaven and Earth are important.
I will do my best.
I know.
The longer the time,
the more power the power will be consumed.
If it's not important,
I will not let you be so tired.
This is my duty.
I will do my best.
One can do no blow and the other will turn vs the river.
I am afraid you are not with us.
Because we are no look What?
Are you sure?
It wasn't you.
That was weird.
You must ask me
Jinxiu
Jinxiu, come out, don't play this kind of kid with me
Little ancestor, what are you shouting for? Why are you here?
I fell asleep a few days ago and turned around and forgot to find him
He came when he woke up
Where is he?
Master Jinxiu is not in HuaZhao Palace
Jinxiu
No, he is not here
Jinxiu, Jinxiu
It's you
Greetings, Kunlun Jun
You have become an immortal
Congratulations
I didn't expect to meet you again in Zhong Tian
Thank you and Master for saving the people in Wuzhang Kingdom
These are small matters, it's not a big deal
In fact, since you are here
Jinxiu must be far from here
I know Zhong Tian's people have no truth in their mouth
Master
really doesn't know what's going on
He really disappeared
Master has not returned yet, he is not in the three realms
Where is he
Why isn't King Zhong Tian back yet
Is the Letherities soul съel and scattered
soul ..
Your hands became thicker than it was hello
The
Unbreakable
My eyes,
I heard a little bit from your words
And then...
Where are you now
Shen Zun, where are you?
Shen Zun
You can hear me
Where are you?
You disappear like this
Because I didn't wait for you at the Flame Bridge
Or you
Can't find your way home
Shen Zun
I'm sorry
I should have been more careful
What's wrong with you?
Shen Zun
Why can't I find it?
I just can't find it
Shen Zun
You're going to find my brother in Mount Baizhou?
I know you have doubts about my dream
But as long as there's hope
I have to try
I think his soul is in the flowers of Mount Baizhou
Something is trapped him
But I've led the heavenly soldiers to look for him everywhere
Even the west coast of my mother's eyes
Can see the three realms, see the yin and yang, see everything
I can't find him
How can you be sure he's in Mount Baizhou?
Because it's a dream
So I'm not sure
Okay, how are you going to find him?
Find every flower on Mount Baizhou
Every flower?
He's a flower god
The grass and the trees are all his eyes
Maybe he's in a place we can't see
A thousand years ago
I was trapped in the white-flower map
I had to count all the petals to get out
The ten thousand petals in this white-flower map
The petals are like stars
I counted a thousand years before I counted more than half
Do you know
How long it takes you to find all the flowers and trees on Mount Baizhou?
I know
If you really want to find him
I'm afraid it will take you a thousand years to finish your cultivation
And the heavenly world won't let you go down the mountain for so long
I've found a way to break it
What's the way to break it?
Find the middle god and borrow a thousand years
Borrow ten years?
This is a forbidden skill, what a joke
It takes you a thousand years to get it back
Calm down, okay?
You know how important he is to me
His god root is damaged because of me
So no matter what I do
A thousand years, even if I die
I have to find him
But you're taking risks just because of your dream
Even if it's a dream
But as long as there's hope
I should try
I'm a fairy who broke into this place
I have something important to ask
Please show yourself
What's the fairy's name?
Hongning?
When did you come back to Zhong Tian?
I'm not Hongning
But you're obviously Hongning
You want to use a forbidden skill
You can't get out of here
I'm not Hongning
You're not Hongning
You want to borrow a thousand years?
Yes
Why do you insist on this?
Although I do this
Just because of my dream
Others may not believe it
But I have to find him
Zhong Tian, please help me
Do you know that a thousand years
Is actually your life?
Are you sure you don't regret it?
If I can't find him
I will regret everything
Master, he has always been kind to me
You can help him to save him
I will do whatever you want
Zhong Ai has been in the house for a thousand years
After a thousand years, Zhong Tian will be completely changed
You must come back before that
Hurry up
What if he doesn't come back after a incense?
Fall into the void
Bound by three elements
What?
thousand
最近总是看到他们走过去
你 Frozen
为什么 Modern
这段时期了米
阿อ
我ansen
哦
走
I still regret the past
For you, I will follow you for the rest of my life
When you get married
If the world is in a trance
I will marry you
It's a deal
If we calculate it
He has been here for 700 years
It's a waste
A dream for a thousand years
It's too much
What's wrong with this
There is a saying
The upper is poor, the lower is the emperor
What mortals can't do
We can do it
But in theory
Mortals have never seen anything
How can they have such imagination
Why do mortals look at it with their eyes
The reason why immortals are immortals
Is because they should have magic
When these magic
Go to the mortal world, it becomes a legend
Give mortals hope and hope
I still can't find any clue
Master
Where are you
Time is almost up
Come out, fairy
Fairy
Come back, fairy
I'm punished with you
I can't wait
Master
Where are you
Fairy, it's been a thousand years
It's time, come out
I feel I'm going to find him
Come back
If you don't come back, you can't come back
Fairy
You're back
Do you know how dangerous it was
If I didn't use the magic
You would have been buried
I know, but
You are looking for my brother
Any clues
Don't take the risk
To save time
Your magic power is also half used
If my brother comes back
I don't want to see you like this
It's good to be back
Where are you going
Tianhu is going to ascend the throne
I want to go back
Tianhu is controlling the whole North Fairy Realm
If you go back, can he let you live
I'm the daughter of the North Fairy Realm
I have something I have to do
Even if you have the responsibility of the star gang
You should think of a way to go back
Instead of going back alone
What else can you do
Except being caught
You and I are friends
I'm not afraid of you
What else can you do
You and I are friends
In your eyes
I'm just a person who doesn't prepare anything
I will only take risks
I won't let you go back alone
It's too dangerous
Kunlun, the North Fairy Realm is my home
No matter how weak the power is
I have to go back
My father is still in his hands
Then I will go back with you
You are the son of the Lord of the Heavens
You go back with me
Isn't it more
Besides
Now the relationship between the North Fairy Realm and Zhong Tian is so strong
You help me without permission
Will represent Zhong Tian's attitude
I know you are worried
But
I am the daughter of the Nine-tailed Fox Tribe
I came from the Ice River, the Snow Valley
My family is there
I must save them
What can I help you with
You do what you should do
You have to think about it in advance
If Zhong Tian Wang really can't come back
You, Kunlun
Must take on Zhong Tian
Fight for your Zhong Tian
You sir
Chu
Write the draw recipe
on the container
Look, look at the human blood.
Look.
Oh, right.
The light.
I am the fairy of the wood.
Greetings, fairy of the light.
No, no, no.
I am also a fairy.
I can't be any younger.
Fairy, please don't be polite.
Is it because the light in this place
has disturbed the peace of the heaven again?
I will clean it up immediately.
No.
I came here this time
to ask for something important.
Me?
What can I do?
I don't know if you still remember
that many years ago,
King Zhongtian set a lamp free on Mount Baizhou.
I want to know what is written on it.
This...
This is not good.
That is King Zhongtian's secret.
To be honest,
King Zhongtian is missing.
If we can find him,
we will do our best.
This time, Kunlun Jun asked me to come.
Wait a minute.
Really.
How dare you write anything?
This.
The moon will be more beautiful next year.
The moon will be more beautiful.
At the beginning,
I thought it was easy.
But King Zhongtian
likes a little monster.
He will be gone next year.
I will go to heaven and find him.
The moon will be more beautiful next year.
Mother.
Why are you here again?
I want to ask you to help me again.
You won't...
I want to take another chance.
The last chance.
Are you crazy?
You have already taken a thousand years.
If you take more time,
you may lose all your power.
Just one day.
But you haven't found it in a thousand years.
What can you find in one day?
Just one last day.
I can definitely find him.
Come and have a look.
It's comfortable.
It suits you.
Come again next time.
Okay.
Miss, come and have a look.
Miss,
we have the latest goods here.
All are the best.
Whichever you like,
you can try it.
Miss, you have a good taste.
This is the latest mask here.
It suits you.
Look at this pink.
It's so beautiful.
Take care, miss.
Remember to come again next time.
Thank you.
Come and have a look.
Miss, come and have a look.
The latest mask.
Everyone, come and have a look.
There are all kinds of food.
Come and have a look.
What's that?
I want you to play the lantern with me.
Go.
Others are always thinking about pursuing their eternal life.
But why do you only want to marry me?
I want to be with you.
I want to wait for you.
The wind blows away this life.
The heart is like a dream.
Have you ever thought about it?
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
The name of this life.
I still remember that day.
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
The moon and the lantern have been waiting for a long time.
The army has returned.
The wind blows away this life.
The heart is like a dream.
Have you ever thought about it?
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
The army has returned.
The white hand that is like a door.
The wind blows away this life.
The heart is like a dream.
Have you ever thought about it?
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
The name of this life.
I still remember that day.
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
The wind blows away this life.
The name of this life.
I still remember that day.
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
The wind blows away this life.
The heart is like a dream.
The time of falling flowers will come back.
I want to wait for a long time.
Thank you for watching.