Dad, Mom.
Sister.
You're awake?
Did you have a good sleep?
You've made new friends recently, right?
What's on your mind?
I think it's not bad.
Making new friends,
and dating someone.
You've grown up.
It's time to do something like that.
But,
are you sure he won't leave you?
How would you know it
if you haven't tried it?
Yes, we should try it,
and then we'll be able to
know the feeling
of having it and then losing it.
I don't think it will feel good,
but I don't know
what you think about it.
Want happiness?
You think when you grow up
and become braver,
you can make up
for what you did in the past?
You can forget
that you caused the death
of your Dad and Mom?
I don't care what you want to do,
but do you deserve to be loved?
Let me tell you a story about Xiaoming.
Xiaoming was very dependent
on his parents when he was a boy.
He always wanted them to
be with him no matter what he did.
On a stormy night...
Stop it.
(My teeth hurt so much.)
I said "stop it". I can't hear you.
(My teeth hurt.)
(Daddy, Mommy.)
(On a stormy night...)
(It was all your fault.)
(Xiaoming's teeth hurt so much.)
(His sister asked him to
go to the dentist as soon as possible,)
(but he insisted that his parents
came back home from work quickly.)
(He caused his Mom and Dad)
(to have a car accident.)
(It was all your fault.)
(I hate Dad and Mom the most.)
(I don't want to see a dentist.)
(I don't want my sister
to take me there.)
(I want Mommy and Daddy.)
I know I did the wrong thing.
Please stop it. I'm sorry.
(It was all your fault...)
(He did wrong and is afraid of the future.
Will he still move on after this nightmare?)
♪Every question you ask me♪
♪I think about it again and again♪
♪What answer should I give you♪
♪I'm afraid♪
♪I can't get your mood♪
♪Every question you ask me♪
♪I can feel your heart♪
♪I get tempted from your tone♪
♪Until we're in sync♪
♪Remember to add sweetness♪
=My Tooth Your Love=
I didn't expect you to
invite me to rock climbing.
It is a full-body exercise
that builds muscle, endurance
and agility.
And it helps you sleep better.
I will have a good sleep tonight.
But, why do you like it?
You can do it by yourself,
and it's very quiet.
So you like to do things alone?
Time shouldn't be wasted
on unimportant persons.
I only want those
who are important to me around.
Bai Lang.
Hi.
What a coincidence seeing you here.
Yeah, it is.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I can teach you rock climbing.
I didn't know you could do that.
She is my good friend, Xia Mingyan,
a technical engineer.
Come, he's Jin Xun'an,
a dentist.
Hi.
A dentist can be so young?
He's not only young but very skilled.
If you have a toothache in the future,
go to him for registration.
I'm not in charge of registration.
You should go to the front desk.
But you're in charge of
the treatment, right?
Please take care of me, Dr. Jin.
Let's have a game.
Okay. You two...
Me?
I'm not very good at it.
You can. You've been working out.
No. I'm not good at it.
This is my first time rock climbing,
so I'm not...
Didn't I tell you
to get closer to Jin Xun'an
and get to know him more?
Didn't you see that he was cold to me?
I have more to talk about with you.
He just looks...
Excuse me.
The bento box you forgot in my house.
No need. I have a lot at home.
Yeah, you have a lot.
Here are two.
Take them.
It's his first time here,
so I'll play with you.
Alex, do you know
what kind of person you introduced?
She's so light-minded
and falls in love with everyone.
How could she be worthy of Jin Xun'an?
(White Dark Bistro & Flavor)
What do you want to do?
Mixing drinks.
You know how to do it?
I'll know if you teach me.
If you don't, go out quickly.
Have you done all the work...?
Yes, I have.
The number of customers
coming to drink this week
increased by 15% compared to last week,
but you're getting slower and slower.
To solve this problem,
either hire another bartender
or teach me.
But I heard bartender's salary is high.
It'll cost too much,
so the best solution is to teach me.
Getting a mixologist with a pay
equivalent to that of a waiter.
Perfect.
Okay, you're getting
more and more ridiculous.
You don't even know the basics,
and you want to
make drinks for the customers?
I'll know if you teach me.
I'm a quick learner.
Stop it. Give it to me.
Or you don't know how to teach?
How can that be?
Then that's a deal.
I know this is liquor,
then red wine, another kind of red wine,
and what you just poured was whiskey.
What's wrong?
Okay, I'll go out.
Let's start with the basics first.
There are
six kinds of base spirits for Cocktails.
Tequila.
Whiskey...
How to spell "tequila"?
It's written on the bottle.
What do you think
of the coffee just now?
I don't know.
You really have poor taste in coffee.
Then what other hobbies do you have
besides rock climbing?
Horse riding.
Your hobbies really
make it hard for you to be got close to.
I don't think you will be well-liked.
My hobbies
are really different from yours.
I like activities
that involve a lot of people,
such as singing with a group of people
and having delicious food.
How about this?
I'll take you to
have tasty food in the future.
So you are inviting me out
now?
Just kidding. You are very busy.
You don't need to
always take care of me.
Are you planning to be selected
as an exemplary dentist or what?
You take such good care of patients.
Actually, you're not
just a patient to me.
Although I am a boy,
you shouldn't do that casually.
What did I do?
Saying something romantic
without consideration.
You have to take the responsibility.
For what?
You heard that?
I'm not casual at all.
Gender doesn't matter to me.
The point is
that I only hold myself
responsible for the person I care.
So do you like...?
It's dangerous.
What was that person doing?
You okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Why did you brake suddenly?
It suddenly...
It suddenly reminds me of a joke.
You haven't finished just now.
When Xiaoming was in school, he once...
No... That's not what I wanted to say.
That's not...
He...
What's the matter with you, Bai Lang?
Right, the principal...
No, no. Then Xiaoming...
Calm down, Bai Lang.
Wait.
Was he with Xiaobao or with whom?
It came to me before.
I remember he saw a...
Calm down, Bai Lang.
Calm down.
It's alright.
But then the professor...
He shouldn't come.
Bai Lang...
But he was preparing for the exam.
It's alright...
It's alright.
It's fine...
Relax...
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You saw me like this again.
It was not embarrassing.
One of my previous patients went through
something even more embarrassing.
He had oral cancer.
When I opened his mouth,
I saw his upper and lower gums
were festering...
Dr. Jin.
Do you know the way you comfort others
is really scary?
Bai Lang.
I know a good therapist.
I can introduce you to him
if you want.
Why did you say that?
What do you mean?
Because I think you were
having physiological
and psychological reactions
caused by acute anxiety.
Your sister once told me
that your parents
died in a car accident,
so it seems to me
that there must be some reason
for your nervousness and anxiety.
Maybe that's one of the reasons
for your insomnia
and dependence on sleeping pills.
I think
maybe talking to a therapist
will be helpful.
Can you not tell my sister
about what happened today
and the sleeping pills?
I really don't want her to be worried.
Okay, but you have to
tell me what made you
overreact to it.
I thought of Xiaoming.
I don't want to hear
stories of Xiaoming anymore.
I'm serious.
Xiaoming didn't know
what he was doing when he was a boy.
He had a toothache
but was afraid to go to the dentist,
so he insisted
that his parents drove back
on that rainy day.
When they were trying to comfort him
by talking to him on the phone,
they had a car accident.
When will you be back?
Mommy, I'm not feeling well.
Don't annoy Mom and Dad.
(Be good, Langlang.)
(We're almost there.)
(Give me the phone.)
(Focus on driving.)
(I'll talk to him.)
I want Mommy and Daddy.
(Langlang.)
(I promise you.)
(Your mom and I...)
(On the other end of the phone
were the screech of the brakes,)
(the sound of the thunderstorm,)
(noises from the collision)
(and screams.)
(So Xiaoming is afraid
of going to the dentist,)
(afraid of the screech of cars,)
(afraid of rainy days,)
(afraid of being alone)
(in a room without lights,)
(and hates lying)
(on the empty bed alone.)
So Xiaoming
always thinks
it was all his fault?
Stupid.
It was not your own fault.
You don't have to
be too hard on yourself.
take it all on your shoulders.
That was Xiaoming, not me.
Alright.
Sorry.
I turned off the lights twice.
It's fine.
Anyway, it's only you
who can turn off the lights in my house.
Thanks.
Are you feeling much better?
Yes.
Okay, then I will ask you a question.
It was me who invited you out, right?
What was that all about this afternoon?
You were fixing me up?
Nothing.
Can you drive me back to my bistro?
(White Dark Bistro & Flavor)
Cheers.
You're so excited today.
Great.
So you already knew
that Bai Lang is not mentally stable?
I only know
when there is a thunderstorm,
he will be in a very bad mood.
I found him out of breath once,
but he refused to tell me
what happened.
No one can get answers from him.
How could you just see him
trapped like that?
You know
he is so stubborn.
Even his sister can do nothing about it.
If you can't, leave him to me.
So do you
feel for him
or fall for him?
The latter.
Will your family be okay with this?
Does that
have any conflict
with my relationship with him?
So you're here to ask for my proval?
Whether you agree or not
will not affect our relationship.
Why are you talking to me?
Because you are his best friend.
So,
I respect that.
If I say no...
I don't drink.
Xun'an.
Let me introduce him to you.
He's my good friend, Jin Xun'an.
He's a dentist,
a very skilled one.
If you have any dental problems,
just go to him, okay?
And he has many talents
like rock climbing.
You know what?
He's a super fast climber.
Nice to meet you.
I'll have a word with him.
Enjoy your drinking.
Go ahead.
I'll have a chat with him.
Okay, I'll leave you two.
(Finally,)
(there's someone
who's able to keep him in control.)
Alex.
Do you know what other customers
think of you and Bai Lang?
What is it?
Well, a classic story
of a boss and a bartender.
Who told you?
I'm not like you who's
always hiding behind the bar.
Maybe because I was forcibly kissed
when I was serving food,
I still got it in my mind.
I can't get out of it.
You were forcibly kissed?
What a bad person.
How could he do that?
We shouldn't learn
from that person, right?
We shouldn't...
Have some water.
Thanks.
Why did you start
speaking in English after drinking?
Happy.
You're not drunk?
Of course not.
People who are drunk
will always say they are not drunk.
Then will you be like this
when you're drunk?
I don't drink.
You know that.
I heard that doctors
are very good at drinking,
because they often inhale anesthetics.
Is that true?
You can invite me for a drink alone.
I don't mind it.
Sure.
Why not?
Alright, I'll send you home.
Rock climbing this morning
and drinking this evening.
You'll definitely have a good sleep.
You really like pulling me down.
Really? I don't remember.
Yes.
The first time you came to my clinic,
there was an earthquake.
You pulled me down
and got my hand hurt.
Later, your sister
asked me to tuck you in.
You pulled me down
and got my hand hurt again.
And,
when I was having a fever,
did you want to change my clothes?
Do I bring you misfortune
when I'm by your side?
(White Dark Bistro & Flavor)
I will start to teach you
how to mix drinks from now on.
How much do you know about wine?
Not much.
Like,
Martini has a strong flavor.
Margarita is mixed with
sweetness and sour.
The one with aroma
is Between the Sheets.
The one with a fruit flavor
is Sex on the Beach.
And Pink Lady with a dense texture.
Okay, you've searched for them all?
And also the language of wines.
Like, Martini is
wanting to talk to you more.
Others are waiting for love,
inviting you to have a one-night stand,
spending a passionate night together,
and Pink Lady,
I am into you.
Why do you want to learn these?
Because these are
the best sellers in our bistro.
What's wrong?
Pick one.
Pink Lady.
Not today.
I'll teach you Gin Tonic first.
Starting with the basics.
But the meaning of Gin Tonic...
Do you want to learn it or not?
Alright.
This is called Hendrick's.
Hendrick's.
A kind of Gin that is commonly used.
It's Gin.
Basically, Gin Tonic...
Director.
(Xunying Dental Clinic)
Mr. Bai wants to see you.
What's the problem, Bai Lang?
Not me.
It's her.
This is my friend, a vintner.
This is Director Jin Xun'an.
Hello, I'm Jinli.
Langlang often tells me about you.
I didn't expect you
to be so handsome even with a mask on.
Your clinic looks very good.
Do you manage it yourself?
How can I help you?
Jinli, your teeth feel bad, right?
Yes, they feel bad.
Langlang recommended you to me
and said that you are meticulous
because I'm a bit afraid of pain.
I've been under a lot of stress
and had a lot of sweet food recently,
so I feel a little bit...
Sorry, my day is full.
You can go to other dentists.
Wait a second.
Just help her.
She came all the way from the south.
That's none of my business.
You're a doctor.
She's not feeling well. Just help her.
She looks good.
She doesn't.
And you're free until five o'clock.
Who told you that?
Apple.
She said you have
no patients coming until five o'clock.
Apple.
Yes.
Take that patient to Room 7.
I'll see her first.
I'll deal with you later.
Deal...
Deal with what?
Is everything okay?
Your friend is really nice,
but he's slow
to warm up to strangers, right?
He looks cold.
He is slow to warm up to people.
Or did you have a quarrel?
Or I accidentally blacked out again
after drinking that day?
Actually,
when I first met you,
I thought you were
like an uncontrollable
and spoiled child.
But later when I was with you,
I found that some of your reactions
were actually very cute
and I wanted to tease you.
So,
except for being a doctor to you,
I want to
be your
life...
He's gone.
He's gone?
He looks like this
when he blacks out.
He looks sober,
but he'll remember nothing.
If you were saying something important,
I suggest you
tell him again another day.
You're so cute when you're drunk.
You'll be like this.
I would be like this.
It's also right.
How long will it still take?
Haven't you seen
the patient has waited so long?
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much for today.
I feel much better now. We're leaving.
Let's go.
Thanks for today.
What do you want to do?
I need to talk to you.
I got things to do.
See you next time.
Okay.
Bye.
What do you want to say?
What's wrong with you today?
You're so weird.
I'm weird?
Yes.
Sure. I'm not like you,
chatting so happily
with your romantic friends.
It's not like that.
She's just a friend.
What are you thinking about?
That's great.
She sells wine, and you drink wine.
Why did you invite her to come here?
Well. Isn't it normal to go to a dentist
when having a toothache?
And what does that have to do with wine?
Yeah. Going to a dentist
when having a toothache.
But my clinic is not a place
where you can cut the line for others.
That was only because of you.
And I've told you
to stop introducing people to me.
I'm sending a patient to you.
Why the long face?
Why?
I don't need you to do that.
Are you playing dumb
or did you really black out?
I'm like an idiot...
Apple.
Yes.
Leave the stuff there.
You and Orange go out to take a rest.
Director, you have other...
Out.
I'll leave it here.
Jin Xun'an.
You mentioned "black out".
Did I do something that roasted you
the last time I was drunk?
Otherwise, why are you so unhappy today?
I only remember
I drank a lot last time,
and...
you and Alex were chatting.
Then...
Did he speak ill of me?
Definitely.
No wonder you became upset
when you saw me bring a woman here.
Then what bad things
can he say about you?
He could only tell you
that I asked him to
help fix you up at the most.
It was really a misunderstanding.
I have promised you
that I won't fix you up again,
and she's really my good friend.
I brought her here today
because she had a toothache.
Look.
I've texted you before.
Did you see it?
Okay.
I admit that I arranged them
without telling you beforehand
because I'm nosy.
It was a genuine mistake, okay?
But I really think
you deserve to be treated well.
Am I that good?
People who don't know you
would think you're picky,
indifferent and hard to get along with.
It is hard indeed.
Alright.
But after getting to know you,
they'll find you meticulous
and caring.
So I think you should
find the right person
who understands you, cherishes you
and is willing to be by your side.
Then have you ever thought
that maybe I've already found
the right one?
Our director
was very close to a senior
whose surname is Ye at that time.
He helped that guy every time he needed.
Everyone said
that they would end up together.
Look how cute our director was.
But that senior
married someone else in the end.
(Don't tell the director
that I told you this.)
(I'm not a gossip at all.)
(I know...)
Yes.
That person
is your senior, right?
But you deserve
someone better, Jin Xun'an.
Don't waste your life waiting
for someone who won't come back.
Everyone's life is limited
and unique.
Where did you hear that?
Listen to me.
Hello.
Don't sacrifice yourself
for anyone.
It would be a shame to miss it.
You should seize the day.
I'm telling you.
That was in my college days.
I don't know where you heard that.
Excuse me.
I have made an appointment.
♪Saying I love you♪
♪That's what love is♪
♪Accidents on the road♪
♪Put them in the pocket.
That's our future♪
♪We are getting closer and closer♪
♪Every time I doubt, I get firmer♪
♪You'll hear my heart♪
♪Saying I love you♪
♪That's what love is♪
♪Accidents on the road♪
♪Put them in the pocket.
That's our future♪
You are a regular customer here?
No.
I heard the coffee here is pretty good,
so I just want to try it with you.
Do you often drink coffee?
This coffee shop is small,
but the owner is awesome.
Here's your Americano,
and your coffee tonic.
Please enjoy it.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
Why did you order that? So weird.
Try this cake.
It's limited.
I don't like sweet food.
I don't want too much sugar.
That would make it easier
to get cavities.
This is my self-discipline
and principle as a dentist.
Are you sure about this?
Fine. I'll have it.
(This sweetness is mixed
with bitter and sour tastes.)
(It's not to my usual taste.)
(Stop thinking about why he did it.)
(It's a code violation after all.)
(He obviously should have stopped
outside the boundary.)
Thank you.
Is it still hot?
No.
(Other people's love stories
look romantic,)
(but,)
(do I have the courage to set foot)
(on that desolate wasteland myself?)
Xun'an's first love came back.
He chose to leave
for some reason and felt regretful.
But after losing it,
he will cherish it even more
once he gets it back.
You said we should
get through all problems together.
How nice of you.
I have to be nicer to you.
He's mine.
Don't try to take him away.
That's why you've been avoiding me
lately?
Why do you keep talking
about the senior?
Stop it.
I don't want to mess up the friendship.
I am divorced.
♪Who's the one who walks
past me on the streets♪
♪It can't be you♪
♪Our hearts are close. The closer
I want to be, the farther I am from you♪
♪Blocked outside the boundary♪
♪We become intimate in the passing time♪
♪After turning around,
there is no more chance♪
♪Courage is a necessity
and I really want to tell the world♪
♪My feeling for you♪
♪Just keep the way you are♪
♪It's not worth
losing your heart for others♪
♪Even if the sky is falling,
I'll hold it for you♪
♪Love doesn't need to hide♪
♪Just tell me your unsolved confusion♪
♪You make me fall in love
with the freest light♪
♪I can't stop thinking about you♪
♪My tooth for your love♪
♪Before grasping the love, I was
afraid that I would make you cry♪
♪That's why we didn't move forward♪
♪The fragrance of roses
make parallel worlds overlap♪
♪I'll never give up protecting you♪
♪Love is pure and has nothing
to do with right or wrong♪
♪You are the only solution to the future♪
♪Courage is a necessity
and I really want to tell the world♪
♪My feeling for you♪
♪Just keep the way you are♪
♪It's not worth
losing your heart for others♪
♪Even if the sky is falling,
I'll hold it for you♪
♪Love doesn't need to hide♪
♪Just tell me your unsolved confusion♪
♪You make me fall in love
with the freest light♪
♪I can't stop thinking about you♪
♪My tooth for your love♪
♪You have a face that an angel kissed.
You adorn the moonlight with your smile♪
♪You are more than anything♪
♪My tooth for your love♪
♪For your love♪