(Im Soo Hyang as Oh Woo Ri)
(Sung Hoon as Raphael)
(Shin Dong Wook as Lee Kang Jae)
(Hong Eun Hee as Oh Eun Ran, Yeon Woon Kyung as Seo Gwi Nyeo)
(Hong Ji Yun as Lee Ma Ri, Joo Jin Mo as Chairman)
(Nam Mi Jung as Byun Mi Ja)
(And Kim Soo Ro as Choi Seoung Il)
(Woori the Virgin)
I can't believe I gave birth to this angel.
You did. Who else?
This little angel...
brought me into this world, a whole new world.
Your mother brought you into this world,
and I brought her into this world.
How come he's not here yet?
Who?
Right, you said he'd be here early.
- Your husband. - Your husband.
There he is.
Will you...
marry me?
(Woo Ri and Kang Jae Forever)
(Always Radiant, Oh Woo Ri)
Kang Jae. I'm pregnant.
You're pregnant?
She's pregnant, over.
She's pregnant?
- Pregnant? - What's going on?
Who's the father?
He's asking who the father is.
Mission failed. We're pulling out. Go!
Don't tell me...
you're going to keep the baby.
I'm not an idiot.
Why would I jeopardize my own future?
I'll take care of it.
I'll take care of everything.
What do you mean?
I'll take you to the hospital...
so you can get an abortion.
I'll sue the doctor and the hospital as well.
Well...
I'll take care of everything for you.
Just think that nothing ever happened.
Yes.
It was just an accident, so we'll get it sorted out.
I'll do all the work.
We're still the same.
Nothing's changed.
I'll make it work.
When it's all sorted out,
you will marry me, right?
Get going.
Go inside.
You should get going.
After you go inside. Go on.
Woo Ri, you're home. Have you eaten yet?
Yes, I have.
My gosh.
What happened to you, sweetheart?
Are you coming down with something?
No, I'm fine.
I'm a little tired. That's all.
I should go to bed.
All right.
I should order some herbal medicine for her every season.
She's been constantly catching a cold since last fall.
- Mom. - What?
What? Do you want some herbal medicine too?
Your granddaughter is healthy.
She's so healthy that...
What?
Just look after your own health.
(Artificial insemination malpractice)
(Sperm is injected into an egg...)
(IVF mix-up, given the wrong embryo?)
(Looking for examples of malpractice cases.)
(Question and Answers, Writer Oh in Bukgajwa-dong)
How would it feel to be pregnant with a stranger's child...
due to an artificial insemination mix-up?
I'm an aspiring writer.
(Hello, I'm an aspiring TV writer in her late 20s.)
(This is about a storyline I'm thinking of.)
You've got a wild imagination.
I don't even want to imagine what it'd be like. It's too awful.
Talk about a bad soap opera.
It'll be one ridiculous story.
I might do it if I could get paid a fortune.
How much? How much do you want?
It's got to be more than six figures.
I'd go to jail for 10 months if someone offered me 500,000 dollars,
but I can't carry a baby for ten months!
I won't even do it for a million dollars.
There are many apartments in Seoul that go for over a million dollars.
If it's two million, I'd think about it.
Two million dollars in ten months. Then I'm set for life.
I'd be totally up for that.
Two million dollars...
Do you want to join me?
I can't drink. I'm pregnant.
I'm sorry about earlier.
You should've gotten an abortion today.
You couldn't because I caused a scene.
What's wrong with you, seriously?
I can't believe you hit her.
She earned it, didn't she?
Get an abortion first thing tomorrow morning.
Mom.
I want to ask you something.
What?
Why did you...
Never mind.
Just say it.
I said, never mind.
Okay.
You must have a lot on your mind now.
They say most daughters suffer the same fate as their mothers'.
Why must this happen to you too?
Go to bed.
How can I sleep right now?
There was something...
I had always wanted to ask Mom since I was little,
but I couldn't bring myself to do it.
Mom.
Why did you...
decide to keep me?
My mom gave birth to me when she was still a schoolgirl.
My dad died in an accident,
but she still decided to keep me when she was just a young girl.
If I didn't have Woo Ri back then...
If I didn't...
Oh, dear.
Why did you keep me?
If you were going to regret it that much,
you shouldn't have kept me.
Honey.
What are you doing here?
I called him.
I thought I should tell you the results...
when you were here together.
I see.
Wait, I haven't gotten any tests done yet.
I'm sorry.
You can't just leave like this!
Let's sue them.
We'll sue the doctor and this hospital too!
Ma Ri.
How could she give your last sperm to a stranger?
Ma Ri!
This must've been exhausting for you.
All your desperate antics must've taken a lot out of you.
It's really over now.
We're done.
I only have one chance to make a baby.
And thinking about that...
made me feel like there could be someone out there...
who I'm destined to be with.
What's wrong? Are you not pregnant?
Someone else is.
- What are you talking about? - The doctor...
injected the sperm into the wrong person.
That's nuts.
Mom, it's all over now.
No, it's not!
We can't let our three years' worth of work go down the drain.
But we have no other option!
"Option"? That's...
We'll find a way.
You're always so pessimistic. You see, that's your problem.
I told you to be more positive about everything.
Mom, I'm exhausted.
Oh, my sweetheart.
Are you tired of doing all the work now?
Then let the bear do all the work...
so we can just sit back and enjoy the show.
What?
Remember, the power of positive thinking. "I can do it."
"I got this."
- Who is it? - My gosh! Who?
That woman. The one who's pregnant!
Why do you ask?
I cannot disclose patient information.
You have a red pill and a blue pill in front of you.
- Which one will you take? - Sorry?
If you take the red one,
you'll have to share a tiny cell...
and even a toilet with eight cellmates.
If you choose the blue one,
you can continue working as a doctor.
The blue one. I'll take the blue pill.
I just need her to give birth to the baby.
I just need that woman to deliver the baby safe and sound!
One moment, please.
Here.
(Name: Oh Woo Ri)
"Oh Woo Ri"?
Gosh, the name rings a bell.
She's coming in today for an abortion.
No way!
- My gosh. - Reschedule it.
- Okay. - Try to buy some time.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, what's wrong?
Didn't you see a doctor? Are you not feeling well?
- I'm okay. - You don't look okay.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Ms. Yu.
Ye Ri.
What is it?
Nowadays,
abortions are legal, right?
What are you talking about?
If you get pregnant due to an artificial insemination mix-up...
You...
You're...
finally beginning to understand the charm of bad soap operas.
I like that story!
Thanks.
It wouldn't be a sin to get an abortion in that case, right?
An abortion... No, let's not do that.
How about... Two million dollars?
If a rich family asks her to keep the baby for two million dollars,
then you have a classic story.
The thing is, no one would actually offer that much money.
Both the mother and the baby would have a hard time.
Hey, she can just give the baby to that family,
get the two million dollars, and turn her life around!
However,
it'll turn into a tragedy because of the maternal bond.
"I am your birth mother."
Come on. That's too old-fashioned.
What? You're the one who started this.
Come in.
Hello, Director.
Ms. Yu, Seoung Il wanted to talk to you about something,
- in person. - Yes. Sit down.
You too, sit down.
Well, Ms. Yu.
In the 28th and 29th episodes,
Chun Sa Da shows no emotion.
He's not human. He's like a robot.
A robot, I see.
But last time, you mentioned...
that you wanted to protect Ji Dok Sa like Daddy-Long-Legs would.
That's why I wrote those two episodes like that.
He's like a sunflower.
A sunflower isn't human. It's a plant.
I see, it's a plant.
Ms. Yu is already planning to include some scenes...
where Chun Sa Da is taking action starting with the 30th episode.
Chun Sa Da shouldn't stand out just yet.
Who is she?
Oh, she is Ms. Yu's assistant.
Woo Ri, haven't you introduced yourself yet?
I say hello to him every time I see him.
These days, I guess it's okay for a mere assistant writer...
to cut me off during an important meeting like this.
Is this the latest trend or something?
My apologies. I'm sorry.
The script for the 30th episode will be out tomorrow.
Go over it, and we can discuss this again.
- Really? - Yes, just do that.
Your character's doing great,
and the story will revolve around you.
You can't be in the spotlight every day, you know.
I'm not bringing this up because I want to stand out.
If the characters are not consistent,
the viewers will react right away.
In an instant!
I swear, I'm bringing this up for the sake of the drama.
Of course.
Thanks to you, the drama has been getting good feedback.
All thanks to your concern and hard work. Thank you.
- Seoung Il, you're the best. - I know.
Hello?
You found the address? Where?
Wait, hold on.
Something's come up. I have to go.
And let's keep our spirits up.
This drama has to do well, you know?
Let's do our very best.
- You can do it! - Thank you.
You're feisty. Real feisty.
- Have a good day. - My goodness.
Hello? Where?
My goodness.
Who is it, this time?
One bottle of this sells every second...
where I used to live.
It's the most famous vitamin supplement in Sweden.
You should take better care of your health.
I got it just for you.
Thank you.
I was going to stop by the hospital for the marketing meeting.
Oh, this isn't about the drama.
You go to Rosy OB-GYN Clinic, don't you?
How did you know?
The thing is,
I was supposed to be injected with the sperm they gave you.
Sorry?
My husband and I had been preparing for artificial insemination,
but they made the mistake of giving it to you.
What...
But how...
How did you know that I was the one who got it?
By pure chance... I happened to see the chart...
and realized it was someone I knew.
Since I know you, I can't just pretend not to know about it.
So here I am.
I...
I'll just pretend it never happened.
You see, my husband and I are in a bit of a bind.
My husband had stomach cancer.
He froze his sperm before he began his chemotherapy.
Luckily, he's recovered now,
but the sperm you got was the very last one.
You've met my husband. Raphael.
CEO Raphael?
He's your husband?
We will...
never conceive a child.
Please help us.
Gosh, what could I do...
Our baby.
Could you please keep the baby?
Will you kill our baby?
That was his last sperm.
What am I supposed to do?
Sorry?
What about my life?
(General Waste)
Hello...
I thought...
it was something that only existed in movies.
What?
You know, private detectives who track down people.
- Why are you here? - What about you?
Why did you come to see me?
I just happened to be there.
Then why did you suddenly leave me back then?
I couldn't reach you. Why did you do that?
It's been so long that I don't even remember.
You shouldn't have come...
if you were going to leave like that.
It's been thirty years...
Why did you show up?
Duk Chil...
It's you, isn't it?
Mom.
You're Choi Seoung Il, right?
Yes, hello.
She must be your mother.
It's you. It's Choi Seoung Il.
I'm such a fan.
I watch all your dramas.
I've watched them all. My goodness.
Thank you.
Thanks to fans like you,
I'm able to do what I do.
By the way, what are you doing here?
Well...
He's here for the pork cutlet.
- Yes. - Is that so?
My pork cutlets are famous here.
It's the soul food of Bukgajwa-dong.
They try it in their childhood...
and come back for it when they grow up.
I'll go make some for you.
Are you done?
Yes.
No Man Chul filed a complaint.
I was called in for it.
What are you going to do about it now?
He ran away all of a sudden.
You are always calm when you're working.
But why do you turn all crazy when it comes to Chairman Kim?
Did you think if No Man Chul got to Chairman Kim...
he'd just hand you Chairman Kim on a silver platter?
He'd run away.
Na Hee, you remind us who Chairman Kim is.
He exclusively supplied ecstasy known as "Sugar".
No one's actually seen him,
so he's known as the Faceless Drug King.
He killed the only officer who saw him...
and hasn't shown for two years.
Sergeant Kim Jun Hyuk, who was Kang Jae's partner,
died in the line of duty while chasing Chairman Kim.
I also wake up in the middle of the night thinking of Jun Hyuk.
It upsets me too, you know.
Yes, we need to catch Chairman Kim.
But don't move a muscle before you have hard evidence.
You won't catch him with that attitude. Do you understand?
Don't you go anywhere near No Man Chul.
Then, I'll get going now.
Can you really trust that one?
Why would the police react like that for no reason?
I looked into it, and there is no problem.
So why do a cosmetics event?
It's just the start. So, please, just wait and watch.
Hey. Didn't I tell you I'll start a hospital...
in China in three years?
China has a population of 1.4 billion.
How much is that compared to Korea?
If you just divide 50 million,
I could have that enormous amount of people...
get the double eyelid surgery...
and nose jobs.
So, I need you to focus on the hospital work from now on.
Plastic surgery is our leading product.
You can just tie in the cosmetics.
Gosh, my blood pressure.
Get out all of you.
Father.
What is it Ma Ri?
Actually, I have something to discuss with you.
Let's go.
Father...
What were you thinking?
Are you going to make a big deal out of your mishap by blurting it out?
Well...
Father should know about it as well.
Although I didn't get pregnant,
we have your baby.
I met with the woman who got pregnant.
Are you crazy?
Why would you meet with her?
Because it's our child.
What do you mean?
That was a medical mishap. There is no child of ours.
Honey.
In Sweden or Northern Europe where I lived, surrogate mothers...
- My gosh... - It's quite normal.
Are we in Northern Europe?
Is this Sweden?
This is Korea.
How can you ask a complete stranger to bear our child?
She's not a stranger.
What?
We both know her.
Who is it?
Attention, please.
We ask for your cooperation as we inform you of the visitations.
For patient safety and prevention of external infections,
we are limiting visitation hours...
Why do you need the courage to say something you want?
How can you achieve your dream if you can't say what it is?
Say it to me.
My dream is to become a drama screenwriter.
That's it. You should say it aloud so it comes true.
Say it again.
My dream is to become...
a drama screenwriter.
My dream is to become a drama screenwriter!
Writer Oh Woo Ri!
Yes!
But I still want you to find out patients' inconveniences...
Then, keep up the hard work.
Yes, sir.
After I heard you went through all that,
I was shocked.
I also heard that the marketing team leader came to see you.
So I was pondering whether to go and apologize to you.
But I thought it was right that no one bothered you.
I will make sure no one bothers you from now on.
I'm sorry.
What about you?
Me?
I heard you could no longer have children.
Your wife sounded desperate.
I'm curious about your thoughts.
Well...
Being given a chance to live again...
after realizing I could die,
the first thing that came to mind...
was that I wanted to start my own family.
Yes.
I really want a child.
But this isn't the right way.
You should only think of yourself, Ms. Oh.
Pretend you haven't heard about our problems.
It was an accident.
I know you're going through a lot because of the accident,
so I'll do anything to help you fix this.
I had the baby back then.
- I thought you had an abortion. - It's a long story to tell.
You said you had an abortion.
You wanted to end the relationship.
You said you didn't want to see me and that I should go away.
And now you tell me, there's a child?
What's the reason for revealing this after 30 years?
Well...
She's the assistant writer for your drama.
The assistant writer?
I wondered what kind of fate this was.
You would have met once or twice while working together.
The thought of you two in the same space...
not knowing each other...
seemed too harsh.
That's why I decided to tell you.
- I should go meet her right away. - I'll tell her.
Let's go right now. We'll tell her then.
She's going through a lot now. Give her some time.
What is it? What is she going through?
How can this happen?
This is big for us,
but you said something bigger happened to our daughter.
So what is that?
Yes, something big happened.
Not us, but our daughter!
Your daughter's name is Woo Ri. Oh Woo Ri.
Oh...
That artificial insemination accident story I told you about...
What if the girl knew who the sperm belonged to?
What would she feel like?
Yes, that's how you should approach this.
Gosh. You really are talented for outlandish stories.
You should say that he turned out to be her first love.
And the girl should have secrets about her birth.
Excuse me?
What did you learn from Writer Wang?
Secrets about one's birth are a given.
The middle-aged man she knows turns out to be the father.
That's absurd.
Hey, what's your problem?
You're the one who brought it up.
Hello.
Mr. Choi.
Hello, Seoung Il.
I brought something to eat. Some snacks.
Thank you.
I'll work on the script revision.
No need for that.
I took a look at the script again, and it's perfect.
I don't know what got into me earlier.
No need for revisions. It's perfect.
Are you sure we don't need to revise it?
Of course.
I think I was a bit rude earlier.
I wanted to apologize as well.
And to our assistant writer.
Ms. Oh Woo Ri.
Yes?
I don't know what got into me earlier.
I mean you work so hard.
And you're so beautiful.
Didn't you say you didn't have any scenes to shoot today?
Your outfit changed.
It's all about self-maintenance.
I've always done my best in all the shows I've done.
That's why I was able to get to where I am today.
I have 957,000 followers so far.
I'm by far the best amongst all the middle-aged stars.
DiCaprio of the provocative dramas.
You also follow me, don't you?
Yes... Sure.
How have you been?
- Excuse me? - Any troubles?
You don't look so well.
No, that's not it.
I just don't feel myself today, that's all.
Yes, Woo Ri doesn't feel so good today.
She was going to leave early today.
Would you like to leave early? We don't need to revise the script.
Yes, would that be okay?
- Of course. - Then...
I'll give you a ride if you're sick. I was about to leave now.
No, that's okay.
Why don't we talk about the script?
What's there to talk about? It's perfect.
You just need to write it as you want.
- Hey, wait... - But since you are here...
I think I can write it properly once you tell me precisely.
What should Chun Sa Da do to Ji Dok Sa here?
I told you it was perfect!
I heard you knew the girl already.
It's someone who works for the drama that we sponsor.
Father should know about it as well.
Ma Ri made a big mistake.
What mistake? She did well.
Ma Ri went over her head and caused this medical mishap.
Both of you need to get it straight.
You should be the one to get this straight.
We can't have our family line cut off here.
It already has!
It won't work. Nothing works.
No matter what I do, it won't work.
What's wrong now?
Raphael just hates me.
Nothing is easy.
You need to think positively.
What do you want me to do when nothing is working?
Stop crying...
and do as your mother tells you to.
If Raphael won't cooperate,
you need to work with someone that will.
The chairman is on our side, isn't he?
You need to work with your father-in-law.
Father?
Darn it.
Who is it?
You can't ignore me.
If you want me to keep calling you ma'am...
you need to listen to me.
Make sure you keep this necklace on you.
Only then I'll feel relaxed.
You're still mine.
Don't you know him? He's called Chairman Kim, the drug dealer.
I have my hands on one of the lists that'll make money.
There was a reason why the police came for you.
Right, I didn't tell you.
My shift changed.
I'll come with you to the hospital tomorrow.
What hospital?
Well...
She has dry eyes. She's going in for a prescription.
Yes, that's it.
Okay. Let's go.
That was close.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Let's see.
Gosh.
Gosh. That feels so good.
Anna, you should try it as well.
I don't need to. My shoulders are fine.
How?
I'm healed when I see my granddaughter Woo Ri.
I have no pain.
If I had a granddaughter like that...
I'd be full without eating.
Veronica, you should take care of yourself.
You had pain all over your body...
when your daughter got divorced last year.
Our Maria hasn't even gone on a trip...
being abstinent.
Anna.
- Anna. - Yes?
- Maria... - What about Woo Ri?
She's pregnant.
Lee Kang Jae, you jerk.
Gosh.
You jerk!
How dare you do this to my granddaughter?
- Grandma, what are you doing? - You good for nothing jerk.
- Grandma. - How dare you touch her?
- What? - What did I do?
It's all over the church that Woo Ri is pregnant.
- What? - Pregnant?
You promised. How could you?
- Grandma. It's not Kang Jae. - What?
What do you mean?
I am pregnant, but it's not Kang Jae.
What?
Then, who?
What's all this?
How could this happen to a girl who has been kind all her life?
Say something.
Anna.
I heard the story,
but it's out of the ordinary.
Should we keep the child since it's new life?
Or have my granddaughter have an abortion and make her a sinner?
What should I do?
Is this why I've been to church all my life?
To have my granddaughter go through such a thing?
What do I do with Woo Ri?
I feel sorry for my Woo Ri.
Anna.
Have some tea.
Yes.
But...
I know it's rude coming to you so suddenly,
but it's such an urgent matter.
Please have my grandchild.
- Excuse me? - My son is the only child...
but he can no longer make babies.
I can't believe my son has no sperm.
He's the eldest son.
It's up to you...
whether my family lives on.
This old man is begging you.
Shall I kneel?
No, this is not that kind of matter.
I understand your unfortunate circumstance.
But as I told you before, I have my circumstances as well.
No need for a longer conversation. Get rid of this.
- Yes? - Get rid of the fruit basket.
Right.
(Fresh Apples)
You should take this.
We have enough apples as well, thank you.
It was difficult in such situations back in the day.
There weren't any 50-dollar bills.
Stuffing the box with ten-dollar bills...
barely came up to 200,000 dollars.
It became more convenient now.
I filled up this box with one million dollars...
for you to take.
- Excuse me? - I, Kim Duk Bae,
do not behave that indecently in my old age.
I'm not trying to ruin your life.
We are in a difficult situation...
and ask for a difficult favour.
If you would just have the child,
we will make the right compensation for it.
I'm sorry, Ms. Woo Ri.
I kept on telling you our side of the story...
and left out what we would do for you.
Stay abroad for about ten months.
Think of it as going to a language school.
I'll give you a million now and a million more after the baby.
I'll give you two million in total.
(Fresh Apples)
Two million dollars...
If that's not enough,
just tell me how much you want.
I'll give you as much as you want.
Just have our child, that's all.
She can just give the baby to that family,
get the two million dollars, and turn her life around!
Two million dollars in ten months. Then I'm set for life.
I'd be totally up for that.
It's a private loan.
If you don't pay back,
the interest becomes larger than the principal.
With 50,000 dollars,
I'm confident I can make an album and become a big hit.
You don't want any apples?
At least take the fruit basket.
Father, what do we do?
If she turns down money...
That's how they are at first.
They have their pride in not accepting money right away.
Money solves everything.
Goodness.
What should we do, Woo Ri?
What else is there to talk about?
She'll get an abortion tomorrow at the hospital.
She'll be committing a sin then.
What are you talking about? That's not a sin.
Don't talk like that in front of her.
How could something like this happen to my granddaughter?
Oh, no. What do we do?
Abortion is considered a sin in the eyes of the Lord.
Enough.
Then you expect her to carry out the pregnancy?
Will the Lord give her an award? Will the government give her money?
It's not a sin. She has the right to do so.
Woo Ri's life can't be ruined.
Mom. What about you?
Did I ruin your life?
What?
I won't have the baby, so don't worry.
Why would I complicate my life with a burden?
I will never do something I'll regret for the rest of my life.
Right.
You should get an abortion, right?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
I'm all right, Grandma. Don't worry.
Okay.
Should I turn on the radio?
- Love isn't a joke - Goodness.
I'm sorry.
(Rosy OB-GYN Clinic)
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Please come this way.
This way.
Ma'am, here.
Ma'am. Woo Ri.
What are you doing here?
Who are they?
I would like to...
discuss something with you.
So you want my daughter to have the baby. Right?
Yes. But...
Get up. We don't need to hear it.
Gosh. Please.
I'm sorry. Please sit down.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You know,
I worked day and night and became successful all on my own.
I don't want much at this age.
I only have one son. But my son...
I can't believe he has no sperm.
He's the eldest son.
That's your problem.
That's none of our business.
How could you be so harsh?
What if there's no one left to hold a memorial service for you?
Would you be happy with that?
We are Catholic.
Then should I let my lineage stop here?
Do you want my granddaughter...
to ruin her life just for your lineage?
Well, you see,
we don't plan to make a ridiculous demand.
We offered reasonable compensation to your daughter.
Reasonable compensation?
How can you reasonably compensate her for ruining her life?
You can stay abroad for as long as you want.
We will make sure it stays confidential.
And we will also compensate her financially too.
You're asking my daughter to be a surrogate mother.
You want her to sell the baby for money.
They are unbelievable.
Two million dollars.
We offered two million dollars.
We can give you more if you request it.
That money will not ruin your life.
It can give you a new chance at life.
It's the kind of money...
even your mother and grandmother won't ever get to make.
It's two million dollars.
I told you I needed 50,000 dollars to make my album.
They won't let a single mom become a singer.
I had to give that up to raise you.
It would've been better if I were ten years younger.
If I didn't have Woo Ri back then...
Two million dollars?
You want her to carry out the pregnancy?
The answer is no even if you offer 20 million dollars.
Why?
Woo Ri is my daughter.
You think money can solve everything, right?
There are things you can't do with money.
Not my daughter.
You can't ruin her life...
even if it can save my life.
Ma'am. Why are you so unreasonable?
Will she die from it?
We're simply asking her to have the baby.
Should we kill the baby in her womb?
Will you commit murder?
Hey! Watch your mouth!
If you bring up money again,
I'll arrest you all for violating Clause 3 of Article 23...
of the Enforcement Rule of Bioethics and Safety Act.
Who are you? A lawyer?
When did you get here?
What are you doing?
Why are you meeting with them?
I told you this was illegal.
I'm sorry.
I would like to apologize to you and your family.
Please forget everything...
they told you.
Well, sir.
Yes?
Woo Ri.
This way. Let's go.
Goodness.
Did it go well?
You said it was a simple procedure.
What?
- Ma'am. - Mother.
- Are you all right? - Are you okay?
- Be careful. - I can't believe this.
My mother had me as a teenager when she was still in school.
Even I don't know what to do at the age of 29.
She must have had a lot on her mind.
How scared she must have been.
But she must have had a reason when she decided to have me.
There must be a reason why I'm in this world...
and why something like this happened to me too.
There must be a reason for that.
She's still not answering her phone.
Where did she go?
Woo Ri. Where have you been?
Why didn't you go through with the surgery?
Woo Ri.
You're not considering their offer, right?
Don't give a thought to what those jerks said.
Mom.
Grandma. Kang Jae.
I'm going to...
have this baby.
What do you mean? Why would you?
You were a victim of a medical accident.
This is the same as getting infected at the hospital.
Then what about me?
Was I an accident too?
Was I an infection?
What?
Why did you have me?
Do you regret having me?
What are you talking about? Why would I regret having you?
Mom.
When I was in middle school,
I heard you say...
you shouldn't have given birth to me.
You couldn't be a singer because of me.
What you said had scarred me my entire life.
It didn't go away.
I was a burden to you.
I didn't want people to look down on me.
I didn't want to make even a single mistake.
That's why I pledged to abstain.
Woo Ri.
I thought...
you went through with the pledge...
because you were embarrassed that I had you at 16.
I never thought I couldn't be a singer because of you.
I wanted to be a successful singer...
because I wanted to be a mom you could be proud of.
I don't care what my job is. I have you.
There were so many moments...
you made me happy ever since you were born.
It's quite the opposite. I always felt bad for you.
The thing you tell me the most is...
"Mom, why do you live like that?"
I'm not good at anything.
I always cause trouble.
I'm far from being a perfect mother.
You're embarrassed of me.
No, Mom.
Why would I be embarrassed of you?
I'm so proud...
that you are working so hard to achieve your dream.
You're my mom.
You brought me into this world.
I wouldn't trade you for anything in the world.
You just healed the scar in my heart.
You don't have to tell me why you decided to keep me.
I know why.
I'm the reason why.
Woo Ri.
Mom.
You gave me a chance.
So I'm loved by so many people in my life.
Now, I want to give a chance to this baby.
Why you?
Why did this happen to you?
Do you think having a baby is easy?
You think it will just come to you?
It's a huge responsibility.
I know that too. I'm ready for it.
When your mother told me...
she was pregnant 30 years ago, I didn't think about anything.
A 16-year-old girl was pregnant. I told her to get rid of it.
I dragged her to the hospital to get an abortion right away.
But your mother ran away.
She's a good runner.
If she wasn't a good runner,
it would have been a huge problem.
I don't know why I was so against it back then.
I prayed and repented all my life.
But you and your mother are in different shoes.
You didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything that requires you to be responsible.
I know that.
But still. I have a chance to bring a baby into this world.
You have a very beautiful, generous heart.
But still. Why must you do it?
Grandma. If Mary's grandma was against it,
Jesus wouldn't have been born.
You're not Virgin Mary. Will you give birth to Jesus?
That's my religious name too.
You gave that name to me.
Goodness. Oh, no.
Oh, no.
- Gosh. - We'll be okay.
(Seo Gwi Nyeo's Pork Cutlet)
Must you have this baby?
I'm sorry.
I know that my decision right now is very unrealistic.
Just ask anyone on the street.
They will say I'm crazy.
Right.
To be honest, it's not easy for me either.
Even my family can't understand me.
I won't ask you to understand my decision.
I'm sorry for making a selfish decision.
But I don't have the right to stop you...
from making that decision.
I'll just...
I'll just help you make a wise decision.
Kang Jae.
Woo Ri.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Yes!
- Hello? - Ms. Oh?
This is Raphael.
Hello.
What's this about?
The hospital said you didn't get the procedure.
I was wondering what happened.
If there's a problem, I'll help too.
There's no problem.
Actually, there was something I need to tell you in person.
Are you free tomorrow morning?
I'll go to your hospital.
Sure. But what's this about?
I'll tell you in person.
You're certain, right?
Yes!
She said she would have the baby.
I had a feeling she would...
when she left without getting the procedure.
There's always a way out!
You were right about everything.
- We must be positive. - We must be positive.
It was perfect until now.
I forgot about this problem.
Mom. What do I do?
We can't mess up our grand plan because of a bug.
Gosh. There's a bug!
Hey, you're here.
If that couple is the parent, the baby will be happy for sure.
But we should discuss this thoroughly with the couple.
It won't be as easy as you might think.
We'll have to draw up legal documents too.
So...
we should talk to them first.
If you don't agree with them, you can change your mind.
- Kang Jae. - Yes?
I'm so relieved to have you by my side.
Hello.
Thank you for coming to our hospital.
No Man Chul.
No Man Chul!
(Special appearance by Hwangwoo Seul Hye)
(Woori the Virgin)
Gosh. It turned out Raphael used to be quite the party boy.
I want this baby to grow up in the perfect family.
Of course. I agree.
The wife desperately wants to have a baby.
And I thought she would be a great mother.
You know, the CEO is a total player.
What do I do? Would I be able to raise this baby well?
You want us to raise the baby.
You and I are on the same boat now.
Raphael? Can you look into him, Kang Jae?
I saw something fishy with my own eyes.
We've met before. Right?
(Woori the Virgin)