(Im Soo Hyang as Oh Woo Ri)
(Sung Hoon as Raphael)
(Shin Dong Wook as Lee Kang Jae)
(Hong Eun Hee as Oh Eun Ran, Yeon Woon Kyung as Seo Gwi Nyeo)
(Hong Ji Yun as Lee Ma Ri, Joo Jin Mo as Chairman)
(Nam Mi Jung as Byun Mi Ja)
(And Kim Soo Ro as Choi Seoung Il)
(Woori the Virgin)
What's this?
Throw it out.
Then this list will make us money.
You keep the list with you.
Give the necklace to someone.
Oh Woo Ri?
How are the scripts coming along?
They are great.
Gosh. This is a set.
Goodness.
I put the necklace in her bag.
- No one saw you, right? - No.
You're sure nothing will happen to her, right?
Like what?
They'll scare her a bit and take the necklace from her.
Go to the hospital...
and spread the word Oh Woo Ri has the necklace,
so Chairman Kim knows.
Okay.
I should mention it here and there, so it won't look obvious. Right?
You don't have time for that.
Do it in one go.
- Hello. - Hello.
You guys are working so hard, so I brought some coffee for you.
Thank you for the coffee.
How are things going? Do you need any help?
What? No.
Please have some coffee.
Oh, no. My necklace.
What about your necklace?
My necklace is gone.
I must have left it in the writer's studio.
I left it in the assistant's seat. So she must've taken it. Right?
The assistant writer?
I'm sorry. I don't follow you.
You know, her name is Oh Woo Ri.
I'm sure the assistant writer took it.
It was a present to me.
An artisan handmade the necklace.
He told me not to lose it, but I forgot it there.
I should get it from her later.
From Assistant Writer Oh Woo Ri.
Hello.
Were you trying to broadcast your chitchat?
I'm sorry. When did this happen?
I'm sorry.
Guys, let's go home now.
If you keep staring at it, your eyes will get bad.
You already checked everything before.
If Na Hee is right and there is a list,
where would that be?
The list of card transactions.
I'm reviewing every single document.
What? A necklace workshop?
What do people do here?
Hey. I went to one with my girlfriend.
You can pay and make a necklace you want.
Right. There are a lot of handicraft workshops these days.
Hold on.
You will be able to make the necklace however you want.
Right.
- What's this? - Your necklace.
You submitted it as evidence before. And I'm returning it to you.
Gosh. The one who gave it to me is dead now.
No Man Chul gave this to you?
He gave it to me and nagged me to wear it every day.
He was so sensitive when I didn't wear it.
- Darn it. - Where are you going?
- Where are you going? - Kang Jae!
Sir, do you remember this necklace?
I remember this.
A client custom-ordered this necklace.
He asked me to make a small gap in the necklace,
so he could insert a memory card.
I'm sure there's a list that shows their before and after photos.
- Thank you. - Sure.
(Lee Ma Ri, Team Leader at Diamond)
Mom.
Mom!
Mom. Are you all right?
What did you say?
Okay. I got you.
- Why didn't you answer your phone? - How did you find me here?
Where's the necklace from No Man Chul?
- I don't know! - I must find it.
It's not here!
Where is it then?
Oh Woo Ri has it!
Where's the necklace?
What necklace?
Grandma!
Woo Ri!
I'm a cop.
- Grandma. - Police.
Drop your knife
Please don't hurt my grandmother.
Chairman Kim?
Don't move. Drop it.
Kang Jae!
Mom.
Fine.
Please let her go.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Oh, no. Grandma.
(Sungho Hospital)
Ma'am.
Mom.
She has no external injuries.
They did a CT scan and examined her.
She had a concussion,
but due to her age, her vitals are a bit shaky.
When will she wake up?
She might wake up tomorrow or in a few days.
But they can't guarantee anything.
But she will wake up, right?
She will.
They have to examine her brain...
once she wakes up to know if her brain had been damaged.
Okay.
You guys went through a lot without me.
Are you all right, Woo Ri?
Are you hurt? Should we get you a doctor?
No.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
She's hurt because of me.
Why is this your fault?
Had I gotten there sooner...
No.
I couldn't have done anything without Kang Jae. I was so scared.
Thank you, Kang Jae.
I have to go back to the scene.
Okay.
Thank you. You should get going.
Hey.
Woo Ri.
You must have been scared.
I'll catch the culprit.
He took the necklace.
He was looking for the necklace.
I had a necklace I didn't even know I had.
How did he know?
And his voice sounded like it was altered through a machine.
I'll look into it.
It...
reminded me...
of a cold snake.
I'll take care of this right away.
Until then,
you must be careful and don't be alone. Okay?
Okay.
I'll get going now.
Call me if there's anything.
Kang Jae.
Thank you.
- There's Kang Jae. - That's Detective Lee.
So Chairman Kim was here?
What makes you think so?
The scalpel.
Chairman Kim took No Man Chul's necklace.
I'm sure the plastic surgery list of criminals was in the necklace.
Any evidence?
He's about 175cm tall.
And his build...
His shoulders were broad. And that's pretty much it.
It was dark, and he was covered up. He wore gloves too.
We found out his shoe size is 270mm from the footprints.
And that's everything the forensic team found.
Not even a fingerprint or a strand of hair.
This will be tough.
Gosh. This guy is meticulous.
Chairman Kim broke into Woo Ri's house.
But I lost him right in front of me.
I'll do whatever it takes...
to find him.
Just pack the necessities.
We'll be away for a few days.
You think Park Du Pal won't come back after a few days?
How did he get out of the chains?
If he wanted to harm us, he would have done it by now.
Considering everything he's done, he can't come after us.
Mom.
Weren't you scared when you were taped up like that?
Why would I be scared?
He'd better not show up.
I'm going to...
That startled me.
What are you doing here at this early hour?
The necklace.
Why did Woo Ri have that?
Do you know what's inside the necklace?
Something is inside the necklace?
Why did Woo Ri have that?
Did you give it to her on purpose?
Why would I give that to her?
I was carrying it because I didn't want to wear it.
But I remembered that I left it in her seat...
when I went there for a meeting.
Is that a crime?
You really...
don't know anything about the necklace?
I told you.
I didn't like it because No Man Chul gave it to me.
Did something happen?
Someone was after the necklace.
Who?
We're investigating, so we'll find out.
You should go home. You need to go to work.
I'm not going to work.
I'll stay by her side.
Then go home and change your clothes.
Let's take turns.
I can't go.
I want to stay with her.
Woo Ri. Go and come back.
Go and bring me some clothes too.
You should bring back what you need as well.
The rosary.
The rosary?
We need her rosary.
She prayed with the rosary for important occasions.
And her prayers were answered.
The rosary she had ever since I was a kid.
I'll be back, Mom.
(Funeral Hall, Basement 2)
Hello?
Woo Ri. Did you go to work?
Raphael.
Woo Ri. What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
My grandma is unconscious.
What?
Sir.
The buyers from China have arrived early.
Something urgent came up. I'll be back soon.
What came up?
What's more urgent than our guests from China?
Sir, I'm really sorry. But I'm in a hurry.
I need to get there fast.
I wish I could help you too.
But it's not like I can fly. This is too bad.
What?
Why didn't you tell me about this?
I'm a teacher too. A teacher at a singing school.
So I'll be the perfect teacher of the day.
What will you teach us?
Singing.
Trot.
Mom. Please.
Woo Ri. What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
Nothing, Grandma.
I should pray too.
Do you want to borrow my rosary?
I have one too.
Woo Ri,
this rosary is special.
All the prayers are answered when you pray with this rosary.
I save it only for important occasions.
- Really? - Yes.
A long time ago when I was young,
at my first Communion,
my mother...
So your great-grandmother gave this to me.
From mother to mother.
It's been in our family for generations.
It seems like you have something on your mind.
I'll let you borrow it this once.
What do I do?
I didn't tell her about the teacher of the day event.
I can't tell her because if I do,
I'm going to hurt her feelings.
I don't want her to act silly at school.
I think I'm going to be...
really embarrassed by my mom.
Where is it?
(Teacher of the Day Program)
Here is your sauce.
- Thank you. - Eat a lot.
Let me know if you need more.
Woo Ri, your mom is the best!
This is so good!
Woo Ri, your mom is so pretty. She looks like a celebrity.
Here.
Here's your rosary.
Okay. Did you pray with it?
Was your prayer answered?
Yes.
This rosary is the best.
Woo Ri.
Do ask me again.
When there's a prayer you want to be answered,
ask me if you can borrow my rosary again.
And then pray. Okay?
Grandma.
Woo Ri.
Dry skin, combination skin, oily skin,
triple care, tone-up care, whitening care, and anti-ageing.
In total, we have seven types in our skincare line.
Now, we'll take a look at the details in order.
Chairman Kim went into Woo Ri's house.
He was looking for a necklace.
He even altered his voice.
Altering his voice means that he's someone we were in contact with.
We need to check yesterday's alibis of the Diamond Foundation people.
We can't poke around the hospital without proper evidence.
We won't even be issued a search warrant.
You're not in the right mind because Woo Ri's house was robbed.
Let's calm down and respond.
Captain, Woo Ri's grandmother is hurt. How can I calm down?
Kang Jae.
I'll be going to a Patrol Division next year.
While I was working in the Violent Crimes division,
five got hurt badly and one died.
You are not in your right mind right now.
Big accidents happen in such a time.
People should no longer get hurt.
Get a hold of yourself first.
- Mom! - What is it?
You said we should take turns sleeping.
I dozed off.
Are you seriously sleepy in this situation?
Darn it.
He won't come here.
How would Park Du Pal know we are here?
You are the one who suggested the night watch.
I'd rather go home than do the night watch.
Wait!
Can't we just let everything go?
What if we get hurt or something?
I heard that he started to look for the necklace.
What if something really happens?
Mal Ja, that list in the necklace...
is definitely worth something.
Otherwise, they wouldn't have moved so fast to look for it.
We still need to wait. Okay?
(Device has been connected.)
I have the list that you want.
Don't even think about hurting me like No Man Chul.
If something happens to me,
the list will automatically be delivered to the police.
If you want it, make a payment.
You have a new message.
(You said this would be over when you got the list.)
(You said no one would get hurt. What's going on?)
(Reply back quickly before I put you away.)
(If I get caught, you'll be done for as well.)
(Just listen to me until the job is done.)
(Message sent.)
- Your son is here. - Okay.
What brings you all the way here?
I can't get a hold of Eun Ran since the morning.
I'm getting a little worried.
Is Ms. Seo Gwi Nyeo here?
I can't get a hold of her either.
(Eun Ran)
Stop making me cry...
and wake up.
Mom,
the last thing I said to you was...
When we were fighting over Hyung Sik,
I told you I didn't want to be your daughter.
If you don't wake up like this,
I will hate you forever.
I'll be the daughter...
that was spiteful to her mother because of a man.
Hello? Eun Ran.
Duk Chil.
Why? What's wrong?
Mom collapsed.
She won't wake up.
What? Mother is ill?
What do I do if she doesn't wake up?
What are you saying? She'll wake up.
Which hospital is she at?
I'm sorry, but I have a full schedule today.
It's okay. You are busy.
I'll call you back later. You take care of her.
You can't be weak. All right?
Okay.
Please take care of the rest.
- Where are you going? - Something urgent came up.
What urgent thing?
We need to show our guests around the hospital and have dinner.
- Right? - Okay.
I'm sorry Woo Ri, I just left. Are you at the hospital?
I'm on my way to the hospital with a few things from home.
All right. I'll go and pick you up.
No, it's okay. I think I'll get there faster if I take the taxi.
Okay, then. I'll see you at the hospital.
- Woo Ri. - Kang Jae.
Isn't that the rosary that you borrowed from your grandmother...
every time something came up because it answers your prayers?
Yes, it is.
Your grandmother will really like that.
What made you come back?
I heard from Mother. I told you not to stay alone.
You must be really busy.
I feel bad about it.
It's okay.
Even if it's not for you, Grandmother did so much for me.
Her soy sauce braised beef was so good.
It'll be difficult to taste it from now on.
What? What do you mean by that?
Why are you saying such a thing?
I don't mean that.
I mean since we broke up.
Right.
Right, last year...
Last winter when I was on a stakeout for a few days,
Grandmother came over with a packed meal.
It was so good, I still remember it.
Soy sauce braised beef and quail eggs were the best.
It must have been her sincerity, right?
You know it takes a long time to make it.
It's difficult to peel the shells of each quail egg.
She uses the peeled ones.
Right.
Woo Ri, don't worry about it too much.
She'll wake up soon.
She's one of the strongest people I know.
That's right.
She'll wake up soon.
Grandma, your rosary...
It's just a rosary.
She collapsed because of me.
- Stop saying ridiculous things. - Grandma...
Grandma.
What's happening? What's wrong?
We'll tell you after we treat her. Please step outside.
Quick.
Woo Ri, drink something warm.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Woo Ri,
don't worry anymore.
I'm here now.
They said her vitals were off a little,
but they came back to normal quickly.
So you don't have to worry too much.
Why won't the doctors explain things clearly?
Emergency rooms are a bit like that.
They must have been busy, and things must've been hectic.
They said they didn't have any rooms and told us to wait in the ER.
But they moved us here.
It turns out that I had some people I knew at the hospital.
So I asked them for a favour.
They'll take care of her more from now on.
Thank you.
No, it's nothing.
I should've come earlier.
Mr. Choi.
Didn't you say you have work? How did you make it here?
I cleared up my schedule. How is she?
She'll wake up soon. You can stop crying now.
Only think good thoughts from now on.
Detective.
I heard you missed the culprit at the scene.
I told you there was a criminal hiding in your hospital, didn't I?
- Yes. - That guy broke into Woo Ri's home.
Who is that man?
I'm looking for him.
I'm going to catch him.
I'm never going to let this happen...
to Woo Ri and her family.
I'll take care...
of Woo Ri.
This happened because of the culprit hiding in your hospital.
Two people died...
and I ran around to solve this.
But you were only concerned about the Foundation's image.
Hello? Hi. How are you?
It's been a long time.
Well...
didn't you say you had a person who caught an industrial spy?
Right. A private investigator.
Ms. Lee.
Are you feeling better?
You said you couldn't come in today.
Mr. Kim was looking for me, that's why.
We also have that PPL meeting later.
That meeting has been cancelled today.
There was a break-in at the assistant writer's home.
- At Oh Woo Ri's home? - Yes.
Someone in her family got hurt and is in the hospital.
(Sungho Hospital)
Woo Ri.
Yes?
Grandma's rosary.
She said it was a secret and told me not to tell you.
What secret?
Didn't she sound like...
that there's a long history with the rosary?
Grandma was lying.
Didn't she say it listens to your prayers?
That's also a lie.
Your grandmother...
is a great liar.
Whenever you had concerns, you prayed with her rosary.
Every time you prayed...
she eavesdropped on your prayers...
and helped you behind your back.
I don't want her to act silly at school.
I think I'm going to be really embarrassed by my mom.
You said you'd do a singing lesson for Teacher of the Day, right?
Yes, why?
You should change the subject.
What do you mean?
You should change it.
Is this the right thing to do?
Wouldn't a singing lesson be better?
Gosh.
Do you want to teach students trot songs?
I mean it doesn't have to be trot songs.
Just listen to what I say.
Everyone loves food.
This is so tiring.
Enjoy.
(Teacher of the Day Program)
Did you all get one?
You guys are eating well.
Mom.
Thank you.
Grandma was my guardian angel.
Thank you, Grandma.
I'll be your guardian angel from now on.
I'll take care of everything,
from what you want to want you need.
Just as you did for me.
I'll take care of it.
So Grandma,
stop sleeping and wake up.
This way.
You must be worried...
since this happened so suddenly.
According to the test results,
she doesn't have any serious external injuries.
And since she moved to the ward, her vitals are back to normal.
I don't think you need to worry much now.
Doctor,
when will she wake up?
Well...
that's the most difficult part to say.
I heard you said that she was a strong woman...
and that she'd wake up.
Then, she'll definitely wake up.
She'll wake up soon.
Thank you, doctor. Thank you.
It's the first time I heard something good since I got here.
I apologize for not being able...
to care for each patient and their families like we want to.
You must have been so startled.
Many who work as a doctor...
are still quite young.
They can't sleep...
and work frantically.
Let me apologize on their behalf.
It's okay.
Thank you, doctor.
It's nothing.
It's only natural for your family.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's have a meal together next time.
Mom.
You said no one would get hurt.
You know how many people rushed over because you collapsed?
I'm so jealous.
You attracted enough attention...
so please wake up.
I think I'll be annoyed if you keep this any longer.
Mom.
Please open your eyes now.
Stop making me cry.
Mom.
I really regretted saying those words to you because of a man.
I'm sorry.
I must have been crazy. He's not that important.
You are a lot more important to me.
Please forgive me.
Mom,
I'll break up with Hyung Sik.
As long as you wake up, I'll break up with him.
I promise.
So...
you just need to wake up.
Grandma.
Mom.
Gosh, Mom.
- Mom, you woke up! - Are you all right, Grandma?
Stop...
- What did you say, Mom? - Goodness.
Stop shaking me like that!
Mom, do you remember who I am?
- You? - Yes, who am I?
You are...
my troublemaker daughter who never listens to me.
- Grandma... - Mom.
Woo Ri.
Oh, she regained consciousness.
Mother, are you all right?
What? What are you doing here?
What do you mean? You collapsed.
Of course, I should be here.
You must be busy though.
I'm okay. I'm totally fine now.
I'll tell them to run some tests on you right away.
You're here too.
Yes. I'm so glad that you woke up.
Everyone is here.
Are we throwing a party or something?
Kang Jae. Where is Kang Jae?
Why are you looking for Kang Jae?
Some burglars broke in, and Kang Jae came to my rescue.
That's right, Grandma. Kang Jae carried you here.
Hey, Kang Jae. It's me.
Yes, Grandma woke up.
You were the first person she asked for.
Is she okay?
- Hold on. - Thanks.
Kang Jae, I heard you saved me.
No, Grandma. I'm so relieved that you woke up.
You saved my life.
Thank you, Kang Jae.
Grandma...
Don't cry.
- Are you okay now? - I'm fine.
Hey, are you all right?
Yes!
Hey, Kang Jae.
I heard Woo Ri's grandmother regained consciousness.
- Yes. - Thank goodness, seriously.
- Captain. - Yes.
There's something that exactly overlaps...
with the two years that Chairman Kim was gone.
Let's think it over before we tell Captain.
No. What is it? Tell me.
Raphael's battle with cancer.
What?
Raphael was battling cancer...
during the two years that Chairman Kim was gone.
As soon as he recovered and returned to work,
Chairman Kim came back too.
Kang Jae, do you think you're Detective Conan or something?
- Sorry? - Investigate!
Stop speculating.
The chairman of Diamond is close to the higher-ups.
It's already making my life difficult.
And what? You're after his son now?
If you snoop around without solid evidence,
we'll be on the chopping block before we catch the culprit.
Well, since when did we care so much about the higher-ups?
You already went there and caused trouble!
You see, the higher-ups are vying for a chance to teach you a lesson.
Stop talking nonsense.
Anyway, I'm relieved.
You have a new message.
(Lee Kang Jae is coming too close.)
(I'm struggling to keep him in check.)
(We should send him on vacation. I'll help you.)
(Message sent)
Kang Jae, this came for you.
What is this? Who sent it?
The courier left it out front.
The conscripted officers brought it in.
Goodness. They should've checked.
(To Lee Kang Jae)
What is this?
Isn't this for a safe?
Where did I see this?
What? This is...
See? I told you.
Home is much safer than some motel.
You won't run into Park Du Pal at work.
Just listen to me and...
Hey, Park Du Pal.
Don't do this. If you want money, I'll give you however much you want.
- Don't do this, okay? - I don't need money.
Then what do you want?
I'll give you whatever it is that you want.
Just put the knife down, and we'll talk it out.
What can you do for me?
You see, I wanted to get a decent job...
and live a happy life with Mal Ja.
I had decided to devote myself to making her happy.
But...
you beat me up just because we registered our marriage.
That's why I caused the accident, and I'm an ex-con now.
You two ruined my life.
I just want to end everything now.
If you want to end your life, go ahead.
But please let my daughter go.
No.
I need someone to keep me company.
Hey, you're... You're still so young and can turn things around.
Why would you end your life?
Put that down.
I said, put it down.
Put it down.
Mom, do something!
Hey, don't... Don't die.
Do something!
Du Pal. I mean, sir!
Sir! Please forgive me. I'm really sorry.
Please... Please forgive me.
Lee Mal Ja.
I loved you.
Let's meet again in our next life.
Mom...
Mal Ja!
No, Mal Ja...
Mom.
Are you out of your mind? What are you doing?
Mom, I see that you can walk.
Why were you in that wheelchair for the past three years? Just why?
To make me obey everything you say?
Is that it?
I only did it out of love.
I don't want to hear it!
You deceived me for three years!
You scumbag!
What on earth have you done?
I need to talk to you.
Hear me out, okay?
I'll take my hand off. Don't scream, okay?
Hey, your mom can walk!
What?
Last but not least, I need to say this.
She doesn't love you, Mal Ja.
So you don't love yourself either.
I could see it so clearly.
So as a man who loved you, it broke my heart.
Don't worry, Raphael. I'm okay now.
Thank you.
Okay, go inside and get some rest.
I'm so glad you could come home soon.
Thank you for everything.
Visit us sometime. I'll make you dinner.
May I?
You're always welcome at our house.
Thank you.
We'll see you inside.
What? Wait.
- Good night. - Bye.
You must've been really worried and scared today.
You should go inside and rest up.
Raphael.
Thank you so much, for real.
I really mean it.
Gosh, I didn't even do anything.
Then why don't you let me take you out on a date?
And please call me when you have some time.
I'm off tomorrow.
So am I. Then we should hang out tomorrow.
I can see you tomorrow, right?
Yes.
What? That was so quick.
We left you two alone so you could talk.
I'm going to see him tomorrow.
Grandma, go inside and get some rest.
Why are you still here?
She's full of energy now.
I'm still a little dizzy,
but I'm trying not to show it because I don't want to worry you.
Grandma.
Your rosary broke.
Oh, no.
I wonder if it can be fixed.
From now on, I'm your guardian angel.
My guardian angel? Why?
You've been my guardian angel all my life,
so I'm going to protect you from now on.
Right by your side.
My gosh.
You're such a sweetie.
What about you?
Me? What about me?
When I collapsed, did you think of...
doing anything for me like my sweet granddaughter here?
Mom.
I'm going to stop seeing Hyung Sik.
Why? You neglected me and went on about your boyfriend.
And I was wrong.
- I should break up with him. - Really?
Then can I continue seeing Chun Sam?
By all means.
What?
This jerk.
My gosh. How many passports does he have?
US dollars, the Japanese yen...
Here it is.
When you're fixated on something, you go on about it like this.
Honestly, I'm sick of it now.
Kang Jae, we can't be sure yet.
We have to look further into it.
You're fixated on the fact that Raphael was fighting cancer...
during the two years that Chairman Kim was gone,
so you're making this up.
Come on. I've known you long enough!
I swear, I'm not making it up.
We just need a warrant. Then it's game over.
Please.
- Trust me just this once. - That's enough!
I feel drained now because of you.
Gosh, I'm exhausted. I need to go eat something.
Wait, Captain.
What?
You saw it?
I saw it, with my own two eyes.
What is this place? Is it a castle?
This is so cool.
What is this place?
It's a restaurant.
- Please leave. - What is going on?
- Hey! - What now?
We have a warrant.
We need you to open the safe for us.
Where is Raphael?
He's off today, sir.
The safe? Why? What's in it?
Just open it.
And you'll see.
He's not here, so how can I open it? I don't know the password.
Oh, that's...
We brought some tools for that.
- Right? - Yes.
Please cooperate.
Move aside.
Thank you, sir.
Let's see. It was somewhere around here.
- Captain, cover me. - I got you.
Let's see.
Six, four, seven, one...
- Four. - Four?
Hey, what is this?
What? Where did everything go?
Lee Kang Jae, you're in deep trouble now.
What? The necklace was right here.
I swear, I saw it last night.
What are we going to tell the chairman now?
You got it open. So what's in the safe?
Well...
We must've been mistaken.
Listen, you cops.
Must you keep this up?
Are you going to keep doing this to us?
I clearly told you I wouldn't just sit back and watch.
We're just trying to investigate...
Get out!
Get out, all of you.
Where is Raphael? Call him now.
The thing is, sir.
He told us not to contact him today.
Why not?
He's out on a date.
He said he wouldn't pick up.
Do you like it?
Yes.
What is it?
We're the only ones here.
I guess the restaurant isn't doing so well.
But it's nice here.
Oh, that's...
I know, right?
I guess they don't get many customers.
Sir, it's ready.
Thank you.
What is it? Is something up?
No.
Just a moment.
There's...
a lady I like.
Lately, she's been having a hard time.
So I hope...
this will entertain her even if it's brief.
No way.
That can't be.
Don't tell me...
No way.
Has he been watching old-school dramas?
Don't sing.
Seriously, don't.
The door opens
And you enter
The moment I first saw you
- Woo Ri! - I knew
Woo Ri.
- Kang Jae. - Detective Lee, why...
Let's go.
- What? - Hey.
- What's wrong? - Detective Lee!
What's the matter?
Come on. Let's go.
Why are you being like this, all of a sudden?
Detective Lee, what's going on?
You can't be with this man!
(Woori the Virgin)
Just sleep here.
I'm so excited about the next three days.
You can't do this knowing we're under the same roof.
Raphael, let's set a date.
I've never felt this sure before.
This is what it's really like to have a family.
I'm watching you.
I know who Chairman Kim is.
I spotted a face we know in the footage.
Kim Bok Rae is the prime suspect in the case.
- Do you have evidence? - Yes.
Will you marry me?
(Woori the Virgin)