(Im Soo Hyang as Oh Woo Ri)
(Sung Hoon as Raphael)
(Shin Dong Wook as Lee Kang Jae)
(Hong Eun Hee as Oh Eun Ran, Yeon Woon Kyung as Seo Gwi Nyeo)
(Hong Ji Yun as Lee Ma Ri, Joo Jin Mo as Chairman)
(Nam Mi Jung as Byun Mi Ja)
(And Kim Soo Ro as Choi Seoung Il)
(Woori the Virgin)
(Episode 3)
Pregnancy and motherhood...
play a big part in a woman's life.
Definitely. Giving birth is a massive undertaking.
Some women struggle to return to work after giving birth,
and some people end up quitting their jobs.
It's a social issue.
Right. They talk about it often on the news.
There's a novel about it. What was the title?
I don't want to lose control of my life.
Woo Ri, does this mean you've changed your mind?
I want to prove to myself that life can still be the same...
even after going through pregnancy and giving birth.
Even married couples are hesitant to have kids these days, you know.
Having a baby is much harder than you think. A baby is...
No. I'm not going to call it a baby anymore.
Yes. Let's call it "Mallet".
"Mallet"? Will that be the baby bump nickname?
No, let's just call it like that. There's no reason behind it.
I'll call it "Mallet" because I don't want to call it a baby.
I've made up my mind.
I'm heading out to meet that couple.
No Man Chul.
No Man Chul!
What are you two doing right now?
Woo Ri, that must've given you quite the scare.
- Are you all right? - Yes, I'm fine.
You still need to interview me, right?
Well, would you like to go see a doctor first?
The witness interview can wait until tomorrow.
Kang Jae, I'll go see my doctor.
Okay, Woo Ri.
I can't leave while they inspect the scene.
Right. I'll just go alone.
I'll take her to the doctor.
No, it's okay. I can go by myself.
I'll come with you. We can leave now, right?
Sure. Then please come to the precinct with your wife tomorrow.
Sure, I'll help in every way I can.
Help them tidy up.
And try to calm the patients down.
Okay.
Ms. Lee. Your meeting is over, right?
- Yes. - This way, please.
Kang Jae, you were the one who found him.
Did you notice anything?
The aorta was cut with a scalpel.
He bled out and died within 30 seconds.
It's exactly the same as Chairman Kim's MO.
Chairman Kim isn't the only one who stabs his targets in the neck.
Besides, there are scalpels everywhere in the hospital.
Investigate objectively without bias.
Consider all possibilities and comb through everything.
The hard drive for security cameras is gone.
What?
The forensics team hasn't found anything yet.
This won't be an easy case.
Goodness. It must be someone who knows the hospital inside out.
First, let's find out who had hostile relationships with him.
Hey, Detective Kang. Tell Forensics to wrap it up.
Do you remember seeing anyone suspicious at the scene today?
Hello, thank you for visiting...
You must've been so scared.
Gosh, my heart is still pounding.
Yes, it was scary.
But the thing is, I came here to talk to you about something.
Right. What happened yesterday? Is everything okay?
I never thought I'd say this,
but I decided to keep Mallet.
Sorry? Keep what?
Oh, sorry. The baby. I'm going to keep the baby.
What? Why?
Sorry? What do you mean, why?
Oh, don't get me wrong.
It's such a big decision for you.
Why did you suddenly make that decision?
There's no special reason.
I'm just so grateful that I was brought into this world.
What?
Oh, I'm Catholic. Every life is precious, you know.
Right, I see.
Do you not want the baby?
I heard you couldn't make another...
I do. I really want the baby.
I just didn't think that you'd decide to keep the baby.
But you're working at the moment. If you suddenly get pregnant...
The drama will end in three months' time anyway,
so I'm just going to stay home and take it easy after that.
I wanted to write a drama on my own,
so this works out.
I'll give it a shot this time.
Oh, I see.
I'll bill you for my medical and other expenses.
That will be enough.
I don't need the money I was offered the other day.
Don't worry about it.
What?
Money? Did she offer you money?
Yes.
Goodness.
She can be really crude at times.
I apologize on her behalf.
It's okay.
I understand how desperate she must've felt.
If you need anything, just call me.
This must've been a very difficult decision for you.
I don't know how to thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
I made this decision for my own sake.
The test results look good.
You've been sleeping well, right?
- Yes. - Do you get morning sickness?
No, not yet.
I'm glad...
that both you and the baby are healthy.
Yes, me too.
I feel so frazzled today.
Actually, there was something...
I wanted to ask you and your wife in person.
What is it?
I grew up without a father.
Of course, I'm so grateful to my mom and grandmother,
but I want this baby to grow up in the perfect family.
Having everything it needs...
and receiving lots of love from Mom and Dad.
I want the baby to be happier than anybody else.
I made this decision because I trust that you and your wife can do that.
Right? You will do that, right?
Well, that's...
I told you that I wanted a divorce.
Well, I don't want a divorce.
When you told me you'd decided to do this, it didn't feel real.
It's only hitting me now.
I feel the weight of responsibility on my shoulders.
The perfect family for the baby.
Yes, of course. Sure thing!
Wow, yes!
So about the baby, she decided to keep it.
Good. That's great.
I told you. Money solves all problems.
But the two million dollars... She won't ask for all of it, right?
- Let's knock off a little. - We should, right?
How much will you knock off for your own happiness?
Hey, did you talk to her? The more, the better.
I scrapped the whole thing...
and made it zero. Happy now?
You... Well done!
Be embarrassed of yourself.
You see, money doesn't solve everything.
She's offended that she was offered money.
She made the decision because she believes every life is precious.
I bet you can't wrap your head around it.
She doesn't want the money?
Forget it, then. Why would you criticize me?
- Goodness. - Hey, stop.
Once word about the stabbing death spreads,
the hospital will go out of business.
Keep the media out!
This morning, a murder took place...
at a large medical foundation in Gangnam...
that is famous for plastic surgery procedures.
The victim, No, is a man in his 20s.
He was found stabbed to death in an elevator at the hospital.
So, No Man Chul is dead.
It is said that he worked at the hospital.
He died at the scene...
- immediately after being stabbed. - Mom.
Did you kill him?
What am I, Professor X?
How could I kill someone sitting in my wheelchair?
Did you hire someone to do it?
The police will investigate all employees of the foundation...
as well as those connected to the victim.
You know, those who devote their lives to their children.
I always thought they were so pathetic.
"They must have nothing else going for them."
"That's why they want to ride their children's coattails."
I always thought that.
But you see,
ever since this happened to my leg because of you,
your success has been my sole focus...
and my sole devotion.
If I can make you successful,
I don't care who dies,
even if that's me.
I really don't care.
So?
Did you kill him?
If I get caught, I'll be the one getting arrested.
You'll be fine, my princess.
- Mom! - I didn't do it!
I did think I should kill him if he got in the way,
but it wasn't me.
Right? It wasn't you, right?
There are times when the universe looks out for you.
What?
You couldn't get pregnant,
but a stranger shows up pregnant and says she'll have the baby.
There was a jerk whom you wanted gone,
and he dropped dead.
You see, it means...
the universe is focusing its energy on you.
I'm home.
Did you meet the couple? What did they say?
They're very grateful.
How come you look so flustered? Did something happen?
No, it was just a long day. That's all.
I should get some rest.
Woo Ri.
I thought about it all day.
Giving your baby away won't be as easy as it sounds.
Mom, stop calling it a baby.
It's Mallet.
I won't change my mind.
That couple really wants Mallet.
And they're well-off, so Mallet will be happy.
- We have nothing to worry about. - Well, the thing is...
Who is it? Just answer it.
This is about my daughter's life. Who cares about a phone call?
Woo Ri, I understand why you made such a decision,
but the reality is very different from what you think.
Hey! Either answer the call or turn off your phone.
Are you a stalker?
I didn't pick up because I couldn't. Must you keep calling me?
Are you free later?
I want to talk to you in person.
- I'm busy. - Come on, Eun Ran.
I can't even eat...
or sleep.
You see, I've lived like that my whole life.
I told you that my kid is going through something.
I'll tell you once things get sorted out.
Wait patiently.
I'll call you, so stop calling me.
Wait, Eun Ran!
Seriously...
Does she not see how much I care about her?
Gosh, why...
Eun Ran!
Ms. Yu.
You say you have meetings, but all you do is get facial treatments.
When will you work on the script?
The director will yell at us.
She does this all the time.
Hey, I told you that you should get it done too.
With that handsome face, what do you expect?
I knew it.
He has a heck of a nickname.
What is his nickname?
Actress Hunter.
He only dates actresses, one after another.
But he's married.
As if he cares.
He just does whatever he wants.
I heard lots of rumours about him.
What kind of rumours?
There were articles about it. Look it up.
(Diamond Medical Foundation, Raphael)
("Gangnam Hospital Owner's Son Parties With Celebrities")
("Rich Heir Throws Bikini Party on Yacht")
("Caught on Secret Date With Actress Mo Ye Ji")
How about another drink at the hotel?
I'm...
I'll pass.
Come on.
We came all the way here. Let's have some fun.
How about we meet again here tomorrow?
Babe!
You look great today.
("Hospital Owner's Scandalous Conduct")
("Gangnam Hospital Owner's Son Parties With Celebrities")
("Rich Heir Throws Bikini Party on Yacht")
("Caught on Car Date In Middle of Night")
Woo Ri.
Hey, Woo Ri.
My gosh. Why are you working so hard today?
Don't do more than you get paid to do.
Okay.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Were any of you personally close to Mr. No Man Chul?
No one?
Sorry, excuse me.
Detective Lee.
Are you interviewing my employees again?
Yes.
We have to investigate until the perp is caught. Please cooperate.
Clearly, we are cooperating. However...
Must you do this in front of the patients?
This is a hospital, you see.
Ma Ri, could you take them...
Take them to the meeting room.
Sure.
Let's go to the meeting room.
Is the investigation going well?
Well...
It's not easy.
You know, the chairman's son.
He's got an attitude.
Raphael?
Kang Jae, what do you think of him?
Doesn't he look awfully calm considering his employee died?
You should look into him.
I'm already on it. Don't worry.
Look at you, talking like a detective.
No, that guy...
I think he's a philanderer.
People call him "Actress Hunter".
What? That's what you want me to look into?
That's his personal life.
I saw something fishy with my own eyes.
I can't send Mallet to someone like that.
That's not why I made the decision.
"Mallet"?
I've decided to call the baby like that from now on.
Kang Jae.
Can you look into him, Kang Jae?
I heard he caused a DUI accident once...
and even threw a drug party.
Can you please find out...
if he has a criminal record? Please?
Just because I'm a cop, it doesn't mean I can do stuff like that.
If I'm caught, I'll get fired.
Then what should I do?
I can't send Mallet to a dysfunctional family.
The wife desperately wants to have a baby.
And I thought she would be a great mother.
Woo Ri.
I said you'd run into problems you had never even thought of.
You'll run into more unexpected issues.
I suggest you rethink...
No, I can't.
I told Mom that I'd make this work no matter what.
I told her I was sending Mallet to the perfect home.
I'll find out.
I must find out if there's something wrong with the husband.
(CEO Raphael)
Hello, sir.
I was just wondering...
if I'd be able to see you and your wife...
I mean, I'd like to speak with you and Ms. Lee Ma Ri in person.
Both of us?
That's right.
I'd like to discuss a few things regarding the baby.
I see.
Well...
But I'm not sure if Ms. Lee can join us. She's very busy.
What?
This is about the baby. She's too busy?
Well, no. We should meet.
But...
can't you discuss it with me?
Is there a reason I shouldn't meet with your wife?
No.
It's not... It's not that.
You can meet her, of course.
Then I'll check her schedule and get back to you.
- Wait. - Talk soon.
Hello?
He hung up? What the...
He hung up on me?
Is he out of his mind?
I'm asking to meet up because of the baby, and he's too busy?
I had to take this call. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Since there are a lot of eyes watching,
please understand having to meet like this.
I understand.
But still,
I'm just happy that we can meet like this.
Hey!
Why did you come?
Why is fate so cruel?
Let me talk to my daughter.
Let me tell her that I'm her father.
This is so hard on me.
It's difficult for Woo Ri as well.
Stop making a fuss.
Did something happen to Woo Ri?
I met her, but she didn't look so good.
Meet her? Why?
I told you to wait.
Stop shouting at me.
I work with her.
I met her at the writer's office.
You didn't tell her you're her father, did you?
I didn't.
But she's so beautiful.
She is.
She's the most beautiful, the kindest, and the smartest.
Gosh.
- Choi Seoung Il! - Choi Seoung Il?
Mr. Choi Seoung Il?
What?
What brings you here?
- Well... - Well...
Oh...
the other day at the hospital event.
Oh Eun Ran!
Do you know each other?
Well...
- You're back. - What?
Did you like my pork cutlet? You crave it, don't you?
Yes.
Have you been here before?
Well, that is...
Actually,
Eun Ran and I...
Were classmates. From middle school, aren't we?
What? You didn't know that until now?
His face changed a little, that's why.
So, that rumour about plastic surgery and faking your age...
Gosh, no.
What a relationship that is! Take a seat.
You didn't eat, did you? Shall we have dinner together?
- Dinner all together? - Yes!
- Seriously? - Yes!
Then let me treat you.
I'll take you to a nice restaurant in town.
- Yes. - Don't you need to go now?
- You said you were busy. - Me? Busy?
You wanted to meet next time since you are busy.
- Right? - What about dinner?
Next time.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Ms. Oh,
see you again.
Hey, let's go.
- Come quick. - Wait...
- You're so busy, you need to go. - Wait, I should be there...
- What about dinner? - I should...
- No, come quick. - Wait, wait.
- You need to stop this. - Eun Ran, we'll get hurt.
This is not the right time. No.
- You should go and don't come back. - Wait, seriously...
No! Just leave.
("Son of Hospital CEO Spends 20,000 dollars a Night at Club")
(Elaborate parties of rich kids in the movies were a true story.)
(CEO R, known as the son of a hospital CEO...)
(was found to have spent 20,000 dollars at a club.)
I thought about it all night.
Kang Jae,
What if I decide that I can't...
give up Mallet to Raphael's couple,
after careful consideration?
I couldn't sleep thinking about that all night.
Do you think I could raise it well?
Nothing's decided yet.
So, don't think about it too much.
(Diamond Medical Foundation Scalpel Murder Case)
Gosh, do you not have more on...
No Man Chul's surroundings after our last meeting?
I don't care how trivial, just report it.
Don't you have any?
Doesn't he have any girls or something?
See? He has no manners.
That's why you don't even have a girlfriend.
We need to go! Wildcat is out.
Let's go.
We need to go. What are you doing?
I need to change the baby's diaper, first.
Lee Kang Jae!
What?
Don't you have anything to report?
Why are you spacing out like that?
I'm sorry.
I have nothing to report.
This is annoying for me too.
The police officers are at the hospital all the time.
That's why you need to be careful.
Don't leave any traces of you meeting Man Chul.
I know.
I only contacted him through a messenger, so I won't get caught.
And I even deleted all that. Hang up, will you?
We already know that you were in a relationship with No Man Chul.
That's not true.
He just followed me around. We didn't have a relationship.
In Sweden, this is considered a greeting, that's all.
If you throw out such a thing, the police will be suspicious.
Put it back.
The police is suspicious?
I've been interviewed many times, and they didn't know I knew him.
You're the only one who knows about this, aren't you?
For now.
Aren't you, MS. Oh Woo Ri's fiancé?
Ms. Oh Woo Ri has the baby...
She wouldn't want to send the baby to a murder suspect.
So if something goes wrong on my side...
you might end up raising the baby.
That's not a nice thought, is it?
Ms. Ma Ri,
I've been investigating for days.
Your call history, messages, and your e-mails, everything.
I even checked the black box videos.
I didn't report it because there were no charges.
I guess you and I must be on the same side.
Excuse me?
You want us to raise the baby.
I'm so desperate as well.
I think you need to help us a lot.
Make sure you hide the things that my husband shouldn't find out.
Mom, do you know what just happened?
You wouldn't believe it. This is incredible.
I think the universe is on our side.
I met this police officer, and you won't know who he is...
Wait, my necklace.
Nothing, just hang up.
Wait!
Stop.
Detective Lee Kang Jae.
I think you need to help me.
Are you sure this is for us?
- Yes. - I mean, then who sent it?
Hello, everyone.
It arrived. It looks so luxurious.
I wanted you to work in a comfortable environment.
So I sent all of this.
Was it too much?
But this is nothing for me if it's for the baby.
I would do more if I could.
Whatever you do, I'd like for you to run it by me before you do it.
Right.
I will talk to you first from now on. Okay.
Well...
I actually had something...
I wanted to tell you.
What is it? Tell me.
Are you close with Choi Mi Ae?
No, we are just acquaintances.
Just acquaintances...
- Well... - Raphael?
What?
Hello, Da Bin.
Gosh, you. It's me, Ye Rin.
- Right, Ye Rin. - How have you been?
It's been so long.
I'm having a business meeting here. Let's talk later.
All right.
- Call me. - Yes.
- Sir. - Yes?
Do you know a lot of women?
No, well, just a few friends...
What were you asking earlier? What about Choi Mi Ae?
Nothing.
I'm sorry. Just a second.
(Incoming Message)
(Actress Mi Ae)
(I don't want to reveal it yet.)
(How long are you going to keep this a secret? Call me.)
Ms. Oh, shall we go now?
What's going on? Are you okay?
Yes.
I just slipped.
What? Are you all right?
Yes, I'm okay.
I don't know why I slipped.
Do you think that makes sense?
Am I your errand boy or something?
What can I do? The necklace has my initials on it.
Do you want me to be interviewed?
Why don't you help me out a bit?
Good job everyone.
Who's this?
Why are you here?
I just wanted to take a look again.
- What brings you here? - I came to see...
if I missed anything.
- Did you find anything? - No, I didn't.
I couldn't find anything.
You see, I have my own situation.
So I don't want to let anyone know yet.
Why is this embarrassing?
Weren't you sincere about it?
Is this something that we're not proud of?
Please, understand.
Ms. Oh, what are you doing here?
Hello.
I'm here to have a drink.
Alone?
Yes, by myself, of course.
Sir.
What's going on between you and Ms. Choi Mi Ae?
What do you mean?
You shouldn't be this way.
Excuse me? What do you mean?
I think I have a right to tell you this.
If you continue to act like this, I'm going to reconsider.
How can I trust you to have a baby...
Gosh.
Oh gosh.
I think there's a misunderstanding.
We're not like that...
- this is... - Auntie!
Soo Hyun, you're here.
Say, hello. This is Raphael.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Soo Hyun, say hello.
You must be shy.
You even brought a gift for him.
Go ahead, give it to him.
Here, thank you.
She wanted to give you her favourite stuffed animal.
Thank you so much.
Thanks to you, we met some good doctors.
And we were able to get through.
Is it okay for me to have this?
Yes.
(Mr. Raphael, I will get better.)
(Thank you for introducing a good doctor for me.)
But,
I didn't do much.
Honestly, I said that this meeting even was too much.
This is all for Soo Hyun.
Soo Hyun,
thank you for the gift.
I also suffered from the same disease as you before.
And I'm all better now.
See? I'm all healthy.
You will get better too.
So, listen to what your doctor tells you...
and get your treatment bravely, all right?
Yes, I will.
Well...
I have something urgent to attend to,
so I'll get going.
Goodbye.
Go, Soo Hyun!
Wait, Ms. Oh.
Let's go together.
What's wrong. It's fine.
Sir, I think I'll get off now.
Wait.
Here? You can't.
How can you go from here? Let's talk a little.
The weather's nice today.
Right.
I've looked you up online for two days.
You did?
There are a lot of things about me, aren't there?
Yes.
There were a lot of articles,
photos, and rumours...
Yes, I partied a lot.
Nobody hates having fun, do they?
Right, it seems that way.
But a lot of it is exaggerated.
I wasn't that bad.
Do you want to see this?
This is my mother. Isn't she pretty?
But she passed away early when I was in middle school.
I think I started to act out ever since she died.
You know those kids who do things they're told not to.
I was like that even after I became an adult.
And then one day, they told me I had stomach cancer.
The funny thing is...
that my mother died from stomach cancer as well.
And I had the same disease.
When the doctor told me...
I had stage three stomach cancer,
it felt like my mother...
was telling me that I shouldn't live like that...
from above.
I think my mom is so great,
telling me such a thing so that her son would live properly.
Isn't she such a great mom?
Ms. Oh,
I understand that you don't want to send the baby...
to a weird person.
But...
I'm not that kind of person.
I may have been once,
but I'm not that person anymore.
I'm sorry I questioned you.
Wasn't that a reasonable suspicion to have?
I was so worried...
that Mallet would have an unhappy life.
Who? Mallet?
Pardon?
- I decided to call the baby that. - Right.
I was out of my mind because I was so worried.
I followed you.
Sir,
you don't have any problems...
between you and Ms. Ma Ri, right?
There's nothing going on between us.
Please sit. Continue with your work.
Where's Ms. Lee?
She went out for work.
Should I call her?
- No, I'll do it. - Yes, sir.
Did you find my necklace?
I threw it on the tray.
Is this it?
This is it. Thank you so much.
What's wrong?
I'm going to keep it while the investigation is going on.
Aren't we on the same side?
I'm still thinking...
whether or not I should join you.
Honey.
Tomorrow?
Oh, really? No, we must go.
Tomorrow, 2pm, at the hospital?
Okay.
Thank you.
Perfect.
You're going to the hospital tomorrow?
Yes.
You too?
Darn it.
Woo Ri!
Thank you so much.
I don't know how to thank you.
Not at all.
Are you here alone?
Since it's your first ultrasound,
my husband and father-in-law are all here.
Are you alone?
No, they're parking the car.
Hello. How are you?
Thank you so much. You're doing the right thing.
Get your hands off her.
It's good to see you like this.
We might grow on each other if we keep this up.
We won't be meeting again.
You must be glad to have an heir to carry on the family tradition.
You just have to die now.
- What's wrong with her? - Let me introduce myself.
I'm Raphael, CEO of Diamond Cosmetics.
I'm the owner of the sperm.
He means he's the father.
Okay. And I'm Woo Ri's mom.
Thank you for making the tough decision.
Call me if there's anything you need from me.
I think it best we meet as little as possible.
- Let's register. - Okay. Sit somewhere and wait.
Woo Ri, ladies.
What shall we name the baby when it's born?
Will it be a boy or a girl?
I hope it's a girl that looks like me.
How could it look like you?
It could look like me.
Wouldn't a boy that resembles Raphael be so cute too?
Oh Woo Ri?
- Yes? - Yes!
It's her right here.
Hello, doctor.
I'm the grandmother.
Oh, the grandmother of the baby she's carrying?
In that case, I'm the great-grandmother.
I called the hospital director.
Isn't there a bigger room?
This is the largest ultrasound room.
There are too many people. A few of you must leave.
You wait outside.
You should.
Can you not point your finger?
- Hey. - Detective Lee.
Did you not say hello to my father-in-law?
You're an officer?
Say your hellos outside. I can't do anything like this.
Who will leave?
I... I can't leave.
- I'm her fiancé. - I'm the grandfather.
- I'm the mom. - We're her family.
- We can't leave. - We must be here.
Quiet!
- Oh Woo Ri! - Yes? That's me.
- Who's the baby's father? - I am.
Other than these two, the rest of you can leave.
Okay?
- No. - Call the director!
- I called him! - You don't have to worry.
- This is my heir! - We're family!
Republic of Korea!
I can't do anything if you won't cooperate!
- Let's go, then. - Okay.
- We must leave? - You started all this.
Let's begin. The gel is cold.
Okay.
Are you okay, Ms. Oh?
Yes.
You can call me by my name.
Don't call me Ms. Oh.
I'm just an assistant writer.
No. You write stuff and that makes you a writer.
Since when did you want to be a writer?
Since I was in middle school.
I wanted to be a writer,
so I studied literature in university.
The more I learned, the more daunting my dream became.
I considered trying to become a teacher,
but on my pre-graduation trip...
I dream of...
becoming a drama scriptwriter.
But I feel too overwhelmed to start.
It's the first time I voiced what I always thought.
I was too timid to even talk about it.
Why do you need the courage to say something you want?
How can you achieve your dream if you can't say what it is?
Say it to me.
My dream is to become a drama screenwriter.
That's it. You should say it aloud so it comes true.
My dream is to become a drama screenwriter!
That's it!
- Ms. Writer. - Yes?
- Ms. Oh the writer! - Yes?
Writer Oh Woo Ri!
Yes?
There was something I'd never done in my life.
I found the courage to do it on my pre-graduation trip.
That's when I started to try to work as a writer.
I see.
To the person who gave me the courage,
I'm thankful, even now.
Look at the monitor.
It's too soon to hear a heartbeat.
What you see here is the baby.
It's the size of a gummy bear.
It's so tiny.
Hello, gummy bear.
How many times must I tell you?
It's fine.
Okay.
Doesn't it feel weird knowing they're in there alone?
I feel strange too.
I did a lot of thinking,
and I changed my mind.
I'll report it.
What?
Are you crazy?
You'll raise someone else's baby?
Ma Ri!
Yes, Father?
Chairman Lee's wife called.
Is there more to be done?
I got her another nose job done last week.
The baby seems to be so healthy and cute.
The mother's healthy too.
Isn't that just great?
Watch your footing on the steps.
There are steps. Be careful.
That's it. Take your time.
We're almost there.
She's my fiancée.
She has my baby.
What are you two doing?
They're just steps. I can manage.
(Detective: Lee Kang Jae)
Oh, dear. What's this now?
I went against your order and looked into No Man Chul.
No Man Chul's mistress...
is a team leader at a medical foundation,
and the wife of a cosmetics company CEO.
What?
(Photo Evidence)
Why are you bringing me this now?
I apologize. I didn't report it.
Are you out of your mind?
Lee Ma Ri's clean.
But a detective has a hunch.
It was clearly Chairman Kim, but it looks like an affair...
I apologize. I made the wrong call.
I want a written account from you.
The rest to the meeting room. We'll start over.
What is it?
Here.
Divorce papers?
Why did you call me to the hospital?
Hadn't you changed your mind?
Didn't you hear Oh Woo Ri say we can't have the baby if we split?
Look inside.
It's the size of a gummy bear.
Seeing it made me think.
I still can't forgive you for what you did.
But for the baby's sake...
Thank you! Thank you, darling!
How does it feel to be a mom?
A mom?
Why?
What is it? Are you that emotional?
There will be many more things to be emotional about.
What should I do?
About what?
It wasn't a mallet.
What do you mean?
It's a baby, not a mallet.
It's not an object I can give away.
I feel stupid for thinking that way.
To be honest,
I wasn't in my right mind for the past few days.
To see if it was right to send it to a good home,
I did all sorts of things.
I feel this way because of something the size of a fingernail.
I can't imagine how I'll feel...
after I give birth after nine months.
You're right.
You were right...
about how I'd feel about giving the baby away.
I really...
didn't think it would be this hard.
The truth is,
and I haven't told anyone,
but when I look at this photo, I get so scared.
It's okay.
It'll be okay, Woo Ri.
You made this choice,
and whatever other choices you make,
I will support you now.
That's what your grandma did for me.
Yes.
I'll do it for you too.
I really don't know, Mom.
It doesn't mean I found the courage to raise it.
I'm just so scared.
I just don't know anything.
It's okay, Woo Ri.
I don't know anything either.
When Eun Ran had you,
and now that you have this baby,
I didn't know then, and I still don't know what to do.
Let's just...
solve one piece of homework that we're given at a time.
No one knows if our answer is right or wrong.
Let's just do our best to solve it.
You can't cover the sky with one hand.
As a father,
you must protect your family.
The truth no longer...
No longer what?
What is it now?
What's the matter with him these days?
Why is he talking nonsense?
The truth...
Cut!
Are you all right?
You must do another take.
Use the clip we just took and wrap up for the day.
I must be somewhere.
We have to shoot today's quota.
You're doing great. I'll buy you wine.
Seoung Il!
Will someone go after him?
You can't cover the sky with one hand.
I must tell my daughter that.
You can't.
She's too worked up.
She's struggling.
Why is she struggling?
Tell me that at least.
I might end up dying first.
Woo Ri.
I'm your father.
I must tell her now.
Eun Ran.
It's not recycling day today.
- Why is this out here? - Hide.
Hide, quick.
There's something more valuable.
Eun Ran?
- More valuable than revenge. - Wasn't she just here?
Oh? "Mask of Desire" is on.
I missed yesterday's episode.
Duk Chil.
You're overly excited.
Here.
Look into my eyes.
Take a deep breath in.
Breathe in, breathe out.
That's it.
Good.
Why are you so pretty today?
What?
You...
How old are you now?
We're the same age.
Oh, right.
But you're still...
the young Eun Ran...
I knew.
Duk Chil.
How come...
you look the same?
It's unbelievable.
Oh, no. What are they doing?
Shouldn't they not be doing that?
Eun Ran!
Eun Ran! Choi Seoung Il's kissing!
The CEO and his wife asked to meet?
Yes.
It was always chaotic when we met.
We'll have to stay in touch,
and I think it would be nice to meet them formally.
The CEO.
His real name is Kim Bok Rae.
- Did you know that? - What? No, I didn't.
No, I knew.
We agreed not to lie.
What?
There's something I didn't tell you.
What is it?
Well...
Remember when I told you about...
the guy I shared my first kiss with by the East Sea...
on my pre-graduation trip?
Is that guy this Kim Bok Rae?
Yes, it's him.
I was really shocked to find out.
My gosh.
No wonder I felt uneasy whenever he was around.
Sorry for not telling you.
No, don't be.
Why should you apologize?
What...
did he say?
He doesn't recognize me.
That was a few years back,
and it was a fleeting thing.
It happens.
Kang Jae.
You're not angry, are you?
Why would I be?
Not at all.
I feel fine.
Yes. I feel fine.
Woo Ri and that detective.
Her fiancé. Are we meeting just those two?
Yes. I thought we should meet properly.
I'm not sure about the detective,
but we'll see Woo Ri often.
- Ma Ri. - Yes?
Don't call her Woo Ri.
Call her Ms. Oh.
The drama crew calls her by her name.
She's just an assistant writer.
Still, we should call her Ms. Oh.
Okay.
Ms. Oh.
Good.
Writer Oh Woo Ri!
Yes?
Shoot!
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
Sir.
Were you at a beach by the East Sea?
What?
We met, didn't we?
(Woori the Virgin)
Don't open the email!
There was a letter.
I didn't know you wanted to get to know me so badly.
Let's get divorced.
What if she doesn't give you the baby?
I'll protect you.
I can't tell Woo Ri.
How shocked would she be to know Choi Seoung Il's her dad?
Can we chat?
You're leaving? Just like that?
- Is it Raphael? - Yes.
Would it be easy to date a woman carrying another man's baby?
I don't mind at all.
Let's...
sleep together.
(Woori the Virgin)