[Dream of Golden Years]
Our company's second-quarter
[2015]
top seller
is our new colleague,
Xia Xiaolan.
Here's the certificate and bonus.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you.
Everyone should
learn from Xia Xiaolan in the future
and create more value
and benefits for our company.
Liu, come to my office.
[Ms. Xiaolan won the Top Seller title
in the Business Group's Q2 2015 sales ranking.]
Anyone who gets her clients
could become the top seller,
right?
Don't try to deny it.
She goes
to Mr. Gu's office every day.
Who knows
what kind of relationship they have?
How do rumors start?
Is it because of jealousy
or just for fun—
It is often impossible to know.
But I know it.
Running away won't stop rumors.
Backing down
will only be seen
as an admission of guilt.
People will embellish the story
with vivid details.
[Episode 2: Rumors That Grew Wings]
Come here.
You think we don't know
who you really are?
Let me go!
Help!
Weren't you getting along
well with Zhang Erlai?
Let me go!
Why are you pretending to be pure?
Everyone knows you're Xia Xiaolan
from Dahe Village, who sleeps around.
Are you okay?
You guys are really something—
bullying a girl in broad daylight.
Get him!
Come on.
Excuse me.
Move aside.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Want to keep fighting?
No.
No. No.
Stop it!
What's going on here?
Officer.
It's them.
Take them all.
Get up.
Come on.
Get up. Get up.
Easy, easy.
-Ouch.
-Get up.
And you two,
come with us to the station.
Cheng, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you alright?
Alright,
we've understood the situation already.
You can go back.
Miss,
when walking alone on remote paths,
you should be more careful.
Xia Xiaolan is just a loose woman,
not some good girl.
Shut up.
Okay, you can go back.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
That's alright.
Do you have somewhere else to go?
Yes.
Miss.
What are you looking for?
Is it a wall clock
or a wristwatch?
Alarm clock.
Do you have an alarm clock?
Yes, yes. Look over here.
There aren't any
with cartoon prints here.
This is the only one with a pattern.
Let me see this one.
Sure.
Take a look.
Are you buying it?
Don't touch it if you're not buying.
Okay.
I'll take this one.
Have you got it?
You helped me today.
Thank you.
That's alright.
My name is Zhou Cheng.
I am a high school graduate.
I'll start working in two months.
I've been free lately,
so I've been doing some transport work.
But don't worry.
It's legitimate work.
I just make a small profit.
Now,
may I get to know you?
My name is Xia Xiaolan.
As for anything else,
I don't know, either.
You're quite interesting,
not even knowing about yourself.
Xia Xiaolan.
Xia Xiaolan!
Ms. Xiaolan.
You're finally awake.
You just fainted from heatstroke.
Here.
This is my own water bottle.
I've washed it three times.
It's very clean.
Have some water to recover.
Here.
You are...
Wang...
Wang Jianhua.
I'm from Beijing,
responsible for promoting
our agricultural planting techniques.
I don't understand any of that.
So you're just someone
who farms with us, right?
Right, that's not wrong.
Thank you.
Take it easy.
That's enough. Thanks.
No, no.
Your heatstroke was serious.
You should rest a bit longer.
Everyone, stop crowding around.
Get back to work.
Have another sip of water.
Drink some more.
Thank you.
Where am I?
Don't move.
You're still on an IV.
Did I fall asleep?
Yes.
You seemed to be dreaming.
You were smiling in your sleep.
Just like this.
Everyone else has dreams
with happy and joyful smiles.
Why did it seem like
you were mocking something?
I dreamed of
a hasty love story.
You know, people
are really interesting sometimes.
They meet someone a few times,
get a little bit of care,
and then they want to spend
the rest of their lives with them.
This standard for choosing a partner
is really quite low.
So,
you don't believe in love at first sight.
How can you fall in love
when you know nothing about them?
What if the attraction at first sight
is strong enough?
What attraction—
strong enough
to suck my blood?
Nurse, please remove the IV here.
Okay, coming.
Press here.
Okay.
Thank you.
Take it easy.
Come.
Um,
let me take you home later.
Don't refuse yet.
If you insist
on going back alone,
I'll still insist on taking you.
Warm,
considerate,
knows his boundaries—
This boy
actually matches my taste.
But I don't believe a man's feelings
can stay focused on just one woman,
especially when she's
over 10 years older than him
and from another dimension.
Thank you.
What kind of trash
is gossiping
about other people's business,
saying—
Fen.
Go ahead with your work.
What happened?
Just now, on my way here,
I overheard two people saying
that our Xiaolan
was bullied in town.
They even called her a loose woman.
Who said that?
I chewed them both out.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm around,
no one in the village will dare
to gossip anymore.
However,
I can't control what happens elsewhere.
Alright, I understand.
You should
go check on Fen first.
I'll go meet Xiaolan.
Okay.
Just turn the corner ahead
and we're there.
Thank you.
That's alright.
Cheng,
I'll sort the goods.
You two talk.
Wei and I
are staying at the Anqing Guesthouse.
If you're going
to the town again tomorrow,
you can ask us to go with you.
No need.
Thanks.
Gotta go.
Thank you.
Xiaolan!
Who are you?
Why are you following her?
Hello, I'm Zhou Cheng,
and I'm the delivery person.
He helped me today.
Well, thank you then.
You should go back and rest early.
I'll be going then.
Where are you staying?
I'm staying at the town guesthouse.
I happen to be going
to the town tomorrow.
I'll bring you breakfast.
And for lunch,
I'll treat you to a meal in town—
as thanks
from Xiaolan.
Go back now.
Thank you.
Cheng.
Who was that guy just now?
He seemed so fierce.
Probably her father.
Let's go.
He helped you.
We should thank him properly.
Homemade food
shows sincerity.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll go to the police station in town
to ask about today's incident.
And I'll also check
if they're decent people.
Thank...
Thank you.
Kid...
What are you thanking me for?
We're family.
Those two are city folks.
I wonder
if they will like
these sour radish and pork dumplings.
They've probably never had them before.
Let them try something new.
Cook their dumplings
tomorrow morning.
Alright.
It's the New Year! Time to eat dumplings!
Now we can have them
even when it's not the New Year.
Life is better now.
Thank you...
Thank you so much for your trouble.
Xiaolan, it's no trouble at all.
We're making them for ourselves, too.
Oh right, I remember
you make the prettiest dumplings.
You should
make their dumplings.
Yes.
Come on.
Xiaolan makes the best dumplings.
Wrap one.
I don't know how.
The first batch is ready. Here.
Try them and see how they taste.
Try them quickly.
Tao, let Xiaolan eat first.
It's okay.
Tao, go ahead.
Thank you, Xiaolan.
Hurry up.
Be careful. It's hot.
How does it taste?
Even though the alarm clocks
are different,
sincerity makes all the difference.
Please, let me go back.
Xiaolan.
You set an alarm at night, too?
I was just trying it out.
Alright.
Try it. Try it.
Lan.
Is the alarm clock broken?
Let me get you a new one.
It's fine.
No need.
What...
What are you going to say?
No… nothing.
I...
I'll get you some water.
Useless thing.
Stop making noise.
What's wrong with Xiaolan?
She's probably testing the alarm clock
to see if it works.
Why do we need alarm clocks here?
When the sun rises and the roosters crow,
everyone gets up.
Whenever she wants to wake up,
we can call her.
Maybe
she's afraid of troubling you.
Fen.
Have you noticed
that since Xiaolan hit her head,
she seems different from before?
Look, she doesn't eat vinegar,
doesn't drink spicy soup,
can't even make dumplings,
and she's so polite with us,
like she's become someone else.
Later,
you should take her
to the big hospital in the city.
What's wrong with you?
Are you crying again?
It's nothing.
I'm just happy to see
you doing so well.
Don't worry.
I'm not the same Xia Xiaolan as before.
I won't do foolish things anymore.
I know.
Xiaolan.
Today I collected
two big baskets of duck eggs.
What?
Didn't you tell me
to collect duck eggs at home?
At first,
I didn't have much of a plan.
Then I suddenly remembered
what you said,
"Just look for kids Tao's age."
One minute, one kid would pop up here,
holding one.
The next minute,
another would pop up there,
holding two.
In just one afternoon,
I collected two big baskets of duck eggs.
Tomorrow I'll go with you
to sell the eggs.
No need.
I'll go by myself tomorrow.
You should rest at home.
Alright.
Your uncle will
go with you anyway.
I'll stay home and collect eggs.
Although
everything here
feels strange to me.
This woman named Liu Fen
makes me want to get closer to her.
She is simple-minded
and weak,
but she gives her all
to love her daughter.
Xia Xiaolan.
I actually envy you a little.
This kid
is always playing
with new gadgets.
This thing is loud.
What time did I cross over?
Afternoon.
Yes.
I'll try again in the afternoon.
Brother.
Dumplings.
Okay.
Here.
Xiaolan.
Hurry down. Let's go.
Let's deliver these dumplings.
Okay.
Here comes the noodles.
Thank you.
That's alright.
These dumplings are beautifully wrapped.
My family made them.
I'm not very good at it.
I actually know how.
I'll show you sometime.
Wei was there yesterday.
He went with your uncle
to the police station.
It will be handled well.
Thank you all.
Don't mention it.
What's in these dumplings?
Pickled radish?
It's good.
This way, it's not greasy at all.
Your family must be well-off, right?
In these times,
everyone loves oily and meaty food,
but you don't like it.
Yes, that's right.
I did sports as a kid.
My family made me eat meat every day,
so I got tired of it.
You did sports?
I trained in sprinting for a few years,
but then I got injured and stopped.
Although the injury wasn't serious,
I didn't really have
any interest in sports training,
so I quit.
After quitting sports,
you could still go back to high school.
Your grades must be good.
I won't be modest.
They really were good.
Are you trying to say
you envy me?
Having a good family
and being able to do whatever I want?
It's actually not that great.
I've come to realize
that when life's easier,
people lose their drive.
Look at Wei and me.
We seem capable of doing anything,
but we're not excellent at anything.
Then
why don't you find something to pursue?
I haven't figured it out.
And I lack
the motivation to make a decision.
The first day I met you,
you had this spirit—
something I don't have.
That's why I'm so attracted to you.
When you first met me...
Actually, not long before that,
I was a hopeless person.
You were just in a desperate situation.
If you were truly hopeless,
you wouldn't have been the way I saw you.
Ms. Xiaolan.
Everyone faces difficulties
and hardships.
But you
showed me
such vibrant vitality.
I'm not as good as you say,
but
I'm certainly not bad, either.
Take your time eating.
I'm going to pursue my dreams now.
Ms. Xiaolan.
Xiaolan...
Wait for me!
I'll finish eating right away.
Wait for me a moment.
Let me get you ten more.
Good.
You bought twenty,
I'll give you some green onions.
Okay.
Fried duck eggs
with green onions are delicious.
Try it when you get home.
Alright, I'll try it.
Here's the money.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks.
Popsicle!
Your lunchbox.
Thank you.
The dumplings were delicious.
Buy duck eggs and get scallions free?
You're really good at business.
That's nothing,
just a basic sales strategy.
Sales strategy?
You've studied this?
I've read a bit about it.
Don't stand here.
You're blocking my business.
Move aside.
Do you want to buy duck eggs?
How much are these duck eggs?
Take a look.
Duck eggs for sale!
The more you buy, the better deal you get.
Buy twenty
and you get green onions free.
Let me think about it.
Alright.
If you're interested
in making money,
I can introduce you to some people
-I know—
-Stop.
Yes, that's right.
I am interested in making money,
but I don't need anyone's help.
I can do it myself.
Just by selling duck eggs?
Selling duck eggs
was a form of primitive accumulation
and also a way to test the waters.
I'm not very familiar with this place.
I need to research the market first
before changing the sales model.
Once I have the equipment,
I can set up a stall
and sell egg pancakes and hamburgers here.
You're from the city, right?
Then you must
have seen Western restaurants
and eaten hamburgers.
If
I sell egg burgers here,
would people here like them?
I know all the words
you said,
but when you put them together,
I don't understand what you mean.
P-primitive accumulation?
Test the waters?
I've never heard of these things.
Where did you learn
all of this?
I have eaten hamburgers before,
but I've never heard of egg burgers.
I'd actually like to try one.
Ms. Xiaolan,
you really are different from others.
Clothes for sale!
Clothes!
This fabric is really good.
It's polyester fabric.
What are you looking at?
They are really cool.
Do you want to buy clothes?
They look really nice.
No, not buy—
sell.
Selling clothes definitely
makes more money
than selling farm products.
But I don't have enough capital now.
If I were selling them,
I'd definitely sell better than her.
Why haven't you left yet?
I want to buy...
You heard what those thugs said yesterday,
didn't you?
I might actually be
different from what you think.
I don't judge people
based on rumors.
I only believe what I see.
If I have doubts,
I will research them myself,
and I won't just make assumptions
based on hearsay.
Unfortunately, there are too few people
like you.
Some people don't just hate me...
They want to destroy me.
Those "winged" rumors
must come from
my "golden phoenix" cousin
and her boyfriend.
Can't even keep
one Xia Xiaolan under control.
Ziyu.
Jianhua.
What's wrong?
You look unhappy.
No,
I'm quite happy.
Let's go to the dining hall.
Okay.
Let's go.
I don't care what tricks they're up to.
[State-Run Restaurant]
However,
being constantly followed by rumors
is quite annoying.
Alright.
If you need help,
I can actually help you find...
No need.
Actually, I won't be staying here
for too long.
I don't really mind these things.
And even if
I really need to resolve it,
I can handle it myself.
I don't want to owe you any more favors.
There you two are!
Good.
Sir,
I already had dumplings this morning.
No need to treat me to lunch.
That won't do.
That's different.
I've already ordered the dishes.
We must show you our appreciation.
Come on in.
Let's go.
Well, thank you, sir.
Come on.
All the dishes are here.
Sir.
Fish filets in hot chili oil,
fish head with chopped chili,
fish ball soup, and fried fish fillets.
It's one fish prepared in four ways!
You've ordered a brilliant meal.
This is... a black carp?
It must be about 17 or 18 catties.
Mr. Zhou is
really knowledgeable.
You can even tell
that it's a black carp.
Come on, eat up.
Here you are.
Here, Xiaolan.
Use this one.
Eat up.
I'd like to toast you two
for saving Xiaolan.
Don't mention it.
You can call me Zhou Cheng.
Or Cheng is fine, too.
We'd like to toast you.
Xiaolan and I hit it off when we
first met.
You're still so young.
Don't speak so frivolously.
What do you mean
you hit it off when you just met?
We're treating you to this meal
to thank you for saving her life.
That's all.
You must mind your words.
I was being impertinent.
This is my apology.
I'm so sorry
for the misunderstanding.
I didn't mean anything else
by saying that.
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm sincere
about being friends with Xiaolan.
Zhou Cheng,
since you're being so honest,
I'll just cut to the chase.
I admit you're not bad.
But right now,
I don't have time for this.
I have more important things to do.
I understand what you mean.
We've just met.
I'm not rushing it.
And you don't need
to feel pressured, either.
Let's interact
normally,
just like friends.
Try the fish.
Have some fish, sir.
Good that you got it.
I have to admit
that under any circumstances,
this kind of youthful enthusiasm is
always touching.
But touching as it may be,
this isn't my life after all.
Sooner or later, I'll return
to the world I'm from.
Why form an additional attachment?
Hey, man.
We're the ones
who said to treat you to a meal.
Why did you pay the bill?
It doesn't matter who paid.
The point is
that we all enjoyed the meal.
Are you two
going anywhere else?
We can give you a ride.
Don't bother.
We've taken up your whole day already.
Just go ahead with your business.
We'll be fine.
Alright.
Take care on your way.
We'll be staying here for two more days.
If you come into town for anything,
you can find us at the guesthouse.
Well,
we'll take our leave.
Cheng,
you didn't go to the police station today.
What those three thugs said is so nasty
that I don't even want to repeat it.
Then just don't repeat it.
Wei.
Do you think I'm handsome?
Yes, of course!
Back in the compound when we were kids,
all the girls were after you.
Then am I rich?
Since I'm both handsome and rich,
and I've openly expressed
my admiration for her,
if she were really
as terrible
as that rogue said,
why would she turn down someone
with such good conditions as me?
She'll be your sister-in-law one day.
Let's go
do something.
Weren't we going back
to rest at the guesthouse?
These two must be
smugglers
doing illegal business.
They might
lose everything one day.
You can't just be fooled
by this man's handsome looks
and sweet talk.
How do you know all this?
Aren't you a mason?
How do you know so much about smuggling?
Because I'm smart.
Let's s-stop talking about those two.
Let's talk about those three thugs.
They're now insisting
that they only went to hurt you
after hearing those rumors.
They'll definitely get a heavy sentence.
At your age,
reputation matters so much.
These days...
P-Please don't do anything for now.
Let me think about it.
Hello, excuse me.
I'd like to ask about someone.
Do you know Zhang Erlai?
He's just a hideous scoundrel.
He's messed
with many young girls
from several villages around here.
Thank you, ma'am.
Sir,
could I ask you about someone?
Do you know Zhang Erlai?
I'm busy and don't have time for you.
Cheng,
see?
We've been hearing all day about how she
failed to seduce her cousin's husband
and turned to mess
with that rascal.
Screw you.
Look, even if I believe
that Xia Xiaolan isn't
that kind of person,
everyone here is saying it.
Getting mixed up with her
will surely bring you endless trouble.
First of all,
your family won't easily accept her.
Look at you.
You saved her,
confessed your love in public,
and showed off your wealth.
But look at her.
She's not interested at all.
Just pack up and come home with me.
I'm not leaving.
Let's go
to Shipozi Village
they mentioned
and meet Zhang Erlai.
You've been bewitched by that woman.
This alarm clock
rings whenever
you want it to.
Xiaolan,
your alarm clock rings so loudly.
Auntie,
this is the money I earned
selling duck eggs in the past few days.
Please take it
for our food expense.
Well...
Take it.
Oh...
What's this for?
You don't need to do this
while living at your uncle's house.
We don't need your money.
That's right.
I know you don't need it,
but if you don't take this money,
I'd feel bad
staying here any longer.
Look at this girl...
How about this?
Your auntie will
keep this money for you,
and when you need it,
she'll return it to you.
Yeah, good girl.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's just
that I didn't get many eggs today.
Anyone can tell your sadness
from your face.
What's really going on?
The villagers said
duck eggs are profitable.
They want to sell them themselves
and can't give me many.
I should have told you earlier.
I actually expected this.
People always fight
for jobs that pay well.
So what if we didn't get duck eggs?
Fen?
What's wrong, Fen?
Why are you crying?
What are you crying for?
Fen,
don't cry.
They were talking
about Xiaolan.
What did they say?
They said she...
Who's got nothing better to do
than gossip around here?
What are you doing?
Get your ass over here!
I'll rip that tongue
right out of your big mouth!
That's enough.
How despicable,
talking rubbish about our innocent girl!
You shameless people!
Enough, Fengmei. Stop it...
You think our family has no one
to stand up for her?
Stop shouting!
Xiaolan is still here!
And you, stop crying.
Your tears
won't solve anything!
Those damn bastards are
spreading rumors and causing trouble.
I know
it must be that Zhang Erlai!
Zhang Erlai is
a filthy hooligan,
a scoundrel!
I'm not the Xia Xiaolan they gossip about.
These things can't hurt me.
But they can hurt them,
my unfamiliar "family."
Don't let me see you!
I'll beat you
every single time I see you!
What they're saying isn't true.
Xiaolan, you are the best.
See? He failed to get what he wanted,
so he's spreading rumors here!
All right,
stop crying.
Zhang Erlai,
right?
Zhang Erlai is
always getting handsy.
The women in Shipozi Village
all avoid him.
It's improper for me
to confront him directly.
Could you help me find out
if he has any hobbies
or places he likes to go?
You want to catch him?
Words alone aren't solid proof.
We must catch him in the act.
Someone like him will strike
whenever he gets the chance.
I've already spoken with people
in his village and told them
to keep an eye on him for me.
Ma'am.
Oh, right,
they said recently,
someone else was also
asking about Zhang Erlai.
This guy seems to have offended
quite a few people.
Everyone wants to get him.
Someone else?
Looks like Zhang Erlai
lives up to his name.
He's no good at all.
Hello, sir.
Excuse me,
do you know Zhang Erlai?
Get lost!
Don't run!
Kids, come here.
I must catch him.
I have a question for you.
If you
know anything,
you'll get a candy.
Okay! Me!
Who knows Zhang Erlai?
I know! I know him.
Xiaoling's sister stays at home all day,
cursing Zhang Erlai.
Yeah.
Dan'er,
didn't he once
grope your sister, too?
He groped your sister!
It was your sister!
[To Xia Xiaolan]
[See you at the usual spot. From Jianhua.]
The handwriting is completely different.
She fell
for such a clumsy trick.
What a silly girl.
What's wrong, Cheng?
This Zhang Erlai has gone too far.
Xia Xiaolan must have been wronged.
Visit two more houses
and send all this evidence
to the police station.
W-Where are you going?
Aren't you coming with me?
I'm going to help your sister-in-law
sell duck eggs.
Cheng!
Xiaolan!
Are you still buying duck eggs?
Yes.
I have twelve here.
I have eight.
I'll give you 70 cents.
And 50 cents for you.
Okay.
Put them in here.
I'll get you money.
Okay.
I'll put them here.
Here's yours.
Thank you.
And yours.
Okay, thanks.
Are these duck eggs for sale?
Yes.
Xiaolan,
good morning.
Why are you here?
I still have some unfinished business.
Why so few duck eggs today?
The villagers
heard that selling duck eggs makes money,
so few would sell them to me now.
They all want to make money themselves.
But it doesn't matter.
I don't plan
to stay in this business anyway.
What will you do next?
Next?
I haven't thought about that.
Since there's no business today anyway,
come on,
I'll show you some rural scenery.
Handle them gently.
You'll have to pay if they break.
Okay.
That's the one from Dahe Village, right?
I think so.
That's her.
-Why did she get mixed up with Zhang Erlai?
-That's how rumors spread.
Exactly.
It's the same in the city.
Some things
get distorted when passed around.
It's hard to keep everyone quiet.
You scoundrel!
You have nowhere to escape!
Isn't that Zhang Erlai?
Zhang Erlai!
Why are you here?
You harass young girls
in the village every day!
You disgusting pervert!
Why is your uncle here, too?
Since we're here,
let's watch the show.
Zhang Erlai,
you bullied Xia Xiaolan
from Dahe Village the other day.
This person should've called the police
and sent you to the police station!
Yes, that's right.
Call the police to catch him.
Don't talk nonsense.
There's nothing
between Xia Xiaolan and me.
If you keep making things up,
I'll tell the police to arrest you!
Did you see it with your eyes?
Dare you come to confront me?
He's still denying it!
He thinks he's right!
-That's horrendous!
-Let me confront you myself.
Zhang Erlai,
do you remember me?
Xia Xiaolan?
Repeat what you
just said.
I...
What did I say?
Speak!
Weren't you quite talkative just now?
Say it again!
Be it in the past or present,
when misunderstood
or slandered,
many people only choose to run away.
But when you hide from rumors,
the rumors will chase after you.
There's only one way to end rumors.
And that is
to confront them head-on.
Fine, I'll speak!
I'm not that kind of perverted person.
And I've never done that filthy thing!
Oh... How shameless!
Look how nervous he appears!
Of course he's nervous.
He's obviously lying.
Zhang Erlai and I
have met only three times in total.
The first two times,
you verbally flirted
and got handsy with me.
I scolded you and drove you away.
Later, I don't know
who left you a note,
claiming that I fell for you.
Who'd possibly
fall for someone like him?
Exactly!
Someone really did leave me a note.
Zhang Erlai!
That doesn't make any sense.
You just believed
some random note?
That girl is
so capable and competent.
She'd have to be blind to like you.
Exactly.
I was just thinking,
"What if it's true?"
Seriously?
Who gave you that note?
How ridiculous! Look at yourself.
So hilarious.
How would I know who left me that?
When I got home,
the note was right under my door.
I received a similar note,
but it wasn't about you.
After meeting you,
I immediately made my position clear.
I also showed you the note.
You knew perfectly well
that I was tricked into coming.
Yet you still got handsy with me.
I tried everything to get rid of you,
and you, embarrassed and furious,
spread rumors everywhere,
saying that we were dating.
How can a young woman like you
be so shameless?
We're in front of so many people.
How can you eagerly talk about
such embarrassing things?
Why should I be embarrassed?
If I didn't speak up,
people might think
I was admitting it silently out of shame.
Should I let
a rogue like you
and all those
malicious rumors
belittle me?
-You're right!
-Exactly.
Should I let someone like you,
who spreads rumors everywhere,
continue doing evil,
and let someone like me,
a completely innocent victim,
live in shame and fear?
On what grounds?