[Dream of Golden Years]
Something this serious had happened,
[2022]
but why didn't you report it to me?
You just made the call yourself.
Are you the team leader,
or am I?
They were going too far!
I just gave them
a taste of their own medicine
to teach them a lesson.
Besides,
this won't affect the work,
will it?
Of course it matters.
If you don't handle relationships well,
it will have an impact.
If it does,
I'll just quit, okay?
Young people are really
reforming the workplace, huh?
Mr. Wang.
Actually, sometimes,
you should learn from
them today.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
[Episode 29] [An Eye for an Eye]
Fellow workers,
listen, we...
do have some problems here.
But the management
is already working on a solution.
Look, well,
just sitting around here
isn't the way.
This has nothing to do with me.
I tried to talk them out of it.
Listen up, everyone.
If you don't want to work,
get your pay and leave now.
Let me talk to them. Let me talk to them.
Hey, fellow workers,
which other construction site
treats you better than here? Right?
Let's just get back to work, okay?
Liu, Liu.
Dali.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Xiaolan.
Something happened at the bank too?
Yes.
Not just the bank,
but also the Haihua Hotel
and the Golden Sands Pool.
It seems this coordinated attack
is targeting me.
The materials center can provide 700,000.
My personal savings
can add a bit more.
Right, and mine too.
We can scrape together a million.
Yeah, yeah.
As for me,
the balance from the Haihua Hotel
hasn't been paid yet,
and the workers haven't been paid.
But I can go back and ask Fengmei
to see how much money
we can scrape together at home.
I can come up with more this time.
I should have 1.5 million.
Tell me in advance,
and I'll get the money ready.
Come in.
Ms. Xia,
my colleagues just told me
that they can skip
their salaries this month.
They can wait until the company's finances
improve.
Please thank everyone for me.
Salaries will be paid as usual this month.
I can handle my own problems.
There's no need for you all to worry.
Okay, Ms. Xia.
I'll head out now.
Thanks to everyone.
It's all right.
I know everyone is worried about me.
But the hole we're in
is just too big.
Even if all of you
went bankrupt,
it wouldn't be enough to pay it back.
And you are my safety net.
I can't destroy that, can I?
Xiaolan,
you have to listen to me on this.
If the bank
really demands payment,
everyone here
can scrape together a little bit
to pay them back.
You don't want the bank
to really take
your Golden Sands Pool
to be auctioned, right?
Stay calm.
Aren't we trying
to figure out a way together?
Xiaolan.
Regarding the financial issues,
I don't understand much,
so I can't be of much help.
But regarding Nie Weiguo suing you
for plagiarism,
what do you plan to do?
As far as I know,
he has already prepared
the original design drafts.
But everyone is well aware
and knows clearly
that they must be fake.
But can current technology analyze
which is the original draft
and which is the copy?
Mr. Mao, you're right.
Based on our law firm's experience,
the difficulty of copyright cases
lies right here.
With current technology,
there is simply no way
to accurately judge
the creation time of the design drafts.
Plus, Hou Qi
indeed served as Nie Weiguo's assistant.
Logically speaking...
there is a possibility of plagiarism.
Then how do we judge?
Connections?
Seniority?
Then young designers
would be at a huge disadvantage,
wouldn't they?
Mr. Mao, calm down.
Future judicial appraisal technology
will definitely advance rapidly.
In the future, none of this
will be a problem.
As for now,
we will definitely
fight for fairness.
This isn't just for Xiaolan
but also for
more young designers in the future.
Hello?
Uncle Tang.
So much has happened recently.
Don't you want to talk about it?
Right now,
we are one.
No matter how much
you try to avoid suspicion,
in the eyes of others,
we are one.
Since we are one,
we share the same fate.
We are inseparable.
Xiaolan,
you're a smart person.
Am I making myself clear?
I understand.
It's just that I'm...
A bit unaccustomed to it?
Not used to
having someone
cover for you now?
Then you'll have to get used to it.
But by the same token,
given our relationship,
there will be many eyes
watching you,
so you must be even more careful
not to make a wrong move.
Uncle Tang,
rest assured.
Every procedure at Qi Hang
was done according to regulations.
I believe you've been following the rules.
But right now,
everything
is coming at once.
What you need to do
is stay very calm.
Regarding the bank,
I've asked around for you.
As for the early repayment,
the bank won't make a decision
immediately.
So,
there is still some time.
The most important thing now
is this plagiarism lawsuit.
If the plagiarism issue
can be resolved,
then the loan
will be easily solved.
However,
with your ability,
do you already have a plan?
If you need anything,
you can come to me anytime.
I will,
as a family member,
give you some advice.
Okay.
The meal is ready. Come eat.
Let's go eat.
Look at these 2 drawings.
The strokes are obviously different.
I'll go compare them.
Okay.
Ms. Hou Qi,
here are the drawings you wanted.
Thanks.
Okay,
I'll contact him right away.
Hello, this is Qi Hang Property.
See you tomorrow.
I'm off.
See you tomorrow, Ms. Xia.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
See you. See you. See you.
Hou Qi, look.
These are completely different.
Look at this.
These 2.
These 2 obviously have
the same drawing style
by the same person.
Look at this part.
Yes.
This one is clearly better.
The pressure used—
Alright.
It's getting dark.
Let's call it a day.
Thanks for your hard work.
I'll treat you to a good meal.
San.
Xiaolan.
Zhenzhu told me about it.
If there's anything I can help with,
just say the word.
Okay. Thanks, San.
Actually, there is something
you can help with.
Prepare a feast
for my colleagues.
Sure. Coming right up.
-Okay. Have a seat.
-Thank you.
Let me tell you,
don't judge this place by its looks.
The food here
is just as good as big restaurants.
I guarantee that after this time,
you'll want to come back.
Next is today's top story.
After much preparation
and a massive publicity campaign,
Chengrong Electronics City
is about to open.
But recently, it has been embroiled
in a design plagiarism scandal.
Today,
our reporter interviewed
one of the parties involved,
Architect Mr. Nie Weiguo.
Hello, everyone.
I am from the Jiangcheng Design Institute,
Nie Weiguo.
He has the nerve to be interviewed?
Thank you for accepting our interview.
We see
that public opinion suggests
that Xia Xiaolan
is a young designer after all
and should be given another chance.
Why do you
insist on taking her to court?
This matter concerns
the integrity of the industry.
It's a matter of principle.
Actually,
I am doing this
to help these young people,
to keep them on the right path.
You know how it is.
Young people these days,
especially this kind of
young girls
who rely on their youth and beauty,
want to take shortcuts.
But has anyone thought about it?
Chengrong Electronics City
is such a massive project,
and how did it end up
with someone like Xia Xiaolan,
who has very little
design experience,
a young female designer?
I want to reiterate one more time.
Your favorites.
Thanks.
In the face of such injustice,
I can't pretend to be above it all.
I'll play the villain this time.
However,
this kind of behavior
can't be tolerated.
What a hypocrite. I'm furious!
Change the channel!
Wait.
Don't change the channel.
Look.
See how engrossed the people nearby are.
Actually,
it was quite unexpected.
My main job is usually
at the Jiangcheng Design Institute.
I mostly deal with
state-owned enterprises
and public facility projects.
I don't pay much attention
to commercial projects.
It was just a chance conversation
with a friend in the industry...
Hello?
Xia Xiaolan.
That jerk Nie Weiguo
gave an interview. Do you know that?
Isn't Zhou Cheng supposed to be
a top law student?
Did he buy his degree?
He's doing nothing.
We haven't even gone to court yet,
and we've already lost the battle
of public opinion.
You have to do an interview too.
Right now,
I'm calling the TV station.
Du Zhaohui,
can you stop
causing trouble for me here?
The court cares about evidence,
not public opinion.
Besides, I'm the defendant.
I'm not even worried, so why are you?
How can I not be worried?
If this keeps up,
my reputation will be ruined
before my Electronics City even opens.
My entire fortune and life
have been invested in it.
He claims
that I plagiarized
his architectural design.
It has nothing to do
with Electronics City's operations.
Besides,
don't you think that after this ordeal,
Electronics City is actually
getting more attention?
Or perhaps, Designer Xia Xiaolan...
Then...
if you don't do an interview,
I can, right?
Suit yourself. Bye-bye.
Thank you for accepting our interview.
As for the follow-up,
we will also try to interview
Chengrong Electronics City
and Ms. Xia Xiaolan,
so that the audience can have
a more comprehensive understanding
of the event.
It's okay.
Eat up.
Ms. Xia,
Mr. Zhou also said earlier
that the creation time of the drafts
was hard to confirm.
Then is the method you mentioned
feasible?
Facing such injustice,
I want to tell everyone
that we must have the courage to resist.
We must trust our laws.
We must believe
that justice is in the people's hearts.
Nie Weiguo is right.
We need to trust the law.
Justice is in the people's hearts.
Let's eat.
Come on,
have a taste.
Eat.
That concludes our interview
with Nie Weiguo.
Regarding the progress of the case...
Have you seen the report?
Good.
Then I'll make things
even bigger.
Based on my understanding
of Nie Weiguo,
he's bad, but he's not stupid.
He knows better than anyone
that Ms. Xia is innocent.
Then why did he
come all this way to frame her?
I think he must have been on the take.
If he isn't Ms. Xia's enemy,
then he's Mr. Du's enemy.
That's not something
we can worry about.
We just need
to do our best to finish
the work Ms. Xia assigned.
I keep feeling like
someone betrayed Ms. Xia and Qi Hang.
How could those people know
about Nie Weiguo?
Aside from the seminar incident,
there were no other grudges.
It could only be someone close
who leaked it.
Right.
Then we can check
who has connections with people
in Gangdao.
I think that'll work.
I'm home. See you tomorrow.
See you.
Could it be me?
Recently,
the case of plagiarism in the design
of Chengrong Electronics City...
It's this woman.
I bet she must
have some personal connections
behind the scenes.
Exactly.
Come on, cheers.
Come on.
The focus has shifted
from the plagiarism itself
to Designer Xia Xiaolan...
She's a bit too lucky, isn't she?
She does whatever makes money.
Unless she's clairvoyant,
there's something fishy going on.
But the root of this matter
is still whether Xia Xiaolan plagiarized.
Nie Weiguo has stated multiple times
that Xia Xiaolan's
current design assistant, Hou Qi,
used to work at his unit
and therefore saw his drafts.
Xia Xiaolan's side has consistently
refused interviews.
The owner of Electronics City,
Du Zhaohui, has stated multiple times
that regarding Xia Xiaolan's
design process,
he witnessed it all,
and that Xia Xiaolan
could not have plagiarized.
Nie Weiguo stated in a radio interview
that young designers
can't, just because they have
a boss's support,
do whatever they want.
If they are not punished,
it will cause great harm
to the entire industry.
[Plagiarism Allegations]
Previously,
Du Zhaohui stated in an interview
[over the Architectural Design
of Chengrong Electronics City]
that he and Xia Xiaolan are the victims,
and that Nie Weiguo
is making false accusations.
Plagiarism
is intellectual theft.
I won't tolerate it.
Mr. Du's reaction
doesn't surprise me.
He's playing the knight in shining armor.
After all,
he gave her such a massive project.
He's bound to protect her to the end.
However,
I might have disrupted Mr. Du's
plan to win a smile from a beauty.
This Nie Weiguo
is quite good at playing the victim.
He portrays himself
as an honest man,
who, because he wasn't slick enough,
gained no commercial benefits,
like a workhorse.
But you?
A beneficiary
who used your looks to get ahead.
And you have an ambiguous relationship
with Mr. Du
of Chengrong Electronics City.
Are you looking for trouble, Zhou Cheng?
Seriously,
the fact that the trial
is starting so soon
shows that the other side
has been planning this for a long time.
I guess it started from the day
construction began at Electronics City.
Investor Du Zhaohui has repeatedly stated
that he and Xia Xiaolan are the victims.
Come in.
And he accused Nie Weiguo...
Ms. Xia, everything is ready.
Currently,
the other party involved, Xia Xiaolan,
has refused all interviews
and has not issued any statements.
You may leave.
This makes the case even more mysterious.
Chengrong Electronics City
is a key project in Shengcheng,
aiming to build Asia's...
Looking at him,
I guess he has already
realized his mistake.
So you still choose
to continue trusting him?
But the plagiarism incident
has cast a shadow
over the future of Electronics City.
The Electronics City side
has not yet revealed if they
will postpone the opening.
I believe in the law,
and I believe in my own judgment.
The trial will begin tomorrow morning
at the Shengcheng court.
Why hasn't this female designer
come out to speak yet?
The trial is about to start.
Exactly.
[Shengcheng People's Court]
Mr. Du,
I heard that you and Xia Xiaolan
are more than just
employer and employee.
Is the Electronics City project
just a gift to promote her
because you want to woo her?
Regarding the plagiarism,
did you use your resources
and connections?
Nonsense.
This is a multi-million-yuan project.
It's the largest electronics mall in Asia.
And you say I used it to pick up girls?
I am rich, but I'm not stupid.
Did you take someone's money
to write this rubbish?
I wouldn't dare.
Then Mr. Du,
what exactly is going on between you two?
Can you tell us?
It's just a cooperative relationship.
-The car...
-The car is here.
The car, the car.
Mr. Nie.
-Mr. Nie.
Can you say a few words to us?
Say a few words, please.
Look at that Nie Weiguo.
Look how smug he is.
I knew
he was no good,
doing such dirty things.
And these people
are just blindly following along.
Regarding today's trial,
are you confident?
Of course I am.
Xiaolan said she has a way,
and she'll make it work.
Why isn't Xiaolan
here yet?
Yeah. She left very early,
but why hasn't she arrived yet?
She should be here soon.
I'm actually
quite calm.
Xia Xiaolan is here!
Which one is Xia Xiaolan?
Is it that young woman?
I was wondering,
isn't there only one young woman?
Watch this.
My apprentice
has come up with a surprise move again.
There is only one truth.
Why didn't Xiaolan come
with them?
This girl
has one trick after another.
Just watch.
Hello, everyone.
I'll take a moment of your time.
These past few days, the media
has been very concerned about my case.
So, I have prepared
a small gift for everyone.
I forgot to introduce myself.
Everyone gets one.
I am the defendant in this case.
Take a look, everyone.
I'm Xia Xiaolan
from Qi Hang Architectural Design Firm.
Nice to meet you all.
Mr. Du,
why are there
2 identical drawings here?
Let me see.
What does this mean, Mr. Du?
I don't know either.
Go.
Here.
This one clearly belongs to Nie Weiguo.
Xiaolan draws much better than this.
Mr. Mao, look.
When Xiaolan drew this last year,
I-I saw it.
Pass them around and take a look.
Pass them around. Pass them around.
Alright.
These are the design drafts.
Design drafts?
But mine
is different from yours.
Look at mine.
While Comrade Nie Weiguo
was busy appearing on TV programs
and complaining to the media
about the injustice he faced,
I certainly didn't sit idly by.
But I don't intend to debate him
on television.
I believe designers
should use other ways
to prove themselves.
As for who is lying
and who appropriated whose work,
the judge will decide.
I believe there is no threshold
for appreciating architectural works.
Beauty is an intuitive feeling.
What you have now
are all the works
by Comrade Nie Weiguo and me
since the start of our careers.
For these works,
I deliberately didn't label
the authors' names.
I want to invite everyone
to play a game
to guess
which ones are my works
and which are Nie Weiguo's.
Where did she get
so many of my design drafts?
Look at Nie Weiguo's face.
He must be furious.
You've all received
the materials, right?
The trial is about to start.
In the meantime, you can
take a good look at these materials.
Score them in your mind
and make a judgment.
When the verdict comes out,
see if it matches
what you think.
I believe
the court will deliver
a fair and just judgment.
I also welcome
everyone here today
to judge for themselves.
Today,
everyone has a say.
See?
That's my apprentice, Xia Xiaolan.
She doesn't back down
or take any nonsense.
Say a few more words, Ms. Xia!
Ms. Xia, please say something!
[Presiding Judge]
We request that the defendant,
Xia Xiaolan,
and Chengrong Electronics City Plaza,
immediately cease their infringing acts.
Xia Xiaolan
must publicly
apologize to my client,
pay RMB 200,000
for mental and reputational damages,
and bear all litigation costs.
The defendant denies
all accusations made by the plaintiff.
The creation time of these 2 drafts
is very close.
With current technology,
we can't accurately determine
when they were drawn.
Nie Weiguo?
Never heard of him.
From start to finish,
our Electronics City project
was entrusted only to Xia Xiaolan
and Qi Hang.
Did you work
at the Jiangcheng Design Institute
for 2 years?
Yes.
Were you
Nie Weiguo's assistant at the time?
Did you have access to all of Nie Weiguo's
drafts?
Yes,
but I didn't—
You only need to answer yes
or no.
Yes.
You and Hou Qi are university alumni.
Did you introduce her to Qi Hang?
Yes.
It is understood
that when you introduced her to Qi Hang,
Hou Qi had not yet
resigned from the Jiangcheng Design Firm.
Did you invite her
solely because you valued
her professional ability,
or to take advantage
of her previous position?
Is your relationship with her
merely that of classmates?
I object.
This is entirely
speculation by the plaintiff's lawyer.
The witness
need not answer that question.
Defendant Xia Xiaolan,
regarding Hou Qi,
was it before or after
the Electronics City project
that she joined
Qi Hang Architectural Design Firm?
It was before
the Electronics City project.
In other words,
you judged whether Hou Qi was qualified
for the job at Qi Hang
mainly based on
her past work experience,
specifically,
at the Jiangcheng Design Institute,
right?
Yes.
Then can we
reasonably speculate
that among the works used to demonstrate
Hou Qi's professional ability,
perhaps there was this work
now suspected of plagiarism?
I don't think
there is a necessary connection.
The expert just stated
that current judicial appraisal technology
can't determine
the specific time the drafts were created.
Then,
can we
further reasonably speculate
that you exploited
the limitations of technology
to boldly plagiarize
what Hou Qi provided to you,
the plaintiff Nie Weiguo's
architectural design?
I object to the opposing counsel's
line of questioning.
The opposing counsel's speculation
seems logical,
but the premise is flawed.
All of the above speculation
is based entirely
on the assumption that Nie Weiguo
was capable of designing a work
like Chengrong Electronics City.
And that
is simply impossible.
We request leave to call a new witness.
Granted.
The details are clearly much better.
Look here.
It doesn't even look like a copy.
Look,
this one is obviously Xia Xiaolan's.
Look at the strokes.
They're obviously from a woman.
Look at this one I have.
It's so simple.
I feel like even I could draw it.
These 2
are obviously very different.
-Yeah.
-Right?
Doesn't he
have beef with Mao Kangshan?
How did he get him here?
Professor Ning.
You are a leading figure
in our country's architectural industry.
Everyone knows the title
"Northern Ning, Southern Mao."
Even in the global architectural industry,
you enjoy a very high reputation.
Now, my client
would like you to evaluate 2 portfolios.
Do you agree and promise
to make a truthful, fair,
and professional judgment?
I agree.
You won.
You let me win.
You know, although Nie Weiguo
is a scumbag,
he still made it
to the position
of Vice President of the design institute.
In the entire architectural industry,
only you and I are qualified
to judge him.
Since I am a consultant for Qi Hang,
I have to recuse myself.
So today,
I swallowed my pride to ask for your help.
I've heard about
this lawsuit in Jingcheng.
If I can help the judge
make the correct judgment,
I am duty-bound.
But let me state beforehand:
I will seek truth from facts.
You haven't changed a bit,
always preaching with your big principles.
Your words are watertight.
I might trick you,
but I'd never trick myself.
When you see
both of their drafts,
you'll naturally understand.
Aren't you the same as always?
Protecting your own.
For so many years,
you have never
taken the initiative to contact me.
This time,
if Xia Xiaolan
weren't your apprentice,
would you be so concerned
and run around like this?
Yes.
I don't deny
Xia Xiaolan is my apprentice.
But I absolutely do not mean
to shield her unfairly.
I've watched this project
from start to finish.
If I just watch facts
being distorted like this,
Professor Ning,
then what future
does our architectural circle have?
Still,
I'll seek truth from facts.
Between the plaintiff and the defendant,
as to who has the ability
to create such original work,
please use your professional knowledge
to make
a judgment.
Okay.
Objectively speaking,
the original draft and the copy,
in terms of forensic identification,
are very difficult
to distinguish accurately.
But
if you have enough
professional experience,
it is entirely possible to make
an accurate judgment.
Today,
I
will venture to give this judgment.
Chengrong Electronics City's
original architectural designer
is undoubtedly...
Xia Xiaolan.
They're coming out!
It's open! It's open!
Mr. Nie! Mr. Nie!
Who won?
Was there no verdict in court?
We absolutely do not
accept the trial results.
My client
will continue to appeal.
Please make way, everyone.
Where is Xia Xiaolan?
Ms. Xia.
Ms. Xia! Ms. Xia!
How do you feel, Ms. Xia?
I am grateful for judicial justice.
They dismissed
Nie Weiguo's lawsuit on the spot,
proving my innocence.
What is real can't be fake,
and what is fake can't be real.
In the future, I'll continue to work hard
to design more
influential works.
Thank you.
Electronics City will open soon.
Everyone is welcome to come see
Xia Xiaolan's design
and buy your favorite products, alright?
Ms. Xia!
Ms. Xia, say a few more words!
Dean Nie, hold on.
What is it?
Is there something else?
You lost the lawsuit,
and you rushed to leave?
There are other scores
we need to settle together.
Deputy Dean Nie.
Do you remember
these people?
What is the meaning of this?
Aren't you curious
about how I collected
so many of your works?
While you were busy
putting on a show on TV,
Hou Qi and I visited
all the colleagues you worked with
after you joined
the Jiangcheng Design Institute—
those who later resigned
or were transferred—
as well as your college classmates.
They provided me
with quite a few of your works.
Ms. Xia,
I didn't expect
that I wasn't the only one.
There are so many other victims.
Nie Weiguo
has been throwing his weight around
for years.
Too bad he met me this time.
I'm going to skin him alive.
This visit
turned up more surprises than I expected.
You have always
abused your position
to steal others' work,
suppress the younger generation,
and even sexually harass
female colleagues.
[Complaint]
This is the complaint
they collectively signed.
Today,
I'm going to drag you,
a pest in the architectural circle,
out into the light.
Xia Xiaolan, you...
Xia Xiaolan!
What are you doing?
This is too much!
Hurry, get in the car!
Xia Xiaolan!
Xia Xiaolan, I won't let you off!
Don't even think about surviving
in this industry!
Do you hear me?
Xia Xiaolan!
Let's go.
What are you up to?
Are you keeping something from me?
What happened to our deal?
Why were there
so many unnecessary moves?
Were those moves targeting Du Zhaohui
or someone else?
Do I look like a fool to you?
Second Young Master,
put the gun down first, okay?
I'll talk. I'll tell you everything.
Just put the gun down first, okay?
I didn't lie to you, Second Young Master.
I said I'd join forces with you
to deal with Du Zhaohui
and win the competition
for the inheritance.
That was absolutely not a lie.
But the one who backed me into a corner,
forcing me to follow Du Zhaohui's orders,
the one who started it all,
was Xia Xiaolan.
Second Young Master, do you have time
to hear a story?
A story about a female college student
who was framed as a fugitive.
Come in.
Second Young Master,
here is the information you wanted.
[Vivi after plastic surgery]
[Xia Ziyu before plastic surgery]
It was Xia Xiaolan
who did this to me.
She has joined forces with Du Zhaohui now.
They sink or swim together.
O-Our goal
is still the same,
isn't it?
For a woman whose face and name
are both fake,
how much of what she says is true?
Mr. Liu.
Ms. Xia.
About what happened last time,
I am terribly sorry.
The other directors
will be here soon.
This way, please.
Once we won the lawsuit,
you transferred
the final payment to us right away.
That was a quick response.
This way.
Du Zhaohui.
It's about the acceptance
of the Haihua Hotel.
Why are you getting involved?
Electronics City will open tomorrow.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I'm waiting for your orders.
After you finish the acceptance,
I'll take you back to Electronics City?
It's rare for you to come up with
such a good excuse.
Fine.
I'll go with you then.
Mr. Liu.
Ms. Xia.
Congratulations, Mr. Liu.
Thank you.
About what happened before,
I'm sorry.
My people didn't know any better.
It's okay.
Anyway, we have to do the acceptance
sooner or later.
Yes, yes.
Mr. Tang.
How is it?
Indeed.
Compared to the renderings,
it looks even more spectacular
and beautiful.
It really does look good.
Ms. Xia,
the edge of the pool ahead
doesn't have a fence.
Will there be any
safety issues?
That's the feature of an infinity pool.
As for safety issues,
it's clearly stated
in the project proposal.
That's right.
You didn't read it carefully.
Look, it's very safe.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
It's safe.
It's been tested. Very safe.
Water brings fortune!
-Great!
Electronics City will definitely
be a great success tomorrow!
We'll make a fortune!
Make a fortune!
♪ The sunlight fell on me ♪
♪ And sets my heart ablaze ♪
♪ Are you also the same? ♪
♪ Dreams will always shine ♪
♪ There may also be regrets ♪
♪ If you lose something,
be strong ♪
Are you too nervous,
♪ And head to the distant place ♪
or did you catch a cold
from falling in the water?
I guess I'm too nervous.
♪ The dreams we dream in the day time ♪
Also a bit excited.
After all, I sold my car and house
♪ Is passionate yet naive ♪
to build this business,
and it's finally opening.
I just feel my blood pumping.
♪ Our youth ♪
Don't be nervous.
♪ Why don't we move forward
and never look back? ♪
We've done
everything we can ahead of time.
Plus, with the publicity
♪ Even if our youthful ambitions
are not fulfilled yet ♪
that Nie Weiguo sent us,
Chengrong Electronics City's title
as No. 1 in Asia
♪ We never give up ♪
has already been hyped up.
Yes.
♪ As long as we do our best ♪
Whether I stick my neck out
or pull it back,
the blade will fall anyway.
Whether I live or die,
♪ That'd be enough ♪
we'll see tomorrow.
[Succession War Erupts
in Gangdao's Du Family]
Do you know that in 3 days,
it's your daddy's birthday party?
I know, Mommy.
Young Master.
Your clothes are ready.
I'll wake you up tomorrow.
Good night, Young Master.
[Asia's Largest Electronics Mall,
Chengrong Electronics City Plaza,]
[to Open Grandly Tomorrow in Shengcheng]
[Day 1 of Electronics City]
[Chengrong Electronics City]
Did I even set an alarm?
Du Zhaohui's Electronics City is opening.
Why am I more nervous than he is?
Mr. Du,
it's opening day.
Will business be good?
Business
has to be good, right?
Look at the sea of people outside.
How could it not be booming?
Listen to how they talk.
Business will definitely be good.
Good morning.
Don't be nervous.
Look outside.
It's not even 8 o'clock yet,
and there are already
so many people in line.
Once the doors open,
those lovely customers
will rush in to spend money.
What we need to do
is serve them
like kings.
Let me be clear.
If
our service desk
receives
any service-related complaints,
I will record them all.
You'll be fined at the end of the month.
Understood?
Yes, yes.
Remember that.
I'll tell you
some good news.
To encourage customers to spend,
we're having a grand opening sale.
Today,
spend at least 100 yuan
at any stall,
and they can enter the raffle!
-Great!
Friends,
good news!
Grand opening sale today!
-Great!
Anyone who spends
100 yuan or more
can redeem a raffle ticket.
Our first prize
is a car!
-Great!
Second prize is a motorcycle!
Third prize
is a Wenquxing electronic dictionary!
-Great!
And our lucky prize
is a bag of laundry detergent!
Not bad.
Can we really win?
You have to spend at least 100 yuan.
If you spend 99 yuan,
even one yuan short won't do,
right?
-That's right.
-Yes.
Giving away a car in a draw?
It's not a scam, is it?
You probably have to buy something
before you can draw.
Right, right.
Quiet down, everyone.
Listen to the rules first.
First,
this lucky draw event
is hosted by Chengrong Plaza.
After redeeming your ticket,
make sure to keep it safe.
Damaged tickets are invalid.
Fake tickets are invalid.
Second,
for every 100 yuan spent
in a single transaction,
you can redeem a raffle ticket.
100 yuan gets you one ticket.
200 yuan gets you 2.
And so on.
For example,
if a customer
spends 398 yuan,
they can redeem 3 raffle tickets
and get 3 chances to draw.
But spending 398 yuan
for 3 draws
seems a bit of a waste, right?
So what do you do?
Add 2 more yuan...
Where can you find
a 2-yuan item in Electronics City?
You want to round up the sum,
but then you go over.
Then with the extra amount,
you wonder if you can
reach 500.
Before you know it, the merchant
has led you astray.
This will be a popular trick
in the future, right?
Attorney Zhou, you really are smart.
Of course.
It won't just be popular in the future.
It will also be used for scams.
Spend a few more yuan for another ticket
and another chance at the jackpot.
But you definitely won't win.
But Du Zhaohui wouldn't do that.
These prizes mean nothing
to him.
However, we need to arrange
the timing of the wins.
Otherwise, if the first prize is drawn
early in the morning,
the later customers
will lose interest.
Attorney Zhou,
do you want to draw one?
Sure.
Okay.
I'll set it up for you.
Alright,
it's almost time.
Let's look forward to
the grand opening
of Chengrong Electronics City!
Open the doors and welcome the guests!