The weather has been fine recently.
I'd like to invite the Dragon Sovereign.
Would you come?
Since the invitation is from you.
I, Dragon Xian,
won't let you down.
Our Clans, the Dragon and the Celestial,
have always been enemies.
Aren't you afraid of
been entangled with me?
Here.
This flower blooms once every 100 years.
It's connected to our Dragon bloodline.
Can I exchange it for wine?
I like it.
Please.
So fragrant.
This wine,
it name is Forget Worries.
Forget Worries.
Yes.
Wait.
Something happened to the Dragon Clan!
You.
What should come
has finally come.
The Celestial Sovereign has rule his clan for tens of thousands of years.
The Four Seas and Eight Desolations
have successively submitted to the Celestial Clan.
The only exception
is the Dragon Clan.
The increasingly powerful Dragon Clan
has not only aroused the Celestial Sovereign's alert,
but also brought about
a fatal disaster for itself.
Yingluo, God of War, hear my order!
Kill Dragon Xian, the leader of the Dragon Clan, now!
They shall not be our concern anymore.
Yes, Sovereign.
Why is it you?
It is the Celestial Sovereign's command.
I dare not disobey.
I'm Yingluo, the God of War of the Celestial Clan.
In a great war between the Celestial and Dragon Clans,.
I turned into a spirit stone
and slept for ten thousand years before awakening
Though I lost my past memory during reborn,
I'm still the Celestial Sovereign's
most trusted God of War.
You're really lucky
to meet me.
I saved you.
From now on,
you're free.
Go.
You're free.
And so am I.
So it's this person
who broke into the Celestial Clan's territory.
Who are you!
Where are you going?
Speak!
The Yunsu Forest in our domain.
What are you doing here?
Sister, please forgive me.
You're so beautiful.
You're honest.
So confess yourself.
Since I'm pretty and kind,
maybe I can spare you.
If you fall into the hands of immortal Chilian,
you'll be in for a hard time.
Sister.
You tied me too tightly.
I can't think.
I don't think you can escape anyway.
You.
What did you do to me!
Nothing else.
You're beautiful and dashing.
I just want to get close to you.
You don't mind it, right?
The Dragon Name Sword.
Where are you taking me to?
Sister, I got to go.
See you later.
Watch out.
Weird.
That person
gave me a strange feeling,
like I've met him before.
Who are you,
dare to provoke the Dragon Clan?
The Dragon Clan？
Didn't they perish
ten thousand years ago?
How did you manage to survive?
Take a good look.
Here.
The territory of the Celestial Clan!
Wherever I stand
is under the Dragon Clan's jurisdiction.
So arrogant.
Ouch, that hurt!
Thanks for the help.
See you another day!
Hey, sister.
Remember to miss me.
You two are a gang?
You can lift this sword?
It's just an ordinary thing.
What's so special about it?
This sword and I share a connection.
It's the most precious treasure of the dragon clan.
You, a Celestial being,
is not qualified to touch it!
Fine then.
I've been needing a suitable weapon.
Don't even think about it!1
Yingluo.
Get back, now.
I'll let you off the hook today.
Who the hell are you?
Celestial Sovereign.
Took you long enough to show up.
You realize how much crap you've stirred up?
I don't know
where I went wrong.
So, how'd that job I gave you went on?
By the time I got there,
the guy was already gone.
Ow!
Can't you be a little bit more gentle?
You know who my mom is?
Listen carefully.
My mother is...
Sister!
Here!
I came to play with you again!
Heard your name while I was outside.
You're, uh...
Yingluo, right?
Dongfang Ruo...
This little creep
is from the Moon Clan.
Not just that—
he's the Moon Sovereign's youngest son.
Having affairs with Moon Clan
is strictly forbidden here.
You better stay away from him.
Dongfang Ruo,
The Celestial Clan and the Moon Clan have always had Inter-restriction.
Let's keep outta each other's business.
I'll take you back myself.
Please tell the Moon Sovereign
if any of you come sniffing around,
we won't hold back.
I know.
I'll tell my mother.
Sister.
Easy.
Celestial Sovereign.
I confess.
It's too early for that.
I have another mission for you
to make up for it.
Who is she, really?
Dragon Sovereign.
Like you said,
all the spies we caught
were Celestial lackeys.
We've killed them all
and sent the bodies back.
Good.
Sovereign, what's wrong?
Lu Shui.
That's impossible.
This sword woke up when you did.
You're linked.
Only you can touch it.
But some Celestial member
just picked it up.
If she can control the sword,
does that mean she can control me too?
You know anything
about that guy?
Sovereign, the Celestial Clan sent a note.
Heard you have an ancestor ring of the dragon clan.
An interesting masterpiece.
I thought I'd like that.
Prepare yourself.
I'm coming for it.
Since you're such generous,
you won't let me leave empty-handed, will you?
Yingluo...
So you're about to bring the muscle
since your sneaky stuff failed.
Dragon Sovereign.
Yingluo's the Celestial God of War.
We can't underestimate her.
I'll tell the guards
to tighten security.
Don't bother.
The Dragon Clan's
only just bouncing back
since I woke up
The Celestial Clan has rule the world for so long.
Time to find a way and take them down.
Do you remember Dragon Xian?
The leader of the Dragon Clan.
He survived big war
ten thousand years ago.
Now he's back,
and the Dragons are making a comeback.
They'll cause trouble for sure.
So you want me to kill him?
No.
Though he's the Dragon Sovereign,
he has my bloodline.
He's my grandson.
I want you to take him back
to take over as Celestial Sovereign.
Why is this place dead empty?
Did everyone bail when they heard
I was coming?
I don't understand.
With their relationships,
why bother all these troubles?
The ancestor ring of the dragon clan.
He's wearing the ring.
So he must be Dragon Xian.
That was close.
Luckily I turned invisible.
Stop digging.
There's no eggs left.
Show yourself.
That feeling...
It's him. That's her?1
So the God of War finally shows up.
It's you?
Never thought
the great God of War of the Celestial Clan
would be a thief targeting for trash.
My only target is you.
Can I take that as
you just admitted that
you're the 'trash'?
You came to the Dragon Clan
just for this?
I don't think so.
Actually.
I'm here on behalf of the Celestial Sovereign
to bring you back to the Celestial Clan for a cushy life.
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't you know
your relationship with the Celestial Sovereign?
What she said was true.
How could the Celestial Sovereign be your...
She's not lying.
My mother was
the Celestial Sovereign's daughter.
He didn't even spare his daughter.
Run!
He wiped out the Dragon Clan.
None of us survived.
Ten thousand years later, the Dragon Name Sword brought me back.
The Celestial Clan and Dragons
are sworn enemies.
I'm the only descendant of the Dragon Clan.
I'll never betray
the Dragon Clan's destiny.
Though I don't remember
how the Celestial Clan defeated me,
I won't let what happened before
happen again.
Then Yingluo is the biggest threat.
She doesn't look that tough.
If the Dragon Clan attacks together,
maybe we can kill her.
Once I was practicing in the forest.
I fought with her.
She's way more
powerful than you thought.
If someone like her
stands by our side,
the revival of our Dragon Clan
may stand a chance.
This is Flower elixir, the Dragon Clan's Highly toxic elixir.
Take it.
And we'll talk.
Is this how
the Dragon Sovereign treats guests?
No.
It's for special guest.
Interesting.
Treating guests with poison.
I want to partner with you.
I have a score to settle with the Celestial Sovereign.
I'll never go back.
But you can stay here.
As for that old man,
I'll explain to him
that you want to stay with me.
Keeping me here
won't be that easy.
I'll offer you the position of
Left or Right Protector.
Protectors
are second only to me.
Not bad.
Cooperations
need sincerity‌.
Sounds reasonable.
That could be an interesting deal.
My target
is just you.
Easy enough.
Didn't expect the God of War
to have so much
interest in me.
What do you want to do?
Yingluo.
I know your Primordial spirit isn't here.
I have another mission for you
to make up for it.
But before that,
I need to take your Primordial spirit out.
To ensure your loyalty,
that old man took your Primordial spirit.
Now
I want it in the Dragon Clan.
Reasonable.
I'll replace
the one there with a fake.
They won't notice
for a while.
Your "invitation"
is rude as hell.
You started with the trust issues.
Doesn't the Dragon Clan
deserve your real spirit core?
My physical form
has done many things.
But no one in the world
has seen through it.
Your sense
is sharp indeed.
After all, I fought with you.
If that were your real self,
I couldn't have bested you.
Rude.
This physical form is cuter anyway.
Too scared to show your Primordial spirit?
Are you afraid of staying alone with me
would got you killed?
We'll see
who dies first.
Interesting.
I have a sword.
Wanna check it out, Lady Yingluo?
It's nothing special.
This sword and I are bonded.
No one else
in the world
has ever wielded it.
I do feel familiar with it.
After the Dragon Clan fell,
only me and this sword remained.
Maybe you had a link
to the Dragons ten thousand years ago.
Me?
Impossible.
I don't remember.
I don't even remember who I am.
Maybe the Dragon Clan
is the key to unlocking your memories.
Are you saying
my destiny is
tied to the Dragon Clan?
If so.
The strongest warrior in the world
who swears loyalty to the old man,
will Yingluo waver?
What do you mean?
I'm betting on you.
The old man
wants you.
And so do I.
If this is just about your competitive desire,
I'm not interested in your fight.
No.
I'm betting that
once you get to know me,
you'll leave the old man.
The only thing valuable about me
is my loyalty, right?
Fighting for that old man
won't bring you a good ending.
Serving me might be a better choice.
Why?
Because you're tough.
Because you can lift the Dragon Name Sword.
Maybe
you're the Dragon Clan's last hope.
You don't have to answer me now.
Take you time and think about it.
All clans in the realm depend on
the mortal world for power.
Controlling mortal territories
equals power.
This book
maps all Dragon Clan territories on Earth.
Take it.
Consider it as my good faith.
Aren't you afraid I'll destroy everything?
After all,
I haven't agreed to partner yet.
That cheap trick doesn't suit your position
as the God of War, right?
Yingluo.
I'll think about it.
I'll learn more about the Dragon Clan.
If she can be mine,
maybe...
Dragon Sovereign!
Trouble in the Market!
Dumplings.
Dragon Sovereign!
Trouble in the Market!
Some thugs are causing a ruckus.
We had oath to
not to drag the mortals into our conflicts.
But these guys are breaking the truce.
They even killed kids.
It's beyond brutal.
Let's check it out.
Yes.
Why risk coming to me?
How's your mission?
Did you bring Dragon Xian back
to report to the Celestial Sovereign?
Dragon Xian refused to return with me.
He wants me to stay in the Dragon Clan
and even offered me a Protector position.
What?
I need more time.
Dragon Xian is really hard to deal with.
Who does he think is showing him kindness?
It's the Celestial Sovereign!
How dare he refused?
Though they're relatives,
the hate between them is too deep.
What's Dragon Xian's game here?
Be careful. This smells like a trap.
But don't worry.
Maybe
it won't take you long to come back.
What does that mean?
The Dragon Clan
recently took over more
Celestial territories in the mortal world.
immortal Chilian is raged
and decided to let them suffer.
What's her plan?
If she can't have it, she'll destroy it.
I came to warn you.
The Dragon Clan is in for a rough ride.
You must be careful.
Candied haws!
Great.
What a stunning painting.
Wonder who'll get lucky to have it
and how much it'll go for.
I bid 3 taels of silver.
25 taels!
100 taels of gold!
100 taels?
How about
sell it to me?
100 taels of gold.
You do surprised me.
It's a charity sale.
No need to go that far.
It's fine.
She is rich.
Sell it to her.
But the price is too high.
God of War.
You sure spend
like a king.
You came to the Market
without using Vital Qi to protect yourself.
Do you know how many eyes are on you?
Perfect.
I'm baiting them
to come to me.
You're risking your life.
Listen.
If you run into trouble,
don't go alone.
This is a Celestial Clan trap.
You're right,
but a little late.
Who are they?
The Wing Clan.
I just don't know
why have some people
causing troubles
in Dragon territories lately?
You want to investigate.
But you can't just
come to mortal world unguarded.
With the God of War here, what do I need to fear?
Don't let them escape.
Your Clan killed so many of my brothers.
Now you fall into my hands.
The Dragon Sovereign.
You're nothing special.
Take them to the poisonous jail!
Doesn't your Dragon Clan want to rule the world?
Now that you are here,
the Dragon Clan should face its end.
Are you here for revenge
or for justice?
I'm here to kill you.
The Dragon and Wing Clans
never had any conflicts.
Why start a new feud?
New feud?
You massacred my brothers!
You must die today.
You can't even figure out your real enemy.
No wonder your brothers died.
What did you say?
Today,
I'll revenge for my brothers' lives.
Little by little.
Bring that woman here.
Since you're after me,
let her go.
You're in no position to bargain.
Poison them.
福
This poison
is extra potent, kids.
Enjoy it slow.
And I'll take over
the marketplace outside.
You knew it was a trap.
Why came here to find me?
If I don't
stand with you now,
how can we partner later?
So you'll stay in the Dragon Clan?
I need to know
who I am
and my link to the Dragon Clan.
Save the talking for now.
The poison is getting thicker.
No.
We must find a way to get out.
This poison can weaken one's Vital Qi.
We can't fight back.
When's your backup coming?
Looks like
we're on our own.
Who gave you the courage?
Knowing that the Wing Clan had an ambush,
yet you let down your guard and walked right in it.
The Wing Clan
is no threat.
Dragon Xian.
Hold on.
I'll find a way our,.
Water.
That's it.
Dragons are born to master water.
Maybe
this can save you.
Let's go.
Your Qi is fading.
I'll transfer my Qi to you.
Don't resist.
The Qi of our Clans are mutually contradictory
You may die!
No time to care about that.﻿1
Your Qi is getting weaker.
I’ll transfer my Qi to you.
Don't resist.
Dragon Sovereign.
We caught a few of the Winged Clan’s minions.
But the Tiger with wings escaped.
A mere Tiger with wings is nothing to fear.
You had it all planned from the start.
You used your life to save me.
For now,
I’ll forgive you for keeping the truth from me.
You—
You schemed against me.
If you want to talk about scheming,
wasn’t it the Celestials
who plotted against us Dragons first?
How do you know that?
That old man, the Celestial Sovereign,
has been running wild across the realms using our Dragon Clan's name!
Lured the Tiger with wings to take revenge on me.
I thought the God of War was acting under the Celestial Sovereign’s orders.
Turns out,
You are not so obedient after all.
I—
I’ll leave this to you.
I’m going back to bathe and change.
You’re not hurt, are you?
Those bastards from the Winged Clan
have no idea how to hold back.
Is Dragon Xian okay?
If such a small wound counted as serious,
he would’ve died a hundred times already.
Your Qi is unstable—
You don't look too well.
That—
That’s because I saved Dragon Xian.
Don’t be foolish.
What does Dragon Xian’s life have to do with you?
If Dragon Xian dies,
do you think the Celestial Sovereign will spare me?
Even so, you can’t risk your own life to save him.
The immortal Chilian orchestrated this,
making the Winged Clan hate the Dragons.
Dragon Xian is also my mission.
I knew it would be dangerous for him.
But how could I let him walk into the lion’s den alone?
But you, Yingluo,
you’ve always solved problems with your fists.
Look at you now.
How did you become like this?
Yu Jing,
I’ve decided to take a risk.
I’m planning to stay with the Dragon Clan.
You’re going to defy the Celestial Sovereign’s decree?
I just want to block his control—temporarily.
What do you mean by that?
I just want
to get to know Dragon Xian again,
and get to know myself again.
To figure out
who I really am.
That idea is far too dangerous.
If I don’t truly let down my guard,
how can Dragon Xian trust me?
How can I
find out everything I want to know?
You're recovering quite well.
Tough, as expected.
Had I known, I wouldn’t have saved you that day.
The Dragon Clan’s Protector Assembly is in a few days.
Be sure to attend.
What are you planning now?
I heard you risked your life for Dragon Xian in the poison prison.
You’ve really changed my opinion of you.
Are you alright?
Nothing serious.
This is a Mystique of the Dragon Clan.
You can study and learn it more.
Don’t overthink it.
It’s my thank-you gift,
and also a condition of our cooperation.
Why—
Have you suddenly dropped all your defenses?
After all,
Now my body
Carries your Qi too.
Seems like you’ve become familiar with the Dragon Clan.
I’m curious—
Why did you say you’re sworn enemies with the Celestial Sovereign?
Do you know
the Dragon Clan has a unique technique—
The Finish Touch of the Dragon.
I’m curious, too.
The God of War of years past—
what was her true identity?
This technique
lets the sword wielder peer into the past.
If you want to know your connection to the Dragon Clan,
you may as well give it a try.
What exactly did you see?
Dragon Xian.
Yingluo.
Why did Yingluo disrupt the Winged Clan’s affairs?
Celestial Sovereign, please quell your anger.
The God of War would never dare betray you.
What is she doing?
Everything—
Everything is to gain Dragon Xian’s trust
to better complete the mission.
Bring her back.
I will question her myself.
You scared me to death.
Your Qi is extremely chaotic.
What exactly did you see?
I...
I think I saw
the fall of the Dragon Clan,
and I saw—
you being pierced by a sword.
That’s all in the past.
Look at me now—
I’m just fine, aren’t I?
It must have hurt terribly.
It was that sword that killed me.
And also that sword—
remade me.
I was wondering...
What kind of feelings
did the swordbearer hold that day,
to destroy me,
yet also grant me hope?
You don’t know who that person was?
No idea.
I only know—
Ten thousand years ago, it was the Celestial Clan that sought to wipe out my Dragon Clan.
Before that,
I did many unclear and confused things.
If this really is
the Celestial Sovereign’s scheme,
sending you back
to serve your enemy,
then I will never allow it to continue.
They’ve summoned me to return.
I cannot defy it.
These matters—
I will question the Celestial Sovereign myself.
Do you believe me?
I’ll wait for your return.
You truly suspect Yingluo?
If you kill her,
it would also be a loss for the Celestial Clan.
Yingluo has willingly fallen,
colluding with the rebellious Dragon Clan.
This defies the order.
If we don’t deal with it in time,
she will surely become
a calamity to the four Seas and eight Wastelands.
Celestial Sovereign!
So this is your doing.
Do you truly not know—
the Winged Clan is just a tool to harass the Dragons?
Calm yourself, my lord.
You are one of the Celestial Clan’s
strongest forces,
and the God of War I trust the most.
I sent you to bring back Dragon Xian,
not to aid the Dragons.
Celestial Sovereign,
Dragon Xian is no ordinary foe—
This I am well aware of.
Give me a bit more time.
At the very least,
Dragon Xian has agreed
to let me take the position of Protector.
He’s allowing you
to meddle in Dragon Clan internal matters.
Then perhaps he still finds me useful.
I came today to ask you one thing:
Who am I, really?
Why, ten thousand years ago,
did you annihilate the Dragon Clan,
yet now wish for Dragon Xian
to inherit the Celestial Sovereign’s position?
How dare you!
Are you questioning me?
What else do you wish to know?
Who was it back then
that pinned Dragon Xian on the Jade Platform?
What is that sword’s connection to me?
Was it the Dragons who were arrogant,
or the Celestials who were rotten?
You want to know who killed Dragon Xian ten thousand years ago?
Then I shall tell you.
Why is the sky raining fire?
Could Yingluo be in danger?
Dragon Clan bloodline commands—
Everyone,
form ranks and prepare for battle!
Yingluo—
You're back.
Weren’t you curious
why I can wield the Jade Sword?
Because
It was mine to begin with.
Your life—
is also mine.
This wine is called “Forget Worries.”
Dragon Xian—
I’m sorry.
I couldn’t stop the Celestial Sovereign,
nor disobey his command.
Let me take you away.
He won’t let me go.
If I want to save you,
there’s only one way.
I’ll use all of my power
to seal you within the Jade Sword.
Ten thousand years from now,
this sword will bring you back to life.
Ten thousand years later,
I’ll be waiting for your return.
So that’s how it is.
You remembered everything.
You know it all now.
So
the one who killed me ten thousand years ago,
destroyed me,
and gave me hope.
Dragon Xian.
Yingluo.
You’re awake.
Since you’re awake,
I will return the sword to you.
What happened?
You’re not hurt?
If you want to know—
agree to one thing first.
What is it?
Stay in the Dragon Clan.
Help me.
Build up the Dragon Clan.
That’s what you owe me.
I saved you back then!
I promise you—
I will use my life
to protect you.
Besides that,
whatever power I have in the Dragon Clan,
you will have the same.
You really dare make demands.
You have one incense stick’s time to consider.
If you agree,
I’ll tell you everything.
I agree.
Speak.
I trusted her too much after all.
Yingluo has always been loyal to you.
Maybe...
something dangerous happened.
Don’t you know how strong she is?
Even if she faced a war across the four Seas and eight Wastelands alone,
she’d still come back alive.
Celestial Sovereign, calm your wrath.
Don’t forget Yingluo’s identity.
She and Dragon Xian must not be allowed to join forces.
Why not
bring her back first,
then make plans?
This Ancestor Jade of Dragon
has been connected to me since birth.
It represents the power of the Dragon Clan—
it grants control over all Dragon affairs.
Now,
I’m splitting it in two.
I’ll give you the other half.
Take it.
I just worry…
am I worthy of it?
With the bond between us,
who else but you deserves it?
Once inside your body,
this jade
will erase all Celestial Qi from you.
It will also remove
the binding lock that old man placed on you.
How did you know?
If it weren’t for that,
why else would you still feel distant from me
after all this time?
I clearly struck you with my sword that day—
so why
are you now completely unscathed?
Have you forgotten—
my greatest strength
is enduring pain.
Besides,
you once made me coexist with the Jade Sword.
How could it possibly hurt me?
I see...
Dragon Sovereign,
The Messenger of the Celestial Clan is outside asking for Yingluo.
It should be Yu Jing.
I destroyed Qing Yu, my link to the Celestials.
The Celestial Sovereign is suspicious.
I’m guessing…
he’s already figured everything out.
So he sent Yu Jing to take me back.
Then let’s eliminate him.
No.
I’ll handle this myself.
Yu Jing is just following orders.
Staying with the Dragons
was my decision—
it has nothing to do with him.
Why was Qing Yu destroyed?
Why did you lose contact?
Do you know
how furious the Celestial Sovereign is?
Did he send you here to capture me?
He wants you to end your mission
and return to his side.
Yu Jing,
we’ve worked together for years—
you know me well.
Rest assured,
I’ve said plenty of good things about you to the Celestial Sovereign.
As long as you cut ties,
he won’t hold it against you.
Later,
I’ll “attack” and injure you.
It might hurt for a bit,
but if you go back with those injuries,
he won’t trouble you.
Do you know
what you’re doing?
This is my choice—
I don’t want to drag you down.
Are you really
going to surrender to Dragon Xian?
That has nothing to do with you.
The less you know, the safer you’ll be.
Yingluo, wake up!
You’re the God of War of the Celestial Clan!
What kind of spell did Dragon Xian put on you?
God of War,
come with me.
Where is this place?
This is the Moon Clan.
The Moon Clan?
The Celestial and Moon Clans
have never interfered with one another.
Why would they capture us?
Keep your voice down.
Here, in Moon Clan territory,
our Celestial powers are suppressed.
Be careful, we might not be able to fight them off.
Why did they capture me?
That’s…
a long story.
Let’s just hope we make it out of this alive.
Have you found Yingluo?
We searched everywhere.
Wasn’t there a Celestial messenger who came?
Could it be…
the Celestials took her back?
Unless that old man came himself,
It’s nearly impossible for anyone
to forcibly take Yingluo away.
Dragon Sovereign,
aren’t you worried Yingluo went back
willingly?
With her strength,
how could she just vanish like that?
No—
Maybe
she wanted to confront the Celestial Sovereign.
Then she’s a fool.
The Celestial Sovereign would rip anyone
who betrays him to pieces on the spot.
No matter what,
I’ll go to the Celestial Clan myself.
I cannot bear
the pain of losing Yingluo again.
This Moon Clan place is chilling—
cold to the bones.
I hope it doesn’t leave lasting effects.
You should focus on getting out
before worrying about side effects.
What?
Would the Moon Clan
really dare kill two Celestial beings?
No—
Two noble Celestial elites.
Who knows
we were abducted?
If they attacked us
and dump us in the wilderness…
no one will know.
Are you still hoping
the Celestial Sovereign will avenge you?
If he knew,
he’d probably thank the Moon Clan.
One less problem—you.
Is that an assassin?
Sister Yingluo,
long time no see.
What is going on here?
This is…
your little follower?
You…
You came to see me—
dressed like that.
Must be something important.
I hope you don’t confront my mother.
I’ll talk to her properly.
Back then, I let you go in good faith.
I didn’t know you were Moon Clan.
And I never did anything to harm you.
Didn’t expect
you still cared about me.
You’ve got a strange way of interpreting things.
My mother was just really angry—
so she had you kidnapped.
Angry?
I never did anything to harm the Moon Clan.
What’s this all about?
Actually—
the moment I saw you that day,
I fell for you.
So,
I used just
a tiny bit of trickery…
I stole your pill body
and secretly nurtured a spirit form.
Dong Fangruo!
You’ve gone too far!
I, Yingluo, am pure and proud—
Someone’s coming!
Don’t worry, sister—
I’ll take responsibility.
Come here.
I like you.
Bring her up.
Moon Sovereign—
this is her.
The Celestial God of War—Yingluo.
Since my son is lovesick,
you will stay in the Moon Clan
and become one of us.
What?!
I never intended
to have anything to do with the Moon Clan!
Dong Fangruo—
You heard that, didn’t you?
She doesn’t like you at all!
I know.
I’ve known from the start.
Mother Moon,
please spare them.
This
has nothing to do with them.
I didn’t bring her here
to facilitate your romance!
We’ve looked into it.
It was the Moon Clan.
As expected—it was the Moon Sovereign.
In that case,
should we demand her return from the Moon Sovereign，
and deal with her ourselves?
The God of War defied my will—
and forcibly joined the Dragon Clan.
She’s brought about her own destruction.
And if the Moon Clan dares kill my Celestial God of War,
they’ll earn my wrath.
That’s the way of the world.
You mean…
to use the Moon Clan’s hand?
Report!
Celestial Sovereign—
The Dragons sent messenger for peace talks.
They’re willing to relinquish a few disputed human territories.
Withdraw voluntarily.
Yes.
But...
But?
They think the God of War is in our hands.
They want her back.
Delusional.
Yingluo is not with them.
She was taken by the Moon Clan.
We’ve never had dealings with them.
What should we do?
Fortunately...
if that old man had taken her,
she’d be as good as dead.
The Moon Clan is troublesome,
But at least they can be reasoned with.
Yun Jing,
you and Lu Shui stay and protect the Dragon Clan.
Wait for my signal.
You’re going to the Moon Clan for Yingluo again?
No choice.
I promised her,
I’d protect her with my life.
I’m sorry.
It’s all because of me—
that things have come to this.
I haven’t even cried yet.
Why are you crying?
I’ll talk to Mother and Sister.
I’ll ask them to spare you.
Sister Yingluo’s been so good to me.
I didn’t mean to hurt you.
It’s alright.
There are plenty who want to capture me.
If not your Moon Clan,
I’d have been caught by the Celestial Sovereign.
At least
your methods are more straightforward.
I’ll figure something out.
Is he always like this?
If I’d known,
I wouldn’t have cared if he lived or died back then.
Don’t cry.
You finally showed up.
Storming into the Moon Clan alone—
I guess you really don’t take me seriously.
Cut the chatter.
I’m here for her.
Name your terms.
Ruo, what are you doing?!
Sister—
if you hurt them again,
I’ll kill myself in the most painful way possible!
You—
Go to your room.
Dragon Xian,
Why are you here?
Not bad.
You’re in good spirits.
All limbs intact—
better than I expected.
Didn’t expect you and Dragon Sovereign
to be so close.
Closer than me and my own brother.
Enough nonsense.
Yingluo is Dragon Clan.
Name your terms.
Though the Dragons have no feud with us,
you still carry Celestial blood.
If you want to take her back,
you’ll have to bleed.
Celestials and Moon Clan—
our bloodlines clash by nature.
If you dare take this Moon Clan elixir
and survive the chaos of clashing Qi within,
then you may take her.
No need.
Trading one life for another
isn’t worth it.
Relax.
It won’t kill the Dragon Sovereign.
But his power and cultivation
will be stripped back ten thousand years.
He did nothing to offend you.
The Dragon Clan has never interfered with Moon Clan affairs.
I’m the one who offended you.
Why target him?
You are nothing.
I set this trap
for Dragon Xian.
Making the Celestial Sovereign lose his heir.
His last heir—
this is the opportunity
I’ve waited for.
You knew about me and Dragon Xian.
So—
You used me as bait.
Well then, Dragon Sovereign,
my condition is simple:
Swallow this elixir,
and I’ll return you and Yingluo
safely to the Dragon Clan.
I will never become the Celestial Sovereign’s heir.
Whether you cripple me or not,
I refuse.
You know full well
what the Celestial Sovereign is like.
The Celestial Clan shines bright—
but without a successor,
it’s doomed.
Dragon Sovereign—wise as expected.
But I can’t take that risk.
The grudge I bear against him
is no less than yours.
But you two share the same bloodline.
Erasing—
a chosen heir
will shake the Celestials to their core.
But my Moon Clan thrives endlessly.
If it comes to it—
I’ll wear the Celestial Sovereign down.
Why not talk alliance?
The Dragon Clan
might be stronger than you think.
No need. I know the Celestial Sovereign.
The stronger you are,
the more he’ll see you as prey.
Mother Moon—
everything you did…
wasn’t for me?
Ruo,
don’t be foolish.
If I stay in the Moon Clan,
let Dragon Xian go.
Pretend none of this happened.
How about that?
Yingluo—
Don’t say another word.
Yingluo!
You think that if Dragon Xian didn’t show up today,
I’d let you go?
Mother Moon, no!
Stop!
Don’t hurt her!
Mother Moon,
please spare Yingluo.
The blame lies
With me alone.
Ruo,
take this elixir to Dragon Xian.
If he swallows it,
I’ll release Yingluo.
God of War—
you owe the Dragon Sovereign your life.
If I didn’t have plans for him,
you wouldn’t survive the day.
Dragon Xian—
don’t believe her.
The Dragon Clan still needs you.
The Dragon Clan and I
exist because of you.
The Celestial Sovereign’s words can’t be trusted.
And the Moon Sovereign’s can?
The Dragon Clan
is still waiting for you.
Don’t forget—
you belong to them.
That’s why I’m stopping you.
I promised—
I’d protect you
with my life.
Who asked for your promise?
I chose to stay with the Dragons—
not because you protected me.
Yingluo,
from now on,
maybe I’ll need your protection.
If I lost all my cultivation ,
Will you take care of me?
No.
I’ll torment you.
I’ll abuse you.
I’ll humiliate you.
I
I believe you.
Moon Sovereign—
make sure you send us back to the Dragon Clan.
Don’t let others take advantage.
Understood.
No wonder the Celestial Sovereign is so obsessed with you.
If you were my heir,
I’d fight
to keep you too.
No—
don’t, Dragon Xian!
Don’t—
don’t listen to her.
We’re going home.
Don’t be afraid.
I
I’m not worth your sacrifice.
Trust me—
I’ll be fine.
You forget—
I’ve always been hard to kill.
Dragon Xian…
Dragon Xian, don’t!
Dragon Xian!
Dragon Xian
Look at me
Cry
No. Not pretty.
Come on, help him.
How is he?
There is a strange energy
within him intertwined with
the yin and yang energies.
It seems
to be protecting him.
By the way
He carries
both Celestial and
Dragon bloodlines.
What exactly did the Moon Sovereign feed him?
This is a rare pill even among the Moon Clan
It contains the purest yin energy of the clan
and is a secret treasure they use for cultivating their spiritual energy.
A single pill
grants a thousand years of cultivation power.
So
Now, three forces
are intertwining within him.
He's really something,
surviving this long.
How long will the effect last?
How much time does he have left?
The pill
carries a powerful invasive essence.
It greatly amplifies the Moon Clan's bloodline energy within him,
while simultaneously eroding the blood force of other clans.
It's a very domineering
and unreasonable pill.
Protect him
Let me help him
Are you sure... Shut up!
Hold him up!
What are you doing?
Help you
How could you abandon yourself
after all these years of practice?
Just as you saved me
No reason needed
Yingluo secretly colluded with the Dragon Clan to
betray the Celestial Clan
and was also involved with the Moon Clan.
To dare defy the laws of heaven…
Hear the command!
Slay Yingluo at once — no mistakes permitted!
No delays, no mercy!
Who are you?
How dare you act recklessly here!
After all
Now, my body
carries your energy.
I promised you
I will protect your safety
with my life.
I'll take the risk
because I believe that
once you understand who I really am,
you won't want him anymore.
I’m finally here with you
How can you fall?
Dragon Xian
Wake up!
This can't be happening…
Why wasn't
my inner energy destroyed?
You were lucky your blood wasn't pure.
When the yin and yang energies collided,
the Dragon essence balanced the force
just in time.
Something's wrong!
The Celestial Sovereign knows about the two of you
and has already issued a death order on Yingluo.
The Dragon Clan is to be driven out
from all corners of the world.
While the Empress is too busy to notice you
Leave now!
Otherwise
Once they know Dragon Xian is safe,
They won't spare any of you.
Thank you
This time
Stealing your body core
has caused so much trouble.
It's none of your business.
I know
You saw it as mercy.
I felt
it as salvation.
But now things are better.
This guy is willing to risk his life for you.
You'll be safe with him.
Alright
She was always mine.
Don't speak as though
you've made a sacrifice.
Don't get too full of yourself.
I don't believe
the two of you will never have any misunderstandings.
You can protect her for your life
Sure
Listen
If you dare hurt her,
I'll find her
to the ends of the earth.
I'm afraid you won't get that chance.
Stop arguing!
Dragon Xian
You're not healed yet.
Head back to the Dragon Clan.
Dongfang Ruo and I will go save him.
Yingluo
Long time no see
It's you
I saved you
Is this how you repay me?
I can't go against the Celestial Sovereign's orders.
And he promised not to harm you.
Bullshit
Yingluo
The Sovereign gave you your life.
How dare you betray him?
I'll go with you.
But the Dragon Clan is innocent.
Let them go.
When do you
have to step in and decide for the Celestial Sovereign?
You and Dragon Xian really do share a bond of mutual respect.
He was in danger, and you came to his aid.
Now that you're in danger,
I wonder if
he'll return the favor?
I guess it was all in my head.
He won't come.
Who would
care for an enemy?
And who would truly welcome
someone who slaughtered their entire clan?
Who would ever trade their
own life for that of an enemy?
Do you
remember now?
He used me before to take down the Dragons.
Now he's trying the same play?
You think he'll get fooled by the
same person twice?
Look
A war god forged by Tianzun himself,
yet you betray those who made you.
I suppose it falls to me to
remind you of your place!
The immortal Chilian
Didn't the Celestial Sovereign promise not to
kill the God of War?
He's right.
It sounds like the Dragon Sovereign
didn't come here with saving in mind.
There seems to be no one here
that I wish to save.
Perhaps I
should take action in place of the immortal Chilian.
I've been waiting for this day
for a long time.
Yingluo
Ten thousand years ago,
You pretended to love me,
But in truth,
You served the Celestial Clan
And destroyed Dragon Clan
Then, you had me nailed to the Jade Platform of the Immortals for ten thousand years.
Dragon Xian
Now
it's your turn to
know the pain of betrayal.
Between heaven and earth,
I am utterly alone.
It's me.
I have failed the Dragon Clan.
The immortal Chilian
Tell that old man
I won't be
controlled by him,
no matter what he does.
He gave you
the ultimate power
But now that it's useless,
What else does he think can control me?
One day
You will pay.
All of you will.
Ungrateful!
If it weren't for the Celestial Sovereign's will to spare you…
Got it now?
Dragon Xian knows it all.
Now that your memories have returned
let us speak plainly.
Running to the Dragons
won't save you.
Without the Celestial Clan,
you're nothing
but a lost mutt.
Yingluo
It's all my fault.
I'm the one who destroyed you.
Told you so.
How could
Dragon Xian make the same mistake
twice?
Yingluo
Yingluo was already weakened from giving you her breath
during the Moon Clan ritual.
Just now, the immortal Chilian nearly killed her
I didn't expect
You almost got Yingluo killed.
I
I had no choice.
If I hadn't intervened,
Do you really think the immortal Chilian
would've let her go so easily?
What?
Was it all just an act?
Yingluo
Wake up
I'll explain everything to you.
She's fading fast.
We need to anchor her soul and spirit now!
Our souls are bound to
The ancestor jade of dragon.
The ancestor jade of dragon
will be placed in the Spirit Energy Pool for healing,
until Yingluo is fully restored.
I'll be with Yingluo
as she faces her
mortal tribulations.
Yingluo
Our memories
have been sealed within this amulet.
It will also
hide our presence.
So that old man won't find us.
May all go as planned.
So
Madame Li sent you here
did she tell you anything
about my family?
Well
You agreed to marry me
the first time we met
It's kind of embarrassing, actually.
I may not be rich
but I'll work hard and take care of you
So from now on,
You'll carry water
Plow the fields
Weave cloth
And water the garden, how does that sound?
I don't ask for much
Us two...
Why won't you talk to me?
You're not… mute,
are you?
My fairy
Aaaaaaah! It hurts!
You're the mute!
Tell me
Who's in charge of our home?
You, you, you!
You're the boss!
Honey
Seriously, you can't do anything?
I have
my own mission.
You
just handle your part.
That's all
you need to know.
But I
Save it!
Done.
You know what to do with the rest.
Well then,
I've got some prep
to do before tonight's cultivation.
Cultivation?
Just do as I say.
And
Chop the wood, then boil some water.
After all
Cultivation takes time.
But I don't know how!
Don't?
It hurts!
I...I will! I'll learn!
Honey
Can you
stop being so violent already?
What are you doing?
Leave me alone
I've called for help.
Go ahead
let's see who comes running for you.
What's this?
What are you looking at?
This is a new formation I just learned!
Do you know why I married you?
It's because this book said that
For practical cultivation
I need someone
with a strong body.
You're not bad.
Let me go
Fine
Don't move.
Show me a miracle.
No reaction at all?
One more time.
Show me a miracle.
The force
just wasn't enough, that's all.
Again
Show me
a miracle.
Why didn't
the last plan work?
The text is
never wrong.
It must be me.
Let me try another way.
I was once a deity in the heavens
but somehow,
I've fallen to the mortal world and lost my memories.
Gods of everywhere,
If you hear my call,
I beg you, answer me.
You called for me?
Did you do that on purpose?
No
It's not like that.
Be honest
How much do you really know about me?
Was it you who
caused me to end up like this?
I swear
I had nothing to do with it!
I'm just getting old.
And I wanted a pretty bride, okay?
From West Street.
Old Matchmaker Li told me about you.
Really?
I swear.
If I brought you to ruin,
let lightning
strike me now.
Still denying it?
It hurts!
Let me go
Allow me to explain
If you trapped me here…
Watch yourself.
Then
I'll tell you a secret.
Actually
I'm not human.
I'm a god from the heavens.
I've just lost my memory.
Help me get back
When I remember who I am
I'll grant you anything
you want.
Hmm...
That's not the key.
I've lost my memories.
That's all.
No way!
I didn't finish.
Two silver coins for one try.
You're seriously trying to renege on this?
Two silver coins!
Impossible!
Jesus!
You got it again!
You're playing dirty!
Hey!
Are you out of your mind?
Go ahead, take a few throws
Here's your ring!
One more, one more.
Okay, fine.
Place your bets, big or small! Final call!
Win!
Come!
Small
Small! Small!
Eight! Small!
Big!
Bravo!
Wow!
Jackpot!
Wait a sec
Are you
actually handing over the shop?
But
At this rate
I'm worried you'll anger the gods.
I think
I'll take a statue home.
Just in case I need to pray for your safety.
What would
you like to worship today?
Fortune?
Luck?
Marriage?
Or for peace?
All of these
Great!
Oh, I've got
a few powerful ones right here.
Look! This is a real celestial deity!
Only the heavens could match its power.
Boss
This thing's falling apart!
No way
Look this one.
Trust me, it's solid.
Oops!
What's wrong?
My statue!
You broke it!
Let go! Let go! Let go!
Your statue's quality is so poor
How is it our fault it broke?
There's definitely something off about you two.
I've been running this stall for years
And I've never seen anything like this.
Alright then,
How do you think we should handle this?
You damaged two statues.
Ten taels
Then we're done.
What?!
These two statues are just mud and wood, they fall apart at a touch.
You want ten taels of gold?!
This is a noble celestial deity
God from the heavens!
You two must’ve picked up something foul
Even the gods don't want to get involved with you.
And I haven’t even said anything about how unlucky you are!
I'm a person of the heavens too!
You're just trying to rip me off!
We're not exactly rolling in gold right now.
Is that enough?
Enough
Thank you
Only when I figure all this out
will my life truly have meaning.
If that's the case,
I'll find a way to earn the money
and send you back.
Tea is ready
Enjoy your tea.
Boss
Can I ask you something?
Sure
Is there any
good way to make money in this city?
Good way?
You think
I'd still be here if I knew better?
Note it
No profit in tea.
What?
Dragon paintings, that's where the gold is
Everyone's
after them.
Rarer than gold.
Dragon painting?
Right
Dragons bring luck.
Hang a dragon painting,
and you'll have good weather
and a great harvest next year.
Let's go for a look.
Go
Now now, everyone!
the dragons I paint are not mere beasts,
but true celestial beings.
Only for nobles and high officials.
You think this kind of money
can buy a dragon scroll?
Who do you take me for?
That fat shopkeeper's always picking on common folk.
It's just a dragon painting.
Anyone can do it.
You can draw a dragon?
This is the real dragon.
You've seen a real dragon?
Nope
But I'm certain
This is the real dragon.
Stay here. x
I'll be back after a quick round at the market.
Why did it take you so long?
We're gonna rich.
What happened?
Listen
Your dragon painting
Made people go nuts for it the second I showed it
Bids soared higher and higher
Finally, the shop owner paid
a hundred gold taels for it!
What?
No way!
As long as your hand
can still paint,
we're going to
get rich!
Bravo!
Then starting tomorrow,
I'll paint you as many dragons as you want.
Find them!
Daring to mess with me?
I guess he's got a death wish.
Search!
Who the hell sold me a dragon painting at the market yesterday?
Come out now!
Who's that?
It's her! Move!
Watch out!
Go away!
I've gotten so powerful now
You actually dared to mess with my man?
You have grown tired of this life.
You want a fight? Take me on.
Go!
A piece of cake.
Are you alright, Dragon Xian?
No. no, no.
Don't come any closer.
I guess you're tired of living.
Come here.
Kneel down
Say sorry to him
Sorry, bro.
Forgive my ignorance
We were only
following orders!
Who told you to do this?
It was
all set up by the nobles
in the city.
What do you mean — a setup?
Originally,
painting dragons was just a tradition
where the people showed gratitude to heaven.
Yet when the nobles
declared them auspicious
and suddenly everyone's losing their mind over scrolls.
Painting a dragon? That's easy
If you want them,
I can paint
dozens in a single day.
Absolutely not!
Why?
There used to be many dragon painters in the city,
but…they all died
under mysterious circumstances.
That's why the art of painting dragons
has nearly been lost over time.
Then who exactly painted all those
dragon scrolls in the city?
Of course it's the nobles who are painting them now.
They're the only ones who still know how… and dare to.
With a single dragon scroll so hard to find,
Everyone's desperate
to pay more for one.
Could it be
that the painters
were...
were killed by them?
That's outrageous!
I'm just giving you a friendly warning
if you start painting dragons like crazy,
everyone will have one.
And then who's going to pay extra for it?
It's not worth much to begin with.
The people
just want a little good luck
hoping for peace and prosperity in the coming year.
Since that’s the case
I
might as well use this chance
to teach them a lesson.
If his words hold truth
wouldn't us painting dragons again
just anger those people?
Are you afraid?
Afraid?
So what
if they do?
I'm tough.
and heal fast.
You really can take a beating.
Got another plan, huh?
Exactly!
That's a chance
to help the people
and make some real money!
Alright,
Are you sure
this is the place?
This is the place SiKong Yuan told me,
it won't be wrong.
That person looks a little scary.
You two are finally here,
I've been waiting for you.
Hunter in Chaos,
has the power to solve any problems
around the four Seas and eight Wastelands.
If you have any problems,
go ahead and ask me.
I want to know
who I am,
why I am here,
and how can I get back to where I belong?
A thousand pieces of gold.
Pay first, answer later.
You just asked me three questions,
that will be three thousand gold.
That's too expensive,
can it be cheaper?
Is he frozen?
who I am.
I'll find it out right now.
You're indeed not a mortal person.
You were the thing born when the world was created,
and later you become
the strongest fighter
around the four Seas and eight Wastelands.
Are you sure?
So how can I get back?
A thousand gold for one question.
Pay first, answer later.
Are you crazy?
You're a total treacherous man.
He's frozen again.
Is he lying?
Never mind,
let's
go home.
I'll paint more dragons,
this is enough for me.
You're really leaving now?
You don't want to ask me any more questions?
Actually, I want to say that,
we can just wait for the perfect moment.
You're gonna go out?
I need to do something.
I see your dress,
are you planning to go to the earth and find them?
Is it that obvious.
Please,
the two of them keep their memories and hide from the earth
to not let the celestial sovereign finds out.
If you go just like this
and stimulate them to think of something,
you're going to expose them.
I know,
I'm just worried.
What if they have any problems or dangerous
on earth?
But he will have his experience
and toughening sooner or later.
I'll go check them in secret,
I won't let them spot me.
There's a messenger from the heaven
in the room waiting for you to call.
I'll leave the dragon clan to you,
I need to go, bye bye.
No one is trustworthy.
Are you really not going to take another try?
Maybe live here all my life
is my fate.
You don't have any regrets?
Not at all,
I am from heaven,
if I know how to go back,
you'll be the only one left here.
You're staying here, for me?
You don't have much time all your life,
let's just say I give you my time.
You really don't regret this?
No,
because I know
you're the people who treat me best
in the world.
Come and taste,
I learned a new dish for you,
is it good?
Looks like the life on earth
is not so bad,
if Dragon Xian is not the Dragon Sovereign,
does he can also have this
peaceful and easy life?
Dragon Xian,
wake up.
I always feel
somebody's watching us.
You're an immortal,
don't be scared.
Dragon Xian.
I don't know what's wrong with me lately,
I always feel that someone is watching me
in the dark.
It makes me so messed.
Since I know who you really are,
I feel that there's nothing could
scare me anymore in the world.
No way,
we still need to find a good master to help me.
What are you scared of?
Nothing could be
even more scary than you.
What the hell is going on here?
I've heard that you guys are trying to find a good master,
what do you think of me?
Lord celestial sovereign,
you've been watching a lot
this little town on the earth,
what's wrong with this place?
Although nothing special,
the energy of the dragon clan keeps happening here,
it makes me wondering.
Good master,
my wife lately has always felt that
somebody is watching over her
in the dark,
is she encounter
some bad energy?
I always feel that
there's someone watching me in the dark,
could some freak ghost
has his eyes on me?
Maybe it's someone
who cared about you.
How about this?
I'll give you a very top quality treasure,
as long as you make a wish to this with devotion,
the heaven will listen to you.
Is this thing can
contact with the heaven?
Of course,
this is made
by the green birds' wings,
every wish will come true
as long as you two do not be too greedy.
This,
this looks very high quality.
Of course.
Then it should be very useful.
Then,
we wish to be rich.
No,
we need to be safe and sound,
it's more important,
to be safe.
To be rich.
No, safe.
I want to be rich.
It's so good that you two have lost your memories.
If you make a wish for something like
unifying the four Seas and eight Wastelands.
I wish the two of us
will grow old together,
and I can be her husband forever long,
we could a family forever.
I wish him to be safe and sound
all his life,
and the two of us will support each other,
we can be together forever long.
What are you wishing for?
It's not gonna happen if I say that out.