[Shi Ya]
[Shi Ya is so beautiful. They would be a perfect match if they were together.]
[E-sports Goddess,Boys Killer.]
E-sports Goddess.
[I like you so much.]
[You are so elegant.]
[Congratulations, hahaha.]
Boys Killer.
Hi, it's such a beautiful night.
[Hi, it's such a beautiful night. Do you want to have supper with me?]
Do you want to have supper with me?
Eat.
All you know is eat.
Are you a pig?
I want to lose weight.
Did your team
get the sponsorship back?
Yes.
To find them,
I stayed up
for several nights.
I'm exhausted.
Do you want to eat cake?
I just finished.
No.
I want to lose weight.
Lose weight?
Here.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
Isn't this the leader
in your team?
Son,
get some food for Ya.
I'm hungry.
I want to
eat
right now.
Waiter,
order taking.
Didn't we just eat?
Mrs. Shi,
although my son is 24,
he's still like a child.
Son,
you and Ya are both in E-sports.
You two should have many common topics.
They seem to be on a blind date.
From now on,
you should hang out with Ya often.
Mom,
She is the commentator.
I'm a player.
I don't rely on words.
Watch your mouth.
Auntie,
Chuan is right.
I'm in charge of commenting the game.
If they let me play games,
I can't do it.
But Chuan,
I can train with you.
Yes.
I'm not a kid anymore. Why do I need company?
Here.
Let's eat.
Why don't you try
their coconut jelly?
It is famous.
I don't want it.
Why?
My teeth are not good.
It's okay.
This is not very sweet.
I have diabetes.
Don't listen to him.
Why does he has diabetes?
What are you doing?
Let me help you.
No.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
I have a cramp.
Here.
Wipe it.
Ya.
Sit down.
Let's eat.
Here.
Ignore him.
Here, Ya.
Let's eat.
Ya.
Here.
Thank you.
[Out with a Bang]
[Episode 11]
Here.
Please come in.
Chu Tian.
Why are you here?
Sit.
Miss Chu Tian, the great designer,
designed our uniform personally.
Here, take a look.
Is it beautiful?
Yes.
Let me tell you.
I spent a lot of money
asking the master
to calculate
the color of the uniform
for our team.
It can guarantee our
winning the first battle.
I've played an
integral part in this.
Am I right, Tian?
Xiong Jiujiu.
Get the clothes
and distribute them.
I'll get some water for Tian.
Tian.
What do you like to drink?
Mineral water, soda, juice drink, coke.
Coke.
Okay.
I knew
you like carbonated drinks.
Otherwise, why would I bubble up
with excitement when I see you?
Guess
what I like to drink.
I like to take care of you.
Do you like water?
Then you will like
70 percent of me.
Chu Tian.
You smiled.
Who smiled?
I'm going to see Chu Tian.
Xiong Jiujiu.
What do you like to eat?
Do you like the infatuated me?
Infatuation is not a sin.
Forgetting is not carefree.
I...
I'll give it to her.
You two can debut.
Legend of Phoenix
Tian.
Wait for me.
Shi Ya has nothing to do with me.
Did anyone ask you?
My mom asked me to have dinner.
I didn't know Shi Ya would come.
I knew it.
Oh.
I really don't like woman who is
smart and generous,
kind and gentle,
pretty and cute.
It's hard to coax a jealous woman.
You...
Do you really not need me to drive you?
No.
I don't want to listen to cheesy pickup lines anymore.
What flavor do you like?
I can learn.
Well.
Your competition is coming.
Just focus on your training.
I'll take a taxi.
Was Chu Tian
often bullied in the team?
Bullied?
How is that possible?
Who?
Don't play dumb.
Xiao Yichuan
doesn't look easy to get along with.
Chuan just doesn't look easy to get along with.
Actually,
he encouraged Chu Tian a lot.
There is Xiong Jiujiu in the middle.
It's impossible for Xiong Jiujiu to like Chu Tian.
So,
we outsiders
should not interfere
in matters of love.
What do you mean?
I also hope Xiong Jiujiu
can get her own happiness.
It has nothing to do with Chu Tian.
You are such a sensible woman.
Don't use your name
to play this pun with me.
I know what Xiong Jiujiu is thinking.
But I can't persuade Chu Tian.
I hope he won't get hurt here.
I think JR
should not be a place
where Chu Tian can
continue to have a crush.
I can understand how you feel.
How about this?
You can come to watch our game.
I think you should see
the other side of Tian.
My mom offered to
lend us money today,
[My mom offered to lend us money today, I haven't agreed yet.]
I haven't agreed yet.
[You'll get the bonus if you win, right?]
You'll get the bonus if you win, right?
[My mom offered to lend us money today, I haven't agreed yet.]
[You'll get the bonus if you win, right?]
[Can you win?]
Can you win?
I'll try my best.
[You'll get the bonus if you win, right?]
[Can you win?]
[I'll try my best.]
This team is strong.
Shall we hide for a while?
Chuan!
Let's play.
OK.
Chuan.
Lead them.
Yes.
[Flight Route]
[Advanced Supplies]
[Ultimate Supplies]
Where to jump?
Jump to school.
After you've searched for supplies, go to a place with fewer people.
Leave the rest to me.
No need.
I have two teams here.
[Flight Route]
[Advanced Supplies]
[Ultimate Supplies]
Chu Tian and I are very poor.
We haven't finished searching.
Leave if you can't.
Don't wait for help.
[Landing Scattered]
[Insufficient Coordination]
# [杚线散]
Those who are capable are powerful.
But Chuan,
why do I feel
we’re holding you back?
Yeah, Chuan.
I can't keep up with you.
You think too much.
Relax
and focus on your problems.
The points of games
are divided into two parts:
the ranking points and the number of eliminations.
Eliminating opponents in the early stage
will get a higher score
than in the later stage.
So under such rules,
most teams
will choose to fight head-on in the early stage.
Chuan and Chu Tian's speed
and shooting accuracy have no problems.
So the scores
mainly depend on you two.
But we have to
fight for ranking points.
Dongshi comes first.
Hong Yang, you need to be familiar with the map.
Let's cover each other.
Live longer.
Any problems?
No.
Anything
can happen on the stage.
Hurry up
and cooperate with each other.
Cheer up before the game.
Trust yourself.
[Dr. Chen]
Hello, Dr. Chen.
I'll go to the hospital tomorrow.
If I don't find you,
you just go to the hospital yourself?
Stingy.
I'm just here to prescribe some medicine.
All right.
Here.
Get me the medicine.
Don't stand here.
OK.
Give me your arm.
Let me check.
There's edema.
Dr. Chen.
Can you give me an injection
for emergency treatment?
The competition is the day after tomorrow.
The injection can only be temporary relief.
It's not a long-term solution.
Numb.
Pain.
If these symptoms can't be cured,
your condition will get worse
in the future.
Besides,
the side effects of the medicine
is inevitable.
You'll feel tired
and can't focus.
These will directly affect
your game status.
Go ahead.
Did you think it through?
Dr. Chen.
My list...
What's wrong?
Your hand.
Let me see.
It's okay.
What happened to your hand?
Nothing.
What is this injection for?
It used to be external.
Why is there an injection?
This is a kind of injection
to help my hand recover.
Are you lying to a kid?
Dr. Chen.
Tell me.
What's wrong with his hand?
Hey, Xiao Yichuan.
You still won't tell the truth?
How long are you going to hide it from me?
I'm not.
I have taken the injection
and the medicine.
You can take the injection,
but you're not allowed to go to the competition.
Go back
and explain it to them.
You won't go to the competition.
I'll be fine after the injection.
Are you lying to a three-year-old kid?
Can you put your health first?
Can you take care of yourself?
Do you have to make me worried?
Right?
Is this the first day you know me?
Don't worry.
I can go to the competition.
It’s not a competition.
But give up your life
for this team.
I didn't do it for them.
They made me understand
if you want something,
don't miss any opportunity
to fight for it.
I want to try again.
I don't want to hear you talk about the chicken soup.
I only care about your hand injury.
Xiao Yichuan.
What good results can you produce
when you play with an injury and drag a bunch of rookies?
Why are you so stubborn?
Stubborn?
Didn't you say
you saw the younger me
in them?
As long as I don't give up,
I won't lose.
Do you have to compete?
Of course.
Hello.
I'll get the medicine.
Wait inside.
[JR Basketball Team]
Are you ready to
go out for a drive at night?
Take me with you.
I'm working.
The basketball team's car?
Yes.
I borrowed it from the basketball department.
Does our team
deserve to own a car?
Those without grades
don't deserve anything.
I believe that
no grades are only temporary.
Don't think those who can't do it now
will never do it.
Manager.
You're getting excited again.
Come on.
I'm listening.
I'm serious.
As long as we don't give up,
we won't lose.
You...
Why are you looking at me?
Give loving encouragement
to the manager.
Go to work.
[Carpal Tunnel Syndrome]
[Contact]
[Xiao Yichuan]
[Detailed explanation of carpal tunnel syndrome]
[Cause 1 There are several sources of pressure on the median nerve.]
[Click to invite friends]
Hey.
You...
Don't sleep at night,
come to train?
It's not your style
to make effort at the last moment.
Don't make any mistakes
in tomorrow’s game.
Wang Boyu.
Are you stimulated?
How many years do you think
we can play?
How many more games can we play?
Since we still have a game to play,
we have to do our best.
If you want something,
you must never give up and fight for it.
This is what I just heard today.
Together.
♫ Believe the faith in your heart ♫
[Universe Borrowing Method]
[Universe Wuji]
[Baraka]
♫ The dream is always in front of me ♫
♫ In a challenging world ♫
♫ Step is hot like a flame ♫
♫ Face the bright sun ♫
You must come today.
Cheer for us.
♫ Stick with the choice to swim upstream ♫
♫ Get everybody to see ♫
♫ Our charming youth ♫
♫ Let's set sail with passion ♫
♫ Feel the cool of the rain ♫
Come on.
[Come on, I'll wait for your good news.]
I'll wait for your good news.
♫ Go up and down with the waves ♫
♫ This is our most memorable moment ♫
♫ No one can stop ♫
♫ Buzzing with gunshots ♫
♫ My heart goes up and down ♫
The JR Team.
Come on.
♫ I just want to have a good fight ♫
♫ No one can stop ♫
Wait.
I suddenly remembered
the lunar calendar said
you should step your left foot before going out.
Come on.
Left foot.
One, two, three.
Go.
[JR]
Let me tell you
the arrangement of the game.
[The 7th TLO Global League]
In this case,
the time, location and process
are all
on this list.
Later,
I'll send you
an electronic version.
The most important thing you need to pay attention to
is that our competition involves
a lot of personnel arrangements.
So try to
follow the entire schedule we sent you.
If there's anything special,
you can tell me in advance.
Now,
I'll take you to the preparation room.
This is it.
[Preparation Room]
Please come in.
Okay, thank you.
Stingy.
You miss me again?
Be careful later.
Chu Tian.
Play well for your captain
and get more points.
Enough.
He doesn't need you to teach him.
Let's go.
Go.
[The 7th TLO Global League in China]
What's wrong?
Are you nervous?
No.
I can't wait.
Do your best later.
Don't be affected
by the environment.
If you're really nervous,
put your earphones on when you sit down.
Don't listen to anything.
Don't replay
and discuss after each round.
Adjust your mindset
and state.
Continue the next round.
If there's any problem,
just listen to Chuan.
Alright.
Let's warm up.
Rub your hands.
[I'm in the audience, you cheer up and tell Chutian.]
Chu Tian.
Your sister told you
to come on.
The JR Team is ready.
OK.
Get ready to go.
[Preparation Room]
This is your last season.
Cherish it.
Play well.
No one
will remember who you are.
As for you,
the passerby bureau you killed
is just a joke.
Hey, Chu Tian.
Forget it.
You need to practice your mental quality.
[Doping Waiting Area]
[Athletes Dressing Area]
[Audience Entrance]
I almost thought
I couldn't catch up with you guys.
Thank you, manager.
Boss.
Come on.
Hong Yang.
Chu Tian.
Come on.
[The 7th TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
You...
We can do it.
[TLO Global League]
Welcome to
[Play-in match]
the 7th
TLO
Mission Global League China
play-in match.
I'm Ka.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Shi Ya.
I'm your Brother Long.
Long.
All teams
are ready to go on stage.
Let's introduce
the rules.
The top four teams in a single game
[Competition Rules]
will get
10, 8, 6,
and 4 points.
Whoever knocks out one person in the first round ## 首圈淘汰一人(whoever knocks out one person in the first round/Whoever knocks out one person in the first round)
gets three points.
Two points for the second round.
[Competition Rules]
After that, whoever knocks out one person
will get one point.
Next, let me introduce
the participants team this year.
There is an OP Team
and AOE Team
that we are more familiar with.
They left us
a deep impression
in the last season.
When it comes to last season,
I have to mention
the SIK Team.
The SIK Team
entered the top eight in Europe.
It is the best result
achieved by the Chinese team
in the World League
in recent years
after Xiao Yichuan led the PUP Team
in recent years,
to the second best result
in the World League.
Yes.
The SIK Team has
won many champions
in the Cup and League.
But they never win
in the global league.
It's their regret
and also the regret of
the Chinese team.
I hope
this year they can make their dreams come true.
Next, we'll see that
the teams that signed up for the league this year
have added a lot of new faces
compared to last year.
Yes.
This year we have
ON Team and JR Team.
Two new teams
that have just been formed.
This is the first time
for them to show themselves.
As we can see,
Xing Ziyi
is the newcomer king
voted by netizens in the latest quarter.
We look forward to ON Team's performance.
Although the team is newly established,
there are some old faces inside.
For example,
Xiao Yichuan from the JR Team.
I believe everyone here
knows him.
Xiao Yichuan
has joined an unheard-of new team,
JR Team,
for the first time
since the club's contract expired last season.
Now that
he is back on the field,
I am sure many of you
are looking forward to it
as much as I am.
Coming.
The JR Team.
[The 7th TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
OK.
As we can see, 16 teams
[The 7th TLO Global League]
of the TLO Global League
have entered.
Let’s wait and see
their performance.
The competition is about to begin.
[The play-in match in China, Elite gathering, the game starts now]
Please get ready.
Come on.
The game starts now.
The position I'm marking.
Jump.
This...
So many teams
want to jump here.
Fly in the opposite direction to the factory.
The three of the JR Team
went in the opposite direction.
Maybe they found that
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
there are too many people here after skydiving.
It is wise to avoid war.
Chuan.
Why are you still flying in that direction?
Are you going to fight them alone?
The tactics of three-point search.
There are many people there.
I'll get the points first.
Find a place to hide.
Search the supplies if you have the chance.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
The JR Team uses
the tactics of three-point search.
According to our points rule,
whoever knocks out one person in the first round ## 首圈淘汰一人(whoever knocks out one person in the first round/Whoever knocks out one person in the first round)
can get three points.
Chuan
will never give up
the chance to score.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
He landed.
Xiao Yichuan got
the first elimination.
Xiao Yichuan returns to the game.
The first shot.
This shot
seems to be directly on my heart.
It's the feeling of heartbeat.
[Points Ranking]
Xiao Yichuan used a landing gun
to announce his return.
I have a personal request.
Director, can you cut
Wang Boyu's expression?
In the past six months,
he was basically taking the first points.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
Xiao Yichuan.
Hurry up.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
Xiao Yichuan again.
His shooting is stable.
It looks like he's still at his peak.
Just now,
Chuan force the gun.
Familiar taste
and operation.
It's New Year.
[JR Chuan]
Xiao Yichuan stole a gun to get points.
The scariest thing about him
is that
he can fight head-on
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
and play dirty.
But
why hasn't Xiao Yichuan go to meet his teammates
after collecting supplies?
You see, he's getting farther and farther from his teammates.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
Is he excited to play by himself?
Now on the screen
are Yang and Dong Shi
of the JR Team.
[JR Dong Shi]
Someone is coming over.
Is there a smoke bomb?
Yes.
Cover me to take the car.
Now?
Hey.
What's going on?
Dong Shi of the JR Team
blew up his teammate with a grenade.
Capt. Qin.
Is this your strategy?
I think Hong Yang rushed too fast.
Dong Shi pressed the wrong button in a hurry.
What?
Is this no communication?
Maybe CEO wants to blow up the vehicle
so that the OP Team can't get it either.
CEO's grenade throwing
is not too much to call
a vehicle stroke master.
The OP Team on the opposite side are stunned.
Maybe they are writing a letter of gratitude.
They didn't come to get the vehicle.
I heard
the CEO of JR Team
is a person who believes in metaphysics very much.
So,
the teammate before the car sacrifice,
the champion is in my hand.
Is he from the Devil Sect?
Chuan.
How’s it going over there? I’ll go find you.
You drive to meet Chu Tian.
I'll pick up airdrop.
Chu Tian.
What's going on over there?
I'm looking for you.
I haven't got the gun yet.
What is Tian doing in the JR Team?
He hasn't picked up the gun.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
This team
is
so magical.
Maybe you don't know that
Tian of JR Team
has a habit of using only domestic guns.
He became very passive
in collecting supplies
because the rhythm of skydiving
was disrupted in the early stage.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Nice.
Chu Tian escaped again
with the sound of the explosion
of the grenade thrown by the Ocean Team.
Is he
too early to be happy?
SIK is here.
[Auto Rifle]
[Chinese People's Liberation Army Active Duty Rifle]
[Prison]
Wang Boyu
At the moment when Chu Tian is about to pick up the gun.
Wang Boyu took him away.
The legendary genius boy
didn't shoot a single shot.
The safe zone is refreshed again.
Only ON Team is still in the circle.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
The transfer and confrontation
of the ON Team are good.
It's mainly because they are lucky.
Every time the safe zone refreshes,
they take a head start.
It is undoubtedly
the first team in the blessed zone
in this game.
Wang Boyu
is so ruthless.
Didn't he always
like Chu Tian?
This is a competition.
Points are the most important.
Chu Tian hasn't
had a chance to play yet.
Why is he so unlucky?
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
What JR Team lacks
is not luck.
Xiao Yichuan encountered two people of the SIK.
Xiao Yichuan is at a disadvantage.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
Love and hate
is the script
of the Boyi brothers.
Wang Boyu.
It's SIK again.
Wang Boyu
eliminated Xiao Yichuan.
The JR Team was wiped out.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
Did they use the tactics of three-point search again?
None of them
ended up together in the same place once.
Xiao Yichuan picked up airdrops alone
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
and got
his best weapon.
MK14.
[The poison circle has 20 seconds to start shrinking.]
Xiao Yichuan, the standard teaching for continuous attacks.
Xiao Yichuan is indeed
the spokesperson to MK14.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
Chu Tian is a war reporter, right?
Can't he take another gun?
It makes me want to see him shoot.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
ON Team is in blessed zone again.
In this round,
ON Team won.
The points of the OP Team are following.
SIK wins this round.
The JR Team didn't cooperate.
It’s a pity
in this round.
The winner of this round is
SIK again.
Let's take a look at the scoreboard.
SIK currently
ranks first
with a high score of 78 points.
ON Team got 72 points,
and ranked second.
OP Team
ranked third
with 71 points
following
the ON team.
In these rounds,
Xiao Yichuan got 60 points for JR Team.
[Points Ranking]
If they want to
rely on this score
to get to the play-in,
I believe the pressure will be very high.
Xiao Yichuan's comeback battle
is also very difficult.
[I watched the live stream. You have to work hard.]
I watched the live stream.
You have to work hard.
Get some fresh air.
Okay.
[TLO Global League's play-in match in China]
[OK, we will try our best.]
Qin Zheng.
We know each other?
I already knew that
you came to the JR Team as a coach,
I should have come to visit you earlier.
Who are you?
Three years ago,
the National League Playoffs,
the night before the final,
Rong Mansion Banquet?
I don't know
if you
notice me
sitting in the corner?