[English subtitles are available]
Sit.
What do you want from me?
Capt. Qin.
I guess Xiao Yichuan doesn't know
you were paid to
lose the game that he first officially participated
on purpose,
right?
If you have something to say, just say it.
I want this card.
You
bring Xiao Yichuan
to ON Team.
That's not gonna happen.
This card doesn't belong to me.
I heard you were planning to get married.
Are the wedding house and bride price
all prepared?
This is the internal subscription card
of the property you visited.
Take it.
You'll get a good discount.
As a benefit for company employees,
I don't mind giving it to you in advance.
I will also offer you and Xiao Yichuan
a very good transfer term.
Of course,
the breach of contract
will also be borne by us.
It's not the matter of money.
Capt. Qin.
You can't
feed on passion.
Running a team
is a business in nature.
This is the truth
you understood a few years early.
Didn't you?
I won't take anything.
I can ask Chuan's opinion first
at most.
[Out with a BANG]
[Episode 13]
I have a medical kit here.
Chu Tian, take it.
You keep it first.
Be careful about where you are.
Behind the stone.
53 seconds to shrink the circle.
Help me set up.
I'll go find an AK.
Watch out.
There's someone in front of us.
Second floor opposite.
There's one on the second floor.
Watch out.
Capt. Qin.
You can't see very well, can you?
Second floor.
Watch out for the grenade.
I'm throwing a grenade.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I said tomorrow we…
Are recording the show.
Wang Boyu told me.
Then why don't you get well prepared?
What's there to prepare for?
I'll improvise.
Um.
I have something to do tonight.
I might not be back.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
I mean.
It's only been a few days since the game ended,
and this is already the second time of you going to the hospital.
I can't rest assured
without 24 hours of watch.
I went to the hospital as you told me to.
And I'm much better now.
Hey,
you see?
Leave it.
Xiong Jiujiu
can't take care of you
as well as I do.
What would you do
without me?
Just stay at home.
What would Xiong Jiujiu do without me?
You don't know her.
She's bad at everything
except being jealousy.
She's needy
just like you.
Drink your water.
So you're really going to
the show tomorrow?
Hmmm.
It's not appropriate to not go.
Lead the team,
and attend the show?
Xiao Yichuan.
What kind of power
has turned you who you're now?
When SIK was recording a show,
why didn't you quit?
We have different personas.
I've always been known as
friendly and easy-going.
And you?
Cool guy.
Let's see if this
can keep your mouth shut.
Well, no wonder.
You've got a girlfriend on the JR Team.
And a boyfriend too.
As your first official partner,
I feel very relieved.
How jealous.
Stop it.
They are…
Teammates.
That sounds even more jealousy, okay?
Chuan.
You've really changed.
You've become more…
like me now.
Wang Boyu.
Your sarcasm is excellent now.
You don't even swear anymore.
Tomorrow you're going to the show.
I'm going to choose our outfits,
see how we should match.
It's a pity your thick skin
is not used for level 3 armor.
Hey, Meng.
The house lottery has begun.
Since you all think the house is good,
let's do what you think.
About the down payment,
I'll keep it in mind.
Capt. Qin.
I'm busy here.
I'll talk to you later.
I'm hanging up.
Capt. Qin,
have you had breakfast?
Yes.
I came out for some fresh air.
Get in the car.
It's the auspicious time to go.
But
I think Xiao Yichuan hasn't arrived yet.
I've called.
He said he's waiting for us at the meeting place.
Get in the car. Get in the car.
Happy, joyous, pleasant.
Let's go.
Excuse me?
What brings
Miss. Chu here today?
Well,
I lack fire of the five elements today.
Miss. Chu Tian has the basic nature of fire.
Fire is also good for our team.
All right.
No need to explain.
We all understand.
I came here today mainly to see you.
How dare you not answer my calls after winning a game?
You don't see me as your sister anymore
after winning the championship, do you?
You tell me.
I believe you.
Bastard, if you behave like this again…
Well,
Chu Tian.
Your sister has asked me to ask you
if you're feeling better lately.
Don't be embarrassed.
Love should be said out loud.
Look at me.
Not only do I care about you in my eyes,
I also care about you in my heart.
Stop it.
Are kids nowadays
so flashy in love?
So you really got Miss. Chu Tian?
She is your girlfriend?
No.
Nice talk, Hong Yang.
Say something more.
I say,
I don't know what she sees in you.
Shut up.
Want some snacks?
Chips?
And other things?
How about some chocolate as sweet as you?
Oh, right.
I also have purple potatoes here.
I only belong to you.
Chuan.
Let me help you clean up.
Tian.
I've missed you for a few days.
Did you miss me?
No.
Director.
Manager Xiong.
This is our flying guest for this episode,
Shi Ya.
This interview will be conducted by her.
Hello again,
Xiong Jiujiu.
Many of our teammates are new here.
Please take care of us.
That's a must.
For the sake of Chuan and you,
I personally
favor JR Team.
Excuse me.
Shi Ya.
What did you say?
Keep some integrity.
You're being mean to SIK, right?
I'm busted.
Where are the people of the ON Team?
I thought three teams are recording the show together today.
Their team went on a trip abroad
for relaxation after the game.
They asked us to make up a separate recording.
Today only you and SIK are recording.
Oh, that's...
a pity.
This is good actually.
Their captain is so cocky
that I'm so pissed at the sight of him.
They came the second place entirely by luck
and they're even taking it abroad.
If they had won first place,
I'm afraid
the earth can't hold them.
What do I teach you guys?
Don't bully the underprivileged.
The captain is right.
Director.
It's all set.
We can get ready.
Good.
Guys.
Let's go in and get ready.
Okay. Let's go.
Qin.
These three guys on your team seem to be new.
But it's been a long time
I haven't seen
such strong motivation.
Ah.
That's right.
They all just want to play well
with no more distractions.
It's easier said
than done.
Nowadays, many newcomers
think of E-sports
as a way to make money
just by playing video games
with the purpose of making money
who can achieve nothing in the end.
A lot of capital and hot money
has made the business a mess too.
But Xiao Yichuan in your team
is truly skilled
and also truly controversial.
He always lashes out during many years in the industry.
Our Captain Wang has been suffered a lot.
I think
he only listens to you.
Chuan
has changed a lot.
How's the shooting going?
Almost done.
Almost done, right?
Then let's get ready for the interview.
Ya.
You get ready.
We'll interview the captains of the two teams first.
Okay.
I should be considered Xiao Yichuan's
life-saving benefactor and soul coach.
If I...
That's right.
He did change my life.
If it wasn't for Wang Boyu,
I would be healthy both physically and mentally
and have a bright future ahead of me.
Xiao Yichuan, you're heartless.
Why didn't you bring up
the time when I sent you to the hospital and cooked for you?
What?
You did cook for me.
You also caused me to have gastroenteritis.
I said my stomach hurt but you didn't believe me.
You had to make me do physical training.
I ended up with a fever and dehydration of over 38 degrees Celsius.
You didn't send me to the hospital.
What did you want?
I later
learned to cook well
and have made it up to you for years.
Do you have a list?
I do hold a grudge.
You stay at my house
in the name of cooking for me.
Needy.
Sleep in my bed.
Wear my pajamas.
And eat my chocolate.
Good.
Do you believe me to
release the video
of you singing love songs?
That's because I can.
Unlike you, all alone,
who can only touch your own face in the mirror at home,
being in a relationship with yourself.
So?
Chuan is not single?
You've gotten yourself into a ditch.
Next question.
There is a saying on the Internet
that the two are like
the AB sides of the life of the top E-sports player
whose career paths diverged
because of the different results of the first battle.
If ULT hadn't lost so badly
in the debut,
Xiao Yichuan, how differently do you think
would you turn out today?
This question is not so proper.
Director.
Let's re-record this part.
It's okay.
You only care about Xiao Yichuan's success
or failure.
But only I know
all Xiao Yichuan wants to become
is a qualified professional E-sports player,
whether in the past
or in the future.
Thank you, Chuan.
And thank you to Wang Boyu.
Let's ask Wang Boyu to take a short break.
Then I'd like to invite
the youngest player who made into this global league,
Chu Tian.
Welcome, Chu Tian.
Here.
Please be seated.
In fact, we can see that in this game,
there are many fans,
even professionals,
questioning your use of
domestic guns only.
You didn't fire a single shot at the start of the game
due to your use of domestic guns only.
How do you feel about it?
This is my own paranoia.
I admit
the failure.
But it doesn't mean I'll always lose.
This is what our captain
once said.
So, as a first-time rookie,
why do you want to be a professional?
What does a professional
mean to you?
It means
to go forward with my best efforts,
to do something
that is worthy of my talent
and passion.
Thank you, Chu Tian.
From his words, we can tell
his sincerity and love for E-sports.
Then we will continue to invite
other members of the JR Team
to talk about their feelings about this league tournament.
Welcome.
Miss. Chu Tian.
You're done?
Yeah.
Everything went well.
So I come over and help you with the dinner.
It recently came to me
that Chu Tian has adapted to this career.
It's just
I'm still worried he'll regret it later.
He's already 20 years old.
He has his own way to go.
And
he is more mature than all of us.
He knows what he wants.
And you
also know what you want, right?
You two
haven't come clean yet?
Since you got here,
he's looked at you more than ten times.
Who cares?
Oh, good.
If you don't, someone else does.
Can't you see
the pretty lady over there likes him?
Her eyes are overflowing with love.
If you were half as active as she is,
Xiao Yichuan would have been taken down by you long ago.
Okay.
The interview is over.
Good job, everyone.
Chuan.
Should we go watch the replay together?
There's a replay?
I'll watch it too.
Let's go.
Come on, let's have a look.
Director.
We need to watch the replay.
Okay.
Oh,
really?
Here you go.
A girl's trump card.
Go ahead.
It's all done?
Look.
Jiujiu is here.
Why is your mouth so red?
You ate a pitaya?
Where is it?
I feel like one too.
No, I didn't.
I mean.
I mean,
if you want to have one,
I can buy it for you.
You must be tired today.
Drink some water.
What did I do wrong?
Just tell me.
You're so scary this way.
You must be thirsty after such a long interview.
Capt. Qin and the others have all gone to drink water.
You are the only one who still has no water.
Drink some water,
in case you get thirsty.
I haven't had any water either.
Go find your manager.
Oh.
Didn't your team make the cut?
I believe the good times are near.
They'll be opening in a while.
Should we go and register?
This is the internal subscription card
of the property you visited.
Take it. You'll get a good discount.
You
bring Xiao Yichuan
to ON Team.
Capt. Qin.
What's going on?
Why don't you play with others?
I'm here to get some fresh air.
Capt. Qin.
Tell me.
Why do people always ask you
why you want to do this?
Maybe it's because they're afraid
that someday you will forget your answer.
Capt. Qin, you've also been asked this kind of question?
Right.
It was a long time ago.
Tian.
Capt. Qin.
I'd like to draw Chu Tian in
for SIK.
Can you avoid it?
You brat.
Chu Tian.
You really don't want to think about it?
If you come to SIK,
not only will you have better conditions and facilities,
you will also have a captain who loves you.
My captain is very good to me.
He's not good to you.
How good?
Come on.
Tell me what's good about your captain.
Good character?
Handsome?
Excellent skills?
Or gentle and virtuous?
Stop it.
This is used to describe me, okay?
Shame on you.
-Chu Tian, come... Come here. -I've got enough integrity,
unlike you.
Wang Boyu, compensate my shoes.
I'm about to catch a cold.
Does anyone care about me?
No.
Some men are really terrible.
They always act cute.
He?
He is cute?
Do you have bad eyesight?
Women are always so deceptive.
Why are you blushing then?
I'm not.
That's right.
You're not.
Xiong Jiujiu.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
I'm going to go back with the director team to edit the film.
And this show
will probably be aired in a couple of days.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you.
You helped us arrange the accommodation,
so we can rest for one night.
I'm concerned you guys
can be tired from the intense training.
Think of it
as two days of relaxation.
Hmmm.
How is Chuan
doing in your team?
He's doing well in our team.
The four of them are
not only teammates but also brothers.
JR is a team
with team spirit.
Oh, really?
That's good.
I'll be off then.
Okay.
Thank you for today.
What are you watching?
Come and help.
I'm coming.
Chuan.
I can't believe you brought a suit with you.
Why didn't you tell me at home yesterday?
I haven't asked you to compensate my shoes.
My shoes haven't dried yet.
Come on.
Blind box opening activity has begun.
One for everyone.
The gifts we prepared during the day
are all here.
Let's see who they'll go to.
A stereo?
Who prepared this gift?
Are all gifts of this standard?
I only prepared a nail clipper.
And it's…
used.
You've got a lot of luck.
This stereo
is from me.
I like it, thanks.
You can keep this nail clipper for yourself.
No need to give me.
Thank you.
A compass?
So retro.
Wow.
It suits you,
otherwise you will be too proud to orientate.
I mean,
that's disrespectful.
“Basic introduction to spatial geometry”?
The third domestic competition league souvenir?
Wow!
Here you are.
Chinese medicine foot bath voucher?
Hey, Yu. Here it is.
I wanted to give it to you.
You work so hard in design.
But it's okay.
When we get back,
I'll give you a full set of vouchers.
Mr. Dong.
Why don't you show some sincerity
and invite our whole team over?
We can also bring Chu Tian with us.
I don't think foot bath is enough.
Can I request a massage?
Let's have a hot pot in the evening.
We didn't bring Hong Yang and Dong Shi last time.
Let's do it together this time.
Hey.
I second the motion.
KTV and barbecue.
Bring them along.
Hong Yang, which side are you in?
Now we're talking about me paying the bill.
You turned against me so soon.
Aren't you the boss?
You take me as the boss now.
A heart-shaped stone?
I prepared this
rather random little gift.
I really like it.
Hmmm.
Xiong Jiujiu.
Look at yours.
Right.
[A kiss]
A…
A what?
The food is getting cold.
Everyone, eat up.
Come on.
Eat up.
Something doesn't feel right.
Who else's gift is not delivered?
What a coincidence.
Do you want to receive the gift?
I'm full.
You guys continue.
I'll leave now, bye.
Chuan…
A kiss?
Oh!
Tian.
Where are you going?
Why are you going?
Miss. Chu Tian.
Chu Tian.
Chu Tian, why are you going?
Leave me alone.
Don't you know
what the situation is now?
Who does Xiong Jiujiu really like?
Don't you know it better than me?
You obviously know everything.
But you just wouldn't admit it.
Otherwise, why don't you go confess your feelings
all these years?
What's the point of fooling yourself?
When exactly will you
be willing to face the reality?
Chu Tian.
Why are you going so fast?
I'm not walking.
Who's walking?
I'm going to my room to get something.
What do you have to get now?
Oh.
Is this it?
Why would I take this?
My breath is especially fresh.
So fresh.
Then why are you blushing?
I'm...
I'm not blushing.
I just
I just ran
and was deprived of oxygen.
You are obviously shy.
I'm not.
Or do you mean
you want to receive the gift in the room?
I don't want to.
Capt. Qin, leave it to me.
You can talk to our coach.
Have you asked Xiao Yichuan?
[Have you asked Xiao Yichuan?]
Who is it?
It's me.
Capt. Qin.
What's up?
I passed by your room
and saw your light was still on.
Sit.
I talked with Coach Liu
for a long time this afternoon.
You and Wang Boyu went all the way from the youth training camp
to leading your respective teams.
It's been so long since then.
The former rookies
are leading the younger generation now.
Wang Boyu went to SIK,
coaching Monster Team and Ocean Team.
And you've come to JR Team.
Capt. Qin,
what are you trying to say?
I just want to ask you,
if there is a chance,
do you want to go to a better team?
We're fine now, aren't we?
But we all know
the problem with JR Team.
But you said during the game
that we are not incompetent.
Capt. Qin.
You brought me into this industry.
In my heart,
you will always be my captain.
Why do you…
have such irresponsible thoughts?
Forget it.
I'll go first.
[KINDMAX PRE-CUT KINESIOLOGY TAPE]
[Wrist]
Which hand?
It's just…
Carpal Tunnel Syndrome.
It is not a difficult disease…
Which hand?
That's why you didn't train after you joined the team.
So it was because of the injury
when you were sweating that day?
Chuan,
you can't ignore this.
Capt. Qin,
I want to participate in this year's tournament.
-I don't want to give up…
-But you can't play in full force
with the injury.
No matter what the result is,
this is at least my explanation to JR Team.
It's also my account of my career.
But if you're going downhill because of the hand injury.
You'll no longer be the Xiao Yichuan
known as all-powerful.
Have you thought about
what kind of comments you will face?
-I don't care…
-That's because you're not going down for now!
You haven't experienced that feeling.
You don't know the helplessness.
Many professional players
after all the glory
choose not to resign
when faced with injury or illness.
But what happens?
They go downhill, lose the competence,
and can't win.
In the end, they're scolded as a parasite to the team by fans
and forced to retire
amidst the boos and curses.
Chuan.
I don't want you to be like this.
It's not that serious.
At least one of you, say something.
I'm not used to this.
You can't race anymore.
I'm fine.
You're fine?
How could you be like this if you were fine?
Would you tell me
you were not going to the basic training
if you were fine?
I'm stupid like a pig.
I complained about your laziness.
I was so selfish to make you
stay in the team.
I didn't even notice
your hand was injured.
Who asked you to do a self-examination?
You were so afraid that I'd run away.
What about everyone else
if I leave?
It's not that bad.
I'll try to hold on.
If you're worried,
we can train another commander.
Ah?
He has too little experience.
Chu Tian is a talented player.
His personal ability is unbeatable.
But he's still young
and inexperienced.
We have to make him gain more experience
from now.
His future
is so promising.
Capt. Qin.
You once said,
“Look at this kid.
Does he look like me back then?”
You retired in a hurry.
I stumbled to this day.
Now let's
think of it as helping ourselves back then.
Let's do as you say.
But if your hand injury worsens
and you go downhill,
I won't let you play anymore
as your coach.
Got it.
Xiong Jiujiu.
Yeah?
You are the manager.
You have to supervise this young man.
You know what you should be
most concerned about right now?
Well?
What you should be most concerned about right now
is your own hand injury.
Don't worry about other things.
If Chu Tian can share the pressure of the game
and training for you,
can I take care of everything else?
I mean,
can you not carry all the things by yourself
in the future?
Don't make me worry anymore, okay?
I know.
Don't frown.
I've been seeing my doctor regularly.
I'll be fine if I take more rest.
And
if you hide anything from me again,
don't blame me for being rude.
Okay.
It's too cold.
I gotta go.
Xiao Yichuan won't go to ON Team.
Don't waste your energy.
Where's the pitaya?
Are you serious?
This is the lipstick Miss. Chu Tian gave me.
Lipstick.
Why are you wearing lipstick for good reason?
Are you a pig?
Shi Ya is my mother's friend's daughter.
She was the commentator
for my first game which I lost.
She is very nice.
But we're just friends.
I know.
But
she likes you a lot, doesn't she?
You should ask me
who I like.
You can talk to
whoever you like.
I'd like to.
But someone
run away
during the dinner.
Around the table, do you want to…
Do you want
the gift I gave you or not?
You can't miss this opportunity.
It won't come again.
Like I care.
Wow hahaha.
What's wrong with you guys at night?
You've lost.
Bring the red envelope now.
I knew you would do this secretly.
Hey.
We didn't lose, okay?
They haven't kissed.
That's right.
You lost, Wang Boyu.
Transfer the money now.
My legs are thickened by mosquito bites.
Be a good loser, captain.
Hurry up and kiss.
It's about hundreds of RMB.
Wow!
[Bonus scenes ahead]
Hey, Chuan.
There will be a blind draw for gifts tonight.
Prepare something.
Write it down.
I don't have anything with me.
Find a way.
[A kiss]