[English subtitles are available]
How about this?
Let me be the commander.
Currently, Chu Tian pays too much
attention on confronting.
If we don't lower the risk of depleting players,
we might lose
in such a big competition.
The elimination game is fierce.
If JR Team loses,
we will be under great stress
and even get scolded.
As a newcomer,
Chu Tian shouldn't bear this.
But I'm different.
If it happens,
I'll take the responsibility.
After all,
I have experienced things like this.
Capt. Qin, you shouldn't...
What are you talking about?
Have you been scolded more times than me?
We share weal and woe together.
That's right. We're like brothers or fathers and sons in war.
No, well...
I mean we're a family.
Right.
[Out with a BANG]
[Episode 21]
Okay, Dr. Chen.
I'll be careful.
I'll go to the hospital as soon as the game is over tomorrow.
Okay.
Where did you go?
I just checked with the organizing committee on
the rules of tomorrow's competition.
What are you doing here?
I just talked to Dr. Chen on the phone.
The hospital bed has been arranged.
After the competition,
I'll go to the hospital with you.
Thank you, Manager.
You have to lead the team
and date at the same time.
Am I not wearing shoes?
What a coincidence. Me too.
All right.
It's time to eat.
Ask everyone to join us.
Brother-in-law, time to eat.
Capt. Qin, time to eat.
Capt. Qin.
Time to eat.
Eat slowly.
You...
Don't eat too much fried food. It's bad for your stomach.
Hong Yang,
don't eat too much spicy food.
What if you have diarrhea?
I shouldn't have agreed to have dinner with you.
Other players don't eat anything
before competitions to maintain their condition.
But you guys are eating too much.
Don't be so nervous.
It'll be better to stay calm.
I'm nervous.
I feel like I've fallen behind.
I'm not stressed at all now.
I won't mistake smoke bombs for grenades anymore.
People now call you China's Best Demoman.
After this championship,
people will call you the World's Best Demoman.
Tomorrow
is the first day of the elimination game.
The teams in the same group with us include KL,
GO and Lime.
They are all strong.
The strongest is with SIK Team.
They have Mars,
the defending champion.
Why don't you just feed me?
I want to eat that chicken.
Eat it yourself.
You're the captain-to-be.
You need to treat your teammates with warmth like spring.
Captain,
feed me before, right?
You are so arrogant.
If you win the game,
will you be more arrogant?
When I win the trophy, I'll bring you along and we both be arrogant.
Alright.
Eat!
Have you had enough today?
Yes.
What about you?
I'm very full.
Wait for me.
Slow down, you three.
Are you in a daze?
I'm fine.
Nervous?
No way!
The invincible first-generation sharpshooter
is nervous before a competition?
Chuan,
I...
Well,
look what you've been through.
The team was almost disbanded.
But we made it through.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Your wife is waiting for you to go back and prepare for the wedding.
Let's go.
Let's see what those people are talking about
so happily.
Wait for us!
Let's go.
Let's go back to the hotel.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
[Preparation Room 1014]
Have you arrived?
Yes.
I brought my friends here today.
Go, JR!
Go, Chu Tian!
Go! Go! Go!
The seat I've prepared for you has a good view.
You can take a good look at me later.
Oh yeah.
Your sister.
How are you, Chu Tian?
Are you nervous?
I'll cheer for you.
Okay.
I know you're the calmest.
Get ready then.
I won't disturb you.
Okay.
I'm going in.
I'll contact you
after the game.
Have your hands been warmed up?
You removed your brace.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can't let anyone see me
half-disabled.
I'll go to the hospital after the competition.
Let Coach Xiao feel
if the hand temperature is up to standard.
Don't feel pressured.
Get ready to enter.
Come on.
JR.
Go!
Go.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's welcome JR.
Tian.
Yang.
CEO.
And Ranger!
Come on.
Say hello
to the audience.
How are you?
Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Please take a seat.
Let's welcome the next team.
Xiao Yichuan is absent from this game.
Many people feel sorry for it,
but Qin Zheng, the substitute,
is also an experienced
player.
Qin Zheng once led ULT
and won twice.
In terms of experience,
he is Xiao Yichuan's master.
He came back this time on behalf of JR.
We're looking forward to his performance.
I also believe that JR
will get good results.
So I don't know if
this refreshes the audience's memory
of E-sports.
Do you think
a trivial elimination game is more important?
Or a brother
who has trusted you for so many years is more important?
The game is about to begin.
Contestants, please get ready.
Jump at the place I've marked.
JR jumps quickly
and chooses an area with less supplies.
Looks like they are planning to do it steadily.
In the beginning, they won't get points
nor lose points.
Capt. Qin is too conservative in choosing the location to jump.
Chu Tian will be in a passive position if he can't get a gun.
Does Capt. Qin think
our team is not mature enough
to fight against these international strong teams?
So...
Maybe.
Jim from the Korean GO Team got the first kill.
Three points.
Xing from ON Team
also got three points right after.
Xing is really a brave newbie.
In front of the world's top teams,
he is valiant.
As we can see,
JR didn't get many supplies.
Fortunately, there are no people around.
There's no risk of fighting.
Chu Tian,
I got the 95 Rifle.
Okay.
Tian finally got a domestic gun.
As we can see,
they meet ON now.
Capt. Qin.
There's a team on the opposite.
Go to where I've marked.
Dong Shi, you go first.
Hong Yang and Chu Tian, go and drive.
Retreat?
If we fight with them,
there may be a team behind us coming to stop the fight.
So I asked Dong Shi to go to the marked place to get some information first.
Don't shoot.
I'll cover you.
Roger!
Direction 20.
A sniper.
The opponent is ON. I'll help Dong Shi.
Hong Yang, cover me.
Okay.
You can't help him.
Our position is not good.
They're on higher ground now.
It's not safe here.
You two, go and drive.
And leave from behind.
Is JR going to
give up CEO?
But if Ranger and Tian
cover him together,
there's still hope to help him.
As we can see, CEO keeps bleeding.
JR may still want to be conservative.
They may not help him.
At this position,
Xing will definitely have a gun standoff with them.
In this way, both teams will lose members.
Yes, Yu Dan has just been helped.
His position is not good.
Fortunately, the commander of JR is cautious,
so they didn't fight.
Otherwise, we'll suffer losses.
Capt. Qin could have sniped them.
Hong Yang could have driven to coordinate.
Chu Tian could have shot to suppress the left flank.
They could have helped CEO by maneuvering.
It's okay.
It's just the first round.
GO and Lime
have also lost their members.
But it will be a loss if Dong Shi is eliminated from this round.
The transferring point was too hasty.
Actually, they could have waited
until ON and KL finished fighting.
Why did they attack from this position?
If they are discovered,
there will be no chance of winning.
Just attack.
Chuan, go from the left.
The rest go from the front after him.
I'll cover the rear.
There are many parachutes in Ice Team.
I'm afraid there's an ambush.
There's no time to wait.
The side terrain is complicated.
-Once spotted, we won't have a chance... -Just do it.
Don't waste time.
Go!
What's wrong?
Don't be greedy.
Leave this to me.
You and Hong Yang enter the zone first.
On the third floor's rooftop ahead of me.
Roger!
It's okay.
This is only the first round.
We got some points.
Okay.
A new round has begun.
I'm ready to go to the room.
Come here.
Coming.
But the shape of the zone is not favorable to JR.
Xing hit two people in a row.
ON is very aggressive.
Okay. Let’s see
the points of two Chinese teams.
[Ranking According to the Points]
ON ranks fifth.
JR ranks seventh.
Now ON ranks fourth.
JR ranks sixth.
Only the top four can be qualified for the final.
There's only one round left in the first half.
Given the points JR has gained, it's a bit dangerous.
15 points away from fourth.
I didn't expect ON to be performing so good.
I think their routes for transferring
were designed by their coach before the game.
They controlled the rhythm well under the points rule.
They're very active in getting the elimination points.
It's mainly because they are lucky.
They got ranking points
by surviving several times.
As for JR,
the absence of Chuan
may affect their tactics.
They were too conservative at the beginning.
The number of players joining the fight was not enough.
And they always acted separately.
If they still perform like this in the second half,
it may be difficult for JR
to reach the final.
JR and Blue meet each other.
Given JR's ability,
they should be able to score a few points.
Tian defeated the opponent.
Tian shot again quickly.
JR takes down the opponent first.
Okay.
ON, who is next to JR,
is coming right after hearing the gunshots.
Looks like ON is here to stop the fight.
Xing starts to shoot!
He didn't wait for the opponents to attack first.
Yu Dan, come with me to attack JR.
Block those losers of Blue.
Roger!
-OK. -OK.
The opponent is ON.
I can charge first,
defeat the two players of Blue,
and then attack ON.
Retreat.
Dong Shi, drive and leave first.
Hong Yang and Chu Tian, separate.
Give the motorcycle to Chu Tian.
It's a pity to retreat now.
The two opponents are in an unfavorable position.
And we're a full team.
If you defeat Blue now,
their unfavorable position will
become your unfavorable position.
If ON comes for us,
what should we do?
I can camp.
We should secure our ranking points.
Listen to me.
Retreat.
Capt. Qin, crawl forward.
The place ahead is a blind spot from the perspective of the second floor across.
Don't help me.
Continue.
Watch out for the second floor.
Dong Shi.
Drive the car
to cover us.
Blue and ON
are coming to attack us.
There's a SCAR behind the car.
There are two semi-auto rifles on the second floor.
There's a sniper behind the east wall.
I'll go and save Capt. Qin.
Cover me.
Roger!
Capt. Qin.
I'll give you my level 3 armor.
Hong Yang.
Take Capt. Qin to the spot I've marked.
Dong Shi and I will finish them off.
Fighting against eight opponents, the four players of JR
all survived, and they even defeated
three players of Blue.
He didn't leave Capt. Qin behind.
Good job.
-Especially after Qin Zheng was defeated... -In terms of the ranking points,
-we rank fifth. -It was so aggressive.
It's only nine points behind ON, who ranks fourth.
If we surpass ON,
we can reach the final.
It's also very straightforward.
Yes, that's right.
I think it will be one of the highlights of this competition.
I used to be your leader,
and now I'm your coach.
From now on...
I'm sorry.
I hope I won't lose you anymore,
my brother.
There's another team
at the right rear of ON.
The zone will be refreshed soon.
We can't stay here anymore.
We must move now.
Capt. Qin.
What are you doing?
Pack up.
You go first.
I'll cover you.
Capt. Qin.
Cover Capt. Qin!
Retreat!
Ranger shot the vital part.
He is as brilliant as ever.
That shot was quick and clean.
-This is how the first-generation sharpshooter will play. -Beat them!
Besiege them!
They are trying to catch up with ON's points.
Ranger covers his teammates by himself
to gain precious time for them.
Yes.
Three years later, this first-generation idol returned to the competition
to protect our young people.
My youth is coming back to me!
We can see that the safe zone refreshed again.
JR caught up in such a short time.
The points are quite close.
We're now fourth,
and we're still behind third by a lot of points.
We'll be overtaken if we're not careful.
JR started to play actively.
Xing didn't stay calm.
The score of JR is still far behind.
It will be very difficult for them to reach the final.
There is a team at the left rear of the blindage,
and another team in the housing area on the right.
We can go around from here
and enter the safe zone from the right.
There are more blindages over there.
We can hide from the sniper.
Hide?
Then we may not get enough points.
Our equipment is not good enough
for us to fight against them directly.
Do you have enough bullets and grenades?
Barely enough for this round.
Hong Yang.
How many bullets do you have?
I have 150 5.56mm bullets.
and 60 7.62mm bullets.
You two go to the safe zone from behind.
Dong Shi, you sortie
and cover Hong Yang.
Hong Yang.
Give me
all your remaining 7.62mm bullets.
I'll go get the points.
Okay.
7.62mm?
Tian of JR didn't enter the safe zone.
He ran in the opposite direction instead.
What's Tian going to do?
Where is he going?
His teammates didn't even help him.
He's going to pick up airdrops.
Airdrop is a target.
No one will pick up airdrops
in such a world-class competition.
Why did he pick up airdrops alone
at this time?
It's too risky.
-What is this young man thinking? -What is he gonna do?
He is eager to pick up airdrops at this moment.
Is he crazy?
Did he just give it a go?
He could have gone to the houses if he needed supplies.
Why did he act so recklessly?
If he picks up airdrops and gets equipment,
and then disguises himself as a target,
people around him will be attracted and be exposed.
Then he will fight them back.
No, no, no.
I think it is a
mission impossible.
Now we are watching from the perspective of
Tian of JR.
So Tian picked up airdrops
to change the gun?
Okay.
We can see that Chu Tian
got a new gun, MK14.
Yes.
Tian,
the player who only uses domestic guns...
Today,
in the game where Xiao Yichuan is absent,
he raised the gun
that only
Xiao Yichuan would use.
That's right.
This weapon is Xiao Yichuan's signature.
So the reason why Tian
tried so hard to get the MK14
is obvious.
In this game,
he will fight
with Xiao Yichuan's passion.
Tian,
with the MK14 in his hand,
replicated Xiao Yichuan's divine operation.
JR won the first place in this round.
In the first half,
JR's points surpass ON's.
Now JR is among the top four,
only seven points behind
GO, who ranks third.
My brother is so great!
My brother defeated ten of them alone!
Good job, Chu Tian!
From Ranger to Chuan and to today's Tian,
JR Team tells us that
even if the wood is burnt out,
the flame will keep burning endlessly.
This is E-sports!
This is sportsmanship!
Tian of JR
really got our adrenaline flowing
in the last round of the first half.
With the MK14,
he seemed to have brought
the passion of Xiao Yichuan,
who is absent from the game,
and turned the tide again and again
and finally won in adversity.
We rank first in this round alone.
We have surpassed ON Team,
and we can reach the final!
I know
what I'm doing.
As for what you want to do,
it doesn't matter.
JR will try their best next around.
Good luck.
The luggage you left at the base
has been packed up.
How to perform next
is up to you.
The second half is about to begin.
Please get ready.
Go, JR!
The second half starts.
Hong Yang, search for supplies.
Dong Shi and Chu Tian, clear the factory with me.
Jim of GO
was eliminated by Xing at the very beginning.
Xing was the first one to defeat others.
GO Team lost their main player.
I wonder if Jim underestimated his opponents.
As we can see on the screen,
he looks very surprised and frustrated.
After all, in the first zone, one defeat equals three points.
Everyone will try their best to get the points.
So they can't take it lightly.
Tian and Ranger of JR cooperated perfectly
and defeat one player of Dark.
Seems that JR and ON are trying their best.
Their points are very close.
I can't guess
which team
will be qualified for the final.
Xing scored again!
Even veterans have to
surrender themselves in front of
E-sports new stars.
Xing's performance in the second half
is so amazing.
His shooting is fast and accurate.
The opponents had no time to react.
As we can see,
JR is catching up.
They are in a good form today.
In this battle,
JR defeated three opponents.
Okay.
Xing scored one point after another.
This is the last round.
JR's points
will soon be catched up with ON's.
Today, these two Chinese teams
made this competition very enjoyable.
ON's Xing Ziyi
is too crazy.
He caught up
all by himself.
We've done so well.
But why are the scores still so close?
In terms of points, GO, MW and Lime
have been among the top three.
They will definitely reach the final.
We rank fourth now.
But we only have
two more points than ON.
Now it's the fourth zone.
Only Chu Tian and Xing Ziyi are left in the two teams.
Who defeats more players
and who stays alive longer
will decide the final result.
Okay. We can see that Tian of JR
and Xing of ON meet each other again.
Tian was defeated.
Actually, he has already located Xing.
It was so close!
Xing's last shot was so accurate.
It hit Chu Tian's head.
In the second half,
Xing has been in good form.
It seems that
JR has to end its championship journey here.
Given the current points that ON has got,
ON will definitely enter the final.
Okay, the game is over.
Let's take a look at the scoreboard.
Congratulations to GO, MW,
Lime, and ON.
With the outstanding performance in the second half,
ON got the last ticket
to the final.
Congratulations to ON
for being the first Chinese team
to reach the final.
I'm looking forward to their performance.
Hong yang, it's okay. Don't be sad.
About the final of
the National League Playoffs three years ago,
the one in which I led ULT,
Capt. Qin.
I have something
to say here.
I lost that game
on purpose.
I cheated.
Otherwise, ULT Team
would have won the championship.
I made an unforgivable mistake.
My request is simple.
Don't block Ice's way to win.
As for how to perform,
discuss with Coach Huang.
When the third safe zone is refreshed,
ambush at the southern part of the circle.
I'll bring ULT over
and give you points.
Besides that,
you need to get less points in the beginning.
You have to lose.
Got it.
It's easy to lose.
We've paid the medical expenses and hospitalization fees.
On the day of the final, after Ice win the championship,
the rest of the money for the surgery
will be given to you.
Mom.
I'll pay for the surgery today.
Don't worry.
It's time to play.
Let's go.
Just attack.
Chuan, go from the left.
The rest go from the front after me.
The defending champion, ULT Team
was annihilated unexpectedly.
It's the biggest unexpected defeat today!
I used my teammate,
Xiao Yichuan.
I used the trust of everyone in ULT.
E-sports
is sacred and pure.
It shouldn't be sullied
by anyone or anything.
I've been running away for three years.
Now I decide
to face my mistakes.
Here,
to my ULT Team,
to my old teammates,
to Xiao Yichuan,
I apologize.
Today,
I almost made the same mistake.
Fortunately, I didn't.
From now on,
I will leave JR Team
and quit the E-sports industry.