[English subtitles are available]
I know Xiong Jiujiu likes you.
And I admit
I like her.
I've been in love with her
for many years.
When I was young,
I followed my sister everywhere
so that I could see her more.
I didn't understand
what kind of feeling it was.
But I only know that
Xiong Jiujiu is the only person
that I want to
get close to.
Afterwards,
we grew up
and left home for study.
I couldn't see her.
Every time she sent me a voice message,
I could listen to it many times.
Every time I made a phone call with her,
I felt like celebrating the New Year.
Every time before the holiday,
I started to feel happy
a month earlier.
Anyway, everything about her
can be carved in my mind easily.
Every food she likes,
her habits,
every Weibo tweet
and Wechat Moment she posted,
I can remember all of them.
Because of her,
I want to become
a better person.
I've never absent in her life.
Even if I could only stand by her side
and look at her quietly,
I feel satisfied.
You've been holding it in for so many years.
Don't you feel bad?
I'm used to it.
Then
what do you think?
I know her well.
Even though I tried my best to stay by her side,
she still treats me as a friend,
as her family,
and a younger brother.
So I never wanted to give her pressure
until
you appeared.
One day,
Xiong Jiujiu told me
she met a boy.
Although they've never met,
she understood his dream.
She was looking forward
to meeting you.
I was a freshman in college at that time.
I knew
I might never have a chance.
But then you didn't meet each other.
I wondered
whether it was another chance
given by the god.
But Xiong Jiujiu
never opened her heart again.
My plan was that
after graduation,
I would come back
and keep her company.
I'm not going anywhere.
I thought one day,
she would see me standing behind her.
I just didn't expect that
I waited for her for three years,
and she waited for you for three years.
Did you join this team
because of Xiong Jiujiu?
Aren't you here for her?
Yes.
I did it for her.
I hope
in the long-term partnership list of the company next year,
I can see these names.
If you do well,
you'll be the general manager of the business department.
I won't let you down,
Mr. Huo.
Go.
As soon as possible.
Okay.
These clients
have been working with JR for many years.
Are you confident to get them?
They just haven't met
new partners who can bring
more profits.
Businessmen
are profit-seeking.
Is this also your way to poach Xiao Yichuan?
Xiao Yichuan is not the only man I want.
It's great to get him here.
But if we can bring more strong clients
to the company,
do you know
how many times of ON's market value
will increase?
[Out with a BANG]
[Episode 15]
Uncle Hong.
Why did you slash the E-sports department?
Several major clients of our company terminated the cooperation with us.
They won't renew the contract next year.
These big frames
are one of the main source of cash flow every year.
Without them,
the operation of the company next year
will be greatly affected.
But that's the problem of other departments in the company.
Why did you slash our E-sports department?
Didn't you tell my dad at the last meeting
that since we're qualified for the play-in match,
we have great potential?
You're right.
This is not the responsibility of the E-sports department.
But the company is short of funds.
In order to ensure
the steady operation of the company
from the latter half of this year to next year,
we must reduce the cost
and focus on the stable business of the company.
So you turned the focus away from the E-sports department?
The E-sports department
is not the only one who faces cost reduction.
The company won't calculate
the cost that the E-sports department has spent.
As for the budget that hasn't been used yet,
the company will withdraw,
including the deposit for the competition.
Besides,
your base, as the company's asset,
will be taken back
and be used for other purpose.
If the company is under financial pressure,
the base might be sold.
You have three days
to move out.
Mr. Hong,
this is too sudden.
How can we train if we move out?
There is only one month before the competition.
We...
I'll go find my dad.
Dong.
The chairman is also very sad now.
You should grow up.
Well,
could you please give me some time?
We can't quit.
Keep the disbandment of the E-sports department a secret.
Give me some time.
Don't be sad.
The company is under financial pressure.
We should understand that.
Dong Shi and I
will continue to follow up.
I'll make everyone come back as soon as possible.
Just see it as a break.
Yes.
Capt. Qin is right.
Everyone has been working hard lately.
You can use this period of time
to have a rest.
Consider it
as a short break before the competition.
The day after tomorrow,
the company will come to check the base.
Let's have a rest
and pack up.
The manager asked you to rest,
but the captain didn't agree.
He just asked you to go somewhere else.
Why do you look like it's the end of the world?
Capt. Qin and I
used to train in internet cafes.
You are like those young masters who have never lived a hard life.
Hong Yang.
Don't slack off when you get back to the dorm.
Even if you have to do your homework,
don't give me back
the poor skills you have learned.
Don't worry, Chuan.
And you.
Kid,
I'll check your training results.
Anytime you want.
It doesn't matter where we train.
We can also make an online training.
Besides,
Capt. Qin
can also watch our live stream and screen recording
to review it for us.
Okay.
It's a deal.
During this period,
Chu Tian is mainly responsible for commanding solo and foursome.
Hong Yang should improve the speed and shooting rate.
Today,
the E-sports JR Team is officially formed.
Our base
is facing south.
It's square and full of Yang energy.
To my best teammates.
Every one of us
is like each other's family.
Cheers.
Good luck, my family.
Leave me alone for a while.
Hey.
Don't forget
how you promised me and Miss Chu Tian.
Chuan.
Are you leaving?
Why didn't you stay with your mom?
Someone is still waiting to be fed at home.
Chuan.
Wait.
I have something to tell you.
Remember the show you attended last time?
The response was very possitive.
A few bosses
wanted me to introduce
them to you.
Why?
I'm not interested in socializing.
Because they want to sign you!
I have a team.
Your current level
doesn't match the team at all.
Did you stay in that stupid team
because of Xiong Jiujiu?
Can you be more mature?
This is my own business.
Delete Wang Boyu
in case he keeps harassing you.
It's okay.
I just take him as a practice.
But
as the commander of SIK,
he's calm
and has a quick response.
The rhythm is under his control.
In face of an emergency,
he can solve it quickly.
What?
You changed side in the war so quickly?
I'm just telling how I feel.
There are many excellent seniors.
Learn from them.
In the future,
surpass them all.
Don't worry.
You are no exception.
Come on.
Try the soup my mom cooked.
It's been cooked for hours.
I even brought the pot here.
Thank you.
Drink slowly.
After leaving the base,
you can't even take care of yourself?
It's not like you.
When do you think
we can go back?
It doesn't matter.
If the earth doesn't explode,
the training will not stop.
If the universe doesn't restart,
don't think about resting.
I'm not talking about training.
I'm worried about the team.
Are you worried about Xiong Jiujiu?
I know what you're thinking.
I will face myself
and give myself an explanation.
I hope you will too.
Okay.
Eat slowly.
Did your sister abuse you?
Didn't she feed you?
Eating the food cooked by my sister
is being abused.
How about
we order takeouts?
No need.
It's good.
Alright.
Stop eating.
The food is not eatable.
I'll order takeouts.
Don't act tough.
I once promised you
I would give Chu Tian
a reliable and stable job
and take him to the world's top competition.
I might break my promise.
I told Chu Tian that
when he graduated,
I'd be an independent designer
who earned millions a month,
and his daily work
would be to count money for me.
So I broke my promise too?
Why do you want to
be an independent designer and open an online store?
I used to work for
a fashion magazine.
The salary and prospects were all good.
But it was not enough for me.
I've learned fashion design for so many years.
I fell out with my parents
because I wanted to resign and run an online store.
At that time,
I stayed up late
at night
to create designs.
In the morning,
I went to the factory to carry fabrics.
It was tiring.
I thought about giving up.
And then?
Then I've been persistent till now.
Look at me now.
I'm not a famous designer,
but I do
what I love every day.
So I'm happy every day.
But sometimes, passion and love alone
cannot support the dream.
Passion may not support your dream,
but sticking to your passion can.
If you feel like you can't persist,
just grit your teeth.
Your teeth haven't been broken yet.
Don't ever mention quit.
Okay.
I'll grit my teeth.
[Office of the Chairman]
As for the company's decision,
I understand
and also respect it.
The E-sports department didn't grow rapidly.
The profitability
is much weaker
than that of other departments.
It's been holding the company back.
As an employee
and your son,
I couldn't do more for the company.
I'm sorry, dad.
But I just want to make one last request.
Can you keep the relevant qualifications of JR Team?
It may just be an empty name for you,
but for us,
this is a chance we finally got.
Is it meaningful?
As for the 5 million deposit for your participation,
-with your ability... -It's meaningful.
As long as the seat is still there,
everything is meaningful.
Going with empty hands?
Is that okay?
Sure.
The company will no longer provide any support.
It's okay.
We'll figure out a way.
We can seek investment
or find sponsors.
We'll handle it.
As long as JR is still there
and our team is still there.
From your words,
I can see that you've grown up.
I promise you.
I'll keep the relevant qualifications
of the E-sports team.
If
you can make your own living
whether by sponsorship
or investment,
the company won't take it.
It's
all yours.
Thank you, Dad.
Previously,
I have been criticizing you
because I thought
you just liked playing games.
Back then,
I gave you some money to do E-sports
to see
if you just did it halfheartedly.
Today, I know
you're not fooling around.
I really hope
to help you fulfill your dream.
But you have to
make the dream come true by yourself.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
Okay.
Mr. Li.
I'm Dong.
Mr. Wang.
I wonder if
you know anything about E-sports?
That's great.
When do you have time?
I will go find you.
What's going on with the department?
Xiong Jiujiu.
How about
I transfer you to the basketball team
for internship?
Back then,
I forced you to join the E-sports department.
If you want to quit,
I can transfer your internship certificate.
No.
I just want to stay in the E-sports department.
Is the circumstance
very bad?
Yes.
My dad told me
the qualifications of our team
can be kept.
But
the competition deposit
can't be raised in a short time.
We should pay the deposit
15 working days before the competition.
Now,
we only have less than two weeks.
Time is running out.
I need to find a way.
You're just an intern.
I can't risk
your future.
Let's do it together.
Let's attract investment for the team
and get the deposit.
I'm the manager of JR Team.
I can't give up my team
at this moment.
It's what I should face.
It's what we should face.
Alright.
After I handle the matters
in the school,
I'll go back to you.
Wait for me.
Xiong Jiujiu.
Mrs. Zhang.
I haven't seen you in the school recently.
How was your internship?
Did it go well?
Not bad.
I have something to tell you.
NESG came to our school to recruit.
We recommended a few students.
Your resume was approved.
They will come for the interview tomorrow.
Go back and update your resume.
Every year,
only three or five students
can get the chance for the interview.
You must seize the chance.
But Mrs. Zhang,
I'm an intern at JR Sports Ltd.
I don't want to go to another company for the time being.
You don't want to go to NESG either?
NESG is one of the organizers of
the Global League Tournament this year.
An interview opportunity from such an international company
is so rare
for the fresh graduates.
Well,
how about this?
Tomorrow
I will still go for the interview.
I'll explain to the HR.
You're the manager of JR Team, right?
I have seen you
on the show E-sports Canteen.
Yes.
I'm the intern manager
of JR Team.
Also a manager.
Are you satisfied with your current job?
Do you have a long-term career plan?
I like
the current job very much.
At the same time,
I'm very satisfied with myself
because I've grown up for this job.
So,
I want to take it
as my future career and work hard.
I can see
you really like your current job.
As for this year's Global League Tournament,
NESG is one of the organizers.
What do you think about our company?
Actually, I'm here
to express my gratitude to your company.
I don't want to leave JR Team for now.
I want to stay with my team
forever.
It seems that she values loyalty and love.
This is the information of the job for which you interviewed today.
Take it back and have a look.
We really like you.
I hope you not to make hasty decisions now.
Think about it carefully.
We'll contact you again.
Thank you.
[Introduction to NESG]
So great.
Is the team not going well?
Not bad.
Tomorrow,
Dong Shi and I
will meet the sponsors.
But your sad face
doesn't show "not bad".
Are you crying?
You can cry on my shoulder.
I was just thinking
how I joined this team
accidentally
and dragged you all in.
I wonder if you will regret it.
What about you?
If I give you another chance to choose,
would you still join the team?
I think I will.
So, look.
What is supposed to happen will happen.
No need to struggle with it.
Just...
Like you.
Just like me.
Back then,
I joined the E-sports team
because of you.
It's like when I was young.
Wherever you went,
I would always follow you.
Do you remember once
we skipped night study to set off fireworks?
In the end,
the fireworks burnt my leg.
You felt so guilty
that you insisted on riding a bike to send me to school every day.
You didn't stop despite the weather.
You insisted for half a year.
Actually, my injury had already recovered.
I lied to you for months.
I cherish the days so much.
I still can't forget
the days I spent with you.
At that time,
you only worried about my leg
burned by the fireworks.
But I only remember
the fireworks we watched together.
They were very beautiful.
Xiong Jiujiu.
Yes?
I like you.
But this like
ends here.
I might be used to it these years.
Wherever you go,
I wanted to follow you.
I wished to
be with you forever.
I wished to follow you,
stay by your side,
and protect you.
But I realized
you were strong enough
to protect yourself.
You've known clearly
where your happiness
is.
So I can,
with relief,
say goodbye
to my feelings.
I didn't expect
that my brother
has grown up.
You have your own thoughts.
But I never realized it.
Now I realize
I was the one who didn't grow up.
I took your care for me
for granted.
I didn't notice your thoughts.
I ignored your feelings.
I'm sorry.
I've always treated you as my family.
I never thought
there would be other feelings between us.
You will find your
own love.
You will find the girl
who treats you as the only one.
Alright.
The fireworks are over.
You let slip me.
It's a lifelong regret.
So don't let slip Xiao Yichuan.
Actually,
if you lower your standards,
he is quite good.
I promised Miss Chu Tian
to go back early.
I'm leaving.
Did you sleep here
last night?
It was too late when I finished the proposal last night.
Have you read what I sent you?
Print it out later.
We need it for signing with clients in the morning.
I've read it.
I have added some content.
I've printed it out.
You,
go and wash up.
Leave the rest to me.
I'll tidy up.
Xiong Jiujiu.
You are the best manager
I've ever worked with.
Come on.
I'm the only manager you've worked with, right?
We'll get enough money for the deposit.
Yes.
Go wash up.
Manager,
I'll wait for you after work downstairs at night.
I'll do my best.
See you tonight.
Is this the birthday gift
you prepared for Xiong Jiujiu?
Are you sure it's because she can't keep it in her dorm,
not because
she doesn't want it?
She loves it so much.
When she asked me to keep it for her,
she was so reluctant.
I admire your confidence.
Hey.
What are you looking for?
I know the location of things better than you do.
I found it.
Business cards?
How long have them been kept?
What are you doing?
I want to introduce investors to our team.
These brands came to me before.
Xiao Yichuan,
I don't care if you buy shoes.
But now you want to sell your charms for commercial shooting?
Why didn't you discuss with me?
I'm telling you now.
You go to Chu Tian's live stream every day
and tip him a rocket.
What do you think?
You're showing partiality to Chu Tian!
You want me to lose both men and money, right?
But what’s going on
with your team?
Why do you have to attract investment by yourselves?
JR Sports has some financial problems.
We have to pay the daily expenses
and the five-million competition deposit
on our own.
I asked Xiong Jiujiu
to get me some commercial activities
and sponsorship.
It may be faster.
For a team,
you even broke your bottom line.
Xiao Yichuan,
what should I say about you?
You've been stumbling all the way.
Will you be able to compete or not?
In my opinion,
you might as well give up
and recuperate.
Nonsense.
No one else in the team gave up.
The 21 keyboard Chu Tian asked you to give...
Was it in vain?
It was an accident.
But Chu Tian is a very nice person.
If
one day,
your team
suddenly
disbands,
the gate of our SIK
will always open to him.
Piss off!
Hey.
When will Tian come here?
I'll train with him.
You have a rest.
He's not coming today.
Don't think about bothering him.
I have something to do today.
Where are you going?
I'm going
for a date.
No way.
So Wang Boyu
will be alone today?
How many companies did you visit today?
Did it go well?
Not bad.
At least one
is interested in us
and willing to consider it.
Oh, right.
How is your hand?
If you don't train recently,
take a good rest.
I've been too busy
with the matters of the team.
I don't have time to take care of you.
Did you see a doctor?
What did the doctor say?
I did.
The numbness is gradually disappearing.
The inflammation is gone.
The doctor said
as long as I don't exercise hard,
the medicine I take can be reduced.
Great.
This is the best news
I've heard recently.
Open that.
This one?
What is this?
Some brand owners.
Try to contact them.
See if you can get enough money for the deposit.
Mr. Du on the top
contacted me a few days ago.
You can ask him first.
The farther down, the longer since the last they contacted me.
Just follow the order.
Great.
So many.
Ah!
It's finally your turn
to save the team with your charms.
Are you that happy to sell my charms?
Of course.
What do you want to eat?
I miss the food in the canteen.
Let's go.
Okay.
The library is ahead.
That's the main teaching building.
That is the report hall.
The canteen is next to it.
You've been here before
more than once, right?
Stop being narcissistic.
I just wanted to feel
the campus atmosphere.
Oh.
When I was in college,
I've never been in a relationship.
There was one online, but I was cheated.
Again?
Let's go to the canteen.
Do you want to eat in the canteen
or I want to?
There's no difference between you and I.
Before you sell me,
I have to satisfy my belly.
I'll call Dong Shi first.
Am I not delicious enough?
You haven't looked at me
since you sat down.
Don't look at your phone.
Look at me.
I'm more delicious to go with meals.
You don't have to work right now.
Okay.
I think someone recognizes you.
The Xiong Jiujiu Couple
took a sweet campus trip.
This is the first time I found
forming a couple
really interesting.
Just eat.
Okay.
I have arrived.
Well,
I'm going up?
Okay.
Which dorm do you live in?
The second room on the third floor.
That one.
It's dark.
No one is there.
I'm a senior now.
My roommates are out for internship.
No one lives in the dorm now.
Okay.
Well,
I'll go back then.
You too.
It's late.
Let me see you go upstairs.
Give it to me.
Okay.
I'm really leaving.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Good night.
Bye.
Did I forget to buy electricity?
[Women's Dormitory of Ruiyang Sports University]
[Electricity Purchasing Hours: 9:00-18:00]
Ah.
Xiong Jiujiu.
Why are you still here?
Why don't we order takeouts?
Leave me alone.
Go out. It'll be ready soon.
[First Prize 100000 RMB]
[Sign up for Red Ant Late Spring Talent Contest]
100,000?