Your Excellency.
What does Qidan King think
of our proposal?
Our King says
if Youzhou's 100,000 troops
and Qidan's
50,000 warriors
could strictly
follow your lead,
they'd sweep through defenses
and storm straight into Shendu.
Your King is truly wise.
So, please advise him
to start preparing.
However,
our King heard
that you had
obtained Jinlouzi's treasure.
Who told you that?
Last month,
rumors spread from Shendu.
I wonder
if it was true.
Jinlouzi's treasure?
There is no such thing.
My lord,
since you seek cooperation with Qidan,
please show us some sincerity.
We don't covet any treasure,
but sustaining an army costs dearly.
If you possess such wealth,
our march against Tang
would gain greater certainty.
Moreover,
it would help speed up
your ascension to the throne.
That was a rumor.
Without treasure,
you may not
be able to
obtain our elders' approval.
What does
your King want?
You're Qidan-born, too.
You know our kind
outnumber the Han people
in Youzhou.
If you would
cede Youzhou to Qidan,
then our King
will march south beside you
with full force
to crush Shendu.
If I surrender Youzhou
to Qidan,
that'd leave Shendu
defenseless against invasion
like meat before wolves.
My lord,
think about it carefully.
Li Ya'er was killed.
It might be too late
to play loyalist now.
Should our King
accept Tang's terms,
Youzhou will face
attacks from both
front and rear.
Is this a threat?
Not at all.
Think carefully.
I shall
take my leave now.
My lord.
Bad news.
Li Ya'er raided our camp
with the Shadow Guards.
They killed our commander
and burned our provisions.
You...
You set us up.
Who did he say
raided the Qidan camp?
=Treacherous Cases in Shendu=
=Episode 17=
Xuanzhi.
Are you still mad at me?
Do you have more medicine?
You don't need it.
Give it all to me.
I've suffered so much
this past month.
I was losing it.
Soon my tears will flow
more than your medicine.
Panpan.
Will you try to
get through to him?
I dare not.
He's in rage.
You caused the trouble.
Fix it yourself.
Lord Wuwei has arrived.
Lord Wuwei.
Princess Changle, Wu Lingling.
You do bear some resemblance
to your father.
I pay my respects.
We'll soon be family.
No need for formalities.
Do you truly intend to marry me?
Why else would I have you travel
all this way?
After dinner,
come to my chamber.
Among all my sons,
I thought you alone understood me.
But you killed the Qidan commander
and burned their provisions.
You left Youzhou with no way out.
Father.
Stop being obsessed.
What's the point
even if we obtain Jinlouzi's treasure?
After what I've been through in Shendu,
I've obtained the ultimate truth.
Whoever wins over the people
claims the throne.
Whenever you wage a war
for whatever reason,
the suffering
always falls upon the people.
Has that girl bewitched you?
Are you
betraying me for her?
It has nothing to do with Ling.
I'm only telling you the truth, Father.
You're not my son.
My son Li Ya'er
was meant to conquer the world for me.
Father,
do you mourn
the loss of a son,
or weep for losing
your unstoppable
bloody blade?
I'll kill her right now.
Why can't you see, Father?
She has nothing to do with it.
What?
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
I've risked my life repeatedly
to complete missions.
You never asked
if I was in pain
or severely hurt.
Even when I faked my death,
your only concern
was whether I ruined your great plan.
Tell me.
What kind of father
treats his son like this?
Only Ling showed me care.
She was my salvation.
I've sealed your major acupoints.
If you truly love this Ling of yours,
break through the seals and save her
before I reach her chamber.
♪Grinding new ink in this crimson tower♪
♪Each brushstroke
births shades profound♪
Governor.
♪Our story dissolves in ink♪
♪Fate separates us way♪
♪Lovers finally come together♪
♪Yet couldn't withstand hardships♪
♪The waning moon sinks,
the lamps lit up♪
♪No visitors knock at the gates♪
♪Pristine moonlight
first clings to sleeves♪
♪Pear blossoms bear love's weight♪
♪Monastic vows
intensify earthly desires♪
♪Red beans gathered♪
♪Buddha speaks of
countless paths to truth♪
♪Yet eternal gazes can't ferry one soul♪
♪Trapped between your brows,
devotion runs deep♪
♪Dim lamps leave monastic vows unlit♪
♪Memories of the past cling fast♪
♪You inhabit my dreams♪
♪We drift through bitter seas♪
♪I can't forget
the starlight in your eyes♪
♪Though fate's roots grew firm and tall♪
♪Yet mortal affairs engulf us all♪
♪Lovesick in endless plight♪
♪Dim lamps leave monastic vows unlit♪
♪Memories of the past cling fast♪
♪You inhabit my dreams♪
♪We drift through bitter seas♪
♪I can't forget
the starlight in your eyes♪
♪Though fate's roots grew firm and tall♪
♪Yet mortal affairs engulf us all♪
♪Lovesick in endless plight♪
♪Stormy tides engulf the realm,
yet compassion remains♪
♪A debt of blood, a soul in torment♪
♪Beyond Chang'an's walls♪
♪Unease fills the people's hearts♪
♪Darkness looms with impending doom♪
♪A lone hero casts life and death aside♪
♪Sacrificing himself
to right the world's debt♪
♪A long-sealed heart begins to thaw♪
♪Only to lose this forbidden love♪
♪Through any crowd,
I'd find my way to you♪
♪Through every trial and fear,
I'll see you through♪
♪Till dust at last,
within your heart finds rest♪
♪Never to part, whatever betide♪
♪Through any crowd,
I'd find my way to you♪
♪Our love transcends the worldly storm♪
♪Yearning burns as snow melts,
mists clear away♪
♪My heart departs with you today♪