A covert organization of 12 agents
established by the late Empress
monitored officials
while amassing wealth,
which was later managed by
the Jinlouzi agents after her passing.
(Palace Sedan Painting)
Turn in the Jinlouzi agents.
I'll make it painless.
Where's the painting?
(Jinlouzi?)
Ling.
What is this?
I took this painting
from Li Ya'er.
The man in black
was also after this painting.
What is Jinlouzi?
I've heard about it.
I'll look into it.
Right,
why are you keeping
that stranger around?
He might help me
find my sister's murderer.
With him
and this painting by my side,
the killer will surely show up.
You're using him as bait?
No.
I'm using him as a blade
to eliminate all my enemies.
=Treacherous Cases in Shendu=
=Episode 2=
Xuanzhi.
Where have you been?
I've missed you so much.
Xuanzhi.
Stop training
your chest muscles.
They're so bulky now.
Panpan.
What are you doing?
Xuanzhi?
So, you...
(Zhao Panpan)
Who are you?
Why are you in my cousin's clothes?
I'm sorry.
He took advantage of me.
Panpan.
How could you
mistake him for me?
I'm way more handsome.
Ling.
Don't be lured by his looks.
You can't keep him around.
Since you're working for me,
from now on,
you'll obey my rules.
First,
address me as "my lady" in public.
Second,
since you had nowhere to go
and I took you in,
you should protect me
and my family.
Third,
always obey my orders.
You will do
whatever I say.
Otherwise,
I'll kick you out.
Understood?
Understood.
My lady.
Why...
Why are you here?
What did you dream about?
I...
dreamed...
Just answer
my question.
I dreamed
that I killed many people.
Who did you kill?
My lady.
I'm scared.
About what?
That I'm an evil person.
That I might harm you.
Stop overthinking.
Right now,
you're Wu Ya'er.
Take your medicine.
It's over there.
I feared the dark
when I was little.
My sister stayed with me at night.
Later,
she gave me a puppy.
It may be small.
But the moment we took it home,
it became our family.
It will grow with you
and protect you forever.
So adorable.
What's its name?
Ling, give it a name.
Got it.
Let's call it Naughty.
Naughty.
Behave yourself.
No biting.
No potty here.
Do you understand?
Ling.
It's a dog.
It doesn't understand you.
Woof.
Woof, woof.
Sadly, we fled Chang'an
without it.
I lost it.
My lady.
Don't be sad.
If you fear darkness,
I'll guard you every night
from now on.
If you miss Naughty,
just look at me.
♪Darkness looms with impending doom♪
Your eyes kind of
remind me of that puppy.
Woof.
Woof, woof.
Who's there?
Palace Sedan Painting.
Watch out.
Are you okay?
My lady.
What's wrong?
Who are you really?
I don't know.
I told you
not to lie to me.
I'm not lying.
Turn around.
You bear the Qidan tattoo.
You're from Qidan.
What...
What tattoo?
I have no idea.
Only Qidan people have this tattoo.
Li Ya'er is from Qidan, too.
You came from Youzhou.
Li Ya'er.
You saved my life
and gave me hope,
yet named me after your enemy.
Why?
My life is yours to take.
If you think I'm your enemy,
just kill me.
Don't move.
Someone's outside.
He died?
What happened?
We caught him trying to steal
my sister's remains.
Xuanzhi.
What happened?
Who is this man?
He looks
quite familiar.
You know him?
Isn't he the Judicial Minister
from Qingqing's wedding?
I've seen him.
This fragrance.
He died a while ago,
but there's no stench.
His blood even carries
a subtle fragrance.
This fragrance
persisted against
natural decay.
It's...
- Poison.
Ling.
My lady.
Found anything?
Judicial Minister's remains
carry a rare poison.
Poison?
This unique toxin
is from the Western Regions.
It's been
in his system for a while
and broke out yesterday.
This must be
a premeditated act.
So he was stealing my sister's remains
to hide something bigger.
My lady,
stop drinking.
You're drunk.
I can't sleep
without drinking.
The moment I close my eyes,
I hear my sister's agonized screams.
May I call you Ling from now on?
You...
Say that again.
May I...
call you...
Ling?
Have it.
This will help with
the hangover.
You helped me to bed?
You remember?
Nothing on Qingqing's remains.
But we found a major clue.
What are you doing?
Having tea.
It's early morning. Why did you come?
The Judicial Minister turns out
to be a Jinlouzi,
code name Di Long.
These were seized from his residence.
They don't look like
ordinary treasures.
And they bear
engraved inscriptions.
Recognize them?
Burial objects.
You recognize them?
So he
tried to steal the remains
for some other reasons,
not money.
Xuanzhi.
What's this?
This is the poison
that killed him.
Immortal's Ecstasy.
It's from a wine house
called Zuixian Tower
owned by the Hu people.
(Zuixian Tower.)
♪Stormy tides engulf the realm,
yet compassion remains♪
♪A debt of blood, a soul in torment♪
♪Beyond Chang'an's walls♪
♪Unease fills the people's hearts♪
♪Darkness looms with impending doom♪
♪A lone hero casts life and death aside♪
♪Sacrificing himself
to right the world's debt♪
♪A long-sealed heart begins to thaw♪
♪Only to lose this forbidden love♪
♪Through any crowd,
I'd find my way to you♪
♪Through every trial and fear,
I'll see you through♪
♪Till dust at last,
within your heart finds rest♪
♪Never to part, whatever betide♪
♪Through any crowd,
I'd find my way to you♪
♪Our love transcends the worldly storm♪
♪Yearning burns as snow melts,
mists clear away♪
♪My heart departs with you today♪