♪Before I met you♪
♪I didn't care
who my life was related to♪
♪And the capricious borrowing from time♪
♪I never thought about repaying it♪
♪Before being in love,
it didn't matter who it was♪
♪You are more precious than freedom♪
♪If not for your smile♪
♪That had changed the whole world♪
♪How would I realize it belatedly
yet willingly♪
♪The furrowing and relaxing
of your brows♪
♪The depths of your dimples♪
♪Before I met you♪
♪How would I have understood those♪
♪I was a blank slate♪
=The Heir's Forbidden Love=
=Episode 17=
It seems that
it's two against one tonight.
I never get drunk.
People call me the Wine God of Bincheng.
An'an.
As long as I have fun tonight,
I'll naturally sign the contract.
Okay.
I'll drink with you.
Let's get wasted.
Don't go.
Why are you so close to me?
I've never seen you drunk before.
How many more sides of you are there?
What did you say?
Go.
Pour me a drink.
One more drink.
Actually, with me here,
you don't need to try so hard.
What's wrong, Mr. Meng?
I drank too much
and forgot everything.
Were you drunk?
No.
Huo Siting didn't
do anything to you, right?
Don't talk nonsense.
Thank goodness
you're okay.
Isn't it Mr. Meng who never gets drunk?
Good morning.
You pulled some tricks last night, huh?
Drink less
if you can't hold your liquor.
Why are you blaming it on me?
Who can't hold his liquor?
That's enough.
Stop arguing.
Mr. Meng, have you had breakfast?
Not yet.
Since Mr. Huo is here,
why don't you prepare breakfast for us?
I'm not hungry.
Even if you're not,
An'an must be hungry.
Hurry up.
An'an.
Actually,
I'm not so interested
in the resort project.
As you know,
I'm the only heir to the Meng family.
If you want,
I can transfer all my shares
to you.
That's huge.
Stop joking with me.
I'm not joking.
Of course,
I have a request.
I'm listening.
Can you
date me for a day?
Just the two of us.
Don't get me wrong.
I know
I'm crossing the line here.
But it's not what you think.
If...
Okay.
No problem.
I understand.
I won't get it wrong.
Really?
What about Mr. Huo?
I'll send him to do research tomorrow.
Rest assured.
He won't disturb us.
That's great.
I'll prepare for it.
Okay.
Mr. Huo.
Why aren't you
preparing breakfast?
Do you want a fist-sized bun?
No need.
I'm not hungry anymore.
Forget it.
Keep the fist-sized bun for yourself.
(Date him for a day)
(and I'll get his shares of the resort.)
(Gu An'an,)
(if it was this easy,)
(why bother anymore?)
What do you need?
Can you do some paperwork
in the city tomorrow?
I've sent the files to your email.
Is there really paperwork to do
or you're trying
to be alone with him?
What do you mean?
Why did you agree to date him for a day?
You eavesdropped on us?
Answer my question.
Yes.
I agreed to go on a date with him.
But it's just for a day
and he said...
What if he's lying?
I don't care.
I have to give it a try.
Doesn't it benefit both of us?
Have you forgotten
our original intention?
Benefit both of us?
You're the one who forgot
our original intention.
Anyway, I said yes.
An'an, you look amazing today.
Do I usually look awful or something?
No, no.
You're just prettier than usual.
You're going out?
I just went jogging
and bought some water.
Here.
Don't thank me.
That's nice of you.
Mr. Meng, what's wrong
with your car tire?
It's okay.
I have Plan B.
An'an.
Please.
Mr. Huo.
We don't have a seat for you.