♪Before I met you♪
♪I didn't care
who my life was related to♪
♪And the capricious borrowing from time♪
♪I never thought about repaying it♪
♪Before being in love,
it didn't matter who it was♪
♪You are more precious than freedom♪
♪If not for your smile♪
♪That had changed the whole world♪
♪How would I realize it belatedly
yet willingly♪
♪The furrowing and relaxing
of your brows♪
♪The depths of your dimples♪
♪Before I met you♪
♪How would I have understood those♪
♪I was a blank slate♪
=The Heir's Forbidden Love=
=Episode 8=
Keep following up on the project.
Make no mistake.
Understand?
Okay.
Huo Siting.
What is this?
Do you know what day it is?
Why do I care?
It's my mom's death anniversary.
As the lady of the Huo family,
please offer her an incense.
I'll offer incense to this lowlife?
Watch your mouth.
Lowlife.
I swear I could set all of you on fire
to keep her company.
You mad dog.
I'm telling you.
I won't allow the photo
of this lowlife in my house.
What do you want?
How dare you?
Huo Siting, you just wait.
I will tell your dad
what you have done today.
An'an, let's go.
Just you wait.
Seriously.
That was outrageous.
He's like a mad dog
biting everyone.
An'an,
my silly child.
That madman has lost it.
What if he hurts you?
It's nothing, Ms. Lu.
You have shown me kindness.
I can get hurt
as long as you are safe.
With Huo Siting in my house,
I can never be at ease.
Keeping him by your side
only causes endless trouble.
I know what to do
about him.
As for you, An'an.
You'd better
stay away from that madman.
If you really get hurt,
I wouldn't know
who to entrust the project to.
Don't worry, Ms. Lu.
Time waits for no one.
Work is the priority.
An'an.
You're such a good girl.
Ms. Lu.
Please don't hesitate
to assign me tasks.
There's a final payment from last month.
Wire it to this overseas account for me.
You know what to do, right?
Rest assured.
What's with the knife?
Ever since he barged in,
I've been having nightmares.
Why did you come at this hour?
I got you into this whole mess.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it
a bit too late for that?
Why didn't you hit me earlier?
I couldn't.
Do you know
that a move of yours
might render all my efforts
completely futile?
Huo Siting.
When did you become
so indecisive?
Should I just
watch you get hurt?
Compared to my mom's injuries,
that would be nothing.
If you can't even pay
such a small price,
then I've been
wrong about you.
I see.
It won't happen again.
Lu Yuzhu gave me a card.
She wants to wire money
to an overseas account.
The same mysterious beneficiary.
I think it's our chance
to bring her down.
She's transferring money so openly.
It's probably not so simple.
(Secretary Wu)
Hello, Secretary Wu.
Ms. Lu.
Miss Gu came to the company.
What? She went to the company?
Yeah.
I think she's here for Mr. Huo.
Okay, I see.
Don't you owe me
an apology for what happened?
What are you doing here?
It's my father's company.
I'm free to come.
You almost hurt An'an.
I haven't told your father.
Yet you're demanding an apology?
Be sensible.
Go away.
Huo Siting.
You'd better show me some respect.
Otherwise,
I won't go easy on you.
How?
Are you going to
kick me out just like back then?
Lu Yuzhu, listen.
This time, I will not leave.
Your days are coming to an end.
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
You framed my mom
for cheating with a servant.
My dad got enraged
and drove us out.
I even suspect
that my mom didn't die of illness.
You sent someone to kill her.
Don't talk nonsense.
You know better
if I'm talking nonsense.
This time,
I will kick you out by myself.
Fine.
I'd like to find out
who will remain in this family
in the end.
Madman.
Good day, Ms. Lu.
- Ms. Lu.