♪Before I met you♪
♪I didn't care
who my life was related to♪
♪And the capricious borrowing from time♪
♪I never thought about repaying it♪
♪Before being in love,
it didn't matter who it was♪
♪You are more precious than freedom♪
♪If not for your smile♪
♪That had changed the whole world♪
♪How would I realize it belatedly
yet willingly♪
♪The furrowing and relaxing
of your brows♪
♪The depths of your dimples♪
♪Before I met you♪
♪How would I have understood those♪
♪I was a blank slate♪
=The Heir's Forbidden Love=
=Episode 13=
What will you do?
I'm checking your seat belt.
Why don't you just tell me?
You think I stopped the car
to do what?
Sir, your room card.
Thank you.
My room is next to yours.
You have such a fine hotel
in your resort.
Of course.
The resort was only half-built
when you took over.
I haven't even stayed here.
You took huge advantage of us.
Rest assured.
It will be yours sooner or later.
The Meng Group people haven't arrived.
Would you
care for a ride?
Sure.
It's really pretty here.
Yeah.
And the air is so fresh.
I'd also love to ride a bike by the sea.
Go ahead.
But I can't ride a bike.
Who would've thought
that the mighty Miss Gu
couldn't ride a bicycle?
Get down.
I'll do it.
Alright.
Can you do it? I'll help you.
To the left.
To the right.
Left. Right.
Forget it.
I'm done. You do it.
Hop on.
I had enough.
You're in charge of this project.
How can you
manage this project
if you don't even know this place?
Hop on.
What a beautiful sea.
Let's look around.
Go slower.
Do you really know how to ride?
I'm much better than you.
Let me show off
my skills.
If I fall,
I'll drag you down with me.
Hold on tight.
Go slower.
What's on your mind?
We had a driver
when I was a kid.
But one day,
I saw all the other kids
riding bicycles
and wanted to learn.
So my mom bought me a bike.
But
I was afraid of falling
and never learned.
So I had to sit on the back
when she rode it.
It's just that she's in hospital now.
I can't lean on her back
for a ride again.
She will definitely get better.
Let's hope.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Continue our ride.
Let's go.
Be careful.
♪Before I met you♪
♪There were many things
I'd never considered♪
♪Except for the occasional loneliness♪
♪It was quite a happy life♪
♪Before I met you♪
♪I had plenty of time♪
♪Those random thoughts about love♪
♪Are nothing but parts of my intuition♪
It's been a long day.
Rest well tonight.
Go back first.
I want to stay a bit.
I'll be with you.
No need.
Let me walk around alone.
After all, this resort represents
my mom's lifelong effort.
Alright.
Stay safe.
I'm off then.
Go back.
Why did you pull me down?
You are so pretty.
Lunatic.
Scoundrel.
Don't you remember me?
Your pick-up line
is a bit cliché.
You're back.
What happened?
I fell into the pool.
Why did you fall into the pool?
You think I wanted that?
No, it's just that...
Now you think I'm a burden?
That's not what I meant.
You're so annoying.
What's so annoying about me?
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
I was in a bad mood yesterday.
It wasn't directed at you.
I didn't mind it at all.
Are you hungry?
Have some breakfast.
Still not feeling well?
Just a bit dizzy.
Don't go to the dinner meeting.
I got this.
That won't do.
The Mengs finally agreed to invest.
If I don't attend
our first formal meeting,
who knows what they'll think?
Can you stop trying to be tough?
I'm not that soft.
Fine.
Come back if you feel unwell.
I can handle it.
Okay.
Take your medicine.
Sleep some more.
Mr. Meng.