Pinocchio
Mother. Where are you right now?
Sir.
Oh, Ms Choi.
Why are you back already?
Why aren't you at your assigned post?
I'm sorry.
I have something important to do.
Do you know where the Chief is perhaps?
She's in the meeting room.
What's wrong with her?
-Were you this low, Chief?
-What are you doing at this hour?
The cell phone
that you were looking for...
I restored all the deleted messages.
Try to explain to me what these are.
It's been 13 years...
No, it's been 14 years already.
I thought that you might've misunderstood
the situation because of the media.
I thought that you did it
because of your own conviction.
But was it like this?
Were you someone who just writes down
whatever the Chairwoman orders?
Are you sure...
you're a real reporter?
-How did you get this?
-Please explain.
The texts that you sent to Ms Song...
Telling her to use fireman Ki Ho-sang...
What does this mean?
Tell me you're not.
Tell me that you're not this scary.
Tell me that you're not
this horrible please.
Who else knows about this other than you?
-Did you really do this, mother?
-I said who else knows about this?
What if someone else knows?
Just why did you do this?
Either explain it to me
or at least make excuses.
I told you before right?
I'll tell you
when you quit being a reporter.
Captain. This is Seo Bum-Jo.
Starting today...
I'm quitting MSC.
Is that good?
I think I'm qualified to listen
to you answer.
Episode 17 - The Scarlet Letter
That's right.
I did send all these texts.
Because of that incident at that time.
The Assemblyman that was looking after
my business was in a difficult situation.
Issues with the plant
and the chemical disposal business...
He was looking after all of them.
But he was in a sensitive time
because of his by-elections...
So...
You framed fireman Ki Ho-sang
to cover that person?
We just had to divert the attention
until the election was over.
But I didn't even know
that the matter would get that big.
If you consider everything,
what I did wasn't exactly illegal.
I just did a small favor for someone
who was helping my business.
This business is the same as farming.
Things don't just grow
because you planted the seeds.
You have to grow them
while getting your hands dirty
with smelly fertilizer and pesticides
until you can finally hold the fruit
with your hands.
Next month, I'll have the grand opening
at the Duty Free shop
and the new shopping mall permit
in Yeonjoo.
They're all businesses worth
several hundred million dollars.
Those are all the farms
that I worked hard on for 20 years
while I fertilized and nurtured.
I just have to harvest now,
but it keeps getting infested with bugs
so I'm really about to get irritated.
What if...
What if these texts
are revealed to the world?
Well, I'm sure we'll get criticized a bit.
But it's already been 14 years.
There's no law to apply
and even if there is one...
the statutes of limitation must be over.
I don't think
there's going to be any problems.
By granting these kinds of favors...
what did you gain for yourself?
All the things that
you've been enjoying until now.
And...
And all the things
that you'll enjoy in the future.
I just thought that you made a mistake
as a reporter.
That you and Bum-jo's mom
were simply friends.
No.
I wanted to believe that.
But how could you do such a thing?
As a reporter... No. How could you do
such a thing as a human being?
Where...
Where did you get that?
You told me to argue with proof,
didn't you?
I don't think there will be
any definite proof than this.
Please answer me.
Just why did you do such a horrible thing?
-Lower your voice. Don't make a fuss.
-No.
I am going to make a fuss.
What Bum-jo's mother and you, mom...
no, Chief, have committed...
The atrocity you have committed...
I'm going to report it no matter what.
I'm going to reveal it
to the world in detail!
I will reveal them all.
February, 2000
Now that I'm aware of the truth,
I can't keep my mouth shut as a reporter.
I'll report everything on the connection
between the Chairwoman and Chief.
Do you think that I will let you do that?
Do you think that's possible?
No. I'm sure it will be impossible at MSC.
The report will go out from YGN.
What?
I think that it's only right to report it
no matter what.
So I decided to give
all the proof and files to YGN.
Are you saying
you're going to be a whistle-blower?
Are you aware of the consequences
of your action?
I am prepared, to some degree.
You won't be a reporter ever again.
I'm curious to see
if you're prepared to that degree.
Do you think that
you have the strength to report this?
There's no way
this will be reported at MSC.
I know.
-The report will be given at YGN...
-So you'll be a whistle-blower...
Are you aware that once you become
a whistle-blower, you'll be fired?
I'm not afraid.
The company where I can't say what I want
and has dirty connections...
I'm not sorry to let it go.
I'm going to start over
as a reporter at a proper company.
Do you think you'll be able
to be a reporter again?
Yes.
Who will hire someone
who has been branded as a whistle-blower?
What organization will welcome someone
who tattles
about the internal problems to the world?
There aren't any companies
in the world...
that are that innocent...
and righteous.
14 years ago...
I was exactly like you.
Think about it very carefully.
You just have to change your choice.
If you cover this up,
I can have you gain more power.
I can bring you up a position
where you will have a greater voice.
For example...
you can be the first woman captain
in the press.
Opportunities like that...
That decision brought me where I am.
Of course, it's possible for you
to make a different choice.
You can give up being a reporter
and live as a part-timer
at a convenience store.
Following your conscience and purely...
Now...
you're almost done with the internship.
Don't you want to be a full-time employee?
-Ms Song!
-Think about it.
Just once...
you can speak about one thing they want...
and then speak about 99 right things.
Or...
a powerless person
who doesn't have a voice in the world.
I don't want you
to become a powerless person.
I'm telling you this not as a Chief...
but as your mom.
I saw how someone can be destroyed...
when they become a whistle-blower.
Who?
Your father.
You probably don't remember
because you were young.
But your father...
he was a pretty successful manager
at a bank.
But he found out
about the president's illegal loans...
and got fired
after reporting it to the newspaper.
What do you think?
From what you can see...
which is more pathetic,
between your father's life and mine?
I've never thought
that dad's life was pathetic.
If that's the consequence
of telling the truth, I'm rather proud.
I'm going to make
a different choice than you.
That bastard.
How could he date some other girl so soon?
Hello?
Can you come see me briefly?
-I'm here.
-Are you bragging about being tall?
If you came, sit down.
Your face looks good.
Did something good happen?
There's nothing special going on.
Does In-ha know that you got another girl?
Excuse me?
What do you mean another girl?
I saw it when I went
to your house recently.
There was a long strand of woman's hair
in your room.
Even if you're in a hot-blooded age,
how could you bring another girl
to your room?
A strand of woman's hair?
-That's...
-Or...
Are you going to tell me
that it's a guy friend with long hair?
How can your heart be that shallow?
How can you change your heart so easily
when you liked In-ha
for such a long time?
That was In-ha's.
-What?
-In-ha came to my house that day.
-It's not some other woman's.
-Really?
That's what happened?
I just thought perhaps...
That was In-ha's?
The more I think about it,
the more disgraceful I think it is.
How could In-ha go in and out
to a guy's room like that?
Dad.
-Where are you, dad?
-You brat. I got you now.
-Dad, I have something to ask you.
-I'm the one with something to ask you.
I heard it from Dal-Po that
you went to his house before, right?
Although you guys grew up
as uncle and niece,
he's still a guy.
I never thought
that your life was pathetic.
If that's the consequence
of telling the truth, I'm rather proud.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It doesn't feel good.
No. It's nothing.
What did you want to ask me?
I'm not going to ask you.
In-ha! In-ha!
Are they crazy?
Who do they think they are
to manipulate the public opinion?
This is NTS, isn't it?
This is clearly NTS from what I can see.
Captain. Don't try to stop me.
-I'm going to expose them all.
-You stand aside.
I'm going to be the one to expose them.
No. I'll do it.
We have to show them
what public opinion is.
It's not NTS but our company.
These are the texts between Ms Song and
our second major shareholder, Park Rosa.
-What?
-Really?
Yes. The chief mentioned in the texts
are the current Director Yeon Doo-young.
They're our chief and director?
You should've said that sooner.
Captain, you can report this, right?
Right?
Well, that's...
Hey, this is a different story.
You have to go through the chief
and the director.
There's no captain that can go through it.
What if I give the information
over to YGN?
It's worse because
it will be whistle-blowing.
Once you're marked as a whistle-blower,
you can't work anywhere else.
It will be the end of the reporter's life.
Captain, you said it all the time.
The blade of criticism has to be sharper
the higher you aim.
Hey, but I can't be stabbed by that blade.
My life would be on the line.
My kids are studying overseas.
And it will be a while
until my kids go to college.
I'm still renting.
And there are 37 more
monthly payments left on my car.
Captain. Il-joo.
I'm too ashamed to look at you.
But...
Do you know when a dog gets eaten?
It's when they don't recognize their owner
and bark at them.
I know this is cowardly...
but I don't want to be eaten yet.
-Captain.
-Are you able to become a whistle-blower?
Is it okay for you to give up
on becoming a reporter?
Yes, I can.
You can't.
See?
Just keep your mouth shut.
By granting these favors,
what did you gain for yourself?
All the things you have enjoyed until now.
And...
And all the things
that you will enjoy in the future.
What is it?
What do you have to give to us in secret?
February 2000
Is this it?
No.
Never mind.
I can do it.
Even if I lose everything,
I must still reveal it to the world.
What is it?
What brings you all the way here?
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's just amazing.
-What is?
-I had a lot to worry about,
but they're gone now that I see you.
What were you worried about?
Just some ridiculous worries.
So ridiculous that I'm sorry
for even worrying about them.
-Are you lying with the enemy?
-It must be nice.
Whoa.
Hey, what's the matter?
This is my workplace.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I have something to tell you.
Should we go get some tea?
Sure.
You're so strange today.
What did you have to tell me?
I came to give you an amazing exclusive.
An exclusive? What is it?
This is it.
Why are you giving it to me?
Why don't you do it yourself?
Because I can't do it, but you can.
What is it?
It's the cell phone that my mom
was using in 2000.
And those are the restored
deleted text messages.
Take a look.
Those are the text messages between
my mom and Bum-jo's mother.
Bum-jo's mother?
Restored Text MMS Messages
I need somewhere
to avert the attention to.
Highlight fireman Ki Ho-sang
in a negative light.
Even his family if you need to...
You're saying your father isn't at blame?
Was he interested in promotion?
It's fortunate
that we have a Pinocchio witness.
-A witness saw that he was alive.
-Use that characteristic.
The witness is a Pinocchio, he can't lie.
I'm a Pinocchio. I can't lie...
To the direction that
enrages the nation the most...
You must be happy your father's alive.
Because of the unreasonable...
Afraid of nine deaths...
The public's rage...
These text messages are...
between Ms Song and Bum-jo's mother?
Yeah.
Just because of these texts...
my father became a criminal.
Just because of few lines of these texts.
Yeah.
They made it that way...
with just few lines of texts.
Oh, no!
Dal-Po, your hand...
Are you alright?
You're bleeding too much.
Does Bum-Jo know about this too?
Yeah. It seemed like he was quite shocked.
What about you?
Are you alright?
I'd be lying if I said I was.
I'm sure you're angry right now
but calm down and listen.
It's impossible to report this from MSC.
As you can see,
it concerns both the chief
and the director.
It's too difficult to go through
all that and report it.
So you do it.
Please do it for me.
What did Chief Song Cha-ok say?
She admitted that all of it was true.
But she said I can't report it
at MSC no matter what.
That's I'm handing it over to you.
You can do it, right?
I have to.
No matter what... At all cost...
Thank you.
Thank you for handing it over to me.
-Bum-Jo.
-Yeah.
Did you ask your mother
about the text messages?
What did she say?
Why should I tell you?
Should I give you an advice?
No matter what you and Ha-myung do,
it won't really affect my mother.
So don't waste your energy
on useless things
and keep your positions.
-What?
-I'm going to return to where I belong.
-Captain.
-Let me drink this.
Yes, sir.
Thanks.
-Who reported these texts to you?
-It was reporter Choi In-ha.
I heard that she confirmed it
with Chief Song Cha-ok.
If these texts are true...
the connections between MSC executives,
Chairwoman Park Rosa
the Assemblymen started
at least 14 years ago.
Yes.
Ki Ha-myung, leave your assigned position
for now.
You cover the story
and report it yourself.
Yes, Captain.
Jang Hyun-gyu.
Yoon Yoo-Rae and Cha Woo-chul.
-You guys come here and work on this also.
-Yes, Captain.
This is an incident from 14 years ago.
It will be a long and difficult coverage.
We'll be criticizing our competitor,
so be very cautious.
Ki Ha-myung. Go see Chairwoman Park Rosa
and confirm that she exchanged the texts.
Jang Hyun-gyu.
Find out the cause of the fire
and see how Chairwoman Park was involved.
Yoon Yoo-Rae and Cha Woo-chul.
Find out how the direction of reporting
changed after these texts were exchanged.
We must report...
how these few texts changed
the truth of the case and shook the world.
Ms Choi In-ha.
Congratulations.
Director Yeon just notified the HR team.
You are now a permanent employee.
He started to the appeasement process
to prevent whistle-blowing.
So forget about whistle-blowing
and report about other things.
There are a lot of things to report
in the world other than whistle-blowing.
What is this?
It's my resignation letter.
Thank you for everything.
Why?
I just told you that you became
a permanent employee.
A permanent employee!
A permanent employee
that can receive all four insurances.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear just now?
-You're a permanent employee now.
-Yes, I heard.
I was so excited.
I almost asked
for my resignation letter back.
Are you saying that you'll hand that
over to YGN?
-You'll really be a whistle-blower?
-I already am.
What?
I already handed the files
over to YGN yesterday.
That's why I submitted my resignation.
Are you crazy? Just why?
So that I could make the decision
without regrets.
I think it's the right decision.
Just why do you have to go this far?
-Why don't you listen to me!
-I'm trying to apologize instead of you.
What?
Mom, you should've done this then.
But you didn't do it and you aren't now,
so I'm doing it instead.
Why do you have to apologize for me?
Because I'm your daughter.
I promised myself so many times...
to think of you as a stranger.
Since you abandoned me already,
I just have to let go
and that will be the end.
But I just can't do it.
I just have to let go of this hand.
But I can't. Like a fool...
Where are we going first today?
We have to interview Chairwoman Park Rosa.
We have to barge in without an appointment
so it might get a little rough.
That's my specialty.
Captain wanted me to give this to you.
Is this a hidden camera?
We might have to put down
the cameras for the interview.
Wow, you can't tell at all.
Let's go.
MSC
YGN NEWSQUARE
I'm going to interview
Chairwoman Park Rosa.
It has begun.
Dig up properly until the end.
If you come up empty, you're dead. Cheers!
Dad, I'm home.
What are you doing here at this hour?
-What is that bag for?
-I quit.
What? You quit?
Yeah.
You hated that I became a reporter.
I did well, right?
Were you fired?
No. I quit.
I quit so that I can tell the truth,
like you.
How did you feel, dad?
Did you regret after you quit?
In-ha.
You didn't regret it, did you?
Tell me you didn't regret it.
Tell me I did the right thing.
Please, tell me
I did the right thing, dad.
You did the right thing.
My daughter did the right thing.
Mom...
Chairwoman Park Rosa.
I have something to ask you.
-You can't do this.
-No interviews. Please move aside.
You can't do this.
Oh, my? Who is this?
Aren't you reporter Ki Ha-myung?
-It's your friend, right?
-Yes.
It's alright since he's my son's friend.
Do you remember the texts between
you and Chief Song Cha-ok from MSC?
I heard about you a lot from Bum-Jo.
But this is the first time
we've met, right?
Yes. I'll continue to ask you.
You said that this person in the text
should be hidden.
You asked for this person
to not be mentioned as guilty.
Who is this person here?
I don't know what you're talking about?
What is he talking about?
"We should avert the attention.
Frame him in a negative light."
"Even his family if you need to."
Do you not remember this either?
I don't remember. What is that?
"We're fortunate
to have a Pinocchio witness."
"Use that characteristic.
To enrage the nation the most."
Oh, no.
Since it's been such a long time,
I just can't remember
what you're talking about.
I didn't say that it was a long time ago.
We got her.
You said you can't remember,
but you do remember
that this is from a long time ago.
I'll ask you again.
Did you exchange texts with
Chief Song Cha-ok of MSC 14 years ago?
-Get rid of him.
-Please move.
-Did you get it, Jae-hwan?
-Yeah.
I got it clean.
We should meet.
In-ha.
I made Bibimbap. Don't you want to eat?
I'm not going to eat.
I don't have an appetite.
I got an interview with Bum-jo's mother.
She admitted that she sent the texts.
Good job.
I knew you could do it.
You still have a long way to go,
so stop bragging.
This blunt witch.
Who is it?
That friend from that time?
No, sir.
It's a good time.
I guess spring is not that far away.
Even though I'm dying inside,
I guess I didn't lose my appetite.
Dad.
I'm going to start practicing
driving tomorrow.
Ji-hee said she'll teach me with her car.
I'll look into government testing job test
and private sector also.
I'm still young so it won't be hard
to look for another career. Right?
I was also thinking about registering
for English lessons.
Grandpa. Grandpa. Grandpa.
Tell me. How much do you need?
Are you going to pay for my lessons?
Thanks, Grandpa.
It's not a crime to say
what needs to be said.
It's a crime to say
what you shouldn't say.
So don't be so defeated
and cheer up.
You got it?
Grandpa...
I heard everything from your dad.
You did well, In-ha.
-My baby... Yes. Yes.
-Thank you, Grandpa.
Did you know about the relationship
between Assemblyman
and Chairwoman Park Rosa?
I'm not sure. I don't know.
In-ha!
Just sit still.
I can't focus because of you.
-Be careful!
-Be quiet!
-Hey, you need to watch out!
-Just stay still.
Reporter Song Cha-ok.
Factory Explosion Cause and casualty
Hey!
If they are to go stronger...
Letter of Resignation
I couldn't say what I wanted to.
Whose resignation is this?
It's Choi In-ha's.
Choi In-ha resigned? Why?
She didn't want to be mistreated
because of whistle-blowing.
She submitted this and left.
Is it because of the report
she gave to us?
Yes. I tried to stop her
but she wouldn't listen to me.
Are you really going to report it?
Did you accept that resignation yet?
I haven't yet.
I got goose bumps all over me.
I matched the date of the texts
with the news reports from MSC.
Yoon Yoo-Rae. That's pretty good.
Captain!
I organized the direction of reporting
after the texts into charts.
-If we request for CGI..
-That's enough.
Put a hold on making the connections
for now.
Why?
Ki Ha-myung. I want to see you.
Yes.
Why is Captain like that?
Why does he keep changing his mind?
It's so irritating.
I'm sorry.
-I got mad without realizing...
-I understand.
I completely understand how you feel.
Do you want to join me
on the path of a Nitpicker?
The content of those texts,
you said you got them
from Choi In-ha, right?
Yes. I even received a request
from her asking me to report it.
Did you check to see if she's okay?
This is whistle-blowing.
Whistle-blowing?
It's criticizing the chief, director,
and major shareholder of her own company.
The fact that she gave this to us means
she's prepared to quit.
Did you not know?
I had a lot to worry about,
but they all disappeared when I saw you.
I didn't know.
I confirmed with her captain today.
She submitted her resignation letter.
A resignation letter?
Go see her find out she's really alright.
You have to put your life on the line
when whistle-blowing.
You have to be ready to lose your company,
your colleague and even your future.
Don't think that it's simply reasonable.
-Ki Ha-myung.
-Yes.
I know how angry you must've been
because of this connection.
And I know that you want to satisfy
your grudge through this report.
But don't be so blinded
by satisfying your grudge
that you forget about the things
you must think about as a reporter.
Yes, Captain.
I'll be out for a little while.
Choi In-ha, where are you?
I stayed up all night making this.
He didn't even acknowledge it...
This is...
Let me drink this.
Hey, Captain just flirted with me, right?
What are you talking about? What flirting?
He stole my drink from me that time.
This is the same drink from that time.
So?
He remembered that he stole it
from me that time and bought me this.
It's 100 percent flirting.
Don't you think he's amazingly detailed?
Or did he steal my drink intentionally?
To kiss me indirectly?
Then...
Did the Captain flirt with me too?
-You got one too?
-Yeah.
Really?
-Then am I the only who is strange?
-Yeah.
You're the only one who's strange.
You're really strange.
Go see a doctor.
I guess...
Even when I think about it,
I think I'm a little narcissistic.
Even though I was taken advantage of,
here I go again.
For a beginner,
wasn't my driving pretty great?
It's not great, but it's crazy.
Every time you had to turn left,
you made a u-turn...
Wow, it'll only be a matter time
until I make Chan-soo
a single dad, if I keep giving you
driving lessons.
Choi In-ha.
-You're here.
-You came, my friend?
-Come out and talk with me.
-What is it about? Talk to me here.
-Hey, you!
Okay, I'm coming out.
Teach me tomorrow too.
Chan-soo, I'll come by again next time.
Why didn't you tell me
about the resignation letter?
Look at yourself. I knew that
you would just get mad for no reason.
You think that I'm getting mad
without reason?
No. I know that you're mad
because you're worried about me.
I know what you're going to say too.
But I'm completely fine.
I'm practicing driving
and I'm taking English classes too.
I'll be submitting my resumes again
starting tomorrow.
Your resignation hasn't been processed yet
so hurry up and return to your company.
I don't want to.
I'm going to pretend that
I didn't receive those texts from you.
What?
You won't report them?
No.
I must've heard you wrong.
If not, you must've gone crazy.
Don't you know what I was feeling
when I gave it to you?
I didn't know.
I was so focused on revealing
what happened 14 years ago
that I didn't realize
that it was whistle-blowing,
or what would happen to you.
If I knew that you gave up on
being a reporter to give me the report...
I wouldn't have accepted it.
Are you crazy?
With that you can reveal to the world
how unjustly your family was destroyed.
So why would you give up on it?
If you were me,
would you accept this report?
Even if my life would be ruined?
Could you really do it?
Answer me.
I'll do it according to your answer.
Yeah.
I can do it.
Whatever happens to your life,
I would've accepted that report.
See?
You can't do it either.
Why are you telling me to do something
that you can't do yourself?
Then you answer me too.
What would you do if you were me?
Would you just bury this?
No.
I won't bury it.
I'm going to do whatever
it takes to reveal the connections
using other ways than using your report.
What other way?
-What other way is there than this?
-There is.
Of course it will take longer
and it will be hard but there is a way.
So return to your company for now.
Let's look for another way together.
But it's such a waste.
We can reveal it all with this.
I'm not saying that I won't do it.
I'm just saying that
I'm going to find another way.
I found out while I was talking to my mom
about the texts.
She tried to be a whistle-blower
on connection 14 years ago too.
But because of the threat
of getting fired...
...she went along
with Bum-jo's mother's appeasement.
This is Song Cha-ok,
a promising reporter of MSC.
She's a talented reporter.
It's nice to meet you.
I think that was when she started...
to be a blower for Bum-jo's mother.
It seems like after she made that decision
she started to get continual success.
The first female reporter captain
and special correspondent.
And even the youngest chief.
Don't you think it's incredible?
Yeah.
But I didn't want to make
the same decision that my mom made.
That's why handed the texts over to you.
I know.
But truth be told, I was scared.
My dad was the opposite of my mom.
His life was ruined by whistle-blowing.
-Your dad?
-Yeah.
My dad used to be
a successful bank manager.
Your dad?
Yes. This is Choi Dal-pyung
from Loans Department.
Yes.
Loan consultation?
Yes, it's possible.
Please visit us. Thank you.
I can't believe it either but it was true.
But what did he report?
He reported the bank president's
illegal loans to the newspaper.
Because of that report,
the bank president was fired
and the loan corruption decreased. But...
I knew it since he started to brag
about being the youngest manager.
Everyone should watch their words
around him.
Hello. Good morning.
Let's go.
I think his work life became
really difficult.
Everyone stopped talking in front of him
and they didn't eat together with him.
He said he felt like
he was an invisible man.
In the end, he thought that it wasn't
a job but a waste of life, so he quit.
But he was marked as a whistle-blower,
so it was difficult getting a new job.
And IMF crisis happened,
so he was forced to stay jobless.
He was in conflict over that with my mom
and ended up getting a divorce.
I see.
But I'm curious.
About what?
Whether the two of them
regret their decisions.
I know. I'm getting curious too.
Recently my son wanted
to slowly start studying business,
so he quit being a reporter
and is traveling with me.
How do you find the painting?
I  heard Assemblyman Shin's wife
painted these.
I'm not sure.
I don't know much about paintings.
I don't either.
They all seem like a waste of paint.
The purpose of these exhibitions
is obvious.
They're saying that someone like me should
open up their wallet, so what can I do?
I have to go along with
what the Assemblymen want.
Would this be enough?
If our Assemblymen hold exhibitions,
I buy paintings.
If they hold a publication party,
we give congratulatory money.
If there's a problem,
we use the news to keep it covered.
Ms Song, you know how much I did
for those Assemblymen too, right?
Yes, ma'am.
But all that hard work is being shaken,
so I'm a little worried.
These days you have to be careful
about trivial gossip even.
A little while ago, was it Ki Ha-myung?
That guy even brought the camera crew
and asked about what happened
14 years ago.
Yes.
Since he's not from our side,
he'll be difficult to appease.
He didn't even seem like the kind
you can easily persuade.
That's why I'm saying this.
Your daughter...
Choi In-ha.
Can you arrange a meeting with her?
Why do you want to meet my daughter?
You know that she is very close
with Ki Ha-myung, right?
I think it might be easier to target her.
Ma'am.
Don't worry. I won't treat her badly.
You know me.
I only make good suggestions
that you can't refuse.
I treated you so well 14 years ago too.
I just want to make another
good relationship, like the one we have.
You understand what I mean, don't you?
Yes.
I didn't know that you'd wear
those rotten sweats again.
I'm going to rip it up or burn it
next time I do laundry.
What? It's perfectly fine.
But I'm curious.
About what?
Whether the two of them
regret their decisions.
Dad.
Don't you regret reporting
the bank president?
No, I don't regret.
If I didn't do it and hold it in,
I would've died of repressed anger.
So you would've made the same decision
even if you went back to the past?
No. I wouldn't make the same decision.
What? I thought you didn't regret?
I do regret.
After I quit,
I was jobless for over 10 years.
Then you don't want to report it
and live like mom?
-Is that right?
-No. I would hate that even more.
Then what is it? What are you regretting?
I should not have quit and endured longer.
That kind of regret...
Although they were nasty and
petty toward me,
I should've endured in the company.
I regret most about giving up so easily
and leaving.
Are you going to practice driving?
No.
I'm going to the company.
The company?
My mom tried to be a whistle-blower
because of that connection 14 years ago.
Choi In-ha.
-Did you decide to return?
-Yeah.
I called the captain, he told me to come.
So I'm going to try to endure
no matter what.
Just like you said, I think
I'll have to look for a way inside there.
Cheers.
You need to go over there.
This is my company.
I have a business over here too.
Let's go.
I just want to make another
good relationship like the one we have.
You understand what I mean, don't you?
Reporter Song.
I have something to tell you.
Please let me have a brief moment.
-What is this?
-The texts I received from In-ha.
The cell phone is inside too.
I'll pretend that I didn't receive them.
If I do this,
In-ha didn't blow the whistle.
So I hope there won't be any
negative results for In-ha because of it.
Why are you doing this?
-Don't you know what this is?
-I know.
Those are the files
that can reveal the people
who framed my father 14 years ago.
These files can also
bring you down as well.
So why are you doing this?
I thought you desperately wanted these.
Yes. I do want it desperately.
It's my wish to report this to the world.
But I can't ruin someone else's life,
because of that wish and greed.
Is that why you're giving up
on reporting this?
No.
I'm asking you to report it.
I heard that you gave up
on blowing the whistle
and accepted Chairwoman Park's
appeasement 14 years ago.
And because of that decision...
my family was horribly destroyed.
In-ha doesn't have the power
to report that.
But if I report it,
In-ha will be hurt too.
So?
The person responsible for that tragedy
is not In-ha, but you.
So you have to be the one
to reveal this to the world.
Do you think that I would report this
for that reason?
So you're handing these over to me?
Aren't you too naive?
Yes. I know that
this is a ridiculous gamble.
But I want to believe in my craziness.
There was a moment...
that you were determined to
become a whistle-blower.
You were once a reporter.
And maybe you might regret the decision
you made 14 years ago.
I wanted to naively believe in that.
I'm asking you.
Please report it yourself.
In-ha and also you, Ki Ha-myung...
You both are so reckless
to the point that I'm irritated.
Why should you be sorry?
Because my mom is not apologizing
or correcting it.
Why don't the people believe you
even when you're telling the truth?
They're whining so much
that I'm really irritated.
You're a fraud.
You abandoned me anyway.
President Joo Sang-ho. You fabricated
this death certificate, right?
Our relationship will end
if I just let it go.
But I just can't do it.
Why couldn't you even believe in yourself?
I'm stressed to the point of irritation.
-Are you even a reporter?
-I just need to let go of this hand.
But I just can't. Like a fool.
Embarrassing me to the point
that I'm irritated.
When will I be able to see Choi In-ha?
Could it be a warning?
To watch your mouth.
I have an informant.
I wonder if we were too reckless.
Dig up without the director knowing.
It's so annoying to have bugs in my farms
that I've worked on for 20 years!
I'm going to give the report.
Just cover it properly.
Now that I think about it,
this is a first.
That you added a condition on my request.
I dreamt that Dal-Po asked me
for permission to date In-ha.