Li
Li Yang
Liu
What does this have
to do with you becoming a writer?
I'm telling you
if he hadn't had
that martial arts competition
he wouldn't have gotten the inspiration.
If I hadn't gone to detention,
I wouldn't have this inspiration either.
My novel is amazing.
My novel
is much grander than theirs.
Mine goes international.
The main villain is from Dongying.
His name is Gou Changzi.
Gou as in survival,
Chang as in the Spirits of Death,
and Zi meaning son.
He commits all kinds of evil,
absolutely unforgivable,
just a total villain.
Alright, alright.
Write if you want to,
but don't leave the house.
Look at me,
I
only got inspired because I fought with Dog Intestine,
that's how I got the inspiration.
If I hadn't fought,
I wouldn't have this inspiration.
Wait, so you need to go out
and get into how many fights
to finish this book?
You might as well
write in a labor camp.
The material there is much richer.
Enough. Eat your food.
Uncle, what's our protagonist's name?
Huo Dongfeng.
That's great!
You used my father's name.
Your father was indeed
the first hero of the Dalin Three Heroes.
So the name Huo Dongfeng is very fitting.
What about the villain?
Didn't I tell you already?
Gou Changzi and Dong Yingren.
Uncle,
how far have you gotten with the writing?
Gou Changzi was beaten black and blue by Huo Dongfeng,
foaming at the mouth.
So he needed the Great Revival Pill to extend his life.
He sent his subordinates
to search for the Great Revival Pill.
Because his subordinate was too clever,
he mistook a piece of dried dog poop
for the Great Revival Pill
and brought it back to him.
After eating half of it,
he suddenly slammed the table and stood up,
shouting,
"This isn't the Great Revival Pill!
This is clearly a divine delicacy!"
Go on.
What's going on?
Why are you laughing so happily?
Huo Xiaoyang is telling us about
his uncle's new novel.
Really?
What's it about?
You all seem so amused.
It's about the villain
who mistook dog poop for a magical pill
and ate it.
Alright, that's enough.
Stop talking about it.
Let's get ready for class.
How's your dance practice going?
Very well.
Alright, hurry up now.
How long has it been?
Why haven't they released him yet?
I'm just a junior detective.
I don't have the authority to release anyone.
Listen to me.
The Criminal Procedure Law of the People's Republic of China,
Article 156 states that
after a suspect is arrested,
the investigation and detention period
must not exceed 2 months.
For serious cases,
with the prosecutor's approval,
detention can be extended for one month.
Am I right?
But how long has it been already?
You're right.
Are you suggesting we're illegally detaining him?
Criminal Law Article 158.
Do you know it?
Article 159.
Do you know what it says?
Yes, I know all of it.
Criminal Law Article 158.
Yes, theoretically,
you can
detain him for another month.
Article 159,
on top of that,
you can further
extend detention for another month.
The problem is,
you don't have
any key witnesses or evidence.
Because he didn't kill anyone.
So how can you convict him?
That's exactly why we can't convict him,
so we're still detaining him.
It's because of insufficient evidence
that the prosecutor's office
keeps sending the case back for review.
Besides,
didn't you,
in college,
study something about
spacecraft or something?
How come you know these legal articles
so well?
I just took the bar exam.
What?
You're becoming a lawyer?
Yes. That lawyer you introduced me to
was completely unreliable.
I really regret it.
I feel so guilty.
If I hadn't been so loose-lipped back then,
he wouldn't have gone fortune-telling,
and none of this mess would have happened.
Well, you know what,
you really are unreliable when they say so,
but when you're reliable...
Stop talking nonsense.
Do you have any solutions?
We need to figure something out!
Yes, there is one way.
Go study criminal investigation.
If you catch the real killer,
then he'll be proven innocent, won't he?
You're messing with me.
I'm not messing with you.
I think you could really learn it.
Criminal investigation is your job.
Yes, it is our job.
We all believe
Guo Dapao is the real culprit.
Anything else?
I'm leaving.
I'm busy.
Brother.
Remember that little girl
who was eating meat here last time?
I already paid the bill.
Has she been back?
She's been here twice.
Just wandering outside the door.
Too scared to come in.
When I called out to her,
she ran away immediately.
This kid.
Next time,
grab her
and tell her not to be afraid.
Let her eat until she's full.
Alright.
Grill me 30 skewers,
give me 5 steamed bun slices.
I'll take them to go.
Okay.
Make it 50 skewers.
Sure, sure.
Last time, I was chatting with Guo Dapao here.
I told him to find
a fortune teller.
Did you hear that?
No, what's up?
It's fine.
What did Grandpa say?
He said
he won't let me eat at this kebab place
because last time
after you took me for kebabs
I had diarrhea for days.
You're eating too fast.
Slow down.
Uncle, I'm getting my lawyer's license soon.
When that happens,
I can personally defend Dalei in court.
Mr. Cui,
did you know that Huo Xiaoyang
is going to perform a solo dance?
Yes, I know.
What is he performing?
'Date with the Stars.'
I taught him.
He's practicing by himself now.
What do you mean?
Nothing, nothing. It's great.
Dad.
Get your own water.
I'm rushing to finish my manuscript.
My classmate is pressing me for it.
How much have you written?
I still need to write 20,000 to 30,000 words out of 100,000.
What's the title?
'Cleansing the Sword in the Vast Sea'
That's a good title.
Has the factory contacted you recently?
No contact. Why would they contact me?
My lawyer's license is coming soon.
I'll be a lawyer then.
Who wants to mess around with them
and that antique machine?
Children grow up and make their own decisions.
You're on your own now.
You're always talking about breaking through bottlenecks.
I've gotten used to it.
Just remember this.
You're not alone.
You have elderly parents and young children to care for.
Other families with just one child might manage,
but you have two!
There might be more than two in the future.
Who else?
I'm just kidding.
To continue our story...
That day, Huo Dongfeng was walking through a small grove.
He discovered a female warrior
lying in the grove.
This female warrior
was young and beautiful.
Huo Dongfeng was immediately stunned by her beauty.
Then Huo Dongfeng took out
his special antidote.
But
when the female warrior woke up,
she mistakenly thought Huo Dongfeng
was the one who had stabbed her.
So the female warrior immediately drew her sword
and stabbed at Huo Dongfeng.
Such ingratitude!
What a pity.
What happens next?
Huo Dongfeng was stabbed
and left dying by the female warrior.
It was then that the female warrior realized
she had wrongly accused Huo Dongfeng.
So then,
the female warrior found a swift horse,
and the two of them rode together
to her home.
Then, over several months,
under the female warrior's care,
Huo Dongfeng's wounds finally healed,
and he regained 90% of his martial powers.
That's a relief.
That's so tragic.
Did the female warrior and Huo Dongfeng get married?
I'll tell you about that tomorrow.
Let's continue tomorrow.
Is this a good story?
And what's the name of the female warrior in this story?
She must have a name, right?
Yes, tell us quickly.
That's right.
Exactly.
Tell us now.
Go on.
Cui Xiaohong.
Uncle.
Did the heroine and Huo Dongfeng end up together?
It's a secret.
How's your dance practice going?
Very well.
Show us.
Very good! With my level of expertise,
I can't really point out anything wrong
with your performance.
Miss Mengmeng,
what do you think?
I studied folk dance,
I don't know much about this style.
But it looks pretty good.
Thank you on behalf of Erpang.
Mengmeng,
if I become a famous writer,
how much do you think
this pen of mine would sell for?
One yuan.
I paid more than 8 yuan for it!
But think about it.
If you want to become a famous writer,
by then this pen
would be completely worn out.
The clip would probably be gone,
and it's already quite worn now.
But some things
are more valuable the older and more worn they get,
like antiques.
That's because those are actual antiques,
at least hundreds or thousands of years old.
How long have you been using this pen?
Besides, many classmates in our class
have the same pen as yours.
So couldn't my pen be valuable
because
I'm the one who used it?
Why would a pen you used be worth anything?
Besides, who could prove
that this pen was actually used by you?
How about this:
why don't you use my pen today
so it can become valuable too?
You're my biological daughter.
Why do you
always argue with me?
Because when you meet unreliable people,
you need to debate with them,
otherwise they'll become
even more unreliable.
How am I unreliable?
You're unreliable in everything you do.
For example?
For example, you said you'd buy me
a Xiali car. Where is it?
I knew it would be like this.
Alright. Today
I'll let you witness the process of buying a Xiali car.
I've finished my manuscript.
My classmate works at the publishing house.
I'm going to meet him later.
You can come with me.
I'm not going.
I have dance lessons today.
You forgot.
Then you'll miss
a chance to witness history.
Can I come?
Uncle.
Wait until I change my clothes.
When people arrive later,
eat more slowly.
It's like I never feed you.
Can I have 50 more skewers then?
You haven't eaten anything.
Sure.
When you grow up,
I'll lease this skewer shop for you,
let you be the boss,
and you can eat whatever you want. How's that?
That would be awesome!
That's my dream.
Over here.
I'm a bit late.
Is this your son?
My sister's child.
Your sister is beautiful,
and your nephew looks...
Don't you think he looks
a bit like me?
Something about the brow line.
Let's talk about the manuscript.
Fine, let's discuss the manuscript.
I've read it.
It's brilliant.
The writing flows very well,
and the plot is very intricate.
But I haven't
told our publisher about it yet.
Why? Because
there are a few issues
I'd like to discuss with you.
Then I'll make some small changes
before sending it to the publisher.
I understand. Good.
So,
the main character is named Huo Dongfeng, right?
That local gang leader?
What's the problem?
Let him finish speaking.
Before we went to high school,
wasn't there something called the 'Three Heroes of Dalin'?
That name sounds familiar.
So I think this name...
Let's not change the name.
There are many people with the same name,
and besides,
this book will be distributed nationwide.
Right?
It doesn't really matter,
and
the name Huo Dongfeng itself
sounds like a hero's name.
Right?
Okay, fine.
The name is a minor issue. We won't change it.
Let's talk about the content.
Regarding the content, I think...
Could you ask your nephew
to go play some video games outside
and come back in half an hour?
Why?
It's a bit inappropriate for children.
He can hear you saying that.
Take the skewers outside
and warm them up again.
Alright!
Eat more!
Chubby kid!
Let's start talking.
All the content in this book,
the characters,
the martial arts schools, the chivalrous spirit,
all of these are fine.
The problem is with
the main character. He's too proper.
Today's readers
all want to read something a bit risqué,
you understand?
There's not a single
naked woman in your book.
Not even a bit of that kind of content.
Who would want to read this book?
So you want me to write erotic novels?
That's not what I meant.
I mean every dozen pages or so,
you should add a scene like that.
I believe with your writing skills,
this kind of content
you could definitely make it vivid and exciting.
Let me tell you,
if you write it my way,
this book will sell at least 20,000 copies.
But with your current style,
you won't even sell 100 copies.
I understand.
I can write it,
but
where do you think
would be appropriate to add these scenes?
To include them?
It's easy.
The main character,
this Huo Dongfeng and the female warrior Cui Xiaohong,
they should have a bedroom scene,
right?
And then that female villain,
they should have another scene together.
That would be exciting.
And if you could include
the female bounty hunter who's chasing him,
and write a scene between them,
that would make the book thrilling.
All spicy. People would love to read it.
What do you think
about Huo Dongfeng and his brothers
having some bedroom scenes together?
How about that?
That would be fantastic!
I could sell 12 million copies of this book.
Discussing art with you,
real literary creation,
I truly regret
not doing this all these years.
This is really inspiring!
Please give this note to the boss for me.
Alright.
I'm going to take a leak first.
Go ahead.
After chatting with you today,
it's really wonderful.
Passion. Spice.
Um.
Boss.
Here.
This note is for you.
A note from the great writer.
Keep it safe.
For when he becomes famous.
This is great.
Sixty-two.
What's this sixty-two?
Number 62.
I didn't eat any of these skewers.
What does this have to do with me?
Isn't this you?
Well...
[Let this pervert pay the bill]
Where do I pay?
At the counter.
Let's go.
I'll cover it.
Thanks.
Want these skewers to go?
No, thanks.
Who does he look like?
Hailong?
Or more like his mother?
Come on, be happy!
Let me propose a toast, brother.
Thank you all for coming
to my son's one-month celebration.
I'll drink mine.
Please, everyone, drink as you like.
I'll use tea instead of alcohol.
Thank you.
Kids are so fun.
So cute.
Call me godfather.
He's only a month old.
Nezha? Would you dare to answer if he called you?
I'll call you godfather on his behalf.
Godmother.
Is this sweet and sour pork?
It looks like dumpling soup.
What's going on here?
How could they cook like this?
It's because Chef Zhang was
poached by Jufu Restaurant.
They offered him
twice our salary.
When Manager Cui was here before,
he felt too loyal to leave.
That's why I felt awkward inviting Manager Cui.
I'm afraid he'll get angry when he comes.
Keep your voice down.
What is this?
It's too salty.
Have some water.
Kids are the most fun at this age.
These ribs are way too salty.
You should stop eating. You're still...
Wait until he grows up like Mengmeng
When he gets older,
he'll start annoying you.
Just wait and see.
She deliberately annoys you.
That's what you get for being so unreliable.
Who says that? My brother Cui is very reliable.
He does everything properly.
If you pass the bar exam this time...
That's really impressive.
He's decent.
He got suspended.
I heard your company is offering severance packages.
He'll definitely be the first one targeted.
Absolutely the first one.
I've always been first in everything since childhood.
Just wait for my bar exam.
Wait for my results.
Shut up.
It's really too salty.
Eat it yourself. Eat it yourself.
Have some water. Have some water.
Let me pour you some more.
Sister-in-law,
I never interrupt,
but today I have to speak up.
My brother Cui
can do fine without working at the factory.
He can do anything outside.
With his physique,
he could carry sand bags.
What physique?
He could be a construction worker
or something like that.
An engineering graduate carrying sand bags?
When I married him,
I actually checked
his college diploma.
It didn't look fake.
But look at his behavior every day.
Does he look like a college graduate to you?
It doesn't matter if I look like one or not.
I am one.
Try this meatball.
It's just steamed bun.
Try it. Try it.
Here. Here. Here.
How's everyone enjoying the food?
Very good. Very good.
Thank you, Manager Tang,
for the discount.
Don't mention it. Don't mention it. Don't mention it.
Here, this is.
No need.
This is for the child,
not for you.
This...
Hurry.
What a loud voice!
He'll achieve great things in the future.
Keep it down,
you're making too much noise.
You'll wake the baby.
Manager Tang,
sit down and have a drink.
No thanks. I have other guests to attend to.
Enjoy your drinks.
Oh, by the way,
I'll have some good news for you in a few days.
What good news?
Tell us now!
I'll tell you in a few days.
Enjoy your drinks for now.
Alright, take care, Manager Tang.
I mean,
such a big guy
doesn't know his own strength.
Why are you making such a fuss?
He's just a manager.
You don't need to suck up to him like that.
You're criticizing way too many people.
When Manager Cui was here before,
didn't I respect him too?
No, well...
How can he compare to Old Cui?
We should respect people who deserve it.
Just look at him.
He doesn't look like a good person, right?
What gives you the right to say he's not a good person?
As if you're such a good person yourself.
Listen to yourself.
I'm not a good person.
Would you marry me?
If I weren't a good person,
would you marry me?
I'm not a good person.
I'm not a good person. Come on.
Let's eat.
Try some of these braised dishes.
These are the only decent things here.
The child is so cute.
Looks like a little piglet.
What?
I really envy you,
not having to worry about anything.
Look at me,
helping my sister raise my nephew.
Now
I've got Guo Dapao's daughter
and her father to deal with too.
I wish I could be like you,
doing math problems every day,
carefree
and happy.
You need to pay for it.
I told you I didn't want to play with you,
why did you insist?
Stop messing with it!
What's going on?
He broke the pinhole glasses
that I borrowed from my deskmate.
I told him many times
not to let him play with them,
but he insisted.
Glasses?
So they're broken.
Can't we just buy another pair?
Exactly.
This is high-tech stuff,
it costs over 100 yuan.
Alright, come on.
Come inside.
What high-tech stuff?
This costs over 100?
Why?
They say it's high-tech
and can cure nearsightedness.
I really didn't mean to.
Okay, don't cry.
We'll buy another one.
Those pinhole glasses are popular in schools now.
And my uncle spotted a business opportunity.
My uncle and aunt
went to my grandpa's house.
Guess
what my uncle is up to?
It doesn't matter.
Why doesn't it matter?
Whether my dad is chasing dogs or chickens,
is it really that important?
This time it's really promising.
Didn't you say the same thing about writing novels last time?
I bet it won't work out.
You two are always ganging up on me.
Dad's cooking is still the best.
The food at Dingqing Restaurant is terrible now.
You come here in the middle of the night
just to complain
that Dingqing Restaurant's food tastes bad?
I can't do anything about it anymore.
No, no,
that's not why I'm here.
Dad, look at this.
Aren't these the glasses that Erpang broke?
Why are they like this again?
You two are really something, father and son.
I want Dad to take a look.
What is this?
Where are the lenses?
Erpang broke them.
Just look at that part.
Try them on.
It gives you that 'seeing through a tube' feeling,
right? But this one
is what they call
high-tech pinhole glasses.
They sell for over 100 yuan outside.
This...
What's so high-tech about this?
You're absolutely right!
I've been studying it all day.
What high-tech?
It's fake!
What technical value could this possibly have?
The frames are just ordinary frames,
these lens materials
are available everywhere.
So, I have a bold idea.
You've got another one?
How long has it been since your last scheme?
You've sold singing performances,
set up chess stalls,
written books, and now what?
Selling glasses?
It's like this.
The cost of these things
is only about 5 yuan.
But they sell them for over 100 yuan in the market.
What an outrageous profit margin!
Aren't they just profiteers?
Isn't this taking advantage of people?
Over 100 yuan for
an average family
is not something everyone can afford.
What I want to do
is bring down the price
so every nearsighted child
can wear affordable pinhole glasses.
So you're saving all the kids in the city?
I want to save children across the country!
I'll price them at 19.9 yuan,
not even 20 yuan.
Ordinary families can definitely afford this.
The cost is only about 13 or 14 yuan,
so I make about 6 yuan gross profit.
No big problem, right?
You're like Huo Dongfeng
who makes money in the fish market
by marking up prices in the distribution chain.
He's making money,
but he doesn't create any value.
What I want to do is different.
I create value for society,
make a contribution,
and earn money at the same time.
This isn't just killing two birds with one stone.
It's three birds.
How much money do you need?
100,000 for startup capital.
How much do you have?
Less than 50,000.
Fine. I'll cover the rest.
Dad.
Dad's being generous.
Work hard.
If you're going to do it,
do something that benefits the country and the people.
Absolutely.
Who's coming with me tomorrow
to withdraw the money from the bank?
I will.
I think this time
I can make a fortune.
You
you're just not cut out for business.
All I care about now is
when your lawyer's license will come through.
You may be bad at business,
but you're good with words.
Once I get my license,
I'll represent Guo Dapao in court.
His case is tough,
but I'll become famous overnight.
After that,
many people will come looking for me.
I've already told
Guo Dapao's father
and his daughter about this.
You've already told them?
You told them before even passing the bar exam?
Can you please stop
counting your chickens
before they hatch?
That metaphor
is quite accurate.
But it's too crude.
You think that's crude?
Do you know before leaving work every day,
how much time I need to spend
preparing myself mentally?
So that when I come home and see you,
I can keep myself from yelling at you.
Just wait.
You'll be proud of me.
In the past,
Old Master Zhang from Dingqing Restaurant,
when he was alive,
used to say something.
Combining your passion
with making money,
that's what success is.
If you combine your passion
with losing money,
that's being wasteful.
I know your abilities.
You should
combine your talents
with making money
and be successful.
As for that factory job,
it's fine if you quit.
That's why I say
you're truly my father.
Just don't make your father
worry too much.
I'll walk you this far.
I need to get to the train station.
I've already booked tickets
to Wenzhou to purchase stock.
You're moving so quickly.
In martial arts,
speed is unbeatable.
Just watch me.
Since the reform and opening up,
our city's largest
independently operated state-owned restaurants
number only seven.
Now three of them
have already been contracted to private operators.
The higher authorities have instructed that
our Dingqing Restaurant
will also be privately contracted
and responsible for its own profits and losses.
Of course, this restaurant of ours
isn't something just anyone can contract.
There are certain requirements.
For example, the contracting fee
requires an upfront payment of 250,000.
I am definitely interested in taking the contract.
I promise that after I take over,
the remaining staff
will receive monthly salary increases of
150 to 300 yuan per person.
Of course.
This contract bidding
is open to the whole society.
Although I have high hopes,
I still hope everyone will support me.
We must support you.
In the early 90s,
the iron rice bowl of state-owned enterprises was broken.
Many factories were transferred to private contractors.
This was just the tip of the iceberg.
The clever ones seized business opportunities.
Individual small shops were increasing.
While everyone was still chatting idly in the factory.
They've already caught the scent of reform
and ventured into new businesses.
Sir, help me load these goods onto the truck.
To the factory. Thirty yuan.
Forty.
Thirty-five. Final offer.
Thirty-eight. Non-negotiable.
Thirty-seven and we go now.
Thirty-eight.
Let's go.
Is Guoming back yet?
Not yet, Dad.
He said he'd be home today.
I was worried something happened to Guoming.
He's fine.
Dingqing Restaurant
is switching to individual contracting.
Five years.
Who's getting the contract?
They say it's an open bidding process.
But before bidding,
you need to pay the first year's contract fee
in full,
250,000 yuan.
So when
do they need the payment?
Just these two months.
Has anyone taken the contract yet?
Manager Tang wants it.
If Dingqing Restaurant
falls into his hands, won't it be ruined, Dad?
Those two chefs have already left.
The regular customers are complaining.
Dad, let's take the contract.
You can continue as manager.
We don't have enough money.
Thank you.
Your surname is Cui, right?
You are...
You don't know me,
but I know you.
Who are you?
I know your brother-in-law, Huo Dongfeng.
A few days ago,
he just got out.
Before we could even meet,
I heard he went back in.
That man,
that's just his character.
Loyal.
He's never been locked up for his own mistakes,
always for his friends.
He's 47 this year.
Counting juvenile detention,
that's 24 years inside,
and 23 years outside.
Are you his friend?
Do you know about
the late 70s,
early 80s,
the Three Heroes of Dalin District?
You know them all?
Your brother-in-law was the First Hero,
I was the Second Hero.
The people sitting in front
are blocking my view.
Right away.
Here you are.
Cui.
My change?
No need for change.
We agreed on 38.
Please keep it.
I work for my money.
I'm not a beggar.
Brother Chuan.
Until we meet again.
See you around.
Dad, were you working at the construction site?
Why are you so dirty?
Isn't your father part of the working class?
What? Are you looking down on me?
Do you know
that workers created your
happy and beautiful life?
This TV, that pen,
erasers, pencil cases,
radios,
and everything in the kitchen:
knives, spoons, spatulas,
flashlights, candles, plates and bowls -
all of these were created by workers.
Which one did you create?
Very well.
Let me tell you,
I'll be creating things very soon.
Hehe.
What?
Uncle,
I know what you're planning.
Tell me.
Pinhole glasses.
I don't have anything against Manager Tang,
I just don't think he can manage
Dingqing Restaurant properly.
Dingqing is Dad's life's work
and where I've worked for over a decade.
I don't want to be the boss.
I just don't want to see
decades of reputation being ruined.
Can we
really bid for it?
Of course you can.
But you need 250,000.
There are only two months left.
What should we do?
Almost there.
What do you mean 'almost'?
Once I make money with my pinhole glasses,
we'll be close.
Go to sleep.
Tomorrow at 7 AM,
I'll get up and start working.
For someone like Uncle
who graduated from Engineering University,
making pinhole glasses was a piece of cake.
In just a few days,
he created
a product superior to anything on the market.
19.90!
Pinhole glasses for 19.90!
Pinhole glasses
for 19.90!
Pinhole glasses for 19.90!
Hey, Cui!
Pinhole glasses!
Miss Yang, what brings you here?
Just passing by.
What are you selling?
Pinhole glasses.
Pinhole glasses?
They protect your eyesight.
I make them myself.
You make them yourself?
Yes.
That's impressive.
Let me try them.
Go ahead.
So many holes.
Do I look good in them?
You look good in anything.
Of course.
How much?
19.90.
I'll buy one.
No, no.
You can't buy it.
Just take some, take some.
What do you mean 'take'?
19.90.
I want to support your business venture.
No way.
Put the glasses away first.
Hurry, let's go.
We're not taking them.
What are you-
Miss Yang, hurry!
No!
I need to pay-
Get in the car!
Get in, Miss Yang!
You can't do this!
Get in!
You scared me!
Go, quick!
I'll be going then, Brother Cui.
When it collapsed,
why didn't you warn me?
I did it on purpose.
Why?
Did you notify us before selling things here?
My name is Lv Jun.
I'm here every day.
Are you Lv Jun from the Dalin Three Heroes?
That's right.
Nice to meet you.
Goodbye.
These glasses
cost 100 outside.
I'll sell them to you for 12 yuan.
You can sell them for 19.9.
That's 8 yuan profit each.
You gave me 10 yuan last time.
And someone got stabbed here.
What kind of trouble are you getting into this time?
No stabbing this time.
Just making money.
I don't believe you.
You should.
Once you make money,
you'll believe me.
Fine.
I'll take two sets for now.
Is two sets enough?
I'm afraid I can't even sell two.
Wait.
Why are you closing the door?
I'm cold.
Open the door.
I'll keep 10 sets.
Fine.
So we have a deal.
Add 5 more sets.
15 sets?
Deal.
Dad,
how much have you
contributed to our family's better life today?
It's my first day.
I'm not very familiar with the business yet.
I sold 13 pairs.
You got over 10,000 pairs of glasses.
At this rate,
it'll take about three years
to sell them all.
I am
a good product manufacturer.
There's nothing wrong with my products,
but that doesn't mean I'm a good marketer.
I do lack skills in marketing.
Hehe.
Uncle, I'll help you sell them.
How will you help me sell them?
I'll take them to school to sell.
My classmates will definitely buy them.
You're very clever.
That's a good idea.
I'll give you 10 sets tomorrow first.
Final Trailer/EPK/MV/Behind-the-Scenes Production
Han Xueyi
Wang Qi
Post-Production Supervisor: Fan Lei
Peng Yanqiao
Guo Yue
Behind-the-Scenes Team
Xiangshang Xiaokong Chengxiang (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Deng Yulong
Short Video Marketing Company
Beijing Yichao Yixi Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Zhou Ying, Zhao Chunyu, Yang Rongxuan, Yu Shuangjie, Qin Mingxi, Wu Jiawen
Beijing Shiheng Yuexiang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Creative Planning: Liao Xingkai, Xue Yu, Zheng Yixin
Two Bits (Beijing) Technology Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Compositing
Beijing Zhongshi Northern Film and Television Production Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Compositing: Li Jianzhen, Geng Jin, Guo Yahui
Post-Production Company
Zeng Gong'an
Post-Production Coordinator: Yu Qiulan
Visual Effects Supervisor: Liu Yang
Digital Matte Painters: Qin Jiandong, Liu Mengxin
Li Jiaxiang
Post-Production
Zhao Yichen
He Zhaoyi
Guo Junshan
Special Effects Production Company
Beijing Liuguang Yicai Film and Television Technology Co., Ltd.
Production and Business Director: Yu Liang
Zhao Yuxia
Ren Yujia
Fan Luxi
Post-Production Coordinator: Xu Tao
Music and Sound Post-Production
Beijing Guandai Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Cheng Rang
Beijing Chenjia Shiyin Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Bai Ru
Featured Songs
"Date with the Stars"
Little Tigers
Liu Yitie
"Season of the Wind" (Cantonese Version)
Tang Zhengchuan
Original Copyright Owner: Subito Publishing Co.
Zhou Qiang
Adapted Music Production: Chen Jia
Performed by: Guo Jingfei
Tan Qiyin
Gou Yin
Harmony Design/Vocals: Liang Guchi
Zhou Taotao
Mastering Engineer: Quan Xiangyan
Zhong Zhirong
Huang Shujun
Original Copyright Owner: EMI MUSIC PUBLISHING HONG KONG
Wang Jie
Music Copyright Owner: Universal Music Publishing (China)
Hong Shirui
"Wedding Invitation Street"
Wong Wai-man
Zhou Qiang
Chuanzi
Chen Jia
"Ten Things That Shouldn't Be"
Copyright Belongs to: Changying Group Audio-Visual Publishing Co., Ltd.
Theme Song/End Credits: "Hey, Uncle"
Dong Baoshi
Rock
Filming Location Support
Changchun Wanda Film Industrial Park
FAW Foundry Co., Ltd. Black Casting Division Plant 2
School of Public Health, Jilin University
Nanling Campus Hospital, Jilin University
Jilin Petrochemical Design Institute
Changchun Sacred Heart Charity Hospital
Changchun Jingyuetan Experimental Forest Farm
Changchun Hualian Antique City
Changchun Victory Park
Lingyan Temple, Jilin City
Jilin Longtan Mountain Scenic Area Management Center
Xiaoer BBQ Hotpot & Roast Lamb, Jilin City
Jinxiaobao BBQ, Jilin City
Hadawan Seafood Wholesale Market, Changyi District, Jilin City
Xinfeng Yuening Film & Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen Godox Photo Equipment Co., Ltd.
Special Thanks
Publicity Department of CPC Anhui Provincial Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Jilin Provincial Committee
Jilin Provincial Radio and Television Bureau
Publicity Department of CPC Jilin Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Baishan Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Kuancheng District Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Luyuan District Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Chaoyang District Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Nanguan District Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Erdao District Committee
Party Working Committee of Changchun New Area
CPC Jilin Fengman District Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Jilin Changyi District Committee
Jilin Provincial Department of Culture and Tourism
Jilin Broadcasting and Television Station
Changchun Jingyue High-Tech Zone Administrative Committee
Changchun Public Security Bureau
Changchun Broadcasting and Television Station
Traffic Police Detachment of Changchun Public Security Bureau
People's Court of Changchun Economic and Technological Development Zone
People's Court of Erdao District, Changchun
Dehui Public Security Bureau
Jilin City Public Security Bureau
Jilin Train Operation Section, China Railway Shenyang Group Co., Ltd.
Changchun Train Operation Section, China Railway Shenyang Group Co., Ltd.
Dehui Railway Station
China FAW Group Co., Ltd.
FAW Jiefang Automotive Co., Ltd.
Changchun Film Studio Historical Site Museum Cultural Communication Co., Ltd.
Changchun Runde Investment Group Co., Ltd.
Nanhu Branch, Joint Logistics Support Force Hospital 964
Kaixuan Branch, Jilin Provincial People's Hospital
Jilin Provincial People's Hospital
Changchun International Convention & Exhibition Center (Group) Co., Ltd.
Changchun Vanke Real Estate Development Co., Ltd.
Changchun Xincheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Jilin Galaxy Hotel Co., Ltd.
Jilin Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Jilin Guoyuan Investment Holding Group Co., Ltd.
Jilin Railway Investment and Development Co., Ltd.
Jilin International Hotel Co., Ltd.
Copyright Notice: All rights to this work belong to Shanghai Tencent Penguin Film & Television Culture Communication
Shanghai Mingjian Film Co., Ltd.
Jilin Changchun Sanhao Film & Television Co., Ltd.
Production Support
Changchun Film Group Corporation
Jilin Broadcasting and Television Station
Beijing Mint Culture
Changchun Film Group Film Academy
Co-produced by
Tomato Film & TV
Beijing Zhengfu Film Co., Ltd.
Jilin Changchun Sanhao Film & Television Co., Ltd.