The doctor said I shouldn't drink.
It's fine. Drink.
One sip is better than none.
The doctor told you not to drink.
What's wrong with you?
At my age,
having some health issues
isn't that normal?
You scared me.
As long as you're okay.
You write such wonderful novels,
and you're so good at singing and dancing.
I'd like to know what else you can do.
This question...
You should ask differently.
You should ask me
what I can't do.
Or be more specific.
Can you cook?
In our city,
there's
a very famous restaurant
called Dingqing Tower.
My father
was the general manager there for decades.
I was abroad
and even ran a restaurant.
So do you think I can cook?
Can you play basketball?
In high school,
our school had a team,
and I was the captain.
I led my team
to win the provincial championship.
I've never met such an all-around talented person.
You know,
my whole life
I've known too many things.
But
I'm not good at anything. So
that's why I ended up like this,
a complete failure.
After meeting me,
you'll become successful.
I heard from Mr. Huo
that your wife passed away a long time ago.
Yes.
So you're single now.
I grew up abroad,
so I'm quite straightforward.
Hope you don't mind.
Can I be your girlfriend?
I admire that carefree spirit you have.
What year was your father born?
1955.
He is indeed a few years older than me.
Age isn't an issue.
As long as there's attraction.
Young lady,
are you serious?
I am serious.
Very serious.
Thank you.
Did I startle you?
Do you think someone like me
would be startled?
Then think about it.
I'm afraid I have to reject you.
You probably
haven't been rejected before, have you?
I'm too old
and not in good shape.
I don't have high expectations in that area.
It's not about that.
It's my health
that's very poor.
Since you've been so honest
with me about
what's on your mind,
in return,
I'll tell you a secret too.
You're
the first one to know.
I went to the hospital a few days ago.
They diagnosed me with lung adenocarcinoma,
terminal stage.
I've been
given a death sentence.
Are you that desperate
not to be with me?
Just to avoid being with me,
you'd tell such a terrible lie?
To reject you,
I wouldn't need to make up such a lie.
I really envy you and Erpang at your age.
It's wonderful.
In my life,
I've made too many people
suffer along with me.
You shouldn't
catch this last train.
I'm leaving.
Don't go.
Can you hug me?
Of course.
Can I stay here
and hear you sing 'Season of Wind' one more time?
I'll try my best
to sing it well for you.
Mr. Cui, I've told you so many times.
No deal.
Why do you keep pushing me like this?
If I don't push you, then who...
Our city has so many
newly opened commercial streets.
They not only don't make you
pay for renovation costs,
but also give you a rent-free period.
Isn't that a better deal?
That's different.
The original Dingqing Restaurant...
I'm begging you,
please stop coming here.
No matter how many times you come, I won't agree.
Dingqing Restaurant's original location is right here.
It used to be a restaurant.
Reopening a restaurant here
would definitely be good.
In the future,
people returning from other cities
or from abroad,
they'll want to taste this food again.
If Dingqing Restaurant is still here,
waiting for them right here,
that taste would be completely different.
But when they come back and see
this is a beauty salon,
imagine how disappointed they'll feel.
Don't you agree?
Wouldn't that be perfect?
They could get a beauty treatment here
and experience our city's
beauty techniques.
Let me tell you something,
young lady.
This is about nostalgia.
It's not just my nostalgia,
nor is it just someone else's.
It belongs to everyone in this city.
I was also born and raised in this city,
so why don't I feel this nostalgia?
You're too young.
Artificial flowers really can't...
No, no, miss.
Because what you're doing
affects the feng shui
and is bad for business.
My business is doing fine
without your concern.
Please reconsider.
Sir,
I have many customers waiting outside.
Why don't you look around somewhere else?
I'll go for now,
but I'll be back.
I will definitely
keep talking to you about this.
Because you...
Please.
Just think about it again, will you?
There's nothing to consider.
Mr. Huo.
Stop messing with me.
You keep pacing around
and it's driving me crazy.
You keep walking here
and it's making me anxious.
I'm just thinking about
company strategy.
The previous accountant
when he left
told me
there was 1 million in the account.
Then you started your second business
and left me with just 30%,
300,000.
Now with your third startup
it's another 30% cut,
100,000 yuan.
Let me tell you,
after paying salaries,
utilities,
and rent,
we can't even afford a bottle of water.
That's not your concern.
I'm the accountant.
If I don't worry, who will?
You know those employees
and the landlord,
they come to me asking for money.
What am I supposed to do?
Don't worry.
I have my ways.
This vertical e-commerce I'm talking about
is definitely the future
direction of internet development.
It's absolutely the next big thing.
Alright.
Stop talking to me about it.
I wouldn't understand anyway.
Let me confirm a few things with you.
You have local household registration, right?
I've checked your credit report.
No late payments.
You haven't borrowed money
from anyone else, right?
No, I haven't.
And that house from your grandfather,
you've been living there all along.
You have inheritance rights,
just haven't transferred the deed yet?
Correct.
Good.
150,000 for three months.
Pay interest monthly.
Okay.
When will you be free?
I'll explain everything to you then.
Miss Feng,
for the sake of my nostalgia,
could you sell your shop to me?
Please get up first, would you?
No, don't kneel on the ground.
I'm not kneeling.
My butt is right here on this.
Just sell the shop to me.
Look, sir,
I run a beauty salon.
I don't understand
anything about running restaurants
or this nostalgia thing you're talking about.
Young lady, nostalgia belongs to all humanity.
It's universal.
It has nothing to do
with beauty salons or restaurants.
Fine.
You come here every day saying the same few things.
Nostalgia.
My ears are getting calluses from hearing it.
If you sell the shop to me,
you won't get calluses anymore.
I won't sell it.
Absolutely not.
I'm just trying to convince you
to sell it to me.
When it was just you alone
upstairs, it was fine.
But now
you two grown men
sitting in my dining area,
how am I supposed to run my business?
That's exactly
my goal - to stop your business.
No, why are you being like this?
It's not like that.
No, no, that's not it.
Let's go.
I'll leave for today then.
How could I possibly get a perm?
I'll
come back again.
I'll definitely come tomorrow.
I really mean what I say.
I'll definitely come.
Please think about it carefully.
Please leave.
I'm begging you.
I heard their pancakes are really delicious.
Are they good?
Let me have a bite.
What makes a craft special?
It's simply about putting your heart into it.
When you make it with care,
it stands out from the rest.
Right?
I've been thinking
about renting that shop across from yours.
The landlady?
She won't agree.
Can you help me think
of any other solutions?
What solutions could I possibly have?
Shady tactics?
Sorry, buddy,
I left that life behind long ago.
I never said
I wanted you to use shady tactics.
Do I look like
someone who knows any other way?
I'm just brainstorming with you.
Please don't bother me.
I'm swamped. Look at this line.
Want green onions?
Yes.
This morning, all the suppliers
called me.
They said they're going to sue us.
Sue us!
And you're still smiling.
You're grinning like an idiot.
That stupid grin on your face.
Liu.
Tell me,
what major company
doesn't have lawsuits?
They are major companies.
You're just a big fraud.
Your phone is ringing.
Liu,
please step outside for a moment.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Why did it take you so long to answer?
I was in a board meeting.
Board meeting my ass!
When are you paying me back?
I need to
consult with the board to make decisions.
This isn't something
I can decide on my own.
Look,
could you please
be more polite when talking to me?
I've been plenty polite with you.
You've been promising to pay for a month now.
I haven't seen a penny yet.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Damn it!
Don't talk to me like that.
It's irritating.
Who do you think you are?
Have I disrespected you?
Talk to me properly, you hear me?
You little punk, where are you?
I'm coming to find you right now.
I'm at the company.
Come on over. I'll be waiting.
Fine. Wait for me.
Don't you dare run away.
I won't run.
If you don't show up, you're a coward.
Why do you keep calling?
Someone might come
to collect debt by force.
How did this happen?
Can you find some guys
to help me deal with this?
Where are you?
I'm at the office.
Okay, got it.
He's a man
and he's blind.
What are you going to do?
This guy looks so familiar.
Where have I seen him before?
You were in jail together.
Come with me. I need your help.
What for?
To solve some debt issues.
You've already taken this job?
Let's go.
Why are they leaving?
Abandoning the stall?
What about my pancakes?
Everyone should leave now.
How can you just leave like that?
You still owe me three months' salary.
I'll definitely pay you your salary.
Let's wrap this up.
If I don't get my salary back,
my wife and kids will leave me.
Brother Liu, you don't need to be so upset.
Boss, if you don't pay up,
I'll deal with you too.
Do you actually want to work for him?
I'll do whatever I want.
Alright, everyone calm down.
I understand how you feel.
But,
some debt collectors are coming soon
threatening to wreck our company.
I don't want to drag you all into this.
As for me...
No, Brother Liu, what are you doing?
I'll keep this for now.
Take it home and have a look.
Can you even carry that thing?
Where's the remote?
I'll bring it back when you're on your feet again.
What kind of person is this?
Boss, I believe you'll bounce back.
Stay strong!
Thanks.
Uncle.
Uncle, where are you?
Coming right away.
Your uncle says he's coming.
What's up?
Hey, you know,
don't you have some buddies in the streets?
Get a few of them over here.
Who?
Dapeng.
Dapeng?
Dapeng won't work.
I heard that Dapeng
got into some trouble a few years back,
got caught,
and they broke his leg.
Broke his leg?
What about Xiaofei?
Xiaofei?
He became a thief years ago.
Got locked up a while back.
Zhuzi's got a big crew.
Zhuzi won't work either.
I think Zhuzi
works at some farm now,
as a feeder
out in the countryside.
How did they all end up like this?
Come on!
What are you talking about?
'End up like this'?
Let me tell you, among all the guys,
I'm doing the best now.
I earn my living through honest work.
But I'm just
a pancake vendor, right?
Isn't that?
No, why are you asking me all this?
Where are we going?
You've got me confused.
You just said 'let's go'
so I came right away.
It's just a small matter.
Take off your apron first.
When we get there,
act like those tough guys
from the 90s.
Hey, who are you
calling a thug?
No, no.
Who's a thug?
I mean show some
heroic spirit, that's all.
That's more like it.
After being inside
for so long,
do you know anyone tough
who can intimidate people?
How about Scarface Ming?
I've heard of him.
He scares everyone.
He'll do.
He's perfect.
Get him.
He's serving life.
At least 20 more years.
If you need him urgently,
you two can help me break him out.
Damn, look at your stupid face.
Do you know how to talk?
If you can't speak properly,
shut your trap.
What kind of talk is that?
So irritating!
Who are you?
What do you mean 'who am I'?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at you, so what?
What do you mean 'so what'?
Don't hit me!
Stop fighting!
No, no, stop!
He's biting me!
Stop biting!
Stop fighting!
Uncle, hurry up!
Everyone's already downstairs.
Bro.
Hey.
You! Get down here!
Don't go!
Take one more step and I'll jump.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
Jumping off?
Fine. I won't interrupt your business.
Listen.
I need to ask you something.
Can I ask before you jump?
Go ahead.
Weren't you
shouting orders on the phone,
dragging me all the way here
just to watch you
livestream your suicide?
You're the one who pushed me to this.
Who pushed you?
I'm going to force you.
I should make you jump from the 20th floor.
Why would I make you jump from the 2nd floor?
Am I crazy?
I won't die jumping headfirst from the 2nd floor.
If I die, you'll have to pay with your life.
Pay?
If you really die today,
I'll really pay with my life, okay?
Go ahead and jump.
Too scared to jump?
If you don't dare to jump, then listen,
pay back what you owe me today.
Then I'll livestream for you.
I'll jump instead, okay?
Come on.
I'll go up there.
Don't pull this on me.
Pay me back and I'll come down.
No, no, no.
Come on.
Don't pull this stunt on me.
What stunt?
Do you really think I won't jump?
No, you think I'm afraid of you, don't you?
How could I be afraid of you?
Come on, jump. I'll sit right here today.
I'll watch you jump with my own eyes.
So you're really going to jump today?
I'll give you a discount.
How's that?
How much?
3,000.
I'll consider it payment
for my boys to watch a monkey show.
Deal?
Deal.
Come on.
Look at you every day,
acting like you're from a TV show,
like Ke Zhen'e.
Talking the toughest game
then taking the worst beating.
What kind of habit is this?
Are you addicted to it?
Are you jumping or not?
Are you going to jump?
Don't mess around.
Jump or not?
Stop messing with me.
Who's messing with you? Jump!
I said I'm messing with you.
Stop!
Are these three your friends?
What kind of people are these?
Young man, you need to speak politely.
Show some respect.
I'm his uncle.
No.
You look only
about 30 or 40 years old.
How can you be
Tell me
who you used to hang out with.
After you tell me,
I'll see if I know them.
Well, I
like to study Buddhism in my spare time.
If you ask who I hang out with,
let's just say monks.
Which organization are you three from?
The Sunset Years Club?
Have you heard of my name?
I'm called Dog Intestine.
What intestine?
Dog.
Wangwang.
Did you see it?
It's a C-section.
Let me tell you again.
A few years ago, I got into a fight.
Many of my intestines were stabbed and cut.
When I got to the hospital,
the Western doctors said they couldn't save me.
But my family
found an old Chinese doctor
who replaced mine with dog intestines.
I don't have many years left to live.
I've come to terms with death.
Now let's look at this one.
Just from his appearance,
he just came back from abroad.
Don't laugh.
He committed a crime,
just returned from overseas,
fled abroad after seriously injuring someone,
and only came back after the statute of limitations expired.
Now look at this one.
This guy is even more impressive.
A murderer.
One slash, instant death.
Stop, stop, stop.
I...
Listen.
I don't care if you're Dog Intestine or whatever,
so you're back from abroad, right?
I don't care if you're from overseas
or somewhere in this country,
it's none of my business.
Even if you were a ladyboy today,
you better keep your mouth shut.
Hey, you, the quiet one,
I'm talking to you.
So you're a murderer, huh?
Your knife skills must be good.
Carve me a radish sometime.
Not you three.
If I weren't considering your age,
I would've buried you all by now.
This is none of your business. Get out of here.
Get lost!
Young man.
Don't talk nonsense.
Tell me
what will it take for you to release him?
Did I kidnap him?
Look,
he owes me money.
It's been overdue for over a month.
Won't even answer my calls.
Keeps dodging me, then suddenly calls.
My mom's stuff is still in there.
Insisted on meeting up with me.
Wanted me to come so we could 'talk it out.'
So I came.
And now he's sitting on the windowsill.
Too scared to jump down.
Won't jump from the second floor.
You're his uncle, right?
Yes.
This kid...
How did you raise him when he was young?
Just tell me what you want today.
Listen, uncle.
I've been in this business for over ten years.
I've never used violent collection methods before.
But this kid is just too infuriating.
He's really infuriating.
Don't fight. You want trouble?
You think we three old men are easy targets?
You young people nowadays
don't fight, you just swing wildly.
Have you ever
seen real kung fu before?
Today he won't join in.
Just us three.
Yes, you four or five guys.
Let's go downstairs and show our skills.
It's too cramped here.
Alright.
Let's find a place with better feng shui.
Let's go, Erpang.
Okay, coming.
Hurry, follow your uncle.
Come on, let's stretch a bit.
The event has started.
Did they run away?
You stay here and lay low for now.
And take care of these two while you're at it.
You know what, Uncle?
These two look quite similar to us.
How so?
They dress like us.
And have identical hairstyles.
I thought you were saying I snore too.
Erpang.
When you're in the mountains,
you must learn how to make fire.
For your food and warmth.
We have to rely on this stove.
Mountain water can't be drunk cold.
It must be boiled first.
So making a fire
Have you learned how?
I have.
Uncle,
could this stove
set the house on fire?
Theoretically, yes.
I've never tried it.
You probably won't try either.
You don't have the guts.
Why wouldn't I?
What if I do someday?
Then congratulations to you.
Uncle.
How long do I have to hide here?
Wait until I sort this out.
When will you sort it out?
I don't know.
How do you plan to fix it?
Then
what am I supposed to do?
How much money do you owe?
Don't ask.
I really don't know.
Besides, you can't help me pay it back anyway.
How much do you owe your employees?
That
needs to be paid first.
They all
have families to support.
I'll cover it for you first.
The employees' wages aren't much.
Ask our accountant Liu and he'll tell you.
Erpang.
Did you know when you were eleven months old,
you won the city-wide
baby crawling championship?
So young,
yet such a glorious achievement.
This proves
you were born extraordinary.
Among your peers,
no one
can surpass you.
Just think, at such a young age,
you've already achieved such remarkable success.
Sooner or later,
you'll win another championship.
Dapao, let me sing you a song.
We are the Three Dogs Band
from Rabbit Hole Mountain.
Full Body Oil Massage
(Full Body Massage
Palace Body Massage
Foot Salt Scrub, Back Walking)
Tomorrow
you'll have a chance to change your fate.
The reason for all this
is because of that one cut you made.
I didn't kill Boren,
but he died because of me.
What's up?
You're looking for me?
I need to talk to you.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
That fortune teller who scammed me,
remember him?
I do.
He's right in there.
Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure.
Very sure.
It's definitely him.
Wait here.
I'll check for you.
Your lower back strain is quite serious.
What do you do for a living?
I'm a truck driver.
I thought so.
Sitting for over ten hours at a time,
no wonder it's so bad.
My life is hard.
How so?
My wife passed away early.
I have to raise two children.
One is mine,
and one is my sister's.
My nephew, that chubby kid,
gives me nothing but trouble.
It's too much.
You speak so eloquently,
so measured and calm.
You shouldn't be doing such hard labor.
Haven't you consulted a fortune teller?
What? A fortune teller?
Does that even work?
Well, this thing,
it works if you believe, and doesn't if you don't.
I learned a bit when I was younger.
My master said I had the gift.
Perhaps I revealed too many heavenly secrets,
and now my eyesight is failing.
These days,
I just do massages,
hardly read fortunes anymore.
How much do you charge for a reading now?
Same as a massage, 198 yuan.
That's quite expensive.
198 yuan,
but if my reading isn't accurate,
you don't have to pay.
Alright, I'll try it.
Tell me your birth details.
July 6, 1960.
At 2:30 in the morning,
born in this city.
Although you were born during
the Three Years of Hardship,
you never went hungry as a child.
Compared to other children at that time,
you ate quite well, didn't you?
Yes.
And you have an exceptional destiny.
You're multi-talented
and write excellent articles.
Do you know that you are
the reincarnation of Han Xiangzi's young page?
Has anyone ever told you?
What? Getting excited?
You mean Han Xiangzi from the Eight Immortals?
Of course.
You were sent to earth
because you broke his inkstone.
That's why you're so talented,
but have no place to use your skills.
When you were young,
things went quite smoothly.
But in middle age,
your career suddenly became rocky.
Running here and there,
I do all kinds of fortune-telling.
Do you know me?
I'm just a blind man.
How would I know anyone?
You really can tell fortunes.
You be the judge of my skills.
But let me tell you something privately.
I think you're a good person,
kind-hearted.
You've helped quite a few people in your life, haven't you?
He helped me today.
Who?
Fortune telling.
Just casual talk.
Not very accurate.
Why bother if your predictions aren't accurate?
Hey, you called me over.
I did your fortune.
Do I have some grudge against you?
Come here. Open your eyes
and look at who I am.
How can I tell who you are?
I'd be happy just to see you beat me up.
Why are you yelling at me?
You don't remember who I am, right?
Let me help you remember.
September 1993.
Didn't you tell fortunes
for a pork seller
by the river?
I've been fortune-telling for over 40 years.
I've been everywhere.
Think carefully.
Five in the morning by the river.
The Zhen position.
You told me to burn three yellow talismans
that would rise to the heavens.
Then wash my hands in the river.
And then it was done.
You told me I'd never worry about food or clothing,
that I'd be successful in my later years
and become famous.
Isn't that what you said?
Remember?
I remember now.
Was my prediction wrong?
I admit it.
So you admit it?
Let's go to the police station.
What for?
Why should I go to the police station?
What? Why?
Go to the police station?
What police station? What for?
Do you know?
Do you know who I am?
Just because of those few words you said,
I spent over ten years in prison.
Over ten years behind bars!
What did you do
to get locked up for so long?
I didn't do anything!
I did exactly what you told me.
I threw a knife in there.
The day after I threw the knife,
a female corpse floated up.
How could I explain that to the police?
I told them it was a fortune teller
who told me to do it.
I told them everything.
After I told them, they went looking for you
but couldn't find you. Where did you go?
Where were you?
Wandering the world.
Where else can I go?
What are you doing here?
Why are you looking for me?
You're here for money.
More than 20 years have passed.
Let's go to the police station.
I won't go.
Go? What would I do at the police station?
Me at the police station?
Can I report you for feudal superstition?
I'm just asking if my fortune-telling was accurate.
What accuracy are you talking about?
You spent over ten years in prison.
While you were in there,
didn't they feed you?
Didn't they give you uniforms to wear?
Nothing to say now, right?
You call that
living without worries?
Living comfortably.
That's what I call.
So what?
One day this case gets overturned.
The internet is so powerful nowadays.
Once the case is overturned,
you'll become famous throughout the world.
What's wrong with that?
Can I just kill him?
No, no, no. Calm down first.
No, I've already been sentenced to more than 10 years.
If I beat him up, that's what he'll get.
That makes sense in theory and logic.
Whose side are you on anyway?
Beating or cursing him now won't help.
You might end up back in prison.
What you should do now
is bring him to the police station.
To testify for you.
On your part,
he really spent over a decade in prison
because of what you said.
We're still appealing the case.
So we need your statement.
Once you're there,
you'll only talk about his case.
Whatever you've done in the past
has nothing to do with this.
You're a fortune teller.
I believe
and you believe too
that karma exists,
right?
Dapao.
What?
Take this.
What's this for?
Take it.
I took 50 yuan from you back then.
Now I'm giving it back.
But prices have changed.
Why are you bringing this nonsense up?
Even now,
I still believe my fortune-telling was correct.
It was clearly about you.
Free from worries about food and clothing,
living comfortably.
How dare you mention this?
I need to have the courage to tell you what comes next.
Remember this:
The day of vindication
will be when you become famous
and renowned throughout the land.
What about my fortune-telling fee?
I'll give it to you too.
Let's talk about fate.
Come visit me often in the future.
Keep coming back here,
I'll continue for free.
No need for free service.
Next time when I need you to testify,
just show up.
About testifying,
I'll come whenever you call.
But brother, you...
Brother, what's
wrong with me?
You might face a calamity.
Can it be avoided?
Life in this world
is nothing but suffering.
Finding release sooner
might not be such a bad thing.
Erpang.
I thought you really committed suicide.
I thought debt collectors had chased me all the way here.
How could you get instant noodles
all over your head?
Why didn't you make a fire?
I don't know how.
The fire went out soon after you left that day.
Then how did you cook the noodles?
I didn't cook them.
I ate them dry.
Then a bite of noodles and a sip of wine.
A bite of noodles and a sip of wine.
It's quite satisfying.
The biggest difference between us and animals is
that we know how to use fire.
I know how to use fire too.
But there's no fire here.
There'll be hot food later.
I'll just have a few bites first.
How long has it been since you've eaten?
I can't remember.
Two or three days.
Maybe three or four.
Time passes easily in the mountains,
while a thousand years of prosperity have passed in the world.
With that attitude of yours,
you wouldn't starve even if you didn't eat for ten years.
When did your phone get disconnected?
I really don't know.
I think it's actually better this way.
Saves me from all those annoying calls.
Don't just eat by yourself.
How long have the dogs gone without food?
I haven't eaten for days.
So they haven't eaten for days either.
Uncle, if you hadn't come,
we would've all starved to death up here.
Hurry up and grab a sausage
to satisfy their hunger first.
I'll cook you all a proper meal.
The steps and methods for lighting the stove
Have you got it all clear?
Yes, I got it.
Uncle.
Actually, these quilts are thick enough.
As long as I don't turn over,
I won't feel cold at all.
I just can't stick out of the covers.
It's too miserable when I do.
Anyway, I've taught you how to light the stove.
Whether you do it or not is up to you.
Here you go.
Is today Spring Festival?
Tomorrow.
Mengmeng is coming back.
I'll celebrate the New Year with her.
Originally,
we should be together,
but I'm afraid if you're here,
the creditors might come too,
and that would frighten Mengmeng.
Why is Mengmeng still so fragile?
You're not fragile.
You're hiding in the mountains.