Li
Li Yang
Liu
Hey.
Stop rushing me. I just uploaded it.
I even wrote 500 more words today.
I still have to go up the mountain every day.
Dig for wild ginseng and feed the dogs.
I come back at night without even eating dinner.
Just to write novels for you.
I am indeed your uncle.
But you can't work me to death.
No.
My grandfather wants someone to come keep him company.
I have to go out tonight to interview an executive.
You're going to a nightclub for interviews at this hour?
How did you know?
All those executives of yours,
aren't they all recruited from nightclubs?
No, not a single one was recruited from nightclubs.
Besides, the person I'm interviewing today is a man.
When dealing with talent, shouldn't we be
enthusiastic and generous?
I'm going to entertain him.
Fine.
I'll go.
Uncle, you're finally here.
So now you're recruiting talents
from nightclubs, huh?
Well, for executives, what can I do?
I'm just showing respect to talented people.
How's the website doing?
I see my article only got about 500 clicks.
And that includes our own people
who clicked over 300 times.
What's the point then? Let's just quit.
Look at Liu Bei.
When he was being chased everywhere,
did he give up hope?
No, he didn't.
Not only did he keep going,
he also sought out Zhuge Liang.
He visited Zhuge Liang's cottage three times.
And what happened in the end?
The Battle of Red Cliffs was a huge success,
forming the Three Kingdoms with Eastern Wu and Cao Wei.
You should talk less.
No, Grandpa,
I'm just explaining a truth to my uncle.
Do you know what your uncle's
biggest problem is?
I know, but I'm younger,
I can't say it. You should.
Your uncle's biggest problem
is that he has too many skills,
too many ideas,
no persistence in anything he does,
and in the end, he doesn't do anything well.
Erpang.
Do you know what
your biggest problem is?
I don't know.
Your biggest problem
is that you have no skills,
but you have plenty of ideas.
Dad, you're absolutely right.
Dad.
What should we do?
Anyway, I think I can do well.
This guy just fell asleep sitting up.
He can fall asleep just leaning on his arm.
I'm not sleeping. I'm going back to my room.
You talked your grandfather to sleep.
You're something else.
I'm heading out now.
Where are you going?
To a job interview.
Then why did you ask me to come?
I didn't ask you.
Grandpa asked me to call you.
I need to hurry, Uncle.
What are our website's
unique visitors and page views this week?
Lucy, this should be your responsibility,
shouldn't you know this?
Yes, it is my responsibility,
but I can't give you the exact figures.
Hold on.
Uncle.
I need to discuss something with you.
I'm in a meeting right now.
I'm just outside.
Come out.
Alright.
I'll be right there.
Uncle, I'm really in a meeting.
You know, except for disbandment meetings,
all other meetings are meaningless.
What do you want from me anyway?
Your grandfather
I don't think he has much time left.
I want your mother to come back.
You can make that decision yourself.
Then give her a call.
I won't call her.
You call her.
You're her son.
You should be the one to call.
You're closer to her than I am.
Weren't you abroad recently
and spent time with her?
I'm not calling her anyway.
If someone has to call, you do it.
Someone has to call her.
I'm going upstairs now.
Mr. Huo.
Our new company has been operating
for over four months now,
and we only have a little over 100,000 yuan left in the account.
How much money has our new company
spent since we opened?
Over 1.34 million.
What are we going to do about next month's payroll?
Alright, I understand your concern.
You should head home early.
I'll be going then, Mr. Huo.
Hello? Who's this?
Hello?
My name is Zhou.
Are you the person in charge of Qigou Literature Website?
Yes, that's me.
Sorry to bother you so late.
I have some business matters
I'd like to discuss with you.
You mean about product placement, right?
No, I wanted to ask
if you would consider selling your website?
What?
Excuse me?
Would you consider selling your website?
As long as the price is reasonable,
we can discuss it.
Great.
Would it be convenient for me to visit your company?
Sure.
Would Monday next week work?
Yes, no problem.
I'll send you the address.
Is Gu Longju your contracted writer?
Yes, exclusive contract.
Lifetime contract.
Would it be possible for me to meet him too?
That's no problem at all.
Not an issue.
Mr. Huo.
Hello.
You must be Miss Zhou.
Yes.
I'm Huo Xiaoyang.
Hello.
Let's
go upstairs
to talk.
Okay.
This way, Miss Zhou.
Miss Zhou.
Over here.
Please come in.
Let me introduce you.
This is Miss Zhou from Beijing.
Miss Zhou's company
has been acquiring distinctive companies like ours
in the cultural and artistic website sector.
Of course,
we're very grateful to Miss Zhou
for her interest in our website.
Now, let's have our colleague Lucy
give us a brief introduction about our company.
Our company was established in November.
Excuse me, I need to interrupt.
Darling, please put your clothes on first.
Please sit.
I came from Beijing early this morning.
Besides learning from everyone
about operating
this literary website,
my main purpose is to meet
the author Gu Longju.
Mr. Huo, didn't I tell you before coming
that I wanted to meet Gu Longju?
I've arranged for us to meet him
during lunch.
It's already 11 o'clock now.
Why don't we start lunch early?
I have a 2:30 flight back to Beijing,
and I have a meeting there.
Then we'll skip the company introduction.
The true core of any literary website is always the creators.
The company presentation is very good.
Please send it to my email.
I'll study it carefully when I get back.
Sure.
Remember this.
Remember to send it to her later.
Let's eat first.
Miss Zhou, rest assured.
Although we currently only have Gu Longju,
we believe that
in the future, more and more
excellent writers like Mr. Gu
will join our team.
Where does your confidence come from?
Our original intention for creating this website
It's about providing these talented creators
with the best environment
and the most generous compensation.
Excuse me.
As a professional internet investor,
I'd like to be honest with you
if that's okay?
Your Qigou Literature website, from its design to its concept,
is quite frankly
extremely crude
and very amateurish.
There are not just 10,000,
but probably 8,000 similar sites out there.
If we only look at the value of your website,
it's not worth much,
not much at all.
Then why did you
come all the way from Beijing
and want to acquire our website?
Because of the writer Gu Longju.
Because of your contract with him.
Of course, don't be discouraged.
You have good taste,
signing an author like him.
It's really impressive.
His writing style is truly unique
and distinctive.
I believe that someday
he will become one of the greatest
professional writers on the Chinese internet.
Of course.
This Gulongju,
Actually, at first
I suggested he write about tomb raiding,
but he insisted on writing martial arts fiction.
The genre doesn't matter.
What matters is writing well.
So, when is he coming?
Artists,
they all have this bad habit of being late.
Erpang.
This...
This guy must have gotten lost.
Erpang is...
Mr. Huo.
This is Miss Zhou from Beijing,
who came specifically to acquire our company.
Not to acquire the company.
I'm acquiring their website.
You are?
This is the Gu Longju you've been looking for.
Teacher Gu, pleased to meet you.
I came specifically to see you.
Pleased to meet you.
So you two already know each other?
Erpang this year is...
Mr. Huo this year is...
Twenty-six... twenty-five years old.
So we've known each other for 25 years.
Known him since birth.
I'm his uncle.
I see.
No wonder.
So Mr. Gu, are you a professional writer?
No, I'm not.
What do you do for a living then?
I grow wild ginseng professionally.
And I breed Tibetan mastiffs as a hobby.
You're from Beijing.
There are many rich people there.
They must be into dogs too.
The market for Tibetan mastiffs is excellent.
This one is a Black Pearl.
Good breed and fierce.
If your friends there need one,
you can recommend me.
They can come to me for breeding services.
It's very powerful.
Okay, but we can't afford such luxury right now.
You just mentioned 'now',
so what did you do before?
I was an engineer before.
And later,
well, to tell you the truth,
you'd have to ask me what I was doing in a specific year and month.
Because I've worked in
more than 20 different industries.
Do we even have that many industries in our country?
I've been involved in some overseas projects too.
Yes, my uncle has lived abroad for over ten years.
No wonder your style
looks quite distinctive.
Alright then.
Let's get down to business.
Are you looking to acquire his website?
Rather than acquiring his website,
I'd say
I'm interested in buying your copyright.
You see, I'm not really interested in his website.
I'm mainly interested in your work.
The main reason I came today was to meet you,
to see if there's a chance to sign you directly,
to make you our contracted author.
I... no signing,
no contracts. I'm not a professional writer.
I only write because he forces me to.
Let's get down to business.
How much are you willing to pay for his website?
If Teacher Gu completes the serialization of his work,
I can offer up to 300,000.
No, no.
Miss Zhou,
we've done the calculations.
From the founding of this website until now,
we've invested nearly
1.3 million.
The logic of capital
is never about how much you invest,
but how much you're worth.
If Mr. Gu completes the serialization of his work,
I can offer up to 300,000.
But if you think it's not suitable,
then we'll stay in touch.
If one day your website improves,
you can come back to me.
Does that work for you?
Or would you rather look elsewhere?
Okay, okay.
Good.
Just 300,000.
Then my conditions must be met.
Mr. Gu must complete the serialization of his work.
Important things need to be said three times.
This is already the third time I'm saying it.
That's no problem at all.
Wait a moment.
Before you agree to her request,
you need to agree to one condition of mine first.
I'll finish writing this serial.
You need to fire all those
decorative employees
from your company.
Just keep one legal and finance person
and an assistant.
Will you do it?
I mean,
is that okay?
Just tell me if you'll do it or not.
Yes, I will.
Then I have no issues.
Have you really not considered becoming a professional writer?
No, I can't do that.
Being forced to write
is painful enough already.
If I had a contract binding me as well,
I probably wouldn't live much longer.
I respect that.
Make sure you keep your promise to me.
Thank you. Thank you.
That's enough now.
Let me drive you to the airport.
No need,
we can take a taxi ourselves.
I'm going to the mountains to feed my dogs. It's on the way.
Then I won't refuse.
Let's go.
Miss Zhou.
About the dogs,
I'm not joking with you.
They're good dogs.
Sorry,
the AC in this car is broken.
It's fine.
Actually, with your talent,
you should be driving a Bentley or something.
The car you drive doesn't matter.
Being happy is what matters.
You mentioned earlier that you've worked in
more than 20 industries.
Could you elaborate on that?
I was a singer,
but not a star.
A nightclub singer.
Really?
More than ten years ago, around here,
nightclubs were very popular.
In those nightclubs,
Cantonese songs were all the rage.
I sing Cantonese songs at nightclubs.
Could you sing a bit for us?
Sure.
Fragrant but expensive.
I'm up in the mountains.
I'll write it when I get home.
That's not what I'm calling about.
I just called Grandpa.
He didn't answer.
I'm busy right now.
Why don't you go check on him?
Alright, I understand.
Dad.
What are
you doing?
Why are you shaking me like that?
I was just
taking a nap on this old plaque.
You scared me sleeping like that.
Why are you lying on this thing?
I don't know either.
How did I end up on this plaque?
I just had a dream
that Dingqing Restaurant reopened.
I dreamed your mother came back too.
Even old Mr. Zhang returned.
Only your sister wasn't there.
Then I'll call her to come back.
No need.
How are you feeling?
I feel like
my time might be coming to an end.
Seventy-three to eighty-four is a critical time.
I'm afraid I won't make it past this hurdle.
Stop talking nonsense.
What hurdle are you talking about?
I know my own body.
At my age,
being able to die in my own bed
would be a good ending.
My grandchildren are all grown up,
my granddaughter is almost getting married.
I have no regrets.
That's enough, Dad. Stop talking, you're wasting energy.
I want to say a few words.
Are you still trying to control me?
Go ahead, speak.
If I have any regrets,
there is one.
Old Master Zhang instructed me before he died
to keep Dingqing Restaurant running for a hundred years.
To pass down this culinary craft.
But now,
Dingqing Restaurant is gone,
and no one in our family is in this profession.
I've really let Old Master Zhang down.
So,
after I'm gone,
burn this old signboard.
Half for Old Master Zhang,
and half for me.
When I'm in the underworld,
I'll apologize to Old Master Zhang.
This one,
keep it safe.
Just in case
someone in our family
wants to become a chef someday,
give it to them.
In this society,
no matter when,
we'll always need chefs.
People need to eat.
With this skill,
you'll never starve.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Sounds like a last will.
No, but what if one day I suddenly drop dead?
How can there be a sound if you're dead?
A cracking sound?
Alright,
go about your business.
Let me rest on this old signboard
for a little while longer.
Guoming.
Your blonde hair looks really good. Very stylish.
You're the only one
in our family who says that.
Well, I am your sister after all.
You should dye your eyebrows too.
Make them blonde as well. It'll look even better.
Really?
Trust me.
I'll give it a try.
How long can you stay this time?
I quit my job to come back.
I'll stay for a while.
That's great.
Spend more time with Dad.
Which district is this?
It's so well developed.
Longshan District.
It's even better than abroad.
That's why I keep saying China is so good now.
Why do you have to
stay abroad all the time?
There wasn't a day I didn't want to come back.
It's not that simple.
Dad always says
if you never return to China,
you're either a traitor
or a deserter.
I'm definitely not a traitor.
So I guess I'm a deserter.
You can explain that to Dad yourself.
Go tell him
that you're a deserter.
Fine.
Lying on the plaque again.
Dad,
look who's back.
You've taken Uncle Liu home already?
Yes, I have.
Alright then.
What have you been up to lately?
I made a website and sold it.
How much did you sell it for?
Only 300,000.
Have you visited your father recently?
I go every month.
In about another year,
he should be released.
Has he changed?
Not really.
Just a lot more gray hair.
Do you have any photos of him?
No.
Could I go see him?
Probably not possible.
Only immediate family members can visit.
I'm not considered immediate family?
Have something to eat.
I'm not eating today.
Xiaohong,
where are you?
No matter what others say,
you'll always be Mom's good child.
Sis,
come home with me.
Let's call him
Erpang,
okay?
What I promised you,
I will definitely make it happen.
Ms. Zhou
Coming!
What are you looking for?
Where's my dad?
He went to a meeting at the Business Administration Bureau.
Ms. Zhou
I need some soup.
My mom is sick.
Manager Cui already paid when he left.
The soup is cooking.
It'll be ready in half an hour.
Just wait a bit.
Alright.
Didn't you order dumplings?
I know.
I also know your name is Huo Dongfeng.
Do you want garlic?
I can peel it for you.
What's up?
Hey girl,
are you Cui Xiaohong?
Wait there,
I'll come down to find you.
Gentlemen,
please tell me if you need anything.
This doesn't concern you.
Shut up.
What a surprise,
running into you here.
You're quite famous.
Famous for what?
Beautiful, pretty, and attractive.
Like I need you to tell me.
I got two movie tickets today.
Look, the movie's starting.
We still have half an hour.
Come watch the movie with me.
Three people, two tickets.
How are we supposed to watch?
Here's the deal,
choose one of us.
I can't choose.
Why can't you choose?
I'm not interested in either of you.
What are you laughing at?
Eat your dumplings.
Think carefully about your choice.
I'm quite handsome, you know.
Have you finished peeling?
Yes.
What exactly are you trying to do?
You think this store
belongs to you?
It's my family's business.
My dad is the general manager here.
Stop talking about managers and all that nonsense.
I asked you to watch a movie with me
and now you're finding problems with it?
I'm going to choose today.
I've decided on this one.
What are you doing?
I just want to watch a movie.
Let go.
What are you doing?
Someone come quickly!
Zhang!
Help!
Someone help!
I'll kill you!
Help! Somebody!
Murder!
Stop! Don't run!
Call for help!
Call for help now!
My name is Cui Xiaohong.
Where's your brother?
My brother?
I thought you were inviting me to a movie.
He's starting school soon.
Let him study instead.
Let's go.
So all the theaters around here
are accessible to you?
Don't you believe it?
What's wrong, bro?
That happened too quickly.
Where is he?
It's nothing.
It's fine.
How much did you make today?
This.
A little over 20.
Here.
All the money you earned today is yours.
Buy some food for the guys.
Thanks, bro.
Go on.
Go.
Brother,
what happened?
Perfect timing.
I brought you the money for the movie tickets.
Keep it for yourself.
Buy some cigarettes and drinks for the guys.
If you say so.
Here.
Brother, I was reading a book recently
called 'Beacon Fire Mocks the Lords.'
So you're
just messing with us, aren't you?
Had enough?
Stop wasting time.
Get to work.
Alright,
let's go.
Selling movie tickets?
Sometimes I charge five cents extra.
Sometimes ten cents extra.
Profiteering! Troublemaker!
Are you going to arrest me?
Well, you're not wrong if you put it that way.
But I can guarantee you.
People who come to these theaters
won't lose their money.
Thieves are afraid of me.
I'll beat any one of them.
I'll beat a whole gang if they come.
Then why am I not afraid of you?
It's just that when I come here to watch movies in the future,
I'll have face being with you.
That goes without saying.
What are we watching?
Shaolin Temple.
Why don't I just look at you instead?
Guoming,
call your dad's workplace when you get to school.
Okay. Pass the ball!
Why call?
Afraid I'll get lost?
You're the one who gets lost.
These past few days you told Mom and Dad
you were staying at a classmate's house.
Where were you really staying?
You think I don't know?
Where was I staying?
I think Huo Dongfeng
is a pretty good guy.
I admire him too.
But his looks,
he doesn't look like someone from our Cui family.
What do you know?
I don't know,
those people who hang out in the streets,
whether he is one of them.
He looks like...
When he's with you,
he looks like your uncle, you know?
That's not important.
What matters is he's always fighting with people.
If he's not fighting,
he's on his way to a fight.
Living for today with no thought of tomorrow.
You can admire him,
that's fine, but living with him?
Mom and Dad would be terrified.
Are you scared?
What would I be scared of?
I'm not the one dating him.
Then that settles it.
Think about it some more.
I've already decided. It's him.
As long as you're happy.
Thanks for your effort.
I think
you should just keep it casual.
Huo Dongfeng
You don't want us to live anymore, do you?
If you say I don't want you to live,
then I don't want you to live.
Others may fear you,
but I, Xiasi, don't fear you.
Get him!
What are you doing, Huo Dongfeng?
I don't feel well.
How much longer do we have to hide here?
We need to wait until things cool down.
The police know about my place.
They're waiting to ambush me.
Good news!
Are you two having more children than allowed?
It's fine.
My wife is a midwife.
Let me know if you need anything.
I'm broke and can't afford food.
You need to eat something decent.
That's your problem then.
Of course it's my responsibility.
Honey.
What's wrong?
What happened here?
What's the matter?
Why is it so hot?
What should we do?
What should we do? What medicine should we take?
I don't know.
You're the doctor.
How can you not know?
Well, I'm not omnipotent.
I can't cure this disease.
Why can't you?
Beijing Yige Guangmang Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Chen Siwei
Wang Qi
Peng Yanqiao
Guo Yue
Side Shooting Team
Xiangshang Xiaokong Chengxiang (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Deng Yulong
Short Video Marketing Company
Beijing Yichao Yixi Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Zhou Ying, Zhao Chunyu, Yang Rongxuan, Yu Shuangjie, Qin Mingxi, Wu Jiawen
Marketing Agency
Beijing Shiheng Yuexiang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Exclusive Data Strategy
Liangbite (Beijing) Technology Co., Ltd.
Post-production Compositing
Beijing Zhongshi Northern Film and Television Production Co., Ltd.
Beijing Renshi Jumei Digital Co., Ltd.
Zeng Gong'an
VFX Supervisor Liu Yang
Wu Ruimin
Digital Matte Painters Qin Jiandong, Liu Mengxin
Li Jiaxiang
Tian Huajian
Zhao Yichen
Guo Junshan
Special Effects Production Company
Beijing Liuguang Yicai Film and Television Technology Co., Ltd.
Production and Business Director Yu Liang
Ren Yujia
Fan Luxi
Xu Tao
Music and Sound Post-production
Beijing Guandai Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Cheng Rang
Huo Xiyu
Beijing Chenjia Shiyin Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Insert Songs
Chinese Lyricist Li Ziheng
Little Tigers
Liu Yitie
'Season of the Wind' (Cantonese Version)
Tang Zhengchuan
Li Yasang
Original Copyright Owner Subito Publishing Co.
Zhou Qiang
Adapted Music Producer Chen Jia
Guo Jingfei
Li Yasang
Gou Yin
Yang Ninghao
Mastering Engineer Quan Xiangyan
'I Have a Date with Spring'
Zhong Zhirong
Adapted Music Producer Chen Jia
Cantonese Adaptation Lyricist
Music Copyright Owner Universal Music Publishing (China)
Zhou Qiang
Hong Shirui
'Wedding Invitation Street'
Huang Weiwen
Guo Weiliang
Wang Shilin
Chen Jia
'This Life'
Theme Song/End Credits 'Hey, Uncle'
Zhiguo
Qiu Linghao
Rock
Filming Location Support
Changchun Wanda Film Industrial Park
FAW Foundry Co., Ltd. Black Casting Division Plant 2
School of Public Health, Jilin University
Jilin Agricultural University
Former Russian Consulate Exhibition Hall, Changchun World Sculpture Park
Jilin Petrochemical Design Institute
Changchun Sacred Heart Charity Hospital
Changchun Jingyuetan Experimental Forest Farm
Changchun Hualian Antique City
Changchun Light and Sound Story Bar Co., Ltd.
Jilin City Second Experimental Primary School
Lingyan Temple, Jilin City
Jilin Longtan Mountain Scenic Area Management Center
Jilin City Xiao'er BBQ Hotpot and Roasted Lamb
Hadawan Seafood Wholesale Market, Changyi District, Jilin City
Equipment Support
Xinfeng Yuening Film and Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen Godox Photo Equipment Co., Ltd.
Special Thanks To
Publicity Department of CPC Anhui Provincial Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Dehui Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Jilin Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Baishan Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Kuancheng District Committee, Changchun
Publicity Department of CPC Chaoyang District Committee, Changchun
Publicity Department of CPC Nanguan District Committee, Changchun
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Automobile Economic and Technological Development Zone Working Committee
Party Working Committee of Changchun New Area
Publicity Department of CPC Fengman District Committee, Jilin City
Publicity Department of CPC Changyi District Committee, Jilin City
Jilin Broadcasting and Television Station
Changchun Jingyue High-Tech Zone Film and Television Service Bureau
Changchun Municipal Bureau of Culture, Broadcasting, Television and Tourism
Changchun Public Security Bureau
Changchun Broadcasting and Television Station
Traffic Police Detachment of Changchun Public Security Bureau
People's Court of Erdao District, Changchun
Jilin Municipal Bureau of Culture, Broadcasting, Television and Tourism
Traffic Police Detachment of Jilin Public Security Bureau
Jilin Public Security Bureau
Jilin Train Operation Section, China Railway Shenyang Group Co., Ltd.
Changchun Train Operation Section, China Railway Shenyang Group Co., Ltd.
China FAW Group Co., Ltd.
Changchun Film Group Corporation
Changchun Film Studio Historical Site Museum Cultural Communication Co., Ltd.
Changchun Culture, Tourism and Film Investment Group Co., Ltd.
Changchun Runde Investment Group Co., Ltd.
Nanhu Campus of Joint Logistics Support Force 964 Hospital
Kaixuan Campus of Jilin Provincial People's Hospital
Changchun People's Art Theater
Changchun Vanke Real Estate Development Co., Ltd.
Jilin Huixin Land Real Estate Natural Resources Assessment Co., Ltd.
Changchun Xincheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Jilin Galaxy Hotel Co., Ltd.
Jilin Guoyuan Investment Holding Group Co., Ltd.
Jilin Ferroalloy Co., Ltd.
Changbai Mountain Liquor Group Co., Ltd.
Jilin International Hotel Co., Ltd.
Copyright Notice: All rights to this work belong to Shanghai Tencent Penguin Film and Television Culture Communication
Co., Ltd. and Shanghai Mingjian Film.
Shanghai Mingjian Film Co., Ltd.
Jilin Changchun Sanhao Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Production Support
Changchun Film Group Corporation
Beijing Mint Culture
Co-produced By
Beijing Intercontinental Brothers Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Tomato Film and Television
Beijing Zhengfu Film Co., Ltd.