Li
Li Yang
Liu
Do you remember 1993?
That year
due to the Three Gorges Project
1.31 million urban and rural residents were relocated.
The whole nation
was cheering for Beijing's bid
for the 2000 Olympic Games.
The food ration coupons that had accompanied Chinese people for decades
officially exited the historical stage.
The TV series playing on television
was 'New Legend of White Snake'.
And
that year's stock market
reached a peak of 1,558 points.
In such
a passionate era of reform,
there were bound to be people who liked to stir things up.
If we talk about
the person who loved stirring things up the most,
I think
it must be him.
His talent for causing trouble
was unmatched in our area.
He was a firecracker,
just like those double-bang firecrackers.
When handling matters,
Cui Guoming
never had any proper behavior.
How could one live like that?
But you know what,
this unreliable fellow
Coming right away!
actually had a warm heart.
Here you go.
Even if he suffered losses himself,
he couldn't bear to see others suffer.
What can you do?
He's smart.
Loyal.
Didn't you ask me to keep a low profile?
He looked carefree and sloppy
but was actually quite talented.
Anyway.
When he was out making his way,
there was no trick he couldn't think of
or thing he couldn't do.
Thinking...
I understand.
If it weren't for those seven years
when I was inside writing appeals for you.
As for who this child is,
yes, it's me.
And the person holding me
is my uncle.
I am your uncle.
And the story between my uncle and me
begins in the autumn of 1993.
My uncle
is an all-around genius.
He can clear the table in one shot when playing pool.
He can even do bicycle kicks when playing soccer.
He plays Chinese chess and Go
and has never lost.
He can memorize everyone's cards when playing poker.
He sings better than Jacky Cheung
and dances better than Aaron Kwok.
Any household appliance,
my uncle can fix after reading the manual just once.
No matter how complex the instrument,
my uncle can master it in just a few days.
My uncle's greatest skill is cooking fish.
When the fish is served,
it still moves.
I asked you to write about 'My Someone'
to truthfully describe a family member,
not to write fairy tales here.
Everything I wrote is true.
That's enough.
Sit down.
Who's next?
Huo Xiaoyang,
why are you such a show-off?
Bragging in daily life is one thing,
but how could you write it in your essay?
Everything I said is true.
The teacher already said you were making things up.
Just admit it.
What I said is absolutely true.
If you don't believe me, go meet my uncle someday.
My dad knows all about your family.
My father told me.
Your father is a convict,
and who knows what your mother is doing abroad.
Say that again.
Don't deny it.
Who knows what your mother does.
I-
Uncle.
Hello, teachers.
You're his uncle?
Yes, I am.
Cui.
Guoming.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know me?
I do.
No, no, no.
I don't.
Well.
You don't know me.
But I know you.
You're from No. 27 Middle School, right?
I am.
I'm two years behind you.
Well, you were so popular at school.
Everyone knew who you were.
Whenever there was a school event,
from hosting to performing,
it was always you, wasn't it?
What about my nephew?
Your nephew?
Well, he...
I wanted to tell you that
he writes excellent essays.
Because his essay is titled
'My Uncle.'
That's you.
I think he wrote it very realistically,
quite vividly,
and with a touch of
childlike innocence.
So you called me here
because his essay was good?
No, no.
It's because there's
a small conflict between them.
This student said some inappropriate things
that upset Huo Xiaoyang.
However, I believe
this issue is Wang Ning's fault.
Then why is he standing there as punishment?
That's their turn to stand as punishment.
Hey,
Wang Ning, stand up.
It's his turn now.
You're causing trouble for me again, aren't you?
Causing trouble again.
It takes me an hour to get here and back,
losing thousands.
What are you doing?
You can't hit children!
It wasn't me.
Who else could it be?
Huo Xiaoyang hit me first.
You're Huo Xiaoyang?
He is.
And who are you?
I'm his uncle.
Is Cui Xiaohong
your sister?
Is she your sister?
Yes.
There's been a misunderstanding.
It's all a misunderstanding.
I'm your sister's classmate.
Your sister is so beautiful.
Well...
Um, you know...
You don't really look like your sister.
This kid...
This kid looks even less like her.
We really are from the same family.
Blood relatives.
Right, so you're all family?
Classmates fighting is normal.
The more you fight, the closer you become.
Right?
Wang Ning.
Shake hands.
Look,
that's nice.
But I still need to sort this out.
This matter was
started by Wang Ning.
Why is it you again?
That doesn't mean you can hit a child.
I'm telling the truth.
Be quiet.
Um...
Hey, Cui.
If there's nothing else,
you can take Huo Xiaoyang and leave first.
Let's go.
Come visit us again sometime.
Why did you hit someone?
What did he say to you?
He said my mom might be doing who knows what abroad.
Your mother is abroad
running a cosmetics business.
When is my mom coming back?
When you stop being naughty,
she'll come back.
I'm not being naughty.
Dad, why are you here?
Just passing by.
Did he get into trouble again?
Your brother is very well-behaved.
Let's go.
This is my sister.
My uncle's daughter.
She's looked down on me since childhood.
Xiaohong's brother?
Why don't you ride with me?
It's exhausting to handle two kids alone.
Little chubby.
I'm not getting in.
Look at your tires.
They're all flat.
Get in.
Let's talk about my sister.
Sure, let's talk.
Can we talk privately?
Let's go.
Come.
Wait in the car.
Let's go.
How's your sister doing?
She's fine. Have you eaten?
What should we eat?
Let me take you somewhere nice.
What's there to eat here?
Boss.
Can we use your place to talk for five minutes?
No, not like that.
I don't need you. I've got this.
Here.
For you.
Then let's talk for ten minutes.
Such a classy person.
You went abroad.
No, I haven't.
And you didn't see my sister?
No.
But your sister is
very beautiful.
How do you know that?
What's my sister doing abroad?
I... I don't know.
Then how does your son know?
My son, he...
Why are you closing the door?
Didn't you say we'd only talk for ten minutes?
Dad,
how much was that red car they had?
I don't know.
Several classmates in my class
their families all bought cars this year.
When will our family buy one?
When I make some money.
When will you make money?
Soon.
Isn't a bicycle just as good?
There's not much difference.
You're riding in a car, not cycling.
Look how exhausted my dad is.
I'm not tired.
But for the Xiali car,
we'll buy one too.
Is that okay?
Go inside and find your mom first.
Ji Qiang,
studying again?
Need any help?
Don't want me to disturb you?
Alright,
I won't bother you then.
Sister Zhou.
These sunglasses look stylish,
don't they?
This is Dingqing Restaurant,
our province's famous establishment,
almost a hundred years old.
Grandpa told me
it was opened by a famous Beijing chef
named Old Master Zhang from the last century.
The signboard was personally inscribed by Xu Shichang.
The man cooking there is my grandfather,
the general manager of Dingqing Restaurant.
He has deep feelings for this place.
After all, he's been here since he was an apprentice.
This restaurant is his life's work and memories.
This is my grandmother,
who was a famous opera performer in the province.
Unfortunately, because of her heart condition,
her health was never good,
so she stopped performing.
You've spent your whole life at Dingqing Restaurant.
Now that you're really retiring,
what will you do?
Go home.
Go home and cook for you.
Three meals a day.
When you retire,
the new general manager
won't be as dedicated as you.
As long as I'm the manager,
this is my home.
No, it's more important than our home.
You've made all this mess
for Qiangzi again.
He loves vegetarian dishes.
I'm planning to name this dish
called
Vegetable Medley.
It might even become
a famous dish nationwide.
Famous dish, really?
Come.
Qiangzi.
Ji Qiang.
You must be hungry.
Come.
Auntie,
this beautiful woman
is my aunt.
She also works at Dingqing Restaurant
as an accountant.
A soccer ball costs 20 yuan.
My aunt is incredibly good to me
and often helps me with my homework.
It cost 770 yuan.
Mr. Meng,
but even my aunt
doesn't know all the answers, right?
At those times,
we go ask Ji Qiang.
That's him.
But I heard
he was accepted to university before,
but something happened to his family,
and he ended up like this.
But he's really smart
and knows all the problems I can't solve.
It's that simple.
I'll leave the kid here first.
I need to go back to the factory for some business.
What time is it already?
And you're still going to the factory?
Didn't we just get a new factory director?
He asked us for suggestions.
I've written over 200 pages.
Just 7 or 8 pages left.
Then I'll be done.
What?
Over 200 pages?
What have you been writing about?
Mainly about product marketing,
equipment updates,
and employee benefits.
That's it.
Look,
when the new director asks for suggestions,
he's just being polite.
Putting on a show of democracy.
Don't actually write a massive treatise.
Over 200 pages?
Are you trying to take his job?
That's not it.
These issues affect all of us.
Besides, it's a rare opportunity.
I need to get it all off my chest.
Listen,
have you forgotten what I told you?
How your Uncle Zhang lost his position back then?
It was because he talked too much.
Always running his mouth.
The leaders asked for opinions,
but he didn't just give suggestions,
he started insulting people.
I won't insult anyone.
That would be so uncultured.
I'm just being profound and incisive.
Besides,
it's 1993 now.
Don't worry.
Listen...
Why did you come back?
Doesn't the factory allow suggestion letters?
I haven't finished writing it yet.
Have you two finished yours?
I haven't written mine either.
I forgot.
You two don't need to worry.
You don't need to write anything.
Mine will be more comprehensive.
What should I write?
You two definitely don't know.
Then what should I write?
Do you know?
I don't want to know.
What's there to argue about?
Isn't it good to have different opinions?
Go ahead and write.
Your dad made you such a nice kite
and you just threw it away.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
I don't enjoy playing with these things anymore.
Your father spent the whole weekend
making that for you.
This kite isn't worth anything.
So what if I threw it away?
Then tell me,
what do you value?
When Dad used to make these things for me,
my classmates were all quite envious.
But now many of them
have Xiali cars at home.
How can our little things compare with that?
Why don't you compete with others on something worthwhile?
Like studying.
You only care about these useless things.
Anyway, Dad said
we're going to buy a Xiali car too.
What?
When did he tell you that?
This afternoon when he picked me up from school.
Did he say when?
No,
but he said very soon.
What did you write?
Dear Factory Director,
hello,
I am employee Zhao Hailong.
I would like to make
some personal suggestions about the cafeteria.
Every winter,
we always eat pickled vegetables.
I think
we could buy some dried cabbage.
Since the price of dried cabbage
is almost the same as pickled vegetables.
Eating pickled vegetables all the time
can easily upset your stomach.
Your suggestion is excellent!
Don't you think
it will be accepted?
Well then,
I'll write mine here too
to make a stronger impression on the leadership.
Wait a minute.
What are you writing?
Read it to me.
I wrote that
our equipment maintenance department
should get two more sets of work uniforms each year.
We crawl inside machines every day,
our clothes get dirty and torn
much faster than other departments.
We're the ones who really need uniforms.
Those office workers,
what do they need uniforms for?
Really?
Well said!
Add mine too.
Sure.
Brother Cui.
What are you doing? Writing a ten-thousand-word petition?
Ten thousand words isn't nearly enough.
Mine has at least 70,000 to 80,000 words.
What are you writing about?
The first 20 pages are fairly simple.
Just about marketing
and after-sales service.
The next 100 pages
I wrote in much more detail.
I suggest our factory
should sell
half,
or at least a third of our land
to update our equipment.
Brother Cui,
you know the most about technology and equipment,
don't you?
Are you really willing to sell it?
Our equipment
was built in 1957
with Soviet aid.
It's too outdated.
Our factory's products in the market
can't even compete with small southern factories.
If China joins the WTO,
our competitiveness
will be almost zero.
By that time,
if the factory closes down,
we'll all lose our jobs
and be laid off.
Brother Cui.
Our factory.
A key project built with Soviet aid,
how could it possibly go bankrupt?
Even the Soviet Union collapsed.
Why wouldn't our factory close down too?
With my business model,
even our most ordinary workers
will be able to buy a Xiali car
a sedan model,
Do you believe it?
You definitely believe it.
I...
It's time for me to get off work.
I need to think about it.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bro.
I need to go home and cook for my wife.
Hurry.
I'm leaving now.
Hey.
Why haven't you finished work yet?
When will you get here?
I'm writing something.
Wait for me. I'll be there soon.
See you at the usual place.
You...
Compared to when you were on TV,
you've lost quite a bit of weight.
They made it clear to me in detention.
I'm a celebrity now.
Celebrities need to maintain their image.
With so many people there,
why did the reporters pick you as the spokesperson?
I was waiting for you to ask.
Isn't it obvious?
It's crystal clear.
Because the TV station
saw that I had the best image among everyone.
And look at my speech.
How touching was my attitude when admitting mistakes?
Without this quality...
Excuse me.
It's a gift.
What do you mean?
It's for you.
That was you being interviewed on TV the other day, right?
You recognized me.
I watched it.
That reporter interviewing you was quite impressive.
This is a gift.
Chives.
Do you understand what it means?
Its effect is nourishing.
You could use that.
Thanks.
You're showing off.
Thank you.
Come, have a taste.
Don't listen to him.
You know, in these past two years
I've been on TV
just this one opportunity.
Am I a bit unlucky?
If you're not feeling good about it,
find a fortune teller
to break your bad luck.
That might make you feel better.
You know a lot of people and have connections.
Do you know any masters
who can solve problems like this?
I have connections,
but not that kind.
I don't really believe in that stuff.
If you want to find someone,
look in the mountains or by the water.
Those hermits
are the ones with real skills.
That makes sense.
Excuse me for interrupting again.
This is for you.
Lamb kidneys!
This is too kind.
Do you know what they're good for?
They're nutritious.
What's your name?
My surname is Guo,
they call me Guo Dapao.
That's a powerful name!
Look, if
hypothetically speaking,
if you get on TV again...
What are you talking about?
Just giving you good wishes.
What good wishes?
I mean...
I'm not good with words. I mean,
when you become famous,
you'll get lots of interviews.
That's fine.
When you get many positive interviews,
could you maybe mention
that I gave you chives
and kidneys,
and praise them,
saying they're really good?
That would be even better.
I get it. You want free advertising.
You want promotion.
That's exactly it.
If you do this,
next time you're on TV,
I'll give you something too.
Alright,
I'm not good with words.
Eat up, enjoy!
Come feel what advertising fees taste like.
I don't want any. Really.
Brother, excuse me again.
What do you want now?
I brewed this myself
for my own drinking.
I feel you need this more than I do.
Ginseng.
There's some deer antler in here,
really potent stuff. And goji berries.
Mengmeng is asleep.
What's going on?
Did you tell Mengmeng we're buying a Xiali car?
I...
I didn't.
Would that child lie to me?
She told me herself.
Well, I just mentioned it casually.
She's just a kid.
I didn't promise her anything.
I didn't say when we'd buy it, right?
I...
It's nothing, really.
Do you know how much
a Xiali sedan costs nowadays?
About 40 or 50 thousand.
40 or 50 thousand?
My classmate just bought one last week
for 118,000.
That's so expensive.
This won't work.
It's impossible.
Do you know how much money we have?
About 40 or 50 thousand?
Here.
Take a good look yourself.
What's this?
You've brought out the bankbook.
What are you doing?
44,500.
I have another 500 in my pocket.
So that makes exactly 45,000.
That's about right.
With just this much money, you still want to buy a car?
Can you please be more down to earth?
This 45,000
is what I've saved over our ten-plus years of marriage,
penny by penny, scraping it together
with great effort.
Money is meant to be saved,
not scraped together like that.
Then how else would we get it?
Rob a bank?
We need to earn it.
Find a way!
What era are we living in?
Deepening reform
and expanding openness.
Even nobodies can make money these days,
but I can't?
I don't think you can.
Where would you earn it?
By stealing machines from the factory to sell?
That's good. You
have given me a new challenge.
Starting today,
I will seriously think about
how to make money.
I never meant for you to make money.
Our life
may not be great,
but it's not bad either.
Be serious when I'm talking to you.
You're just too unrealistic,
completely out of touch,
coming up with new ideas every day,
living in your own mental world.
How can you brag like this to our child?
I wonder how you'll face Mengmeng.
By buying the car,
wouldn't that solve everything?
Zhang.
Director, please take a look at this.
Which department's feedback is this?
There's so much of it.
Equipment Maintenance Department.
Equipment Maintenance Department?
Those few people there?
Three people.
All engineers.
Three people wrote all this?
Mainly.
This person.
Cui Guoming.
According to his suggestion,
even our most ordinary factory workers
will all be able to drive
Xiali cars within three years.
How much does a Xiali car cost?
I certainly can't afford one.
I'm guessing
it's about
over 100,000.
How does this Cui Guoming usually perform?
In terms of technical skills,
he's quite good.
After all, he graduated from the Engineering University.
As for his personality,
the old factory director really appreciated him.
I can't afford to offend him.
Is that so?
Of course.
When I was in the publicity department,
he looked down on me.
He has plenty of suggestions
and some make sense,
but it's not that easy to implement them.
[Close the switch]
[Received]
Let's think about where to go this afternoon.
My uncle's painstakingly written ten-thousand-word petition
became waste paper
the very next day after submission.
But who would have thought
that what was once a laughingstock that no one believed
would later come true word for word.
Hey, buddy.
Why do I have to pay just to take a look?
50.
What?
At the train station and bus station entrances
they only charge 2 yuan.
The most I've seen at People's Park is 5 yuan.
Why are you charging 50?
Go complain to them then.
Goodbye and good riddance.
Well, that's how you're going to be?
Figure out what I do for a living.
If you get it right, I'll be your customer.
So what's this place for?
Wasn't my gesture clear enough?
Then guess what I'm here to consult about.
Relationship issues.
Master!
Master.
Do this.
Give me your hand.
Feel if this money is right.
Will that work?
Tell me about your problem.
I'll try my best to help.
You don't know?
These past two years...
I've suffered so much.
This outfit with this outer layer looks pretty good.
Not too flashy.
But still quite dignified.
And quite handsome, right?
What are you getting dressed up for?
Are you accepting an award?
I'm going to my high school reunion.
What? A reunion?
Almost everyone from our class is going.
I've heard about these things.
For people our age,
nothing good comes from attending reunions.
These so-called reunions with classmates...
It means fooling around.
Have you heard this expression?
I don't fool around.
I just go there to eat and drink.
Don't think I don't know.
Back in high school,
all the girls in your class had a crush on you.
It was all the girls in school who had a crush on me.
You're shameless.
They had a crush on me,
but I'm not shameless.
Just wear your work clothes.
Wear what you usually wear. Got it?
Are you serious? You must be joking.
I'm not joking about anything.
You're naturally good-looking. You'll look great in anything.
No.
It's not just that the work clothes look bad.
They're dirty and covered in oil.
Just wear these.
Or don't go at all.
Put those away.
You won't need them.
At your class reunion,
will Guo Dapao be there?
He'll be there. He definitely will.
You know, in high school,
you were top of the class,
while he was at the very bottom.
Yet you insisted on hanging out with him.
What about those other good students?
Why didn't you hang out with them?
We were desk mates.
The most loyal friends often come from humble backgrounds.
He really is from a butcher's family.
A meat seller.
A family business of selling meat.
What about your college classmates who work in aerospace?
Why don't you attend reunions with them?
They're all working in aerospace now.
Why would they want to hang out with me?
I'm just a mechanic.
Don't be so snobbish.
I'm snobbish?
You're not?
What about the promise you made to your daughter?
Let's see how you'll keep it.
Have you bought that Xiali car yet?
Put it away.
We won't need it.
Did you give the new factory director
a hundreds-page proposal?
It went straight to the trash.
You're too bold.
Are those things you should be saying?
I heard
you suggested selling the factory land
to buy new equipment.
That's right.
Our factory equipment is from 1957,
just three years older than me.
Internationally speaking...
Forget about international standards.
Even by national standards, it's outdated.
If we continue like this,
our factory will collapse within three years.
What does it matter to you if it fails?
How could it not concern me?
I'm a worker here.
If the factory fails, don't I fail too?
Right, you also said
that if they followed your advice,
you could help every worker
buy a Xiali car.
The sedan model.
This is based on Hayek's theory.
Ha-what?
Hayek.
Which department is he from?
Human Resources.
Enough.
That statement of yours
has become a joke
among the factory leadership
circle now.
They're saying let's see if after three years of your antics,
you yourself can afford a Xiali.
Everyone becomes a joke at some point,
but who will have the last laugh
remains to be seen.
You're already in your thirties.
You're not that young college graduate
from ten years ago anymore.
Don't be so impulsive about everything.
You need to be more practical.
Keep a lower profile.
I know, I know.
Don't stick your neck out
when you shouldn't.
Got it, got it.
I'm heading out now.
Where are you going?
Class reunion.
I'd rather leave work early
than be late for the reunion.
My job at the factory
is to ensure that all machines
operate normally.
Today I guarantee
none of the machines will break down.
Isn't that enough?
I'm leaving.
Wait.
You're going dressed like that?
Didn't you tell me to keep a low profile?
Guoming.
Dajian.
You drive pretty well.
Just bought it recently.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll drink to you later.
Everyone's here.
Guoming.
Why are you getting your hands dirty?
How did you end up like this?
I just came from the factory.
Aren't you an engineer?
Don't touch it if it's oily.
Then why are you still...
I'm an engineer.
I'm a worker too.
Labor is glorious.
The thing is
you're not interested in any of the girls from our class,
so you just came dressed like this.
If I were your wife,
I would never let you go out looking like this.
If you were my wife,
how would you want me to dress?
What,
get you a Dunhill suit?
I prefer mink fur.
You said it yourself.
I'll get you one tomorrow.
Fine.
I'll tell your husband right away.
When did he become so naughty?
Everyone's here.
Hello everyone.
Teacher.
Come.
Please sit down, everyone.
Let's raise our glasses.
Let's toast to Teacher Li again,
wishing her good health and all the best.
Thank you, students.
Thank you.
Everyone,
it's been over ten years since graduation.
During these years,
our China has truly undergone tremendous changes.
The legendary multi-story buildings,
electricity and telephones,
every family has them now, right?
I dare say,
in another decade or so,
our China will undergo even more dramatic changes.
Everyone,
the country has given us such a great opportunity now,
we must seize it.
Well said.
Zhang Xiaoxia.
Mrs. Li,
what are you doing these days?
My husband and I opened a clothing store.
On good days, we make 2,000 to 3,000.
On bad days,
just over 1,000.
Not bad.
Li Dayong,
how are you doing?
Mrs. Li,
as everyone knows,
I didn't learn any skills in school.
I can't do anything special,
so now I can only drive a taxi.
I make about
3,000 to 4,000 a month.
That's quite a bit more than those with regular salaries.
Right?
Dajian,
what about you?
I'm the only one at this table who's not doing well.
Business isn't always good.
No.
When was the last time you had a good deal?
Was it last month?
The net profit was just over 100,000.
Over 100,000?
I'm paying today.
Don't anyone fight me for the bill.
Guoming,
among all the students I've taught,
you were the smartest.
How have you been lately?
Every month, I make
573.5 yuan.
Fixed salary.
We're about the same,
though you make 20 more than me.
Then you need to work harder.
Sure, bro.
Guoming.
I remember you're a great singer.
How about singing one for us later?
Of course.
My singing doesn't come cheap.
Got your money ready?
Money's not an issue.
Here's to you.
Cheers.
Teacher, cheers.
Drink up.
But you know what?
That outfit of yours
looks just like the prison uniform I wore during labor reform.
Don't you think so?
Don't talk nonsense.
I've never been in labor reform.
I don't even know what a prison uniform looks like.
How about this:
next time you go in,
bring one out so I can see for myself.
These days,
you can't ask me about that anymore.
The real expert now
is our classmate Guo Dapao.
Haven't you seen the news?
He got arrested at a massage parlor.
Why don't I see him?
Our
class.
has produced a
celebrity.
Haven't you watched TV, Ms. Li?
No, I haven't.
Guo Dapao was arrested and shown on TV.
During the interview,
he was talking like he owned the place.
Really?
Here, let me imitate him.
You have to hold your hands like this.
As everyone knows,
what I did was wrong.
I deeply regret my actions.
I hope everyone will learn from my mistakes.
Whoever breaks the law
will surely be punished by it.
As the old saying goes,
good and evil will eventually be rewarded accordingly.
The right path in life is through hardship.
I hope everyone stays on the right path.
Dajian,
if I were you,
I'd be too embarrassed to imitate Dapao.
I remember your last rehabilitation
was for organizing prostitution, right?
Guys like Dapao were your customers.
The customer is always right.
How can you criticize the chef after eating the meal?
He wasn't even my client.
Besides, I'm not in that business anymore.
Let me tell you, Ms. Li,
I won't do that kind of thing again.
I won't end up on TV either.
If I were on TV, I wouldn't act like that.
Wait,
that Guo Dapao...
Guo Dalei.
Why didn't he come today?
Police.
Please cooperate with us.
We have some questions for you.
Wait, I just
went to a hair salon.
Besides, wasn't this matter already resolved?
The whole city witnessed it, didn't they?
Don't misunderstand.
This is just an inquiry,
not an interrogation.
We just want to get some information from you.
That stupid little incident
never seems to end.
No.
What inquiry?
What do you want to know?
You want more details?
It's not about that incident.
It's something else.
What else could I possibly be involved in?
We just need some information.
Let's talk at the market office.
Can you tell me
where you were on the night
of the 17th?
The 17th?
Which year and month's 17th?
That was so long ago.
You're asking me out of nowhere.
How would I remember?
I'm just asking you.
What did you do on the 17th?
Can you remember?
I'm asking you a question.
Don't answer with questions.
Well, I don't remember.
It's okay. Take your time.
If you can't remember, we'll help you.
Well, here's the situation.
I did have something that day.
There was an
annual class reunion that night.
I organized this.
Everyone's waiting for me.
One of my classmates is your colleague.
Alright.
Come on, sing.
Guoming, give us one.
I've had too much to drink.
I'm not singing.
Come on.
Didn't you just say you'd sing if we paid you?
Is this enough?
I'll have to hum a bit then.
So tell me
how much would make you sing?
118,000.
I'll sing for you until dawn.
Final Trailer/EPK/MV/Behind-the-Scenes Production
Han Xueyi
Chen Siwei
Peng Yanqiao
Guo Yue
B-Roll Team
Xiangshang Xiaokong Chengxiang (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Deng Yulong
Hu Han
Short Video Marketing Company
Beijing Yichao Yixi Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Beijing Shiheng Yuexiang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Creative Planning: Liao Xingkai, Xue Yu, Zheng Yixin
Two Bits (Beijing) Technology Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Compositing
Beijing Zhongshi Northern Film and Television Production Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Company
Zeng Gong'an
Yu Qiulan
VFX Supervisor: Liu Yang
Digital Matte Painters: Qin Jiandong, Liu Mengxin
Li Jiaxiang
Post-Production
Zhao Yichen
He Zhaoyi
Guo Junshan
Special Effects Production Company
Beijing Liuguang Yicai Film and Television Technology Co., Ltd.
Production and Business Director: Yu Liang
Zhao Yuxia
Ren Yujia
Fan Luxi
Xu Tao
Music and Sound Post-Production
Beijing Guandai Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Chengrong
Beijing Chenjia Shiyin Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Bai Ru
Featured Songs
'Date with the Stars'
Little Tigers
Liu Yitie
'Season of the Wind' (Cantonese Version)
Tang Zhengchuan
Original Copyright Owner: Subito Publishing Co.
Zhou Qiang
Adapted Music Production: Chen Jia
Performed by: Guo Jingfei
Tan Qiyin
Li Yasang
Gou Yin
Harmony Design/Vocals: Liang Guchi
Zhou Taotao
Mastering Engineer: Quan Xiangyan
Zhong Zhirong
Huang Shujun
Original Copyright Owner: EMI MUSIC PUBLISHING HONG KONG
Wang Jie
Music Copyright Owner: Universal Music Publishing (China)
Hong Shirui
'Wedding Invitation Street'
Wyman Wong
Zhou Qiang
Chen Jia
Chuanzi
'Ten Things That Shouldn't Be'
Copyright Owned by Changying Group Audio-Visual Publishing Co., Ltd.
Theme Song/End Credits: 'Hey, Uncle'
Dong Baoshi
Lock
Filming Location Support
Changchun Wanda Film Industrial Park
FAW Foundry Co., Ltd. Black Casting Division Plant 2
School of Public Health, Jilin University
Nanling Campus Hospital, Jilin University
Jilin Petrochemical Design Institute
Changchun Sacred Heart Charity Hospital
Changchun Jingyuetan Experimental Forest Farm
Changchun Hualian Antique City
Changchun Victory Park
Lingyan Temple, Jilin City
Jilin Longtan Mountain Scenic Area Management Center
Xiaoer BBQ Hotpot and Roasted Lamb, Jilin City
Hadawan Seafood Wholesale Market, Changyi District, Jilin City
Xinfeng Yuening Film & Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen Godox Photo Equipment Co., Ltd.
Special Thanks To
Publicity Department of CPC Anhui Provincial Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Jilin Provincial Committee
Jilin Provincial Radio and Television Bureau
Publicity Department of CPC Changchun Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Jilin Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Baishan Municipal Committee
Publicity Department of CPC Kuancheng District Committee, Changchun
Publicity Department of CPC Lyuan District Committee, Changchun
Publicity Department of CPC Chaoyang District Committee, Changchun
Publicity Department of CPC Erdao District Committee, Changchun
Party Working Committee of Changchun New Area
CPC Fengman District Committee, Jilin City
Publicity Department of CPC Changyi District Committee, Jilin City
Jilin Provincial Department of Culture and Tourism
Jilin Broadcasting and Television Station
Administrative Committee of Changchun Jingyue High-tech Zone
Film and Television Service Bureau of Changchun Jingyue High-tech Zone
Changchun Public Security Bureau
Changchun Broadcasting and Television Station
Traffic Police Detachment of Changchun Public Security Bureau
People's Court of Changchun Economic and Technological Development Zone
People's Court of Erdao District, Changchun
Dehui Public Security Bureau
Jilin City Public Security Bureau
Jilin Train Operation Section, China Railway Shenyang Group Co., Ltd.
Changchun Train Operation Section, China Railway Shenyang Group Co., Ltd.
Dehui Railway Station
China FAW Group Co., Ltd.
FAW Jiefang Automotive Co., Ltd.
Changchun Film Studio Historical Site Museum Cultural Communication Co., Ltd.
Changchun Runde Investment Group Co., Ltd.
Kaixuan Campus of Jilin Provincial People's Hospital
Jilin Provincial People's Hospital
Changchun International Convention & Exhibition Center (Group) Co., Ltd.
Changchun Vanke Real Estate Development Co., Ltd.
Changchun Xincheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Jilin Galaxy Hotel Co., Ltd.
Jilin Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Jilin Guoyuan Investment Holding Group Co., Ltd.
Jilin Railway Investment and Development Co., Ltd.
Jilin International Hotel Co., Ltd.
Copyright Notice: All rights to this work belong to Shanghai Tencent Penguin Film and Television Culture Communication
Jilin Changchun Sanhao Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Production Support
Changchun Film Group Corporation
Jilin Broadcasting and Television Station
Beijing Mint Culture
Film Academy of Changchun Film Group
Co-produced By
Tomato Film & TV
Beijing Zhengfu Film Co., Ltd.
Jilin Changchun Sanhao Film and Television Co., Ltd.