♪In a sudden instant♪
♪Dreams shattered and then recovered♪
♪Babylon's youth♪
♪Fearlessly living their lives♪
♪They keep moving forward♪
♪The noisy coastline in June♪
♪Reminds me of midsummer nights♪
♪The subtle emotions between you and me♪
♪No longer ordinary♪
♪Seasons come and go, steps never cease♪
♪Leaving behind evidence of existence♪
♪Watching time flow away♪
♪Anxiety gradually grows♪
♪Don't want to miss the scenery along the way♪
♪The scenery along the way,
evidence of existence♪
♪Dazzling you in my dreams♪
♪Are the source of my courage♪
♪The scenery in the air is amazing♪
♪Turn around to see the girl I miss♪
♪And the familiar nice wind♪
♪When this story reaches its conclusion♪
♪Perhaps it will be moving♪
=Young Babylon=
Here is your bill,
285 yuan in all.
I'm sorry, I was
in a rush when I came
and didn't bring enough money.
How about this?
I'll leave my ID here
and come back to settle the payment
another day, okay?
This really won't do, sir.
That's against our rules.
Well, how about this?
I'll give you 20 yuan now,
and you wait for me a bit.
I'll go home and get the money.
- No, sir.
- You have to trust me.
Listen,
I've been friends with the owner
of your hotel for many years, really.
Sir, this really won't work.
I'm sorry about this.
Big Feet, I didn't expect you
to be doing so well.
Just treating us to a meal
won't be enough.
No matter how much you earn,
you should have come to the wedding.
What's going on with you?
Let Big Feet arrange another one for you.
No, Juan won't agree.
Enough fussing. It's late.
We have to go home.
We'll meet again another day.
You must treat us again.
We're leaving now.
- Bye.
- Let us know when you get home.
Bye, bye, okay.
If you have any difficulties,
tell me anytime.
I'll smoke a cigarette.
You two go home first.
- Okay.
- Take care.
I'll call a taxi.
No need.
I've had a bit too much to drink.
Have a walk with me.
=Episode 21=
=Never Stand By When You're in Trouble=
Vice Mayor Bi.
This is the last sip.
And then it's finished.
Another cup?
Can you still handle more?
Let me tell you the truth.
I usually
don't come out to drink,
but tonight,
I must drink
until I can't drink anymore.
Bottoms up.
Let's have another bottle.
Okay, okay.
- Okay.
- Waiter.
Enough.
That's enough for today.
Let's drink another day.
Why postpone it?
Listen, Mr. Huang,
I have some issues with you.
From the start, you've been
caring for her, defending her.
Why is that?
Tell me clearly today
what's going on between you two.
Otherwise, we must
continue this drink.
Is that okay?
Waiter.
Miss Bai is my fiancée.
I can't bear to see her drink more.
Mr. Huang,
you have good taste.
Alright,
since that's the case,
I wish you both well.
Are you okay?
Luckily, the room is upstairs.
You go back and rest first.
I'll come back after dropping him off.
Your acting was good.
Thank you.
Come on,
let's go.
How long do you plan
to keep deceiving me?
Lacoste belt,
Montblanc watch,
and the Beijing roast duck...
Chen Guowei,
you're quite impressive.
Xiaoying,
I'm sorry.
I'm just afraid that when I come back...
What are you afraid of?
That I won't like you anymore
because you are not doing well?
That Xiaolu, Guangnan, Little Pouter
will avoid you and not be friends
with you anymore?
I'm afraid of disappointing you.
Xiaoying,
I know that you have been
doing business with Xiaolu
to make money these years
just to support me,
to support my singing career.
But I feel really guilty.
I know how hard you've worked.
Xiaoying, more than once,
I've told myself
to just forget it,
come back and settle down.
But I really can't face you like that.
I've also told myself more than once
to hold on a little longer,
that I might succeed if I persevere
a bit more.
But Xiaoying,
I really tried my best.
I didn't achieve anything.
I have nothing now.
When you were in the factory,
you also had nothing,
but everyone still treated you
like a friend.
♪Will I miss the beat♪
When you first arrived in Beijing,
you suffered so much,
and I didn't leave you.
♪In this, I have a talent♪
♪You and I walk side by side, far apart♪
Xiaoying.
♪Truth is hidden in my pretentious words♪
♪The seagulls have come♪
♪Flapping their wings,
laughing at my confusion♪
♪A life unchanged♪
But I dislike you now.
Xiaoying.
The Big Feet I like,
even if he's broke,
at least has dreams
and stands by friends with sincerity,
unlike now,
pretending to be rich.
Xiaoying.
♪I think everybody knows♪
♪But you♪
♪Being with you is my happiness♪
♪I look forward to your attention♪
♪Counting every memory♪
I also dislike myself now!
♪So let me shout it out♪
♪I think I'll make you proud♪
♪Nobody tell me what to do♪
♪My life is not a boring loop♪
Why did you drink so much?
Which room?
2302.
Okay,
I'll help you over there.
Let me tell you,
you did not see,
that old thing surnamed Bi
kept trying to get me drunk.
I saw through him at a glance.
He used to do this too back then.
But guess what?
What?
I got him drunk.
I'm not bad, am I?
Yeah, you're the best.
After several years,
how come your drinking capacity
has improved so much?
It's not always been this good.
I remember
the first time
negotiating at a drinking table,
I ended up in the hospital
getting my stomach pumped.
Another time,
I got drunk
and hit someone,
messed up a deal,
and had to apologize to the client.
But
things are different now.
I'm really good now.
It's safe to say
I'm second to none.
I've conquered the drinking scene
in Shanghai.
Didn't you say
you've been doing well these years?
Yeah,
I have.
Come on, get up.
If I don't say it like this,
I'll lose.
Let me help you lie down.
The floor is so cold.
Come on, get up now.
I'll stay on the ground.
You just said "lose".
What do you mean?
I just don't want to lose to Lu Xiaolu.
I want to tell him that
even without him,
I can still live well.
I, Bai Lan,
can live well without anyone.
What are you looking at?
Don't believe it?
If I had known you'd go through so much,
I would never have left you.
Who do you think you are?
A savior?
Let me tell you,
even though I've had
a tough time these years,
I do have savings.
Soon, I'll have my own company,
my own projects.
By then, I won't have to talk business
by drinking anymore.
No,
more accurately,
I'll drink when I want to drink
and won't when I don't want to.
No one can force me.
So, this food factory project
is important to you, right?
Go to hell.
I don't want to live
this kind of life anymore.
But
if I stop drinking,
won't my great capacity
go to waste?
I have a good idea.
I've decided to pass on
my drinking skills to you.
How about that?
Will you be my disciple?
Alright.
I'll accept it.
But not today.
You're already too drunk
to pass your skills.
Let me help you lie down.
Get up.
- No.
- Come on.
- No, I won't.
I'll just lie on the ground.
I'll go get you some water.
Wait for me.
I don't want water.
I want alcohol.
You're already drunk.
You can't drink anymore.
I'm not drunk.
I want to drink.
I'll pass that to you today.
Okay, okay.
I'll go buy you some alcohol.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Please get me two dozens of beer.
Sir, which brand do you prefer?
Double Deer, Aoke,
or Singo?
Never mind.
Just give me two yogurt
and a can of honey.
Alright.
Didn't you say
you won't compromise this time?
Are you really sure about this?
(Director's Office)
I see.
Simply put,
the factory has lost control
over the workers.
That's why someone maliciously threatened
Manager Bai's personal safety.
No, this factory has always had
unresolved issues like unpaid wages
and medical expenses.
The workers have no choice.
After such an incident,
why didn't you report it?
- Well, you see, they are...
- It was my decision.
Manager Bai.
Your friend?
Yes.
He should be fired.
Why?
Doing this will only backfire.
He's your friend.
I won't pursue legal action against him,
but I can't pretend nothing happened.
Mr. Huang,
this worker has been
an outstanding worker in the factory
for many years
and was even awarded
as a city-level labor model.
But now, he's neither outstanding
nor exemplary.
I... I'll step out for a moment.
(Director's Office)
Do you have to be so arbitrary?
Didn't we agree that I would
handle this matter entirely?
Why don't you listen to my advice?
Only by doing this
can the workers understand
that causing trouble
will never achieve their goals,
no matter how long they've worked
or how high their status is.
I don't want to
see such things happen again.
You are just using violence
to control violence.
I don't think firing anyone
can solve the problem.
If you insist on doing this,
just fire me too.
Before completing this task,
you have no right to leave.
Manager Bai,
the keys to the cold storage.
The workers aren't entirely unreasonable.
I've reported to you before
about the cold storage issue.
They have returned the keys.
It's surprising that someone in the factory
has such awareness.
What's his name?
Lu Xiaolu.
Master Niu,
even Xiaolu has backed down,
what should we do?
Well...
You need to figure out a solution.
(Refrigerated Truck)
Master,
don't worry about it.
- Let's go.
- But...
Who is that person?
Veteran fitter Master Niu.
The model worker who splashed
pig's blood?
All of us
can put in some effort
to tide over this situation.
To others,
this might solve a big problem.
Why are you still thinking about others?
When Ma led people
to take the ice storage,
your attitude was not like this.
I'll pay for the rent
of the new cold storage.
I won't implicate you.
Do you think we're afraid to spend money?
We just don't want you
to be manipulated by Bai Lan every time.
That's enough.
I know.
This is the last time.
It won't happen again.
You all know that
I left Shanghai
without saying goodbye.
I owe it to her.
This time,
consider it as me repaying her.
Hello?
What?
They might fire Master Niu?
Okay, okay, I got it.
Lu Xiaolu,
look what you did.
♪Escaping the night in moonlight♪
♪Avoiding the guards using darkness♪
♪Lost and no longer lost♪
♪You go find a spaceship♪
♪I'll lead away the guards♪
♪I don't have a spaceship♪
♪So we can't reach♪
♪The moon♪
Doctor Bai?
Big Feet.
Long time no see.
Well,
it's been a while since I last came.
I really missed here.
So I came to take a look.
Me too.
How have you been doing
in Beijing these years?
Beijing
is great,
a big city.
But
there are many people
with the same dreams as mine.
There are more stages, too.
Doctor Bai,
do you know?
In Beijing, there's a bar street
where I perform
every night.
Many people come to watch me sing.
It's lively.
When you release an album,
remember to send me a copy.
Do you remember?
Xiaolu sneakily
fixed your bike there
back then.
It was so many years ago.
Was it that long ago?
It's like
yesterday to me.
It's been a long time.
Things have changed.
But you
finally won Xiaoying's heart.
Xiaolu
argued with Guangnan
for you today.
Is it about the cold storage?
Yeah.
You know, Doctor Bai,
Xiaolu never stands by
when you're in trouble.
Technically, I should thank him,
but I don't want to see him now.
Do you not want to
or are you afraid?
It's been a long time
since we drank together, right?
Yes, Dad.
I've spent little time with you
these years.
You don't have to accompany me.
I'm quite comfortable
here by myself.
I understand.
Our house is full of memories
of you and Mom.
That's right.
Your mother
used to complain that
my cooking was too oily
and salty,
but I could never change.
Now that she's gone,
whenever I cook,
I feel like she's nagging at me.
I just...
That's insane. Come on.
They say time can make you
forget everything,
but it's not that easy.
I've heard about
Bai Lan's situation.
After all these years,
she seems like a different person.
I don't know if I should believe her.
Do you
believe in yourself?
Believing in myself?
I mean
do you believe you are right about her?
Dr. Tian.
- Long time no see.
I called you out in a hurry
because an old friend
also wants to see you.
- Okay.
- I hope you don't mind.
- No problem.
- Please.
Master Niu.
Please sit.
Please.
Thank you.
Coming.
Dr. Tian,
I heard about your wife's matter.
Tian's wife
had no job.
The factory used to
reimburse some of her medical expenses,
but then they stopped.
Her hepatitis
turned into cirrhosis,
and then liver cancer.
Tian sold his house
to treat his wife.
Ah, let's not talk about this.
Let's have a drink.
Let's drink.
Okay.
By the way,
these are the medicines you often take.
I remember they're
hard to find in Fucheng,
so I brought some
from Shanghai for you.
Thank you.
You are so thoughtful
and even care about an old man like me.
It's been years.
I was worried you wouldn't
like the Fucheng dishes,
so I made some sandwiches for you,
just like
you taught me back then.
(Good Cat Restaurant)
Our factory hasn't been performing well.
They can't pay salaries,
so they distribute canned goods
from the inventory
to everyone.
I use bread
and various canned goods
to make different flavored sandwiches.
I remember back in the factory,
the canned fish
was the most popular.
Every Friday, you would rush off work
to line up and get some.
Yes.
I didn't expect
you still remember these things.
But you should also remember that
you were once
part of our food factory, right?
Are you blaming me
for something?
You two must
have a lot to say to me.
I'm all ears.
Dr. Bai,
I'll still address you
the way we did
in the factory.
Us workers
don't have big demands,
just pay us our wages
and cover
our medical expenses.
Then we'll do whatever
you ask us to do.
But if you drive me away,
will that solve the problem?
Salaries still won't be paid,
medical expenses won't be covered,
and the factory
will continue to deteriorate
until it closes.
Workers will be laid off.
Not to mention the whole country,
how many factories
in Fucheng have closed?
So what I need now is
for everyone to trust me.
As long as we revive this factory,
these lingering issues will all be solved.
How can we trust you?
The factory has promised us
many times before.
But each time,
it's just an empty promise.
They keep delaying, day after day.
So many people,
so many families,
have been dragged down by this.
But this time is different.
We're all in the same boat.
Our goals are the same.
Yes,
reforming definitely has risks,
but it's only temporary.
Once we have a modern corporate system
and improved management,
the food factory
will definitely be revived.
When the factory is profitable,
medical expenses and wages
won't be a problem anymore.
And in the future, we will expand
and introduce new equipment
and develop new products,
don't you look forward to that?
Why should we believe you?
I will convince the Italians
to cooperate with us.
When I succeed,
you will believe me, okay?
Really?
I'll be honest with you.
I made a bet.
If I can't revive the factory,
I lose.
Bottoms up.
(Good Cat)
(Lili Video Lounge)
Did you arrange this?
Since you did,
why didn't you come out yourself
but let your master talk to me?
It is good to make it clear
to Master Niu.
He has authority in the factory.
Everyone listens to him.
I know.
But the pig blood incident last time
really had nothing to do with him.
Will he still be fired?
Don't worry about that.
With me around, it won't happen.
That's good.
Thank you.
For what?
For the cold storage.
No need.
I did it for myself.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'm exhausted.
I don't want to battle with you
every time we deliver goods.
Alright, I'll leave then.
Go talk to your master.
He'll tell you the outcome
of our conversation.
(Lili Video Lounge)
What do you think of
Bai Lan's words?
Besides taking a gamble,
what other choice do we have?
(Transfer Method, Violation Responsibility,
Transfer of Premises)
Hello?
I have good news to tell you.
There's progress on the workers' side.
Master Niu promised me that
he can convince the workers
to resume work.
Really?
They changed their minds so quickly?
Because deep down,
they all love the factory
and don't want to give up
the last bit of hope.
That's good.
(Huaxing Investment Group
Land Transfer Agreement)
Master,
the factory really didn't fire you?
Of course.
What do you think we are doing?
Taking some parts
and selling them for retirement?
We all agreed that
if you were fired,
none of us would work anymore.
Master, it's great that you're back.
It seems that Doctor Bai
does have a conscience after all.
Stop the nonsense.
We're about to start working.
Let's quickly inspect
to prevent any issues
once work starts.
Alright.
We workers have strength!
Every day...
Every...
Oh no.
Master.
I forgot to take the new parts.
When can you stop
being scatterbrained?
Go get them now.
One hour later,
we still have to attend
the workshop leaders'
return-to-work meeting.
- Alright, Master.
- Be quick.
I'll come back in a minute.
Why did you come back so soon?
Dad!
- Master!
You scared me!
Why were your eyes closed?
You also scared me!
It's okay. I won't die.
Who hit you?
Tell me, I'll deal with them.
Master, didn't you see clearly?
- Tall or short?
- Fat or thin?
I didn't see clearly.
Are you okay elsewhere?
I'm fine.
What's this?
Oh, that...
A friend
brought me
some books
and a chess set
for me to kill time.
I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Master Niu,
I brought Mr. Huang here to see you.
Don't get up.
Hello, Master Niu.
It's regrettable what happened.
I promise you and all the workers that
we'll get to the bottom of this
and catch the real culprit.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's a Greek gift.
I heard you've been working hard
to ensure the factory resumes smoothly.
Why not take this opportunity to rest?
The hospital expenses
will be covered by the factory.
Alright, Manager Bai?
No problem.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute.
Lu Xiaolu,
we meet again.
What's the matter?
How do you plan to find
the person who attacked my master?
This is a matter of the factory.
As far as I know,
you're no longer part of the factory.
Looks like
you like to meddle in my affairs.
Be my guest.
♪Coldness is a form of protection♪
♪It seems that tenderness♪
♪Makes one weak♪
♪Once hurt♪
♪Obsessions fade away♪
♪Things become a lot easier♪
♪Especially when it comes to love♪
♪But facing this loneliness♪
♪I realized my♪
♪Melting coldness♪
♪A brave choice♪
♪This is how the journey begins♪
♪Forget about the result♪
♪Just see it as a dream♪
♪'Cause I say♪
♪This is why I stay♪
♪I'll be on my way♪
♪Listen to my play♪