[Coroner's Diary]
[Episode 34]
[Marquis of Zhongyong's Mansion]
Father, Mother.
Yu is back.
Yu. My dear Yu.
-Mother.
-You're finally back.
It was with great difficulty that
I gained the Empress Dowager's pity
and was granted the chance
to leave the palace,
so I cannot stay for long.
I have important matters
to discuss with Father.
Mother, please return to your room
and rest.
I want to stay with you, Yu.
Yan,
escort your mother back.
I'll wait for you outside.
Mother.
This is a letter from the Empress
to her brother, General Zhao.
Please deliver it to the Northern Army
as soon as possible, Father.
What exactly happened?
The Crown Prince was eager
to defend his mother
and ended up offending His Majesty.
Father.
Okay.
I'll send your brother
to deliver it immediately.
The Empress said
we must first ensure
the Crown Prince's safety
before planning our next move.
I understand what's at stake.
I'll return to the palace now.
Yu.
Must you really
accompany the Crown Prince
during his confinement
in the Imperial Clan Court?
Wherever he is,
that's where I'll be.
Alright.
You may leave.
Once everything is arranged,
I will send someone
to deliver the message to you.
I, Yu,
thank you, Father.
Farewell, Your Majesty.
Sui.
Are you still afraid of your father,
His Majesty?
Then can you tell me
what you're worried about?
Father is very angry.
Will Mother and Che die?
Here.
Sui, don't worry.
Her Majesty and His Highness
just did something wrong,
and His Majesty only deposed them
from the position of Empress
and Crown Prince.
If only people didn't have to die.
Once they die,
they can't speak
or move anymore,
just like my mother.
Consort Jin was a fairy from heaven.
Now that you've grown up,
of course she had to return.
The dead cannot come back to life,
nor do they return to heaven.
Wan, you don't have to comfort me
with lies.
Sui...
Little Wan'er!
Why has Che been confined
in the Imperial Clan Court?
Such a refined person as he is,
how could he have behaved improperly
before His Majesty?
That's not something we should discuss.
Right, right.
It's none of our business,
so we shouldn't pry.
Sui.
Don't follow my example.
Have you visited the Empress Dowager?
Not yet.
Yan asked me to invite you and Chi
to his residence.
He said he needs your help with something.
Both of us?
Not just me for medical treatment?
Yan specifically instructed
you to bring your coroner's kit.
[Prince Xin's Mansion]
Your Highness, they're here.
Esteemed couple.
Newly wedded as you are,
I apologize for the intrusion.
I truly have no choice.
Chi.
You won't blame me, will you?
You jest, Yan.
Has your eyesight improved, Yan?
Thanks to Wan's treatment,
my vision has indeed improved,
though
I can only make out shapes
in dim light.
Yan, why did you ask me
to bring my coroner's kit?
If there's any legal matter,
it's best to report it
to the authorities first.
It concerns a private matter
from years ago
in Prince Xin's family.
Before the truth is uncovered,
Wan and Chi, I kindly ask you both
to keep this matter discreet.
That's only proper.
Mother.
I've brought Chi and his wife, Wan,
to see you.
Are these...
The late Princess Xin's remains?
All these years,
I've done everything in my power
to preserve Mother's body,
but this is the best I could do.
Yan, do you want me to perform an autopsy
on the late Princess's body?
Why?
Because I want to know
what exactly caused Mother's death.
Please help me, Wan.
Yan, there's no need for this.
I will certainly do my best.
It's just
investigating the cause of death
will inevitably damage the body.
It would be best for you to stay away,
Yan.
It's okay.
She's already gone,
and her body
will eventually turn to dust.
The truth
is my only consolation now.
Mother's spirit in heaven
will surely understand my intentions.
Besides,
Wan, you probably don't know that
before my late mother was married,
she also studied with the Medicine King,
learning pharmaceutical skills for a year,
making her somewhat his apprentice too.
She had long come to terms with
the cycle of life and death,
and surely wouldn't mind
what happens after she died.
So the late Princess Xin and I share
the bond of being fellow disciples.
I'm deeply honored.
I'll definitely do everything in my power
to bring the cause of
the late Princess's death
to light.
Thank you, Wan.
The skull is intact,
muscle lines unclear,
small and thin.
The pelvis is wide and short,
with thin pelvic walls.
The side walls are flat and shallow.
The pelvic cavity is short and wide,
forming a cylindrical shape.
The corpse is well-preserved,
and there are obvious signs of childbirth.
Yan.
The late Princess was
in the prime of her youth when she died.
Since you suspect
the cause of her death,
what unusual symptoms
did she show before passing?
That day,
Mother went into the palace
to deliver medicine
she personally prepared for the Empress.
She only returned home
after the night watch began.
As soon as she got home,
she shut herself in her bedroom.
I was worried,
so I snuck in to check on her.
Ze.
Ze!
Ze...
At first,
Mother only had chest pains.
Ze!
Then she lost her sight.
Soon after, her hearing
failed as well.
Before dying, she lost all her senses
and was vomiting blood continuously.
In just one night,
she was gone.
The imperial physician came,
but claimed that Mother
showed no signs of poisoning.
But since that day,
my health
and my eyesight
have been deteriorating day by day.
Did the physician examine that cup of tea?
Since the physician said
it wasn't poisoning,
why would he bother with
such trivial matters?
May I perform an autopsy
and test for poison on the late Princess?
The color of these bones
is too dull.
Use mine.
No.
Mine should be used.
The late Princess indeed
died of poisoning.
The mystery that has troubled me
for years is finally solved.
Thank you, Wan.
The incense is cool and delicate,
carrying a serene grace reminiscent
of winter plum blossoms.
It's seemingly made from
submerged agarwood,
cloves,
and rose water.
Indeed.
This incense
is called Soul-Reviving Plum,
my late mother's favorite incense.
If you like it, Wan,
I'll make some more for you.
Yan.
You still need to avoid
straining your eyes.
Since childhood, my late mother
had taught me how to craft
and appreciate incense.
Now,
whenever I blend fragrances,
it feels as if Mother
is still right here by my side.
Yan, you still have your mother's memories
for comfort.
That's already much more than I have.
Chi.
Have you ever questioned
your mother's cause of death?
What do you mean by that, Yan?
Less than seven days
after my mother passed away,
your mother
died due to
postpartum hemorrhage.
In life, they were
close friends,
and they both met tragic deaths
almost simultaneously,
which seems too coincidental.
The Empress Dowager and my late father
never mentioned this to me.
Back then, your father entrusted you,
barely 100 days old,
to the Empress Dowager
and went to Shuoxi alone.
Rumors spread throughout the capital,
saying that your father believed
you weren't his biological son,
so he abandoned you
and returned to Shuoxi in anger.
If not orchestrated,
how could the rumors all be so consistent?
Yan Chi.
Rumors stop with the wise.
These petty tricks
are nothing compared to Father's
loyalty and courage.
Yan.
Are you suggesting that
my mother was framed?
I have only suspicions,
but no proof.
With all these considered,
Chi and Wan, please
help me uncover the truth.
Yan, since you've suspected the causes of
the Princesses' deaths for years,
have you discovered anything about
the culprit's identity or motive?
Since my father followed my mother
in death,
I, as a
blind and frail royal descendant,
despite all my suspicions and resentment,
am powerless.
Chi, if you and Wan
can help resolve my doubts,
I would be
deeply grateful.
Yan Chi.
Childbirth for a woman
is like passing through death's door.
Even without poison,
there are many ways
that can cause death.
Mother has been gone for years.
Even if I were to exhume her remains now,
it would still be difficult
to determine the cause of death.
If what Yan said is true,
we might as well start by investigating
the late Princess Xin,
so as not to disturb Mother's spirit.
Do you know who the late Princess Xin
brought medicine to in the palace?
It was His Majesty.
His Majesty returned gravely wounded
back then.
If the late Princess Xin
hadn't brought medicine into the palace,
he might not have survived.
So you mean
the person who poisoned Mother
might not only be the Empress,
but also be His Majesty?
I can't make sense of this, either.
Logically speaking,
the late Princess Xin
saved His Majesty's life,
so why would His Majesty and the Empress
want to kill her?
Perhaps it was because the late Prince Xin
had extensive connections at court,
and His Majesty was just
recovering from serious injuries,
so he wanted to secure his power.
But that doesn't make sense either.
Why target the late Princess Xin?
Forget it.
There are too few clues.
I'm at a loss at how to proceed.
Too many things
are connected to the palace.
Let's investigate Prince Jin's case first.
Today,
Sui brought up Consort Jin's death
to me unprompted.
I noticed his expression was
very different from usual,
as if he remembered something
but was afraid to speak of it.
In the next few days,
I want to enter the palace more often
to keep the Empress Dowager
and Sui company.
With everything that's happened,
they must be suffering the most.
There's one more thing.
Jiang Heying,
the one who assassinated Father,
indeed works for Yan Qi.
Yan Qi has been sending him money
frequently these years
to train assassins.
When His Majesty
allowed him to return to his hometown
in Qianzhou as a chief general,
it was likely arranged
by Yan Qi behind the scenes as well.
How heartless.
Even if he disregards
the brotherhood between you two,
Prince Rui is still his uncle.
In the royal family,
there are no true father-son bonds,
let alone uncle and nephew relationships.
However,
whether Prince Cheng acted on his own
or under His Majesty's orders,
we may never know.
If it truly was on His Majesty's order,
we won't be able to touch him
anytime soon.
We need to find a way
to make Yan Qi
fall out of royal favor first.
Don't worry about that.
I already have a plan.
Now that he has hopes of becoming heir,
his ambition is at its peak.
He will certainly use Wang Han's testimony
to try to depose the Empress
and root out the Crown Prince completely.
As soon as he takes action,
that's when I'll spring my trap.
Your Highness.
This is freshly stewed
angelica mutton soup.
Have some while it's warm.
I have no appetite.
Just leave it there.
Then perhaps later.
All right.
Mother also specifically instructed me
to prepare medicinal food
for Your Highness as prescribed.
You've gone to visit Mother?
Has Mother suffered any more torture?
Mother is a woman of strong will.
Now that the Empress Dowager
has regained control of palace affairs,
no one dares
to withhold Mother's allowances.
Mother
hopes Your Highness will remain calm.
In time,
someone will help us
resolve this crisis completely.
I've asked my father
to deliver Mother's letter
to your uncle's army.
Please don't give up hope, Your Highness.
Thank you for your efforts, Zhaoyu.
As long as Your Highness is well,
no matter how difficult it is for me,
I'm happy to endure it.
This sweet soup I prepared for
Your Majesty
simmered for a full four hours.
I've been waiting for
Your Majesty to come tonight.
You finally came.
My beloved, as for this sweet soup,
why is it always
so mild in flavor?
Wouldn't it be better
if it were a bit sweeter?
I'm worried that too much sweetness
might be bad for my complexion.
My beloved, you've always been
the most beautiful woman in the palace.
With Your Majesty's praise,
even if I were to die right now,
my heart would still be filled with joy.
I'm quite tired today.
Let's
retire early.
Your Highness. Your Highness.
It's time to get up, Your Highness.
The contact is waiting at the door.
Uncle has come for us?
Hurry up and get changed.
It's time to go.
All right.
Zhaoyu,
why haven't you changed yet?
Your Highness, I'm not leaving.
I've never practiced martial arts.
I'm not good at riding horse,
nor can I run fast.
I would only be a burden to Your Highness.
If I stay behind,
I can stall them a bit.
Any delay will be helpful.
No,
staying here is too dangerous.
Come with me.
Your Highness.
After all, I'm the eldest
legitimate daughter of the Qin family.
They wouldn't dare harm me.
Please hurry up and leave, Your Highness.
Please go.
If I can escape safely,
I promise I'll come back for you.
Go.
Greetings, Your Highness.
The situation is critical.
I'm afraid you'll have to
put up with this.
How did it go?
His Highness has met with the contact
and safely left the detention area.
The Crown Princess took the initiative
to stay and cover for His Highness.
Great.
The Qin family deserves
great credit for this.
Now that His Highness has escaped,
you should find a way to seek shelter too,
Your Majesty.
If the attendants notice this
when bringing breakfast,
His Majesty will surely
come to question you.
I'd like to see
in what manner he dares face me.
[Qionghua Palace]
Fire! Fire!
Help! Someone help!
Help! Fire!
There's a fire!
Someone come quickly!
Yuan Qing!
Where's the fire?
Your Majesty,
judging by the flames,
it seems to be the Imperial Clan Court.
Your Majesty,
please put on more clothes.
Your Majesty!
Father,
the fire at the Imperial Clan Court
has been put out.
Only the detain area of Prince Che
suffered severe damage;
the fire didn't spread elsewhere.
How are Prince Che and his wife?
Princess Zhaoyu is unharmed,
but Prince Che...
His whereabouts are unknown.
I searched the fire scene
and found no corpse or remains.
How absurd!
The heavily guarded restricted area
mysteriously caught fire,
and somehow the confined Prince Che
just vanished without a trace?
Father, please don't worry.
I've investigated and found out that
the fire
started in Prince Che's bedchamber.
But with Prince Che missing,
it's inappropriate for me to question
Princess Zhaoyu about matters
in their private chambers.
However, I believe
Prince Che's disappearance
and the fire
must be connected.
I've ordered a review of the Imperial Clan
Court's personnel records
to identify any suspicious individuals.
Would an arsonist bold enough
to set fire to the Imperial Clan Court
be so obedient
as to register
their name in the records?
I was foolish.
Chi.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Do you also believe
Prince Che's mysterious disappearance
and the fire at
the Imperial Clan Court
are somewhat connected?
I haven't examined the fire scene,
so I dare not speculate.
However, I believe
Prince Che's disappearance
should not be made public.
I'm willing to depart immediately
to search for Prince Che.
Anyone capable of
sneaking in the Imperial Clan Court
at night
is no ordinary person.
Take Wan
to the Imperial Clan Court
for investigation immediately—
be sure
to find the mastermind behind this arson.
As for
the search for Che,
leave that to Prince Cheng.
As
you command, Your Majesty.
You may leave as well.
Come on.
Rise.
Thank you, Father.
I have received
a report that
Lord Zhao has secretly brought a troop
and is staking out outside the capital.
I'm worried that
your brother Che
has been bewitched by Zhao
and may commit treason.
I specially order you
to go and stop him immediately.
If he truly harbors rebellious intentions,
then don't blame me
for setting aside our father-son bond.
I am
willing to ease your burden, Father.
You are good.
Now,
you are the only grown son I have
fit to serve as heir.
If
anything goes wrong,
you must
prioritize your own safety above all.
Father, you've shown me so much care.
I'll definitely
not fail your expectations, Father.
Go now.
I take my leave, Father.
Prince Che
hasn't been sleeping well lately,
[Imperial Clan Court]
so Princess Zhaoyu doesn't allow us
to attend to him before bed at night.
Right.
That's why we slept quite deeply
last night,
with no one keeping watch in the yard.
By the time we smelled the smoke
and rushed here to put out the fire,
Prince Che was already gone.
Where were the Imperial Guards
on duty last night?
Your Highness.
Only we servants were stationed here.
No Imperial Guards
have ever been assigned.
Understood.
You may leave.
Yes.
Is there anything wrong?
According to the rule,
the restricted quarters
where a prince is confined
should have at least three shifts
of Imperial Guards on duty in rotation.
But there isn't even
one Imperial Guard here,
which is truly abnormal.
The Imperial Guards
answer directly to His Majesty.
Perhaps
His Majesty intentionally left
Prince Che a way out?
If His Majesty truly had such intentions,
he could have simply
demoted Yan Che to a commoner
and sentenced him to exile.
Why would he confine him here,
neither releasing him
nor guarding him strictly?
His Majesty's actions
seem more like setting a trap.
This must be where the fire started.
There are no tables or desks around here,
which suggests this candlestick
wasn't originally placed here,
but was used by someone
to set the curtains on fire
and then carelessly discarded.
The duty room is right
in the outer quarters.
It would only take the attendants
a few seconds to get here.
Prince Che must have left
before the fire started.
What if the arsonist
was Princess Zhaoyu?
Ms. Qin, come out and respond immediately,
or you'll be charged with treason.
What is he doing here instead of
searching for Prince Che?
Because when villains gain power,
they first become wildly arrogant.
It took you so long to come out here.
What,
feeling too ashamed
to show your face?
Prince Cheng, mind your words.
Even though Prince Che
has been deposed and confined,
I'm still your sister-in-law,
and you should show me some respect.
Sister-in-law?
Are you worthy of that title?
You committed arson
and helped
the deposed Crown Prince escape.
You only deserve to call yourself
Sinner Qin.
You accuse me of arson,
but do you have any evidence,
Prince Cheng?
My word is the evidence.
Let me ask you,
where has the deposed Crown Prince
fled to?
I was in shock,
so I don't remember anything.
Then I'll have to let the matrons
from the Imperial Punishment Department
help you jog your memory.
Someone,
tie her up!
Yes.
You even put on the hood.
You're shameless!
Prince Cheng, are you trying to openly
assault a member of the imperial family?
Yan Chi.
What are you doing?
I want to kill you.
Are you sure?
If you kill me with your own hands,
Father will never let you off.
Your entire family
and your Princess Wan
will all be buried with me.
Buried with me!
I'll spare Qin
if you spare me,
what do you say?
Yan Chi.
His Majesty is still waiting for
the investigation results.
His Majesty personally ordered
me and Princess Wan
to investigate the scene.
Princess Zhaoyu is an eyewitness,
and should rightfully be in my custody.
Prince Cheng,
I hope you'll carefully remember
the task His Majesty assigned to you.
If you overstep your bounds again,
I wouldn't mind
disciplining you on His Majesty's behalf.
I've taken note of it.
It won't happen again.
I've already examined the fire scene.
You deliberately set the fire
during breakfast to give
Prince Che time to escape, didn't you?
This matter cannot be concealed.
Even if it weren't me,
someone else would investigate
and easily conclude it was arson.
Did you consider
the consequences before acting?
I did.
But what other option did I have?
If Prince Rui were in danger,
what would you do?
If you could risk your life
to give him a chance of survival,
would you do it?
I would.
Therefore,
I will never reveal his whereabouts.
I never intended to survive.
Imprisonment or beheading,
I accept whatever His Majesty decides.
If we wanted to charge you,
we wouldn't have saved you
from Prince Cheng just now.
But do you know that
you won't be the only one
held accountable?
If His Majesty pursues this matter,
the entire Qin family's lives
will be at risk.
I know.
But I couldn't bear
to watch him
trapped to death here.
Even if we were willing
to stay here for the rest of our lives,
Prince Cheng would never spare us.
I had no choice.
It was my fault for lacking resolve.
If I had taken my own life
during the fire,
I wouldn't have implicated
my parents and siblings.
Wan,
I beg you.
If you would help me,
the Qin family could be saved.
I only ask you
to wait another two hours.
Once Prince Che
safely leaves the capital,
you can tell His Majesty the truth.
I beg you.
Please get up.
Zhaoyu, you don't need to beg me.
Even if just for my father's sake,
I won't stand by and do nothing.
Besides,
in my heart,
you're also a victim.
I'll do my best
to protect you and your mother.
But since your father and brother
are too deeply entangled
with the Crown Prince,
I'm afraid I can't save them.
Gamblers must accept defeat.
Since Father chose
to assist the Crown Prince,
he should bear the consequences.
All right.
Previously,
out of jealousy,
I grew suspicious of you,
and that was wrong of me.
I apologize
to you here.
Please get up, Zhaoyu.
Let bygones be bygones.
As long as
there're no more misunderstanding
between us in the future.
Yan Li.
Chi.
What's up?
Did His Majesty mention anything
about Prince Che's escape?
No.
His Majesty has been handling
state affairs all morning
and hasn't said a word
about Prince Che.
Perhaps
he wants to conceal the news
to prevent unrest among court officials.
Everyone knows about
the fire at the Imperial Clan Court.
If it's not clarified,
that's what would cause unrest.
His Majesty must be aware of this.
Perhaps
His Majesty is demonstrating
his unpredictable imperial authority,
deliberately keeping us in the dark
about his intentions.
Prince Che's fate is still unknown.
No matter how much he wants
to demonstrate his authority,
he wouldn't use this situation
for posturing.
Not necessarily.
Yan's eyes haven't recovered,
yet he still runs around happily all day,
delaying my marriage with Ning.
Isn't that just to show that
he can remain calm
even if Mount Tai collapses before him?
Perhaps
it's precisely because I cannot see
that I have no fear.
And without fear, there is no worry.
Yan, you're really as light as a swallow.
I didn't even hear your footsteps.
Why have you come here, Yan?
I originally wanted to ask about the fire,
but hearing what you've said,
I'd better not
bring trouble upon myself.
Let's pretend I was never here.
Then
we never saw you, Yan.
Chi.
Considering how often you took the blame
for me when we were little,
I'll definitely keep it a secret, Yan.
If it weren't for my eye condition,
whenever you got into trouble,
I would have outrun you.
Do you really mean it?
Without a doubt.
Chi.
Look.
This is me.
Then this is me.
Holding hands.
Why did you draw yourself as tall as me?
I want to draw it even taller than you.
Taking off!
Yan,
come with me.
It's right here.
Feel it.
His Majesty has arrived.
Sinner Zhao, kneel immediately
to welcome His Majesty.
In the first year of Zhaohui,
His Majesty personally bestowed upon me
the title of Empress.
Unless there is an imperial edict
announcing to the world
that my position is revoked,
I remain
the most noble woman under heaven.
The Empress Dowager is still alive.
The most noble woman under heaven
is not yet you.
Now,
your brother has dared to
lead the Northern Army into the capital
without imperial permission,
conspiring with you
to help Prince Che escape.
How dare you still shamelessly
claim yourself Empress?
My elder brother
has commanded the Northern Army
by imperial order for years,
serving Your Majesty loyally
and protecting the nation without fail.
Everything I've done
is also for keeping
the legitimate bloodline
of the Yan family unstained.
Why am I not worthy of being the Empress?
A weak and incompetent
Crown Prince,
unfit to be a ruler—
what does it matter even if he's of
the legitimate bloodline?
If you
have any self-awareness,
relinquish the position of Empress
as soon as possible.
I
will ensure the safety of
you and your son
for the rest of your lives.
Otherwise,
don't blame me
for disregarding our marital bond.
Marital bond?
What marital bond ever existed between us?
If it weren't for
Che's claim to the throne,
how could I have borne with you
all these years?
Do you think
just by securing your position as Empress,
and with the Northern Army
backing that worthless son of yours,
you can seize my empire?
You're truly outsmarted
by your own cleverness.
Zhao Shuhua.
Haven't you ever wondered
why the security
at the Imperial Clan Court was so lax,
allowing that worthless son of yours
to escape so easily?
What have you done?
I had promised the Empress Dowager
to spare Yan Che's life.
If he hadn't escaped,
as long as the Empress Dowager is alive,
I
would never cause her grief.
But alas,
he ran away.
Since he doesn't want my protection,
I have no choice but to let him
resign himself to fate.
I'll kill you!
You demon!
Give me back my Che!
Let him go!
Spare him!
The Empress dislikes light.
Remove all candles and lamps.
From now on, Fengyi Palace
shall not see even
a glimmer of light.
Don't go! Come back!
♪ Endless wind and rain ♪
Come back!
Che...
♪ What a pity ♪
My Che...
♪ Endless wind and rain ♪
♪ What a pity ♪