[Coroner's Diary]
[Episode 20]
Little Wan'er.
You must have waited for a long time.
What's wrong?
It didn't go well?
Chi,
can you please behave yourself?
Keep your hands to yourself.
I can't see.
I'm leaving now.
Crazy girl.
Ning is best this way.
Every time I see her,
I feel envious.
I feel envious when I see you.
This is the prefect's office.
Watch your words.
Then we'll talk when we get back.
When we get back?
Even then, wait till we have free time.
Alright, alright.
Tell me,
if I were Qing—
no medical skills,
no forensic knowledge—
and tried to take revenge,
would I have ended up like her?
You wouldn't.
I know you sympathize with her.
But what she sought
was vengeance for evil.
What you want is
a world without injustice.
Even with the deepest hatred,
you could never bring yourself to kill.
You're right.
Our ancestors set the laws
based on reason and principle.
I hope Qing's loyalty
and righteousness
can help her keep her life.
Don't worry.
His Majesty has been troubled
by the gold heist case
that's still unsolved.
If Governor Wang solves this case
before his retirement,
the rewards he'll receive
will benefit his family
for three generations.
He won't let this opportunity slip away.
Governor Wang,
please let me go!
I don't want anything anymore!
Pang Fuliang,
you're causing trouble even in death!
You'll have no son to tend your grave.
All the scum have been dealt with.
Does it feel satisfying?
Absolutely.
Chi,
let's go.
I'll wait for you outside.
This may be goodbye for good.
What are your plans, Madam?
Governor Wang returned my dowry in full.
Before marriage,
I helped my father run an inn.
This money is enough to open an inn
for us to make a living.
Your Highness,
Wan,
we're good to go.
♪ The Dharma sees
the child's filial piety ♪
♪ He tries to find
and save his mother in hell ♪
♪ Ride on the auspicious cloud,
heading for Mount Lingshan ♪
♪ Buddha's compassion guides the way ♪
♪ Buddha's compassion ♪
♪ Guides the way ♪
Are you thinking about the capital?
We'll arrive tomorrow.
I want to visit my parents' graves first.
Alright.
After I report to the court,
I'll go pick you up
the day after tomorrow.
No.
I was about to talk to you about that.
Once we're back in the capital,
we can't go on like this anymore.
Don't worry about
the Marquis of Zhongyong.
He wouldn't dare harm you.
What if he uses me to pressure you
into serving the Crown Prince?
Qin Yan saw you risk your life to save me.
He knows how you feel about me.
The Marquis of Zhongyong
is my elder in name.
If he uses my future as a bargaining chip…
He wouldn't dare.
Even so, we need to vindicate
Prince Jin and my father.
We can't afford any new complications.
At least in public,
I should only be your strategist—
Master Wan.
Alright then.
As long as it puts your mind at ease,
I'll certainly comply.
But I'll never let you be pushed around.
Not by anyone.
Then Your Highness, please help me
make a name for myself in the capital.
Of course.
[Yan Che, the Crown Prince]
I, Qin Shu,
pay my respects to Your Highness.
[Qin Shu, the Marquis of Zhongyong]
[Zheng Baishi, the capital prefect]
Your Highness,
what troubles you?
Capital Prefect, go ahead.
The Marquis of Zhongyong
isn't an outsider.
Yes.
Just now, before His Majesty,
Prince Cheng openly questioned me
about the girls' case
and repeatedly implied that
His Highness has mishandled it.
His Majesty looked very displeased.
Yan Qi is such a conniving rat.
He keeps turning Father against me.
How shameless.
Your Highness, please calm down.
Though Prince Cheng
has acted against you again and again,
His Majesty's trust in you hasn't changed,
so he's no real threat.
If you can bring this case
to a successful close,
then no matter how hard
Prince Cheng schemes,
he won't be able to do a thing.
But His Majesty wants the case
solved by the end of the year.
New Year's Eve is approaching,
yet we still have no leads.
If all else fails…
we'll have to find a scapegoat
to break the deadlock first.
Your Highness,
don't do that.
It might offer temporary relief,
but if Prince Cheng found out,
it could land you in even deeper trouble.
Then what do you suggest?
Am I supposed
to let Yan Qi humiliate me
in front of everyone
at the New Year's banquet?
Your Highness,
I'd like to recommend someone.
This person has brilliant forensic skills
and is highly adept at deduction.
The murder cases in Jingzhou and Yuzhou
were successfully solved
thanks to his contributions.
Where is this person now?
If he's truly useful,
I'll reward him generously.
He'll arrive in the capital tomorrow.
Where is he currently employed?
I'll have him transferred over now.
Hold on.
Capital Prefect, don't rush.
This person is not a government official.
And due to his special background,
we'll need
to keep this operation under wraps.
This must be handled with extreme care.
If Prince Cheng finds out,
he's bound to interfere.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
I'll proceed with the utmost caution.
My Lady, the city gates are just ahead.
We're really back in the capital.
From today on,
there's no turning back for us.
Where did you pick it?
On a hill.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Are you headed to the palace?
I'll take you
to the Marquis Mansion first.
No.
If someone saw you,
how would you explain it?
I'll just say
I was escorting Yue Ning.
She's returning
to the Grand Princess's residence.
Alright then.
Be careful at the Marquis Mansion.
Don't compromise yourself for them.
Keep the Red Flare and eagle whistle
with you at all times.
Don't worry.
I won't let myself be taken advantage of.
There are too many eyes here.
You should go now.
Pass.
Wait for me.
His Highness treats you so well.
I'll learn to treat him well too.
Ning,
I should avoid
being involved with the Qin family.
Once we're in the capital,
I'm entrusting Wan to your care.
Little Wan'er is basically my sister now.
Chi, you don't get to entrust her to me
unless you're my brother-in-law.
My wife
can only be Wan and no one else.
Chi,
it'd be better
if you let me take care of her.
I promise I'll make sure
Wan enjoys herself.
Don't get any ideas.
Now that I'm back,
your days of partying and fooling around
are over.
I...
[Marquis of Zhongyong's Mansion]
Father,
Mother.
No need.
Greetings, Father, Mother.
How was it?
You must be exhausted from the journey.
I'm not tired.
Don't worry, Mother.
Did everything go smoothly?
Yes.
Father,
I've brought all three of my cousins back.
Good.
This one is Xiang.
This is Shuang.
And this
is Wan.
So you're Qin Wan?
Greetings, Uncle.
When I last saw you,
you were just a little girl
babbling baby talk.
And look at you now, all grown up.
Xiang and Shuang
have both turned into fine young women.
-Thank you for your compliment.
-Thank you, Aunt.
[Hu, the Marquis of Zhongyong's wife]
You must be hungry.
Let's head inside for a meal
and catch up over food.
Come.
Let's go.
You must be tired.
I'm not tired, Mother.
[Marquis of Zhongyong's Mansion]
Usually, Yu is the only girl in the house,
but now that you're all here,
the place is going to feel so lively.
Mother,
we've already had lunch.
Why isn't Yu back yet?
The Empress summoned her today,
so she went into the palace.
Wan,
though you grew up
in the Medicine King Valley,
you've been taught proper manners.
Uncle,
because of my poor health,
my late father never pushed me
to learn needlework and the like.
But when it came to manners,
even the slightest misstep
would earn me a scolding.
That's just how my brother was.
Easygoing and carefree most days,
but he was always strict
about manners and conduct.
That's why
you've turned out
to be such a fine young woman.
Yes, indeed.
It's a pity that
you don't look anything like your father.
You're right, Aunt.
I've wondered
if I take after my late mother.
But she passed so early.
I never got the chance to see her.
Aunt, do you still remember
what my mother looked like?
How could I ever forget?
Look.
Your eyebrows and eyes
are exactly like hers.
She was such a gentle
and thoughtful woman.
If only
she had been in better health.
Let's not talk about those sad things.
Wan,
have a seat.
Sit down.
It's not often
you girls come to the capital.
The New Year is
just around the corner.
By then, let Yan
give you a tour.
Really?
Of course.
The markets here are far livelier
than those in Jingzhou.
Are Yan and the girls back?
[Qin Zhaoyu, the legitimate daughter
of the Marquis of Zhongyong]
Greetings, Father, Mother.
You've had a long journey, Yan.
Are these
the two cousins from Jingzhou and Wan?
Yu,
this is Xiang.
This is Shuang.
And this is Wan.
Greetings, Xiang, Shuang.
Wan.
Greetings, Yu.
I used to be
the youngest one in the family.
Now that you're here,
finally, someone is younger than me.
Look how happy Yu is.
You're back so late.
Did you eat in the palace?
I did.
It happened that
the Crown Prince
came to greet the Empress today,
so Her Majesty kept me for lunch.
I had to say I was in a hurry
to see my cousins
before she agreed to let me go.
Wan and the others
have been traveling nonstop.
They must be tired.
They should get some rest soon.
Dear, you're always so thoughtful.
From now on,
this is your home.
If you ever need anything,
feel free
to tell your aunt.
Let's go.
Father.
His Majesty lost his temper
with the Crown Prince again today.
Stay
out of this.
Don't ask the Crown Prince about it.
But...
If you truly wish
to become the Crown Princess,
you mustn't appear to meddle in politics.
I understand.
You should get close
to your three cousins,
especially Wan.
I understand.
When she arrived earlier,
she was so poised
and tactful,
reminding me
of her father's gentlemanly grace.
Keep a close eye
on Qin Xiang and Qin Shuang.
Qin An's case
caused a huge stir at court.
If the Crown Prince hadn't
spoken in my defense before His Majesty,
I might've been blamed
for failing to keep my household in order.
The Qin family must not be involved
in any more scandals.
I understand.
Should we help move things forward
between Yan Chi and Wan?
It's not as simple as you think.
Prince Rui and his son have always
kept out of power struggles.
They won't openly
side with the Crown Prince
just for a marriage.
Besides,
with Yan Chi's status,
his marriage
would need His Majesty's approval.
If we interfere,
His Majesty will become suspicious.
Yes.
This time,
Yan Chi parted ways with you
before even entering the capital
to avoid suspicion.
As for how he really feels about Wan,
let's wait and see.
Just go with the flow.
Yes.
Lately,
Prince Cheng has been
handling matters decisively
and has won favor with His Majesty.
Noble Consort Su
rose in status thanks to her son
and became His Majesty's favorite.
The Empress and Crown Prince are
in a tough spot now.
Make sure
there's no repeat of what happened
with Liu Renli.
I know I was wrong, Father.
I've recommended Wan
to the Crown Prince.
If she can help him out of this crisis,
the Qin family's standing
in his eyes
will rise even higher.
And Wan's future may not be
any less promising than Yu's.
Father, are you thinking of
making Wan
the Crown Prince's concubine?
But Yu truly loves the Crown Prince.
Will true love secure the marquisate?
In our dynasty, noble titles
cannot be inherited
without great achievements.
It took
all I had to become
the Minister of Personnel.
If we don't prove our worth
by supporting the future emperor,
how will you
hold on to the family legacy?
I'll keep that in mind, Father.
My Lady,
are you thinking about your parents?
My home was just over there.
I wonder
where my parents' remains are now.
Now that we've returned,
we can start
searching for them bit by bit.
My Lady, do you know why Lady Yu
went to the palace today?
I heard from a maid that
the Crown Princess will be selected
after the New Year.
It's very likely
to be Lady Yu.
If Yu
is willing,
it would be her dream come true.
It's good news for the Qin family too.
Lady Yu is quite pretty,
but honestly,
if you dress up,
you'll be even prettier than her.
Words like that can stir up trouble.
Don't say that again.
Got it.
I was just trying to make you smile.
It's getting late and chilly.
Why aren't you resting in your room, Wan?
You may catch a cold.
The courtyard looked so lovely.
I just wanted to take a walk.
Cousin Yan, what brings you here?
I came to invite you to the outer study.
Father has important matters
to discuss with you.
Moyi.
Madam.
Yu, take a break.
Just a moment, Mother.
I'll join you after I finish this page.
Even His Majesty
has praised your calligraphy.
You don't have to practice every day.
Every day's practice
matters.
Yu,
did the Empress
say anything definite today?
Miss Feng was there too.
The Empress is dignified.
She didn't say much.
You mean Feng Chenbi, the legitimate
daughter of the Duke of Zhong?
She's clearly coveting
the Crown Princess's title.
Don't worry, Mother.
Father is the Minister of Personnel
and also the Crown Prince's mentor.
In terms of influence at court
and loyalty to the Crown Prince,
the Empress knows whose daughter
is the best choice.
But right now,
you're no longer
the only girl in this family.
Even your father
praised Wan's looks and bearing
after meeting her.
He called her to the outer study just now.
If the Crown Prince sees her…
Do you think I can't compare to Wan?
Silly girl,
how would I think that?
It's just that the selection
keeps getting delayed,
and it makes me uneasy.
Wan is certainly outstanding,
but my reputation
as the capital's most talented lady
is well-deserved.
The Crown Prince and I were
childhood friends.
Mother, there's no need to fear
she'll take what's mine.
She's the foster daughter
of the Marquis of Anyang now
and backed by the Grand Princess.
Mother,
the capital is full of noble families.
If we start doubting ourselves over this,
we've already lost the upper hand.
I understand Father's intentions.
Just take good care of Wan and the others.
It'll be good for my brother's future too.
I'm worried that
she'll try to reach higher
after meeting someone more powerful.
Don't worry, Mother.
If that day ever comes,
I won't let her have her way.
These are
all kinds of ledgers and deeds,
reviewed by the elders of the family.
The second branch's properties
are listed on them too.
Check if anything is missing.
Uncle, it was thanks to your help
that I could return to the capital.
These properties
should rightfully be managed by you.
Nonsense.
They were left to you by your parents.
Naturally, you should be the one
to keep them.
It's just that
your father was never one
for worldly affairs,
so he didn't leave much behind.
When you get married,
your aunt and I will add to your dowry.
Father,
Wan just got back.
Why are you talking about her dowry?
It sounds like
you can't wait to marry her off.
Don't get the wrong idea.
That's not what I meant at all.
Then I'll gratefully accept them, Uncle.
That's more like it.
Sit, sit.
What a shame.
Your father was so devoted to medicine.
He passed away before he could see
what you've achieved.
It's such a pity.
Father's heard that
you're not only skilled in medicine
but also helped solve several major cases.
He's truly glad your father has someone
to carry on his legacy.
Regarding the cases,
I haven't yet apologized to you
for what happened with Uncle An.
Qin An got what he deserved.
It has nothing to do with you.
If anything, I should thank you.
Before it was too late,
you stepped in
and rid the Qin family
of that disgraceful, immoral scumbag.
What surprised me most
was how you, a delicate girl,
faced all those corpses and remains
without flinching.
I was scared at first, of course.
But the more I saw,
the more I realized—
death is simply a flame going out.
The fear we feel
is just an illusion.
Naturally, I'm not afraid anymore.
Your strong character
puts most men to shame.
In that case,
I want to ask you
for a favor.
Anything you say.
For the past few months,
several women
in the capital
have been raped and murdered.
The killer has yet to be caught.
This case concerns the safety
of all in the capital.
I took the liberty
of recommending you
to the capital prefect.
I wonder if you're willing
to assist the authorities in this case?
I'm willing to do whatever I can
to help bring peace back to the people.
Good, good.
Please rise.
Very well.
[Prince Cheng's Mansion]
Your Highness,
our men at the capital prefecture
[Yan Qi, Prince Cheng]
have disposed of the exhibits.
Any movement
from the Qin family?
Young Master Qin Yan returned
with his cousins today.
No other visitors other than them.
Only two days left till New Year's Eve.
I don't believe
that old fox Qin Shu would just be
a sitting duck.
The capital prefect has no leads at all.
Forget two days—
even if they had
until the Lantern Festival,
they'd still come up empty.
The Marquis of Zhongyong
has staked his entire family's future
on that worthless fool.
To protect him,
he may even stoop so low
as to frame someone.
Keep a close eye on the Qin family.
If they dare make a risky move,
I'll take advantage of it
to wipe them all out in one blow.
Yes.
[Yan Huai, the Emperor]
No need to push yourself too hard.
I
allow you to take back your piece.
No need.
You handled those cases
in Jingzhou and Yuzhou well.
I thought you'd finally
learned to think ahead.
But clearly,
you're still a lousy player.
I spend every day
thinking about how to do my job right.
How would I have time
to think about this silly game?
He calls this a silly game.
You're the only one
who dares
talk to me like that.
Have you really decided
to join the Ministry of Justice?
Yes.
That means from now on,
Shuoxi will no longer
have a young marshal.
Will you regret it?
A capable man can make his mark anywhere.
If Your Majesty truly cares for me,
could you give me a high-ranking post
with the freedom to recruit my own people?
That way, if my father scolds me,
I can defend myself.
You want to drag me into the fight
between you and your father?
Fine.
The Empress Dowager is
getting on in years.
If you're willing to stay in the capital
and spend more time with her,
I'll do you
this small favor.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
The capital prefect has been waiting.
[Morgue]
Thank you, Constable Zhan.
Wan,
this is Capital Prefect Zheng.
Greetings, my lord.
Mr. Qin Wan, I'm deeply grateful
to have your help.
Please.
Capital Prefect.
This is Mr. Fang,
the head of the coroner's guild.
He performed the initial examination.
Mr. Fang.
The postmortem report.
The first body was found
a month and a half ago.
The second was discovered two weeks later.
And the third,
just two weeks ago.
Where was the first victim found?
Beside the bridge pier at the Yushui River
in the southern part of the city.
She lived in the southern district.
When her family reported it, they said
she went out the night
before to buy vinegar
and never returned.
Are there steps
by the bridge at the Yushui River?
No.
Then that means
the riverbank
was only where her body was dumped.
She must have been killed somewhere else.
What makes you say that?
Based on the bruising on her neck
and the petechial hemorrhaging
in her eyes,
it's clear that
she was strangled
and died from asphyxiation.
But the backs of her hips,
the backs of her calves,
and her heels
all show large areas of bruising
without any signs of bleeding.
That suggests
she was dragged down
some steps after death.
There are no steps by the Yushui River,
so where did she get
these injuries?
The second victim
was found in an abandoned house
in the southwest.
Lock your doors and windows.
Watch out for fire and thieves.
After delivering dinner to her brother,
who was working
in the southern district,
she disappeared.
Her brother reported her missing
the next day,
and two days later,
her body was discovered.
Because the two victims had no connection,
we didn't see their deaths
as one case.
Two weeks later,
the third victim was found.
She lived in the Hao Village
outside the city.
That day, she went to the West Market
to buy New Year's goods.
Wake up.
But unfortunately…
Someone died!
One detail
doesn't match the postmortem report.
Based on injuries to the private parts,
it appears all three women
were sexually assaulted after death.
What?
Pardon me,
but how can you be certain
it happened after and not before death?
Just like the dragging marks
on the first two bodies,
there were tears in the genital area
but no bleeding.
The third body hasn't
decayed too much yet.
I might be able to find more clues
by examining the organs.
Capital Prefect,
I need to perform an autopsy.
An autopsy?
[Precision in Every Detail]
Greetings, Your Highness.
-Your Highness, what are you doing?
-You…
The main hall is that way.
Not here.
It's you, Young Master Qin.
I thought it was my runaway servant.
Greetings, Your Highness.
This is a restricted area for postmortems.
Why has someone unrelated been allowed in?
Capital Prefect,
if I'm not mistaken,
this man
isn't registered with your office.
You're not mistaken, Qi.
Master Wan is with me.
Chi?
This case is of great importance.
Even if he's with you,
he can't just walk into a restricted area.
Qi, you may not know—
after the New Year,
I'll officially join
the Ministry of Justice.
His Majesty personally allowed me
to help the capital prefect with the case.
He's also
allowed me to bring Master Wan in
as a forensic expert.
Joining the Ministry of Justice?
I see.
Chi, you've been known
as the invincible commander.
You'll surely be
a great help to the Crown Prince.
Looks like this case will be
cracked in no time.
His Majesty allowed me
to assist the capital prefect
with the case,
not to help the Crown Prince.
Assisting the capital prefect is
an official duty.
Helping the Crown Prince
is a family matter.
If official and private matters
get mixed up,
even I would have a hard time
explaining it to His Majesty.
Looks like that runaway servant
really got to me.
The guards mistook a young lad
with a similar build
for the runaway
and ran after him.
It was all a misunderstanding.
Master Wan,
don't take offense.
Since everything's cleared up,
I'll take my leave now.
Young Master Qin,
you're not on duty, are you?
Shall we leave together?
I...
Qi.
Young Master Qin was a great help to me
on my way back to the capital.
I've promised to buy him drinks tonight.
Young Master Qin,
why don't you
head to the restaurant first?
Alright.
I'll go now.
Come by my place another day.
It's time we had a proper chat.
Sure.
Let's go look somewhere else.
I don't believe a small-time nobody
can stir up so much trouble.
Let's go.
Thank you for your help, Your Highness.
With your support,
this case might be solved.
With Master Wan's help,
the case will be solved very soon.
Capital Prefect,
the cases in Jingzhou and Yuzhou
were all solved by Master Wan.
Heaven finally smiles upon us!
I've just made a discovery.
Please, Capital Prefect,
review it with me.
Please, please.
[Postmortem Report]
I found orange seeds and fish
in the victim's stomach.
Her last meal
must have included oranges and fish.
Typically, food takes about four hours
to digest in the stomach.
While the fish has mostly broken down,
there are still visible remnants.
So
she had her last meal
roughly three hours
before death.
Impressive. Very impressive.
But what does knowing her last meal
have to do with solving the case?
Constable Zhan said
the victim lived
in the Hao Village outside the city
and had planned to go to the West Market
for New Year's goods.
She would've likely eaten
at the West Market.
Oranges are common,
but fresh fish
is rare this far inland.
And even if available,
it's very expensive
and mostly found in wealthy households
or high-end restaurants.
But the victim wore ordinary clothes
and was of modest means.
So she likely ate at an affordable eatery.
But at the West Market,
there aren't many eateries
that serve fresh fish.
We can start there
to locate the eatery where she ate
and then use the digestion time
to estimate where she might've gone next.
Thank you for the guidance.
Bad news.
Young Master Qin,
the third victim's clothes are missing.
How's that possible?
That's not right.
During the initial examination
at the prefect's office,
I personally
placed all the belongings into the basket
and had them sent here with the bodies.
Mr. Fang, did you see their undergarments
during the initial examination?
Now that you mention it,
no.
All three victims
had their outer and inner garments,
but their undergarments were missing.
The killer
likely has a fetish
for women's clothing.
What do you mean by that?
Capital Prefect,
are you familiar
with your wife's dressing habits?
How would I know something like that?
I meant no offense.
Please take a look.
These clothes
are made of ordinary fabric,
but the stitching is exquisite.
The fastenings and ties are
completely intact.
This suggests the killer
was so familiar with women's clothing
that he could redress the victims fully
without damaging
a single thread or fastening.
That's not something
just any man could manage.
Capital Prefect, you don't know
your wife's dressing habits
after spending so many years with her.
Yet this killer
managed to put on every piece of clothing
for the three victims,
except for their undergarments.
Zhan Yang, Mr. Fang,
go find out
who transported the bodies.
Yes.
This involves the killer's private fetish,
which he certainly
wouldn't display publicly.
It'll be difficult to find clues.
One more thing.
This is the black frostbite ointment
I found on the third victim.
Her nails were neatly trimmed,
so she cared about cleanliness.
And she had no signs
of frostbite herself.
If she had
gotten this ointment on her
before being attacked,
she would've cleaned it off right away.
It could only have ended up
under her nails
if she scratched the killer
when fighting back.
Only people
who work with their hands in the winter
suffer from frostbite.
The killer could afford it
and was willing to spend money on it,
which means he not only
has a decent income
but also takes very good care
of his hands.
That rules out ordinary farmers
or blacksmiths.
He likely makes a living
with fine craftsmanship.
Someone who can afford this ointment
and possesses fine skills
must also have his own shop.
Based on the same drag marks
on the first and third victims,
I suspect the murders
all took place
in a building with stairs.
The killer likely dragged the bodies
up and down the stairs to hide them
before dumping them at night.
A craftsman who knows women's clothing,
earns a decent living,
has both a home and a shop
where he could commit three murders…
The killer
killed the three victims
in the same building,
so he's likely living alone.
Though a jeweler
would also know women's clothing,
no jewelry shop or gold store
could possibly be run by one person.
It'd be too hard to avoid being seen.
So he's very likely…
-a tailor.
-A tailor.
Thank you for pointing me
in the right direction.
I'll look into it immediately.
Wait.
There are many tailor shops
at the West Market.
And the three dumping sites are different.
There's only one day left
before the deadline.
Capital Prefect,
where do you even begin?
Young Master Qin, do you have any ideas?
All I can do is find clues
from the autopsy.
Tracking the killer isn't
my area of expertise.
Now that we finally have a lead,
we don't have the time to run it down.
Do you have a map of the capital?
The map is stored at the prefect's office.
If you need it,
feel free to get it.
Don't lose hope, Capital Prefect.
Give me the capital map
and four hours.
I'll find the crime scene.
You mean that?
Catching killers
is my specialty.
I'll have a carriage prepared
and return
to the prefect's office at once.
[Jinyi Clothing Store]
Sir.
Are you here for a wedding dress?
Is this enough money for a wedding dress?
This isn't nearly enough.
But I'm my mother's only daughter.
She wants me
to have a proper, beautiful wedding.
Please,
do me a favor.
Sir?
Come and get measured.