[Coroner's Diary]
[Episode 9]
The coroner has confirmed that Ms. Yang
had given birth before,
but Madam Qin has never mentioned this.
Do you know anything about this,
Third Madam?
Your Highness,
I know nothing of this.
When Concubine Yang entered the household,
she was already over twenty years old.
But my husband favored her greatly
and gave her separate quarters to live in.
Although I am the principal wife,
I never even received her tea offering.
I only heard that...
she was exceedingly beautiful.
As for anything else,
I know nothing.
In that case,
we'll have to ask Master Qin An
to come in person.
Your Highness, please allow me to report.
My father
is gravely ill
and has been unconscious for two days.
Since Master Qin An is so seriously ill,
I should pay him a visit in person.
Prefect Huo.
Do you still need to investigate the well
in the Purple Bamboo Grove?
If you've finished investigating
that well,
my grandma wishes to seal it
as soon as possible
to ease people's minds.
The search concluded last night.
Madam Qin may handle it as she sees fit.
Thank you, Prefect Huo.
Leave us.
Your Highness.
Has Master Qin An awakened?
Not yet.
What did the doctor say?
My father hasn't eaten or drunk anything
for the past two days
and hasn't even taken any medicine.
No doctor can do anything about it.
If that's the case,
why not try my method?
I think my treatment would be just right
for Master Qin An's condition.
This should work.
Will this work?
This is a secret method
from the Beiyi Tribe in Shuoxi,
used specifically
for sudden unconsciousness.
You just need to drive this iron nail
through the brow into the brain
for seven days,
and it must not be moved during that time.
After seven days,
once the blood clot in the skull
has been drained,
the patient will
naturally regain consciousness.
Can...
can he survive that?
Whether he survives,
we'll know in seven days
after the nail is inserted.
He's awake, he's awake!
See?
I told you this treatment was just right
for him.
Master Qin An, now that you're awake,
you can answer our questions properly,
right?
Be careful.
Officer,
may I ask where His Highness is now?
His Highness and the Prefect have returned
to the office.
This is bad.
Wanxing,
go to the prefect's office
and tell His Highness
to come to
the Purple Bamboo Grove immediately.
Yes, My Lady.
My Lady,
I was just coming to escort you home.
It's about to rain.
Where's Wanxing?
I'll explain later.
First, come with me
to the Purple Bamboo Grove.
If Qin An hadn't confessed it himself,
who could have imagined this?
Constable Qi, could you
have ever imagined this?
Or you, General Bai?
Concubine Yang was, in fact,
trafficked here!
The Marquis of Zhongyong's own brother
actually engaged in human trafficking!
It's simply beyond belief.
Prefect Huo.
Over the past decade or more
in the surrounding counties,
a lot of people have been abducted
and sold!
And how many
were taken during your term of office?
There are so many case files here.
How long will it take us
to go through them all?
Let's start with the nearest counties.
Ms. Yang was already an adult
when she was taken—
not someone easily hidden.
The location of her abduction
must've been near Jingzhou.
[Missing Person File]
[Moxibustion Manual
for the Eleven Meridians of the Limbs]
[Missing Person File]
[Twenty individuals went missing
in October]
Where are the guards?
Where are the officers?
Who removed them all?
My Lady, let's find shelter
from the rain first.
Or you might become ill.
Lady Wan!
In such heavy rain,
what brings you here?
Caihe,
why are you here?
You may all return now.
Thank you for your hard work.
Okay.
Madam Qin
has been fretting over that ominous well
for two days.
As soon as Prefect Huo said
the investigation was complete,
she had me find men
to seal it up immediately.
The well's been sealed?
Yes, just finished.
And while we were at it, I also
had the men repair the well
by the flower shed,
so Madam Qin wouldn't have to worry about
anyone else falling in again.
Madam Qin can now rest easy.
Such a beautiful umbrella.
It's such a shame it's broken.
I remember that in our storeroom,
there's one with the same base color
as yours
but with different patterns.
I'll have it sent to you later, Lady Wan.
Thank you, Caihe.
No need to be so polite with me.
Please hurry back now.
What's wrong?
Madam Qin had someone seal the well again.
So quickly?
Qin An has just confessed
that Ms. Yang was abducted
and sold to him.
She had indeed been married
and had children before.
Qin An coveted her beauty
and, after buying her, kept her confined
in the back quarters.
Until the day she threw herself into
the well,
she had never once left the mansion.
But Madam Qin,
knowing full well
that I'd questioned Qin An,
still rushed to seal the well.
Clearly,
what she's trying to cover up
is not Ms. Yang's death,
but this well itself.
This is a piece of palm bone discovered
during the examination.
Judging by the skeletal features,
this should be from a girl
who hadn't yet reached maturity.
You mean
there are more remains in this well?
But that day,
Bai Feng went down the well himself.
If there had been more remains,
he couldn't possibly have missed them.
Qin Li told me then
that the well in the Purple Bamboo Grove
was originally a water well,
but later somehow it dried up.
Could it be
that someone, before Ms. Yang's suicide,
filled in the well
to cover up their evil deeds—
so no one would uncover the truth?
Outrageous.
I'll have the well reopened immediately
to re-examine its bottom.
Mother!
Something terrible has happened!
Yan Chi
has had that well dug open again.
And he's also ordered
our entire mansion surrounded—
people can enter, but no one
is allowed to leave.
Didn't Prefect Huo say
the investigation
had already been completed?
Why...
Prefect Huo said
the coroner discovered a young girl's bone
during the examination.
Grandma!
This is
the old residence
of the Marquis of Zhongyong.
That Yan Chi, how dare he?
How dare he?
-Grandma.
-Mother,
please think of something quickly.
Caihe,
hurry and fetch my large cloak.
Chen,
tell them
that I've suddenly fallen seriously ill
and need to leave for treatment.
Hurry and send your father
out of the mansion.
Hurry!
Yes.
Go quickly!
Mother,
didn't you say
that the Crown Prince
and the Marquis of Zhongyong
would protect us?
It's too late.
Too late!
My child,
if we had known this day would come,
we wouldn't have done it
in the first place.
Your Highness,
should we send a batch of the remains
to the morgue first?
Wherever the Qin family
hosts their guests,
that's where we'll send them.
Yes, Your Highness.
Follow me.
Yes, my lord.
-Yes.
Go rest for a while.
No,
I need to clean
all of them thoroughly.
[Government Office]
Go take a break.
I'm not tired.
Leave the rest to me.
They've suffered too much already.
I can't let anyone hurt them again—
no one.
But you can't keep torturing yourself
like this.
If you collapse,
who will help rebuild their bodies?
♪ If I fall like dust into the gloom ♪
Who will help them find justice?
They need you.
They shouldn't have needed me.
They should have been alive.
♪ The snow will cloak me
in the purest white ♪
They could have been living
the lives they dreamed of!
But why?
♪ If I engrave my love upon my heart ♪
Why were they
buried at the bottom of this dark well,
reduced to nothing but bones?
How can there be
♪ Even pain will feel like joy ♪
such cruel people in this world,
such vile deeds?
Why?
♪ I lay my heart bare ♪
♪ Love is laced with pain ♪
♪ Please give me strength again ♪
♪ Let my fate surge like a wave,
unchained ♪
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♪ When starlight fades ♪
I assure you,
♪ The stars will still be shining bright ♪
no matter who the culprit is
or where he is,
♪ Beyond the reach of darkest night ♪
I, Yan Chi,
will never let him get away
in this lifetime.
♪ I'm but a speck the stars may hide ♪
♪ Yet in their glow, I still reside ♪
Alright, alright.
Let's go, hurry.
Don't let them see my face.
Put it on me, put it on me.
Cover me properly.
Let's go quickly.
Lift the sedan.
You don't need to follow us.
Go attend to Grandma.
[Frontal Bone; Zygomatic Bone]
The sludge at the bottom of the well
has been cleaned out.
Only some bone fragments remain.
Is there anything unusual
about the remains?
Girls.
All of them...
were girls.
Once I catch that monster,
I'll make him suffer a fate
worse than death.
That would only bring
momentary satisfaction.
What we want
is to seek justice for these girls
through the law.
Justice?
What is justice?
Even if you bring the criminal to justice,
they cannot come back to life.
What good is this so-called justice
to them now?
Clearing injustice and restoring names
serves the same noble purpose
as bringing them back to life.
Has Your Highness forgotten this already?
Prefect Huo!
Let Madam Qin through.
Prefect Huo.
Our Qin family
has always treated youwell.
Why do you bring unidentified remains
and display them in our main hall?
This is deliberately
ruining our family's fortune.
How can we face others after this?
Prefect Huo, if you can't stand up
for our family,
I...
I'll go to the capital
and petition the Emperor directly!
Madam Qin,
this was ordered directly by His Highness.
I am in no position to object.
Besides, even if you want to petition,
you'll need to wait until the case
is closed to have grounds.
The innocent need not fear scrutiny.
Why make things difficult for me?
Who's really making things difficult
for whom?
You ignore the real murderer
of Concubine Liu and Steward Liu
and instead throw mud on our family name!
What are your true intentions?
Prefect Huo,
if you won't give our family a way out...
what's the point
of me living anymore?
I might as well die and be done with it!
Madam Qin!
Mother!
Your Highness,
Madam Qin and Prefect Huo
are arguing at the courtyard entrance.
Saved me the trouble.
Attempting to assault a court official
in full view of the public—
arrest her now!
-Yes, sir!
D-Don't...
Your Highness, please calm down.
My mother was only overcome with despair.
She never meant to harm anyone.
The case remains unsolved,
yet Madam Qin rushes to take her own life.
I wonder if she's committing suicide
out of guilt
or just making a scene to interfere
with our investigation?
No, no, no.
Your Highness,
my mother was just momentarily distraught,
which is why she acted inappropriately.
I beg Your Highness's forgiveness.
Four murders have occurred in succession
within your family,
and the case of the girls in the well
is even more appalling.
Prefect Huo!
From now on,
without my token,
no one from the Qin family,
regardless of their status,
may leave the premises
before being questioned.
Violators
will receive 100 strokes of the cane.
If anyone
dares to obstruct official business,
they will be charged as an accomplice.
Understood, Your Highness.
F-follow me.
Mother.
Madam Qin, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Mother.
If Yan Chi
truly uncovers something,
what are we to do?
As long as An remains safe,
your third branch will be safe.
For Chen's sake,
we must protect him at all costs.
Officer,
there will be a generous reward
in the future.
Open the door.
-Constable Qi.
Constable Qi.
Wasn't it Madam Qin who was supposed to
be seeking medical treatment outside?
How did it turn out to be Master Qin An
instead?
Put me down!
Chen!
Chen...
Save me, Chen...
Unfilial son!
You...
Prefect Huo.
According to the preliminary examination,
these girls...
these victims were likely
between the ages of 12 and 16.
Considering that the mud
at the bottom of the well
slowed down the decomposition process,
the time of death
was at least seven years ago.
The bone surfaces show
no fatal external injuries,
and the bone quality is healthy,
but the limbs, ribs, and finger bones
all show old fractures that have healed.
Were these girls
forced laborers when they were alive?
Why would they have so many old injuries?
Judging from the bone quality,
they were well-fed during their lifetime.
The injuries healed properly,
so definitely not from hard labor.
During warfare,
to extract intelligence from the enemy,
interrogators would
inevitably use certain methods
on prisoners.
But some interrogators
enjoy the torture itself.
They would,
after torturing, use the best medicine
to heal the prisoners' wounds,
just so the torture could begin anew.
Are you saying
they were subjected to long-term abuse
and, after recovering,
were beaten again until disabled?
I...
I've only seen similar cases before,
but their circumstances
might have been different.
You don't need to comfort me.
I thought
that, having handled countless cases,
I had already seen the full extent of
human wickedness.
But little did I know,
I was still so naive.
The evil in human hearts
has no limits.
But the human heart
holds more than evil...
there's also loyalty, goodness,
and righteousness.
Don't doubt yourself.
Didn't you abandon medicine
to become a coroner
precisely to use the law
as your instrument
to punish evil and promote good?
I promise you,
I will bring that criminal
to justice.
I will make it so
that these monsters
won't dare harm others so easily.
Your Highness, Miss Qin,
shall we continue?
Yes.
With such a heinous case
in the Qin family,
the Marquis of Zhongyong
will surely inquire into this.
Now that the case remains unclear,
M-Madam Qin is already being so difficult.
If we don't resolve this soon,
and Madam Qin...
falls ill from anger,
I fear...
Judging by how hard
she threw herself at you today,
Madam Qin
is probably sturdier than you.
Relax.
Her causing a scene today
was just a diversion
to help Qin An leave the mansion.
Could it be
that the person who committed
such beastly crimes
is Master Qin An?
We're only speculating.
We have no direct evidence.
But the concubines' quarters
are the furthest
from the Purple Bamboo Grove.
Eight years ago,
Concubine Yang chose to end her life
in the well at the Purple Bamboo Grove.
There must be a reason.
Bai Feng has gone to investigate
Concubine Yang's trafficking.
Let's talk about it when we have updates.
For now, you
need to rest.
I'll take care of everything here.
Miss Qin.
Please take a look at this small bone.
It doesn't match any
of the small bones
in the skeletal diagrams you've drawn.
It appears to be a phalanx.
Yes.
However,
I've compared it with
the hand and foot bones
of every skeleton,
but it doesn't match any of them.
Let's wait until we've excavated
all the bone fragments
before drawing further comparisons.
Okay.
Tomorrow, we still need to
analyze the bone coloration
to ascertain the cause of death.
Everyone, get some rest early tonight.
Thank you for your hard work, Miss Qin.
And you as well, Your Highness.
Let's go.
Go guard the entrance.
-Yes.
My Lady,
you must be freezing.
If you hadn't come out,
I would've rushed in to get you myself.
Don't just stand there.
Go make some ginger soup now.
Yes.
The autumn rain is chilly and damp.
Take this to stay warm.
I never use such things.
Just take it.
If you fall ill,
no one can
take your place.
Let's go, Fuling.
Had you not acted
with the reckless bravery of a fool,
dozens of valiant soldiers
from our Shuoxi Army
wouldn't have died in vain!
You're not worthy to lead
my Shuoxi soldiers.
[Yan Lin, Prince Rui]
You're not worthy to be my son!
Beat him!
Father...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
[Grace and Purity]
My Lady.
The Second Young Master is here.
Please invite him in.
Second Young Master, please come in.
Wan.
Li,
this is your first time coming through
my front door by day.
Li, you're feeling much better now?
Wan, thanks to
your miraculous treatment...
I...
Fuling, you may leave us now.
Li, did you come to see me specifically
because you heard about the bodies
in the well?
Wan,
you're the most capable person
I've ever known.
I'll tell you everything I know.
I only ask that when His Highness
handles this case,
he might consider my contribution
in reporting it first
and show some leniency,
giving the third branch a way out.
But they've never treated you kindly.
Although Madam Qin and Third Madam
don't care about me,
the fact that I could grow up
without worries
already puts me ahead of
many other concubines' sons.
Besides,
Chen has always been good
to me, his disappointing younger brother.
Isn't Master Qin An close
to the Marquis of Zhongyong?
Why hasn't he stepped in to help?
It's all for show.
If they were truly close,
why would he send gifts every year
but never visit in person?
If the third branch truly falls,
the Marquis of Zhongyong won't help them.
Aren't you afraid they'll hold a grudge
against you?
They've never liked me anyway.
Li, you are kind at heart.
I'll persuade His Highness to punish
only the true culprit
and not implicate others.
Thank you, Wan.
No need to thank me, Li.
Just tell me everything you know.
Please have a seat.
Here.
Father...
no,
Master Qin An once had quarters
specifically for keeping girls
he'd purchased,
teaching them various talents and skills.
Then one day, Madam Qin suddenly
sealed off the quarters,
and those girls disappeared
without a trace.
You mean
those female corpses
at the bottom of the well
were...
I didn't know before either.
But one night,
I sneaked out to steal food.
When I passed through
the Purple Bamboo Grove...
I saw...
Liu Chun carrying a rolled-up straw mat.
The following day,
Madam Qin ordered
the quarters where the young girls
were kept to be sealed.
The well in the Purple Bamboo Grove
subsequently became dry.
When these things happened,
had Concubine Yang
already entered the household?
No.
After the quarters were sealed,
Master Qin An rarely came home.
Madam Qin had no choice
but to allow Concubine Yang
to enter the household.
Do you know why Concubine Yang
took her own life?
I suppose...
it had something to do with Concubine Liu.
Concubine Yang was exceedingly beautiful
and was once greatly favored
by Master Qin An.
He often painted portraits of her.
But she was always melancholy
and never tried to please him.
Master Qin An forbade her to leave
her quarters in a fit of anger.
Honey.
[Sunrise Grove]
After Concubine Liu came,
Concubine Yang fell further out of favor
but gained a certain degree of freedom.
After the quarters for the girls
were sealed,
only Liu Chun,
Master Qin An's trusted servant,
was allowed to enter.
Concubine Yang often stood outside
the quarters,
sometimes for half a day.
I used to sneak over to watch her
from afar.
[Sunrise Grove]
Did she know someone in the quarters?
I don't know.
I once secretly investigated the quarters
but found nothing unusual.
However, Concubine Yang
would go there every single day.
Concubine Liu was jealous of her beauty
and often made things difficult for her.
But she never fought back.
Until one day...
Please.
Please tell me.
Please tell me the truth.
I followed Concubine Yang all the way,
but I could only watch helplessly
as she walked into the Purple Bamboo Grove
and never came out again.
Her death caused a stir
throughout the entire household.
Only then did Madam Qin order
the dry well to be sealed
with a demon-suppressing stone.
Later, she even
had the quarters demolished.
Li, why didn't you stop Concubine Yang?
Because I was afraid.
Every time I thought of
that rolled-up straw mat,
my whole body would tremble.
I didn't even dare to go near
that bamboo grove.
It's not your fault, Li.
Wan.
Don't think I'm useless.
This is all I know.
Li.
Why were you
so concerned about Concubine Yang?
Because
she had a beautiful smile.
Back then, I often thought
that if my own mother were still alive,
perhaps
she would smile at me just as beautifully.
I understand.
Thank you for trusting me, Li.
Get a doctor! Get a doctor!
-Get a doctor for me!
-Master!
We can't get out!
Get a doctor!
Get me a doctor!
Chen!
Help Father get an imperial physician.
Master Qin An.
Get an imperial physician for me!
Father, you're delirious from illness.
Where would there be an imperial physician
in Jingzhou Prefecture?
Besides, our mansion's gates are sealed,
and no one gets in or out.
You'll just have to endure it, Father.
Get back here!
You ungrateful child!
You...
Master Qin An!
Master Qin An. Master Qin An.
Master Qin An, wake up!
I know you love your son,
but I love mine too.
An is already in this state.
If he's also found guilty,
then our Xiang and Chen
will be completely ruined.
Things have already come to this point.
I am the true sinner of the Qin family!
Qin An's death is no great loss.
He's already so ill.
He may not have many days left.
For the sins my son has committed,
I, as his mother,
will bear the consequences.
Chen, remember this:
don't follow your father's  example.
I understand, Grandma.
[Grace and Purity]
Master, a message from the Eagle Squad:
on the night Shen Yi
and his wife were killed,
there was a shipwreck
downstream on the canal.
The following day, two young women
claimed their father had drowned
and asked nearby households
to help with funeral arrangements.
Afterward, they claimed
to be escorting the coffin home
and disappeared without a trace.
Just as I suspected.
If Medicine King Valley
had river transport,
I would suspect that those two young women
were Miss Qin and Fuling.
Master,
shall we continue our search
for Miss Shen's whereabouts?
No need.
Pull all the men off
the Shen family leads.
Keep a close watch on the Ministry of War
and catch the traitor who leaked Father's
border patrol route.
Everything else can wait
until I return to the capital.
Yes, Master.
Your Highness, why are you here?
We've discovered Ms. Yang's background.
According to records from Yang County
and testimonies
from the Yang family's neighbors,
the Yang family matriarch who went missing
10 years ago
matches Concubine Yang in every aspect.
The Yang family matriarch
was born beautiful
and disappeared with her daughter.
There were rumors at the time
that she had eloped with someone,
taking her daughter along.
If Concubine Yang was indeed
the missing Yang family matriarch,
then the mysterious quarters
my second brother mentioned
might be where her daughter
was being held captive.
The mysterious quarters?
The quarters were already torn down.
Also,
the neighbors said
Ms. Yang deeply loved her daughter.
If Qin An had used her daughter
to coerce her into becoming his concubine,
she would have had no choice
but to comply.
But Concubine Yang was already
in her twenties when she went out,
and she had her daughter with her.
How could she suddenly disappear
and then end up in Qin An's hands?
I'll know the answers to these questions
once I interrogate Qin An.
According to the records from Yang County,
the missing Yang daughter
was about 11 or 12
and was born with six fingers.
Folk legend holds
that people born with six fingers
are blessed by heaven,
so many people in Yang County knew
about the Yang daughter's six fingers.
Six fingers...
I know.
That's a supernumerary digit
formed during pregnancy,
extremely rare,
less than one in a thousand.
Then this confirms
that the missing Yang family matriarch
is indeed Concubine Yang.
But among the hand bones we've found,
none shows any trace of
a supernumerary finger.
I personally supervised
the final verification of all bones,
so I can guarantee
that nothing was overlooked.
Unless
there's another place
where bones are hidden.
A dead body!
A dead body grabbed me!
-Quickly pull me up!
-A dead body?
There's no dead body!
How could there be a corpse in the well?
Pull her up now!
Hurry up.
Shuang wasn't mistaken.
The well by the flower shed is closest to
the Purple Bamboo Grove,
and the two wells might be connected
by an underground waterway.
The Purple Bamboo Grove
is on higher ground,
so the buried remains could very likely
flow through the underground waterway
to the well by the flower shed.
Quickly order someone to dig up the well
by the flower shed.
Give it to me.
Pull harder.
Guys,
put your backs into it!
Get this job done properly,
and you'll each get one extra tael
this month!
No,
two extra taels!
-Yes, my lord!
Calling them "guys"
and even using personal funds.
Prefect Huo really
has staked everything on it.
With back-to-back heinous crimes
in his jurisdiction,
even if only to keep his position,
he has to stake everything on it.
Put your backs into it!
Come on!
It's a... a skull.
Bai Feng.
Yes, sir.
Arrest Qin An immediately,
without fail.
Yes, sir.