Why was Chairman Ji's list removed?
I don't know what you are talking about.
I will say it again, so you understand what I am saying.
Why was the lobbying record found in the church's safe removed from the list of evidence?
Why are you bringing that up with me?
You said you were going to review it and took it, Deputy Chief.
What are you trying to do?
Aren't you embarrassed, Deputy Chief?
How dare you raise your voice when you've done no good, you bastard?
I didn't reprimand you for your unauthorized target investigation, and now you have no respect for your higher-ups?
- You gave the order, right?
- What?
Ji Seong Goo and Chairman Ji were arrested with crucial proof, so nothing could be done about them.
So we should at least take good care of the politicians they have been supporting,
so that you can become Prosecutor General without concern, right?
You people are really something! Why don't you go amend the Constitution?
All sovereignty of Korea belongs to those in power, and all power comes from the chaebols.
You must be crazy. Do you want to be fired?
Yes!
I don't have any regrets as a prosecutor.
But I can't leave like this.
If I go, when I go, I'll reveal and clean those dirty connections before I leave.
Just watch.
You! You bastard!
He didn't have to go to this extent.
He sometimes goes too overboard.
Is this Al Queda?
Where is it?
Since you also illegally locked someone up,
let's just call it even.
Don't get too upset... ^^
Where is the key? What?
The key!
I'm sorry.
I really have nothing to say.
We tied them up for sure
and I double-checked.
I'm sorry.
You should just erase that.
What?
Oh.
What happened?
Let me go.
- Go in.
- This is clearly an illegal arrest.
An illegal arrest.
It is up to ten years in jail, don't you know that?
I don't know. I don't. Sit down.
Tie them up. Tie them.
- I warned you.
- Be quiet. Be quiet.
What are you doing?
Why are you touching my younger sister?
Is this sexual assault?
If you continue to not cooperate with us, we will send you to jail.
Jail? What did we do wrong?
Identity theft, fraud, robbery, document theft.
Use of physical violence, and illegal computer use! Need me to say more?
I did not use violence.
If you don't want to go to jail, sit down quietly.
I have not assaulted anyone!
All I said was I didn't do any violence. You did, you pig.
Stop wiggling!
What is this bastard?
Yes, Prosecutor, everything ended well.
Problems? No way, sir.
I am Section Chief Maeng, Prosecutor.
You know how well I do my job.
Yes, I'll keep an eye on them, so take your time.
Sure, I will see you soon.
It just
all happened within a blink of eye.
There was no way we could prevail against them.
I understand what you mean, so first find out what they're up to.
Yes.
I will wash this and return it to you.
Move now.
Things are not easy.
Little sister.
Oh, Uncle!
Don't wake Uncle up.
That guy. He looks more relaxed than before.
So, have you found them?
I found one of them. What should I do?
Should I arrest him right away?
Yes, yes, yes.
No, just tail them for now.
Your delivery is here.
The door is open, so please come in.
That bastards will be in touch sooner or later.
You should catch them all at once then.
Especially the scammer who looks like a slacker.
Yeah. We really can't let him go.
Why can't we just get along?
You should have formally invited me then.
Isn't that polite for both of us?
- You bastard.
- Hey.
Will it be faster for you to catch me or for my people to come up upstairs?
Let's not make a ruckus for the neighborhood in the morning.
Is there nothing to drink?
You should take a sip too.
You're tidier than you look.
You really did the work that all the prosecutors in Korea are supposed to do, huh?
You're the one who sees me like that.
By kidnapping us, threatening to arrest us,
and even offering reduced sentences if we did your work for you.
Your way of negotiation is just way too old-fashioned.
You all are smart people. Why do you have such poor imagination?
Who said so?
Your subordinate.
Maeng... What was it again? Maeng...
That damn Section Chief Maeng.
Yes, yes, it was Section Chief Maeng.
Anyway, you guys seem pretty cornered.
So let's stop wasting time and cut to the chase. What do you want?
Do you want us to bring you evidence to convict bastards like Chairman Ji and Ji Seong Goo?
So the USB was you?
Was it useful?
Why did you send it to me?
We needed someone to do the dirty work, and you just happened to be the assigned prosecutor.
Chairman Cheon's case too?
Oh, you're pretty quick on stuff like this.
You guys are really fearless.
Well, what more is there to life. We're just doing what we please.
Anyway, if that's what it is, then I can consider your offer.
All these secret and foreign bank accounts are useless to us, you know that. But in exchange,
all the cash we find while exposing their dirty secrets is ours to keep, okay?
What did you say?
We can't work without cash. We're not amateurs. Did you think we were volunteers?
There's no meaning in airing their dirty laundry if there's no cash involved. We want to empty their pockets.
In the end, they'll just get arrested and stay in jail for a few months before getting released in a wheelchair again. Isn't that the routine?
But you think you guys taking the cash is acceptable?
But we're pure... relatively speaking.
Get out if you're going to keep talking nonsense.
I don't intend to use these kinds of methods. Here's the delivery fee.
Alright.
You play fair, as expected. Korean prosecutors are great.
If you don't want to then there's nothing I can do about it. Have a nice day.
Hey, take your boxes with you.
They're empty.
Want me to tell you one thing? Why you guys can't do it.
It's because you guys can't abandon your petty ethics and moral obligations.
Those guys don't bleed the weak till they're dry because they have stuff like that.
Remember that.
So...
You're telling me to be like them and disobey the law?
What? What can you do with that oh-so-great law?
Who do those laws exist for?
Aren't laws supposed to punish the guilty and protect the innocent?
Then why is it that the guilty ones escape and always walk free?
They make it so that they can use the law to their advantage and judge themselves. Why do we have to...?
Then, keep a hold on your ethics.
Contact me if you change your mind.
The former Attorney General, Kim Jin Wook, who was imprisoned on charges of bribery worth billions,
has been released on probation.
The court revealed they adjudicated on the former Attorney General Kim's charge in such a way
because he was exculpated from receiving a part of bribery.
As a result, the fines that the former Attorney General Kim received were
only 15 million won and 9,890,000 won.
Assemblyman Kwon Tae Jin was sentenced  to
3 years of imprisonment, 500 million won of fine, and 300 million won of additional penalty
on the charge of receiving stocks from CEO Jo Yeong Kwon as bribery.
He admitted his guilt for receiving some stocks,
but he was acquitted on the charge of obtaining the stocks that in a way that netted an 18-billion won financial gain.
Alright, a handful of potatoes. A handful of onions.
A handful of everything.
And as much meat as I want.
Hey, hey, hey! You're back?
Did you see the list of swindlers? How was it? Did you like it?
Good work.
What's wrong? You don't like it?
Are you making curry? It smells good.
Don't change the subject. I haven't even started it yet, so how would you know?
At this rate, we'll starve to death.
They say, "The longest way round is the shortest way home."
I'm here after turning around the longest way. Now, what should I do?
Wait and see. Something interesting will happen soon.
Hwa Yang Trade President Na Won Hwak was charged on suspicion of bribery during bidding on governmental projects
and hosting illegal gambling but it was decided not to bring charges against him.
The prosecution claims that there is not enough evidence to convict President Na
and therefore have dropped all suspicions and charges against him.
We couldn't find any evidence that he embezzled slush funds
or used funds as bribes for lobbying.
The prosecution will not bring charges against him.
We're closing this case. This is all.
Are you just wrapping up this case like this?
How do you say there isn't enough evidence?
President Na, give us just a word!
President Na!  President Na!
Please look to this side!
- You've had a hard time, President.
- How about Father-in-law?
He's on a business trip in LA and will be returning tomorrow.
Is my wife at home?
She's in Sapporo.
What a great father and daughter!
Hey, stop the car for a bit.
Yes, sir.
Are you uncomfortable by any chance?
Why is this here?
I thought it smelled nice, so I prepared it specially—
- Haven't you read the performance manual?
- I'm sorry.
- Did you read it or not?
- I read it.
- And?
- I'll get rid of it immediately.
- No, no.
There's no need for that.
- You drink it.  I said drink it. You said it smells nice.
- What?
- You don't want to?
- No, sir.
Stop dawdling and drink it already.
Drink all of it, you bastard.
Barbarous bastard.
You bastard! Bastard! I should kill you.
Drive the damn car!
Yes, sir!
Are you really going to be like this?
Go on ahead.
Why are you ending an investigation that has clear grounds to investigate?
You know very well what that scumbag will do when he's free.
I know, right? You should have prosecuted with proper evidence.
Why are you so bothered by not being able to catch an innocent person?
Innocent? Do you know how much that scumbag has embezzled so far?
There's no evidence. Evidence. Did you forget, "innocent until proven guilty"?
- You said all the evidence I brought to you was inadmissible!
- Proper evidence.
Besides, you never reported this case to me in the first place.
This isn't the time for you to nitpick, when you deserve to be punished.
This is my last warning to you.
Try to see reason, unless you want to be demoted.
Anyhow, who wouldn't know that you're a part of Choi Hyeon Gi's line? Just look at the way you work.
What did you just say?
What?
I'm asking what you just said.
Don't mention Director Choi's name with that filthy mouth.
You bastard!
Why? Did I say something wrong?
It was your superior who made our prosecutors embarrassed by hiding money abroad after taking it from Choo Won Gi.
Ah, he was not taking money only from Choo Won Gi, was he?
Deputy Chief!
You punk, how dare you!
Jang In Gyu!
That's enough, I'll be sure to teach him a lesson.
Follow me.
So you moved without reporting to me?
I thought that if I reported it, they wouldn't have permitted me to do it.
I thought that if I pushed the investigation to a certain point,
it would reveal that Deputy Chief Prosecutor Kang or the Attorney General might be related to  President Na.
How about your personal feelings?
Pardon?
You didn't have any personal motives in doing that?
Are you still suspicious of Choi Yeong Gi's case?
You think they framed him?
I don't know who was the mastermind behind it all, but I'm sure there was someone helping the prosecution.
After that incident, they were the ones that benefited.
You also know that he's not that kind of person.
So if you would give me another chance—
In Gyu.
Prosecutors look for evidence.
Suspicion, doubt, or circumstantial evidence is all meaningless.
If you can't be specific about it, don't even try to start.
You don't deserve to be a prosecutor.
Then do I just need evidence?
Then I'll bring it to you.
No matter what.
Hurry up so we can play one round.
I don't want to play.
Come here, let's play just once.
I told you that I don't want to.
I told you I don't want to.  Why do you keep asking and making me annoyed?
What. Are you upset?
Fine then. Let's do it.
Let's see it. Give it to me.
- Are you actually going to do it?
- I really am.
Pick one, pick one!
Swindlers List
They present themselves falsely to be a team who launders the Blue House slush fund.
They're saying they will give 10% of the former presidents' slush fund to someone who would give them operating funds.
You don't like it?  How about this person?
You like women. A swindler!
You bring out your fake government ID.
You use your way with words and get the swindler and score on her!
- How's she look?
- Well, she looks like this.
It's just eh.
Yes. Hello?
Okay,  you can swindle and rob them as much as you want.
I'll let it slide even if you empty out them completely,
but make sure you sweep them completely!
So they can't deny it at all.
Who is that?
What?
You could call it something like a broker.
What are you going to do?
We have to start our job.
Then to whom? The female swindler team?
Withdraw the embellishing words!
Withdraw!  Withdraw!  Withdraw!
Stop your tricks!  Reflect our opinions!
Reflect!  Reflect! Reflect!
Stop immediately the unsafe measures on the site!
Stop immediately!  Stop immediately!  Stop immediately!
Withdraw the haphazard development!
Withdraw!  Withdraw!  Withdraw!
Mom, why are those men doing that?
That's because they're poor.
If you don't study hard, then you're going to be like them.
Withdraw!  Withdraw!  Withdraw!
Ma'am,  what did you just say?
Hey! Do Jin Woong!
Stop!  Stop!  Stop!
Haphazard Development with no safety measures endangers the lives of citizens.
What do you mean I would fight?  I just tried to talk.
I saw you raise your eyebrows like you do when you're angry.
Please don't guess.
Here. I ordered two fried eggs just for you.
I really just wanted to talk. Do I look like a thug?
Hyung, don't worry about me but you stop doing this.
Your late wife would roll over in her grave.
I need to protect the gym first so I can manage the  athletes.
You could just move to another place.
That's why you're not fit for this.
If I sign the contract just to save myself,
what are these people going to do?
The world changes a little bit for the better from your actions.
People do everything their own way.
Okay. I get it. Eat your food. It's going to get cold.
Stop doing this and start exercising again.
Too much time has passed. The incident before—
Forget it. Don't bring it up.
Why are you getting mad all of a sudden.
Don't enter.
"Let's start our next round."
Ugh, I have to get going.
Next time we'll get a drink.
Ji Woong
What.
Nothing. We'll talk next time.
So bland. I'll call you.
Don't waste food. Eat mine too.
- Don't get into trouble.
- Worry about yourself.
Hey!  Long time, no see, Cha Ah Ryeong!
You see, I have a new project.
Join us again.
It's a great opportunity.
I washed my hands already.
If it's about that other time then—
That's okay. There are so many drivers in this world, why would you come to me?  You look pathetic.
Don't disrespect your elders.
Crazy bastard.
Hey, you wanna die?
You're still the lowest of the low.
What?
You bit—
I knew you'd be like this.
Why are you getting into trouble when you just got out of jail?
Follow me.
What the hell are you?
Me?
Why? Are you thugs?
Who are they?
Wait.
Wow, they were like photocopies.
I can't remember the wanted posters well because I'm outside and don't have them on me.
Let's go together and check on you?
Follow me.
Let's go.  I'll show you what police station looks like.
Let's go.
Why?
You don't want to go? You don't like the police station?
Then you should leave now.
Okay, okay.  See you next time.
What do you mean "next time"? Bastard.
Look away.
Leave.
Yo!
Are you kidding me?
Ah, they looked terrible.
Ah we almost got into trouble this morning.
Where did you find that?
What brings you here?
I came to pick up my best accomplice,
so you can't be taken by anyone else.
C'mon. We have work to do.
Ugh, why can't I reject him.
Hurry up.
Been playing games all day?
What do you mean games? You guys came early.
Ah, we just happened to meet each other on our way.
What happened to Jin Woong?
Jin Woong?
He probably got on the wrong bus again.
Usually, people who use their bodies aren't so smart.
His brain may be as small as a black bean.
Black bean?
- I'm saying it's good for your health.
- Right!
You're all still the same.
Ah Ryeong, have you been good?
I've been a bit bored but how about you?
I've been good. Bored.
Now, since it looks like we're all here, let's start.
Come here. There's going to be a person to brief us.
Another person is coming?
What?
Who's going to come, idiot?
What if the police come in? And a prosecutor comes to investigate?
Are you going to take responsibility?
Huh, are you?
Did you do research on this?
How can you—
He did come! A prosecutor!
You crazy bastard!
- Why do you turn on a green light—
- That's what I'm saying, the green light—
Go, go, go.
Kill them.
What's with all the noise?
Didn't you tell them?
Work is dramatic isn't it?
Dramatic? Ugh.
Everyone sit. We're not here to arrest you.
What?
Now, we will formally introduce ourselves.
I'm Prosecutor Jang In Gyu from Seo Won District Prosecution.
You guys met him before once.
He is Section Chief Maeng who works with me.
Nice to meet you everyone.
Very nice.
Now let's...
Let's start by discussing work.
Wait, what? What is he talking about?
Wait just a sec.
Come here. Let's talk.
What are you doing?
What do you want us to do with a prosecutor?
He kept sticking to us. And he already knew where you all were.
Then you should've told us to run away!
Do you think just running away will resolve this problem?
But how can we work with a prosecutor?
It's alright.
Everything in this country is about connections, don't you think?
It's alright. It's alright.
What is this?
The people you have to capture.
Corrupt chaebols, politicians, judges, prosecutors, lawyers, ministers, vice-ministers, organization bosses.
Despite their crimes, they got all kinds of special treatment in prison.
No matter how heavy their crimes were, they were sentenced to imprisonment for 3 years and probation for 5 years.
Amidst all that, they used all kinds of tricks like reprieves or special audiences with lawyers.
Even though they took tens or hundreds of billions illegally,
they still got freed with special pardons or bailed out and have lived happily afterward.
Catching those heinous criminals and putting them into jail.
It's your job.
It's not bad.
Why are we supposed to capture these scary guys?
So, who's the first target?
Na Won Hak.
Na Won Hak? The Hwa Yang Trade President?
What did he do?
The rest of the information will be given by Section Chief Maeng. All I need from you is definitive evidence.
Concrete evidence they can't worm their way out of.
Well, the money that you guys collect from the case will be...
split?
What?
I was kidding. Keep all yourselves.
I'll promise this.
So it's like this? So I thought it was like community service or something.
Okay, stop the lecture right there. If we listen to more, we'll get bored and not want to do it.
They're not such easy targets.
We're not that easy either.
You have confidence.
But how can we trust you?
Everything that we discussed until now,
is recorded on this phone.
From now on, the only point of contact is that phone.
Any questions?
Let's go.
- Goodbye.
- You should drink this.
It was not because I was scared.
No, no. Still, we're not doing this with a prosecutor.
What do you mean, not with a prosecutor? We're focusing only on business. The prosecutor is in the same boat with us.
Is this really okay?
If we want to drag guys like them in, I need to at least give them my arms.
Should we investigate them separately?
No.
We'll take this opportunity to see their abilities.
Will he go back on his word later?
Right? Somehow, it's hard to trust someone who is employed by the government.
Don't worry.
He's not lying.
How would you know?
Lying is my specialty.
You are persuasive.
Who wants to do it? I won't force you.
We should do it. We were going to do it anyway.
It's not bad for me either.
Then, is it just me to decide now?
Let's start this in a few.
Hey hey. I still haven't decided yet.
Don't you know 'majority rules'?
'Majority rules'? We're not voting for our class council in elementary school.
Why do you play hard to get? You'd do it in the end.
Sometimes he seems like a girl.
Hold me.
Let's do it together.
I'll hold you.
Who should I blame? I should blame my innocence.
Let's get working.
Hey, you bastard!
Hit him, you punk, hit him!
Ugh, you imbecile.
Our President Na, nothing goes well for you nowadays.
You must be upset.
Bring the broker.
Yes.
You said he was a martial artist. You said he would fight well because of that, you bastard!
But he got knocked out so easily?
Do you know how much I've lost because of you, bastard?
What did you say? What did you say until the next fight—
I'll find someone again.
Bring me a better player.
I'm sorry.
You know what I'm saying?
What does President Na look like?
He entered in Hwa Yang Trade as a regular employee in 2002 and was promoted all the way to a director position in five years.
He even became a president the year before last.
He is legendary in this field.
Basically, he got promoted super fast.
He is like that on his resume but he is actually very messy.
He is very famous for beating his subordinates to achieve results and bribing here and there to win bids.
Moreover, he even changed related regulations to win bids.
He's also had experience being a player at host bars in college.
He did?
Then he must've used his talent to flirt with a chairman's daughter, so he would be set for life.
He's very ambitious.
Do you have any other information about him?
There is an illegal fighting ring that only VIP's can get into and gamble.
Its security is so heavy that I don't have much information, but I heard there is a lot of cash flow.
Sounds like there'll be a lot of money.
Do you want to work on this place first?
There is no reason that we shouldn't since they're doing half the work themselves.
How are we going to handle this?
We're going to have to hire a player.
A player? Who?
Who? What player?
Who you say?
- Who?
- Look at these hard muscles.
Why are you guys like this?
I'm not doing this.
Touch him.
- I'm not doing this.
- Stone. It's solid rock.
- Don't touch me.
Honey. Please speak to Father-in-law, honey.
If a board meeting is held, I really—
I'll trust you with this. Okay?
Of course, I love you.
Okay. I'll see you later. I love you.
Why isn't there any progress on the apartment bid?
Because of protesters, it's delayed a little.
You don't have to worry. It will be handled in no time.
How about bidding on the governmental project?
That is... the requirements the government suggests are very stringent.
We received "not qualified."
Not qualified?
The administrative scope of construction sites is problematic,
but our company received the rating of "not qualified" last time because of the arrogant and bossy attitude of the large company.
I think it's a little hard this time.
Ah seriously. You can bribe the government officials a bit.
We've always done this. It's nothing new to say that.
We don't receive any support from the upper ranks so we need to do it on our own.
President, the lobbying problem as well...
Prosecutor Jang is fishing around, so we should restrain ourselves for a while.
I'll be over if I don't get any profit results this time.
My father-in-law is trying to drag me down by holding a board meeting.
In this situation, I should be bothered by that bastard Prosecutor Jang?
Look at those pathetic people.
They don't have much money but to celebrate some kind of anniversary, they have to be at an expensive place like this.
They always search the internet to find coupons, wondering when deals will come out and take pictures after being here happily.
They put those pictures on social media, being proud of being here.
Then people click "like." Those people are all morons!
What are you looking at?
Hey,  I...
Na Won Hak, should live like that again, like a barbarian, huh?!
Figure out the apartment issue today.
Yes, sir.
Meet the people who are related to bidding as well.
Yes.
Of course. I'm always ready.
I'll send the player's profile first, so let's have a meeting next week.
Goodbye.
Please give me a double espresso.
No, please give her a single espresso.
Coffee just looks black but actually, it has multiple layers.
The top layer consists of oil and the bottom layer consists of micro-fine soluble substances.
For me, Mandheling Ice Tea, please.
What is funny is that each layer has its own different flavor.
If you order a double espresso, each layer gets thick, so you can't taste both flavors at once.
If you need caffeine, and that's why you're ordering a double, better order a single twice.
That will be better.
You must work in this field.
No, I just like it because I have a lot of time.
Do you like "Na Hong"?
Yes, well... sometimes I'm attracted to luxury things. If it's sexy, it's even better.
Excuse me, but what is it that you do?
I am an agent. I manage mostly martial artists.
Why? Do I not look the type?
No, but, really?
We must be meant to be.
I think so.
Yes.
You look prettier every time I see you.
It must be because you're about to get married.
Is this your soon-to-be husband?
No. What are you talking about? You're so playful.
Byeong Joon, say hello. This is—
Long time, no see.
President Na.
Who is this? First time seeing him.
Hello, I am Oh Byeong Joon. I run a small business in Japan.
You look good.
You guys are from the same university. Korea University.
Really? What major?
I majored in law. You're my senior.
Law?
So you're from law?
Yeo Hoon, come here for a bit.
You came, Seonbaenim?
You must know each other, you both graduated from the law school there.
Oh. How? Wow, long time no see!
What happened to you? You haven't been to any reunions.
I know it's been a while. I'll show my face now and then.
You really know each other?
Of course. If anyone doesn't know him in our department, they must be an alien because he passed the bar exam in his freshman year.
How have you been? I heard that you didn't go to the Judicial Research and Training Institute.
I left it because it didn't fit my aptitude.
Yeo Hoon, Vice-Minister Kim is here!
I have to go.
Contact me.
Yes, see you another time.
I will meet you later, sir.
I understand you. I don't like judges and prosecutors at all.
If they accepted any kind of rabble, this kind of position wouldn't exist.
You are correct.
Next time, I will bring my student ID card.
You're funny.
Yoo Ri, let's talk.
Rude ass bastard.
You know I just met Soo Hyeok?
Who?
You know, the guy who passed the bar in his freshman year and quit.
Ah, Choi Soo Hyeok!  I know him.
Don't you have a person that I could use?
Why?
Oh nothing. I just wanted to get them a part-time job.
That gambling place again?
You know I don't like stuff like that at all.
Kids who can't compete because they're caught doing drugs. It's good for them to make some money while they're resting.
We don't have any.
Why don't you ask Byeong Joon?
He said that he manages players too.
Really?
You came?
It's them?
I brought him here.
His frame is good.
But, aren't you a little too fat?
He's the ace in our team but is resting a while.
Why? Did you use drugs?
It's nothing like that.
He has some women problems.
Don't women look at appearances anymore?
Never mind.
But I only need one.
Put him in. You won't regret it.
Hey fun junior, how can you put him in when he is not even verified?
Here you go.
Winner gets it.
You don't need to do this here. Just trust me—
Now this is fun.
He's really something, isn't he?
You've done a big deed.
- Look.
- I'm sorry.
I told you we have to verify like this.
What if I picked this punk?
What if? I'm asking what would have happened, huh?
You damn bastard.
He's funny.
What an idiot, hm?
Let's sign a contract right now.
Okay?
We'll prepare it right away.
I'm really sorry. Use this for the hospital bill.
Let's get that bastard, no matter what.
I wonder what that bastard President Choi's face will look like already.
What happened to what I told you to do?
Oh yes. I finished talking with the people who are related to bidding.
Regarding the apartment issue, the contractors already started their move.
- So it'll be settled soon.
- All right.
Make the project go without a hitch!
President, why don't we think about setting up insurance, just in case?
Insurance?
In case, even in the slightest chance, if we lose the match, we won't have enough cash.
So, I planned something.
Excuse me.
Doesn't sound like a bad idea.
I understand.
Drive quickly!
What are you?
I'm looking forward to today.
Right?
It'll be a killer night.
Don't get too excited.
- Do it calmly.
- Yeah.
You don't trust me?
I do, bud, I do!
Are you ready?
Yeah. The setting (setup) is done.
Okay.
Let's go.
Good luck.
What do you think? Wil I do better or the other side will do better?
- Definitely you!
- Right?
Get ready today.
Cheers!
Wait a sec. What's this?
Who is that?
Oh, nothing. It's the Yang Pyeong house, the housekeeper.
Then, you must've picked them without looking at their appearance.
But she cooks very well.
Okay, for victory!
Cheers!
You brought a novice today. I'm not sure he'll be okay.
Worry about yourself.
Let's play.
Which player would you like to bet on?
You should stop, and start exercising again.
A lot of time has passed.
- That incident then—
- Stop.
Drop it.
The match is starting soon.
Okay, let's get it.
The main event will start.
Everybody, have a seat.
Okay. Yes.
Start attack!
The preparation is finished.
Let's watch the match first. We're not in a hurry.
Okay.
Go!
The main event starts now!
♫  I invite you to this ground, where your ambition will be satisfied  ♫
♫  Try controlling me however you want, there's no reality  ♫
♫  Choose something, check to make sure that's your choice  ♫
♫  I'm the one who gave you the key  ♫
♫  Turn all the tables  ♫
♫  You're getting sucked in, you keep getting tricked again and again  ♫
♫  The perfect moment when betting's over  ♫
♫  You're done for, game over  ♫
Let's do this the right way.
♫  Try finding the real reason  ♫
♫  If you lose your everything  ♫
♫  Think you can’t go back to the time  ♫
♫  Keep in mind, it’s not your fault  ♫
♫  Now I'm here 'cos I am gonna be with you  ♫
♫  Just walk without thinking, when you lose  ♫
This isn't how you get revenge.
I'll make sure you can catch him.
Wow!
What's with your expressions?
Look at the serial numbers.
Why are all the numbers the same?
It seems like we got tricked.
The important thing is who took the real cash.
Hwa Yang Trade President Na?
I think they hid the money in the warehouse.
Will he follow according to our plan?
We'll have to make him follow.
You punks, what are you doing?