Let's finish up now.
Do you have proof?
I do have it.
We secured security footage of them.
His name is Do Jin Woong. Until recently, he was a nationally-recognized fighter.
Next, Im Byeong Min. He won security system hackathons, as a high-schooler.
There's a rumor that the NIS scouted him.
He's known to have the "hands of God" in this field of work.  Lastly, this con artist is the most important.
About his personal information...I still don't know yet.
A fighter, a con artist, and a hacker in one place?
It's an interesting combination.
- How about someone like him?
-You want to mess with a chaebol?
Hey, who's driving?
There's someone I know.
- Talk about what?
- About work, business.
- Why do you do this type of work?
- I don't know.
We allow Defendant Ji Seong Goo to be released on bail!
As you said, we did things through the law.
And it feels really great.
Search up the Daechi-dong high school girl murder case.
I murdered that girl.
But look what happened. I got released.
The guy, the man...
I think we were traced.
Hurry get on!
By the way, how do you know Ha Ri?  I've never seen you before.
Ah that...
We're friends who work together.
Friends?  He has friends?
Oh, by the way, don't trust Ha Ri too much.
He's someone who can stab you in the back when it comes to money.
What do you mean?
Don't you know? Whatever he says is all lies.
I have narcolepsy.
How could I not know a person as important as you?
Seong Goo, since we took care of it according to the law, it feels great, doesn't it?
Wow.
You're the one who sees me like that.
You let your subordinates kidnap us and threaten us with violence.
Do you want us to bring you evidence to convict bastards like Chairman Ji and Ji Seong Goo?
Then I'll bring it to you. No matter what.
But in exchange, all the cash we find while exposing their dirty secrets is ours to keep, okay?
- C'mon. We have work to do.
- Ugh, why can't I reject him?
Wow, long time no see!
The guy who passed the bar in his freshman year and quit.
Ah, Choi Soo Hyeok!
Want me to tell you one thing?
Why you guys can't do it?
It's because you guys can't abandon your petty ethics and moral obligations.
Those guys don't bleed the weak till they're dry because they have stuff like that.
How would you know?
Have you ever experienced something like this? All you've ever done is scam people. When have you—
If I have?  If I have, what changes? Huh?
Do you think nothing happened to me?
I'm saying this because I've failed before!
I'm saying this because if we acted on our emotions, we might lose that bastard in front of our eyes!
Have you fallen for me?
I'm also someone who commits crimes but you're just too much.
I'm planning on creating a new task team.
I'll recommend the next project. There is a person called as Chairman Cheon...
Prosecutor Jang, you should put him in jail—
So you're Soo Hyeok.
I heard that your dream is to become a prosecutor like your dad.
Congratulations on your being really broke.
You have to work with me later on, okay?
Watch over me...  Because this is just the start.
This is interesting.
Wanted for suspicion of pocketing about 180 billion won of the national budget funds,
the former WG CEO Choo Won Gi is brought up
regarding his crimes again.
According to an informant, a part of that money
might be brought into Candidate Kim Kook Jong's presidential election camp.
The campaign director from Candidate Kim's insisted that it was just a false accusation
that was maliciously fabricated and strongly expressed that they would counteract it with law.
I just sent video clips through email so if you check it, you'll know.
Yes. What those bastards are up to now.
You don't need to worry, Candidate.
Everything will go as we planned.
I'll just trust you, Captain.
Hey, you bastard! Check the damn signal!
I found him!
- Come here!
- What is this?
But save my daughter, please.
Take him away!
Please save me! Save me, please!
Don't come near me!
If you come near me, I'll kill all of you!
There was someone behind it all.
They got someone from our side as well.
Okay. Let's talk more details later.
They might tap in to our conversation.
Keep in mind.
Don't trust anyone from now on.
Yes, Team Leader.
I heard we had a mole on our side, too.
No, Captain said he would speak to me in person.
Captain.
Captain! Captain!
Captain! Captain! Captain!
Please help!
Captain.
Someone, please help!
Help!
Prosecutor Choi Hyeon Gi who was in charge of investigating CEO Choo Won Gi
was shockingly revealed to have received bribes to help him.
Prosecutor Choi previously arrested highly-ranked government officers and received wholehearted support.
But the evidence that he continuously received bribery personally from Choo Won Gi appears one after another.
As it was revealed in the will of an officer who worked at Candidate Hong Jong Hyeon's presidential election camp,
it's assumed that they had been involved in committing the crime together for a very long time.
New suspicions have been raised over whether even other ruling party assemblymen received bribery as well.
It has become a very big issue now.
Things are becoming more favorable for us.
If Candidate Kim is selected, a lot of opportunities will open up to us.
What?  Hey, Deputy Chief Kang!
You're really going to be like this?
You said Prosecutor Jang worked under you, didn't you?
That idiotic moron, really!
Why on earth are you being like this?
We're also taking care of things internally.
Chief Prosecutor is paying special attention to this matter.
If you stay away for a short time—
What?!
F**k, really!
Let's start... the next project.
Anyhow, these government bastards only gulp our money but can't do anything.
- You have a car waiting outside, right?
- Yes.
Hey, what are you doing?
- It's under construction.
- Get out of the way!
You think I'm doing this because I want to?
Get out of the way, you bastard!
Why does this mister keep speaking to me informally when I'm all hot and bothered?
Hey, turn around the car. Turn around the car.
Mister! Do you have a trouble at home? Need to destress?
CEO Park is coming down.
You guard your tongue! You never saw me, okay?
We got it.
How can you say that now, you punk?
Haven't you seen Prosecutor Jang, that bastard arresting CEO Na?
Ah, seriously! That's why I said to exchange all that to cash before it's tied up!
Yeah! Tell Kim and Choi as well to bring it after taking care of it.
Collect cash as much as you can and give it to Baek—
Wait a minute! Who are you?
Me?
Aren't you a woman?
N-no, I'm not.
What do you mean you're not?!
Hey! You're—  No way!
Ah, seriously! I told you to be careful about eye contact!
I didn't look at him!
What do you mean you didn't look at him? I saw you glance at him through this mirror!
I looked at a car behind us.
Hey, there are side mirrors. What's the point of them if you don't look?
Geez!  Would you stop nagging me?
- I'm nagging because it's necessary!
- That's how I do things, what am I supposed to do?
Hey, then your way is to look at another man like this, huh?  Like this?
- Why would I look at a horrible one like him?
- What?
Then when you were caught, you should've acted naturally!
"N-no, I'm not."  Is this your first time acting? What sloppy acting!
That's why I told you I didn't want to! Or you should've given a script in the beginning!
Hey!  Because you don't have a script, you can't act?!
Then what am I supposed to do?  Do you think everyone is a con-artist like you?
What? Con-artist?!
- By the way, you bastards!!
- We're in the middle of talking!
Ah! Annoying!
Con-artist?! Geez!
Y-you're getting road rage right now?
Hey! Don't do that!
- He is trying to get off right now.
- You stay still, punk!
If you get off, you'll regret it so sit quietly and be still!
Stop the car! Stop the car!
Hey! Hey! Pull over there! Stop, stop the car!
Ouch! Come over here! Hey! You! You!
I saw and remember your faces perfectly! Watch and wait!
What do you mean "watch and wait"? Look behind you.
- What is this?
- Oh, CEO Park?
- How did I get here?
- We're on our way to see you.  Are you here to meet us?
See?  I told you that you would regret it if you got off the car. Please take good care of him.
- I was on the way to business.
- Thank you for coming here.
Yes. Good job.
Let's go.
Just pretend doing it! Just pretend!
All of you got bribes from CEO Park. Why are you actually trying to look for them?
Is there anyone else who is related to Eun Hyeong Construction's corruption? Do you plan on any additional summons?
It's hard to tell right now.
First, we have to investigate the seizures. Then we'll find the related personnel—
Aigoo.
What are you doing right now?!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.  Aren't you hurt? I'm sorry.
Sit up straight.
You inflated the construction rates, received rebates and embezzled.
And I see that you sent the money from the inflated rates to a paper company, and took up to 30% in toll fees.
Why is that a paper company? Who decides that?
Is there a company that has only two employees with a tiny unit as an office?
And those two employees are President and Vice-president?
And the company paid each of them a monthly salary of 30 million won.
Moreover, made-up accounting, real estate investments...
Where did such a large amount of money disappear to?
Do you think I did this to make only me rich?
Speaking bluntly,  it's not like I did it to eat only my fill, is it?
That's what I'm saying... That's what I'm curious about.
Who is it? Who did you make full?
Don't do anything that you'll regret later. Let's finish up here.
In my opinion, you can't take responsibility for this.
It's okay. I don't really have a sense of responsibility anyway.
Ah, really. You're someone who doesn't get it. Why don't you try looking for it?
Where that money went.
Let's do that.
I understand what you mean. Don't worry. We'll figure it out. Okay.
What did he say?
Just an old man's solicitude. Let's finish up summarizing the main points.
Okay. Let's look at it.
Kim and Choi that President Park mentioned are these guys.
Cho here, is the person-in-charge.
It's a very high possibility that he has the slush fund account books.
How did they launder the money?
It looks like they've made several dozens of borrowed-name bank accounts and have been transferring money among them.
They use a method where they take out and deposit checks of what seem like business transactions among them.
- They avoid lump sums of money.
- Exactly.
How much do you think it is?
About 6 billion won.
Probably more than that.
They would exchange their accounts to cash before asset forfeiture.
"Asset forfeiture"?  What is that?
If they didn't seize something at the crime scene, they could expropriate it upon conviction.
So they freeze the assets in advance so that criminals can't hide their money beforehand.
Then they must be very busy now.
How much do you think it is then?
At least, 20 billion won?
- 20 billion?
- 20 billion won?
How can you launder that much money in this situation?
You said they're experts on exchanging cash. They probably use private moneylenders.
Chairman Cheon used to do that too.
Yeah! Tell Kim and Choi as well to bring it after taking care of it.
Collect cash as much as you can and give it  to Baek Seon—
Right! On the phone earlier, he said something like "collect cash as much as you can and give it to Baek Seon."   Is he the guy?
Baek Seon? Do you know him?
No, not at all. First time hearing it.
Don't mind. We'll intercept it before it's delivered anyway.
The important thing is that the cash will be brought to one place.
Byeong Min, try to find out the real estates owned by people close to CEO Park.
Including the house maid and driver. And find out if it's moving properly.
Even driver?  How can I do it all by myself? I can't do it even if I stay up all night.
After climbing mountains, you can see the flatland.
Why do I climb mountains all by myself?
Then who would climb mountains? You're the only person on hacking here.
You're using "only one" only at times like this. If you didn't use it much, I wouldn't hear it—
Why did you let the sparks fly in my face when I'm just sitting still here? That man's just saying it.
Look, look. She is so cheeky!
You, until when are you going to call him as this man or that man, huh?
-Then what can I call him?
- Hmm.  Oppa?
Ah, what did I just hear just now?
I don't like it either.
What to call each other isn't that important. Just call each other whatever you feel comfortable with.
- Then what do you want to call him?
- I've not thought about it.
Then call him comfortably, whatever you like.
Con artist?
She is doing it again.
Ah Ryeong, what about me?
Ahjussi.
- This is what you're in the present—
- Hey, you Talkative.
You said to call you comfortably.
That's it for today. Let's end things.
Already done for today? Where are you going?
On a date.
-Then I'll leave too.
-  Do you have plans?
My brother is going to be discharged from hospital.
- Hey, hey.  I'm leaving too. Give me a ride on your way.
- What is this? You're very different from what I expected.
Only I am different? You're very narrow-minded.
Don't do that. Let's play just one game. I'm bored.
Am I kid? To play games?
- You always play games.
- I won't play games with you.  Never.
How childish!
If you're bored, call your friend and play. Or play games.
- Just wear it.
- I feel stuffy when I wear it.
Do you want to eat pork belly?
Ah, she drinks well.
Pickpocket!
Halt over there!
Come on! Come on! Stop there.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- Ma'am.
-Where is my purse?
Where is my purse?
Ah, she picked a lot.
You're the one, Unnie.
Wow, I was shocked. I didn't even notice. How did you do it all of a sudden?
What do you do? A player? When did you learn?
- Can you teach me?
- Don't follow me.
Don't act like that. I really want to be like you.
Give me a break. Look for someone else. I'm done with that kind of work.
You should carry on a tradition then.
I'm Byeon Yeong Ji. What is your name, Unnie?
Okay. I got it. But if you show it once—
That's enough, right?
Wow, Unnie, you're really—
Unnie!
How amazing! He can still eat even after he betrayed his family.
He's probably comfortable with that.
Ah, you guys are too much. We're all family in prosecution.
Ah, really.
Just eat, please. Don't mind them.
I still get indigestion.
- Prosecutor, are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
-  You're really great at times like this.
How can you not be concerned? There are so many enemies all over.
I just live the way it is.
Learned from Captain Choi Hyeon Gi?
Yes.  He said it when I was a rookie prosecutor.
"Endure not trusting people but thinking about the organization,  then good days will come someday."
Do you think good days will come?
You're here! Welcome!
You're here, Prosecutor.
Have you eaten, sir?
Yes.
Those days are on the way.
You've been working hard. Let's gather our strength and run once more!
- Good Luck!
For our Prosecutor Jang!
Yes!
How is that for me? It's for justice.
Are you able to pick up, Prosecutor?
Yes, Deputy Chief?
Right. You're doing well. Keep doing like this.
Yes. I'll do my best.
Here.
Share this with your staff in the office.
Thank you.
Our section chief likes snacks very much.
Do you have any other problems?
No, I don't yet.
Good. If you have any, tell me right away.
Yes. I understand.
I love you, Deputy Chief.
By the way, about Choi Hyeon Gi's son...
- You mean Soo Hyeok?
- Right, Soo Hyeok.
How is he doing? I heard that he went to America.
He died a long time ago.
What? What happened?
I heard he committed suicide.
After Captain died like that, even his wife passed away.  So it must've been hard for him to endure by himself.
I'm always indebted to you.
You still don't say, "thank you."
You're cool. I'm getting recharged too.
You made a team. You look like you're stuck together.
Stuck, my butt. We're not glue.
Did you start again?
I should.
Take care of yourself. Don't get hurt again.
I have you, my main doctor.
You bad punk.
You haven't been contacted?
I guess nothing happened, right?
Probably.
If you hear news, let me know.
I've not decided yet whether I'll let you know or not.
I'll wait.
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
I barely found you.
I told you not to follow me—
Hey!  Cha Ah Ryeong!
Smile a bit, don't have so much attitude.
Who are you? You're good looking.
Get inside.
Hurry!
Didn't we already finish talking?
That's what you think.
CEO Nam said to bring you, no matter how.
Is that a threat?
No, no. I'm suggesting. Suggestion!
Then I'll suggest one thing too.
Get lost. If you don't want to die.
You bitch, I took it easy on you.
If you don't take it easy, what will you do?
Ah, hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, Ah Ryeong.
Ah Ryeong.
I got it. I told you I got it.
This is the last time I'll use words.
Yes, Boss.
No. I'll make sure to bring her by tomorrow.
Yes.
If it's CEO Nam, isn't he the boss of the Jeong Soo gang?
That gang is known for making a strong punch, isn't it?
What should I do?  I really want to see them.
Get real. It's not like what you imagine.
If you become a member, it'll be nice.
It may be like a family. They have loyalty and you don't feel lonely either.
Why are you looking for family over there when you have a mom and a dad?
I don't have mom and dad.
What do you mean?
I came from an orphanage. I've never seen my parents.
Why did you run away from an orphanage?
Just... because.
Unni, should we do this? I'll clean, cook, and do laundry.  You just teach me skills.
I'm good at housekeeping.
Or I can pay you tuition. I have money.
- Whose is that now?
- This?
Kim Geun Woo's?
I usually don't give advice to anyone, but I will this once.
Go back to your orphanage.
You'll get abandoned as soon as you're not useful here.
So don't have fantasies about things and don't snoop around, okay?
Yeah. I understand.
Unnie, you seem like a good person.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have saved me.
You're doing it again!
I told you to call me first before coming here.
Ha Ri.
Kang Ha Ri!  What's wrong with you?  Kang Ha Ri!
Ha Ri?   What's wrong?
Ha Ri, are you okay?
♫  It doesn't wither away, the thorn-like memories  ♫
♫  It doesn't heal, the old wounds  ♫
Come on!  Attack me!
♫  My day hovers around the same place  ♫
♫  Even if I look forward, run backwards, I've stopped  ♫
♫  My time my life lives yesterday again  ♫
♫  I'm in the yesterday  ♫
♫  Still in my yesterday  ♫
♫  Shadow-like memories  ♫
♫  Keep following me  ♫
♫  To help me escape from here  ♫
- Choo Yeon Hee.
- Don't call my name.
♫  To help me from falling further  ♫
I'm scared of you.
I don't know who you are.
Are you here to use me too?
To find my father?
Right?
If you didn't use me, then tell me you didn't!
♫  Still in my yesterday  ♫
♫  Shadow-like memories  ♫
♫  Keep following me  ♫
♫  To help me escape from here  ♫
♫  To help me open my eyes  ♫
♫  To help me from falling further  ♫
♫  Someone get me out of here  ♫
What do you think? Am I useful?
I got it. I'll go.
Keep your promise that you'll go back.
I got it.
By the way, can I call you?
Don't call. I won't answer.
Mom.
How annoying.
What?
I've stayed up all night because of whom?
Did my voice just crack? The office is very dry.
So?  Who?  Byeon Yeong Ji?
If I find out about her and send the information to you, what will you do for me—
Such a rude punk. She's getting ruder.
Ai-Ai-Aigoo.
Well... I've not seen her in about 2 years.
She told you that she would come back here, didn't she?
Yes.
By the way, what relation do you have with Yeong Ji?
Just an acquaintance.
Anyhow, I looked for her here and there after she disappeared. I also filed a missing person report with the police.
She didn't make trouble when she was a kid, and she always followed me around, calling me dad.
Other kids also call you dad, Director.
Most of them do that. It's the same at any other orphanage.
We didn't do that.
We?
Never mind.
By any chance, were you raised in an orphanage?
That's why you paid more attention to Yeong Ji.
I also ran away from there at the age of 9, without knowing anything. I thought the outside world might be different.
Don't worry.
I believe Yeong Ji will come back.
Ha Ri, look at me. Ha Ri.
Ha Ri. Please look at me.
- Is it unbelievably amazing?
- Yes. it's unbelievable.  Are you going to a cabaret to dance?
What do you know?
Speaking of, are you a dove or what?
You always wear white.
What do you know about fashion? It's all your negligence.
- Wow, it's ready.  Let's eat. Clean up.
- Hey!
What is this? Chicken again? I've eaten so much chicken because of you, I think I'm going to lay eggs.
I specially put some oil on it today.
- Excuse me, I'll send a text to Ah Ryeong.
- Go ahead.
- Ah Ryeong, buy a dish of pork cutlet on your way here—
- Hey!
When a person cooks with sincerity, you should at least have a bite out of courtesy. Eat some.
How can you tell a human to eat that?
Ah Ryeong, you're here?
- Ah Ryeong, what do you think about me?
- What about?
- I look different somehow, don't I?
- Maybe.
Look at me from top to bottom and specifically.
You got uglier.
How is she getting cheekier every day?
Why do you look like that? Did something happen to you?
No.
- Is that something to throw away?
- What do you mean "throwing away"?!
I've been cooking this since this morning. Try this, Ah Ryeong.
Here. I tried to dig out information of people nearby CEO Park.
The real estate is divided up into three big lots.
The first one in Nojin in his nephew's name.
Second one in Inkyung in his sister-in-law's name.
And the third one is in Namanju under his housemaid's name.
Who's this. You're good looking.
- The distance between them is pretty ambiguous.
- Right.
It'll be hard to target one particular place.
Then the only way is to catch them and get the info out of them. Where are their whereabouts?
I don't know Managing Director Cho and Kim Ji Hoon's whereabouts right now.
I know only  Choi Yong Gyu's whereabouts.
While digging up their past, I found out that their organization has an autonomous and complex structure.
They work only when an order is given. They've never even met each other.
- They've never seen their faces?
- You mean they don't know each other?
That's right.
Even if we disguise ourselves, Choi Yong Gyu won't recogniz—
Cha Ah Ryeong.
Are you listening?
Yes.
- You're acting strange today.
-What do you mean?
Look, look, look at her attitude of talking!
We have a huge cash project in front of us, what are you doing?
Ah, he's whining about money again, seriously.
Then I'm whining on money because I'm here to make money. Do you know how hard I've worked on this briefing?
Hey, hey. Let's take a break.
You, seriously!
Hey! Let go of me!
Hey you pig, enough let go of me! Ah—
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Don't want to tell me?
If I do what will change?
Oh yeah?
Forget it. Let's just work.
Cha Ah Ryeong.
- I don't know why you're being like this—
- Is money that important?
What do you mean?
I'll go get some fresh air.
Hey, take it!
Hey, get going. Go!
Cha Ah Ryeong! Cha Ah Reyong, hurry! Hurry!
Go quickly!
- Yes—
- Unnie!
Save me! Please save me!
Hello?
Yeong Ji, is this Yeong Ji?
I'm so scared, Unnie. Please help me!
Y-Yeong Ji, what's wrong? What happened, what's going on?
The person from yesterday chased me...
Yesterday?
- Yeong Ji, tell me properly, okay?
- Ah! Aah...
Yeong Ji! Yeong Ji, what's wrong?
Between you and me we don't need to talk much.
You decide if your'e going to save this b**** or not.
You, don't you touch her!
That girl has nothing to do with me—
Hey. Hey!
Yo! You came. How is it? It's been a while since you came home.
Where's Yeong Ji?
Ah why are you in such a hurry?  What a hot temper.
Where is she?
Don't worry. I sent her to a good place.
What do you want?
Oh.... I have a job for you.
President Nam has such an important job, that he wants you to be the one to do it.
There are already so many people who want you.
He'll do odd jobs.
Bring a few more guys and come back.
Don't even think about doing useless things.
Cha Ah Ryeong.
You should leave your cell phone.
- Not answering?
- Yeah.
Ah, forget it, don't! Tell her not to come.
Why are you acting like that? She's just a kid.
What do you mean "kid"? She's already all grown up.
Are you mad?
I-I mean, why would I be mad?
Just... So just what?
Ah, things are just like that.
Hey, there's no time, let's start without her first.
- How about driving?
- I'll do it.
Let's go.
Yes.  I'm done taking out the money.
Yeah.
Have you been well?
You look good.
Who are you?
What do you mean who am I?  I'm here to claim my money.
Ah, jeez.
Get in!
Yes boss... I prepared everything like you said.
Take care of it with no mistakes. This is important.
Proceed, please.
Are you sure?
She's the best driver I know.
Is anything showing up?
No, it's so clean.
Ah really. That punk doesn't open his mouth no matter what I do.
I guess he really doesn't know.
It seems so.
Did we approach it the wrong way?
Huh? Hey, this is odd. This is from unknown caller ID.
Look at this.
What is this?
These must be famous restaurants.
Do I look pathetic to you?
Spicy Beef Soup in Inkyeon is famously delicious. Don't you know?
Hey, hold on. Search the news.
Hurry, hurry! Get it, hurry!
Which one?
Hurry up.
Oh, hold on.
President Park Hyeon Jong... Beef bone soup.
Beef bone soup... Hey where was that beef bone soup place earlier?
Everybody says that Nojin's is delicous...
Nojin?
Hey, it's Nojin!  Let's go!  Hurry, hurry!
Hey, follow me!
Hey, hey, close the door!
Hey,  what, what? Are we going to eat Beef bone soup?
Ah, really. Look at how they use their brains...
Beef bone soup?
You said they were famous restaurants locations.
When did I?
Earlier.
When did I say that? You're saying nonsense.
Hey, that's the place! It's the same.
Jin Woong,  you can see the hanging road sign straight? Turn right there—
Wait. Hey.
Isn't that Managing Director Cho?
I can't really see him clearly, but I think it's him.
Ha Ri, should I catch him?
No, let's follow him first.
Ah, why are there so many?
It's 20 billion won.
- Are you scared?
- It's not scary.
- Yes. You're scared.
- I just asked why so many.
Hey, stop.
If we unnecessarily do anything now, we could ruin everything.
What should we do?
We should call the police.
Police?
When can we use our tax money if we don't use it at a time like this?
But would the police come quickly?
I think they'll run away before the police arrives.
We can make them come quickly.
Ah there're really so many.
I think we need to make it an urgent situation.
Hey, you try doing a woman's voice.
Why should I?
Should he do it?
Don't smile you pig, you do it!
Then you do it!
Aish!
Hey, hey, practice first.
- Hurry practice.
- Ah, ah.
Ah gross, hurry up.
- I should do it right.
- I got it.
- I'll do it.
- Okay, okay.
- This is the police, please go ahead and speak.
- Hello, is this the police—
Please speak slowly, what's the problem?
Yes, hello.
Gangsters are fighting, beating, hitting—
Ow!
Quietly! Shh.
Yes— Ow!
Ah! Hurry and come please!
Is it enough? You punk!
Ah those bastards, what are they holding?
That's why I said let's go ahead first.
Korean police are like this.
Police are coming fast.
They're here, they're here!
Hey, get in the car quickly! Move!
They're running away! You guys follow Cho, all right?
Which one are you following?
Of course, the money.
Sounds like Ha Ri.
Good, what are you going to do when we're following you?
What the!
♫  If you lose your everything  ♫
♫  Think you can’t go back to the time  ♫
♫  Keep in mind, it’s not your fault  ♫
♫  In the end, I am gonna be with you  ♫
♫  Just walk without thinking, when you lose  ♫
♫  Fall, fall as far as you can, when you get further from happiness  ♫
♫  Without a destination, when you hurriedly run  ♫
♫  I be here with you all time  ♫
♫  Everything's alright  ♫
♫  There's no wrong no rights  ♫
♫  The road I take and the place I want to go  ♫
♫  As I wander between, the ambiguous boundary  ♫
♫  I don't need anything else, I just wanna fly one day  ♫
What do you guys think of Ah Ryeong?
You mean there is a mastermind behind it?
It seems that he barely shows up at the front.
What's his specialty?
You can think of him as a mutt that does everything for money.
Ah Ryeong? She looks like Ah Ryeong, doesn't she?
If I interrogate Baek Seon, I might be able to track "the man".
There are guys who keep snooping around us. Get rid of them quietly.
If you even lay a finger on her, I'll—
Should I call you Baek Seon now?
Baek Seon. Let's take the easy route.
♫  Keep in mind, it’s not your fault  ♫