Dad, Dad.
Dad!
We can't give this to her, right?
No.
Dodam!
You're okay. It's okay, it's okay.
Section Chief Maeng...
Ji Hoon...
I understand how you feel.
I also know that you had no choice.
We found your wife and baby.
They're both safe so don't worry.
Thank you!
I'm sorry.
Yeon Hee.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Why aren't you having the funeral?
There's no one that would come anyway.
It'll just be filled with reporters.
He asked me whether it would be too shameless.
After paying for his crimes,
he wanted to ask if he could live with you.
He said he didn't have the right to ask you that.
What did you tell him?
I told him to ask you himself, face to face.
I see.
He was wearing this until the end.
I bought this for him.
After I got my first paycheck from working my part-time jobs,
I said I would buy a better one when I became a doctor.
I'm sorry...
that I couldn't keep my promise.
Turn off the monitor.
Who made you do it?
I don't know.
It's someone I've never seen before.
Did he have any distinguishing traits?
A tattoo.
He had a tattoo on the back of his neck.
Besides that, I have no idea.
A tattoo?
Okay, I got it.
Prosecutor! I'm sorry.
And thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm sorry, In Gyu.
I should've blocked the search order any way I could.
No, I understand that you had no choice.
I... I'm going to catch that guy no matter what.
The man who's behind all of this.
I will use whatever means necessary.
Alright. This time, you take care of things your way.
I'll support you from behind and take responsibility.
Okay, I got it.
Then, I will put my trust in you.
I wonder why Ha Ri is so obsessed with this case?
The person who smuggled him out was
the Special Corruption Investigation Team Head Prosecutor Choi Hyeon Gi.
Choi Hyeon Gi.
Choi Hyeon Gi, I've heard that name many times before.
Choi Hyeon Gi... Choi Hyeon Gi.
Cha Dong Soo...
You're looking for Dong Soo?
He passed away a long time ago.
It's been already fifteen years since that incident.
- Ah Ryeong, where are you doing?
- I'll be right back.
Hey! Wh-Where...
It can't be.
Where is everyone else?
Ah Ryeong just went out and Byeong Min is over there.
What are you doing?
Why do you look so shocked?
It's nothing.
Did you speak to Prosecutor Jang?
Yeah.
Why did Section Chief Maeng do that?
He was being threatened.
His wife and baby got kidnapped.
Ah, those crazy bastards.
Why are they dragging innocent people into this?
There must've been something that had to stay hidden.
Still, there are still things people shouldn't do.
So what's Prosecutor Jang doing now?
He is looking for the mastermind who's behind all this
by interrogating the people who he suspects.
But they still don't know for sure.
Huh?
Then who?
Don't you have anyone you're suspicious of?
I do.
Who is it?
That man.
Oh, no, it was nothing.
Well, I just did what that man asked me to do.
Because of that, I can eat with you, sirs.
Ah really.
This is the first video clip I got when we started working on Jin Yong Joon.
And this is the voice recording of when he contacted someone before Baek Seon was murdered.
Listen to this.
So you're telling me you can't do it?
Okay, bring it on.
I'll spill the beans even about what you're planning with that man.
What is that?
Does this mean that all the guys that we robbed knew each other?
That man, or whoever it is, planned all this?
This isn't everything.
From the presidential election scandal that Choo Won Gi was involved in 15 years ago to something we don't know yet.
There's a high possibility that he has schemed countless other things.
Of course, he may be preparing a big scandal even now.
Then we could find that out by pushing those rascals.
Either way, they're all in jail.
As a matter of fact, Prosecutor Jang is already asking them about it.
But it seems no one is willing to speak.
I guess they think they may be killed like Baek Seon if they speak.
Those cowards. How can they be afraid of that bastard?
Anyway, I'm going to make him the next target.
You guys can stay out of this if you don't want to do it.
This time, we won't be making much money and it's also too dangerous.
What are you saying? Of course, we have to do this one.
Look what they did to Section Chief Maeng.
Isn't that so?
Hey!
What's wrong with you? Are you sick?
Huh?
I'm not feeling well.
Are you okay? Do you need to go to the hospital?
I'm okay.
I'm going to the pharmacy. I'll be back.
But Ha Ri...
You're going to catch that man, right?
Even if I try to stop you.
Yeah.
I'll be back.
Wait a second, please.
I have a question for you.
For me?
The incident that happened 15 years ago, can you tell me about it in detail?
Lee Jong Heon is famous in this neighborhood.
He killed Dong Soo and went to prison for about ten years.
Since then, every time he gets drunk, he says it wasn't he who killed Dong Soo.
He causes a ruckus, yelling it all around town.
I really wonder why he did that to his friend of 30 years.
He wasn't that type of person.
Is anyone home?
Is Lee Jong Heon home?
Excuse me!
I'm looking for Lee Jong Heon.
The customer is not able to answer the phone at this time.
If you'd like to leave a voice message—
He's not picking up?
Nope.
Where is that punk?
I'll go out and look for him.
The customer isn't able answer the phone at this time.
What is going on?
What are you doing?
Why are you so shocked?
It's nothing.
You're going to catch that man, right? Even if I try to stop you.
Why did you apply here?
Ah, y-yes, I'm just...
My mom told me to become a civil servant...
Huh? Hey! That's...
Because it's a secure job.
It's not only that.  This job looks cool.  It's like being a secret agent.
Okay, I'm giving you ten minutes.
Take out as much of the information from this campaign site as you can.
Right now?
Start!
Okay. That's it.
Let's have a look.
You did this all just now?
Yes, well, since you told me to.
Oh, you rascal.
Here.
Start working there tomorrow.   Make sure to seal your lips.
Really?
Thank you, thank you.
- Go ahead.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you!
But, what kind of work will I be doing starting tomorrow?
Good work, for this nation.
- Something like a secret agent?
- Yes, yes.
The situation is going to be favorable for us now.
If Candidate Kim wins, we'll have a lot of opportunities.
Hey... Hey! What are you doing? Hurry up.
Prosecutor, I finished organizing the documents regarding Jin Yong Joon's case.
Yes, prepare the file and upload it.
Okay, I will do it by 3 pm today.
- Prosecutor Jang.
- Yes?
Looks like you're getting a phone call. Over there.
Thank you.
Oh, yes. What happened?
Find me Byeong Min's location as quickly as possible.
It's an emergency, that's why.
Byeong Min!
You're very good at finding out people's whereabouts.
How did you know I was here?
- You still do that work?
- Yeah.
I thought maybe I'd stop but there's really nothing as rewarding.
What are you working on now?
It's the presidential election time.
Watching the opponent candidate, spreading false information, manipulating comments.
It's similar to what you did when you were there.
We haven't done much because the campaign was just set up after the primary election.
Then, you probably don't know the people involved yet.
It would seem that way.
But what's the occasion? You said you'd never step foot here again.
There's someone that I have to find and I was hoping you'd help me.
Me? There's no one in this world better at finding people than you.
It can't be... that man?
Why?
Because of that person, I did something terrible to a friend.
Yeah, did you find him?
The last confirmed location was Su Eun Apartment in Yiryeon-dong.
He's on the move right now so I'll text you updates on his location.
Okay, please do.
But still, you're crazy to go back there.
Do you know who's in charge of his campaign?
It's Chairman Cheon! If you get caught, you could be killed.
I know, so just tell me the location.
And give me the pass. Then I'll take care of the rest.
No, I don't want to. I'm not going to get involved then.
What are you working on now?
It's the presidential election time.
Watching the opponent candidate, spreading false information, manipulating comments.
If you don't want to go to jail, give the pass to me
before I send this over to the police.
Who are you? Huh?
Lee Jong Heon?
Who are you to barge into someone's house like that—
You know Cha Dong Soo, right?
What?
I'm asking you if you know him.
You look just like your father.
Ah Ryeong.
They say that's my name.
So what?
Are you here for revenge?
No.
I just want to know what happened.
What kind of person was my father?
What happened on the day Choo Won Gi smuggled himself out?
I heard you two were close.
From the murderer who killed your father,
to hear the story of that day, you're here.
You're such a funny rascal.
Do that at least.
If you're sorry towards the person you killed,
at least tell me.
Ha Ri!  Byeong Min is not—
What is this?  I've never seen this.
Oh, shit...
What's this?
Some bastards visited here late one night
asking for a boat.
He said he had an emergency so
if we took him to the trans-boundary sea line,
he would pay ten times more than a regular fare.
Dong Soo said he didn't want to but I kept telling him we should do it
because I wanted the money.
But the person that those bastards brought along
was Choo Won Gi.
I called the police right away but the cops never showed up
because all of them were in cahoots.
Only innocent Dong Soo got killed
by the men who were with Choo Won Gi.
Then he switched to a Chinese boat and smuggled himself out.
They framed me as a murderer.
I wanted to tell the truth, too.
But my wife and kids had been kidnapped, so I had no choice.
Was prosecutor Choi Hyeon Gi behind all of this?
No.
Prosecutor Choi tried to help us.
But in the end, he ended up getting killed by them and framed.
Then what happened to Choi Hyeon Gi, that punk? Did he get arrested?
No.
He committed suicide.
Who in the hell do you think you are, saying "suicide"?!
You're saying it wasn't a suicide, but a murder?
You don't have to believe me.
Not one person in the world believes it either.
If what you're saying is true, if it really is the truth,
then who's behind it all?
The person who kidnapped your family and put all the blame on you, who is that person?
I don't know either.
He's just a normal looking man.
Everyone around him just called him "that man."
"That man."
That day, honestly, Dong Soo
was trying to go to you.
Your mother was re-marrying with another man,
only then he found out that she sent you to an orphanage.
But I'm the one who stopped him.
I asked him if he could help me once more and then go.
I was blinded by money.
I killed Dong Soo.
I'm sorry, Ah Ryeong.
Did That man send you, too?
What?
Let go of me, you bastards!
You've done a good job.
But why are you taking that person?
Why are you asking that?
Because he was asking me if "that man" sent me.
Who is that?
I thought you promised not to ask any unnecessary questions.
Alright, let's do that. I'm just here for the money.
Call me if you need me for anything.
So that's why he never came for me.
I thought he abandoned me.
What's wrong with this?
Shit.
The moment you connect it, a warning signal will be sent to that man right away.
There's no way you'll be able to run away.
Yes.
No, let him do as much as he can.
So when it gets revealed tomorrow, everyone will be more shocked.
These bastards...
I caught you, trash-like bastards.
Stop it now, you bastards!
Don't move. I'll kill you.
Find him.
Look me in the eye! Huh? I said look me in the eye!
Head up, you bastard! What are you trying to so hard?!
Look me in the eye! Find him quick, you bastards!
This bastard...
Shit!
Over there! Get that punk! Go!
Hey! Hey, hey, go out there!
Where do you think you're going, you bastard!
Get that bastard no matter what!
You guys go that way! You follow me!
He's over there!
It was you? You bastard.
Byeong Min, you know I don't like to repeat myself.
Where did you send the files to?
I don't know  (informal speech).
You don't know? Are you speaking casually to me?!
This bastard, do you have a death wish?
Should I make you think of the past again?
Kill me.
What?
If you want to kill me, go ahead.
I won't do what you ask me to do anymore.
Ah, this crazy bastard.
Okay, I'll do as you wish.
I'm sorry, Soo Hyeok.
This is your final chance. Where did you send the file?
Boss!
Boss, I think he already sent files to someone.
I'll kill you for sure today.
Hold him up.
You bastard! Just stand by for my beating.
Ha Ri.
You came here with your own two feet.
Ha Ri, don't come here.
Don't come, Ha Ri!
Stay away, Ha Ri!
Don't come here, Ha Ri!
Get him!
Ha Ri!  Don't come here!
♫  In the end, I am gonna be with you  ♫
♫  Just walk without thinking, when you lose  ♫
♫  Fall, fall as far as you can, when you get further from happiness  ♫
♫  Without a destination, when you hurriedly run  ♫
♫  I be here with you all time, everything's alright  ♫
♫  There's no wrong no right  ♫
♫  The road I take and the place I want to go, as I wander between  ♫
♫  The ambiguous boundary  ♫
♫  I don't need anything else, I just wanna fly one day, this is one way  ♫
♫  Can't ever come back  ♫
♫  can't easily look back from my decision  ♫
♫  I'll probably see it if I go a bit further  ♫
♫  If I keep going today, it'll probably be built  ♫
♫  Someday my heart someday the timing will be right, until we part  ♫
♫  I be riding with you  ♫
♫  If you lose your everything  ♫
♫  Think you can’t go back to the time  ♫
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It was you that left the help message.
Who are you?
I came here to scout a capable man.
What do you think? I'll get you out of here and you come work with me.
When I look at you, you look like a genius.
And don't be nervous.
♫  Find the you that's lost your way  ♫
I promised you that I would never let you be caught by Chairman Cheon.
♫  If you lose your everything  ♫
♫  Think you can’t go back to the time  ♫
♫  Keep in mind, it’s not your fault   ♫
Hey, Ha Ri!
You bastard!
Should I slit your throat first?
♫  Think you can’t go back to the time  ♫
Byeong Min! You bastard!
Byeong Min!
Are you okay?
Why did you come here?
Should I watch instead? While my friend gets beaten.
I'm not crying.
Who said something? Wipe your blood, you punk.
Ha Ri.
I have something I want to tell you.
Don't tell me.
What?
I said don't tell me.
It's not like you knowingly did it.
So don't tell me.
You don't do things like that between friends.
Go on with the next plan.
Yes, sir.
I usually get tired too after bathing at a sauna.
Okay, I got it.
Yes, Chief Prosecutor.
Pardon?
Yes, I understand. I'll head over there right away.
Prosecutor Jang, where are you going?
I'm going to the Mooyeong building.
I'll see Chief Prosecutor.
See you later.
I found the mastermind who pulls strings.
Let's meet in person and talk since we could be wiretapped.
What is this?
- Yes? This is prosecutor Jang's—
- Where's Prosecutor Jang?
- He left the office. What—
- I said where is he?!
What?
To Chief Prosecutor Yoo?
Where is that?
Ha Ri, why aren't you picking up—
What?
"That man" is trying to kill prosecutor Jang,
so hurry! Go to the Mooyeong building, quickly!
Yes, I understand. I'll be there right away.
No, Prosecutor Choi said he would tell it in person so—
What's up with all this...
- Yeah, what? What's the matter?
- Why don't you pick up your phone?!
What's the matter with you, all of a sudden?
Get out of there as soon as you can.
Hurry.
Hello?
I'm in the elevator so my connection is bad.
Tell me what's going on.
This time, it's you.
Like Prosecutor Choi Hyeon Gi.
This time, that man is going to use you to take the blame for everything.
So, quickly, get the hell out of there! Hurry!
Huh?
"That man"?
What does that—
Wait a minute. What's wrong?
Ahjussi, what's the matter?
Tattoo... He had a tattoo on the back of his neck.
Shit.
You bastard!
Hello?
Hello? What's going on? Hello?
Prosecutor Jang! Prosecutor Jang!
Shit...
What is it? What's going on?
Prosecutor Jang is in danger.
What?
You should've been less nosy.
Next it's those bastards' turn.
Leave this up to me and go quickly.
Quickly!
Elder!
- Ah, you've suffered a lot.
- Bastards...
How old am I to be an elder? I'm not even married yet.
Get him!
Go quickly! Go, go!
Hey! Go to that side, hurry!
Aish!
Wait here a minute.
Ah Ryeong!
No!
♫  Don't come close  ♫
♫  With translucent eyes  ♫
♫  Don't try to fool me  ♫
No!
♫  I don't believe you  ♫
♫  This game where we trick and get tricked  ♫
I think the incident from 15 years ago is repeating itself.
This shouldn't happen anymore.  I'll going to end it.
Distribute those rascals' identities to the police.
And tell everybody to carry guns.
The one who is called "that man" manipulates all these things.
Yoo Gi Hoon is just a spy who works for him.
- There's no corpse.
- Then, if there's a corpse, is it okay?
Let's use this to show him for sure, that he can't do anything without us!
Hey, Chairman Cheon!  Come on, you bastard!
Do things according to the plan.
What is this? You're on the same side?
Why did you do it?