It finally happened.
Did you apologize to her?
Yes I did,
I don’t know that she’s sick.
Why does she have to be so angry?
It’s just starting..
Hey.. Natt
Natt
What's wrong with you?
My couple is the same.
Little fights at the beginning, and then..
boom!
Don’t listen to her. She’s crazy!
Hey.. I'm serious.
If you continue to be like this, you guys will break up.
Break up?
Do you mean break up?
I don’t want to break up with her.
I don’t want to.
What are you saying?
Are you telling me...
to break up with Kris?
opportunities like this don't come often.
Especially if everyone knows you have a girlfriend,
they might reject us.
Are you okay to accept?
I’d prefer not to.
Why not?
It's not easy for a streaming platform at that level to offer us a role.
I know,
but spread the news out like that
wouldn't be too disrespectful to my girlfriend, would it?
but this is just spreading fake news. it’s not real.
If the condition is my personal matter,
I might not be a good choice for them.
But they specifically chose you,
and opportunities like this don't come around easily.
I understand,
But I also want to make my girlfriend feel comfortable.
And the opportunity to act  with a famous star like Tiwa,
will come again?
Thank you for the opportunity
but it would be better if you offered it to another.
P’toon, I have something to talk with you.
Yes, what’s up Tiwa?
Come on.
Why didn’t you pour me? you’re host.
Do it.
Hey..
why are you drinking too much,
you will be tight.
Eh, would you try my way?
What about your way?
Cause you’re planning to apologize to her,
I once read a novel where they said if you would like to apologize with a partner you have to seduce her.
Seduce!?
It's like… if you can't solve problems by peace then just get naked.
Hey.. Are you telling me to strip naked and dance seductively?
Oh... you truly are like a little buffalo.
Eh! If you're so great,
then come and apologize to me! I'm really sulky!
No.
Why not?
I think this way is well.
because some words don't work,
but I think using body is better.
Since you turn dark ,
you're so obscene.
Karn, Am I look tasty?
Stop it!!
You guys are hopeless,
It has to be like this.
Karn, Are you tired?
Let me give you a massage.
That's so creepy.
Why, I’m helping you.
Thank you, no more next time.
Hey Kris,
I have some good ways.
listen to me.
Get out!
okay, I will note.
It’s….
Hello Madam,
you’re just come back home,  would you drink wine or tea?
The wine has spilled then what can I drink?
Please have a seat, Madam.
I will be back.
Is there no service for madam anymore?
Karn, it will be dirty.
I’m not Karn,
I’m Madam.
Then Has Madam stopped being angry?
Not yet..
let me see how you treat me.
So can you kiss me again?
I just rejected some projects today.
It's a huge project.
Why did you reject it?