Hello Madam,
you’re just come back home,  would you drink wine, tea
or me..?
The wine has spilled then what can I drink?
Please have a seat, Madam.
I will follow you soon.
Is there no service for madam anymore?
Karn, it will be dirty.
I’m not Karn,
I’m Madam.
Then Has Madam stopped being angry?
Not yet..
let me see how you treat me.
Kris
Hm.
I apologize for being grumpy to you today.
I should understand.
That’s alright,
I apologize too.
So can you kiss me again?
I just rejected some projects today.
It's a huge project.
Why did you reject it?
It’s a friendship series
but they would like to pairing partners also.
So I..
Did you reject the project because of me?
No, I have decided.
It's a shame,
Don't you regret it?
Don’t worry about me.
You can decide it all,
that's your dream.
No matter what, We still love each other.
Kris.
Hm.
Nothing.
Thank you.
Hello P’toon,
I have good news.
What do you do when you make love with Karn??
Keep your voice down!