How long are you guys going to sit here like zombies? Huh?!
What should I do?
Why? What happened?
just tell us.
It's hard to explain.
I've really tried so hard lately,
I've supported Karn in everything.
I've adjusted everything for her,
but she still says that I don't understand her.
What did I do wrong?
Do you want an answer that pleases you or the real answer?
Anything, just tell me.
You’re wrong.
Why aren't you taking my side?
Well, You are the one who acted silly towards her first, aren't you?
Right?
I agree.
It's my fault.
No Natty, you're good enough.
It's not your fault.
Don't cry Natty.
How good?
If I were really good, he wouldn't have left me.
Don't cry.
My friend is the best.
If I were really good, he wouldn't have left me.
Kris, Where are you?
You are good. Oh... don't cry.
Hello Karn,
How's the script rehearsal going? Is it okay?
Hello, Tiwa.
Karn, are you alright?
Tiwa, are you free?
Can you come see me?
What about Kris?
Kris is…
Calm down, I'll go to see you.
What's wrong with you?
Isn't you that not answer to her?
I just want her to make up with me.
Hey, If you really want her to make up with you,
wouldn't it be better for her to go with someone else?
I'm your friend!
Why are you saying this?
Stop!
But I agree with her.
Will you be single with me?
No, I'd rather not.
I don't want to be single yet.
Why is that?
And if you don't tell her, how will she know what you're thinking?
You're right.
For love,
you have to give in to each other sometimes.
if two hard sticks come together,
they'll just break.
I do give in,
but the one who's always giving in is me.
Well, if you think like that,
then you have to wait and calm down first then just talk.
You guys keep being sarcastic like this, will anything get better?
When I broke up with my ex-husband, it was exactly like this.
Don't talk about it.
You left it with me when you moved in with Khun Karn.
Then I want it back.
Take it. It's yours anyway.
Kris, don't be soft.
Don't give up.
Hey, where are you going?
Are you going to apologize to her?
No
Oh
It's my fault.
Did you two argue because of me?
What about you?
Did you and Karn argue?
She never understands my work,
only asks for time and time.
I couldn't take it anymore. It feels like only me loves her.