On the 8th of last month, the prosecution
and police began the investigation.
Upon receiving a report
that three followers had been murdered,
the authorities dispatched
about 50 detectives
to the Baby Garden
to arrest the cult leader, Kim Ki-soon.
At the time, we were at a church service.
It was the place we always held services.
It was huge.
Somebody said
that there were tons of people outside.
He said we were completely surrounded.
On the weekdays,
the Baby Garden members go to work.
Then they all come back together
on Sunday evening
to listen to Kim Ki-soon's sermons.
Because there were so many people
who had beaten up the victims,
it was the best time to ensure
that we captured them all at once.
Along with dozens of investigators
and dispatched police officers,
I was also on the scene.
It was a very cold day.
The prosecutors were trying to get in
through the doors here and there,
and people were trying to stop them
from coming in.
There were people fighting
at every single door.
I mean, they were running around
like wild animals.
I remember that one of our investigators
was thrown up in the air
and out the door.
That's how strong their resistance was.
I'm the one who helped Kim Ki-soon escape.
I thought, "Huh? What's going on?"
It was pretty serious.
So I went, "What's going on?"
Then I stopped to think for a moment.
I realized
that they were probably going to take
the leader, Kim Ki-soon, away.
So I started looking to see
if I could find a door to exit.
We had this passageway
that led underground.
There was nobody there
when we went down.
So…
I got her to escape.
In the middle of all that,
Kim Ki-soon got away from us.
IN THE NAME OF GOD: A HOLY BETRAYAL
THE BABY GARDEN OF DEATH
KANG MIN-KOO
My name is Kang Min-koo. I'm a lawyer.
At the time, I was a chief prosecutor
at the Yeoju branch
of the Suwon Prosecutors' Office.
PROSECUTOR KANG MIN-KOO
This is how they tied up Choi Nak-gwi
and dragged him to the pigpen.
We're seeing
which of the victims' accounts
were actually possible in this scene
and how it could've played out.
At first, I was thinking,
"Come on, this can't be real."
That's how shocking it was.
WE WERE DRAGGED TO THE LEADER'S ROOM,
STRIPPED, BEATEN
WITH MULBERRY WOOD AND METAL PIPES
I SAW KANG MI-GYEONG
GETTING BEATEN INDISCRIMINATELY TO DEATH
IN THE STORAGE ROOM C-0
WITH WOODEN STICKS, UNDER KI-SOON'S ORDER
I THOUGHT I WOULD ALSO GET BEATEN TO DEATH
IF I STAYED THERE
After two or three murders
came into the spotlight,
previous members of the Baby Garden
were disgusted by them and decided
to report Kim Ki-soon.
So, they filed a petition against her.
I thought it was worth investigating,
so I started looking into it.
The part that stood out to me the most
was the description of the death
of a child named Choi Nak-gwi.
He was seven years old when he died.
The petition was received
about ten years after his death.
It was written by the child's father.
PETITION
THERE WAS SOMETHING WRONG WITH THIS PLACE
CHOI MYEONG-HO
My name is Choi Myeong-ho.
I'm the father of Choi Nak-gwi,
the boy who died in the Baby Garden.
I think I did that
because I was so desperate.
Because if I hadn't stepped forward,
they wouldn't have been able
to settle that case.
Was there any other way? We thought
we had to take legal action against her
to let the world know
and bring her to justice.
People who agreed on that
worked together to sue her.
DECEMBER 8, 1996
THE BABY GARDEN
COOPERATION TOWN
The investigation was swift
under the order of the chief.
The main target, Mr. Kim Dong-hui,
who was summoned by the prosecution,
was taken straight from his bed.
We were shocked when we entered that room
because there was this huge safe.
It was full of money.
It was more than 700 million won.
Back then, 50,000-won bills didn't exist.
So 700 million was a lot of cash
in 10,000-won bills.
And the cash back then would be worth
about two to three billion won now.
The place where Kim Ki-soon lived,
with a bit of exaggeration,
was like a palace.
She had her personal sauna,
and she had a bed made of clay
at the time.
It was very big.
In contrast, her followers' rooms
felt a bit like military barracks.
That's how it felt.
So there was a big contrast.
When you went into Kim Ki-soon's room,
it was very comfortable,
like it was heaven.
I think the sound system in her room
was worth at least 100 million won.
Some of her things
were extremely expensive at the time.
KIM KI-SOON WANTED FOR MURDER
HOMICIDE, CONFINEMENT, FRAUD, ETC.
Because we lost the queen bee,
I thought that the search and seizure
was a complete failure.
I felt a huge sense of shame.
Of course, we put her on the wanted list.
We also tried to track down her vehicle.
We also tried many other things.
We exposed Kim Ki-soon's face
to the media.
We also tried
to receive reports from the public.
But Kim Ki-soon was not a stupid woman.
So she stayed well hidden.
It was really frustrating.
I was like,
"You can't even catch her?"
Surely, they should've gotten her.
But the police couldn't find her,
so they seemed a bit pathetic to me.
It was obvious where she went.
Where is Ms. Kim hiding then?
At the time, the previous members
told us the truth about what happened.
But the people who were still there
did everything to protect Kim Ki-soon.
Though everyone else
might point fingers at her,
Agaya is still the God of the Baby Garden.
I don't know the specific details
at the moment.
I don't know where she is right now.
About your leader, Kim Ki-soon.
There is no leader. No leader here.
No leader. This is a cooperative farm.
You don't know what you're talking about.
She's not a leader.
She just gives us guidance.
Because she's so smart,
she simply guides us, so to speak.
So, in a way, she was like a friend
and sister, younger or older.
Where is she right now?
She went somewhere.
Of course, I'm satisfied.
I'm content and happy.
It might be a bit noisy
around here for now
as some people raided the place.
People who left call themselves victims,
but they never suffered any damage.
They got a lot of help here, actually.
It's different from the truth.
We are not swayed by something like that.
No one who lived here left the place
because they weren't swayed
by the incident.
Come on, wake up,
or you'll suffer for another 15 years.
Our hard work is worth it.
How is it worth it?
You left us, so don't bother us!
I think they were blindly loyal to her,
just like it is instinctive
for bees to protect their queen.
We'll answer to Agaya only, forever…
This case revolves around three members
who were killed and buried.
But regarding this, the prosecution
has not found any conclusive evidence.
The only answer was to secure the corpses.
But one had been cremated
and another was missing.
Trying to find the truth in a case
where there were no bodies
was a very difficult process
in my opinion.
THE RISE OF KIM KI-SOON
THE GARDEN OF DEATH
The leader, Kim Ki-soon,
established a cult religion here
and indiscriminately beat her followers
who did not obey her.
"THE UTOPIA OF DEATH" OF VANITY
STRIPPED NAKED AND BEATEN
AFTER GETTING CAUGHT TRYING TO ESCAPE
BRUISES COVERED THE ENTIRE BODY,
AND EVEN TOENAILS FELL OUT
Including the Choi Nak-gwi case,
several other people also died.
They all died.
Yoon Yong-ung, Seo Jong-won,
Nak-gwi, and Mi-gyeong.
But the causes of the deaths were unknown.
We have no idea how they died.
YOON YONG-UNG, 44 YEARS OLD
DIED ON JANUARY 2, 1988
It was January 1, 1988.
While I was getting ready for a play,
Kim Ki-soon called me,
so I went to her room.
She held my hands and said,
"You can live without your dad, right?"
She told me my father had died
after drinking pesticide
and said I should live with her forever.
I wasn't even allowed to look
at my father's corpse.
I didn't know anything else
except that my father had passed away.
KANG MI-GYEONG, 21 YEARS OLD
DIED ON NOVEMBER 20, 1988
Mi-gyeong was really pretty.
She would always smile a lot and be kind.
Everyone liked her.
She was pretty, really.
She was exceptionally pretty,
unlike the rest of us.
She was also very gentle.
Kim Ki-soon has three sons.
Because Mi-gyeong was so pretty,
one of them had a crush on Mi-gyeong.
So he had his eyes on Mi-gyeong.
Kang Mi-gyeong used to go
to Kim Ki-soon's house in Muk-dong
and cook and wash the dishes for her.
She was always in and out.
That's why he asked his mother
to keep Mi-gyeong there
as a housekeeper of sorts.
Kim Ki-soon's son.
Kim Ki-soon's son
was the one who liked her,
not the other way around.
Kim Ki-soon found out about it,
and she figured
it would be a huge controversy
if the members heard about it.
So she tried to cover for her son
by saying, "My son would never do that."
She said, "Mi-gyeong,
you seduced my son, so it's your fault."
And she said Mi-gyeong had to be punished.
I heard she made
Mi-gyeong's parents beat her first.
So Mi-gyeong's mother beat her first,
and all these other people
started hitting her with sticks.
I went there after eating dinner
and working at the chicken coop.
Everybody was talking,
standing around Agaya,
while Kang Mi-gyeong was kneeling down.
And some people
were standing there with bats.
At that moment,
one of the people with bats looked at me
and yelled at me to sit next to Mi-gyeong.
They looked at us, kneeling side by side,
and said, "You bitches are both the same."
"The two of you broke Agaya's heart,
so we can kill you both and make sure
nobody will ever find your bodies."
At that moment, after Mi-gyeong
received a few blows from her mother,
she lifted her head
and looked up at Agaya.
Kim Ki-soon called her a cheeky bitch
and ordered people to kill her.
Then people started to beat her.
It was like a scene
of chaos and clamor from hell itself.
My mind went blank
as I watched so many people taking turns
and beating such a small and weak girl
while cussing at her.
I was so terrified
and thought I might actually die there.
I'm the one
who had to clean those factories.
As I was cleaning,
I heard Mi-gyeong screaming for help.
FORMER MEMBER OF THE BABY GARDEN
WITNESS OF THE KANG MI-GYEONG INCIDENT
Later, she was so exhausted
that she couldn't even cry or scream.
Mi-gyeong ended up passing out.
Then, Kim Ki-soon left,
and the others followed her out.
The few people who stayed around
told me to clean everything up.
That night, I didn't get any sleep.
I just hid there, completely quiet,
then ran away from there in the morning.
They went quiet,
so I was wondering what happened.
Then I found all those loud
and violent women leaving one by one.
I looked and saw
that they had completely undressed her,
and they put her
in these loose work clothes instead.
She was lying on the ground,
and she had peed everywhere.
Then she looked at me,
and I saw her struggling
to tell me something.
I think she was asking for help
or asking for me to hide her somewhere.
She still hadn't died yet.
I quickly ran away and hid somewhere else.
Then this woman, Kim something,
came in holding a large broom upside down.
And she beat that dying girl to death.
CHOI NAK-GWI, FIVE YEARS OLD
DIED ON AUGUST 14, 1987
He just missed his mother,
but he wasn't allowed to see me,
and he didn't know how to express it.
So he pooped
and smeared it on the window frames.
He got frustrated and said
that he hates Kim Ki-soon.
Whenever he saw her,
he got so scared and started yelling.
She said, "A demon that defies Agaya
has possessed him."
He was possessed
by an evil spirit that would harm her,
so she insisted
that we get rid of the child.
It was a place
where if she told us to kill a person,
then we had to do it.
If she told us to go beat somebody up,
we had to all go and do it.
We have to obey
whatever she ordered us to do.
What the leader said was the truth,
and the only truth.
You know the people who died,
like Choi Nak-gwi and Kang Mi-gyeong?
When she was punishing them,
she made it so the parents didn't think,
"Why is she hitting my daughter?"
That made the punishments possible.
Mr. Kang was a pastor before he joined.
Even though his daughter had died,
he did nothing about her death
because he had been brainwashed.
He didn't do anything to resist.
You could say
she disarmed those people psychologically.
Through brainwashing.
It was something very scary.
Kim Ki-soon told me to come and see her.
AUGUST 15, 1987
She said, "Nak-gwi is gone. He's dead."
"Everything is settled already."
"You just have to do as told."
I went to the director
of a Christian clinic in Sanggye-dong.
CHOI NAK-GWI'S ACTUAL DEATH CERTIFICATE
AUGUST 14, 1987
9:30 P.M.
HAGYE-DONG, DOBONG-GU, SEOUL
They told me,
"You just need to sign here."
The doctor had the paper
filled out already and said,
"Nak-gwi died
from a myocardial infarction."
"Nak-gwi definitely died
DIRECT CAUSE OF DEATH:
CARDIOPULMONARY ARREST
And did you sign it?
I signed it.
Even though my child was beaten to death,
I signed a document
that said he died
from a myocardial infarction.
I went to the community office
to report his death afterwards.
But the worker at the office
looked a bit confused.
She asked if I was really Nak-gwi's mom,
and if he really died.
I said, "Yes, that is right."
Seeing her confused face,
I realized that a true mother
should be torn up about her child's death.
But I didn't show such emotions,
so she probably thought I was strange.
From my memory, it was a season
when it was pouring with rain.
I saw that Yoon Bang-su
tied up a wardrobe
with some strings
and loaded it in the back of his truck.
He said, "Nak-gwi's body is in there."
That's what he told me.
"You need to follow Yoon Bang-su."
"If you go with him and cremate the body,
you won't have to worry
about anything else."
That's what Kim Ki-soon said.
I waited for my turn,
and when it was my turn,
they said they put his body in there.
So I was waiting for his ashes,
but Yoon Bang-su said we had to leave
because we were told to hurry back.
So I left without even seeing his ashes.
But I couldn't even cry.
THE GARDEN OF DEATH
KIM KI-SOON'S ESCAPE
This is breaking news
about a cult called the Baby Garden.
The leader, Kim,
must be found to solve the case.
The investigation started a week ago,
but there has been no progress.
The prosecution is becoming nervous.
To unveil the truth about the Baby Garden,
the prosecutors consider the arrest
of Kim Ki-soon their top priority.
They are putting all of their resources
toward her arrest.
Though the investigation
started a week ago,
her whereabouts are still unknown.
At the time, the media
were criticizing all the prosecutors.
We had basically let her escape.
Thanks to that,
she bought herself some time.
I think we gave her enough time to come up
with an elaborate countermeasure.
I went to see a famous lawyer
who I found through my acquaintances.
At the time, Lee Soon-bok
was Kim Ki-soon's right-hand woman.
She wasn't very old,
but she was quite intelligent.
Back then, as Kim Ki-soon's advisor,
she was in charge of handling
the whole situation.
She was a woman
with high skills and abilities.
Kim Ki-soon was in a tough spot,
and so were we.
And we had really put our lives
on the line, in a way,
to achieve all of those things.
We couldn't just let that fall apart.
BURIED SECRETLY
A man named Yoon Bang-su
was the key to solving the case.
And that's because he was the one
who took care of Choi Nak-gwi
and Kang Mi-gyeong's bodies.
Eventually, he started to speak out.
Prosecutors suspect that Yoon Bang-su,
who was an excavator driver
at the Baby Garden in 1987,
was the one who disposed
of Choi Nak-gwi and others' dead bodies.
Excavators are needed to dig the ground
to bury the corpses.
So as far as we know,
he was directly involved.
Currently, we're focusing
on interrogating him.
So we summoned Yoon Bang-su.
He was a large man, quite muscular.
He looked like a simple and honest man,
and he was tall too.
But despite his looks, he was quite shy.
He was a bit introverted from my memory.
At first, he denied it.
He said he didn't bury the bodies.
But he had known Kang Mi-gyeong
since she was a child,
so I persistently used that relationship
to persuade him.
"You knew Kang Mi-gyeong
since she was a child."
"Don't you feel bad for her
who died unfairly?"
"Don't you think
you should tell the truth?"
Later, Yoon Bang-su ended up coming clean.
"I CARRIED MS. KANG'S BODY
IN MY ARMS AND BURIED HER"
"I'M THE ONE
WHO BURIED KANG MI-GYEONG'S CORPSE"
People like Yoon Bang-su were used
to move the bodies and bury them.
And after that…
-Collapse.
-Curl up on the ground.
-Stay still.
-Move your body like before…
Film him as he walks out of there.
Okay, walk out. Good.
Do it naturally, like you did before.
DECEMBER 20, 1996
THE EXCAVATION OF THE BODIES BEGINS
Yoon, the excavator driver,
came to the scene
on the third day of excavating bodies.
Yoon said he was the one
who buried Kang Mi-gyeong's body in 1988
and described the situation at the time.
Where did you get the body,
and where did you bury it?
I got the body from the company room,
brought it here, and…
YOON BANG-SU
…buried it here.
-You see that drainpipe right there?
-Yeah.
Considering the location of that pipe,
I'm pretty sure this is the right place.
Yoon Bang-su said that
Kim Ki-soon had called him over
and given him the orders directly.
"I beat her a few times, and she died.
So go bury her."
So he said he took Kang Mi-gyeong's body,
dug a hole with an excavator,
and buried it.
He said he cried a lot
before burying her body.
He even told us something
as detailed as this.
So we were certain
that we would find Kang Mi-gyeong's body.
At the time,
much of the media was competing
against each other to report on this case.
We brought an excavator to every location
that Yoon Bang-su pointed out
and dug into the ground.
Kim Ki-soon said,
"Dig all you want, then."
She knew it wasn't there.
Though we didn't know,
I think she knew where it was.
Unfortunately, the body was never found.
Today, the prosecution again
summoned the excavator driver,
who supposedly buried Kang's body,
to excavate the body,
but they were unable to find the body.
We were almost going insane.
I mean, finding the body
was the only solution.
But we failed to do that too.
It was a big disadvantage
for the prosecution.
KIM KI-SOON'S ESCAPE
DECEMBER 1996
KIM KI-SOON TURNS HERSELF IN
The prosecution revealed
that the cult leader, Kim,
had called them in the morning to say
she would turn herself in
between 5:30 and 6:00 this afternoon.
Two lawyers came
to the branch chief's office.
"Kim Ki-soon will turn herself in soon."
DECEMBER 16, 1996
SUWON DISTRICT COURT IN YEOJU
Hey!
Move!
-Out of the way, man!
-Everyone, move!
Move, you asshole!
In the front, move!
One in the front!
-You in the front, move!
-Move!
Check the audio.
You in the front! Move! In the front!
Move!
Enough! Come this way. Go!
Why are you in front of me?
Damn it. Hey, move!
Do you admit it's a religious group?
-Ms. Kim.
-Why were you summoned by the prosecution?
Are you really Kim Ki-soon?
Are you?
I thought,
"Now we're really getting started."
She was dressed
like an ordinary middle-aged woman.
She wasn't wearing any fancy clothes.
The impression I got was
that she was dressed a lot more humbly
than I thought.
When those two lawyers came to us,
they said Kim Ki-soon
would be released within three days
if she went there,
and she should go without worrying.
So Kim Ki-soon also thought,
"Oh, so I'll be free in three days."
We thought she'd be out
after the interrogation, but she wasn't.
Kim Ki-soon came at 5:45 this afternoon,
and the prosecution arrested her
on the spot for homicide
and abandonment of dead bodies.
It just kept getting bigger and bigger.
The case became huge.
All the news was covering her story,
and it was everywhere.
All the newspapers were blowing up.
So I thought, "Wow, this is no joke."
I interrogated her myself
and almost stayed up all night that day.
But she was a lot calmer than I expected.
She stayed composed
while saying what she wanted to say.
She never swayed emotionally.
Although I tried to actually provoke her
by asking some leading questions,
she didn't fall for them.
So I could tell
that she was pretty experienced.
The Baby Garden's leader, Kim,
has strongly denied all allegations
in the interrogation,
including murders of followers.
She denied them all.
She denied everything
and said she never
ordered anything like that.
She said,
"I don't know what you're talking about."
"Those violent people
were trying to punish the victims."
"But I never knew what was happening."
The first trial
of the Baby Garden's leader, Kim Ki-soon,
and 11 others took place today
at Suwon District Court in Yeoju.
During today's trial,
Leader Kim Ki-soon said
that she was never the spiritual leader
of the Baby Garden.
She also denied all allegations,
saying Choi Nak-gwi, who died in 1987,
had never even lived in the Baby Garden.
DECEMBER 1996
KIM KI-SOON TURNS HERSELF IN
JANUARY 1997
YOON BANG-SU CHANGES HIS STATEMENT
The key witness, who testified
that he buried the Baby Garden members,
told the court that all of his testimony
during the prosecution was false.
Yoon said he made a false statement
due to the prosecution's threats
and assault.
It was devastatingly sad news.
When Yoon Bang-su came to see me,
he said,
"What if the Baby Garden falls apart,
and Kim Ki-soon is never released?
What do we do then?"
"Where are we supposed to live?"
So I told him, "Just take it back,
and say you didn't bury them."
At that point,
the testimony of Yoon Bang-su
had completely lost credibility.
Yoon Bang-su gave us the most trouble
during that investigation.
THE FOLLOWING RECORDING IS A PHONE CALL
BETWEEN YOON BANG-SU
AND A CREW MEMBER ON MAY 21, 2021
THIS CONVERSATION TOOK PLACE 25 YEARS
AFTER THE BABY GARDEN INCIDENT
-Is this Mr. Yoon Bang-su?
-Yes.
Is it true that you buried
Kang Mi-gyeong's body back then?
Yes, that's right.
I said I didn't bury them
because of what Kim Ki-soon said to me.
I heard she gave you land
for you changing your statement.
Is that correct?
I guess you could say
that's one reason why I did it.
-So did you receive land from her?
-Yes.
TRANSFER ALL SHARES
OWNERSHIP TRANSFERRED
OWNER: YOON BANG-SU
After Nak-gwi died,
I drove his body over to the crematorium.
Did Kim Ki-soon also order you to do that?
Yeah, she did.
I'm making this confession after 25 years.
It was a month, no, two months
before Nak-gwi died.
Kim Ki-soon
started looking around everywhere
to see if anyone
was coming out of the factory.
After finding out there was nobody,
she told me,
"Hey, we need to get rid of Nak-gwi."
So I said, "Sorry?"
"Are you going to send him
to his grandmother's place?"
Then Yoon Bang-su showed up,
so she stopped talking and said,
"Look, Yoon Bang-su is coming."
When she said she wanted
to get rid of Nak-gwi
I had no idea what she meant by that.
I only realized it after he died.
"Oh, so when she was saying that,
she had it all planned out."
They're all the same.
They're all murderers. All of them.
JANUARY 1997
YOON BANG-SU CHANGES HIS STATEMENT
MARCH 1997
NAK-GWI'S MOTHER TESTIFIES
There was no corpse or evidence.
All that we had left was the testimony
from Nak-gwi's mother.
So, in such a desperate situation,
the last trial to prove
Kim Ki-soon's guilt was held, but…
To be frank, we weren't sure
if we would find Kang Mi-gyeong's body.
But for Choi Nak-gwi's case,
the people who actually beat him
told us everything.
So, at least, we had enough witnesses.
Because he was cremated,
we had enough evidence
to prove that he had died.
This is back
when Kim Ki-soon was hiding in a hotel.
She told her followers
to bring me to her quietly.
"You'd better cooperate.
This is God's will."
"If we can get past this…"
"If you do well,
as your role as a mother is important,
we have a chance to win this case."
Then she hugged me
and told me to do well.
Sun Yeong-re…
I can remember her.
I remember her coming to the Palace Hotel.
I think, for her testimony at the court,
they probably agreed
on the answers beforehand
to different questions.
"Nak-gwi was beaten and starved to death."
And did you say that in court?
No, I couldn't.
Because there were people
on the other side watching me so closely…
I couldn't say it back then.
MARCH 4, 1997
THE DAY OF THE TRIAL
I told the court
he didn't die from a beating
but from a heart attack
and myocardial infarction.
DEATH CERTIFICATE
CHOI NAK-GWI
CAUSE OF DEATH: CARDIOPULMONARY ARREST
The women who had hit Choi Nak-gwi
admitted that they had done it,
but the mother of the child denied it.
It was truly a sad
but also ridiculous situation.
Back then, I wanted to kill her.
I called her a crazy woman too
because she lied.
My husband said,
"Wake up, you crazy woman."
"Please, just listen to me.
Nak-gwi was beaten to death."
When he looked at me pleadingly,
people on the other side
told me not to listen to him.
What did they do to her?
What kind of wicked things
were said to her
to convince her to lie
about the death of her precious son?
Above all, it was heartbreaking
to watch even the maternal love
get completely trampled on.
MARCH 1997
NAK-GWI'S MOTHER TESTIFIES
THE SUPREME COURT'S VERDICT
THE SUPREME COURT SENTENCES KIM KI-SOON
TO FOUR YEARS IN JAIL
WITH A FINE OF 5.6 BILLION WON
Defendant Kim, whose death penalty
was sought due to the Baby Garden case,
was found not guilty
of her murder and fraud charges.
It was due to a lack of evidence.
The defendant, Kim Ki-soon,
was found not guilty of murder and fraud.
NOT GUILTY OF MURDER AND FRAUD
She was found not guilty of murder
in both cases.
But for Choi Nak-gwi's case,
the court acknowledged
that he had been beaten and killed.
But they said the murder
had not been intentional.
"She was just trying to discipline him."
"She didn't really want to kill him."
She starved a child for two days,
beating him in the sweltering August heat.
Was she really just trying
to discipline him?
Did she really not know
that he would die?
I sincerely regret taking the kid
to a place like that.
I was so foolish to do something
that would break my own heart.
I wish that somebody would just beat me.
If somebody could beat me to death,
then, of course, I…
I truly wish somebody
would just stone me to death.
I want to apologize.
I want to say that I'm sorry.
It'd be shameless to ask for it,
but I still want to beg
for his forgiveness.
I want to tell him it's all my fault,
and that I'm so sorry.
What should I do now?
Please beat me. It's all my fault.
What do I do now?
I wish I could die,
but I can't even do that.
NAK-GWI'S MOTHER STILL WISHES
FOR DEATH EVERY SINGLE DAY
AFTER PAYING HER FINE
OF 5.6 BILLION WON IN CASH
KIM KI-SOON WAS RELEASED
AND SHE RETURNED TO THE BABY GARDEN
KANG MI-GYEONG
WAS FINALLY PRONOUNCED DEAD
24 YEARS AFTER SHE WAS REPORTED
AS MISSING
THE VICTIMS OF THE BABY GARDEN
ARE STILL SUFFERING
FROM POVERTY AND VARIOUS ILLNESSES
ALL INTERVIEWS IN THIS DOCUMENTARY
USE REAL TESTIMONIES
TO PROTECT THE SUBJECT'S IDENTITY,
SOME INTERVIEWS HAVE BEEN REENACTED