THE FOLLOWING EPISODE CONTAINS
DESCRIPTIONS OF SEXUAL ABUSE
WHICH MAY BE DISTURBING FOR SOME VIEWERS
IF YOU OR SOMEONE YOU KNOW
HAS EXPERIENCED SEXUAL ABUSE
PLEASE VISIT WANNATALKABOUTIT.COM
FOR MORE INFORMATION AND CRISIS RESOURCES
You've never thought it was wrong?
No.
-So you're always completely obedient?
-Yeah.
It's not even that weird.
Why isn't it weird?
Do you have to do everything he says?
Like if he asks women
to have sex with him?
Pastor Lee is God.
That makes everything okay.
If the Father says it's not a sin,
then it's not a sin.
"Anyone in love would do this."
Because he's God.
He said, "I want to see your breasts."
Then he asked me to take my clothes off.
And he kept telling me to moan.
He examines that "part" very closely.
He just keeps staring at it.
Even if people can see my flaws,
even if I kissed someone,
and even if I laid next to them,
I believe that you will all forgive me.
But I have no shame in front of God.
I truly have no shame in front of God.
MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH
IN THE NAME OF GOD: A HOLY BETRAYAL
GOD OF MANMIN WHO WENT TO PRISON
Our beloved members of Manmin,
welcome to the castle of the pastor.
For the believers of Manmin,
our Father is preparing
a place as beautiful as this.
So there are five levels to Heaven.
So, on the first level,
you enter a place called Paradise.
The second level
is the 1st Kingdom of Heaven.
Above that is the 2nd Kingdom of Heaven.
The 3rd Kingdom of Heaven next.
At the very top is New Jerusalem.
In Paradise, you just live
in the grass fields forever.
There are apartments in the 1st Kingdom.
In the 2nd Kingdom,
you get to live in a house.
In the 3rd Kingdom,
you are given a castle.
You get an entire palace in New Jerusalem.
That's what they teach you.
Amen!
Yes, it's very big.
The main castles are as spacious
as several millions of square meters.
There's an ocean there too
and a lake that you all love.
My goal in life was to end up there.
The best place?
The place closest to the Throne of God.
They called it the Measure of Faith,
and they started to take advantage of it.
On a piece of paper,
they would put a number
to your current faith and hand that out.
"Your faith is 30% on the second level."
"Yours is 70% on the third level."
So whilst people were going crazy over it,
they were also anxious and tense.
People who get a high Measure of Faith
become celebrities
and breeze through the ranks.
But those who get a low Measure
fall behind the others.
I became so desperate
to get a higher Measure of Faith.
So I started to sow more,
give more, and invest more.
Yes!
I think I got to three percent
on the fourth level.
I was around 40% on the third level.
I was on the third level
with 60-point-something percent.
You were said to be on "the rock"
if you were over 60% on the third level.
I got there pretty early.
I got there early, so I was very happy.
I think I was around 800th place
or something,
out of 15,000 people.
It was like your rank in Heaven.
So 800th place was a very impressive rank.
MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH
If you never climbed up to "the rock,"
if you never received
a single word for years,
if you never received the Measure
for a long time,
there's a reason
why you haven't made it yet.
You need to find out the reason.
Looking back, people who paid a lot
got a good Measure of Faith,
and those who didn't pay a lot didn't.
That's the conclusion I've come to.
THOU SHALT NOT STEAL
MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH
In a way, you could say this sermon
is actually a continuation
of the sermon on Hell.
If you don't pay your tithe and offerings,
you must know
that God will place a curse upon you.
Amen.
I see it way too often.
See, if someone gets into a car crash
and breaks and shatters their bones
or suffers a brain hemorrhage,
it's always the same answer. It's obvious.
They didn't pay proper tithes, right?
An offering of thanks,
sanctuary-building offering,
charity offering, special offering,
offerings made in group services,
the Feast of Harvest offering,
Easter offering.
There was also a Christmas offering
and a tithe.
The tithe was made before the tax.
Some say that they can't pay the tithe
because they're unemployed
and don't have an income.
But every single person can pay the tithe.
Even very young children have income
from New Year's, allowances,
100-day celebrations,
first birthdays, and other birthdays.
The parents can pay the tithe
in their child's name with that income.
There are two ways to give money
in Manmin Central Church.
Offerings and gifts.
Offerings are what you call the money
you give in offering envelopes.
But gifts are money given unofficially.
So, offerings are a separate thing.
The members pay offerings
and gifts separately,
so the members of the church
really don't have any money to live.
Despite all that,
they scrape together some money,
even if they went into debt,
to sow their offerings.
He put the church members
in competition against one another
to see who pays the most.
"So-and-so gets first place."
"This elder gets second place.
That elder gets third place."
"Lee Kwang-oh is in seventh place."
I think I paid over a billion won
over the course of 24 years.
I think my entire family
paid over a billion won too.
At the very least, it's 800 million.
But I think I paid over a billion won.
There were so many people
that were taken advantage of financially.
These people dedicated their whole lives
to giving offerings to the church.
He's an atrocious man
who brainwashed them all
and then used that for his own gain.
Many members of Manmin Central Church
have a very low quality of life.
In terms of monthly earnings,
it's probably fair to say most members
are at the bottom of the ladder.
Despite that, they gave
a lot of offerings to the church.
MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH
How did that happen?
The members would work part-time.
Hey, bring this to that table.
These housewives worked so hard
to earn that money.
Five million, ten million won.
Not only did they barely have
enough to live,
but a lot of them also went into debt.
You usually leave the church
after a service, right?
But in Manmin Central Church,
the members all line up after a service.
-Pastor Lee!
Pastor Lee!
Our entire family supports you!
Sure. Thank you.
If you grabbed Lee Jae-rock's hand
and asked him to pray, his car stopped.
Then a member might get a minute
of prayer, 20 seconds, or 30 seconds.
There's someone in the car
collecting the money envelopes.
He's the director of planning.
As far as I know,
there were thousands of people
who paid millions of won in offerings
to receive his benediction.
May Jesus lay his hand upon you in prayer.
Amen.
Show us the inspiration, influence,
and greatness of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
We pray you'll surround us with light.
So, there is a missionary meeting
for businesspeople,
influential people who paid a lot.
We were invited to that meeting.
When you go, they collect around three
to five million won from each person.
The tithe from August…
There were six or seven people who said
they will pay more than ten million won,
but now, there are more than 12.
Amen.
-I'll become your joy, Father.
-Sure. All right.
Let's go to the car to receive prayers.
-Sure.
-Over here.
-Okay.
-Come on, come out.
-Yes.
-Let us have a hug.
I got a new car for you, Pastor Lee.
Where is it from?
Germany. It's a German car.
-Our Father, please bless this car.
-Amen.
-Please bless the key as well.
-Bless your light upon it.
-Amen.
I pray in the name of Jesus Christ.
You had to pay to take a picture
with Pastor Lee.
I don't remember the exact amount,
but it started
around hundreds of thousands of won.
Later, there were so many members
hoping to take a picture with Pastor Lee.
I remember the price going up
to at least a million.
I'm pretty sure I gave ten million won
in offerings to take this picture.
These are all pictures
I paid to have taken.
I had over 40 of those framed pictures.
Let's say one costs 10 million won,
that's over 200 million in total.
Manmin Central Church had a bookstore
called Manmin Bookstore.
They sold framed pictures of Lee Jae-rock
or key rings or notebooks,
merchandise like that.
So people buy these things one by one.
In a way, it's a really shrewd business.
The funniest one for me
was Muan Sweet Water.
These people put Muan Sweet Water
in these spray bottles
to make it easier to use too.
It was incredulous.
Then they would sell them.
You could spray it on
to get double eyelids.
A broken washing machine
would work again if you spray on it.
Muan Sweet Water worked its miracle
on a broken washing machine as well.
After I sprayed the Sweet Water,
tightened it, and turned it back on,
the water didn't leak at all.
So when I turn it on now,
it's working fine,
so everything turned out well like this.
I think it's because it's so cold.
Oh, no. It's not opening.
The door remained locked
for over 50 minutes,
but it opened with a "click"
after it was sprayed
with Muan Sweet Water.
To Manmin Central Church,
Muan Sweet Water is like a cure-all
for the members of the church.
They say there's this light, this power
in this Muan Sweet Water
because Lee Jae-rock prayed over it.
So, they claim
that you can experience a miracle
if you drink the water
or put it on yourself.
There was a thing called the mailbox
that was like ARS that you could call.
And you could listen
to pre-recorded messages from Pastor Lee.
This is Manmin Central Church.
Press ten to start your day
with Pastor Lee's prayers.
Press 20 to hear a prayer for safety.
Press 30 for a three-minute sermon.
Press 40 for a prayer for the ill.
Before my grandfather passed away,
he was in the hospital.
I really wanted him to get better.
So, I remember playing Lee Jae-rock's
prayers for the ill for him.
Let me begin the prayer for the ill.
Place your hand on the place
where it hurts or feels weak.
If you're not ill,
place your hand over your heart…
He listened to it for a while,
then he looked at me like he wanted me
to take the earphones out.
But I remember I made him listen
to the whole thing as I wanted him to.
I should have just spoken to him more
or gone on a trip with him.
In actuality, it's all about money
in the end.
The church is denying it,
but they saved up
an enormous amount of money.
If you paid over three million won,
you could meet Lee with others
who also paid the same.
Those who paid over five million
would meet him together.
The same for ten million won.
If you paid the most,
you'd meet him privately.
Those people usually paid
around 100 million won.
How did the church treat the people
who paid that much money?
The church
basically treated you like a VIP,
more or less.
There were people
who were dressed in really pretty hanbok.
Those people came to reserve
special seats for us,
right at the very front of the hall.
That basically makes you
the envy of Manmin Central Church.
"Wow, that's not a place
for just anybody."
"They must have given a lot of offerings
and sowed a lot to Pastor Lee."
Honestly, back then, it felt pretty nice.
Because of that,
my dad paid at least three million,
up to tens of millions of won
each year at the devotion worship
to have my older sister sit
at the very front.
If you gave more money,
you got the right to sit up front.
Why is it important
to sit in the front row?
Because you got to be the closest
to Pastor Lee.
THOU SHALT NOT KILL
Illnesses happen
as a result of the curse of sins.
You'll never be ill if you don't sin.
Have you ever seen anyone become ill
when they obey the words and never sin?
Amen.
If you catch a deadly illness,
it means that you committed a sin worthy
of death, a sin that will lead to death.
"Only the sinners get ill.
You're ill because you sinned."
People thought that going to the hospital
reflected a lack of faith.
That's because Lee Jae-rock
was always proud to say,
"Our members never get sick."
In reality, they were very minor illnesses
that could have been cured
if they were treated early on.
But because they just prayed about it,
many people died from tuberculosis.
It's been with the church for a long time.
You could even say
it's a part of the church's history.
The Performing Arts Committee members
are in their twenties or thirties
on average.
They all sing and dance together.
They're also young,
so they are more active.
Fruits of joy
I am changed
His love saved me
So many beautiful people
ended up passing away like that.
My wife…
She passed away in 2006.
Hello, dear beloved believers. I'm Kim…
After the 100th episode special,
God showed his great power
through Pastor Lee…
She was
this really pretty girl who was a part
of the Hallelujah Praising Team.
She was so slender
and had this super feminine voice.
She was brushing her teeth,
then she ran up to me
with toothpaste still in her mouth,
saying she was bleeding.
So I said we should go
to the hospital, and…
She had tuberculosis.
Faith was supposed to be our treatment,
and she was in the faithful praise team.
So, when we first found out about it,
she said she'd get treatment
through faith.
She said, "I was supposed
to only love Lee Jae-rock."
"I got this illness because I got married,
and I'm going to die from it."
So she was a sinner even as she died.
If you catch a deadly illness,
it means that you committed
a sin worthy of death,
a sin that will lead to death.
When she was about to pass away,
she was…
so skinny.
And her lungs were basically gone.
And she…
She died a painful death.
Even aside from tuberculosis,
a lot of people suffered from cancer.
When I saw that happen,
I thought, "What is faith?"
"Is it really faith to stop people
from going to hospitals,
causing many people to die like this?"
That's what I thought.
THOU SHALT NOT COMMIT ADULTERY
The reason you're affected
by evil spirits,
as also mentioned in the sermon,
is because of adultery.
People who commit adultery.
They are possessed by evil spirits,
but they have no idea.
They have adulterous spirits,
so they want to do it.
So they keep doing it,
also committing crimes.
They don't realize they're possessed
and controlled by the evil spirits.
Lee Jae-rock always emphasized adultery.
Relationships between men and women.
And he always said,
"As I don't have
any adulterous spirits in me,
even when I see a naked woman,
I don't feel anything."
He said it quite often.
At one point, they started
to divide up the men and women.
They said,
"Don't sit next to each other."
"Don't even be in the same space."
For example, a man and a woman
couldn't talk to each other directly.
So, what do you need to do?
You had to talk to the other person
through your female sibling,
or someone like that.
In my case, my younger sister
would relay my message,
and when the other person
gave her a response,
she passed that message on to me.
There was an incident involving
the letters of repentance in 2010.
"It turns out that the members
have too many sins."
"All of you have led such sinful lives."
I did not think
that such sinners
would be a part of our church.
There are some people
who gave in to their sexual desires
and acted indecently.
They said, "If you write a letter
to Lee Jae-rock about your wrongdoings,
your sins will be forgiven."
I have cried out in tears…
I cried out so that not a single soul
would go to Hell, but…
But I didn't know it'd be this bad.
I didn't know this pain
would make my life so unbearable.
Please show compassion for us
during this time and forgive us.
Your son begs of you.
I'm begging you.
We had to confess
our biggest secrets and weaknesses.
I had to remember holding hands
with somebody when I was seven
and what I did with some upperclassman
when I was 20.
"What about with an underclassman?"
I had to remember everything
and try to put it down.
That's what happened.
Once everybody started writing
their letters of repentance,
it became a mandatory thing
for all the church members.
Without writing a letter of repentance,
you'd be on the edge of a cliff,
questioning whether you'd be saved or not.
If you are still committing
those deadly sins,
do you not feel bad for your poor pastor?
Is it really that hard to believe?
If you commit a deadly sin, you'll die.
Just like it says in the Bible.
There is no salvation.
You know, this topic is kind of…
I feel kind of bad talking about this.
This might really hurt that person.
Because their family
is still having a really hard time.
He was a bit…
He was a person with a free spirit.
He dated a lot of people.
He was a huge extrovert, you know?
PLEASE NOTE THIS FOOTAGE IS NOT RELATED
TO THE ACTUAL VICTIM
He ran into several problems with women.
Then Lee Jae-rock found out
about those problems with women.
Then that ended up being
a huge disadvantage for him.
He said, "You can't be saved."
Simply, "It's a work of the flesh."
He cut his thing off.
He cut his genitals off.
You could see biological
and physical differences.
He started to become more feminine.
He was a bodyguard who enjoyed exercising.
But he's so skinny now.
He has no muscles
and no facial hair either.
Those things shouldn't have happened.
They were just illogical.
And they didn't just happen
to one or two people.
There are at least around ten people
just from what I know.
He had such blind faith
and thought it was the right thing to do.
Who on earth cuts it off?
But he ended up doing it.
I looked into it as well.
And when I looked into it,
he told me where in Gangwon-do it was,
as well as how much it had cost.
It was done illegally.
He said it took three to five days
to recover from the surgery.
He said it wasn't that hard.
Lee Jae-rock was especially sensitive
about things like dating someone
from the Performing Arts Committee.
There were many pretty girls in Manmin,
like I said.
I think he thought
that all of those girls belonged to him.
But if they dated
or slept with another man,
I think he considered them
dirty or contaminated.
Why? Because he had to have them.
Because other men can't have them.
Manmin Central Church's Pastor Lee
is being accused
of sexually assaulting nine women…
The police believe that the sexual assault
happened frequently
over a long period of time.
You denied all of your charges.
Are you saying you didn't have sex?
This is dangerous.
Please, he's walking here…
-Are you denying you had sex?
-He's hurt…
Go. You can just go.
Are you denying the intercourse
or just the sexual assault?
-Excuse me.
-I denied everything.
Then why did you call
for your followers at night?
They hated it when you asked for sex.
Why did you call them at night?
I never did that.
-You never did that?
-No.
-Any words…
-Ms. Choi, excuse us.
-Any words of apology for the victims?
-Uh, Ms. Choi.
Excuse me, Ms. Choi.
Watch your legs, sir.
Well, it was just unbelievable.
It was unbelievable.
I was like,
"Something like this couldn't happen."
I mean…
Who could have imagined
that he could be a sex offender?
I thought they were false rumors.
Manmin Church and its members
do not acknowledge the claims
of Pastor Lee's sexual assault.
We believe that such accusations
will be revealed to be false,
as we're waiting.
Number one,
stop all false claims right now!
Stop them!
Manmin will prove Pastor Lee's innocence.
We'll prove it!
When we first started gathering material
for this piece,
we thought he was just a leader of a cult.
But we never imagined
that he was such a serious criminal.
Another sexual assault victim
filed a lawsuit
against Pastor Lee Jae-rock
of Manmin Central Church,
who is being investigated
for sexually assaulting his followers.
Reporter Lee Moon-hyeon.
She says she was sexually assaulted
by Pastor Lee of Manmin Central Church…
The female victim
was like a leader
among the younger church members.
MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH
She brought in the evidence,
as well as the pictures
that she took with Lee Jae-rock.
Up until now, I learned things
like virtue, honesty, and love.
I loved learning about those things…
She was very specific about the last time,
as well as the location,
she had been sexually assaulted
by Lee Jae-rock.
These are information
only the victim herself would know,
so I knew I could trust her story.
She said she first received a call
from Lee Jae-rock in 2011.
Yeah, all right.
She said she was ecstatic.
You see, she was born with the religion.
This man who she believed to be God,
to be the absolute good,
who she thought was so noble,
had given her a call.
"Oh, maybe he wants to talk to me
about my Measure of Faith in private."
"Or maybe he'll assign me
a duty and title."
He said, "Yeah, right here.
You can come to the apartment."
"Nobody knows about this place,
so come without telling anybody."
I took a taxi. I took a taxi there.
He was pretty careful.
He said, "Don't use a card. Use cash."
They wanted to show Pastor Lee
their conviction,
so they dipped into their savings,
withdrew the money in cash,
and put it in an envelope.
Then they changed
into their cleanest and whitest clothes.
I felt so nervous
when I pressed the doorbell.
I was praying on my way there.
Then even the way he poked his head out
was so shocking to me.
As soon as I went inside,
I saw a large mattress in the living room.
The stories of the victims
were eerily similar.
They were all invited to his house
out of the blue.
He told them, "I am God."
"So, there's nothing wrong
with the things that will happen here."
Or he said, "This is the Garden of Eden.
Therefore, you must not be clothed."
That's what he told the victims.
And also, the sad thing is
that the victims didn't realize
what was happening to them.
I couldn't think straight.
TESTIMONY OF A FEMALE VICTIM
OF SEXUAL ASSAULT
"What's going on?"
"Is it okay for him to do this
because he's sinless?"
"Wait, what is this? What's going on?"
"Oh, this must be his grace
to protect me from other men,
so that I can love only the Father."
As I prayed for about a month,
I think I decided to accept it, thinking,
"Oh, that must have truly been
God's grace."
He wasn't God. He was the Devil.
He said, "Just by touching my body,
you'll be healed."
He also said,
"You are in the presence of God."
"You'll go to Heaven. You'll be saved."
He was the Devil pretending to be a sheep.
He started unclasping my bra.
I was really surprised
because he was so good at it.
"Who does your ***** belong to,
Jeong-hye?"
He examines that "part" very closely.
He just keeps staring at it.
He brought my face closer to his genitals.
Then he said, "That's not how you do it."
"It hurts if you use your teeth."
While we were having intercourse,
he kept asking me if it felt good.
And he kept telling me to moan.
He was like, "Do you like that?"
You know, everyone just watches on
as he has sex with my friends.
He told us to watch some porn and practice
because we were too inexperienced.
So the assistant would play porn for us,
and you'd hear moaning.
PLEASE NOTE THIS FOOTAGE
IS NOT RELATED TO THE ACTUAL VICTIMS
Those girls were really pretty.
He picked out the girls
who were born religious, like me,
because they were pure and innocent.
Because they'd never been touched
by a man.
After he sexually assaulted the victims,
he gave them each
around three million won.
People got these nice cars and houses
all of a sudden.
These were happening.
I was like, "How on earth did they get
the money for those things?"
He gave me an envelope
that had a million won in cash.
I used to get two or three million won.
He wrote "five million won" in green ink
on a white envelope and gave it to me.
He gave me six million won.
It was the offerings
the church members had sowed.
That's where he was getting this money.
He gave me two, three million won.
Up to five million won at most.
And I gave tithe too.
There were many times
I sowed all that money back too.
I thought, "What do I do
with this precious money?"
I didn't want to waste it,
and it didn't make any sense to use it,
so I sowed it back to the church.
After that, their Measure of Faith
would suddenly increase within the church.
Many Performing Arts Committee members
had really high spiritual rankings.
I think there were 20 to 30 people.
Everything was connected,
like cogs on a wheel.
You had to get to higher spiritual levels,
and to do so, you had to sleep with him.
And his victims
were constantly victimized again.
We will not give in to their demands.
Amen!
Dear beloved Pastor Lee!
We're here for you!
Be strong!
We love you!
The pastor we've encountered
has not changed over the past decades.
He is always kind and loving.
He would cry and laugh with the members.
As we'd only seen that side of him,
we thought, "Those women
who left were always promiscuous."
"They've always fooled around with men."
And that rumor spread within the church.
"They were very immoral and dirty.
They were messy girls."
They secretly spread this rumor,
talking about it at private gatherings.
Many of the adults also knew the truth.
But they didn't leave the church.
And that was because they thought
he was the Holy Spirit.
They thought, "Humans can't pass judgment
on the Holy Spirit's actions."
Only if one or two people
had revealed the truth
and protested against what happened,
this wouldn't have lasted several decades.
Do you admit your sexual assault charges?
Why did you do it?
You're still not admitting the charges?
Where are we going?
Why did you call the women?
Do you remember
the Bangbae-dong apartment?
I remember we kept asking him
questions right up to the elevator.
But at the time,
Lee Jae-rock said nothing about himself.
And the people around him
were too busy just trying
to shove away the reporters.
I remember him acting very shameless.
Oh, sorry.
Why did you call them to your room
at 10:00 p.m.?
Do you remember April 12?
ACCUSED OF SEXUALLY ASSAULTING
CHURCH MEMBERS
PASTOR LEE JAE-ROCK'S
SECOND POLICE SUMMONS
After that, he continued
to deny his charges,
even during the prosecution investigation.
In the trial, he also denied his charges,
saying he didn't sexually assault them.
He hired very expensive lawyers
and asserted his innocence
until the very end, but…
There was this very major incident
that brought down Manmin.
Back then, a file from a female member
started to circulate.
She was one of the most active members
of the church.
She had a voice recording of herself
calling one of her friends.
She thought there was nothing wrong
with having sex with Lee Jae-rock,
and that it was a great honor.
Just because he's the Holy Spirit,
do you really think it's right
for him to demand that
from unwilling women?
-You've never thought that it was wrong?
-No.
-So you're always completely obedient?
-Yeah.
-It's not even that weird.
-Why isn't it weird?
Do you have to do everything he says?
Like if he asks women
to have sex with him?
Pastor Lee is God.
That makes everything okay.
If the Father says that it's not a sin,
then it's not a sin.
When I listened to that recording,
I realized that it was all true.
My 21 years of faith
was shattered in just two hours.
Now, what does it feel like
when 21 years of faith shatters?
It felt like…
It felt like my head had gotten slammed
with a huge hammer.
So I just couldn't think at all.
I was so shocked
that I couldn't do anything all day.
I could've never imagined it.
You just never think
that God could do something like that.
"What?"
I was just…
It felt like I had gotten hit by a bomb.
Lee Jae-rock was more than 50 years older
than those girls.
And it's not like he didn't know them.
These were the kids
who came to the church
on their mother's backs,
who he prayed for
while they were still toddlers.
And he did such unspeakable things
to those children?
At first, I almost swore at him.
To think he'd groomed these girls
since they were in their teens,
and did something like that
when they were barely into their twenties…
He was over 70 years old.
I don't even know what to call him.
A pervert? A sex addict?
I thought about what I would do
if it were me?
What if Pastor Lee called
and told me to come to his room,
and said, "Take off your clothes
like Adam and Eve in the Garden of Eden"?
You might find this pretty shocking,
but I would have obeyed him.
I loved you so much.
I loved you spiritually.
The body is one thing,
but I loved you with my spirit.
I know that.
But if you don't like the physical love,
I won't even consider it.
Okay.
I won't even consider it
if you don't like it.
That's not the reason why I love you.
Okay.
All right.
I'll see you in the morning.
Okay, thank you.
Sure.
I love you. Bye.
Okay. Bye.
May 3, 2018
was the day their God had fallen.
We're here for you! Stay strong.
MAY 3, 2018
Do you admit your charges?
Do you still deny your charges?
What did you mean yesterday
when you said you don't fear
the police and prosecutors?
Pastor Lee Jae-rock
of Manmin Central Church,
who was accused of sexually assaulting
his followers, has been arrested.
The day that he was arrested,
it suddenly started hailing.
"Look at that. God is angry."
Manmin Central Church calls that day
"the Hail Incident."
All members of the church panicked
as he was put through so much hardship.
MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH
Disclose the truth! The truth!
We want the truth!
PASTOR LEE WAS FRAMED
BRING OUT THE LIE DETECTOR
TRANSPORT
At the front?
He's at the very front.
Number 3114?
For many people, it was the first time
seeing him with white hair,
looking like a coward.
He was taking short steps,
as he was getting out of the vehicle.
He looked all timid to me.
They said because Jae-rock is God,
he doesn't get white hair,
that his hair will be black
even though he's really old.
But he just looked like a regular old man.
DEFENDANT LEE JAE-ROCK
SENTENCED TO 16 YEARS IN JAIL
All right, everyone.
Let's keep that in our hearts
as we wish Pastor Lee a happy new year.
Let's say "Happy New Year" and bow.
Happy New Year.
SOME MANMIN CENTRAL CHURCH MEMBERS
ARE STILL WAITING FOR PASTOR LEE JAE-ROCK
Pastor Lee!
We miss you!
Come back to us soon.
I am currently
at Seoul Nambu Detention Center,
as the Director
of the Council of Corrections.
I have quite a lot of authority
in the detention center.
I visited Daegu Detention Center
in March 2021.
I was curious
how the man who deceived us was doing.
I could see him,
so I said, "Hey, Lee Jae-rock!"
And he looked at me, but…
Imagine how hard my heart was pounding
when I called out his name.
"You should be ashamed!
Aren't you scared of God?"
That's what I wanted to tell him, but…
He didn't recognize me.
And even in prison,
he was the leader of his cell.
He always has five million won
kept in custody, which is the limit.
He's living a good life.
ALL INTERVIEWS IN THIS DOCUMENTARY
USE REAL TESTIMONIES
TO PROTECT THE SUBJECT'S IDENTITY,
SOME INTERVIEWS HAVE BEEN REENACTED