[Story of Nangong]
I still have to
show
His Majesty some respect.
Get out!
Don't ever appear before me again,
or I will definitely kill you.
[You think your scheme is very clever?]
[Episode 15]
This is outrageous!
What has Nangong Ying been doing
since she entered the palace?
She hasn't driven a wedge between Su Wuyang and the King of Nanjiang,
but instead made Shen Zhiwei the Empress.
Master, don't worry.
Isn't it time for Young Master to take his medicine?
With Pei Cheng in our hands,
Nangong Ying
wouldn't dare to go against your wishes.
You've done well this time.
To achieve our goals, we must use any means necessary.
Father,
what if I
really die at Nangong Ying's hands this time?
There is no "if".
Achieving the goal
is what matters most.
Rest well.
Keep a close eye on Su Wuyang for me.
Father,
do you really not care about your daughter's life?
It must be that I haven't done well enough.
Please give me some time.
I will surely make you satisfied.
Father.
After taking the medicine today,
why has Cheng's condition worsened?
Have you
forgotten his identity?
How could I forget?
It's just that years of father-son bond
aren't so easily severed.
Nangong Ying is detestable,
but Cheng is innocent.
Don't worry.
Once the stagnant blood is cleared out,
he will be fine.
Master.
Take this with you.
Yes.
Father said Cheng was born with an illness.
I never doubted it before,
but now it seems
it's not that simple.
Your Highness,
Nangong Ying is here.
What does she want?
Well,
she said she's here to apologize to you.
Apologize?
I don't believe her.
However,
I'd like to see
how she looks when she can't stand me
but can't get rid of me.
Bring her in.
Yes.
Is this how you apologize?
Even a lowly peasant would do better than you.
What are you doing?
Let me tell you,
if you dare to harm me,
I'll never let you get away with it.
There's no one else here now.
We both know
that knife back then
was stabbed in by yourself.
You think your scheme is very clever?
As long as it made you fall for it, that's enough.
Your scheme
not only deceived me
but also the King of Nanjiang
and His Majesty.
It's a triple win.
You're exaggerating.
You've intensified the conflict between His Majesty and the King of Nanjiang,
becoming a pawn in your father's hands.
You think this is a good thing?
Utterly foolish.
Oh, right.
As a small token of gratitude,
I've added something to your
beautiful face.
Are you trying to scare me?
Believe it or not.
His Majesty has been ill recently.
I need to go back and attend to him.
Shen Zhiwei,
you're growing on me more and more.
The upcoming play
can't go on without you.
You...
Your Highness,
your face.
look.
Ah!
Nangong Ying.