[Story of Nangong]
Shen Zhiwei.
How could it be you?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
[If Your Majesty won't release my wife, so what if I commit regicide?]
[Episode 9]
I want to hear Mother tell a story.
Be a good boy, Cheng.
In a few days,
I'll take you to see your mother, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Go back to sleep now.
Let's go, Young Master.
Ying,
even if it costs me my life,
I will definitely rescue you.
Nangong Ying.
Even if you betray me,
hurting me over and over again,
but why?
Why can't I forget you?
Why can't I forget our past?
Please let my wife go, Your Majesty!
Xian.
Pei Xian.
Are you trying to commit regicide?
If Your Majesty won't release my wife,
so what if I commit regicide?
Young General.
Do you know that Nangong Ying
was the Crown Princess I betrothed with formally?
Nonsense.
She is my lawfully wedded wife!
Xian,
don't come any closer.
Your Majesty,
I beg you to release him.
Quickly send a message to Old General Pei.
Young General has broken into the palace.
I fear something terrible might happen.
Yes.
You actually plead for him?
If that's the case,
then neither of you can leave!
Did you see that?
It's all because of you
that he ended up like this.
If you have any issues, come at me.
Don't hurt innocent people.
Guess
how much longer he can last.
Su Wuyang,
I'm begging you.
This is how you should beg me.
Your tears are so cheap.
Don't forget,
you belong to me.
♫A thousand sails have passed, spanning the ages♫
Your body is mine,
and your heart is mine too.
♫The lone swan cries out in sorrow♫
♫This fleeting life suddenly reaches dusk♫
Su Wuyang, release my wife!
♫The evening wind brings snow, and the boat won't cross♫
♫The candle by the west window burns out, this life ends in emptiness♫
♫Why yearn for the absent one through changing seasons♫
♫A cup of earth, a long shot gamble, a sigh of late life♫
♫No one to accompany♫