What will you choose?
Did you write the conversation?
I'd prefer to write it with the people out there,
and everyone who would want to know.
Ok...
Whatever you say in case of it.
The Ministry of Justice.
This is a studio.
Yes.
This is the only room that's long.
The juicer seems to have been removed from this story.
In the first place,
it's obvious that you can't do it without your friends.
Thank you.
In this era,
each of the employees is gathered and made.
There is a system called the KABUNAKAMA.
The KABUNAKAMA is a system that can't be removed.
You're going to see that?
Don't you like it?
I'm not a fan of Don Chiki.
You're so mean.
You can't make a book without a script.
You can't just use it in the middle of the book.
But it's not a bad idea.
I'll have to put the one I want in the team.
It's not like that in the world.
It's not fun.
Didn't you say you were going to tell me to go home except for Yoshihara?
That's right.
Juicer,
I'll do this again next time.
I'll be a good friend with Wakamugasaki.
Sir,
I'll do it.
Okay.
aiming for the
Pretty
The end
Thank you very much.
Who are you?
Born and amongst the
которая
I'm sorry.
Yo!
It's been a while.
What's wrong?
I don't remember anything.
Well...
Let's tell them.
What did you do that day?
Don't do anything.
You're not going to see me.
I'm home.
You're home.
Thank you for your hard work.
No problem.
I'm sorry.
I'm home.
No.
Leave it there.
I'll go get it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be a good man.
I want to live a better life.
I'm home.
I haven't done it for 10 years.
But I can't do it.
I can't do it.
So it's not a good way to do it.
Did you say you were Liquorhead?
To make him Uncle?
You do want to see me saying that!
You can't leave your death!
No edginess away.
Would the best time be like this?
To love you here?
Anyone?
One more!
Here,
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're the commander of the Shiba line, aren't you?
You're a good man, but you're not good at it.
I'm sorry, but I'm not good at it.
You're a scoundrel!
If you stop here, you'll be a customer.
I'm not saying that!
I can't take 6.2.
I want more money, but I don't want it.
I'm not saying that!
Shut up!
Don't talk!
You're a scoundrel who's been doing this for 5 years.
Are you talking about the shit?
Shit!
Money is shit.
Do you know where you're going to get your money?
I got it!
I'm going to go back to Edo and get my money back.
Don't you dare to get your money back!
I'm going to get my money back.
You're not getting your money back!
You're going to get your money back!
You're the one who got it and I'm going to get my money back.
I'm going back to Edo and get my money back.
Mr. To-san?
I'm going to get my money back!
What?
Get your money back after we get our money back!
Hey!
If you run away,
I'll let you go!
Excuse me.
Oh, you're not going to let me go.
I'm your husband.
I'm not going to let you go.
You're not going to let me go?
Yes.
I'll sell the things I made in Yoshioara
to the market as a book of the Urokogataya.
I can't be a good man.
I can't do that for each other.
Oh, you're not going to let me go?
I'll sell them more and more.
But I'll sell them more and more
to the Urokogataya.
What's that?
Is it about the good things?
The good things?
If you sell them,
you can't just sell them.
Well,
I'm the only one who's in love with you.
I'm the one who's in love with you.
Hey,
I'm not saying that's bad.
But I can't agree with you.
Really?
Yes.
Hey.
Oh,
Welcome.
The store is in the back.
The promise is different.
Oh,
Welcome.
It's your first time in Yoshioara.
Oh,
Man,
Karamaru,
you're in.
I'm good, Tadzu.
I have a good idea.
I'll give you a good one.
Isn't it a good thing to talk to Mr. Jirobei?
Please come here,
Mr. Tadzu.
Oh,
Yes.
Please.
Welcome.
Yes.
Did you make the money?
No,
I didn't.
I was just hanging around.
Mr. Gennai.
What's wrong?
Please help me.
Mr. Gennai.
Is he Mr. Gennai Hiragawa?
Yes.
What happened?
Please explain.
Let's go.
Karamaru,
I'll order a meal.
Yes.
Soba.
Let's go to the soba.
Sure.
This way.
Hey.
I think I can go now.
Let's go.
Mr. Gennai Hiragawa.
Mr. Gennai Hiragawa
has such a job as a mountain.
I see.
He's been doing mountain work
and is asking him to pay the money.
By the way, how much is the money?
I think it's about 1000 ryo.
What? 1000 ryo?
How can you pay 1000 ryo?
You can't pay it back.
I don't have any money.
I can't pay it back.
Then you have to pay it back.
That's the way to meet people.
I see.
I came to ask you to help me.
I don't have any money.
I want to change the iron into a charcoal.
A charcoal?
Yes.
When you use iron, you use charcoal a lot.
So the charcoal is already in the fire.
And the charcoal is also being grilled.
But I don't want to use iron.
I want to make charcoal and go back to the old story.
I see.
The charcoal will be sold.
Yes.
I want a charcoal to be sold.
A charcoal?
Yes.
I put it in my hand and went to my friend.
You put it in your hand and went to your friend?
Yes.
But didn't you sell charcoal?
I just used charcoal for the fire.
I see.
I can't believe you sold charcoal like a mountain.
You said you didn't sell charcoal.
So there's no one who wants to sell charcoal.
Is there anyone who talks about it in Yoshibaru?
Let's ask the parents.
I see.
Please.
Welcome home.
Yes.
Mr. Jirobe?
I didn't want to come to the house.
I see.
You're a good man.
The house is here.
The parents are running away.
The red one is not drinking.
It's not drinking.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm getting brighter.
I see.
I'll tell you when I'm done.
Thank you for taking the time to talk about this trip.
No, I was just thinking about the shop.
Thank you.
The shop is used as a dog.
I see.
I'm glad you're doing that.
I'll give you 300 yen.
300?
That's a little too much.
What?
If you don't sell it for 300 yen, I won't sell it.
You're holding a debt.
How much?
50 yen.
You're not laughing.
It's a debt.
It's a debt that has been history since ancient times.
How much is it?
I won't lose my debt.
Are you doing business?
How much is it?
Go ahead.
Karamaru.
Yes.
You bought a high-end juicer.
You're breathing lightly.
I don't think I bought it.
Mr. Jirozuya,
did you forget to buy something?
Welcome.
Yes.
You're so generous.
I'm begging you.
You can't do that.
You know it, right?
You're holding a key.
How about next door?
I hope you can be a good servant.
You have to be a good servant.
You'll be a fortune teller.
Tell me.
I'll tell you what you did that day.
Then, you'll be a fortune teller.
You'll be a fortune teller
who's been waiting for you.
You'll be a fortune teller.
You're a fortune teller.
It's not good.
You're so long-winded.
No, no.
But you always do this.
You think about the future,
gather people and make money.
It's not easy.
It's not like that.
I don't have a house or a job to take care of.
If you don't give me a lot of money,
it'll start.
But you'll be a good servant.
You'll be a good servant.
I can do that.
But I'm not a good servant.
I used to be a fortune teller.
You're so good.
You're a good fortune teller.
But I'm a good fortune teller.
You're a good servant.
You're so good.
But it's not like you can live freely.
Live freely?
There are many ways to live.
You can live freely.
But you can't live freely.
Live freely.
You can live freely.
There are many ways to live.
Mr. Kennai.
I'm going to buy a pumpkin tonight.
A pumpkin?
You're going to buy it?
Yes.
Can you tell me who can talk about that?
Mr. Kennai.
Here?
Yes.
Welcome.
You want to buy a pumpkin tonight?
Yes.
If there's someone you want to talk about.
Can you read the book?
No.
I want a pumpkin in Japan.
Welcome.
Japan is not good for pumpkin friends.
What?
I know.
But Tsuruya said that he's a good friend.
He's a good friend.
He's a friend of Mr. Kennai.
That's what he means.
So you're going to buy a pumpkin and go to his house?
That's what I'm used to.
You're a good friend.
I'm not sure.
I'm going to be a good friend.
You can go home.
But you can't get me a job.
How about it?
I'm going to buy a pumpkin tonight.
A pumpkin?
I'm going to buy a pumpkin.
It's a shop that I opened in Norue.
I'm going to Yurie.
Yes.
500 yen?
It's a shop that opens until the next day.
It's a long-distance shopping mall.
Can you sell the items you want to sell?
I'll sell them.
I'll sell the items.
Thank you.
God, God, God, God.
Don't be so sad.
This is what I'm going to say.
By hunting in ANZOKO while traveling,
a stone is to be sold.
If you collect what you might sell,
a garden will be Glass on the tree for sure.
When you get a pickaxe,
better words will flutter.
Weakness and accordion have their field but not greed.
I wonder if he's the right person to be.
I always want to open up a country.
Open up a country?
That's right. We have a lot of stories to talk about.
When I open up a country with a lot of people,
I want to be able to interact with the foreign countries.
I want to be able to interact with people.
If I interact with them, I can clearly understand a lot of things.
A lot of things?
For example, the house of things.
If you ask a person to buy you rice and rice,
you can ask the right person to do it yourself.
You can't sell a single budo.
The person who will help you with the business is King Gindo.
No, it's the same as the house of people.
I don't care if the ancestors are great or not.
I'll tell you what I heard.
I can talk to people who will help me.
I can understand a lot of things.
But on the other hand, I will talk to the people who are great.
If you ask a person to do business with you,
I can tell you a lot of things.
For example, the smell of the cannon.
The smell of the cannon is good, the ears are good.
I remember the word.
You're a common man.
The people eat the meat of the cow's pig.
If you can make a restaurant that can do that, you're very popular.
Well, let's come up with other things.
The one who makes the boat, the one who opens the axis of the one-way street.
The one who takes the road from top to bottom,
and makes the one who has a place to sleep.
The world changes from the bottom when the country opens.
Even if we try to do it, it will change the world.
Goodbye.
If you open the country, you will see the rabbit.
Everything will be returned.
But...
That's not good.
If you open the country,
you will be destroyed.
In this country,
there is no one who remembers the war.
Finally, the owner has returned.
I'm sorry, Mr. Rufu.
Can I go home?
I'm so busy, I'm going to eat something.
Please.
I'm home.
Yes, Mr. Rufu.
Yes.
Did you buy a high-end book?
No.
What do you think?
I feel like the money in the box is decreasing.
I think you bought something.
I think I bought something.
I wonder what it is.
Hey, Karamaru.
What?
I decided to take the story of the new story of Uroko Gata and Kakaya.
Why?
There is no way to get along with the story of the story of the Erei本夜.
So, I decided to take the story of the new story of the Uroko family
and get along with them.
I think it's the best way to get along with them.
Well, I don't have the chance to live like you.
I can't talk about the story of the story of the Erei.
I think that's good.
Oh, you promised to be the first Eri of the Tohda clan.
What?
You promised to be the first one.
I'm actually thinking about it.
First, I'll give you the story of the Erei from the story of Uroko Gata.
I'll write the story of the Erei of Harunobu, who is not the first one.
I'll write the story of the Erei of the same Erei.
I'll write the story of the Erei of Shigemasa, who is the first one.
If you say that, who will be the first one to be the first one?
Then, I'll give you the story of the Erei of Harunobu, who is the first one.
I'll turn the world upside down.
And you'll be the first one to be the first one to be the first one.
What's that?
I don't have the chance to go to that place.
That's good.
I'll tell you a fun story.
I see.
That's good.
Then?
Are you hiding something?
If you have something to worry about, tell me.
I'll be the one to die so I don't feel bad.
Why?
You're my only love.
I'm not.
I'm not worried.
Then why are you looking at me like that?
I'm just saying something strange.
I see.
Shall we go to sleep?
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
Go to sleep.
I'm not going to sleep.
What?
What's going on?
I'm so sleepy.
Yes.
What's going on?
You can sleep here.
Please.
Karamaru.
Karamaru!
What's going on?
You're so annoying.
Where's the key?
Uera, we can't go back to that shop.
So don't bother going back to that shop.
Well, where are you going to be taken away?
I think I have time to say it.
I can't remember.
What's going on?
I've been looking for a place like Shimamaya for a long time.
A child's house?
Yes.
I haven't seen it.
Thank you.
A ballroom!
What are you thinking about?
Let's go.
Excuse me, I didn't mean to go back to that shop.
I'm going to Shimagara in the future.
I won't tell you.
I see.
Excuse me.
What happened?
A child's house.
A child's house?
A man with a scar on his face.
He said it was a child's house.
This is the one in his chest.
This is this one?
I was told that this is the one.
I'm not going to tell you.
Mr. Hachio,
Yoshihara has a role as a tiger.
If you have any doubts,
I'll tell you about it.
How about you leave it to me?
If you do something cute,
I'll know what it is.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
You said you were with a child
who fell into the river
after being bitten by an unwell wound.
What?
Well,
I don't think you should
investigate this.
If you don't know
what Karamaru was doing,
you'll be in trouble.
That's all.
But,
you can't eat human's mouth.
Karamaru is
so stubborn.
A box?
He said he's gone.
He's gone.
He's a villain.
He's my friend.
He's suspicious.
Really?
What's that?
This is
what Karamaru wrote.
What?
What do you mean?
He was a good boy.
But,
I don't know
who he is.
When I was a man,
I was standing in a boat
all the way.
I was aware of it.
I was lying because I didn't remember anything.
I was hiding something.
But,
I was a bad boy.
I was wearing a mask.
And,
I didn't realize its price.
為什麼
It can't be.
I didn't do this.
You didn't do this?
Maybe he's a child of this world.
I'm sorry.
I think Karamaru went back to the Oemoto.
What?
If you don't know about Makoto, you can think of something fun.
That's the spirit of them.
I see.
Karamaru was the eldest son of Oudana, but he was kicked out of the house with a knife.
But he was told to go back home after that knife was gone.
Welcome.
And he didn't look back.
He was just drawing.
Thank you very much.
Karamaru isn't like that.
What?
He's a good guy.
He's not like you.
You said that because you wanted him to.
He's a good guy.
But he's not like that.
Someday, he'll go back to the Oemoto.
He'll tell me to take him to the studio.
And...
I'll call him a mysterious knight.
A mysterious knight?
Yes.
I'll start with a picture that looks like a spring.
I'll call him a spring now.
I see.
That's good.
I'll call him a spring now.
Please, let me keep my promise to him.
I'm counting on you.
If you go to the lake,
you'll never be able to see the mountains and the mountains.
Think about it.
The lake will be destroyed.
The river will be destroyed.
And the other things will be destroyed.
What will you do?
The waves of the lake are so strong.
What?
Hey!
So, you'll be my new master?
Yes.
Of course, I'll be your new master.
I'll be your new master.
Anyway, I hope you can make something that will come to Yoshihara.
I'm sure you'll be a great master.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
Thank you.
The studio has started to move forward again.
That time.
A man has been holding a full phone for the first time.
Good morning.
It's boring, isn't it?
It's boring.
I didn't expect you to say that.
It's a fake crime.
A fake crime?
That woman is so stupid.
How about making a bad guy?
I'll be destroyed.
Let's think about the story of the flying fish.
Yes!