An accounting guy noted some abnormalities in our annual reports.
Today, you'll help Noot
to review our past annual reports.
Before I go to Bangkok, I have somewhere I want to go with you.
I want to apologize
for not coming here sooner.
I'm dating Un.
Phim is just my friend.
Can I stay here?
You take the bedroom, Phim.
What about you?
I'll take the couch.
It's not comfortable.
I don't mind you sharing the bed with me.
We used to do way more...
Phim.
It's over between us.
I don't want you to think we could ever be the same.
When you return, I want you to talk to Noot and figure it out.
As for your illness,
it's up to you when to tell your husband.
I know we will never be the same.
I know I was wrong that day.
If I could turn back time,
I wouldn't have done it.
Kuer.
I know I had chosen the wrong guy.
If I get a divorce,
will you get back together with me?
Please?
Where is everyone? Is there nobody home?
Mrs. Wan has been sick since afternoon, sir.
Mr. Rit and Mr. Noot are not back yet.
Mrs. Phim went out in the afternoon.
- And...  - Okay! Enough!
Where they all go has nothing to do with me.
- Set the table.  - Yes, sir.
Father, is Noot not back yet?
Sit down.
Noot seems very busy these days.
He's been coming home late every day.
Eat your meal.
Good evening.
Get another plate.
I want to talk to you as my granddaughter,
not as C-Itsara's adviser.
Father, are you full?
Or is there some unwanted person
who has killed your appetite?
What about you?
I'm full.
If you're full, just leave.
I want to talk to Un.
Yes, Father.
Clean up the plates.
Did you think carefully before joining C-Itsara?
I did.
At least they saw my worth and made me their adviser.
They trusted me with an important project like this joint venture with JP.
If someone else asks you to join them
with an even better offer...
I'm not looking to change jobs now.
I don't like to betray people.
Unless something is forcing me to change.
Is it because you're grateful,
or is it because of Mr. Kuer?
It's neither.
I want to work in a company where I can express my thoughts
and show what I can do.
If I work for a company whose chairman is so full of himself,
it's no use.
My work won't mean a thing.
Are you talking about me?
Yes.
If I worked for JP today,
you wouldn't see my worth and wouldn't want to talk to me.
Isn't that right?
If you're done talking, I'll go and see my mom.
Rit, look at this.
Since 2017,
the expenditure has been increasing
by many percent year by year.
We haven't invested or expanded.
It's still possible.
The cost of living has been going up.
Everything is getting more expensive.
Look at this.
In 2021,
it was up by 30%.
If it were just by a few percent, I'd understand.
Thirty percent is way too much.
We were making more profits, so we looked at it overall and didn't notice.
We weren't focused on this.
I think I should go into each department's details.
I'll talk to Grandfather about this tomorrow.
Noot.
Do you want that joint venture with C-Itsara?
I don't want it, Rit.
But we have to satisfy them with our offer.
Our company is not a pushover.
Why don't you tell Grandfather
that you disagree with this project?
If I could,
I wouldn't be revising our offer to satisfy them.
You mean you don't want to, but you have to?
I have to.
Why are you in bed so early, Mom?
I'm not feeling well.
Have you had dinner?
I have. Let me see.
You're burning up.
Let's go to the doctor. They can give you an injection.
I took my pills. I'll be better.
Did you see Grandfather?
Of course, I did.
Don't even ask how it went.
You should agree with him sometimes.
He thinks he's right about everything.
He never cares about anything but himself and his profit.
He never changes.
He asked me about you.
He was the one who told me to ask you to come home.
- I think he might be...  - He doesn't actually miss me, Mom.
He just wants to find out what C-Itsara is up to.
Come. Give me a hug.
What happened to your foot?
I stepped on a broken glass.
It's nothing.
- Nok.  - Yes, Miss Un.
What happened to my mom's foot?
Was it Aunt Wing?
I'm not sure myself.
I heard a glass shatter. I ran out to see.
When I got there, Mrs. Wan was already sitting on the floor.
I saw Mrs. Wing's back,
but I'm not sure what had happened.
Mrs. Wan wouldn't tell me either.
Who is it?
Un, what do you want? It's late at night. Don't you have any manners?
I'm trying to sleep.
If my mom can't sleep, you shouldn't sleep.
Your mom can't sleep? What does it have to do with me?
You made my mom step on that glass, didn't you?
She did it herself.
I've got nothing to do with that.
I'll find out what you did to my mom.
I know people like you, and my mom is not that careless.
I just don't have evidence.
If something like this happens again, I'll hurt you even worse.
You're a nobody in this house,
yet you dare talk to me like this.
I do.
You'll see whether my threat is empty or not.
You...
Un.
What are you doing here?
I'm staying with my mom for a few days.
That's good. Aunt Wan misses you. She keeps talking about you.
Did you just get back from work?
We had a little problem.
I needed to review the documents.
Un.
I need to talk to you.
Is Kuer a good man?
He's been good to me so far.
Why are you asking?
Can I talk to you as siblings?
Yeah.
Is there something on your mind?
What can I do to help?
Is it about Phim?
Are you still working?
I need to prepare the documents for a meeting with my grandmother tomorrow.
You should go to bed.
I can't sleep.
I'm worried about seeing the doctor tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
Ask the doctor tomorrow what you should do.
Can you hold me?
We talked about this already.
Just hold me.
Phim...
I'll head to the office to see my grandmother in the morning,
and then I'll drive you to the hospital in the afternoon.
Okay.
I haven't been good to Phim.
I know that.
I love Phim
so much.
What has Phim done to make you think she's changed?
Phim won't
sleep with me.
Not even once?
Not at all.
We haven't even been in the same bedroom lately.
I know she's trying to avoid me.
Sometimes, she stays at the resort she's managing on Phiman Island.
Did something happen before this?
I can't stop sleeping with other women.
I want to stop, but I can't.
Especially
when Phim refuses to sleep with me. It's getting worse.
I see you two getting along well.
Everyone is jealous of you two.
Phim doesn't want anyone to find out about our problems.
She's keeping up the appearance, I guess.
The reality is completely different.
So,
how can I help?
I don't know how you can help.
I just wonder
how serious you and Kuer are.
You don't have to worry about Kuer.
He won't mess with Phim.
Thank you.
Thanks for listening to this nonsense.
Are you serious?
It's not nonsense.
- Nok.  - Yes?
What is the usual menu for breakfast?
Mrs. Wan is still recovering, isn't she?
I can do it alone.
You should take care of Mrs. Wan.
It's okay. I'll help.
- Miss Un.  - Come on. It's all right.
I cook for myself all the time.
- Four eggs?  - Yes, please.
- Nok.  - Yes?
Are you here alone? Where is Wan?
She's living off the company's money.
Can't she just come down to make breakfast for her family?
It won't kill her.
What do you do then?
What do you do in a day?
Un!
Eight years ago,
I threw rice in your face.
I should be able to do more than that now.
Do you want to find out?
That was awesome, Miss Un! Brilliant!
Does she pick on my mom like this every day?
She hasn't told me where she goes since she got a boyfriend.
You can't escape me, Un.
Are you not picking up my calls?
This is Kuer's apartment, 3906.
I'm sorry. I got the wrong apartment.
Who was that?
What should I do?
If Un calls me back, what should I tell her?
Gade, you shouldn't have done that!
Hello?
What's up? There were a few missed calls.
I saw Kuer at the apartment. I thought you had come back.
I didn't. I'm working here.
Kuer will be back here in a few days.
(Oh. Okay.)
Is that all you want to talk about?
I thought you came back and didn't tell me.
I went to Kuer's apartment to surprise you.
And then what?
And I saw an even more shocking surprise.
A woman answered the door.
(I don't know who she was.)
- Good afternoon.  - Good afternoon.
We're here to see Dr. Panida.
Okay.
Mrs. Phimrata, right? This way, please.
Look at the departments with high expenditures.
Okay.
- I'll look at this.  - Just as Mr. Noot said.
(Kuer is with Phim in Bangkok.)
(They're at the hospital to see an ob-gyn.)
(Kuerkhun)
- Un.  - Noot, what's up?
Kuer is in Bangkok with Phim.
(Un)
Hello, Un.
What are you doing?
Are you busy?
Didn't I tell you?
I don't want anyone else to find out.
I'm working at the office. I'm not busy. I can talk.
I did what you asked me to do.
What did they say?
I will
email you the details.
Okay. That's good.
Un, I have to go. I have a meeting.
What did he say? Did he tell the truth?
Is it all done?
Yeah.
She will be in a bit of pain.
It will get better after some rest.
The doctor prescribed some painkillers.
When the results come back, we will call you.
- Okay.  - I'll push you to the cashier.
It's okay. I'll push her myself. Thank you.
You told me not to worry.
Why are they in Bangkok together?
I don't know either.
They're not just there together.
They're there to see an ob-gyn.
How will you handle this?
Is Noot here?
He's not here yet.
Why don't you go to see him out front?
I'd rather not.
We'll see him when he gets back.
Follow them.
Tell me everything you see.
Thank you.
We're done, Phim. I'll drop you off at the apartment.
I'm hungry, Kuer.
Can we get something to eat before we head back?
I need to go to the office. There's something I need to do.
You can order some food when you get back.
Be careful.
Phim, can you walk on your own?
I don't think so. It hurts.
I'll go up with you, then.
Where is the messenger? I have other works to do.
Why don't you just fuse your bodies here?
He used to be admirable.
I could see how good he looked from the moon.
But seeing how bad he is now, I can see it from far out in the universe.
Please sit on the couch, okay?
Don't forget your pills after your meal. You'll feel better.
Kuer, will you come home late?
I'm not sure, Phim.
If you're tired, go to bed. Don't wait for me.
He doesn't pay me any attention.
He doesn't even have time for a meal with me.
How long can he keep avoiding me?
Quite a few departments spent over the budget limit.
We will need to look at the details.
Should I stay and help?
That's good. There's a lot to go through. I can't do it alone.
Let me stay instead. If I go home, I will do nothing anyway.
That's great. We can all lend a hand.
So late.
Yeah?
Have you arrived here?
Please come up to Apartment 3906.
- I'm sorry...  - Mrs. Phim.
You're in another man's apartment when your husband is at home.
Don't you have any shame?
I don't.
Is there any shame in staying with a friend?
There's no shame if you think of Kuer as a friend.
But I can guess from what I see.
It's more likely you're trying to catch Kuer.
Why would I catch him?
I have money. I'm not in any need,
unlike you.
What about me?
You're like a tumor.
You're a tumor your family got rid of.
You came from a great family. You were wealthy.
But they kicked you out and made you homeless abroad.
You returned here because you want to get back to House Jangwangprawas.
Think again.
I chose to leave on my own,
unlike you.
You married into the house because you wanted to get rich.
Though being rich doesn't stop your promiscuity.
Hey!
Un ex should stay in the past.
You'd better learn to know what "the past" is.
I may be in the past,
but I'm unforgettable.
I've slept in this apartment before.
Why can't I come back here?
You don't know yet.
Kuer didn't date anyone after me.
I think he's still not over me even now.
And then you just walked back?
Loser. What a loser! How did you let her beat you?
What if Kuer really asked her to come back?
Hey! I think that woman is not your average girl.
How so?
She's a liar!
Don't you believe me?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Phim?
Are you okay?
I'm alright.
Shouldn't you walk slowly?
Okay.
Crap!
That wench!
Is she pretending or what?
Did she do that?
I saw them embracing in that photo.
It's impossible for Kuer not to notice it.
She made it look like they embraced and took that photo.
Your boyfriend had no clue.
If he did, he'd have turned to the camera,
smiled, posed, or made a cute mini-heart, right?
It's the same!
Did you take that just now?
Yeah! Do you believe me now? She's not your average girl.
Are you letting her steal your boyfriend so easily?
Your food is here.
Wait a minute, please.
I'm here for delivery to Apartment 3906.
Apartment 3906?
The elevator is this way.
Is that the delivery for Apartment 3906?
- Yes. - That's good. I came down to get it myself.
- How much is it?  - It's 980 baht, sir.
Here you go.
Keep the change.
Thank you so much.
I asked you to leave nicely.
What are you doing?
I said what are you doing?
Hey, you!
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
I'm kicking you out.
Remember, I'm Kuer's new girlfriend.
You have no right to stay here.
Hey!
The owner of this apartment welcomed me.
Should I call him to ask?
If you're not sick,
would he let you stay?
You didn't think I'd know you got to stay here
because you pretended to be sick.
Maybe Kuer didn't even notice you took that photo.
Am I right?
If you leave on your own now,
I won't tell Kuer you lied.
Do you want him to find out how fake you are?
This is the list of people I want to bring to our Phuket office.
How is the work there?
Is Dr. Ann doing a good job?
She is.
Grandmother.
There are two things I haven't told you.
What?
Dr. Ann Chang's
real name is Unyamanee Jangwangprawas.
Didn't you wonder
why I sent her on a big project like that
when she had just joined us?
So you knew?
I want to discover
how much a granddaughter like Unyamanee
can influence Mr. Prawit.
As far as I see it,
she's not a pushover herself.
You two work with them. Why don't you know where they go?
I know that Kuer went to Bangkok.
What about Un?
I saw her here this morning.
After that, we were busy reviewing past annual reports.
So...
If you two want to make it big, you need to be smart.
Don't just know some things.
You need to know everything.
It's not just about the numbers in the account.
You have to know what your competitors are up to.
Personally, I can't trust those two just yet.
I don't know when they will stab us in the back.
We're joining forces soon.
Aren't they allies to us?
Un is also your granddaughter.
She's not going to betray us.
Joining forces?
Do you think you can trust someone like her?
Un is just looking out for herself.
I want that joint venture with C-Itsara
because I want to turn competitors into partners.
We'll get a share of their profit.
Maybe Un went home to see Aunt Wan?
You sure are optimistic, Rit.
Un is an adviser.
She disappears all of a sudden.
I built the empire of businesses to be what it is today
because I'm not careless!
I'm sorry, Grandfather.
I'll get that information for you.
What about those accounts? Did you get anywhere?
We're going through the reviews.
When I find out who has been leeching off our company, I'll punish them!
What about the other thing?
I'm
dating Un, Grandmother.
Why do you seem more surprised by this?
I think
Unyamanee
is smart.
She's pretty.
She's interesting.
I just didn't think you were looking for someone.
Grandmother.
It's not that I'm not looking for someone.
I just didn't find the right one.
So is she the one?
I have nothing more to talk about.
You're done here. Just go back to Un in Phuket.
Well, are you rushing me out?
How did you know that Mr. Kuer is in Bangkok?
Grandfather asked me to tail him a while ago.
Is that so?
How do we find out where Un is?
How will you handle this?
You shouldn't be letting Kuer do this.
They may have a history.
It doesn't mean they can get back together anytime they want.
What can I do then?
Phim doesn't say no to Kuer.
She even started it herself.
That's just how Phim is.
I can't stop her.
That's why I'm asking you to do something.
I'm Phim's husband.
It's been killing me to see those two in the office together.
And now I find out they're in Bangkok together.
How do you think that makes me feel?
How did you get this photo?
My friend saw Phim with another man.
He took photos and sent them to me.
For someone like Phim,
if she wants it,
I know she will go for it.
(I saw Miss Un at Mr. Kuer's apartment.)
(Mrs. Phim)
(has left Mr. Kuer's apartment and checked into a hotel.)
Un won't tell us where she is.
We need to wait and see
whose side she is on.
Un.
Where is Phim?
When did you get here?
Have you eaten? Do you want to get something to eat?
I did all the work you asked me to do.
We need to stay at the golf resort for a night or two.
As for Phim,
I told her to get a hotel.
Well...
Phim wasn't feeling well, so she asked to stay here.
Really?
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't want you to feel upset.
So it's better to lie?
It's not like that, Un. Phim went to a doctor and...
It's fine.
I know you can't tell me.
Un.
I'm sorry.
(Phim)
Take the call.
I think you want to know where Phim is.
Hello?
Did I cause trouble between you and Un?
Not at all.
She understands.
It's good that she understands.
I don't want her to get the wrong idea.
I have to go, Phim.
Aren't they arguing, at least?
If they break up, that's even better.
Phim is afraid you'd get the wrong idea.
She called to ask.
I think I didn't get the wrong idea.
See you tomorrow at seven in the lobby.
Un.
Where are you going?
I'm staying with Gade.
What is it?
Are you staying at the resort?
Yes.
When will you come back? Should I go pick you up?
Don't.
(Don't come to pick me up. When I finish my stuff,)
I'll go home on my own.
I miss you.
Mr. Noot, would you like some coffee?
Mr. Noot.
Rit is in there.
Here are some snacks.
Here's some water, Mr. Noot.
Here's some water, Rit.
Thanks.
Would you like some coffee, Rit?
A cup would be nice.
What about you, Mr. Noot?
No, thank you.
Rit.
How was the account review with Noot today?
We couldn't finish it, Grandfather.
Noot said he found the reason why expenses have been going up.
I still stand by my word.
If I find out who did this, I'll give them the most severe punishment.
Yes, Grandfather.
You should have been the first one to find out, not Noot.
What do you mean?
I mean, you're in the purchasing department.
All expenses, big or small, are made through you.
You should have been the first to see
if something had gone wrong.
Didn't you notice it?
Several departments had overspent, Grandfather.
We're checking to see the most suspicious ones.
If you're pointing the finger at the purchasing department,
I think that's not right, Grandfather.
It was right for me to limit your duties!
Should I demote you for a while?
If I let you work your way back up,
maybe that will make you a bit smarter!
What's going on, Father?
What were you guys arguing about?
It's nothing, Mom.
Then why was he angry at you?
He said I couldn't do my job.
Why?
The job you're doing
is going just fine, isn't it?
There's a little problem, Mom.
What is it?
Oh! Noot is back.
You know what? When you have time,
tell me about your problems.
I'll ask Noot what's going on.
Noot, how are you? You must be tired.
- Yeah.  - Are you hungry?
- A little.  - Have you eaten?
I'll get something for you. Come.
Why aren't you sleeping in your room?
If you were a cute guy, I would have no problems.
You won't even sleep in your boyfriend's apartment.
I want to spend time with you too.
I was in Phuket for a while. I have things for you to catch up on.
Catching up with you?
You've got so much going on. I can write a show about you.
Tell me honestly. You're staying with me
because you fought with Kuer, don't you?
You wouldn't show your face here otherwise.
I don't know who I can talk to.
How can I tell anyone
that my boyfriend lied because he wanted his ex to stay in his apartment?
Your sister-in-law is lucky.
How so?
She's lucky it was you.
If I were you, I wouldn't have just kicked her out.
I'll slap the botox out of her.
You're mad.
I'll do it for real.
If you're still mad at Kuer,
how can you stay at the golf resort with him?
You'll be there for a couple of nights.
You're not mad at me anymore, right?
If you're ready, let's go.
I'll get it for you.
I didn't tell you because I was afraid you'd get mad.
You shouldn't have done it if you knew I'd get mad.
But,
- Phim needed...  - Should you think of me over Phim?
I'm your girlfriend. She's your ex.
And she's married.
She needed to go to the hospital, and
she was afraid she would be in too much pain after that.
Too much pain? And you believed that?
I pitied her.
The way I saw her yesterday, seeing a hundred doctors wouldn't hurt her.
Shall we go?
I'm still mad at you.
I love you.
Hey!
Believe me.
I keep my promise.
I don't have feelings for Phim.
She begged to stay at my apartment.
I was sympathetic.
If I have to choose between you and her, I will choose you.
What?
I understand now.
Shall we go?
I'll open it for you.
Watch your head.
Where is Wan?
She's lazy, Father.
She probably overslept. I asked Nok to cook breakfast.
Noot.
We have rice in shrimp soup this morning. It's your favorite.
- Thank you.  - Let's go and eat it.
Your mom takes care of Noot like he's still a kid.
Yes.
Won't you have some breakfast?
I better head to work. There are still documents to go through.
Your vitamin, Father.
It's good you're here. Where is your daughter?
I don't know. She didn't come home last night.
Did she go away without even telling her mother?
What kind of mother are you?
- She didn't tell me.  - Why didn't you ask?
Are your lips sealed shut?
They're not, Father.
She just likes to talk about others, not her own business.
Please stop, Aunt Wing.
Aunt Wan, what happened to your foot?
Nothing happened.
She just woke up late and pretended to be hurt. That's all.
I'm off to work, Grandfather.
You've killed Noot's appetite.
If you want to fight in front of me,
leave.
I said leave!
Yes.
Wan!
You intentionally let Father know about your foot, right?
Are you afraid I'd tell him
that you did it?
If you think your life is not hard enough now,
tell him then.
Try telling him.
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Look. Ever since your kid came back,
you've been talking big.
Nobody can tolerate a bully forever.
You don't tolerate bullies,
yet you're in the kitchen all day.
If you do,
you might have been a wandering homeless on the streets.
Let me tell you something.
You can forget
about your daughter coming back
to make your life better.
Stop dreaming.
Rit.
These are the quotations we asked for from our suppliers.
You asked me for these.
Thanks.
I need to handle the work from yesterday first.
Okay.
Look. There was news a while ago.
People guessed that it was you and Noot.
The way I see it,
it couldn't have been you guys.
How could it have been you guys?
Noot loves you much.
- He loves you so much that I'm jealous.  - Right?
Where is Noot, by the way? Why did you come to Bangkok alone?
Noot thought I was bored. He told me to come and go shopping.
It's the hospital.
Hello?
Your blood results came back.
(The doctor told me to inform you first.)
Your biopsy is still on schedule.
What's the result?
Congratulations, you're pregnant.
(The doctor said to inform you so you can care for yourself properly.)
Okay.
If Kuer is not the father,
I'd rather not have it.
Did you go to an ob-gyn with Phim?
You said she was sick, and her husband doesn't know.
- How should I feel about this?  - How did you know?
I told Un. I'm wondering the same.
What's wrong with Phim?
I don't intend to steal anyone's woman.
Only you know that for sure.
If I were you, I wouldn't blame other people.
I'd go back and see why
my wife would want someone else.