How come I've never seen it before?
It's in the secret room of Young Lord's study.
I saw it by accident before.
Secret room.
There's no clue about the secret room's switch anywhere.
That's strange.
Where is it hidden?
You can tell at a glance that it's been rubbed often.
Could it be...
These
are all me
Strange
These paintings all seem to be of me
but they don't quite look like me
No matter how I look at them
this person is always you
but something still feels off
How about
we just go ask Shaojun directly
That won't do
If he finds out I sneaked into the secret room
he might get angry and
Then what should we do
So what do you want to do
Oh right
Do you remember last time
when I asked you for a favor at the Liucheng Inn
Of course I remember
Don't worry
I've already taken care of everything
I still don't believe
that we can't deal with Xiao Jingyang this way
Shaojun
Something's wrong
The young madam was taken away by the second young master’s men
What did you say
I saw them heading toward the city tower
Mingxuan
Xiao Jingyang
You once promised me
that we would stay together in this life, never leaving or abandoning each other
but in the end, you didn't keep your word
I also once told you
that in the next life, I would never love you again
But no matter how determined I am
when I see you again
all my resolve disappears
In this lifetime,
you haven't given me any promises.
But I want to ask you,
are you willing to hold my hand
and stay with me until we grow old?
I, Xiao Jingyang, swear to the heavens today
that in this life, I will only love Lin Mingxuan.
We will rely on each other in this life, never leaving or abandoning one another.
Mingxuan.
Mingxuan, Mingxuan!
Xiao Jingyang, what's wrong?
Is the poison acting up again?
How did you know it was poisoning?
My master told me.
Since you know it's poisoning,
then you should also know
that I don't have many years left.
What,
do you want to be a widow while I'm still alive?
Jingyang.
What a pity.
I didn't like you in the previous life.
And in this life,
I will never fall in love with you even more.
Did you think that before,
my tolerance for you was because I liked you?
It was only because you took over my body.
I had no other choice.
Since you don't like me,
then what is this?
You don't like me.
Then why did you paint my portrait?
Why did you hide it in a secret room?
How do you know the woman in the painting is you?
What did you say?
Since you've been to the secret room,
and seen those paintings,
you should know
that except for the face,
what else about her is similar to you?
Take a good look.
The actions they're doing—
have you ever done any of them?
So,
I'm just her substitute.
Yes.
Who is this woman?
You're not worthy to know.
Fine.
Xiao Jingyang, you're really something.
No matter if it's this life or the last,
you always manage to hurt me.
That's true.
Who am I, Lin Mingxuan, anyway?
How could I ever deserve the young lord's affection?
Mingxuan
You've locked yourself in for a whole day and night.
Why don't you eat something first?
Mingxuan
Should I go and get Shaojun?
Invite that ungrateful person?
Why bother with that heartless man?
Shaojun
Take it down and heat it up.
Yes.
Mingxuan
You finally came out.
You're leaving?
Thank you, Shaojun, for taking care of me during this time.
I'm returning to the Lin residence today.
This divorce agreement—
Once Shaojun has stamped it, I'll come back to collect it.
Wait.
I'll have someone deliver the divorce agreement.
Mingxuan
Shaojun, what's going on with you?
Weren't things fine just a few days ago?
How can you just decide to divorce like this?
Mingxuan