Hey, Xiao Jingyang.
You didn't get beaten to death, did you?
After all, I died trying to save you.
And yet you want to kill me.
Ungrateful jerk.
No, that's not right.
This is my body now.
I'll save you again.
What are you doing?
I'm applying medicine for you.
Otherwise, do you want to bleed to death?
I'll do it myself.
Don't you dare.
You—you're not allowed to look at my body.
Don't make that kind of face with my face.
You think I want to?
I tried to save you out of kindness.
And now look at what happened.
And you still want to kill me.
Our bodies have been swapped.
This is no coincidence.
Today, I want to try something.
See if we can switch back.
You mean—
Die again?
No way.
I don't want to be a target for arrows.
What if we don't switch back?
We could lose our lives.
But you're in my body.
That could be dangerous.
Are you afraid I'll stop you
from marrying General Wang's daughter?
That's not it.
Don't worry.
In this lifetime,
I will never marry you.
Ming Xuan.
Let's go back to the Young Lord's residence first.
We'll talk about the rest later.
Alright, everyone can leave now.
Yes.
Where are you going?
I don't have a habit of watching people bathe.
What nonsense are you talking about?
My body has wounds.
I need to soak in a medicinal bath.
Otherwise, there will be scars.
So what?
This is my body.
Have you thought about the consequences of a woman having scars?
If you want me to take a medicinal bath, that's fine.
But—
You—
Get out.
This is my body.
There's nothing I haven't seen.
I certainly haven't—
—any interest in being watched while bathing.
Hey!
You can soak,
but don't touch anything you shouldn't.
There's nothing special.
What's there to touch anyway?
You—
True.
I've been married to the Young Lord for three months.
We haven't consummated the marriage.
I suppose the Young Lord
doesn't have that ability.
So during those three months,
you were really looking forward to consummating with me.
Nonsense!
I wasn't!
Could you, Young Lord,
bring me my clothes?
That won't do.
This medicinal bath
was specially prepared for you by me.
You,
just stay here obediently for me
and soak properly.
Since you care about me so much,
why don't we soak together?
You—
There's someone outside the window.
Pretend to faint.
Young Lord, Young Lord!
Young Lord, what's wrong?
Young Lord, wake up!
Princess.
What's wrong?
Were we discovered?
No.
Then why are you embarrassed?
I saw
the Young Lord and the eldest Miss of the Lin family
taking a bath together.
The Young Lord couldn't hold on
and fainted.
My younger brother
never makes a sound,
but when he does, it's astonishing.
I also saw
the second young master go to the Young Lord's room.
Jingyu.
What is he doing there?
The marriage between Jingyang and the Lin family must happen.
No.
Go do something for me.
Remember, don't let your wound get wet.
All done.
What is this?
A marriage contract.
What happened today
will definitely not happen just once.
Mingxuan,
I know you don't want to marry me again in this life.
But right now,
we can't get away from each other.
To get through this crisis,
we have to stay together at all times.
As expected,
it's another divorce agreement.
This is already
the second divorce agreement I've received.
Sorry.
I agree.
After all, I want to get my body back even more than you do.
You're injured.
Stay here tonight.
I'll go to the study.
Mingxuan
As long as you can live well,
I don't care about anything else.
Why are you here?
The old city lord has summoned you.
Wait.
The old city lord, your father,
I can't go with you.
I'll have Wu Liuqi accompany you.
If you can't handle it,
just pretend to faint.
That's not necessary.
It's not like I haven't met the old city lord before.
Be careful with everything.
Elder sister.
Elder brother.
Where is father?
Wasn't father the one who wanted to see me?
Father heard you were attacked while traveling.
He got anxious.
He felt unwell.
He's already gone back to rest.
Quick, tell your sister,
where did you get hurt?
The injuries aren't too bad.
It's just that those assassins were pretty skilled.
Even Wu Liuqi couldn't catch up with them.
Is father’s health alright?
Should I go check on him?
You should wait until father feels better
before you go visit him.
But father asked me to remind you of something.
What is it?
Previously, because of the Lin family's wedding,
you wanted to call off the engagement.
You knelt outside the hall all night.
As a result, you fell ill.
It harmed your health deeply.
Father deeply regrets this.
Although you are the young city lord,
and have your responsibilities,
when it comes to marriage,
if you are unwilling,
you don't have to force yourself.
Father asked me to tell you
that your engagement to Miss Lin
will be canceled as you wish.
Let it go.
No.
Before, you were completely unwilling.
Now that Father has agreed,
why do you refuse again?
Everyone knows
that I brought Lin Mingxuan to stay at the residence
as my fiancée.
If I break off the engagement now,
what will happen to her reputation?
Third Brother
Lin Mingxuan is not worthy of you at all.
Weren't you also completely unwilling before?
Why not just go along with Father's wishes?
Well, Xiao Jingyu, you...
You talked nonsense in the previous life.
You made Xiao Jingyang mistakenly believe
that there was something between you and me.
And now in this life, you insult me again.
This time, I absolutely won't tolerate it.
But Father also said
marrying Lin Mingxuan was to
bring our family closer to the Lin family.
Since Lin Mingxuan isn't worthy of me,
why not let me marry Lin Minghua instead?
I've heard that the second Miss of the Lin family
is extremely talented.
She's skilled in music, chess, calligraphy, and painting.
She should be worthy of me, right?
I want to see
how you handle it when your own relationship is disrupted.
What will you do then?
No!
Elder Sister
The second daughter of the Lin family and I have long been in love.
We've already pledged ourselves to each other.
So he admits it himself.
The kid is actually quite devoted.
Jingyang
Since you want to take responsibility for the eldest Miss of the Lin family,
that's certainly a good thing.
As for your earlier wish
to marry General Wang's daughter,
Father has already mentioned it to General Wang.
You can just marry them both.
What do you mean, General Wang's daughter?
How is it?
Did Father say anything today?
The city lord is ill.
I didn't see him.
What?
Are you really going to marry General Wang's daughter?
So you knelt in front of the main hall all night.
It wasn't just to break off the engagement.
It was to marry Wang Yiqiang.
So you weren't
someone who fell in love with someone else after we got married.
If that's the case,
then in our previous life,
why did you pretend to want to marry me?
It's not what you think.
Then what is it?
Xiao Jingyang.
As long as you explain, I'll believe you.
If we're only pretending to be together,
then why should we keep this marriage contract between us?
Mingxuan
I'm sorry