♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
♫ If you're still a cheater, then there will be no "us" ♫
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
🌟[VIP Thailand]🖤
[Heading to pickup point]
[Driver is on the way, 11 minutes]
Thank you for letting me change clothes.
You're still burning up.
Let me prepare the herbal medicine for you.
It's still warm.
Thank you for making me the medicine.
It's okay.
In the past, when I was sick, my mom also prepared Chinese medicine for me.
It wasn't just the medicine,
it was the care that she gave me as well.
The driver I called must be here
so I'd better go.
Let me see you out.
Rin.
Please come in.
Sir.
What am I supposed to do with you guys?
I forbade you. I scolded you.
I took your condo key card, yet you still meet each other here?
Really?
Why, Lita?
Are you so horny that you can't resist it?
Why are you so shameless?
Sir, it's not like that.
I wasn't feeling well so Lita brought me medicine,
but it's raining so her clothes got wet.
I just let her change the wet clothes.
It's not lust as what you think.
The love and care for P'Pak really came from my heart.
Stop talking.
You are shameless.
You're saying you love P'Pak while standing in his wife's house,
and his wife is standing right here.
I knows it's wrong,
but when I was sick lately,
did anyone take care of me besides P'Pak?
If P'Pak is sick,
I just want to help him the best I can,
the same way that he did for me.
Even if people think that I'm a tramp,
I don't care.
What?
You don't care?
Don't you care? Come here. Come here.
Pull yourself together!
What are you thinking?
Wake up!
- Sir, don't do this.
- Do you have sense, now?
Wake up, Lita!
Sir.
You too, Pak.
I've already told you, haven't I?
Control your women!
Let's go home. Come here.
Let's go.
Go.
Have I told you before?
No matter how much you love each other,
you should go to Hell together.
Rin.
I didn't ask her to come here.
I didn't really bring her here.
You look a lot better.
I was told you were sick
so I was worried about you.
I checked the CCTV camera. I worried if you were okay home alone,
but Lita's medicine is really good. It made you look so much better.
Rin, can you listen to me?
I didn't bring her over here.
I really didn't tell her to come.
I know.
You weren't the one who brought her here,
but how did she enter this house?
You opened the door for her to come in.
Just like you let her enter our relationship!
Clean it up...
like you used to take care of Lita.
Because this is my home.
[The Legend]
Come in.
If you want to discuss yesterday, I've already dealt with Lita.
This kind of incident won't happen again.
No.
I have other matters that I need to bother you with.
What?
I don't think the company is being responsible enough regarding Prae.
Danai has already been fired.
Nate will find her a lawyer. What else do you want?
Prae should receive compensation.
Don't forget that when Prae was harassed, it occurred in the workplace.
The company should be responsible for how she was treated.
Wouldn't that be a bit too much?
It's too little actually.
Compared to what Prae encountered, and the sorrows she's been carrying for a year,
I think the company's employees will also see that
we truly care to solve problems.
There is another thing too.
I'd like you to increase the welfare for all female employees,
the right to take menstrual leave.
Look, every employee is eligible for 30 days sick leave a year.
If you have menstrual pain, just take sick leave.
Why would you ask for more leave?
This is clearly unfair to men.
Well, men don't have uteri.
If you permit it,
people will see that our company really understands women,
but if you think that I'm asking too much,
I'll talk to Ms. Treenate instead,
about everything.
Are you threatening me?
No.
I just want you to know that even without you,
I still have another way.
Wait, Rin.
You shouldn't threaten him like that.
Mr. Jakchai does whatever he wants. He doesn't care about anyone.
Thank you for your concern,
and thank you for having an affair with Lita
so I can threaten Mr. Jakchai with that.
Thank you.
Rin.
[The Legend]
The new VIP Team policy is awesome.
Adding maternity leave.
[Special Policies for Women on the VIP Team]
There's menstrual leave too.
If you have postpartum depression (after childbirth), you can consult a psychiatrist for free as well.
The VIP Team piloted (led) it. How great!
I'll have my department submit the request, too.
It must be Rin who presented this to Mr. Jakchai.
It's probably her.
But it is strange.
Why was it implemented so quickly?
Come on.
The company is aware like this.
I think in the future, they should add a gender equality policy, not just men or women.
The LGBTQ+ staff in my department aren't few.
Right, I think this is good for the company.
When employees are physically and emotionally fine,
they'll perform better at work.
I've thought about it.
Guys who take care of their girlfriends with menstrual pain must have a hard time.
It must be stressful for them.
You spoke so well. Do you have a girlfriend already?
Just a crush on someone.
Don't say it. Others will know your secret.
Stop it.
Come in.
Nate.
What's the matter?
I want to praise you.
I saw your new policy for the VIP Team.
Other departments are interested in this and asked to do it, too.
Who proposed it?
Rin?
It's my team. Can I not figure it out myself?
Why are you being so nosy?
A good policy and a good attitude toward women?
Is this to your credit?
Although you know a lot about women,
you'll never understand a woman's heart.
Are you being pressured by women from the VIP Team?
I was once oppressed by men.
I felt like an idiot.
I would like to see men being treated that way, too,
to see how they'd feel.
Perhaps it's like
being castrated. Am I right?
- Nate.
- Yes, it is.
Rin pressured you, right?
So why did you do it?
Or is it due to Lita?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I see you have a daughter.
Maybe now you understand the heart of a woman, that's all.
Why?
Is there something more?
Nothing.
What are you doing here?
This way.
Go ahead. Take care of it.
What are you doing?
I can't let you stay here by yourself anymore.
Hooray! We're finally under the same roof, Lalita.
I should celebrate this special occasion. Whom should I call?
What about Rin?
I heard you two have been getting closer lately.
You went to the man's house, right?
Wait, did I get the wrong term?
I should call it shameless.
I didn't ask for you to love Lita,
but can you just leave her alone?
I won't touch her.
I want to know how a father like you would raise
his own child.
Your room is next to mine
so I will know when you go out.
Is it that necessary?
And why might it be?
Don't say you're about to sneak out to see Pak again.
You can't control yourself, can you?
Do you miss him that much?
I tell you, don't do anything stupid.
Just control yourself!
Wait until Rin is out of the picture.
- Prae?
- Rin.
I brought you something.
What's that?
Human Resources Department told me they're working on compensation for my assault case.
Is it because of you?
Did you do that for me? And the menstrual leave?
It must have been you who went to Mr. Jakchai.
That's right.
You know what he's like.
He wanted to move you to Phuket.
What you did...
I'm so happy to see it.
If not for you, I would have resigned due to Danai.
Mr. Jakchai has never done anything as our leader.
He deserved it.
I can't help it.
Someone like him deserved it.
But you should be careful.
You should take me along next time, do you hear me?
I want to see how he reacts.
Let's go to work.
- Sure, I'll be there.
- Let's go.
Thank you.
[The Legend]
I want to throw this away; you don't have to follow me.
It's Mr. Jakchai's order.
We need to follow you until you're home.
Why did my brother order something like that?
Why did your father order someone to watch you so closely like this?
Is everything okay?
He must be worried about my safety.
Worried about you?
He made you move suddenly too.
How are you feeling?
Did Mon do anything to you?
You can tell me, Lita.
You can tell me anything.
It's okay.
I can talk to Dad about some of it.
You know your father doesn't care about anyone but himself and his needs.
It's your life, Lita.
You need to decide.
I understand you the most.
No one understands a daughter like her dad.
She's my daughter. I take care of her.
If you'd like to take care of someone, find a husband and have children.
Although, I think it might be too late since I doubt any man could stand you.
Right.
Women desire different things in life.
I don't need a husband or child to fulfill me.
What can truly fulfill my need is to know that everything at The Legend
belongs to me.
Lita.
Let's get out of here.
[The Legend]
I think this blazer suits you well.
You could wear it to the company's anniversary.
This blazer is perfectly fitted.
It can make you look stylish.
It's a good combination of masculine and feminine.
You can see the glittery fabric.
When worn, it shines in the light.
This would make you look outstanding.
I really like it.
Few people know me this well.
I'd like you to work by my side.
Thank you for the opportunity,
but I'm busy with my work in the VIP Team.
You know what I mean.
I'd like you to leave your team.
I can tell that between you, Pak, and Lita,
something is going on, right?
I...
I can handle my own matters.
Don't forget that if something happens,
my brother will take his daughter's side.
If you're here with me,
when you tell me that you have a problem, I can help you.
I...
I'd like to stay with my VIP Team.
To protect him?
No, Ma'am.
I love my team.
No matter what happens,
I won't leave them.
Are you going to be my enemy?
I have to be on a different side.
You're quite something.
I really admire you!
Rin?
What did you say to my aunt earlier?
Why?
I...
Please don't tell her anything.
Her intentions toward you aren't good.
Whose intentions are good then?
Yours?
Thanks for your suggestion.
Seeing you so jumpy like this
makes me really want to know what would your aunt do
if she found out about your affair with my husband?
Please, I beg you.
Please don't tell her.
Please?
This is not just about me.
I don't want Pak to be in trouble.
Can you do this for him, please?
The more you act this way,
the more I want to tell your aunt.
Wait.
You are saying the VIP Team got menstrual leave
because Rin asked Jakchai for it?
She wanted every female employee to get the same thing.
She just needed to start with this team first.
Rin pushed Mr. Jakchai about this,
but what if he tries to get back at her?
Your one and only daughter told you, didn't she?
Rin.
What did you say to my sister?
Whatever I said,
do you really think I'd tell you?
I'm not your playmate!
I was joking.
I know what to say and what to keep to myself.
You're a smart woman.
You should be smart enough not to betray me.
Do you want to work for my sister?
I know I'm a smart woman.
I'm wise enough not to stay with anyone who treats me unfairly over and over.
But if someone annoys me enough,
I could do something about it.
Rin didn't say anything to my aunt, did she?
- Why did she say?
- If she really did, she wouldn't tell us.
If you didn't tell your aunt, I don't think she would know.
I really didn't say anything to her.
I just talked to her briefly before you came in.
I know.
You're stupid about dating Pak,
but you aren't stupid enough to tell my sister.
You may say that P'Pak and I are stupid, but for me, it's love.
"Love"?
You watched too many dramas.
Stop saying dumb things like this. It's so annoying.
It's a good thing that you and Pak are dating.
Pak knows a lot about me.
Now, he must follow my orders.
The problem is Rin.
Rin, wait.
Mr. Jakchai told me to give you this.
[Ms. Rinnara Yamonkan: ฿1 million ($28,000)]
Did he want to buy me off?
I should have said the amount so I could get more.
What? Are you surprised that I asked for money?
I've been hurt enough.
I should, at least, get compensation.
What are you trying to do?
Call Lita and tell her to come here and see you.
You two should take your sweet time so I can earn more.
Rin.
Are you really happy doing this?
Do you worry about my happiness?
Let me know if you need your cut from the check.
- Here.
- Thanks.
I know you feel bad about it.
Rin was being sarcastic all day; how could you handle it?
It's more than that, Hia (Older Brother).
Deep down, you wanted to go back to her, return to the way you were.
I don't know if we can go back to the way we were.
But it would be so great, wouldn't it?
If that's not possible,
and Rin just wants to torture me, then I'm fine.
I'll let her do whatever she wants; I can take it.
I know that you can, Hia.
But for how long?
How long do you two need to be like this?
I don't really know,
but I need to stay by her side right now.
I need to protect her.
[The Legend]
[VIP Warehouse]
Why are they inspecting our warehouse now?
As per the schedule, they were to be here in the next few months.
Perhaps they want to check everything before the event.
Our team takes good care of things. I don't think we need to worry about it.
I see.
Excuse me, can you take a look here?
What is it?
The bags on the list have gone missing.
After inspecting VIP's warehouse,
we found that two Hermès Himalayan Birkin bags were missing.
They are valued in the millions of baht.
No way. We constantly check the inventory,
and all items are waiting to be delivered.
They can't go missing.
You need an employee ID card to get in.
We can check who entered and exited.
We checked that as well.
There was one person who entered the warehouse at 11 last night.
They unlocked the item's safety system.
That person is...
Mrs. Rinnara.
I didn't take anything from the warehouse.
There is something abnormal about this.
I can also confirm Rin didn't do it.
She stayed until late, working overtime.
How can you be so sure?
You joined me in visiting a client at that time.
You seem to precisely know where he was last night.
Rin, I know you're smart,
and you've been working for VIP and The Legend for such a long time.
But the evidence points to you taking those two bags.
But I didn't do it.
If you don't believe me,
we can check the CCTV footage.
Then we can find out who did this.
Calm down. We don't need to go through that.
I trust you.
That's why I'm keeping this a secret.
So the other executives won't find out about it.
But I don't know how long I can cover up for you...
because the client will want to receive the bags soon.
And this will be investigated.
Even if you say that you didn't do it,
before the process is finally over,
you could be suspended...
and you could be fired.
Fire me?
What about this? I can help you out.
But you need to transfer out of the city branch.
In the meantime, I'll clear everything here.
Does that sound good?
I really can't give you access.
Why is that?
Why can't I check the footage from yesterday?
There's a new policy requiring a letter from the executive to grant access.
[Information Technology Department]
Hold on, when was this policy issued?
The other departments asked to check the footage the other day, and they were allowed.
Mr. Jakchai just issued the new policy.
I'm sorry, but I can't grant you access.
Excuse me.
Hey!
I'll try to check it.
It's not her for sure.
Rin didn't steal anything.
The sudden inspection
and Rin's name appearing on the log-in sheet,
I think someone is trying to sabotage her.
The only ones who can do this discreetly...
are top executives.
Which executive wants to sabotage her career?
You tell me.
It's you, isn't it?
You did that, didn't you?
You want to get her out of the way.
To solve what's going on...
between me and Lita.
It's all my fault.
Rin has nothing to do with this.
In the past,
I made her cry.
She has been hurt enough from me.
Please, Sir.
I don't want her to face something terrible like this.
Let her go, please.
Please let her go.
If you had controlled your women,
none of this would have happened.
Rin?
How are you feeling?
You knew about it, didn't you?
You knew Mr. Jakchai did it.
I asked to see the CCTV footage today,
and they denied my request, saying it's Mr. Jakchai's order.
He wants to frame me.
Did you know about this?
I had no idea, really.
I swear that I didn't know.
I didn't know.
If I had known,
I wouldn't have let Mr. Jakchai do something like that to you.
You know that...
I dedicated myself to work to get to this position.
Now my hard work is crumbling down.
It all started when you cheated on me with Lita.
What do you think I should do?
You don't have to do anything.
I'll take care of this.
I won't let him do anything to you again.
What will you do?
What's your plan?
I don't believe you anymore.
♫ If I were to love someone ♫
♫ I would never hurt my heart ♫
♫ Whomever I love, I’ll love only him ♫
♫ So why did you cheat? ♫
♫ Why didn’t you stop yourself? ♫
Dad?
If this is how you want to help me,
I don't want it.
I don't want anyone to be in trouble due to me ever again.
Do you really think the world revolves around you?
I can't let Rin work here with us anymore.
Sooner or later, she will cause me trouble.
And I won't let that happen.
But she didn't do anything wrong.
I don't want to hurt her.
You've already hurt her by having an affair with her husband!
Stop pretending to be a nice person...
and think about this. If I hadn't done it,
could you have beaten her?
You never think first.
Did you get that from your mom?
Stop that.
You can't say that about Mom.
She was a good person.
In the past,
no matter how hard we had to struggle,
she never left me,
unlike you.
What did you say?
I couldn't raise you
because your stupid mom got pregnant and didn't tell me.
She thought she could raise a child by herself.
Look what she did.
She raised her daughter to be someone's mistress.
[Pak]
[I can't talk right now. Send me a text.]
You are fighting with your dad and not eating dinner.
Such a childish act.
Do you think your dad would beg you to eat dinner?
You really don't know him.
I'm not in a mood to fight with you today.
I'm too tired.
Lita.
Do you know what kind of person is the most pathetic?
It's a person who can't design her own life,
who places her happiness in someone else's hands.
It could be her man...
or her father.
Are you telling me I'm pathetic?
I'm not talking about you.
From one woman to another,
don't be in this situation.
Don't be like me.
I created a record of Rin logging into the warehouse.
What about the CCTV footage?
I'll delete everything from that night.
Rin can't get away from it for sure.
I'll let you take care of it.
Yes, Sir.
[The Legend]
I know Jak is trying to sabotage you.
What will you do?
I have no idea.
Did Pak not help you with that?
I don't want to trouble him with it.
And I don't think he could help me much.
If he really wanted to, he would do it.
They both know each other really well.
Pak is the one helping out...
Jak with his mistresses.
See for yourself.
I hired someone to follow them, and I got these.
Since P'Pak has been Director,
he has been taking care of this.
When Jak decides to keep someone,
Pak sends them money.
If Jak decides to get rid of someone,
he uses money to shut them up.
Pak knows everything about Jak,
including his work and personal life.
There is so much more that we don't know.
Pak slept with Jak's daughter,
yet Jak keeps him close. What do you think?
Rin.
Where did you get these photos from?
Is this why...
you're having an affair?
Is this why you dared cheat on me?
You think all of this is normal.
I can't believe you're helping Mr. Jakchai with his women.
You found places for them to stay. You gave them money.
When he decides to get rid of someone,
you're responsible for giving them money to shut them up.
You're living with it. Is that normal?
That's why you did this to me.
It's not like that.
It's not true.
Every time I had to handle that,
I didn't like it.
I was never happy about it.
I felt bad every time...
I had to face his women.
I had to pay them off.
I had to tell them to go away.
I had to break up with them for him.
I never wanted to do it.
Why did you do it?
Why did you?
I have to, I need to.
How so?
I'm so grateful to him.
I have a stable job
and hold a high position.
I got all the stability in my life from him.
He gave it to me.
I'm so disappointed in you.
You're greedier for benefits than I thought.
This makes me so sure...
about Lita.
You slept with her since you thought of the benefits.
It's not true.
Please listen to me.
It's not like that.
- That's enough!
- It's not like that!
You know what?
You don't seem like the man I wanted to spend the rest of my life with.
It's like I've never known you before!
I'm very disappointed in you.
♫ If I were to love someone, I would never hurt my heart ♫
♫ Whomever I love, I’ll love only him ♫
♫ So why did you cheat? Why didn’t you stop yourself? ♫
♫ It is only I who loves this relationship ♫
Rin. Can we talk?
♫ You once promised that we would love each other until the day we die ♫
♫ But when she came in, you easily forgot about me ♫
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
♫ If you're still a cheater, then there will be no "us" ♫
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
[The Legend]
Rin, I have something to tell you.
Last night, my husband got the warehouse's access sheet.
We saw that the access log didn't come from your employee ID card.
Someone programmed it.
I got it.
Here's Rin.
Someone made it up.
Take a look here. It's black.
Mr. Jakchai is a monster.
There's more.
All footage from that night was deleted.
They want to frame you.
What do you want?
I want to remind you.
Stop playing dirty with me.
Don't forget I have these.
There's no point in doing that.
I have the original file.
If you don't change the false accusation that I stole bags,
these photos will be leaked anytime.
Don't forget to take care of it.
I hadn't forgotten that you had these photos.
And I knew you would use them to negotiate with me.
What do you mean?
Are you ready...
for the whole world to see
your daughter having an affair with someone else's husband?
You can try.
People can say anything about my daughter.
I can ship her off to study overseas. They'll forget it all in a few years.
But you...
If you don't transfer like I suggested,
I won't let this case go.
It'll be in your record for years,
and all your hard work will mean nothing.
No one will hire a person with a bad record.
Do you want to risk that with me?
Come on in.
I have some documents for you to sign.
Hello?
In a meeting room?
Sure, I'll be there.
Thank you.
[Resignation Letter]
Is P'Pak going to resign?
Excuse me, have you seen P'Rin?
She should be outside.
Rin.
P'Pak wrote a resignation letter.
He'll take responsibility for the missing bags for you.
So what?
Don't let him do that.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to stop him?
And should I be responsible for it when I didn't do it?
Can you?
How shameless can you be?
You know I didn't steal anything!
But you want me to be responsible for something I didn't do
so your man can keep working here.
What do I gain from that?
What do I get from you?
Please, I beg you.
I'll do anything for you.
I can get down on my knees to beg you.
Just for this one thing, don't let P'Pak resign.
Please. I beg of you.
Do you see the ground?
It's like you're asking me to jump.
If you were me, would you do it?
So Mr. Jakchai told someone to fabricate something to hurt Rin.
Can he do that?
Sure, he can.
The daughter took her husband,
and the father wants to transfer Rin.
Someone like her won't give up easily.
What can she do about it?
She was pushed so hard.
We can't just stay still.
I think...
we need to fight back for her.
People can say anything about my daughter.
I can ship her off to study overseas. They'll forget it all in a few years.
But you...
If you don't transfer like I suggested,
I won't let this case go.
It'll be in your record for years.
Rin?
I called for you...
and you got quiet.
So I came here to check on you.
I wanted to tell you not to worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
I'll resign.
For what?
I...
Tomorrow,
will you be at the anniversary event?
Please let Mr. Jakchai know...
I'll give him my answer soon.
Please.
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
♫ If you're still a cheater, then there will be no "us" ♫
🌟[VIP Thailand]🖤