♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
♫ If you're still a cheater, then there will be no "us" ♫
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
🌟[VIP Thailand]🖤
I'd like to introduce you to the Privilege Team.
I don't think we need more than that.
You should know about them by now.
They will take care of our foreign clients and all VVIP clients.
But they are our top spenders and the highest-paying clients.
Their spending is even higher than all of our VIP clients.
That's right.
I must give VVIP clients special treatment.
The VIP team doesn't have to help with that.
We've been taking care of them just fine.
We are short of staff and we can hire more people.
I don't think we need another team to overlap the work.
Rin, even though you were promoted,
you're just a director.
Do you think I care what you think?
Rin, I have to do what Mr. Jakchai... asked me to.
But I'll make the minimum impact to your team.
If he's about to do anything to you, I'll warn you first.
No need to.
I don't need your good intentions anymore.
I don't trust you anymore.
But...
What do you want us to do?
P'Pak has tried to help you out all along.
And I deserved what I did.
I won't forgive you.
You don't have to.
Everybody knows that you two aren't together.
Well, I think we three should all get a fresh start...
in work and personal life.
Lita.
That's enough.
You're good.
I can't wait to see if your work is as good as your words.
Jak founded a new team to overlap with VIP
and to encourage his daughter, with the help of Pakawat.
I think this is too privileged.
Don't say it in a negative way.
Lita is my daughter.
But she's not too privileged.
She was born with a responsibility to manage the business.
One more thing.
I can give others many chances, but this is my own daughter.
You gave chances to people with high competence.
Is Lita competent?
Your daughter is having an affair so you founded another team!
You even appointed the cheating man to work there!
Don't you fear people will complain?
We can work on her competence.
Lita is his daughter;
blood is thicker than water.
If Lita and Pakawat would like to get serious,
can we wait until things cool down first?
Don't show it off too much.
It could be ruined.
Yes, Sir.
Rin is appointed as new director of VIP Team.
You should be satisfied, and everyone should be happy.
One more thing:
Pakawat doesn't take care of VIP Team anymore.
The ladies can show their real talents.
[The Legend]
We need new brand items to showcase at the VIP client's celebration party.
By tomorrow, can I get the list of brands for the party?
The launch of our team and VIP's celebration party will be on the same day.
Each brand needs to discuss which one will stay with what team.
Does this mean that not all brands will join VIP Team like before?
We need to host this party for our top spenders.
If things change, it'll be big trouble.
We've been working on it for too long.
Saint, what do you think?
Let me ask you something.
What are the differences of the Privilege Team and VIP Team?
Their jobs are overlapping,
and VIP Team's celebration party falls on the same day as Privilege Team's launch party.
This should be fun.
We can see who's the best.
Privilege Team will take care of VVIP clients
and foreign clients.
It means that VIP Team
will lose high-spending clients, right?
So we need to give old VIP clients to Privilege to take care of?
Do you think they'd like that?
Why wouldn't they?
They will be VVIP clients.
Or can clients not separate work and personal life
like everyone in this room?
If you don't like working with me for your personal reason,
then I'm sorry.
I can't change this fact.
Others in this room don't mix their personal life with work.
We're worried that VIP clients
won't be fine with new people to take care of them.
They didn't get to decide based on what they wanted or needed,
since they used to buy items from people they trusted.
Can I say something?
I am a manager.
My job is more than just tell them which items are the best ones.
We need to satisfy clients so they will come back to us.
People with money can buy products anywhere they want.
I can assure you that I know all my clients.
I know what they like or don't like.
Do you get it, Lita?
I kind of get that changing the team could cause decreased sales.
Thank you for letting me know.
What about this?
On Privilege Team's launch party, can I get the brand manager to help me?
- It's fine. We can share...
- No sharing.
Lita asked us...
then she can have all the brand managers.
VIP Team can take care of the celebration party on our own.
Thank you.
[VIP Management Team]
We have a big challenge.
Look at her saying we need to separate work from personal life.
Her dad couldn't do it.
You just encouraged them to get what they wanted.
They should have gone public by now.
I don't care. They can do what they want.
We're still working together, Rin.
How could we separate work from personal life?
Hey, let me ask you something. Must I be with them during the party?
This is just like we are climbing a mountain,
but they are riding a helicopter to the top.
He founded the team to take our VIP clients.
You think someone like Lita can do it?
Maybe since P'Pak is helping her.
I'm not worried.
Do what they want.
It's fine. We can show them
our VIP team needs no luck.
Come on in.
Hey.
P'Pak, should we go to dinner together?
I don't think so. I'm busy, and I have a meeting.
I think I'll have dinner here. You can go.
Everyone knows about us already.
We have nothing to hide.
I've told you for so many times...
I can just take care of you.
That's it.
Why is that?
Why can't we date?
Or is it because you feel bad about Rin?
It's nothing like that.
But...
You should get this delivered.
I'd like to talk to you about what happened in the meeting room.
We can talk here.
Go ahead.
My team...
doesn't want to get in your way.
And I don't want to get in your way, either.
But you know that...
your team was founded to destroy my team.
I won't let that happen.
I won't let that happen, either.
It's good that we're fighting like this.
This is the first task, but our teams are already at it.
Listen.
It hurts me a little:
my team versus
your team.
We used to be on the same team.
You...
[Lalita]
Excuse me.
Where are you?
I'm waiting to have dinner with you.
I already ate.
I'm about to go to bed.
Rin, have you eaten?
- I bought you Japanese food.
- You should have it.
♫ If I were to love someone ♫
♫ I would never hurt my heart. Whomever I love, I’ll love only him ♫
♫ So why did you cheat? ♫
♫  Why didn’t you stop yourself? It is only I who loves this relationship ♫
♫ You once promised that we would love each other until the day we die ♫
♫ But when she came in, you easily forgot about me ♫
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
[The Best Team]
♫ If you're still a cheater, then there will be no "us" ♫
♫ I don't want to believe it ♫
♫ You, a person I trusted, ruined this relationship ♫
♫ Dreams that I thought were beautiful, that we created together ♫
[The Best Team]
♫ Fell apart overnight♫
♫ You once promised that we would love each other until the day we die ♫
Rin. I sent you many restaurants to select.
Why did you choose this one?
Tell me. I'm learning from you.
Our VIP customers really like the atmosphere of this restaurant.
And I think it's a good fit to hold a celebration event.
Most importantly, the award-winning Chef Keller is opening his restaurant here.
They will compete to be the big spenders to taste his dishes for the first time in Thailand.
Wow. So if the event works,
we can make this restaurant a regular venue for VIP customers.
I have asked the public relations team to help.
Chanont should have arrived.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Good afternoon.
- Hi, I'm from The Legend.
"The Legend"? You're here already.
Excuse me.
Rin.
The VIP Team has made an appointment.
Why let other teams intervene like this?
Oh, Ms. Rin, Mr. Pak. Aren't you in the VIP Team together?
Is your team using this place to organize a party for the highest-spending customers?
Lita. Did the VIP Team book this place, too?
Is this overlapping?
I just contacted the restaaurant.
When I told them I was from The Legend, they agreed and told us to come in.
Pretending. So you pretended to be us?
It's not.
I didn't know that you would come, too.
If so, I'll go to another restaurant instead.
We are always on the same page.
No need to find a new place.
We can share.
We have shared many things before.
Rin, I'm so sorry. I was stuck in traffic...
So both teams made an appointment here?
These menus must be prepared for 30 guests on that day.
- Are you sure you can do this in time?
- Yes.
Can I have a look at the wine list?
Okay, I'll prepare a wine list for you.
Yes. This is a menu list.
- I'm sorry.
- Yes.
Do you have a rooftop zone here?
Yes.
But since it's now the rainy season, we closed it temporarily.
Can I have a look?
Sure.
This is the key card.
You can walk this way to the rooftop door.
Thank you.
I'm here to tell you.
I just want you to know I don't want to compete with you.
And I have never thought of stealing anything from you.
I know what I've done...
It's an unforgivable thing. I understand.
It's good that you know it.
And you should know this too,
that your dad established the Privilege Team
to force the whole VIP team to resign.
It's not just me who is ruined,
but all in the VIP Team,
who used to adore you, teach you,
and protect you when you were seen as your dad's mistress.
They will all be screwed (ruined).
Remember it.
- Then I'll list the wine for you.
- Okay.
- Thank you so much.
- Rin?
Saint.
Is it raining outside?
I'm stuck on the rooftop.
Tell the staff to open the door for me. It's locked.
Okay, I'm going right away.
Sorry.
I think the sensor might be broken.
I'll contact the security company right now.
Why are you standing there?
Do you want those coming to see that I made you get wet in the rain?
I didn't think like that at all.
Then get out of the rain and come here.
In the eyes of others, you look pitiful.
And I'm an ex who doesn't want to divorce.
I look like a villain anyway. Don't worry.
What should we do?
The rain doesn't look like it will stop soon.
Excuse me.
Is the security team almost here?
Yes.
- Please speed it up.
- Okay.
Rin, are you okay? You're all wet.
Let me do it.
Please.
I'll turn up the temperature.
Yes. Take Lita back to the office with you.
See you at the office. Okay.
Thanks a lot.
Bro. Why did you do that?
Wasn't it a bit awful?
Rin was also standing in the rain.
No need to go that far even if you're already broken up.
Hey.
Even if I chose to pick up Rin,
she would have ignored me and went back inside herself.
So what?
So you chose to walk over to Lita.
Why?
Because she looks more pitiful than Rin? Really?
Why do you make people hate you?
Maybe doing this might be good.
I behave like a swine.
So everyone won't hesitate to hate me.
You made one mistake.
But will you destroy the rest of your life?
That one mistake...
It was the biggest mistake ever.
I can't get anything back.
I was once...
I was once a happy man.
But when I did wrong that time...
I was left with nothing.
[You were in the rain. Don't forget to take medicine.]
[You'll fall sick.]
[Pak]
[Lita]
Lita, what's the matter?
P'Pak, are you okay?
I saw that you've read the message, but you didn't text back.
Oh, I'm about to take a shower.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
I probably stood in the rain for too long.
But I have already taken medicine.
You...
Take care of yourself, too.
See you tomorrow.
Yes.
[The Legend]
I'd like to ask for information on the VVIP customers
that your team used to take care of.
I have the official permission letter.
That's the information I prepared for the VIP Team's celebration event.
But you won't use it anymore, right?
All those customers must be transferred to my team.
It's necessary for me.
Otherwise, I can't continue to work.
Anyway... I'll leave it to you.
Thank you.
So what now, Rin?
[The Legend: Request permission to use all information and contacts of VVIP customers]
[Dear Mrs. Rinnara Yamonkan, VIP Director]
So what will we do next?
If they want it, I'll hand it in myself.
Are these the documents I asked for?
Why are they paper documents? I thought it would be in digital file format.
That's the VIP Team's work.
We've already analyzed and organized it.
If the Privilege Team wants information,
work it out yourself from the raw data.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Rin must be taking revenge on me.
That's why she's doing this.
No.
Rin is not that kind of person.
She doesn't care about me.
She cares about her work.
[The Legend]
Lita.
It's late now. Go home and rest.
It's okay.
I won't lose to Rin.
Others will see I can do the same.
You, too.
You will see that...
I can be as good as Rin.
We've been working so hard to help the company earn money.
But in the end, it's like we're useless.
When I first came here, I thought of this place as family.
What about now?
It's...
The family of Cinderella.
What? Isn't it funny?
- Just eat.
- Yes.
Wait, Rin.
I have something important to discuss with you.
But I have nothing to say to you.
I have a solution to ensure the VIP Team's survival.
You know that Jak wants to harass the VIP Team.
He even wants to disband the VIP Team.
What do you want me to do?
Should I apologize to him and ask for his sympathy?
No, I won't let you do that.
I want you to work for someone who sees your value,
a person who really wants you.
It's Ms. Treenate.
If you work with her,
she will make the VIP Team stronger,
strong enough to fight against Jakchai.
But if I do that...
your team might lose.
I suggest you do this, but it doesn't mean I'm surrendering.
I want us two to have a fair fight,
an honest competition.
Because...
you have been treated unfairly for far too long.
I need some time to consider.
[The Legend]
[Disaya]
[VIP]
Hi, Mon. You're here, too.
Hi.
It's just so-so.
We should go to the room over there. Rin is there.
Okay. Let's go.
Madam Mon.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Are you here because it's my event?
Do you see me as such a kind woman?
Well, I'd rather celebrate with the VIP Team.
I was in the other room just now and almost fell asleep.
I heard you arranged a designer to measure and customize outfits here.
Yes.
At the lounge inside.
[Fundao]
But if you want the whole collection as before, it will take a little time.
It's okay. Do you serve wine here?
Yes.
Then let's chit chat inside. Let's go.
This way, please.
[Fundao]
[The Legend]
The launch event of the Privilege Team yesterday...
achieved ฿7 million ($198,000) in sales.
Good job.
But the celebration event of the VIP Team
made ฿28 million ($792,000) in sales.
Oops (Sorry).
They are better.
Congratulations, Rin.
This is a good start for the position of VIP Director, Dad.
Thank you.
I have an excellent team.
But for the first task of the Privilege Team, this is still considered decent.
Have you seen the reports of previous years?
Well?
When the VIP Team was launched,
they outperformed the Privilege Team by three times more.
That's because Pakawat was still in the VIP Team then.
If it was really due to Pakawat,
the Privilege Team should have done better.
You can say whatever you want.
Both teams are under my supervision anyway.
I have something to tell everyone.
I think managing two teams is too hard for you.
From now on, you will manage only the Privilege Team.
The one to supervise the VIP Team instead of you...
will be Nate.
Why did you let Nate manage the VIP Team instead of me?
Normally, you never intervene in work at this level.
Or did someone urge you to do this?
Nate always thought I didn't love my children equally.
So I will let you two manage those great teams
and compete to see which one does better.
Thank you, Dad,
for giving me an opportunity to prove myself.
I didn't give an opportunity to Nate alone; I'm giving you a chance, too.
Whoever does the next project better will be the president of The Legend.
[VIP Management Team]
If it were another team, they would need time to adjust to the work system.
But the VIP Team...
is talented and consistently performs well.
Please take care of me.
We need to seek advice from an expert like you.
If we need to improve anything, please tell us.
I have to thank you.
If you hadn't accepted me,
I wouldn't have dared to ask my father to let me lead this team.
And from now on,
the VIP Team and Privilege Team...
are no longer competitors.
We're enemies.
In this competition...
we must only win.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm very uncomfortable right now.
Would you mind if I let loose?
We're on the same team now. Don't be awkward anymore.
Thank you.
Lita.
P'Pak.
I'm really not good.
I felt that I tried my best.
But no matter how much I try, I always lose to P'Rin.
And now Aunt Nate is supporting her team, too.
How can I compete with her now?
Hey. Don't think too much.
This is the first time you've taken on this task.
Mr. Jakchai also said you've started well.
I promise you that, from now on...
No matter how difficult the task is,
no matter what we encounter,
we will get through it together.
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
That's right, Lita.
I believe you can do it.
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
Ji is calling.
Yes, Ji.
Where are you now? Hurry.
Didn't you say you wanted to try Chef Keller's dish?
Okay, turn left.
Do you want to go over there together?
You go.
Won't you go there with me?
Don't you feel lonely here?
I'm fine.
I'll take care of the customers here.
Go ahead.
If you change your mind, meet me there.
See you.
P'Rin.
Saint. What are you doing here?
Did you come for the view?
No.
I saw you walking up here so I followed you,
in case you get locked out again.
Didn't they get it fixed that day?
It shouldn't break anymore.
So why are you here?
Did you not have a good time downstairs?
At first...
I thought... I would be thrilled...
if I really won.
But when that moment came,
I felt nothing.
I was a little sad, actually.
It's because your feelings are still stuck on the rooftop.
We can't lock ourselves on the roof forever.
One day we have to let it go.
Therefore,
let go now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're doing so well these days.
You taught me yourself.
P'Rin... Shall we go downstairs?
Let's go.
How far along are you in your pregnancy?
I am six months.
You are the real working woman.
I wish both you and your baby stay healthy and strong.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Meena.
P'Ji was stuck in traffic and got lost, but she's on her way now.
Prae.
I think I'll resign.
Is something making you uncomfortable?
Or is the workload too heavy?
No. Hard work is fun.
I like it a lot. I'm very happy when I work.
But cooking for my children,
taking care of my children and Jomphol
make me happy too.
Could it be the mood swings during pregnancy?
Did Jomphol pressure you again?
He wouldn't dare to put pressure on me.
He completely understands me and gives me everything.
I want to work. He agrees with it and doesn't stop me.
And he didn't push me to take maternity leave.
It's up to you.
At least it is your choice.
No one is forcing you.
Choose what makes you the happiest.
[The Legend]
Ms. Treenate called early to see Rin. Is anything wrong?
I don't know, either.
[Black Diamond: Invitation to join the auction for art, antiques, decorations and fabrics for special VIPs]
We must win this time.
Yes, Sir.
- Rin.
How was it?
What kind of project did Mr. Jak and Ms. Nate call you about?
And why did they call both you and P'Pak?
Because we have to work with the Privilege Team for this project.
The project's name is... Black Diamond.
It is a project where VVIP and VIP customers will attend the same event.
It's a party,
with an art auction at the event.
For this event, the customers of both our teams
won't be divided for service in tiers like last time.
We will take care of both VVIP and VIP customers.
Right.
So our team has an advantage
because we know our customers better.
Maybe not,
because this project is initiated by Mr. Jakchai.
Therefore, our team will select customers before the VIP Team.
This means if we make our customers spend more, we will win, right?
Correct.
The least event expenses are not the only measure of success in this project.
Whichever team helps customers spend more
will continue to take care of top-spenders for the next five years.
So the winning team will get the highest-tier customers.
The losing team will take care of general customers.
Prepare to disband their team.
We can choose customers first, but we're at a disadvantage anyway, right?
Because the customers who are close to P'Rin and the VIP Team have more spending power.
It's true that Rin's customers and the VIP Team are very close with each other.
But I think we can still persuade several of them to be our customers instead.
We just have to figure out what the customers like, their favorite products,
and find the products for them immediately.
But you have to work harder.
Yes.
Having you by my side is enough for me.
I'll list the potential customers who can be persuaded.
You need to check further on what they want.
Yes.
This is the list of customers that the Privilege Team has chosen.
Splitting in half for each team is fair enough, I think.
You've prepared well.
You know the customers who are close to my team,
whom you can steal from us.
You must be very good at stealing.
I couldn't do something like this alone,
but I have P'Pak with me.
At first, I was very nervous.
But since Pak has guided me in everything,
I feel relieved.
P'Pak is very worried about me,
worried if I work too hard
or get enough sleep.
Even if it's strenuous (tough), I can do it,
because P'Pak is beside me.
P'Pak cares for a lot of people, I see.
What do you mean?
Whom do you think suggested I work for Ms. Treenate?
P'Pak is very worried about me.
He visited my house late at night.
He was afraid that Mr. Jakchai would harass me.
So he recommended I take the VIP Team over to Ms. Treenate.
Although he's not with me,
I'm sure he misses me
more than the girl he works with.
That's not true.
You're lying.
Go ask P'Pak whether it's true.
Yes, Lita.
I myself told Rin to do that.
Why?
Why did you do that?
Even when you know she is our rival team.
You did this since you want her to win?
No, Lita.
But I think both teams...
should compete fairly.
What is "competing fairly"?
Was it really about work?
Isn't it because you worry about Rin?
Right?
Rin and I have been together a long time.
We both...
have been through a lot.
Yes, Lita.
I'm worried for her.
It's just that, right?
Isn't it because you want to go back to her?
Then can you promise me that you won't get back with her?
Can you, Pak?
- Answer me!
- Lita.
Don't force me to say anything.
I don't want to lie.
Don't think about it now.
You should focus on your work.
Don't you care about me at all?
Why can't you do that either?
I did everything. And I gave up everything for you.
Why does it turn out that I matter to you only in work?
[Pak]
Hey.
Since you came home, you've been calling him a million times.
If he doesn't pick up your calls, it means he doesn't care about you anymore.
Don't be pathetic anymore.
No matter how pathetic or pitiful I am in the eyes of others,
I don't care.
The person who has no respect for you... is yourself.
Let me warn you.
Use your brain rather than your naive heart,
and you will see that in this world,
there are guys more suitable for you than Pakawat.
♫ If you want to love her, do not love me. Do you understand? ♫
♫ Go and be with anyone you want. You don't have to care about me ♫
♫ Because I will never share my lover with anyone ♫
♫ Please understand again ♫
♫ If you're still a cheater, then there will be no "us" ♫
🌟[VIP Thailand]🖤