[Dimsum.Asia Ver] E16 Princess Silver
-♥ Hafiz Adam ♥-
http://twitter.com/hafizadam
Episode 16
When are you going to let me go?
We will each take a step back.
Forget about all the unpleasant past.
Okay?
I don't care if you lied
about your identity.
I don't care if you
approached me with motives.
I don't care what happened
between you and Fu Chou.
I can leave those in the past.
Man Yao.
What's done is done.
Blaming and loathing each other...
is completely meaningless.
I promised you.
Your future is my future too.
Future?
There is no future between us.
I do want to marry you.
I also believe...
it doesn't matter if
that book was a fake,
when you handed it to me,
you were hoping I can
keep it safe, right?
What does it matter?
Fu Chou and I completed the ceremony.
Speaking about this
won't make a difference.
I will find a way to get
the dissolution letter.
You are the Emperor's favourite son.
But you are not all mighty.
No,
you have to trust me.
I can't trust you anymore.
In mere days,
I was deceived again and again.
Since we can no longer
trust each other,
what is the point of staying together?
Let it go.
This day is destined to come
since the day you turned me down.
We have different
backgrounds and stands.
We may have felt love,
but we were never
honest to one another.
We should just let go.
Let us become strangers.
It's better than a life of
distrust and pain.
Is that what you want?
This is my wish.
Please, grant me this last wish.
Do you think Fu Chou
will truly love you?
That is not your concern.
Have you ever loved me?
If you did,
how much did you love me?
I have one final request.
Keep me company for
another three days.
I, Zongzheng Wu You,
will give you all of me.
I will never give up on you.
I won't let the world down,
or you.
It's been three days.
The door is opening.
What is going on?
Where are they?
No one came out.
She is coming out.
She came out dressed in that?
What happened in the last three days?
Brother.
Your Majesty.
It really is you.
You are Princess Rong Le.
Yes.
During the feast,
both you and the Emperor
of Western Qi were there.
You allowed the fake Princess
to choose her husband.
What exactly are you planning?
You are supposed to marry my son.
You should have stayed
inside the manor.
But you spread your lies everywhere
and seduced Prince Li.
You beguiled General Fu.
You tried to alienate
my two most important officers!
You caused disruption
to the Imperial Court.
This is outrageous!
-Guards!
-Yes.
Arrest her and lock her up.
-She will be put on trial!
-Your Majesty.
-General Fu.
Do you want to plea for her?
She brought shame to you!
You will be humiliated
for your whole life!
You should be hating her!
Your Majesty.
For the time being,
while we just signed the treaty
with Western Qi,
imprisoning the Princess of Western Qi
might cause an uproar.
It might not bode well for us.
Which is why I suggest...
Your Majesty to calm down
for the sake of greater good.
Father.
All of these happened because Wu You
turned down the engagement...
and took the bride.
General Fu shouldn't be blamed.
Silence!
What happened today...
is brought on us
because she wants revenge.
-Your Majesty.
-My decision is certain.
Say no more.
-Lock her up.
-Yes.
Let her go!
-Let her go.
-Let her go?
Thanks to her insolence,
we are all placed in this predicament!
What happened back there
was my doing alone.
The others are innocent.
But she lied about her identity
to approach you.
She lied to approach me...
to fulfil the six-month agreement
we made in the main hall.
But she has chosen another man.
I gave her the right of choice.
Wu You.
Please, Your Majesty.
Let my mother rest in peace.
Since Prince Li plead for you,
this shall be the end of this matter.
From now on, no one
shall mention this again.
Is that clear?
Yes.
Your Majesty, I will
leave with my wife now.
Brother!
Ling Yue.
Help the Princess change
into these clothes.
Yes.
This should have been done
three days ago,
but the wedlock drink is still needed.
After all, this is part
of the wedding.
With this done,
it will be good omen for us both.
The meaning behind wedlock drink...
is for the husband
and wife to live as one,
they will never be separated.
I know you understand well enough...
the two of us will never become
a real married couple.
Which is why this drink...
is simply meaningless.
I need to have a word with my wife.
You may go now.
Yes.
Your Highness, I'll be right there.
I'll be standing by.
It must be hard to
put up an act all day.
There is no need for acting
while we are here.
I brought shame to you.
You must have hated me for it.
Why would you pretend nothing
has ever happened?
Nothing happened between you
and Prince Li in the tomb.
The Yun's Tomb is the resting place
for Lady Yun, Prince Li's mother.
No matter how vile he can be,
he would never do anything
to disrespect you...
inside his mother's tomb.
You know him well.
You like him a lot.
He brought you into his mother's tomb
for three whole days.
He seems to be deeply
in love with you.
This conversation we are having,
don't you think it's strange?
I can forget what
you two did together.
I care not about what the others say.
Reputation is just show
for the strangers.
Besides,
everyone can be a topic for gossips.
But there is something
you must remember.
From now on,
you are the wife of General Fu
of Northern Realm.
No matter how much you like someone,
you must tell no one.
Did you forget?
This marriage is just a deal
you brokered with Western Qi.
Whatever the motive is,
a marriage is no child's play.
Since you are married to me,
from now on, each and every
action of yours...
no matter how humiliating
it is to me,
must not be humiliating to you.
What do you mean?
You saw it at the tomb today.
I may be the General of Defence,
I may have achieved
great feats for this nation,
but at the most crucial moments,
Prince Li's words
weigh more than mine.
I do want to protect you and save you,
but I cannot do it all the time.
Even under such circumstance,
I will do my best to keep you safe.
You might not even believe this,
but when I married you,
it's not just because
you are the Princess of Qi.
When we first met,
you could understand the song I wrote.
At that moment,
I feel like you are the
only person in this world...
that understands
the shackles in my heart.
After all this time, I am used
to giving up and sacrifices.
But for once,
there is something that I want.
I am flattered, General Fu.
Those are just some
nonsense I told that day.
How could I possibly
understand your thoughts?
That will never be a reality.
It's not that you couldn't,
it's just that you won't.
Rong Le.
You see me as an enemy.
That's only because...
we planned your future without
asking for your thoughts.
You felt like you are tricked...
and disrespected.
Isn't that true?
You and my brother were
planning this for years.
You knew who I am and you
pretend like you know nothing.
I played right into your hands.
I hope you take my words for it.
I will treat you well.
Treat me well?
Then you should get a divorce.
-Not now.
-When?
A year later.
A year? The same excuse again.
Who knows what kind of scheme
you and my brother will have?
I don't wish to achieve anything.
I simply want...
to have a chance at you.
A year-long plan
and you claim it's for me?
If this were six months ago,
I might have bought it.
But when you said it just now,
it's simply felt ridiculous.
It doesn't matter whether
you believe me or not.
All I want to know...
is what you need.
I hereby give you my word.
I will respect your decision.
I won't demand anything unacceptable.
Not until...
you are willing to
become my real wife.
That day will never come.
If a year has passed...
and you still refuse to accept me,
I will end this marriage.
You will be freed.
You have my word for it.
Rest well.
When did you find out she is
the Princess of Western Qi?
I only found out on
the day of their wedding.
You spent so much time with her
and you didn't notice it?
And you said you are
good with riddles.
Why didn't you see this coming?
It was all your fault.
You always said the sight of
her terrifies you.
I wouldn't dare to
get any closer to her.
She was so nice to me.
Whatever the reason is,
I shouldn't suspect her.
Look at how it ends.
The Princess you like
broke my brother's heart.
I don't even know who
I should side with now.
Right now,
Brother Wu You must be very upset.
He locked himself up
in the tomb for days.
I wonder how he is holding up.
Why don't we pay him a visit?
Don't talk to him about
the Princess or Miss Man Yao.
Tell him about the recent good news.
Try to cheer him up.
Prince Chen.
Captain Xiang, how may I help you?
Your Highness, someone made
a report that a few days ago,
you allowed your men to commit
heinous crime to search for a girl.
A dozen of lives were lost.
His Majesty is now furious.
I am sent here to bring you in
for investigation.
How is this possible?
Wu Yu is afraid of everything,
he would never do that.
I need to inform Brother Wu You.
It's fine, calm down.
I know the Supreme Court well enough.
It'll be okay.
They just have some questions.
My father will never wrong me.
As for you, stay here and wait for me.
Remember, do not bother
Wu You with this.
Okay, it's all right.
I am going now.
If a year has passed...
and you still refuse to accept me,
I will end this marriage.
You will be freed.
You have my word for it.
Princess?
Princess, what's wrong?
You can let it all out if you want.
Brother Wu You!
Bad news!
Wu Yu is...
Brother Wu You.
Look at yourself.
Lady Yun won't rest in peace
if she sees you like this.
Pull yourself together!
Wu Yu needs you to save him.
While you were searching
for Man Yao on the street,
Wu Yu's men turned on him.
Someone made a report saying
that he led his men in heinous crimes.
A dozen of lives were lost.
Wu Yu is now arrested
by the Royal Guards.
Brother Wu You, you must save him.
Brother Wu You?
Let's go.
At your service, Your Majesty.
You finally decided to come out.
Look at what you have become.
I have heard about
Prince Chen's arrest.
I gave the order to
search for the girl.
Prince Chen was just following order.
The men caused troubles.
Whatever the reasons are,
they are still my men.
Prince Chen is innocent.
Take a good look at this!
More than ten people were killed!
You wreaked havoc to the city
for one peasant girl!
And you made it sound so lightly...
and admit it without hesitation.
I bet you think I won't punish you.
Isn't that right?
For the commotion my men caused,
I will take full responsibility.
I will see to it that...
all the involved families
are relocated.
You...
Your Majesty.
The real culprit is yet to be found.
We don't know the truth for sure.
Even if Prince Li made
an error in his line of duty,
he takes the initiative
help the victims' families.
That calls for consideration
for leniency.
Never mind.
I, Zongzheng Wu You,
will give up all my titles
and be exiled.
Together with Wu Yu,
I hand in my resignation.
Since you are determined
to leave the capital,
you will have my permission.
Your title as the prince is removed.
With the name as son of the Emperor,
you will be sent to the south
to manage the land there.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty loves Prince Li deeply...
and can't bear to see Prince Li and
Prince Chen suffer.
But lives were lost.
It's not something that
can be made up with titles.
Your Majesty, how do we
explain this to the people?
The Princes broke the law.
They must be punished
like other citizens.
Sir Yang.
His Highness saw you
as his right-hand man.
How could you turn your back on him?
Sir Yang has compassion
for the people.
You obey the laws to your heart.
I respect that.
In that case,
Prince Li won't receive
a death sentence.
But he must be punished.
Fifty beatings to him.
Go on.
Your Majesty.
The campaign against Wei
will be launched soon.
Managing both the nation's and
military affairs might be too tiring.
Your Majesty once ordered Prince Li
to aid you in the affairs.
Now that Prince Li is stripped
of his ranks and titles,
and there are much works to be done,
I wonder which of the princes...
will be able to aid Your Majesty?
The other princes are still too young.
They are not interested
in national affairs.
-And the Crown Prince is...
-Your Majesty.
I understand Your Majesty's concern.
However,
the Crown Prince is
still under house arrest.
He had his time to reflect.
From now on,
he is freed from the house arrest.
He must return and assist me.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
I have a request to make.
Officer Sun, what is it?
The autumn is upon us,
the weather has gone cold.
My health is not as well
as it should be.
I am too old for the work too.
I am willing to follow Prince Li
to the south and assist him...
and at the same time return
to Qingzhou for retirement.
You are willing to assist Wu You.
I am grateful for that.
Permission granted.
I appreciate the consideration.
General Fu.
His Majesty gave the order.
I must go to the royal study
for discussion.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
General Fu, likewise.
I thank you for the help.
I have both the lady and power
that I wanted.
That mere peasant that has nothing....
has no mean to cause us any troubles.
This city is finally rid of
that cursed Zongzheng Wu You.
The Northern Realm...
will be mine!
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Your goal is realised.
Xiang, come over here.
What do you need?
I will give it to you.
How about the title of
Fair Consort of Crown Prince?
Your Highness, I am just a commoner.
I have no place in the palace.
I dare not ask for any title.
I don't want to cause you any trouble.
What do you want then?
You can let me know.
My birthday...
is two weeks from now.
Will Your Highness invite some
of those officers you are close to?
Why would you want to invite them?
I may not have a title,
but I want the world to know that...
I am already yours.
Even if I am a present
from General Fu,
when I see him again,
I don't wish him to see me
as a mere songstress.
I want to be...
Your Highness' treasure.
Good.
You have my word.
You will live a decent life.
No one will ever look down
on you again.
What is going on? I don't know.
Hurry up.
Father, are we leaving for
somewhere far away?
Yes, we are going back to Qingzhou.
We will probably stay there
for some time.
Come on.
Is this part of your work
in the Imperial Court?
-You may go now.
-Yes.
You need not worry.
This is a good news.
I requested to be sent there.
Father, are you retiring from
your career as an officer?
You are returning to
our hometown for retirement?
Congratulations, Father.
Why didn't you think about your life?
By good news...
I actually meant your marriage.
Please, don't make fun of me.
I would never arrange
your marriage lightly.
I remember the
fortune teller once said...
you are destined to
live like a phoenix.
You stand out in the crowd.
The husband I am picking for you...
is none other than Prince Li.
He is the man above all.
The prideful son of heaven.
Father, the engagement of
Prince Li and Princess Rong Le...
made a great wave
throughout the land.
I may be living in the inner manor,
but I have heard about it too.
-Come on.
-Father!
You need not be worried about
Prince Li's future.
He was only acting on impulse
with the engagement.
He won't make the same mistake again.
I could tell earlier that
His Majesty is still...
not impressed by the
Crown Prince's behaviour.
His Majesty punished Prince Li
as a reminder.
It's for his own good.
Prince Li will go on an
ordeal in the south.
Soon enough,
His Majesty will find an excuse
to summon him back here.
Father, I am worried that...
Prince Li is already
in love with someone.
He will never marry me.
It doesn't matter.
He requested to be
exiled in the south.
It means he wants to severe the past.
With influence of Sun family
in Qingzhou,
and the time you will
be spending with him,
you are almost certain
to become his consort.
Father.
I don't want it.
This is more than just
about your marriage,
it also concerns the
honour of Sun family.
Yu Shi Hai placed the wrong bet.
His family failed after
three generations.
I don't want to witness
the Sun family fail in my hands.
Get up. As the daughter of Sun family,
this is the only time
you can forget yourself.
Sixteen years ago,
His Highness lost the protection
from his mother's family.
I took the risk of being killed
like Qin Yong and became his teacher.
It was an wager.
What if he does become the Emperor?
He will repay us with
a thousand times more.
Once you married him,
you can use your family name
to gain his trust.
This isn't hard on you.
Send this to Qingzhou.
When they see this,
they will know what to do.
Prince Li, Zongzheng Wu You,
is exiled to the south.
Naturally,
we need to prepare a warm welcome.
Yes, consider it done.
How are the matters in the manor?
Everything is set for the Princess.
My men are keeping watch on her.
She keep herself in
the Tranquil Garden.
She won't find out about anything.
Take good care of her.
General, Central Secretary Sun
sent a letter for you.
-Dismiss.
-Yes.
Sun Ji Zhou.
Isn't he leaving for Qingzhou?
I never got the chance for proper
farewell since we met in the south.
It's time for my leaving again.
This is urgent.
Can we meet in the
Flying Swan Tavern?
If this is about something urgent,
he should be inviting me
to his manor instead.
Why would he want to meet
in a place with crowd?
Something is at miss.
Maybe it's best to turn him down.
No bother.
I want to see just what...
Sun Ji Zhou is up to this time.
Miss Sun?
I hope you are not offended.
I invited you here in
the name of my father.
I was being presumptuous.
I apologise for that.
Please, come in.
Why do you invite me here, Miss Sun?
If this is something
within my capability,
I am willing to give you a hand.
Please have a seat and hear me out.
Please.
I have been thinking about this.
I had to ask for your help.
Thank you.
I don't want to follow
my father to Qingzhou.
I wish to stay by your side.
What you said...
is not something I would
draw any conclusion on.
I have been admiring you
for a long time.
Ever since we met in the south,
I have been having dreams...
about how astounding you are.
You must have had too much drinks.
It's the wine talking.
Let's pretend I didn't hear a word.
No, my mind is clear as day.
I may have been raised
in the inner manor,
but I have great respect
for the heroes.
Since the moment I saw you,
I wait for a day when
my dreams come true.
All I ever do...
was to look at you from distance.
Every month, I will sew one
of these fragrance pouch.
I could only hide my thoughts...
inside these needle works.
-Miss Sun.
-Please, hear me out.
I am afraid if I don't speak now,
I could never muster
the courage again.