" Princess Silver "
Episode 43
I have to leave
Zhongshan for some time.
There is something...
that I should have done
a long time ago.
Your Highness,
you can't take the risk.
Send a double to stay in here for me.
Yes, Your Highness.
Kneel.
Sir Sun, what is the meaning of this?
Lady Rong Le,
Prince Li spent the night with Ya Li.
She couldn't inform you in time.
So, she is here to apologise.
You knew this too?
Princess, Ke told me about this.
This way, please.
I thought you never
want to see me again.
I thought...
even if I sent my men to get you,
you would refuse to come.
Your Highness asks for me,
I wouldn't dare to turn you down.
Your father was there,
you couldn't say anything.
Now that no one is holding you back,
will you tell me the truth now?
No one was holding me back.
Ya Li.
Even until now,
you still wouldn't tell me
what really happened?
That is what happened.
Prince Li and I slept together.
You can stop lying to yourself now.
I love Prince Li.
He has feelings for me too.
Lady Rong Le, you should
give us your blessing.
You once told me...
that you see me as your
best friend and soulmate.
You want me to have a happy life.
I found my happiness.
But you can't accept the truth.
Ya Li.
I remember telling you...
life may be hard,
but we can all be the masters
of our own destiny.
Master of my destiny?
Each and every step
I take right now...
is the choice of my own.
No one is coercing me.
But your attitude towards me...
is pushing me to desperation.
I am the daughter of Sun family.
For a noble family like mine,
name and reputation...
come before everything.
Since you are betting on
the name of your family,
I have nothing more to say to you.
You and your father...
shall wait for Wu You's decision.
If you can be part of this house,
I will gladly leave this place.
However,
you should watch yourself.
You agreed?
If Prince Li agrees,
you won't stop me from
staying with him?
Ling Yue.
See the guest off.
Yes.
Miss Sun, this way please.
Princess,
I think...
if we love someone,
as long as they are happy,
we will feel happy as well.
I think...
if Prince Li does love Miss Sun,
when he is happy,
you will be happy as well.
Why don't you try to accept her?
It's up to her luck.
This is the allocation of fund
for victims of earthquake in Zhuo.
Is there any objection?
I heard Your Highness
spent the night...
with Miss Ya Li, the daughter of
Governor of Qingzhou.
Sir Cai.
This is His Highness' personal affair.
How could you bring it
up in the court?
That would stain my daughter's honour.
Miss Sun has exceptional
morals and benevolence.
She is the best lady
to be the consort.
Best lady we have?
There can only be one consort.
No other women deserves my brother!
Your Highness, a single woman
cannot have power over the harem.
And she hasn't bear any child
even after a year.
If this goes on, the people
might take this wrongly.
There are rumours that...
the woman is actually the wife of
Northern Realm's Prince Regent.
She doesn't come clean.
She might even be the spy
Fu Chou planted here.
And now she is interfering
with national affair...
and causing disorder.
We all know she has vile intention.
This is unacceptable!
-This is all nonsense!
-Wu Yu.
Sir Cai, do you mind enlighten me...
of what action I should take?
Your Highness.
My daughter showed you her love.
She has the duty
to bring your child...
and continue the bloodline.
He is right.
Sir Sun, you are using the
innocence of your daughter...
to blackmail me
in front of the officers.
This might not sound
humiliating to you,
but have you ever considered
how Ya Li might feel?
Leng Yan.
Your Highness, she is here.
Ya Li, what exactly
happened that night?
Tell us what you know.
Ya Li.
Fear not, I will be here
to speak for you.
Allow me to say it for her.
Prince Li and Miss Sun were
never together that night, not at all.
How is this possible?
You little brat, enough
of your insolence here.
Ya Li.
Was Ke telling us the truth just now?
Your Highness,
did you ask me here
to talk about that night?
I have always loved you.
I couldn't help myself...
when you were holding me in your arms.
I don't hope to replace Rong Le.
I just want to be with you.
Ya Li,
are you sure that night in this study,
we had any intimate contact?
If you refuse to accept me
because of Rong Le,
then so be it.
I won't stay here to bother you.
I shall end my life with
my tainted honour.
Seeing that we were childhood friends,
I will give you another chance.
If you want to keep this going,
then I shall show no mercy for you.
Come in!
Your Highness, the men's clothes
look so awful.
The way of manners is complicated.
Miss Ya Li,
did you enjoy the night
you spent with me?
You sneaked out from the infirmary.
So, you were here for your 'training'?
What do you mean with that?
Your Highness, General Luo Zhi...
wishes to know if the tactical layout
you discussed last night...
are already done.
Last night?
I was already at General Luo's house
at the dusk.
We were discussing works.
I came back to the study
to get changed at half past six.
You were already awake.
The guards in this manor
and the soldiers of Luo Army...
are witnesses for my whereabouts.
May I know...
how you and I had such intimate night?
Your Highness, this can't be true.
I may have slept a little too soundly,
-but we clearly had...
-What have you done earlier...
to fall asleep so well?
I am sure you know it better.
What are you afraid of?
You lit some aphrodisiac incense,
I used some of it on you too.
No!
It was Prince Li.
It couldn't be you.
Everyone knows I wasn't
in here that night.
If you insist you had any
intimate time with someone,
we do have many
strong men in the house.
I am afraid...
Your Highness!
I apologise! Please,
do not let me carry this shame!
Otherwise...
I will have no courage
to live in this world anymore.
Miss Ya Li.
If you don't want the others
to know what happened,
you can show this to them.
See? The virginity fleck
is still here.
Miss Ya Li is still a virgin.
It's true.
This is odd.
Please, judge this wisely.
Prince Li and I never
did anything indecent.
Nothing happened between us.
But...
How could a father do that?
Even I know men and women
must keep their distance.
But you are tainting
your daughter's innocence!
This brat is spitting nonsense
and framing me and my daughter.
Is Your Highness not
going to do anything?
You may leave now.
Sir Sun, I once thought
this is the trick...
the consorts use to win
the favour of the Emperor.
I am surprised that
an officer like yourself...
would stoop so low...
to force my brother
into marrying Ya Li.
Right, maybe during the time Miss Sun
spent in the Northern Realm...
she was having an affair
with the Prince Regent.
Perhaps this is why you are in
such a hurry to get her a husband...
and used such lowly trickery.
I don't know what Your Highness
used to coerce my daughter.
Your Highness won't let
my daughter be the consort,
but the Silver-Hair Demon
that shares the bed with you...
should pay for the death of
those fallen soldiers.
Sir Sun,
you are being frustrated
because your plan failed.
You would even blackmail His Highness.
Your Highness must have overlooked
the proposal I submitted.
We think the terror of
Silver-Hair Demon must end.
Aside from the incident at the inn,
I also heard about...
the murder case
in the camp of Luo Army.
The victim was Luo Qiao,
the brother of General Luo Zhi.
How is this possible?
They are based outside the city wall,
everything was fine.
I was informed they are setting out
for the border tomorrow.
If Luo Qiao is dead,
General Luo will be furious
and charge right in here.
He is right.
Your Highness.
The common folks say
the culprit of the murder...
is the Silver-Hair Demon
that lives inside...
Sir Cai.
Lady Rong Le is in the manor,
how does she kill those men?
You have no evidence
and this is your own wild guess.
What you are accusing now are
Prince Li and the whole south.
The truth doesn't matter.
The people want answer.
Answer? This is the answer.
Lady Rong Le is innocent.
Believe whatever you want.
Your Highness.
This is the request from
the people and the officers.
Please, end the scourge of this demon.
I am curious.
How did the people request this?
How did the officers request this?
Your Highness, end the scourge
of this demon for the fallen souls,
bring peace to the people.
Such is their request.
Marry another consort
and continue the bloodline,
bring order to the Imperial Court,
-such is the officers' request.
-Enough.
Man Yao is my wife.
I won't let her get hurt
no matter what the cost.
-Your Highness!
-Sir Sun!
This is where your acting must end.
As for where the murderous
Silver-Hair Demon came from...
and who the murderer is,
I have the answer.
And I believe you know
the truth better than anyone.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, bad news.
The soldiers of northern base
sent to Zhuo...
have returned an hour ago.
They are having a stand-off
with the Luo Army.
What?
Last night, 13 soldiers
of the northern base died.
Someone spread the rumours about
Silver-Hair Demon to the base.
A riot broke out, they claim
Lady Rong Le is the murderer.
They demand Your Highness
to hand over Lady Rong Le...
or they will invade Qingzhou....
and seize the manor.
But...
Your Highness, there is an uproar
among the people and the soldiers,
the nation's order comes first.
Please, take your action
as soon as possible.
With the nation's fate at stake,
Lady Rong Le cannot be the priority,
please consider this matter wisely.
We hope Your Highness
will take action as soon as possible.
If I wanted to save someone...
and kill innocents
without any evidence,
that would truly be a shame
to my name.
The evidence for the murders
by Silver-Hair Demon...
will be presented to you.
As for the justice
the soldiers demand,
I will give them an explanation.
Justice for our brothers,
have over the Demon!
Brothers of the northern base,
if the 13 fallen brothers
that died last night...
know that you believed
the rumours so easily...
and accuse the innocent...
while the real culprit
is still at large,
I doubt they will rest in peace...
and their souls would be disappointed.
My brother Luo Qiao was
killed by the same villain.
You know me well.
If this is truly Lady Rong Le's doing,
I, Luo Zhi,
will not tolerate!
Give our brothers
the justice they deserve!
Soldiers, calm down!
-We want answers!
-Within the next 24 hours,
Prince Li will get the evidence...
and arrest the true killer.
-This is great.
-Good.
You are right.
Fine.
I followed and carried out
Prince Regent's order.
I hope Your Highness can
shield us from the harms.
Letter from the south, all are
in place just as you ordered.
We left no trace behind.
Prince Li lost the trust of soldiers
because of the lies about Demon.
We can soon invade the south.
Sir Sun...
is so capable at carrying out order.
But he is too greedy and selfish,
he will surely falter.
Very wise, Your Majesty.
We asked him to get rid of Luo Qiao...
and he is already making demands
to save his skin.
Fortunately, we have
other spies there...
and killed those 13 soldiers
of the south.
With each death, there is
one more trouble for Prince Li.
There is another matter
I wonder if I should tell you.
His Highness claims to be sick,
but I found out he is actually
not in his room.
Empress Fu.
Your Majesty, His Highness is ill.
He is taking his rest.
Stand down.
Greetings, Empress Fu.
Where is the Prince Regent?
Your Majesty, the Prince Regent is...
He is...
Speak.
He went to the south.
Why would he go to the south?
I don't know, but he left without
packing too many belongings.
I wasn't allowed to follow him.
He wanted me to stay here...
to keep his secret...
as long as possible.
What else can make him
prepare so well just to leave here?
His feathers have grown full.
How dare he keep me in the dark.
Captain Chang, you failed your duty
and cover up his plan.
By the laws of Royal Palace,
you are punished with 40 beatings.
-But...
-Why?
The Prince Regent is away,
and you dare to disrespect me now?
If His Highness comes back...
and learns that all of you
have disrespected me,
I wonder what the punishment...
will be for all of you.
I apologise, Your Majesty.
I mean no disrespect.
I appreciate the lecture.
I will accept the punishment.
The Prince Regent may be away,
but the laws still stand.
From now on,
all matters of the Imperial Court...
must be reported to
Senyan Palace in details.
I shall make the decision.
If I ever find out...
that someone is keeping
secrets from me,
only death sentence awaits.
Yes, Your Majesty's
order is our command.
Uncle, the officers are
making requests while...
there is a mutiny on the other side,
must we to hand over Man Yao
and let her get killed?
You know how much
my brother loves Man Yao.
He will never sacrifice Man Yao
just to appease the uproar.
Since the ancient times, if a
consort affects the people's life,
the ruler must make the hard decision.
As for the murder in northern base,
if Wu You ignores the public outrage
for Lady Rong Le,
he will lose the trust of
the army and the people.
That will bring even
more troubles afterwards.
Look at the veteran officers that
support the reformation.
Even they requested to have
Lady Rong Le punished.
Under these circumstances,
I am afraid not even Wu You
can turn the tide.
Sir Sun didn't hold any
punches for this plan.
It's one scheme after another.
He knew that even if Wu You
finds out what he did,
there will be no evidence.
After all, people are unpredictable.
Rumour will soon become
reality with enough believers.
The man that set up
this plot has stood out.
But I have no idea what
Wu You has in place.
The soldiers of northern base
are in high spirit.
Things might not bode well for him.
I don't know what
my brother's plan is either.
He just told me to stay
and keep things in check...
and keep Man Yao in the dark.
But he brought Sir Sun and Sir Cai
to the northern base.
Princess.
What are you doing here?
Ke.
Did you know about this?
What was inside this vial?
What happened here?
It was...
the Ageing Frost.
General Luo, you promised us
Prince Li will be here.
Where is he now?
You take money from the ruler...
so you won't let justice
is done to our brothers!
We are just common folks
who wish to survive!
If Prince Li fails to hand over
the Silver-Hair Demon,
we will hand in the armours and quit!
Yes!
Hand over the Silver-Hair Demon!
Justice for our brothers!
Prince Li arrives!
Prince Li is here, behave yourselves!
Your Highness, the 13 dead soldiers
died the same way as Luo Qiao.
They were cut at the throat
and died from blood loss.
There are bite marks at their wounds,
but the marks are used
to cover the cut.
The rumours about blood-sucking
is absurd at best.
This is the dagger
Captain Leng gave me.
I examined it,
this is the weapon of the murderer.
Bring her in.
A woman with silver hair.
-Is she the demon?
-She has silver hair.
-Her hair is silver.
-It's her!
Who else can it be?
The dagger was found on this woman.
Is she really the Silver-Hair Demon?
-She is the demon?
-She is the murderer...
that killed my brother!
Get up!
-That is not her hair?
-It was a wig?
-How is it not her?
-This is weird.
-You are right.
-Indeed.
Sir Sun.
Yes.
Come on the stage and have a look.
See if you know this woman.
I do not know her.
Bring in the waiter.
Sir Sun, why do you want
to have me killed?
Who is this guy?
You are too busy to remember him.
Of course you will forget about
the insignificant waiter.
But he does remember you.
You almost got him killed.
A month ago, Sir Sun
came to me in person.
He gave me a lot of money...
to spy on a woman in our shop,
especially one with silver hair.
He wants me to fall down
in front of the woman...
and expose her silver hair.
But I could tell something was off.
Lady Rong Le has silver hair too.
This is absurd.
After some time,
I faltered from this job.
I asked my boss to return
the money to Sir Sun,
I quitted my job and went home.
Then, Sir Sun used a suicide warrior
to replace you...
as the waiter at the inn.
But the bard was caught in action.
Sir Sun doesn't want any loose end,
so, he killed everyone
who knows this plan.
He is resourceful,
he bribed the prison guards
to kill the imprisoned bard.
But you returned home
and escaped his death claw.
I was lucky enough to find you.
Not only did I saved your life,
I even caught this
silver-headed woman!
This is ridiculous!
You can go now.
Yes.
Bring the chest here.
I am sure you recognise
this chest, Sir Sun.
Your house is guarded,
if I hadn't invited you here,
I doubt I can even find this chest.
That bard was spreading
all kinds of lies...
and took controlled of the
renowned Serene Hill Inn.
That inn was in fact
the property of Sun family.
The seal of Sun family
is on this land deed.
You mean the story about
Silver-Hair Demon...
are all lies made by Sir Sun?
There is more.
'I, Fu Chou, thank you for planning
the mutiny in the year of rooster.'
'The five thousand taels of
silver shall fund your rebellion,
the rest can be kept for your family.'
Mutiny in the year of rooster?
The mutiny six years ago...
was connected to the Sun family?
-Right! The refugees' mutiny!
-How is this possible?
'The Zheng family is doomed,
you need not worried, Sir Sun.'
'I have settled everything
in the Court.'
'I will place all the charges
on the Zheng family.'
'Sir Sun, you have nothing
to be worried about.'
'A hundred acres of land is
for you at the eastern outskirts.'
-Silence!
-Sir Sun.
The Zheng family conspired
with the rebels,
they robbed us of the land
with the war.
Are you connected
to the rebels as well?
'If the reformation at
the south is a success,
both the people and army
will become over-powered.'
'The commoners will rise up
against the weakened nobles.'
'I was hoping to marry my daughter
to Zongzheng Wu You...
to secure my status and power.'
'Sir Sun, the people's
belief is the only mean...
to spread rumours about
terrors of Silver-Hair Demon.'
It was Sir Sun's doing?
I am sure you can see the truth now.
All of these letters are marked
with seal of General Fu Chou.
As for where the stories of
Silver-Hair demon comes from,
I am sure all of you
should know by now.
The ledgers of Sun family...
that record years of
land-hoarding through war...
and the reports from people
he suppressed with his ranks...
are all here.
He committed so many crimes!
Sir Sun!
Sir Sun.
We have witnesses and the evidences.
What do you have to say now?
You made up the rumours
about a demon to frame my wife.
That is your first crime.
You hired an assassin to kill
Luo Qiao and 13 other soldiers.
That is your second crime.
You secretly caused
years of disorder...
in order to help Fu Chou
secure a place for you,
your doings caused countless
people to lose their homes.
And because of your own greed,
you tried to beguile the army
and conspire with enemy.
That is your third crime.
These charges alone are enough
to get your wealth confiscated...
and your rank removed.
You will be tried and executed.
Lock him up!
Your Highness.
Even if there is evidence
to prove me guilty,
your wife still cannot
run away from her crimes.
Even if she never killed anyone
for the blood,
she is married to two men.
She disrupts the order of the Court.
The people of Zhongshan
died because of her.
The army is swayed because of her.
Your Highness,
ask your own conscience.
Is it more loathsome
that I hired a killer...
or is it more terrifying that...
the Silver-Hair Demon seduces you
into abandoning your nation?
Take this man to the cell.
Walk!
The demon is sucking His Highness dry!
She kills the trust of the people!
The people needs answers!
The demon must be killed!
Your Highness.
Sir Sun might be absurd,
but Lady Rong Le has silver hair,
it is indeed suspicious.
The people has great fear for her.
They might start to doubt
Your Highness soon.
If Your Highness insists to let
Lady Rong Le go unpunished,
the reformation and campaign
against Fu Chou...
will suffer setbacks!
He is right.
-He is right.
-The efforts will suffer setbacks.
Indeed.
If you wish to pry my resolve,
then I shall gladly
show you my resolve!
Silver hair!
-What is going on?
-How did this happen?
I have silver hair too.
How will you punish me now?
Whatever you wish to do to her,
you must first go through me.
What is this Ageing Frost?
It's a rare poison.
It's effect is violent.
It's not lethal,
but it brings unimaginable pain,
a pain worse than death itself.
How love and hatred
fool the people.
Time is passing and
your lover is waiting for you.
I'm lost in thought,
thinking about my lonely fate.
The world is warm
but sincerity is easily gone.
Any who takes this poison...
will suffer a reversal in blood flow.
The pain is worse than being
pierced by volleys and smashed organs.
It will turn the hair silver...
in just one night.
Ten years of life will be taken.
The wind blows across my cheeks,
sending him away.
Your words of affection
had me believe you.
Who said that
the world is flourishing?
There are greed and jealousy and
people's hearts are unpredictable.
You'll get nothing even if you can
find out about the truth.
I just hope that at least
one of us can turn Gray.
How love and hatred fool the people.
Time is passing and
your lover is waiting for you.
I'm lost in thought,
thinking about my lonely fate.
The world is warm
but sincerity is easily gone.
How love and hatred fool the people.
Time is passing and
your lover is hurting.
It's inevitable that we part but
I just wish that it won't be so cruel.
After the harsh winter,
comes spring again.
What if she is a woman?
What if she has silver hair?
The people believe in me,
not because of my look,
but for where my heart lies.
Lady Rong Le stood by me
all this time.
She helped planning
the reformation effort...
and improved the life many.
But to avoid any attention,
she never asked for credits.
She never told you...
that half of the south is thriving
because of her.
That is the Imperial Seal!
The Imperial Seal left
by the late emperor!
-You are right!
-It's the Imperial Seal.
My father gave her the Imperial Seal
before passing on.
In order to protect the Imperial Seal,
she put her life at risk...
so it will not fall into the hands
of the villains...
but in the hands of
its rightful owner.
She understands my vision.
She supports my loyalty to my father.
She understands my ambition
to unify the land.
I did not crown myself the emperor...
and kept the Imperial Seal a secret.
She carries out her duty with honour.
Yet she never took
credits for anything.
From now on, we will both
carry silver hair...
and move forward as one.
She will be my only wife.
She will be my only consort...
in the whole south.
Long Live the Consort!
You may go now.
Ya Li.
Did Prince Li mention
how he will punish you?
He didn't say anything.
He did nothing either.
It's just as I expected.
Because of old times' sake,
he won't hurt you.
What old times' sake?
He and I never shared
any old times' sake.
All he has is the newly found hate.