[Dimsum.Asia Ver] E33 Princess Silver
-♥ Hafiz Adam ♥-
http://twitter.com/hafizadam
Episode 33
You are still going to
launch the mutiny?
What's done is done.
Yet, I am still asking
this foolish question.
How silly can I be?
I don't even know...
if your resolve is real...
or simply a lie.
Truth or lie,
you never cared.
All you will ever do
when you started suspect me...
is to tell Zongzheng Wu You
about everything.
Or you would risk your own life
and report to the main camp.
Do you really think...
everything I do is wrong?
Have you ever thought about...
why I made those decision?
I know it all.
You are the son of Empress Fu Yuan.
A man disguised as you and had
conversation with His majesty.
I know that too.
Did you hear that...
the so-called Emperor
that is my father...
never sees me as his son?
Whether you believe it or not,
his is still your father.
This is a fact that
can never be changed.
Fu Chou.
Stop your plan.
Do not let your hands be stained
with the blood of your kins.
Kins?
What about your brother Rong Qi?
Do you see him as your kin?
He used you...
and that brought you great pain.
The so-called Emperor
that is my father...
hunted me down
for five whole years.
The warmth of a family...
was turned into a cold blade
that slaughters.
You want me to stop?
Do you even know...
how desperate I was back then?
I simply feel like...
there is no need to
have the innocents killed.
You asked me if I see
my brother as a family.
Yes.
He used me for his bidding
and hurt the people I love.
But I cannot use others' lives
to have my revenge.
It will make me the same
villain as he is.
The soldiers should be the
nation's strongest defence.
But your revenge will
make the river flow with blood.
How can you be at peace with that?
And in the end,
you will be killing your
own father and brothers.
Even if you won,
what can you possibly get from that
empty and cold throne?
Whatever I get in the end...
is still better than having
nothing at all.
He is not my brother.
The Emperor is not my father!
I had nothing to begin with.
What could possibly be worse for me?
Your Majesty.
Wu You.
Wu You, come down here.
You can't be so rude.
-Mother.
-Wu You.
Come.
Look at yourself,
you are sweating so hard.
-Your Majesty.
-Father.
Wu You is such a nice kid.
Isn't that right?
Wu You, go on and
play with your mother.
Okay.
You should have some rest.
Who is it?
Xiao Sha?
Father!
I have failed you!
If I were at your side,
you wouldn't have been killed
by those scoundrels!
Father!
Crown Prince.
May you mourn in peace.
Crown Prince, please mourn in peace.
Here.
His Majesty has passed away.
This is the loss of our nation.
But the campaign must
go on as planned.
Now, we must deal with traitors
and the enemies.
I suggest...
we leave the coffin at the side hall
and keep it a secret.
Relocate a few troops to create
a distraction at the border.
After the rebels are dealt with,
we will hold a state funeral
for His Majesty.
Sure.
We'll proceed with your plan.
Father!
Leng Yan, with our marching speed,
when will we arrive in Zhongshan?
Your Highness, there is
three days of journey ahead.
Take him down!
I was ordered by Princess Rong Le
to send this to Prince Li.
It seems like the whole Zhongshan
is now under Fu Chou's control.
Even the Royal Army
is doing his bidding.
With Fu Chou's mind,
he won't let someone else
take the command.
If my guess is right,
Fu Chou never followed
my father on the campaign.
He has been hiding in the capital...
to deploy his soldiers.
The campaign was led by His Majesty.
How did he pull this off?
When Zhao Yun was
attacked at the inn,
he ordered someone
to disguise as Man Yao.
He is using the same trick again.
He had an imposter
go on the march in his place.
His Majesty would never
expect Fu Chou...
to use such a lowly
and cunning mean.
Your Highness, if General Fu
is so treacherous,
and this man is his
personal bodyguard,
we cannot trust him even
with the Inked-Jade Fan.
-This might be his plan all along.
-You...
If you don't trust me,
give me back the tactical map.
Man Yao will give up her own life...
before this plan...
and the Inked-Jade Fan
are taken by someone else.
I believe in her.
So, I trust you.
Send out the order.
We will travel in day
and night to Zhongshan.
Leng Yan, you will lead
a troop of elites...
and go to our main force.
Make sure His Majesty is safe.
-Also...
-I understand.
Your Highness can count on me.
Can you still walk?
I am fine.
I hope all will go well
for Lady Rong Le.
Man Yao.
Have you met with my father?
As of now,
are you safe?
-Your Highness.
-At ease.
Thank you, Prince Li.
If Man Yao is willing
to give you the fan,
it means she places her trust in you.
Lady Rong Le saved my life.
My life...
is hers to command.
Fu Chou knows you betrayed him.
That's why he hunted you down.
He only knows I betrayed the Creed.
But he didn't know about
the letter I sent you.
The Creed is tracking Lady Rong Le.
It was an accident that they found me.
So, Fu Chou knew it all along...
that Man Yao found out
about his plan.
If Man Yao is still at the main camp,
and if she didn't get to
inform my father...
and was found by Fu Chou's men,
it will not...
Your Highness!
Did something happen
at the main camp?
Your Highness.
I investigated and
ask around the camp.
His Majesty was assassinated
in the main camp.
His Majesty passed away.
My condolences, Your Highness.
Our condolences, Your Highness.
Who was the killer?
After Fu Chou transported the body
back to the capital,
he framed Your Highness
in front of the officers,
claiming that you are planning
to seize the throne,
which is why you went to the camp
and killed His Majesty.
Fu Chou.
The Imperial Court is
under his control.
The Crown Prince has ordered us
not to say a word about His Majesty.
Once you entered the city,
they have order to kill you on sight.
Prince Chen is under house arrest too.
Your Highness, you must turn
the tide at the capital.
Bring justice to the villains.
Bring justice to the villains!
Your Highness, I found this...
at the location where
the main camp was.
It looks like His Majesty's
handwriting.
Yun, I am advancing with the army.
I could feel the ambition
is beyond my reach.
I couldn't fall asleep.
Sometimes, I wish to
forget all of it and join you.
But Wu You is still young.
I wish to hold on for him
for a couple of years.
As you know,
once a man sits on the throne,
he will lose all that was
once dear to him.
When the time comes,
choice would be a luxury.
Yun.
While I was on the march
with the army,
I kept thinking about the time
when Wu You was a kid.
Back then, he wanted to
learn how to ride a horse.
But I was so afraid
he would fall from it.
So, I let him ride on my back.
Back in the days,
I let him ride on me.
But I am too old now.
I even have to pass the duty...
onto his shoulder.
Father.
You promised me you will
bring peace to the world for me.
Why are you leaving me behind?
Father.
Have you met my mother?
I know she never blamed you.
Honestly,
I understand how hard it was for you.
But I never get the chance
to tell you myself.
Father.
I will shoulder the duty
for this nation in your place.
I won't let Fu Chou get away
with his treachery.
I will bring justice to you.
You shall not die in vain.
Wu You.
Zhongshan will be in a mess soon.
In order to keep
the innocents safe,
you must return here at once.
But I fear for your return.
I don't want you to get hurt...
and I wish to keep you away
from the fightings.
What else can I do for you now?
Princess Rong Le, Ke gave you
two advices before she left.
You must not catch a cold
or burden yourself with thoughts.
And now you are facing the breeze
and bothered by worries.
You are doing everything
that goes against her advices.
You just as disobedient as Ke
when she was younger.
You never talked much before.
When did you learn
to nag like Ling Yue?
Princess, the medicine is ready.
Have it while it's warm.
-You may go now.
-Yes.
I have some important tasks for you.
Yes, Princess.
After you leave to get
the medicine for me,
do not come back again.
Your Highness, I fear the General Fu
might try to harm you.
I should stay here and keep you safe.
The whole manor is being watched.
Even the Tranquil Garden
is being monitored.
Once Fu Chou makes a move,
you are no match for him.
You might even lose your life.
-But under no circumstances...
-This is important.
There is more pressing matter
than protecting me.
If Wu You received the news,
he would be on his way back.
As soon as he enters the city,
you must give him
this letter yourself.
Fear not, I will keep watch
at the city gate.
There is another task.
I want you to stay alive.
Look after Ling Yue for me.
For the rest of your life,
never leave her again.
Princess Rong Le.
Both Ling Yue and I will
follow you to our last breath.
While she is with me,
she is constantly in fear.
She never had any
easy time for herself.
She thought while she is here with me,
this would be her home.
But now,
this is nothing but a prison.
I am glad she escaped.
I hope she never set foot
into this house again.
Soon, I will die.
I might be dead at any moment.
It's my fault for not
finding His Majesty...
and get you the antidote.
But I believe in the
next three months,
Ke will find a cure for you.
I keep feeling dizzy recently.
I know the poison is invading my body.
As of now,
having three months
seems like a luxury.
Do not make it hard for Ke.
This is my destiny.
That was a lie.
You want to leave this place.
That's why you lied to me.
Isn't it?
-You should go.
-You can either tell me the truth...
or none of you will leave this house.
It's true.
I am poisoned.
I am dying.
You are in my house!
Who would dare to poison you?
If my guess is right,
the emperor you mentioned
was her brother.
Only he would dare
to hurt Rong Le.
You take the medicine
from him every month.
You must have the antidote.
Tell me, where is the antidote?
Tell me!
Fu Chou, stop.
You can fool Rong Le, but not me.
You are the spy planted by
Emperor of Qi.
He won't let Rong Le die so easily.
He is in another land,
so you must have the antidote.
You can either hand it over...
or I will slice you into pieces!
Rong Le!
Don't kill him!
Princess.
Don't beg for him because of me.
Hand over the antidote
and I will spare your life.
I don't have it even if you kill me.
Xiao Sha was working for my brother
because he had no other choice.
He lost my brother's trust.
He doesn't have the antidote.
He wouldn't have fought back
unless you struck him first.
Please, let him go.
General Fu!
Seize this man!
Let him go.
Lay down the weapon.
Leave now.
I can take care of myself.
-But...
-Leave!
General, you are hurt.
The wound needs to be treated.
I am fine.
Dismiss.
General.
Yes.
Dismiss.
I assure you,
whatever reason your brother
has to poison you,
I will get to him and
get you the antidote.
If we had got it earlier,
there might still be hope.
-But it's too late now.
-I don't believe it.
If I can't get the cure
from the Emperor,
I will go to Prince Li.
I'll bring Ke back here
to brew a cure for you.
If that doesn't work either,
I will send out
all the soldiers I have...
to search for a healer.
Ke only told the truth about
my condition to me alone.
The poison is invading my organs.
The best option I have...
is to extend my life
with other medicine.
Completely removing
the poison is impossible.
Finding a cure is pointless for me.
Which is why I didn't tell you.
I don't want you to waste time
on false hope.
I...
I will never let you die.
You told me...
you will never forgive me...
for using you and lying to you.
You hate me for
locking you up in here.
So live on.
Stay well and live this life.
You can have revenge on me.
I can spent my whole life for you.
The time I have left...
is getting shorting by the seconds.
I don't have time for grudge.
We became husband and wife.
Whether it was for a year
or just months,
our fate intertwined
in the past lifetime.
But ever since the incident
at Lake Qingliang,
all I have for you is hate.
But now that my life is running out,
I have one last advice for you.
-Will you...
-I will.
Whatever you ask of me today,
I will agree.
Do you mean it?
Will you give up on hate for me...
and put an end to your revenge?
Yes.
As long as you agree to my term,
I will give up all I have for you.
What is it?
Leave this place with me.
Let me have your love.
Let me take care of you
for the rest of your life.
I hope...
you will give me the answer
after you thought it through.
Days of summer,
nights of winter.
Years from now,
I will become a breeze...
and follow you to the next life.
Ash to ash.
Together,
we will leave this world.
Rong Le.
You agreed?
I can agree to anything.
I regret it.
I really do regret it.
If we can turn back time...
If we can turn back time,
when I first saw you,
I would have left all the grudges
behind and leave with you.
We can live in hiding.
Perhaps we can live in the woods.
We can be a normal couple.
A bridge over that little brook.
A land of serenity.
Every morning,
when I see the sunlight
shines on your face,
I couldn't bear to wake you up.
I would stare at you quietly.
And then, you woke up.
I don't have to do anything.
I will just watch you.
In a time of peace and
free from worries,
I am willing to spend
my life with you.
Perhaps...
we would be fighting over
trivial matters such as our meals.
Rong Le, will you believe me?
If I weren't a general,
I would be a great farmer.
If you weren't a princess,
aside from making dumplings,
what other food can you make?
But speaking of which,
I love the dumplings you make.
At every sunset,
we would be holding hands.
Under the glow of starlight,
we have each other.
Time may pass,
but we never left each other.
Seasons after seasons,
years after years.
After all those years,
I will have a face full of wrinkles...
and you will have long Grey hair.
We will tell our tales
to the children.
Those little brats...
will think of our life as
something plain and boring.
But the simple life
and peace we have...
came with a great cost.
In my heart,
this life is more
precious than anything.
As my spent my youth,
we will grow old together.
When we become old,
I will no longer be able
to see your face...
and you can't listen to...
how I say 'I love you'.
But I think...
the best form of love...
is to be together till
the end of time.
Rong Le.
You have nothing to fear.
I can't be with you in this life.
But I have decided...
to accompany you to the afterlife.
Time is running out for both of us.
But I assure you,
in our next life,
I will find you.
By that time, you would have lost
all the memories of this lifetime.
The two of us...
can start over again.
I will wait for you.
Even if you can't find me,
I'll be right there waiting for you.
How to we keep living this life?
Finally, I've learnt how to trust.
But I've underestimated love and hate.
We have thrown away the fate
that we got by chance.
I have to admit to my mistakes.
I regret the one mistake
that I made so much.
All hopes are lost,
how do I start over?
I asked for too much,
I hesitated for too long.
I blamed the mistake
that happened too soon.
You were standing right behind me,
mocking the promise I made for you.
I must give it all I had...
to accept the lies of affection.
It never ends, love will fade.
The blossoms fall,
and I waited in silence.
I cling onto the past
despite the pains.
I won't let our love be a regret.
Live without sorrow,
die without any hate.
This is the leniency that
you've shown me.
We are not holding hands
but you are holding my heart.
Although this might not be forever,
I've locked you in my heart
and I've locked you in my dream.
It's my fault for falling in love...
with you.
General Fu.
Speak.
-General, Lady Rong Le is...
-I know about Lady Rong Le.
There is no need for report.
-Very well, I shall let her...
-It's all right.
Dismiss.
Yes.
Rong Le, will you really
leave with me?
I do hold a place...
in your heart.
Chou.
What did you call me?
Please.
General.
I have made my decision.
I will...
I am sorry for interrupting.
Rong Le!
-My answer is...
-I hope you can just hear me out.
What you saw in there
is not the truth.
I was drunk last night.
I thought she was you.
No explanation needed.
You did nothing wrong.
It was me that failed as a wife.
-I really mistook her as you!
-I don't want to lie to you.
Which is why I am
telling you my decision.
I can surrender my life,
I can follow you to
anywhere you go.
But my heart...
belongs to Wu You.
You are lying.
You misunderstood me because of this.
-That is why you turned me down.
-I didn't misunderstand you.
It was you that misunderstood.
My answer is the same all along.
I was such a fool.
I should have known.
You will never care about me.
You never care about
what I do, unless...
my action will bring
Zongzheng Wu You harm.
You only agreed with me,
reconsider my offer...
and came to this yard...
all because of him!
I so naively thought...
everything you did...
was for me.
Do you even remember...
when was the only time
you addressed me...
as your husband?
That day, Zongzheng Wu You
took you by force.
To keep your illness
a secret from him,
you used me...
to turn him down.
You rushed in front of me.
With me as your husband,
you shielded me.
After all that you did,
I know well enough that...
your only motive is
to keep him from having...
the slightest pain in his heart.
Tell me.
How could I not hate him?
If you must hate,
then hate this fate we have.
We can be husband and wife,
but we can never be lovers.
This is not about anyone.
Even without Wu You,
the outcome will still be the same.
Then I must fight for my fate!
The person who will be
with you to the end...
and die by your side...
is none other than me.
For this lifetime,
this is where my fate with you ends.