Selected Project for Guangdong Province Original Online Audio-Visual Premium Project Database.
Mom,
Youqi,
you're a female Ph.D.
your conditions are so good.
Why do you insist on marrying someone
who touches dead bodies every day?
Mom,
he's a forensic doctor.
He's a police officer.
What forensic doctor?
That Mr. Guo
He's a financial tycoon in the pharmaceutical industry.
You'd be so much better off with him.
Leave Yang Ming.
If it weren't for him,
I would be that
corpse sunk to the bottom of the lake.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
My dad says
life doesn't bully ordinary people,
it only bullies cowards
and those who are pessimistic about life.
Just because I had good grades,
all the girls in my class bullied me.
Old Yang,
what's up?
Any progress?
No progress so far.
How are things
between you and Meng Youqi lately?
Pretty good.
Stop looking at that for now.
Come on,
have some water.
I bought you a new cup.
That's quite thoughtful.
Old Yang,
I've encountered something recently
and I'd like to consult you about it.
What is it?
I have a friend
who only focuses on his work
and completely neglects
his girlfriend.
Later, I found out
that his girlfriend
seems to have cheated on him.
The third party
is a financial tycoon who returned from overseas
and his surname is also Guo.
Surname Guo?
Oh, right.
I just bought a new pot.
It works pretty well.
I'll recommend it to you sometime.
That's where the problem lies.
My friend is completely
unaware of this situation.
How do you think I should
tell him
about this?
Wait,
your friend got cheated on,
why are you so worked up about it?
You might as well tell him directly.
Alright,
Yang Ming,
No, no, no.
What if your friend
can't accept it
and commits suicide?
No, no,
we need to hint at it subtly.
Old Yang,
what do you think of this blotting paper?
This...
Don't we still have a whole box?
Why are you buying it?
What color is this?
Dark green.
And this one?
Matcha green.
Mat-
Oh, right.
Why aren't you wearing your police uniform today?
Because I have a green hat to wear.
I'll go buy one for you too,
matcha green.
I hate green the most.
Hello.
The user you are calling is temporarily unavailable.
Please try again later.
Overseas financial tycoon.
Overseas.
Who can see this?
This is the work of a genius.
This needs a chemist to explain.
God knows what it is.
What's the reward for getting the right answer?
I think I've seen this kind of drug before.
Wang Corporation
People-oriented, excellence in business, quality wins, service with sincerity.
Yang Ming,
Yes?
Youqi,
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
I...
Why are you hesitating?
Oh, right.
Are you free now?
I want to take you somewhere.
Someone wants to see you.
Who?
What?
President Wang from Wang Corporation
wants to see you.
Wang Corporation
Let's go.
Teacher Meng,
Mr. Wang,
My boyfriend has arrived.
Yang Ming.
He's even more handsome than your dad.
This is your father's office.
Your father and I
were once business partners.
Back then, he came to my Wang Group
to help us with product development.
With his help,
our product development work
went very smoothly.
But later,
we discovered
someone was secretly taking the company's research results
for illegal profit.
And then?
That person
was Yang Qihua.
Mr. Wang,
how could Uncle Yang possibly...
Youqi,
let him speak.
It seems
that you all didn't know
about him working here.
To be precise,
he was the prime suspect.
Before we could
find complete evidence,
he had an accident.
Originally,
I wanted to tell you about this long ago.
However,
the truth was too cruel.
So...
Mr. Wang,
may I take a look?
Sure,
feel free to look around.
After Old Yang's accident,
no one has touched anything here.
As for me,
I've always wanted to clear his name.
That's why I left everything as it was.
This is your father's
research he was working on before he passed away.
It was in this project
that he gained benefits.
Back then, due to missing pages in this document,
we were unable to confirm
Yang Qihua's suspicion.
Mr. Wang,
I'd like to take these things back with me.
My dad always loved photography.
I want to develop the photos as a memento.
You can just call me Uncle Wang.
If you need anything in the future,
feel free to come to me.
Yang Ming,
our meeting this time
is all thanks to Meng Youqi.
Thank you.
I won't see you out then.
Let's go.
Lao Yang.
Who are you?
I'm his son.
And you are?
We're not very familiar.
Just colleagues.
Let's go.
Yang Ming.
I don't know about the relationship between Mr. Wang and Uncle Yang.
I don't believe what he said either.
Uncle Yang treated me
like his own daughter.
I trust his character.
I don't believe it either.
How could my dad go to Wang's company?
And why would he suddenly
come to find me now?
I...
Go ahead,
I believe you.
It was my parents.
They didn't want you to be a forensic doctor.
So I had an argument with them.
But later,
I started to waver too.
Then I thought of Mr. Wang's company.
That Mr. Guo,
he's very close to Mr. Wang.
I wanted him to arrange a meeting with Mr. Wang,
hoping to find
a position for you at Mr. Wang's company.
But who knew,
as soon as he heard it was you,
he agreed readily.
I'm sorry.
I took matters into my own hands.
Are you hungry?
Let's have a meal together, my treat.
You're not mad at me?
No, I'm not.
Then, about Uncle Yang's matter,
what should we do?
Don't worry,
I'll take care of it.