Selected project for Guangdong Province Original Online Audio-Visual Premium Project Database.
Dr. Yang,
we've found
the suspect who sold drugs to Wu Zongfan.
The suspect's name is Hu Fengxiang.
Take a look.
Thanks.
Thank you.
What's going on here?
Trying to curry favor, huh?
Don't talk so much when someone's treating.
Come on.
Cheers.
Wu Zongfan
bought
so many special drugs
because he has a history of drug use.
The drug dealer introduced him to this drug.
I know.
We were all there when Captain Xu interrogated him.
He even gave up the drug dealer.
When the drug enforcement team arrived,
the dealer was already dead.
We've examined the body.
What are you trying to say?
I was there too.
I'd like to ask for your help.
You
Go ahead.
I need to do a
physicochemical analysis report on the drugs
found on the drug dealer.
What do you want that for?
I found that
the autopsy report of the drug dealer
is identical to my father's.
Your father?
So I need to figure out
the connection between them.
You know,
my father
had an incident in the physical and chemical analysis unit,
or died from accidental poisoning.
I can't help you with that.
Yang Ming,
you don't want the superiors to know
that you're investigating your father's case, right?
I forbid you to do this.
But this is the only breakthrough.
What breakthrough?
You've been here for less than a month,
and you're already investigating your father's case.
Do you know
this will offend a lot of people?
You don't want to stay here anymore, do you?
You can just leave without a care in the world,
but what about Meng Youqi?
Have you thought about Old Qin and the rest of us?
Alright, alright,
if he won't help, I will.
It's just a pathology matter,
not a big deal.
Have you lost your mind?
Be careful not to bring trouble upon yourself.
Lan Jing.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it just now.
It's not your fault.
You've always wanted to know,
when facing burned bodies,
why I get so troubled, right?
I thought
I was brave enough to face it.
My father
was a firefighter.
During a major fire mission,
he sacrificed himself to save a girl.
When I arrived at the scene,
his body was completely burned,
beyond recognition.
I couldn't recognize him at all.
I kept telling myself,
That's not my father.
That can't be my father.
His teammate told me
he insisted on saving that girl.
He only said one thing:
He said,
'That girl
is the same age as his daughter.'
My father once told me,
'It's not that I chose firefighting,
firefighting chose me.'
I didn't understand it then.
Later, I became a police officer
and became a forensic pathologist.
When I saw
those bodies,
one after another,
I finally understood
what he meant.
So,
it's not that I chose forensics,
forensics chose me.
Youqi.
I'm sorry.
Did you call me for something?
It's nothing.
We haven't
gone out together in a long time.
I'm sorry.
I had to cancel our plans because of the last two cases.
I really feel bad about it.
It's okay.
I didn't say anything.
I'm happy that you can be so dedicated
to your work.
I know that when there are no cases,
you're like a
bird trapped in a cage.
The forensic scalpel
is your wings to soar.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Hello?
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Alright,
you can go.
What case?
Why so urgent?
There's no case.
Did I say there was a case?
No.
What are you up to?
The thing you wanted.
I had my colleagues in the physical and chemical analysis group do it.
Thanks, man.
Don't mention it.
I'm not the type
who would make mistakes for a friend.
As a trace evidence examiner,
I'm just curious about the results.
I didn't give you anything.
Captain Xu,
is there anything I can help you with?
It's nothing.
Please, have a seat.
No need.
I have something to attend to shortly.
Yang Ming.
You still won't give up, will you?
Of course not.
Haven't I told you before?
The case has already been concluded.
Why don't you let it go?
Let it go?
Captain Xu,
I'll say it again.
Do you really believe my father
died from accidental poisoning?
It was an accident.
Old Qin personally conducted the autopsy.
I didn't find anything unusual at the scene either.
All the evidence suggests
he accidentally poisoned himself at home.
Don't you trust me and your Uncle Qin?
I've gone through all the documents my father left behind.
Every experiment that was recorded,
I've tried to replicate.
But I can't find
the experiment that caused his poisoning.
I don't know why.
Captain Xu,
is this matter
related to someone else
in the department?
I'll keep these documents for now.
The files have been brought over.
He won't investigate.
Deputy Chief Peng.
Diandu.