Take it off.
No way, junior brother.
You don't really think
I have an affair with the imperial consort, do you?
Weren't you the one who taught me?
To be skeptical of everything.
Take a good look.
Go on.
Now you're going too far.
You're clearly taking advantage of your position.
To take advantage of me.
Are you taking it off or not?
I'll take it off, I'll take it off!
How could I not?
It's not like you haven't seen it before.
What?
Are you scared?
Who's scared?
People are born naked.
What is there to be afraid of?
I...
Turn around.
Look carefully, junior brother.
Come.
Look.
Do you need me to take off my shoes too?
Take a good look.
Are you done looking?
Aren't you making your judgment a bit too hastily?
So now you can be sure I'm not the murderer?
Junior brother.
Sometimes, you know,
what you see with your eyes isn't always true.
What are you trying to say?
I've told you before,
seeing isn't always believing.
And hearing isn't always the truth.
You have to use this to feel.
And to think.
You're crazy.
You're the crazy one.
Junior brother.
What do you want?
Shut up.
What illness do I have?
Your heart and lungs are so badly damaged.
Why don't you get treatment?
Life and death are up to fate.
I've long since stopped caring.
Fate.
I don't believe in fate.
Junior brother.
You really haven't changed at all.
People who don't change in this world
are rare.
I came to this Peach Blossom Manor before you.
Every blade of grass and tree here,
every mountain and stone,
even the people here,
I'm more familiar with them than you are.
I can help you.
How about it?
You only have seven days left.
And one day is almost over already.
If you don't say anything, I'll take it as a yes.
Then we brothers
can happily investigate cases together again.
But before we start investigating,
we should have a drink together.
You haven't really changed either.
You only care about the present.
You haven't changed.
I don't dare to change.
Open it.
These chains can't hold you, can they?
Sir
Everyone in the manor has been checked.
No one has any scratch marks.
But there are a few people who are difficult to check.
I'll find a way to check the rest.
Why is it this pavilion again?
Kan represents water.
We need to head west.
That's right.
Miss
Young Master Yan did find the correct direction.
However,
he didn't notice the formation in this bamboo forest.
As I suspected.
This bamboo forest
is rather strange.
Every bamboo stalk in this forest
is planted according to the positions of Qimen Dunjia.
If you don't know the method,
you'll get trapped inside.
And the only ones who can break the formation
are the Yun family from Peach Blossom Manor.
So, in that case,
Miss, are you planning to take me inside?
Yes.
Then, the reason you came here...
I suppose that's true.
You're here to investigate the death of the imperial consort, aren't you?
I won't let my sister die in vain.
I have to do something.
But as for you, Young Master Yan,
you were clearly already detained,
yet here you are now.
It seems Young Master Yan and Lord Han Dao
are quite close.
Lord Han Dao is my junior fellow disciple.
Except for the fact that he's always trying to kill me,
we are indeed quite close.
The grudge between you two
has nothing to do with me.
Since our goals are the same,
come with me.
I was just heading this way.
Young Master Yan, keep up.
Xiao Ying was killed right here.
She’s been afraid of this Peach Blossom Pond since she was a child.
So why did she end up in the water?
Unless someone forced her.
There were no wounds on her body.
And look here,
there are no signs of a struggle either.
As for being forced,
there’s more than one way to do it.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
Is there any way
to make her lose her fear of this pond?
Dreaming.
Or perhaps,
poisoning.
Yu Niang also hanged herself.
I think
she must have been poisoned with something that causes hallucinations.
But...
Miss, let me think for a moment.
The culprit poisoned someone.
The empress's medicine took effect.
She scratched the culprit while struggling.
Young Master Yan has an illness in his heart and lungs.
It seems his condition is quite serious.
Miss, your medical skills are impressive.
I didn't expect that just by looking,
you could do as much as our junior did after checking the pulse for a long time.
Young Master Yan.
Young Master Yan, are you all right?
Young Master Yan, did you find anything?
No.
There was nothing under the water except for aquatic plants and fish.
Nothing else at all.
Aren't you afraid of the peach blossom calamity?
Will it really come true?
It's all nonsense.
How could a few dead people's nonsense
possibly determine the fate of the living?
This place is my domain.
You have nothing to fear.
How can this tiny Peach Blossom Manor be called a domain?
I didn't expect your vision to be so narrow.
Why did you come to my room?
Are you here to
investigate the case or just play in the water?
Of course I went
to play in the water.
You—
You sure have time to spare.
I found an important clue
at the bottom of Peach Blossom Pool.
Want to know what it is?
What clue?
Bring me some clean clothes.
Okay.
Junior brother,
you're so obedient.
There are scratch marks on Yun Yang's back.
Then he's a suspect.
It's just scratch marks.
That's not solid evidence.
He could easily say Hong Xiu scratched him.
I found this at the bottom of Peach Blossom Pool.
Not sure if it's a pendant
or just an ornament.
It looks like something a woman would own.
I went through a lot to get this clue,
and you just take it away like that?
Are you giving it back or not?
Call me "senior brother" and let me hear it.
Don't push me, or I'll kill you right now.
Boring.
You were more fun when you were little.
So dull.
Here.
What is this?
Medicine to protect your heart and lungs.
Then
You didn't secretly poison me, did you?
If I wanted to kill you, I wouldn't need to use poison.
Don't worry.
Once this matter is resolved,
we'll settle things between us.
Alright.
Then go ahead and tell me.
What have you found out?
During the autopsy,
this was found in the consort's mouth.
A white hair.
It's Yun Su's.
So,
Yun Yang isn't the only suspect.
There's also Yun Su and the owner of this pendant.
It seems that on the night before the consort died,
Yun Yang wasn't the only one who saw her.