Wife
I'm going to lift the bridal veil now.
Yun Ming
Now you should start calling me husband.
Husband
Why is it you?
Why can't it be me?
It should be Yun Ming.
You are the young mistress of Peach Blossom Manor.
You are my wife, Yun Yang's wife.
I'm not.
Look at me.
I'm your husband.
You're not.
Yun Ming, Yun Ming, save me!
Qing Xuan.
I'm so scared.
You survived a near-death experience.
You've already died once.
There's nothing left to fear.
Besides,
Lord Han Dao and Young Hero Yan
will stand up for you.
What is it?
Do you still have questions for me?
Young mistress.
We didn't mean to disturb your rest.
It's just that
we need to check your tattoo.
Isn't that a bit too rude?
Rude?
It is indeed rude.
This junior insists on seeing it.
He says it's for the investigation.
We have to set aside propriety for now.
How do you want to check?
One at a time,
or all together?
You'll have to ask Lord Han Dao about that.
I...
I'll still check.
Whenever it's convenient for the young mistress.
The tattoo here is an old wound.
Are there any others elsewhere?
It's a bit hard to see.
This looks like
an injury caused by some kind of carving tool.
Young Madam
Why did the Young Master hurt you like this?
Why?
When I walked out of Yun Su's room,
when I didn't say what he wanted to hear,
when I looked at Yun Ming one more time,
What other reason could there be?
Maybe he was in a bad mood today.
Or maybe he just found a random reason.
To throw a tantrum.
Or maybe
he just wanted to torment someone for fun today.
Anyway, he always has his reasons.
He can do whatever he wants.
Otherwise, sir,
what other reason do you think there could be?
When you were tattooing,
did you notice
anything strange?
The tattoo on the Young Madam's calf is old.
It's clearer to see.
But the color seems off.
Yes.
Normally, when ink touches the skin,
it should appear bluish.
But the tattoo on the Young Madam's back
looks a bit pale.
This is...
It's Momantuo.
Momantuo has a whitening effect.
In the ink,
Momantuo must have been added.
And I've heard people say
that if this substance
is introduced into the body in small amounts over time,
the person won't die immediately.
Instead, they'll be slowly poisoned.
Then if this person's blood
is mixed into someone else's food or drink,
would that person be poisoned after consuming it?
Someone is using people to poison others.
That's right.
Using people as the medium for poisoning.
So the young madam was poisoned.
Then the inner core in his body would also be poisoned.
The tattoo on Hongxiu's body
can't be used as direct evidence against Yunyang.
Think about it.
If I were Yunyang,
this is what I would say.
Look,
she also has a tattoo.
Why isn't she dead?
It must be Yunyang.
The mastermind behind the so-called Peach Blossom Calamity
I think it's him.
No, that's not right.
Junior brother,
I think we still need to discuss this carefully.
But I think
Yun Qingxuan is a bit strange.
Strange how?
Think about it.
On the night Yun Su was killed,
besides Hongxiu, who else entered his room?
Who else?
Yun Qingxuan.
If, when I met Yun Qingxuan,
Yun Su was already dead,
then things would have turned out like this.
Everything would go according to plan.
If that's the case,
Yun Qingxuan must want us to fall out with Yun Yang.
Because that way, she would be safe.
That's right.
The entire Yun family,
there isn't a single good person among them.
Unfortunately, this is just our speculation.
We have no evidence.
Everything leaves a trace.
As long as they did it,
we'll be able to find evidence.
But why would Yun Qingxuan
take such a big risk to help Hong Xiu?
I've looked into Hong Xiu.
Hong Xiu has business in the capital.
I think
she probably wants to escape from Peach Blossom Manor.
As for Yun Qingxuan,
she probably wants to escape too.
Think about it—
what if the two of them are working together?
They both want to get away from Peach Blossom Manor.
If that's all there is to it,
then neither of them has really done anything wrong.
If I didn't have my official duties,
I wouldn't care if that old scoundrel Yun Su died.
I'd just consider it as them avenging our master.
At least half of our master's revenge would be fulfilled.
You didn't get to kill Yun Su yourself.
That's a pity, isn't it?
We don't know about our master
and Yun Su's past grudges.
Right now, the most urgent thing is to catch the killer.
Maybe after we find the killer,
the truth will come to light.
And after that,
it'll be the matter between you and me.
Little junior brother,
I'm really scared.
Before the truth comes out,
I might die.
I won't let you die.
At least not from illness.
Your life
belongs to me.
Brother Gu,
Playing chess against yourself
isn't any fun, is it?
Let me play with you.
Chess is only interesting with a worthy opponent.
Did you come to see me for something?
Now that the old manor lord is gone,
we don't have any other options.
But I remember
you wanted to choose Yun Yang before.
Having a choice is always better than none.
But now, he's the only one left.
What else can we do?
Actually, I think
this might not be a good thing.
I'd like to hear more.
Yun Yang is naturally bloodthirsty.
He's not a good leader.
I remember you once said,
"A wise bird chooses a good tree to nest in."
So I think the two of us
should start thinking about the future.
So what do you want to do?
Actually, I'd like to know
what you want to do.
Father,
your body is now as weak as clay,
but your soul has ascended to the immortal realm.
You shouldn't have treated me and my elder brother like this.
Even more so, you shouldn't have treated Hongxiu this way.
Darn it, you truly deserve this.
For as long as I can remember,
I knew you loved Qimen Dunjia,
and loved Feng Shui and the Eight Trigrams.
You tasted all kinds of herbs,
refined elixirs,
and built altars.
You fancied different women in the world,
but it was all just to fight against fate,
to gain more years of life.
When I was young,
I didn't understand anything.
Whatever you said,
I treated it as absolute truth.
But now, it's different.
I understand everything now.
You are an utterly selfish person.
We were all just
stepping stones on your path to immortality.
You took advantage of our love and trust for you,
and turned your sword against us.
You wished you could cut out our hearts and livers,
and suck our blood for your own use.
But even that wasn't enough.
You even wanted to take away everything we wished for,
everything we desired.
You made each of us lose what we loved most.
Yet in the mess you created,
you still dared to chase some dream of becoming immortal.
It's just a pity
No matter how hard you tried later in life
No matter how much you wished to become immortal
and live forever
in the end
you were just an old man who couldn't defy fate
We were father and son
Now we're separated by life and death
I really want to ask you
At the moment of your passing
Did you see paradise
or did you realize that the path to immortality
was nothing but an illusion in the end
Now that you're dead, you finally got your wish
The dead are gone
and will never grow old
Bones buried in the earth
are truly everlasting
But what about the living
I've figured it out
I can't live like I used to
I want to live for myself for once
To live for us
Yun Ming
You
Don't speak
Your elder brother will be back soon
What's really going on
You're not my brother's wife
You're Hong Xiu
You're mine