You're so strong.
I've never lost
I've never lost.
This girl
is such a joke.
Everyone,
Anyone else wants to challenge?
Five taels for once.
1,000 taels.
Come on.
Anyone else wants to challenge?
In this world,
is stronger than you.
No.
Something is wrong.
What are you doing?
What if you hurt someone?
How do you feel?
I don't feel anything.
You didn't use your strength.
Actually,
my best strength.
You mean...
What should I do? My Dali suddenly disappeared.
Oh no.
Well done.
I almost believed it.
Of course. I'm a professional.
Next time if you have something like this,
next time.
Okay, no problem.
And this.
are very suitable for you.
Take a look.
Pick whatever you want.
Where are they?
So lively.
Shen Wang is too arrogant.
and abducted Ngoh again.
What is it?
We need to visit him.
The man who molested on the street just now...
Mr. Shen, you're so polite.
Come with me.
Miss,
Why are you here?
I give up, okay?
Don't be nervous.
We're here to ask you
if you
harass that woman?
I really did it.
you don't have to be so upset.
I was just passing by.
I don't know why
she started shouting
saying that I did something to her.
You caught me
but you caught me.
I was wronged.
So we misunderstood you.
I'm sorry.
Don't feel so guilty.
Look at my face.
I was born with a bad face.
Since young,
I've been framed everywhere.
I'm used to it.
Ngoh.
That woman is a liar.
In other words,
we wronged the good people
and helped the bad.
That's why your power disappeared.
Ngoh.
Did your family tell you
that if you lose your power for doing bad things,
how can you restore it?
The divine power is the blessing
the blessing of the Kuan clan.
Even our people
we rarely have.
I'm the only one in this generation.
Don't worry.
I'll ask Dr. Jia to treat you later.
What if there's a cure?
Ngoh.
I'll do my best to help you.
Shen Wang.
I...
I'm hungry.
Let's go. I'll take you to eat first.
Judging from your symptoms,
It's caused by the wind demon that makes your limbs weak.
Maybe I should use some decoction.
Maybe it can heal itself.
It stinks.
No, no, no.
If you don't want to take the medicine,
And...
acupuncture.
Injection adjustment.
If you don't want to get injections,
And...
the plaster adjustment.
Can I stop treating him?
Enough.
Potion, acupuncture and plasters.
Come on.
Don't avoid doctors.
But this is not a disease.
And I don't want to take medicine.
You're an adult.
Why are you afraid of taking medicine?
How about this?
Dr. Jia,
I'll drink the medicine with her and put the plaster on her.
Then she won't be so scared
she won't be so scared.
Okay.
It's crooked.
I'm fine.
Stop it. You're still acting tough.
Just lie down.
Don't collapse before I recover.
Do you feel better?
Is there any sign of Dali's recovery?
I think Dr. Jia is just a fool.
It's okay.
I'll get you
a better doctor tomorrow.
Forget it.
I think my strength
I can't recover after taking medicine.
Don't be upset.
There's always a way.
I just think
I failed to enter the city.
I got the wrong guy.
and lost Dali.
Jin Mantang doesn't deserve you at all.
He's not your little brother.
I think
it should be a good thing.
Besides,
without Dali,
you'll only become an ordinary person.
Without Dali,
without Dali?
You protect me.
I think
it's not bad
to praise Ngoh.
Praise Ngoh. Praise Ngoh.
Even as an ordinary person,
I can help others.
Pull yourself together.
Don't let anyone worry about you anymore.
Granny, let me help you.
Ngoh, it's you again.
Thank you so much.
Granny, give me a hand.
Granny, I'm going to help others.
Why do I feel weak?
Ngoh, come and help me.
Coming.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
The main actor table.
Praise Ngoh.
Lin Zheng Yu.
Shen Wangwang.
Meng En
Zong Muyi.
Kim Mantang.
Dong-tak.
Kim Yu'er.
Li Yong.
Lee Hye-jin.
Mother of Shen.
Li Ning.
One-eyed assassin.
Wang Zhan.
Fatty Assassin.
Special Actor Table.
Xiao, two.
Chen, Wei.
[Strong man with arm wrestling.]
Liang Chen.
Young girl.
Hu Jiyue
Li Jie.
Wu Qiang.
Businessmen.
The party is mourning.
Sugar man.
Zhang Wencai.
Sir.
Yao Haoming.
Manager.
Andy Wang.
Ji Shu.
Pervert.
Abduction Granny.
Gu Li Ping.
Eunuch.
Staff Form.
Product.
A co-producer.
Liu Guangchan.
Executive Producer
Jiao Yanpeng.
Vice director selection.
Actor assistant director.
Huang Jie.
[Record]
No-eul.
[Writer Team]
Zhou Xi.
Writer...
A co-writer?
Ma Xiao Lu.
The production team.
Director of Production.
Zhou, Qing,
The summary.
Xing Dong.
Pan Linbo.
Live Producer.
Liu Deyeong.
A foreign producer.
Life producer.
Thank you.
Wang Hui.
Car management.
Accountant of the crew.
Wang Li.
Photography team.
Photographer.
Lee Jun.
You Shuangxi.
Photographer assistant.
Jeremy.
Lighting assistant.
Art team.
Art Instructor
Ma Zhihao
Props team
Props instructor.
Ma Yongfei.
Props.
Ma Chunlei.
Wang Zhenfeng.
Props.
He Yuyin.
Loulin Qiang.
Qin Yan.
stylist instructor.
Costume instructor.
Li Peng.
Costume assistant.
The recording team.
Recording.
Lee, friend.
The venue team.
[Shi Zhenbang]
Shi Zhenbang.
Fai Lou Yuan.
Photographer.
Zhou Ling.
Executive agent.
Bei.
Actor assistant.
Zou Jiaxin.
Team Meng En.
The person in charge of the studio.
Qin Qin.
Haixia.
Manager.
Promotion.
I'm Lin Chen.
Dam.
Actor assistant.
Late production.
Liu.
Editing instructor.
Rong Jiqing.
Color guidance.
DIT data management.
Lü Jiaqi.
Shi Meng Film.
DREAMCOLECTOR
Visual effects company.
Visual Director.
Zhao Zixiao.
Production Director.
Wang Xian.
Visual effect producer
Jing Jing
Three-dimensional producer
Yang-ju.
Dubbing team.
Liu Xun.
Dubbing director.
A dubber?
Sun Rui Yang.
Shen Wang.
Wang Ning.
Jin Mantang.
Gao Xudong.
Wei Zhong.
Wang Jing'er.
Jin Yu'er.
Liu Xun.
Mother Shen
Other dubbers
Wen, key, Zhao Mengjiao, Home, Kang
Zhang SiMiao, Li Shen Qian
Zhang Wenjie.
Wang Xiao Kun.
LeOrange Yisheng.
Ding Liang.
Voice Director.
Huang Bin.
Zhang Qi.
Voice producer.
Commander Zhang.
Record.
Voice Effect.
Li JiaGeng.
Mix.
Huang Bin.
Hwang Bin.
Effective recording.
Music production
Music Producer
Music design.
Huang Bin.
Music editor.
Theme Song Music Production Company.
Hangzhou Joy Monkey Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Dongfang Jun.
Music guidance.
Music circulation company.
Wuhan Ziteng Culture Co., Ltd.
Lyrics.
Lianghao.
Producer.
Liu Yang.
Arrangement.
Wu Yi Nan.
Mix.
The ending song.
Singing.
Meng En
Writing lyrics.
Guo Qiaofeng.
composed a song.
Yang Lei Lei.
Zhong Zhuo Ying.
Tele.
Harmony.
[Marketing Director]
Marketing Director.
Zhejiang Jiusheng Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Xiamen Century Qitai Culture Co., Ltd.
Hangzhou Joy Monkey Culture Development Co., Ltd.
Jiusheng Movie.
Zhejiang Jiusheng Film and Culture Co., Ltd.