[GEMINI BY JULIE ANNE SAN JOSE PLAYING]
If I were to represent you
you need to be honest with me.
I only wanted to burn his office.
[STUTTERING] I just wanted to buy
more time so
that I could bring him
his money but...
[YANA CRYING]
[SUGAR] What's "F.O."-
Friendship over!
Stupid!
[YANA BAWLING]
- [SUGAR] Sorry, sorry.
[SUGAR] This is my fault.
I should have encouraged you to...
I'm not going to allow you
to ruin our friendship.
Come on, let's go.
Miss Alvarez!
Huh!?
Godfather...
Why, what's up?
You don't eat fried fish anymore?
What else would you like?
I'll go buy some from the store.
It-It's uh...
[CHUCKLES]
It's not the fish, it-
It's you.
What did I do wrong?
[STUTTERING] I mean, sorry...
[STUTTERING] I mean it's me.
It's just...
I've been so bad to you before but...
Until now, you're still here.
Oh, it's nothing.
And I understand you Yana.
I know that your standards
in life have changed so...
[CHUCKLES]
Don't say that Gabo.
We're in the same situation now.
[CHUCKLES]
Why are you doing this?
Why are you being so kind to me?
You really have to ask?
Of course, you're my friend!
Just a friend, really?
You might ask for something
in exchange later on.
I might not be able to give
you what you want.
Don't be silly. I'm not asking
anything in exchange.
Thank you.
Thank you for being a good friend.
I appreciate it.
[STUTTERS] Sir, what do you mean?
I am suspending you, until further notice.
Sir. [GASPS]
[CHIEF] Sorry.
Hi.
[HECTOR] Uh...
[MARGA] What's this?
[INHALES]
I prepared your favorite.
I'm sorry if...
I was too harsh on you earlier.
I'm sorry.
You were harsh?
Or you really did do
something wrong?
[PLATE CLANGING]
I'm trying here, Marga!
Lately we've been too absorbed in
what happened with our daughter.
I'm trying to reconnect with you but,
this is what I get?
Shouldn't you instead be grateful
that I'm doing this for you?
But you...
You are the one that my heart wants.
That you don't feel anything for me.
I will leave.
[MARGA OVER THE PHONE]
Dear, I'll tell you later, okay?
I'm just going to catch a snake!
- You're a pig!
- Marga.
What are we going to talk about?
Your flirtatiousness?!
- Huh?! You slut!
- Marga, stop!
- [LEONA GROANING] No!
- [MARGA GRUNTS] You're a slut!
- Marga, don't!
- You're a slut!
- Marga, let go of Leona!
- You damn flirt!
- You're a flirt!
- Marga, enough!
- Huh!? I will kill you!
- Marga, that's enough!
- I will really kill you!
- Marga, enough! That's enough!
- Let go of Leona, Marga!
- I will kill you, slut!
- [LEONA GROANING] Marga, I'm sorry!
- [HECTOR] Enough!
- [MARGA] What do you mean enough?
- I will slap this woman!
- [HECTOR GROANS]
Don't interfere here Hector!
This fight is between me and Leona!
Where are you going, you whore?
- [MARGA] Where are you going, huh?
- [LEONA GRUNTING] Marga, stop please.
Where are you going you flirt?!
You're a flirt, Leona!
You're a flirt!
[WATER SPLASHES]
- [HECTOR] Marga!
- This is what you deserve!
[HECTOR GRUNTING] Enough!
[MARGA SHRIEKING]
That's what you deserve!
- [HECTOR] Let go of Leona
- [HECTOR] Enough! Enough!
- [MARGA] Let go of me Hector!
I can kill you Leona! You know that!
I am capable of doing it!
I can do that to you, Leona.
You'll do everything to steal my husband?
Huh?!
- [LEONA SOBBING]
[LEONA SOBBING] I'm sorry.
Hello, Sugar?
Yeah, I just got here.
Yes.
I want to meet the new
investigator of the case.
Alright, bye.
Hello, uh, sir.
Who's the new investigator assigned
to Zach Zamora's case?
It is Inspector Georgia Dimaunahan.
She's upstairs.
Alright, thank you.
Inspector Georgia Dimaunahan.
Kirby Manapat, ma'am.
I am working on the case
with Inpector Juro Catapang.
Well, I'm taking over.
I've already studied the report
that you made about the case.
Let's see what we have here.
Yes, correct.
Huh.
Have you ever heard of the
"Triangle of Fire", Manapat?
If one isn't present, then
there would be no fire.
Exactly.
We've already established the ignition.
Next, we have the fuel.
And finally, oxygen.
The fireworks powder.
There you have it!
There you have it, you can create fire!
[KIRBY] So, what do you mean?
Can you not see it?
It has been here all along.
Uh... What is?
The victim's killer isn't a single person.
to kill Zach Zamora.
This is why your investigation went astray.
Because you were focused
on one killer.
When in fact...
Three.
There are three.
Zach Zamora has three killers.
[AMELIE VOICEOVER] Three versus one.
Three girls are now the
suspects of Zach's murder.
Will it also be three girls vs. Liv?
I know you three very well!
You three killed Zach Zamora.
You cheated on me with that woman!?
Wait until Amelie hears of this!
She told me that all of those
contributed to burning Zach.
Tell me the truth.
Individually you all have a
connection to burning Zach.
You three, did you plan to kill Zach?