[GEMINI BY JULIE ANNE SAN JOSE PLAYING]
You know where Zach's laptop is?
Why didn't you tell us?
I won't gain anything from telling you that.
What did you say? Mmm?
Sir, you don't have to do this.
I'll tell you the truth.
We have a warrant for Zach Zamora's laptop.
It's possible that she's the killer we're looking for.
Whatever you and A fought about,
is it really more important
than your relationship as sisters?
Yeah, I really miss my sister.
[SUGAR] You just made my job easier!
What job?
To make you join A's bridal shower tomorrow.
You'll come, right?
That way, you two can make up.
Where did you get that?!
From Zach's laptop.
And this is not the only video
of you and Zach together.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What's that video?
Can I see?
[AMELIE GASPING IN FEAR]
Umm...
No, no, actually...
[STUTTERING] I was just telling them to leave because
they are disrupting my bridal shower.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
Sorry we came at the wrong time.
What are you asking my sister?
No, no, it's nothing.
If you want to question me,
I'll personally go to the precinct tomorrow.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
9AM, okay?
Okay.
We're sorry for coming at the wrong time.
Let’s go.
- [AMELIE] It's nothing. It's okay, it's okay. No, nothing.
- [LIV] Let's go-
[AMELIE STUTTERS] I'll go there tomorrow, 9AM.
You can leave.
Bye.
- [SUGAR CLEARS THROAT]
- [AMELIE SLAMS DOOR]
- [LIV] Are you okay?
- [SUGAR] Oh.
[AMELIE BREATHES PANICALLY] Yeah.
[LIV] What-
- [LIV STUTTERS]
- [SUGAR] What's up?
Did they ask you about me?
- I'm really sorry for dragging you into this.
- [AMELIE] No.
No, no, no, no.
It's not about you.
It's not about you, Liv.
[SUGAR] Why did Inspector talk to you?
[STUTTERING] It's...
[STUTTERING] It's about Mom.
It's about the video she sent, that's it.
[AMELIE BREATHING PANICALLY]
It had nothing to do with you guys.
Don't worry, it's okay.
Nothing happened.
It's okay.
Zach truly has no shame.
[KIRBY INHALES DEEPLY]
Not only is he a cheater, but he also pursued both sisters
and even filmed a sex video.
[KIRBY SIGHS]
He has no respect for women.
But it's not a valid reason for anyone to kill him.
Still, partner.
[KIRBY INHALES DEEPLY]
The reputation of the male species is getting
ruined, including good guys like me.
Right?
That’s my image on the line.
Come on.
Partner!
Oh.
[KIRBY WHISTLES] Hey, give it everything you’ve got.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
- Wait, is that the inspector again?
- [SUGAR] Um, no. That's the-
[YANA] And because you're all good now...
[SUGAR] Yeah...
[YANA] I think it's time to start the party!
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] Loyalty.
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] One of the key ingredients of friendship.
[LIV] Oh my God-
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] an unspoken promise that
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] whatever you're going through,
[LIV] This is crazy!
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] or if you've done a mistake.
[GIRLS CHATTERING AND LAUGHING IN BACKGROUND]
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] We listen and we don't judge.
[GIRLS PARTYING IN BACKGROUND]
[SUGAR VOICEOVER] And we stay.
[JURO] And this is not the only video
of you and Zach together.
- [GIRLS CONTINUE TO LAUGH]
- [LIV] Let's go!
[AMELIE BREATHES PANICALLY]
- [LIV] Yes!
- [SUGAR] Hey, A!
[YANA] Hey.
[LIV] A!
[AMELIE BREATHES PANICALLY]
A!
A, wait!
What's going on?
I'm sorry, I'm suddenly not feeling well, Liv.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] I have to go.
Let me take you home then.
Just enjoy the party.
I'm sorry, Liv.
- Sorry, sorry.
- [LIV] A.
[GEMINI BY JULIE ANNE SAN JOSE PLAYING]
[HECTOR] I'm sure this will make Amelie happy.
[SLIDING DOOR CLOSES]
I thought you had a party with your friends.
Yana even asked for my permission.
Well, it finished early.
I'm also exhausted.
[HECTOR] Oh.
Well, it’s a good thing you guys finished early
because the sculpture Luke made
for the wedding reception is here.
Hold this.
Ta-da!
It’s magnificent!
I can’t wait for it to be done in marble.
It’s going to be perfect.
Just like my perfect daughter.
[MARGA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[HECTOR] As he should.
Once you two are married, he better treat you like royalty,
or else he’ll be dealing with me.
Amelie.
Are you okay, dear?
What?
[AMELIE GULPS]
I'm just really exhausted.
Um, may I go to my room now?
[DOOR CLOSES]
Zach, no!
[AMELIE GIGGLES LIGHTLY]
No video!
What's with the video?
[ZACH] It's okay, you're pretty anyway!
[AMELIE CLICKS TONGUE] Get over here, please.
Join me now.
[AMELIE EXHALES SHARPLY]
[ZACH GRUNTS]
- [AMELIE GIGGLES]
- [ZACH GROANS]
[AMELIE GIGGLES]
[KISSING NOISES]
[FOOT SLAMMING]
[AMELIE GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION]
[AMELIE SOBS IN EXASPERATION]
[AMELIE SNIFFLES] No!
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
[AMELIE SCREAMS IN FRUSTRATION]
I'm so stupid!
I can't believe I fell for it!
I always fall for it!
I'm so stupid!
[AMELIE SNIFFLES SHARPLY] I’m so stupid!
Stupid!
[AMELIE SOBS IN FRUSTRATION]
[AMELIE] What's that?
It's uh...
It's for me.
Wait.
You look so beautiful.
[AMELIE] Stop it!
What's that?
[ZACH] It's for me.
[AMELIE CLICKS TONGUE] Zach, come back here.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Hey!
[ZACH] One second.
I think I got it.
- Come back here, come on.
- [ZACH] You look so beautiful.
- Come back here, give me a kiss already.
- [ZACH] Extra spicy!
- [ZACH GIGGLES MANIACALLY]
- [AMELIE GIGGLES]
[AMELIE CONTINUES TO SOB IN FRUSTRATION]
Hey, but seriously, stop that.
You have all sorts of my videos
there on your phone already.
[ZACH SCOFFS LIGHTLY]
Why?
I'm not recording you without your consent.
Mm.
[ZACH] And one more thing, I'm careful.
It's for my eyes only.
I just miss you when we're not together.
Regardless, I mean...
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
There have been plenty of video
scandals going around lately.
And also, I don’t want to be one of those girls
that lets their partner take videos of them,
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
and the video gets leaked...
and their reputation gets ruined.
[AMELIE SIGHS SHARPLY]
[KISSING NOISES]
A.
Come on, live a little.
And besides, this is what makes our relationship exciting.
Didn't you dump your ex-boyfriend
because he was boring?
Come on.
[KISSING NOISES] A, please.
Do this for me.
Just this once.
Come on.
Okay, fine.
Yeah?
- Fine, but just for a little while.
- Yeah?
That's it.
Okay, just stay there.
[WATER SPLASHING]
[AMELIE COUGHING]
[AMELIE SOBBING]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[AMELIE GROANS]
Amelie is Liv's sister, right?
They have a sex video.
So, are you saying that she and Zach had an affair?
[JURO SIGHS]
I still don’t have all the details,
but I’ve already scheduled an interview
with Amelie at the precinct tomorrow.
For now, all I can say is
that Zach recorded those videos
without Amelie’s knowledge.
What?!
[LEONARD SCOFFS]
Hidden camera?
I couldn’t believe it either, Godfather.
If your partner agrees to a video, that’s one thing.
But to record her without her knowing?
Not only is that malicious,
it’s a crime.
What are you trying to say?
That Zach's a criminal? Huh?
That's not what I meant, Godfather.
It’s your job to find out who
killed him, not to judge him!
Whatever Zach did, he didn't
deserve to die because of it!
I know that.
Well then, do something!
Find out who killed him!
Juro, I didn't take you in,
put you through school, for you to fail.
Godfather, I’m doing everything I can.
But one wrong move could get the case dismissed.
Which is why I’m being extra careful with every step I take.
I'm so tired of your excuses, Juro.
Find who killed my son.
And put that person in jail.
Or you know what, better yet.
Whoever he or she is, kill that person as well!
Do you understand me?
Do you understand me?!
Yes.
[HECTOR] All she said earlier
was that she’s exhausted.
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY]
She gave the same excuse to Liv and I,
but Uncle, I really think this has something to do with
her interview with the police.
Why would the police talk to her?
They've already spoken to Liv, and your Auntie Marga too.
What else do they need from Amelie?
[YANA SIGHS SOFTLY]
[HECTOR KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Amelie?
Can we talk?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR CONTINUES]
[YANA KNOCKS ON DOOR]
A?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR CONTINUES]
A, we're just worried about you!
Amelie?
[HECTOR KNOCKS ON DOOR]
It's already 12.
It's late. She’s probably asleep.
Let’s just talk to her tomorrow.
Get some rest now, Yana.
Alright, Uncle.
[HECTOR] Good night.
Good night.
[YANA GASPS]
A?
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY]
I don't know how to tell you this.
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY] A, I'm so sorry.
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY]
A, a sex video is circulating.
What?
[YANA CONTINUES TO EXHALE SHARPLY]
A, I'm so sorry.
- [YANA CONTINUES TO EXHALE SHARPLY]
- You've already seen it?
[YANA BREATHES PANICALLY]
- It's so bad.
- Yana.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES] Let me see.
Here.
I mean, isn't she one of your most
favorite Hollywood actresses?!
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY]
- Um...
- [YANA] Oh my gosh! This is so bad for her.
[YANA SIGHS]
Well, I mean, they are liberated in the US.
But if this happened here, in the Philippines, oh my gosh!
Her career, her work, her life?
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY] It would be ruined!
[YANA] Everything!
Oh my gosh, I feel so bad for the victim!
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY] Poor her.
She would be such a victim here.
Oh my God.
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY]
A?
A, what's wrong?
Um.
[YANA] A, is everything okay?
You've been acting like this since last night.
I just feel sorry for her.
I have to go, I have an appointment.
Bye.
Have a seat, Miss Baltazar.
Before you ask me anything...
Can I go first?
Are there more?
Videos, I mean.
Did you watch everything?
Did you all see it?
Only Inspector Kirby and I
are aware of the videos.
We browsed some files to
get an idea of what Zach did,
and that’s when we learned that the videos
were taken with your knowledge.
The others, however, appear to have
been recorded with a hidden camera.
Are you sure that I'm that woman?
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] I mean, I barely saw the video.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] That was probably another woman.
It was probably Zach's other mistress.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Maybe it's another woman, Inspector.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] I don't know...
Miss Baltazar...
[JURO INHALES DEEPLY] I can show it to you again.
[JURO CLEARS THROAT]
[JURO]I’m sorry, Miss Baltazar, but there’s no doubt that
you’re the woman in Zach’s videos.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
Then you should erase that.
I can't.
You got what you need, erase it!
How much do you need, Inspector?
I can buy everything you want.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Name your price!
I really can’t, Miss Baltazar.
Why not?!
Why? Are you planning to watch it again?
[SCOFFS]
- [AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Do you intend to enjoy it?
- [JURO] Because those-
- Those videos-
- You're all perverts!
[JURO] Because those videos are evidence!
Those videos are your motive for killing the victim.
It's proof that you and Zach Zamora had an affair.
Is that why you wanted the video erased?
To keep it a secret because
you’re about to get married?
Huh?
Is that the reason you killed Zach Zamora?
Miss Baltazar!
Did you kill Zach Zamora?!
If I did, can you blame me?!
So you're admitting that you killed Zach?
No.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
I did not kill Zach Zamora.
I did not kill him.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] But I wish I did!
I wish I killed him, Inspector!
How I wish I killed him so I could avenge myself
for all his perverted acts towards me!
He's an animal!
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] He's a monster!
But I guess I’m making it worse for myself
because whatever I say here now,
you’ll never believe me.
Because all of a sudden I'm a suspect.
It's your duty to prove
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] that I'm guilty.
But I'm telling you, Inspector,
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
I did not kill Zach.
I did not kill him!
You will have a hard time proving it because I'm innocent.
With all due respect, Miss Baltazar,
you're not innocent.
Two people were involved in the affair,
which means you must
have wanted Zach too.
Right?
Yes.
Yes!
But I did not cheat on anyone.
You have a boyfriend.
Right?
More than a year ago...
Luke and I had problems.
We've been together since high school,
then out of nowhere, we had a problem.
I got bored with our relationship.
I wanted to experiment. I wanted to have fun.
That's when Zach came into the picture.
He kept pestering me, saying he’d
liked me for a long time, so I...
So I gave in.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES] I gave in.
I wanted to have fun.
I wanted adventure.
I wanted... [AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
I wanted to experiment, and Zach was...
he was fun...
He was a lot of fun.
I thought I would fall in love with him,
but I never did.
So, when I felt that he was...
he was getting serious.
I had to break it off.
What's this?
Sit down, A.
I just realized that
we've been together for a few months,
and I never took you out on a proper date.
So, surprise.
[AMELIE CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
But Zach, we're not really together.
Didn't we agree to not do all these cheesy stuff?
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
To just keep it casual?
A, what if I don't like casual?
What if I want something more?
A, I want to take this relationship to the next level.
I want to make our relationship official.
Zach… [AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
I'm sorry,
but I don't feel the same way.
I'm sorry, Zach.
I have to go.
Sorry, Zach.
Not long after,
Luke and I got back together. [AMELIE SIGHS]
And I never cheated on him.
[AMELIE SOBS] I never cheated on him.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Things were alright since then.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] And as for Zach,
I found out that Liv liked him.
When I found out about that, I pointed Zach to her direction,
and when he and Liv got together, I was genuinely...
I was...
I was genuinely happy for my sister.
[AMELIE SOBS]
I was happy for her.
That's why I told Zach,
[AMELIE SOBS] to delete all our videos, all the videos he took.
To delete all of it.
And he did.
He deleted them.
He deleted them in front of me.
I didn't...
I didn't know he had more of them.
I didn't know that he was
recording behind my back.
[AMELIE SOBS] I was so stupid!
I was so stupid!
[AMELIE SOBS]
I'm so stupid, I shouldn't have trusted him!
[AMELIE SOBS] He's a monster.
He's a sick pig!
Inspector, I know I'm ice cold.
I never beg...
But, please.
Please, Inspector, my family
cannot know about this.
I'm about to get married.
[AMELIE SOBS] Please.
Please, I love Luke so much.
Inspector, please.
I can't embarrass myself in front of everyone.
Liv, how are you doing?
[LIV SCOFFS AND CLICKS HER TONGUE]
Amelie hasn't responded since last night.
And Yana hasn’t given me any updates.
I know A has a scheduled meeting
with the investigators today.
If that’s the case, maybe she’s just busy or in a rush,
that she isn't able to send a text.
[LIV SNIFFLES]
I have a bad feeling.
It's like...
have you heard of sister's instinct?
I could always feel when
something's going on with A.
I remember back then
when I missed cheerleading practice
because I was sick.
I suddenly got worried about A.
And then, I went to check on her and found that
she had fallen and gotten an injury,
and then we had to rush her to the hospital.
[LIV INHALES DEEPLY] So, from then on…
I learned to always trust my instincts.
I sort of get it.
I get the same feeling when it comes to my family.
There's a term for that,
it's what they call intuition.
- [LIV] Intuition.
- [SUGAR] Intuition. Yes, that's it.
- Mm.
- That’s right.
If something’s going on with A, she’ll tell you about it.
Just give it some time.
- [LIV] Really?
- [SUGAR] Yeah.
Instead of you worrying.
- You're stressing yourself out.
- But she hasn’t been responding.
Look, you're stressing yourself out.
- I know she takes a while to respond, but not this long.
- [SUGAR CLICKS HER TONGUE]
Just leave her be.
Just work instead.
[LIV CLICKS HER TONGUE]
[SUGAR] Okay?
This coffee you made is strong.
[SUGAR LAUGHS]
[LIV] No wonder I'm anxious.
[SUGAR] Just let me know if you need anything.
[LIV] Alright, thank you.
[SUGAR] Mm.
[JURO SIGHS] We have no intention
of circulating the videos.
Zach's laptop is securely locked away
to make sure no one has access to it.
Now, it's time for you to answer my questions.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
What were you doing at the gym
when the victim was burning?
[AMELIE SOBS] Um...
[AMELIE STUTTERS]
Inspector, I was just working out.
It’s part of my daily routine to prepare for my wedding.
Did you bring fireworks powder to the gym?
[AMELIE SOBS] No.
No, why would I do that?
Do you use tea tree oil?
Do you know anything about that?
I told you that I wish I killed Zach,
but I really didn't.
It wasn't me.
If I had done something wrong... it was
It was that when I allowed myself to be stupid.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES] I was naive.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] It can’t be helped.
This is my punishment.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES] This is my punishment for
the humiliation Zach caused me.
Why is it always like this?
Why must women always suffer in these situations?
And why do men always seem to be overjoyed
when these issues happen?
And we women...
We get judged.
Shamed.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
Why is it that way?
Are we not allowed to be stupid, at times?
Are we not allowed to make mistakes?
Even just a little?
[AMELIE SNIFFLES] Why is it like this?
It’s so unfair.
A?
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY] A.
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Yana, what are you doing here?
Liv told me your appointment was here.
And I came because I’m worried about you.
You've been spaced out since last night
after the investigators interviewed you.
And now your eyes are all swollen, A.
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY]
What are they asking you to make you cry like that?
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY] Huh?
[YANA SIGHS]
I don’t have to be Sherlock Holmes
to know that you're hiding something.
A.
Are you hiding something?
I’m not hiding anything, okay?
They just asked me questions about Mom.
Come on, let’s go home.
A.
You’ve been there for me
more times than I can count.
Okay? You’re there for me every time I’m sad
because I'm remembering Mommy.
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY] or every time I cry
because Daddy left me as well.
[YANA SOBS LIGHTLY]
Not only are you my best friend,
you’re like a sister to me already.
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY]
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
A, I know you’re going through
something right now, okay?
And,
if you’re not ready,
you don’t have to tell me.
I just want you to know that you’re not alone.
[AMELIE SIGHS]
A.
[YANA SIGHS] Oh my God.
You should’ve told me about this earlier
so I could’ve gone with you to the interrogation.
You know what? Zach is really shameless.
You know what? If he were still alive,
I’m sure plenty of cases can
already be filed against him!
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY]
I would never want things to go that far, Yana.
That would only expose me more.
You know what? I knew it, okay?
I knew it.
I should’ve warned you back then.
I should’ve warned you when
I saw you two together.
I just... [YANA SCOFFS IN FRUSTRATION]
You saw the two of us?
Hey.
I'm so drunk.
- [ZACH GIGGLES]
- Stop!
Stop, stop!
Not here, not here, not here.
But there's no one around.
Zach!
Hey!
Zach, not here.
Alright, just take it easy, babe.
[AMELIE GIGGLES]
Hey, behave!
[AMELIE GIGGLES] Stop it.
[AMELIE GIGGLING]
[ZACH WHEEZES]
[YANA] Just once.
- A.
- Yana, you saw us?
A!
[YANA PANTING LIGHTLY]
Yeah.
But it was just once, okay?
Just once.
You and Zach were flirting on the way to his car.
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY] I didn’t mention it because you
and Luke had already broken up.
And I just thought to myself that you’re a grown woman, you know?
[YANA INHALES DEEPLY] And
honestly, there’s nothing wrong if
you and Zach had a fling, right?
"Had a fling".
Is that the reason why I’m being punished?
[AMELIE SOBS] Because I had a fling
with someone else while-
A, no.
Technically speaking, there wasn't
anything wrong with what you did.
You were single.
Zach was single.
You didn’t hurt anyone else.
You were just trying different options.
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
[AMELIE SIGHS DEEPLY]
So I’m facing the consequences now.
[AMELIE INHALES]
Why is this all happening?
Am I a bad person?
Is this my karma?
Do I deserve this?
No, okay?
You don’t deserve this.
No one deserves this.
You know who deserves this?
Zach.
He better be thankful he burned to death,
because if he was still alive until now...
[YANA SCOFFS]
He’s really going to get everything that’s coming to him.
[AMELIE SOBS LIGHTLY]
He's such a pig!
And to think he kept all your videos
while he was still with Liv!
Oh my God, A.
He's so sick!
- He's such a pig!
- [AMELIE] About Liv...
What about Liv?
Yana, what should I do?
[AMELIE SOBS LIGHTLY]
What will I do once Liv learns about this?
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY]
Yana...
Yana, should I tell her now?
Do I need to talk to her now?
[AMELIE INHALES DEEPLY] Yana, I can't lose her.
[AMELIE SOBS] I-
I can't lose my sister, Yana.
I really can't.
I don't want this.
I just want to disappear.
I can't take it anymore.
[AMELIE'S VOICE TREMBLES] I can't do this.
A, it's okay, okay?
Just breathe, okay?
Just relax.
I'm here for you.
Okay?
I am here for you.
I won't abandon you.
We are in this together, okay?
As for Liv...
[YANA SCOFFS IN HESITATION]
I guess...
What she doesn't know won't hurt her, right?
[STUTTERS] And the police, they said that
the video will be kept confidential, okay?
No one else will see it.
So, it's just us who knows, okay?
A, I promise that I will never
break your confidence ever again.
A, I won't let you disappear.
- "She is A-Okay! She's just overwhelmed
with the wedding prep."
- "She needs to unplug for a bit."
[SUGAR] Oh.
Let's get back to work, alright?
Get it moving! Come on!
What are you guys so distracted wtih?
Is that Coach Zach?!
You guys are pigs!
He's already dead, and yet, you’re doing this to him.
[VIDEO MESSAGE RECEIVED TONE]
Why did you have to unplug now?!
[SUGAR CLICKS TONGUE]
Please.
Sugar!
Have you read Yana's text?
Mm-mm.
[LIV SIGHS]
Well, I'm glad that A's fine.
I guess my sister's instinct was wrong.
Actually, Liv,
I think you were right.
What do you mean?
Why? What's wrong?
Just take a seat first.
Why?
There's something you need to see.
What is it?
[SUGAR'S VOICEOVER] Can you truly be loyal,
if both your friends are clashing with each other?
[SUGAR'S VOICEOVER] Who would you listen to?
Who would you judge?
And who's side would you take?
[LIV INHALES DEEPLY] No.
[LIV INHALES DEEPLY]
If your partner were in a similar position,
would you allow this to happen to her?!
With her videos being sent to people?!
Hey, Sugar.
What's happening?
Why are you shouting?
Sir Luke, there's something you need to see.
Do you think one of the sisters killed Zach?
I think we're about to find out.
Amelie!
Is there something you need to confess to me?
What's happening here?
Your daughter and I
don't just share the same DNA,
we also shared the same man!
[AMELIE SCREAMS]
[HECTOR] Amelie!