- [SUGAR] You deserve to go to hell!
- [MARGA GROANS]
[MARGA GROANS] Ouch, that hurts!
- [SUGAR] You deserve to go to hell-
- [AMELIE] Stop it, Sugar!
- [AMELIE] Sugar, enough! What the hell?!
- [MARGA GROANS]
- [SUGAR GROANS]
- [AMELIE] What the hell is your problem, huh!?
What's my problem?!
She killed my brother!
A, it wasn't your father who
killed my brother, it was her!
Who? Who told you that, huh?!
- [SUGAR] You killed my brother, you mon-
Marga Baltazar is the one
who shot the victim.
Get a warrant now. Right now.
Bro, I'll go ahead.
You're leaving?
I can't just sit here and wait while
there's something happening to my daughters.
The police are still looking for you.
Whatever happens, happens.
This is the reason why I put up
with Marga all these years.
Because I didn't want my daughter to
get caught up in our problem.
But what I feared has already happened.
My daughters need me.
Go home!
[AMELIE] Mom!
- [AMELIE] Mom!
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[AMELIE] Mom, don't!
[AMELIE] Mom!
Mom!
[GASPS] Mom!
Mom! Mom!
[AMELIE] Oh my God, Mom!
[AMELIE] Mom!
[AMELIE] Mom, please wake up!
[AMELIE] Help!
Mom, wake up!
Wake up, Mom!
Mom!
Oh my gosh! Thank God, thank God!
Mom, open the door.
[AMELIE] Open the door!
Mom!
Mom.
- I can't go to jail!
- [AMELIE] Mom, what are you planning to do?
- Mom! Mom!
Mom, what are you-
Are you still planning to escape?!
- [MARGA SOBBING] I can't go to jail!
- [AMELIE] You can't escape anymore, mom!
Mom, you need to surrender!
- I don't want to go to jail!
- [AMELIE] Mom, you need to go to the hospital.
They can't know about my crimes!
What would they say-
Mom, what the hell!?
For once in your life, can you stop thinking
about what other people will think?
Please? [INHALES]
Are they going to help you, huh?!
Can they clear your name? No, right?
I'm your daughter, Mom,
I will help you. So please,
- please, I love you so much.
- [MARGA] I can't, dear, I will rot in jail.
- [MARGA SOBS]
- No, Mom no, Mom,
I'll find you a great attorney,
I'll find one, please.
Please, Mom.
- [LIV VOICEOVER] Genetics tell us
- [AMELIE] Just surrender, Mom.
- that we are mini versions of our parents.
- Help! Help!
- [LIV VOICEOVER] So, when they make mistakes,
- [AMELIE] Help!
we still accept them the
way we accept ourselves.
[GEMINI BY JULIE ANNE SAN JOSE PLAYING]
Oh no!
Wai-
Hey-
[LEONA] Maybe we got disconnected.
No, no!
Wait, where did they go?
Where's-
Oh no, it's gone, Mom.
It got cut, Dear.
[SIGHING]
Oh God, I hope nothing bad
happened to Amelie.
[BREATHES PANICALLY]
No mother wants to hurt
her own daughter, right?
Mom!
She pointed a gun at Amelie!
You saw it, right?
We both saw it!
I'll go to them.
[STUTTERING] Dear, you can't go there,
- Mom!
- because you might get dragged into it.
- You can't go!
- Mom I can't stay put!
I'm restless, I'm worried
for Amelie, okay?
I just want to know that she's safe.
- And she's not hurt.
- [LEONA] No.
Once everything is settled,
once everything is clear,
- you’re absolutely free to go there.
- [LIV CLICKS HER TONGUE]
We’ll go see your sibling,
I’ll even go with you.
But for now, dear,
- everything’s a mess.
- [LIV SIGHS]
Just stay here.
- Let's wait for an update, okay?
- [LIV CLICKS HER TONGUE]
[POLICE SIRENS BLARING]
[AMELIE] Please help us!
[AMELIE BREATHES PANICALLY]
Mom, where is your bag?
Where's the gun?
Give me the gun!
[AMELIE] Mom, give me the gun!
- [AMELIE] Give me the gun!
- [CAR DOORS CLOSE]
Give me the gun!
Give it here.
Here's the gun!
[AMELIE PANTING]
Please, don't shoot us!
[GUN SLIDES ON GROUND]
My Mom will surrender!
She'll surrender!
Mom, come on.
- [AMELIE] Here she is, please don't hurt her.
- Cruz, Perez!
Handcuff Mrs. Baltazar.
[ROLDAN] Lourdes!
- [LOURDES] Oh?
- Our daughter's in trouble.
Huh?!
[STUTTERING] Maybe she's the one who instigated-
No it wasn't her.
It's Marga and Amelie.
Here, watch this.
She managed to record what
was happening, but it got cut off.
My God—this kid, really!
According to the comment section,
Marga is officially wanted,
because she’s the one who killed Byron.
Lourdes.
This is it.
We'll finally get justice for our son.
Oh, thank God but...
Roldan.
Let's go to Sugar first.
Let’s go check on her,
see if she's alright or…
I'll handle this. Go get dressed.
Go get dressed, I'll finish this next batch.
[AMELIE SOBBING]
[POLICEMAN] Ma'am,
you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used
for or against you in court.
You have the right to an
attorney of your choosing.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be appointed to you.
Please don't hurt my mom, okay?
I'll follow you.
I'll go to you immediately, Mom.
- [POLICEMAN] Go, put her in the car.
- I'll call Attorney.
I'll call Attorney, Mom, okay?
I'll follow.
- I'll follow, okay?
- Please follow us to the precinct, ma'am.
Wait.
I have something to say to the suspect.
Go ahead and say it.
Go ahead and curse me.
Say whatever you want to say.
Let's finish this!
[SUGAR INHALES]
I'm just enjoying the moment.
To see you like this.
Wounded.
Handcuffed.
Rock bottom.
You look so different now,
compared to the first time I saw you.
At least,
somehow
I got revenge for my brother.
Whatever you say,
we can never bring him back!
And that's because of you!
Because of you, Marga!
- That's because of you!
- [POLICEMAN] Miss, miss enough!
[AMELIE] Sugar, that's enough!
- [AMELIE] That's enough.
- [SUGAR SNIFFLES]
You didn’t just kill my brother, Marga.
but my entire family!
[SOBS] You killed our dreams!
All our ambitions...
You took all of it away
when you killed Byron!
All of it!
[MARGA SNIFFLES]
All of that is gone, because of you.
[SUGAR CRYING] Everything we dreamed of doing!
[CRYING] Everything we planned to do once
Byron became famous is gone!
All of that is gone, because you killed him!
[POLICEMAN] Enough! Enough!
Why did you kill him, huh?!
Just answer me, why?
Huh?
If you were in a relationship,
my brother loved you.
You must’ve loved him too, right?
So why?
Why did you kill him?
[POLICEMEN] Ma'am!
- I need to know why!
- [POLICEMAN] Ma'am!
- Why did you kill him?
- [POLICEMAN] Ma'am, that's enough!
- Huh?!
- [POLICEMAN] Enough, just get her in the vehicle!
- Why?!
- [POLICEMAN] Get her away from here!
- Answer me, why did you kill him?!
- [POLICEMAN] Please get in! Ma'am, enough!
Ma'am please.
- Why did you kill him, Marga!
- [POLCEMAN] Ma'am follow us to the precinct.
[AMELIE] Enough Sugar, enough!
- Why?
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- I need to know, Marga please!
- Enough!
Sugar, please let her go.
[SUGAR] Just answer me why!?
Sugar that's enough!
She already surrendered, right?
Stop it already!
She'll only go to prison!
My brother was killed, Amelie!
He was murdered!
So what do you want?
You want to kill her too, huh?!
My brother's life was taken, Amelie!
She should pay for it with her life!
[AMELIE SNIFFLES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES AND CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[SUGAR SOBS]
[LEONA] Liv, dear.
[LEONA] You have a visitor.
[LIV] Dad?
Dad.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I went straight here
while my friend is still finding out the
details from Marga's lawyer.
How about Amelie? How is she doing?
I also don't know.
I wish I could say that
they'll be fine.
That it’ll get better
But,
Marga committed a crime.
The...
Her framing me, I can let slide.
But what she did to Jigger and Byron...
she needs to pay for that.
Well, even if I wanted to
be happy for Sugar…
[STAMMERS] I can't do it!
Because,
in exchange for the justice she deserves,
Amelie lost a mother.
[LEONA] But at least, my dear,
the truth is out.
Now, it's easier for your dad
to clear his name.
Even if I wanted to be
happy, I couldn't either.
For many years,
Marga gave everything to me.
But...
I could never reciprocate
the love she gave me.
That's why...
That's what pushed her to
look for somebody else.
She met Byron.
She did what...
she did.
[LEONA] Come on, let's head inside.
It's a good thing you found us.
We moved here to Liv's grandma's house.
Because, well, things have been a bit
complicated these past few days.
So we can forget.
Come on,
let's go inside.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
- [ROLDAN] Dear!
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[LOURDES] Sugar!
- [ROLDAN] Dear!
- Mom!
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Sugar!
Sugar?
Is it true that Marga is Byron's killer?
Sir Jigger confessed.
He admitted to what he knew.
And he says he has evidence
that he’s willing to show.
So that woman won't be
able to escape.
Even if she denies it.
Everything is okay.
It's alright.
[LOURDES] Byron, my son.
Wherever you are,
I hope you're happy now.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
Because justice has been served.
- [LOURDES SIGHS]
- [SUGAR SOBS]
[ROLDAN] Dear,
thank you for not giving
up for Byron's sake.
[AMELIE] What is that, Mom?
- Attorney...
- Attorney, can you leave us?
Mom?
I signed my confession.
I did it.
I’m the one who raised
Byron’s steroid dosage.
I ordered Jigger to
frame your dad.
And I was the one who shot Jigger.
What did Attorney say?
Did she cut a deal with the police?
How long?
How many years will
you be in prison for?
25 years?
20, if I'm on my best behavior.
It doesn't matter.
I won't last six months in prison.
[AMELIE] No, no, no.
Mom.
Mom, don't say that.
You're a fighter.
You can't give up.
I'll do everything.
And yes, you made mistakes in the past.
But you regret them now, right?
We'll find a way.
I'll look for another lawyer.
I'll find someone who can help us.
I'll find someone who can lower your
sentence, Mom. I'll do everything.
You don't have to Amelie.
You don't have to.
20 years.
I'll be 40 then, Mom.
[SNIFFLES]
I'll have children by then.
You might be a grandmother by then.
[SNIFFLES]
We'll visit you.
You know,
I struggled when I was pregnant with you.
They said you weren't holding
on strong enough.
I almost had a miscarriage twice.
So when you came out, I promised myself
I wouldn’t let us be apart.
[CHUCKLES] I think I overdid it a little.
[MARGA CHUCKLES]
[MUTTERS] No, no, no.
[SNIFFLES] Mom.
You were just protecting me.
I know.
And that destroyed us.
You hated me.
No.
[CRYING]
[SNIFFLES] I'm sorry.
The more you despised me,
the more I wanted to control you.
And I'm sorry I was too
strict with you, Amelie.
I'm so sorry.
You're now free.
You're free from me.
You no longer have responsibilities
to be a daughter to me.
Stop it. Stop saying that, Mom.
Stop saying that.
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
That I disappear from your life?
You made mistakes.
[SNIFFLES]
You made mistakes,
but that will never erase the
fact that you're my mother.
Never, Mom.
Never.
[SNIFFLES]
[MARGA SOBS AND MUTTERS]
[MARGA SOBS]
You're now free, my dear.
Do everything you want to do.
Get a tattoo,
find a man who will love you.
Go ahead and do everything
I told you not to do,
since you don’t have a mom
to stop you anymore.
No more!
- [MARGA SNIFFLES]
- [AMELIE] Stop saying that.
- [MARGA SOBS]
- [AMELIE] Stop it, Mom.
Mom, we'll fight this together, remember?
[AMELIE] I'm going to help you. I'll help you!
I'll do everything.
Mom, I promise. I'll help you.
Officer,
I'm ready.
No.
Wait.
Wait, Mom.
Let me help you. Wait.
Mom, wait.
Wait.
[SNIFFLES]
Amelie?
I heard what happened.
I thought you might need
someone beside you.
Even just as a friend for now.
[PHONE RINGING]
Mom?
[ELIZA OVER THE PHONE] Your driver
reported to me,
you went to that damn Amelie.
Stay away from her.
Her entire family is an embarrassment.
Amelie I-
Amelie, I'm sorry.
Luke, your mom's right.
No, she isn't.
I should stay away from you.
I bring nothing but shame to you guys.
- Let me be.
- Amelie.
Please, you need a friend.
You're not that friend.
My God!
So it is true, Amelie?
You have a sex video?
You are disgusting!
Your obscenity is all over the internet!
You're going to leave us?
Huh? You're going back to
your ex Auntie Leona?
Is that it?
Handcuff Mrs. Baltazar.
You're now free! You're free from me.
You no longer have responsibilities
to be a daughter to me.
Amelie, Amelie!
Amelie!
Amelie, get down!
Dear, dear!
Dear.
What are you doing?
Let me be, Dad.
It's no use.
Dear.
I don't want to live anymore.
Dear, that's not true!
I'm here now.
Your dad's here, I won't
abandon you, Dear.
You'll leave me too.
- Dear!
- You'll leave me too.
Dear.
Even if they all abandon you,
my dear, I-
I'm still here.
I'm sorry Dear, if...
that I left.
But Dear,
I promise,
you'll never be alone.
I won't abandon you.
What happened to us?
Why did this happen to us?
Go get some rest.
So much has happened today.
But you still did a good job.
How was that a good job?
We solved someone else's case.
Zach's killer is still on the loose.
[DESMOND] What the hell is this?
[DESMOND] Why are you doing
this to me?!
[POLICEMAN] Sir, don't resist!
Don't you know who I am!?
You have no idea just how
powerful my connections are!
I don't need to know!
Do you want to lose
your job tomorrow?
Garcia!
What's his case?
He's so cocky.
Pedophilia.
Child Sex Trafficking.
With how many kids he's harmed,
look at how pathetic he is now.
The team found boxes of photos
of the children they exploited.
That man looks familiar.
What's his name again?
Desmond Dillara.
I'll be here, sir.
So that's why.
Do you know him?
He's a close friend of Leonard.
Leonard Zamora, Zach's father.
[SCOFFS]
Please contact Inspector Juro.
Yes, ma'am.
This one is too young!
That's right, ma'am.
Those are different kids?
Damn.
[GEORGIA EXHALES]
Inspector.
We just wanted to ask you something.
Just to confirm, Desmond Dillara
was a friend of Zach’s father, right?
The one we interviewed before,
about the case?
Thank you for coming.
Sir Leonard asked me
to talk to you.
Please have a seat.
- [JURO CLEARS HIS THROAT]
- [DESMOND GRUNTS]
Are you absolutely sure with
what you saw and heard?
That Yana was indeed the person
that Zach was talking to outside the bar?
Yes, of course.
I would never forget that face.
You know, I just can't believe
that such an angelic face
will threaten Zach.
I don't even know what Zach did to Yana.
Uh,
I know Zach to be a perfect gentleman.
Yes.
Why, what's wrong?
He was arrested.
Alleged pedophile.
Here are the pictures
of their victims.
Here.
Wait a minute.
I recognize this kid.
You recognize that kid?
I know him really well.
I used to play with him back then.
I even lived with him.
He was like a brother to me.
Hang on, Inspector.
Who is he?
That's Zach.
Zach Zamora.
Zach Zamora was abused as a child?
[LIV VOICEOVER] Genetics tell us that we are
our mini versions of our parents.
If our parents are monsters,
are we doomed to become one?
Did you know Zach
was abused as a child?
Who abused him?
I want there to be a witness
to what’s about to happen.
Don’t put this phone call down, Liv.
It’s Uncle Leonard.
He’s being accused of child abuse.
[JURO AND LEONARD GRUNTING]
You’re an animal.
Go ahead and die
you animal!
it’s Uncle Leonard!
Me and Inspector Juro found
out something about him.
[JURO AND LEONARD GRUNTING]
[GUN COCKS]