[GEMINI BY JULIE ANNE SAN JOSE PLAYING]
This is the combined affidavit of Yana Chua,
Sugar Alvarez and Amelie Baltazar.
It says that you gave them all eye drops
so that you can avoid suspicion!
So that the three of them get all the blame
even if you were the only one
who put eye drops in Zach's water.
She's playing tricks on us, guys.
She's toying with us!
She's breaking up our Squad!
As long as you're allied with her,
we will never be whole again!
This situation has turned very toxic.
Everything-
Our friendship!
You're right, Sugar.
Who needs toxic friends?
You're both hopeless.
I'm just glad we're no longer friends.
Is this all?!
This isn't even half of what I was asking for!
That's really the only money
I can provide right now.
Take it, so we
can live in peace!
Give me all the money I asked for
if you don't want to rest in peace!
Don’t tell me what to do!
[JIGGER GROANS]
[MARGA GROANS]
[GUNSHOT]
- [JIGGER GROANS]
- [MARGA GROANS]
[AMELIE GASPS]
Oh my god!
[MARGA] Amelie!
Amelie?
Amelie.
Mom.
Mom, I saw everything.
I saw everything!
You killed him!
Now that you've caught me,
will you kill me also?
Huh?
[GEMINI BY JULIE ANNE SAN JOSE PLAYING]
[YANA VOICEOVER] Betrayal. Disloyalty.
Untrustworthiness.
All of these runs in the blood.
And my father drowns me in it.
Yana, is this true?
Hector is a fugitive?
[GROANS] I feel so annoyed at myself.
I just want to call A.
But I don’t know where to start because
Liv is still upset with me.
Maybe I should just call Liv.
I just need to explain to
her everything that’s happ-
Yana, stop involving
yourself with them.
Leave them alone.
They are very unlucky that they
have a dad like Hector.
[CHARLIE SCOFFS]
He’s so smug.
He drove us away
like we're stray cats!
How about now?
Look who’s acting like...
[CHUCKLES] a stray cat now?
Dad.
Dad, stop.
Stop talking like that.
Dad, you also went through the same thing.
[YANA SIGHS]
And I know what Liv and A are going
through right now as well, okay?
I know what it is like when you
feel uncertain about your future.
I also know how it feels when you fear
that your dad could be jailed anytime.
[YANA EXHALES SHARPLY]
No daughter should have to go through that.
And I also feel sorry for Uncle Hector.
Remember? He even welcomed
me into their home.
Dad.
Yana.
If I've done anything wrong,
I did it to give you a better life.
That’s entirely different from being a murderer.
Well, now that you caught me, alright.
Shoot me!
Just don’t shoot me in the face.
I don’t want to die like that.
But go ahead, kill me now.
Go ahead and kill me!
You can go ahead and kill me
like how you killed him.
[STAMMERS] What are you talking about?
I saw everything.
You killed him!
What did you see, Amelie?
You killed him.
You killed him, Mom.
I saw it!
You- [STUTTERS]
You’re confused, Amelie.
You must just be imagining
what you think you saw.
Huh? Are you drunk? Are you-
Stop gaslighting me!
I saw everything!
You killed him!
Shhh!
Stay quiet, Amelie.
I did not intend to do that.
It was self-defense!
He planned to kill me, so I went
ahead and killed him instead!
Mom.
Why would Jigger plan to kill you? Huh?
Why?
Jigger killed Byron.
Your dad witnessed it.
He just wasn’t able to tell the police
because he lost the evidence.
He wanted to set up your
dad as Byron’s killer!
Wait, wait.
Wait.
[WHISPERS] Wait.
Okay.
If what you’re saying is true, why
does Dad have to hide? Huh?
Why did you have to bribe that Jigger?
What is happening, Mom?
What is really happening?
Amelie, Jigger tried to ruin
your dad’s reputation.
He’s also the only one who can fix it.
But he’s got many demands!
He is asking for a huge amount of money.
I asked if we could negotiate.
But he wouldn’t agree.
He threatened to kill us!
So I took the gun.
I did not intend to shoot him, Amelie!
Calm down.
Okay, calm down.
If you’re saying that this is self-defense,
then why don’t we report this to the police?
Let’s ask help from them!
I will contact Attorney.
I will go with you.
I will go with you, and let us ask for help.
Attorney Vivero can take care of this, Mom.
- I don’t want to go to jail.
- Why?!
- No.
- I can’t do it.
She can-
Attorney Vivero can take care of this.
She is good.
She can fight for you.
I will go with you.
Amelie, let us please go home.
It’s not safe here.
Please.
Someone might overhear us.
Please. Let’s go home.
How about Jigger’s body, Mom?
His body?
It’s too dangerous to go back, Amelie.
Let’s just go home, please.
Come with me.
[AMELIE] Mom.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Dad?
[HECTOR] Hello, Liv.
Dad?
I’m sorry if I was only able to call you now.
My God.
Thank God.
Are you safe there?
Will no one overhear our conversation?
Ah, yes.
Yes, Dad.
Yes.
I just want to tell you that they
are accusing me wrongly.
I am innocent.
I did not kill Byron.
I know. I know, Dad.
[LIV] Where are you now?
Do you need anything?
Anything.
Food?
Clothing?
Or anything?
I’m doing fine here.
It’s safer if you’re there.
It’s dangerous here.
Don’t go out of the house.
Are - [STUTTERS]
Are you sure, Dad?
Were you able to talk to your lawyer?
Not yet.
But someone else is helping me.
But if I cannot go to where
you are, what will I do?
What can I do for you?
Liv.
You can talk to the inspector
handling my case.
Ask them
[HECTOR] to investigate further.
My fingerprints are not present in the
paraphernalia they got from my locker.
Because I did not touch those things.
Alright, Dad.
Okay.
Last stop. Let’s go!
Someone’s there.
There’s blood!
Hey! Don’t approach!
There’s blood! Someone call for an ambulance!
[LOURDES] Sugar?
I already bought groceries,
and also some of your snacks.
Wow! Thank you, dear.
How have you been?
- Mom.
- Oh?
When you go back
home to the province,
please explain to Kiko why
I can't go home yet.
With everything that's going on with Liv,
and with my job-
Come here, Sugar.
It's a good thing that you work hard,
but don't forget to relax.
I have an idea.
[SUGAR] What are you up to, Mom?
Hold on.
What if we do what we used to do?
I think I know what you're talking about.
We used to watch movies-
Movies! Yes!
Okay then, but,
I want to watch horror!
I want to watch something to make me giddy!
Okay, alright then!
I'll go ahead and pick.
Okay, okay.
Here! My friend told me this is good.
I think you're forgetting something, Mom.
Huh?
This is incomplete!
[LOURDES] I almost forgot!
- Here.
- Ohh!
Thanks for letting me choose.
I should be the one
thanking you, Mom.
At least I got to enjoy
my rest day, right?
Yes! And I got to spend it with you!
- Right?
- That's true!
Isn't it cool, Mom?
Hmm?
There are some things
we never get tired of.
Like us bonding!
Yes.
Inspector.
I was able contact my dad.
Did he tell you where he is?
No. He didn’t tell me.
We only talked for a short time,
then the line was cut.
But he asked me to do something.
He said he’s innocent.
And that he was being framed up.
And I believe him.
It's expected for you to say that.
Of course, he’s your dad.
Uhm. The…
Please check the fingerprints on
the evidence you gathered.
Here.
Here’s a copy of the ID
with my father’s fingerprint.
Please compare that to the fingerprint
found in the paraphernalia.
That will prove that my dad is
innocent of the accusations.
Thank you, Miss Baltazar.
But even before you arrived,
the result already came out for
the requested fingerprint analysis.
We confirmed whose fingerprints
were found on the paraphernalia.
So whose fingerprints are those?
It’s your dad’s.
They belong to Hector Baltazar.
The money that was found at the
crime scene has been checked.
Only Mendoza’s fingerprints were found.
It’s possible that the assailant was wearing gloves.
What does that mean?
Robbery but they left behind the money?
Or maybe a double-crossing took place?
Which led to Mendoza being killed?
If he doesn't survive this operation,
he will be the third murder victim
who's connected to the gym.
Inspector Catapang mentioned that there’s
no such thing as coincidence.
Just unsolved mysteries.
Hmm.
Don’t you think all of these
killings are connected?
Byron Alvarez.
Zach Zamora.
Jigger Mendoza.
Hector Baltazar got jealous of Byron Alvarez.
He killed him.
Zach cheated on Liv.
How about this one?
What do you think his offense could be?
Hector. This is Attorney Silverio.
Hello.
Attorney.
Have a seat.
Alfred already told me about your problem.
I will help you.
We will talk to the authorities.
What?
I need to surrender?
Yes.
Attorney, I don’t want to go to jail.
We can post bail.
Just like you said, you were
only framed, right?
It’s better to talk and cooperate than to keep hiding.
Just trust the process.
Attorney Silverio is great at what he does.
But first, we need to talk to your family.
Liv.
I’m happy to see you both again.
[HECTOR] I thought I would just
be hiding away for life.
But Attorney Silverio promised
that he would help fix this.
He will help me.
We can all be together again.
Where, Dad?
At the jail’s visitors’ area?
Liv. Stop being a pessimist.
Miss Baltazar, your father said he is innocent.
It seems he also convinced
you to believe his lies.
Liv, what’s the problem?
Hector.
Attorney.
Do you believe their false
accusations against me?
Don’t you trust your dad?
I do, Dad.
I trust you.
I even followed your advice.
I had the evidence checked for your fingerprints.
Dad.
The fingerprints they found were all yours.
That’s impossible!
The results of the lab report came out.
Your fingerprints are all over the evidence.
On the black-
the black bag,
on the plastic sachet.
They are probably mistaken.
Maybe they are working
with the one trying to frame me.
They’re just trying to pin it on me.
Why would they pin it on you?
Who did you mess with?
I have no idea!
You have no idea?
Or maybe you’re just pretending you
don’t know so we can protect you?
Liv.
Dad.
Did you kill Byron Alvarez?
[BAG ZIPPER CLOSES]
[AMELIE] Nova, where’s Mom?
Where is she?
[AMELIE] Mom!
Mom, what is this?
Where are you going?
- [AMELIE] What is this?
- I’m just going somewhere.
What is this?
Where are you going?
Are you trying to escape?
Liv.
Look at me.
I didn't kill Byron.
I didn't kill anybody.
I have no idea why the evidence points to me.
But I hope you know that
I will never lie to you.
Dad, I believed you.
Mom and I believed in you.
Dad, we fought for you.
My friendship with my friends is
ruined because I chose to believe you.
Turns out, you were just using me.
[EXHALES]
Alright.
[SOBS] I will prove to you that I am innocent.
I will surrender today.
I will face the cases against me.
But Liv, I just have one thing to ask of you.
Please do not abandon me.
You’re my only source of hope.
I need you by my side.
Liv.
Liv, dear?
[LINE BUSY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Liv.
I just want to tell you this.
You know that I have known your
dad for so long, right?
Don’t tell me that you believe him?
You know that I have known
your dad for a while now.
I know when he is lying.
And when he is telling the truth.
I can feel his sincerity this time.
Do you really believe that someone
is trying to frame him?
Yes.
Who was furious at him
before everything went down?
Wasn’t it Marga?
I just need to go somewhere.
Mom, come on!
- I just have somewhere to go.
- Where are you going?
Are you trying to escape?
Stop it.
Just let me go, Amelie!
Mom, where are you going?
Stop it!
What?
I’m -  [CRIES]
I’m not meant for prison.
Mom, you won’t be sent to jail, okay?
It’s clear that what you
did was for self-defense.
You can never be sure, Amelie.
What if they target me?
What if the cops make
an example out of me?
That’s what they’re doing
to your dad, right?
You know the poor—
they take pleasure in seeing rich
people like us behind bars.
It makes them feel better!
Mom, please.
Dad has abandoned us.
Are you also going to abandon me?
Mom!
You’re already a grown-up, Amelie.
You can take care of yourself.
Mom, you don’t really care about me, right?
Maybe you don’t really care about me.
Because ever since...
I was a child, you have done
nothing but control me.
You control me in everything that I do.
You treat me like I’m a doll.
A living doll that you can control!
Why don’t you just admit it, Mom?
Just face the fact that you
don’t really love me!
You don’t really love me!
You don’t care for me!
You’re so weak.
You’re not strong enough
to be a mother to me.
Because you are not capable.
You can’t do anything.
Go ahead.
Leave.
I am so scared, Amelie.
- Just go, Mom.
- Dear...
I am capable of being your mom.
I can do it.
But I am scared.
I need your help, Amelie.
[SUGAR] Inspector.
Alright, go ahead.
Do you have news about Hector Baltazar?
Were you able to locate him?
Unfortunately, not yet.
We have a lot on our plates.
We also visited someone at the hospital.
You know him.
Who?
It’s Jigger Mendoza.
Isn’t he your supervisor at the gym?
He was found lying on the ground and bleeding.
He lost a lot of blood, according
to the doctors in the hospital.
Right now, he hasn’t regained consciousness.
[STUTTERS] What’s the name of the hospital?
At the Santa Eloisa Mission Hospital.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
Hey Charlie. What made you come here?
Uhh...
I just want to check in with you.
Have you heard the news about our friend?
The police are looking for him.
Charlie, this isn’t a good time.
I have a lot on my plate.
I’m sorry.
Are you busy?
It seems that you have a visitor.
Do you need anything?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
I need to borrow some money.
I just need 50,000 pesos.
It’s for my daughter’s partial tuition
fee this coming semester.
I’m sorry, Charlie.
Unfortunately, I do not have
extra money to lend you.
Maybe next time.
Okay.
Make sure to send me a text
first before visiting.
So Hector’s been hiding here.
Jackpot!
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[SUGAR] Sir. You’re not yet in heaven, okay?
I may look like an angel, but it’s just me.
[JIGGER BREATHES HEAVILY]
Sir.
Sugar.
Hmm?
I have something to confess.
Come on, Sir.
Don’t say anything.
I’m sorry, but you’re not my type.
[BOTH CHUCKLES]
- [SUGAR CHUCKLES] I’m just kidding.
- [JIGGER GROANING]
You must be hurting, I’m sorry.
Sorry!
I’m just trying to make you laugh
so you will recover quickly.
What happened to you?
It’s Marga.
Ma’am Marga?
A’s mom?
She shot me.
She did this to you?
We must tell the police.
Wait.
Wait a minute, Sir.
She - [STUTTERS]
She also killed-
Killed who?
What?
Sir!
[NURSE] Code Blue!
- Code Blue!
- Sir Jigger!
- Please page Dr. Castro!
- Who?!
[SUGAR] Who else did Ma’am Marga kill?
[NURSE] Please wait outside, Miss.
Hold on, hold on.
Who else did Ma’am Marga kill?
- [NURSE] Step outside, Miss.
- Sir! Sir!
[SUGAR] Wait! Wait!
- You can't be in here!
- We're not yet done!
[NURSE] You can't be in here, miss!
- [SUGAR] Who did Ma'am Marga kill?
- Byron.
Answer me!
- It was Byron.
- Huh?!
- You can't be in here!
- Hold on!
You are not allowed to stay here-
Okay, Inspector. I'll just wait
for your deal agreement.
Once I have signed it, then I'll tell
you where Hector is hiding.
Yes.
Alright. Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, dear!
How long have you
been standing there?
You're fast!
I brought you food, Dad.
You might be hungry from
all of your betrayals.
Thank you, dear.
That's so sweet of you-
[YANA] Dad.
I know you're doing everything to survive.
Even if I didn't want to do what
you wanted me to, I did it for you.
But, Dad, this?
Dad, Uncle Hector
is now at rock bottom,
but you're still going to betray
him to Inspector Georgia?
Dad, Uncle Hector did nothing wrong.
On the contrary,
he did everything
he could to help us!
I didn't want to betray Sugar
and Amelie back then.
I justified it to myself
because I thought one of
them tried to kill me.
And with Liv. I forced
myself to believe
she involved me in the posioning
of Zach using her eye drops.
But you? What is your
justification for this, Dad?
What did Uncle Hector ever do to you?
What?!
Tell me where Uncle Hector is hiding?
Dear, you don't have to-
Dad, where is he hiding?
You have to tell me!
I need to repay, Uncle Hector!
I need to repay Liv and Amelie.
You have to tell me where Uncle Hector is!
[CHARLIE CHOKES YANA]
When I tell you
it doesn't matter,
stop prying about it!
- Dad.
- Do you understand?
- Ha?
- Dad, it hurts.
[YANA VOICE OVER] Behind every great
daughter, is a truly amazing dad.
In Dad's case, I wonder
what greatness I'd achieve.
Mrs. Baltazar shot Jigger?
That's what he told me right before
his blood pressure rose.
Let's go and arrest her!
Marga! You animal!
Get out of there!
Sugar!
What's wrong with you, huh?
[MARGA AND SUGAR GROANING AND GRUNTING]
Marga Baltazar was the one
who shot the victim.
Go and get a warrant!
Right now!
I can't just sit here while my daughters
are going through something.
The police are still looking for you!
They need my support.
[AMELIE SHOUTING]
Hey! What's your problem?
What is your problem?!
She’s the one who killed my brother!