Psychopath Diary
Heo Taek Soo, you're with the sergeant, right?
Yes.
Yook Dong Sik appeared nearby. I'm sure he's going after the sergeant. Where are you right now?
That's... Well, that's...
The south gate! We're at the south gate!
South gate of the park?
He says they're at the park's south gate!
Over that way! Go!
Jang Chil Seong
Yes, Chil Seong.
The police are on their way. They're here!
Okay.
The police are headed this way. Let's get out of here first.
This way.
No, that way! Go! Not this way!
When they come, I'll stall them. Let's meet there.
You got it?
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry!
Let's go! Let's go!
Psychopath Diary
Episode 14
You're g-going there?
If I hide, that's the only place the police wouldn't suspect.
I don't know what you're talking about at all.
Let's go.
Go then, go. Let’s go.
I won't ask or nag you about it.
So if you had told us your exact location, we could have caught him!
Well, we were there, but when I got off the walkie-talkie with you and looked around,
Yook Dong Sik was dragging away Sunbae already!
So you threw your whole body while protecting her, and you became like this?
You don't even know.
If you had come a little bit later with backup,
both of us, by that punk...
R-Right, Sunbae?
Anyway, we were inattentive this time, but don't worry.
We will make sure Yook Dong Sik doesn't appear near here again.
Of course. Just leave it to me.
Chief, you should go back now.
If your back is bad, leave the tough jobs to Officer Cha.
Don't worry.
I'll see you out.
- Officer Cha, let's see them off.
- I can't.
Come with me!
You can come out now!
Th-The things is... where should I start explaining it to you?
You don't need to do that, Mr. Bingo-is-a-Dog's-Name.
Stay here comfortably. You know the saying, "It's the darkest under the lamp."
They'll never even dream that you'd be hiding out here.
Yes.
Just wait a second. I'll get you something to sleep in.
So this is Bo Gyeong's room.
The only men's clothes we have are Dad's.
Then the one who left the message at the escape cafe room is...
It must obviously have been him.
I'm certain he was watching us from nearby.
He's around us?
Then, since you know the contents of the diary thoroughly,
if we pare down and compare the people who correspond with the profiling—
There's no need for that.
- Pardon?
- I... at the prison,
it was for a second, but I remembered it. In a flash.
R-Really?
Just when I was about to remember his face, it cut out, but
now, I've started to get my memory back,
so finding that guy is only a matter of time.
After he was arrested, I thought it would calm down, but an escape and a hostage situation on top of that?
I think there will be some damage to the company image as well.
The company is one thing, but maybe Ji Hoon nearly got attacked by that guy before, too?
That's right then! Now that I think about it, it gives me goosebumps! Right?
What's going on here?
We have stocks in the company, too, so we had some things to discuss.
Since the case has gotten bigger, it's starting to affect the sales for the company, too,
and there was a consensus that we may need some type of an emergency management system.
We wanted to see you over Ji Hoon's reinstatement matter.
He's also a victim when it comes down to it.
Being sent away when he's not a sinner is a little—
Yook Dong Sik and Yuseung Biomedi cases are separate issues.
Director Seo Ji Hoon's disciplinary action and personnel action was just,
and there won't be a reversal of the decision.
Well, we could call him back, depending on the atmosphere.
If problems continue to arise internally, it will be too much for you to manage alone.
That won’t happen.
Time will tell.
Sergeant Sim Bo Gyeong
Seo In Woo
- Yes?
- Are you okay?
I saw the news. What happened?
Well, I'm okay.
Did Dong Sik really cause a hostage situation involving you?
Really?
Yes.
How could he do such...
But Bo Gyeong, to be honest,
I still find it really hard to believe that he's someone who could do something like that.
The Dong Sik I know would never do that.
Maybe there was a mistake?
If there's anything you know—
No! (informally)
Pardon?
I'm a bit busy. Let's talk later.
Bo Gyeong
Why don't you just advertise?!
- Dong Sik, red is not it.
- Damn.
Boring Day
What are you doing?
Huh? You never know, so...
Never know, my butt.
Oh! It's Yook Dong Sik! Yook Dong Sik!
- O-Over there, doesn't that look like Yook Dong Sik?
- I can't see.
- Over there, doesn't he look like him?
- I can't see him.
- Can't you see someone over there?
- No.
- What?
- I don't see anything.
How can you not see?
- What? Tell me again.
- I don't see anyone.
- What?
- I don't see.
- One more time!
- I don't see anything!
- That's your future.
Sunbae!
Did I tell you our house is drafty?
My mom got a cold. I'll go take her to the hospital quickly.
Then I'll take you.
Hey! What are you doing now?
You're working right now!
You should guard this place!
So what I'm saying is...
- Repeat after me. Invincible.
- Invincible!
- Alert!
- Alert.
- I'll never
- make the mistake of
- losing Yook Dong Sik
- ever again!
- Never!
- I'm Jeong Won.
- I'm Jeong Won!
You should keep a watch out there!
Boring Day
I was so nervous I'd get caught.
Now, we can just head over there, right?
Yes. Since it's where everything began.
The construction site where I attempted to kill myself and witnessed that guy trying to kill the homeless man.
If we go there and reconstruct the situation back then, I'm sure I'll remember something.
The building already went up. It's been completed.
When did they finish building it?
I know! What do we do?
If my memory flashes back one more time, I'm sure I'd remember his face.
Then if we look for another location or people that can jog your past memory—
Seriously, we don't have that much time. We need to get it done in one go.
You could say this is my specialty.
Now, let's see. You said that when you got hit by the car,
you hit your head,
and your memory flew away, right?
Then you should just recreate the situation and... Whack!
"Huh? Huh?" Wouldn't you then
remember something in a flash while saying that?
What kind of solution is that?
Dong Sik, it's not a good idea.
No, right?
It's do or die anyway!
You have to catch that predator quickly and have him arrested!
Hyungnim! Let's get it!
What now?
Now, here.
Just watch me and follow.
Now, the car comes. It's here! It's here!
You don't need to be afraid. The car—
This is really not the way. You know that, right?
Oh, of course I do.
When it hits, you should just fly through the air a bit
and like this...
Hurry up and stop him!
Hyungnim! It's easy! Come on, let's get it!
It's crushed.
I'm sorry...
Yook Republic
As expected, the police are keeping a watch.
By chance, if involving your family doesn't sit well with you—
If I think about what trouble I must have put them through all this time, I feel bad, so—
You left such an easy way
and you insist on taking the unpaved road. Seriously...
Still,  my family are the ones who know me best before I lost my memory.
I'm sure they'll be of some help in getting my memory back.
Also ...
I missed them, too.
Chil Seong, is there a place where Dong Sik can meet with his family in secret?
Let's see now...
Let's get it.
- Where?
- You know.
Please be comfortable. And sit comfortably, too, huh?
What kind of tea would you like?
Tea?
Oh, it's okay. It's fine.
I thought Sergeant Sim was no-nonsense. How come she called us to a place like this?
Dong Sik!
- Dong Sik!
- Noona!
Have you been... well?
Dong Sik!
Oh, Dong Sik...
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
Go! Go!
Get out!
- So... before your memory loss, you came upon the diary?
- Yes.
Did you see the culprit's face at the construction site?
Probably.
Well, sorry for butting in while you're talking,
but logically, what you physically lost, a physical shock
will bring it back is my personal opinion.
Don't worry about him.
Oh, right!
So as I requested,
is there anything that could bring his memory back?
So I did bring something with me,
but it's been a while since Dong Sik left to go live alone.
So I'm not sure he'll remember. These...
Take a look.
But at that time, why did you go to the construction site in the middle of the night?
- Pardon?
- That's right.
I thought you went straight home after the birthday party.
Oh, you went somewhere really odd!
That day, he was with you, you said, Dad.
Give it back to me!
What are you so sorry about all the time?
Because you act like a nice person all the time, you get taken advantage of!
What a pitiful punk.
You... you... No way, you tried to...
So what happened is...
I, I can't really remember well...
Were you having bad thoughts?
No, right?
Oh, n-not at all.
No. No.
That day, something bad happened at work,
so he probably went to get some air. Right?
Yes.
Oh, you could remember something if you look at this album.
Look carefully.
It was all because of me.
All this trouble was because of me, a lacking father.
No, Father.
It's a new item.
Do you remember something now that you're looking through it?
This person is...
What happened because of me, I have to make right.
I'm sorry, Dong Sik.
Father...
This parasite-like thing, how dare you?
Please save me!
To be honest, I have a secret hobby.
Whenever I see weak people, it makes me feel sick,
so I want to get rid of them completely.
Are you totally blank and unable to remember a thing?
Is there any chance of it ever coming back?
About the Yuseung Biomedi matter, you nearly took the fall for the whole thing.
If something like that happens, it must make you feel helpless.
I think I have the right to know at least that much while lending you 100 million.
Will it get resolved by handing over money?
You have to make sure the person can't threaten you again.
Whatever it takes.
I won't leave you alone... Seo In Woo.
Dong Sik?
My... memory came back.
Yook Republic
- Oh, hello.
- You came!
- Hello.
- Have you eaten?
If you haven't, we'll prepare you something quickly. What are you doing, Honey?
- Oh, yes, yes.
- No, it's okay.
I was on my way to work, and I stopped by to see how you were doing.
By chance, have you heard anything about Dong Sik?
We want to know, too, but it seems like knowing nothing might be better.
I don't know.
By chance, did Dong Sik...
Bo Gyeong.
I-In Woo.
I came because I was worried. What's going on?
Well, that is...
What is it? Did something happen to our Dong Sik?
Dong Sik left a letter.
Huh?
My memory came back.
But I just can't remember the guy's face.
I must have not seen it.
Now the only thing left of my memory is my years as a pushover...
I only remember what a lacking person I was.
How could someone like me go up against a predator?
Please don't worry about what happens to me anymore.
I'm just a fool who's weak, and on top of that, a very unlucky
pushover, that's all.
Yook Republic
Don't worry too much.
He might ask me for help like the last time.  If he does, I'll make sure to let you know.
I guess that could happen, too... Please call and let me know.
By chance, if he contacts you, let me know, too.
I understand you been hiding things from me until now, but it's because I really want to hear it.
Since Dong Sik is a precious person to me, too.
Yes.
Just now he left smirking.
But why do you want me to keep an eye on that guy?
It's a letter Dong Sik left behind.
Where is he?
Hyungnim!
Our Hyungnim isn't the type to run away like this.
That's right. Dong Sik wouldn't do that.
Were you looking for me?
Actually, this letter is a fake.
Dong Sik found out
who the real culprit is.
Then... No way...
I'll go ruin that bastard immediately!
Finding evidence is first.
We put him at ease, so soon Dong Sik will make his move.
It turned out so much more boring than I thought it would be.
That's right, Yook Dong Sik. Like your usual self,
it wouldn't be all that bad to meet your fate while running away frightened.
Hello?
By chance, is this Dong Sik?
Yes, Director.
I saw the letter through Bo Gyeong.
Oh, I can't imagine what you've been going through.
That is... you’re the only one I can ask for help
so I called you.
Director S-Seo?
Yes, Dong Sik. Where are you right now?
I'll go to you.
Can I see you alone at that same bar?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I said I would capture the real culprit,
and it took me too long.
I took a long way around, but I'll make sure to catch him with Dong Sik.
Sleep some more, Dad.
I'll be back.
He just went in. Are you going to go in?
No. I have to make him wait
so that he can't bear to wait any longer.
But what if he tries to kill you?
He won't.
As long as he believes Dong Sik doesn't know his true identity, there's no need to cause a huge issue.
What if he calls the police?
- I'll get the call right away, and—
- He won't be right away.
He'll want to have his fun at my expense a little longer.
Even if I was delusional, I lived as a predator for a while.
Yes, of course. The one who knows how his mind works the best,
of course, you must be the only one.
I'll make sure to find the evidence no matter what,
so let's make sure Seo In Woo gets his punishment ourselves.
Fighting!
Why isn't he coming?
I'm sorry f-for being late.
Oh. I was worried something happened to you.
I wondered perhaps you might have re-reported me, so...
Dong Sik, do I look like that kind of a person?
I waited while having the restaurant emptied out.
Director Seo...
Sit down, first.
Since I haven't seen you in a while, I'll get you a nice drink.
- You want to borrow money so you can run away?
- Yes.
How much? Will 100 million do like the last time?
N-No. Not that much.
J-Just as much as you can.
But are you really going to run away like this?
You should find the real culprit and fight. And you should clear your name, too.
Could I... do that?
I'm just a pushover and a wuss.
How could I possibly
go up against a real psychopath murderer?
Also, even if I cleared my name,
the only place I can go back to when I have lost any sense of self,
for a pushover like me,
is probably a sewer-like reality which only makes me want to kill myself
because I’m not able to handle it.
Th-That's enough now. I understand.
But...
will you help me?
Well, yeah...
Thank you.
Director!
To me,
you're the only one I have left!
Right.
Will you have the last drink with me?
Yes, well...
just wait a bit.
I'll go ask to ready some cash.
Yes.
What a pathetic bastard.
I thought I was going to die trying to keep from killing him.
Yes, I would like to make a report.
That predator murderer, Yook Dong Sik, is right now...
What's the matter with me?
Yook Dong Sik, how dare you?
Why?
Are you angry that you got fooled by the pushover of all pushovers?
It was fun toying with me all this time, wasn't it?
I'll make it even more fun for you.
You can set your hopes high.
Grand Open
- Be safe with your guns.
- Yes, sir.
Yook Dong Sik is going after whom now?
Why are you here when you're on leave?
That's not what's important right now!
A report just came in, but the person who reported is—
It's Seo In Woo!
He got disconnected, and we can't get him on the phone.
Wh-What's the location?
It looks like from tracking his cell phone, he's on his way home.
What? Oh, okay. I got it.
Yook Dong Sik was caught on a security camera kidnapping the victim with a car.
Huh?
First, we should go to his house, right?
Let's all equip ourselves and go.
Yes!
Is it this car?
Yes! It's Seo In Woo's car.
You checked the CCTV?
Well, that is, it's all off.
Could that guy have made his move already?
What do we do? I'm certain this is an emergency situation.
What do you mean what should we do? Yook Dong Sik could be killing Seo In Woo right now!
Let's go inspect his house. At times like this, we can go into the house without a warrant.
- Without a warrant?
- Yes.
Chief, promotion, promotion.
- Promotion?
- Yes!
By now, they should have started to investigate.
I thought my heart was going to burst.
Oh, why are you acting weak all of a sudden?
But the plan was amazing.
Now it's just a matter of time before Sergeant Sim finds evidence that he's the real predator.
I hope that's the case.
It'll end up that way.
I don't think they're here.
The car is obviously here, so something must have been done here.
- Yes.
- There could be evidence, so let's search thoroughly.
Evidence. Evidence!
Thoroughly?
Damn.
Ah, why aren't they calling?
In a little bit, that real culprit will wake up!
Should I just go and take care of him for hurting my Hyungnim!
Chil Seong.
In my heart, I did that same exact thing a hundred to a thousand times.
- Let's just wait a little more.
- Yes.
Hey, hey.
Look thoroughly.
Escape Cafe
I think they failed to find any evidence.
Go out and get the car ready.
I'll be right there.
Hyungnim...
You killed people and...
you made Bo Gyeon's father like that...
and you put me in this situation?!
I just...
can't forgive you!
I have to... myself...
Hey!
Let's leave for now.
Officer Cha, look around the house.
And Officer Heo, call for back up.
Let's leave for now.
It seems like you tried to set a trap of some kind,
but I guess it didn't go the way you planned.
I'm going to kill you!
We played enough now.
Come... Seo In Woo.
This will be your last murderous act.
If there's no evidence, that we can have him create it  himself...
What are you talking about?
He'll make Seo In Woo kill him,
and he's going to film it so he can leave it as evidence.
Our Hyungnim!
He's going to make himself into bait!
B-By killing me,
what are you going to do?
I'll tell the police that I was trying to defend myself
while the predator was trying to kill me.
To disguise it as a suicide as I always do,
I want to stab you too much right now.
Will you be able to pierce through the bodysuit with a dull knife that only looks like the real thing?
Hyungnim! Hyungnim!
That car...
Hyungnim!
Ah, what's that now?
- Hey, you crazy bastard!
- Sorry, hurry up and go.
- Drive properly!
- Okay, good bye.
It's been a while, Yook Dong Sik.
Oh? You...
Oh, don't be surprised.
I came to get you, and the timing was perfect.
Chil Seong
Sergeant Sim, something bad happened again!
Someone took Hyungnim away in a car.
He was captured by Seo In Woo?
No, this time, it was someone else. I was going to follow right away,
but I lost them.
What was the license plate number?
Just thinking about how I suffered for no reason thanks to you,
I want to unburden myself completely,
but I'm holding it in because there's someone who wants to meet you.
Who is that?
Where are we going right now?
Don't worry. I'm trying to help you right now.
What?
- Seo Ji Hoon has returned to Korea?
- Yes.
He came back on the President's orders yesterday.
Are you certain?
Why are you telling me that now?
He did it secretly.
Nice to meet you. I've heard a lot about you.
Don't stand there like that and sit.
Yes.
I'm sure you heard roughly from Director Seo, so I'll make this short.
I know what an unfair situation you were put in.
That means you know about Director Seo In Woo's identity...
Thank you for coming out. I'm Sergeant Sim Bo Gyeong.
What was the urgent matter you needed to see me about?
It's about Mr. Yook Dong Sik.
That person hasn't been caught yet, right?
But what does that have to do with me?
Someone took him,
and when we checked the plates, it was Director Seo Ji Hoon's car.
Where is he right now? Director Seo seems to be out of the house, too.
You wanted to see me over that?
You should ask the company about things like this.
I heard from Chief Park that you were told to keep an eye on Yook Dong Sik.
It was part of my job at the audit team.
I didn't know Section Chief Yook Dong Sik was a murderer, but...
Well, he acted suspiciously enough at the office, too, and—
The murderer is someone else.
The one who killed the last victim, Park Moon Seok, was that guy, too.
You know something, don't you?
I'm sorry, but I don't think there's anything I can help you with.
I'll catch the real culprit, so you don't need to help me.
Just tell me where Seo Ji Hoon is.
You know that your son, Seo In Woo, is the predator?
President, then it's not too late now to tell the police and...
I'm sorry.
I guess you misunderstood my intention to help.
I'll help you leave the country, Assistant ManagerYook.
So you can change your identity and start a new life.
N-New life?
If you want to play, play. Live however you wish.
There will be no shortage of financial support.
But, other than me, you must cut off all your relationships.
Given your situation, is this something you need to think about?
If you take this with you, you'll be able to live the kind of life you've only dreamed about.
If you reject it, while being chased like now,
you'll go back to prison and rot for the rest of your life.
Choose.
You're the one who should be making your choice.
- What?
- Let it be known that your son is a murderer, and stop him.
If not, while leaving him to keep on killing people, you can choose to end up suffering by his hands.
Just because you keep me under control, you think he will stop?
I know him well.
He will never be able to
stop killing others of his own volition.
President, the guards have all been...
What happened? No way, Seo In Woo didn't...
Just stay put.
Got it?
I asked if you got it!
Why did you summon Ji Hoon back?
Didn't I tell you?
That I'll call for him if I think you can't handle it by yourself?
I think I told you I'll take care of it myself.
I already gave you enough chances.
After killing some kid eight years ago,
you trembled like a leaf.
I thought you matured after all this time.
I might seem lacking to you, but then and now,
I've taken care of things well, and I will continue to do so.
The fundamental of business is lowering the risks.
So?
How will you lower a risk like me?
I heard everything from Father. That you're that serial murderer.
Why are you bringing that out? Put it down.
I have to be careful. You don't know what he'll do.
We have Yook Dong Sik.
If you follow my orders quietly, nothing should happen.
So you want to hold something over my head?
What can you do? You have to follow his orders obediently.
Put it down! Put it down!
Let's hand him over to the police. If not, let's just kill him!
You can cover it up, right?
Really? You think you can kill me?
This bastard showing off just because he's killed a few people...
Hey. Do you think I can't do what the likes of you can?
Did you load it?
Don't do it. Hyung, don't do it!
You even begged Yook Dong Sik to spare your life. How dare you point a gun at me?
In Woo...
I, I'm sorry.
Evil Nightmare
What are you doing now?
Please let Ji Hoon live.
Then I'll give you everything you want.
What is it that I want?
Daehan Securities, subsidiaries, real estate, and slush fund, everything.
All this time, what did you tell me I had to do in order to get what I want?
You told me I have to be stronger than everyone else,
that I should be able to step on anyone.
But because of a weak bastard like him, you want to hand me over everything?
That's right. Have everything.
Have whatever you want, and I won't bother with anything you choose to do,
so please... just let Ji Hoon...
Evil Nightmare
Where did you hide Yook Dong Sik?
Psychopath Diary