Psychopath Diary
How can you prove that you are the predatory murderer?
Episode 8
You'll find out soon
since you'll probably find a body today.
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Yook Dong Sik.
You...
Issues in Current Events
- Should we begin?
- Yes.
- For your husband as well, the isolation ward will be safer.
- Please move him carefully so that you don't wake him up.
- Yes.
Where's Yook Dong Sik right now?
How could you do this to me?
I was nice to you.
You were nice to me. You saved me from almost dying and comforted me. You dared to.
You dared ... you dared to pity me
as a pushover who doesn't even know my true identity.
You know now, right? I'm different from insect-like bastards like you.
I'm also a predator now.
Predator?
The Predator Murderer should know that we think alike.
He probably saw it on TV, right? Will he come find me?
Excuse me... To be honest, it's me.
- What is?
- I am...
I am that predator!
Oh, are you really? Just beg me to spare you instead
so that it's more fun to kill you.
How dare you use your head and bull*** me?
I'm telling you the truth!
Seriously...
It's the truth!
Just like you, that wench used that dense head of hers to try desperately to live.
Do you know what kind of bitch she was?
When I earned money for us, she was fine,
but when I couldn't anymore, the look in her eyes completely changed.
When she looked at that punk from the pharmaceutical company, her eyes were dripping with honey.
She dared to... like looking at an insect,
raise her eyes at me.
Every time she did that,
I beat her up a little, and then it would be calm again!
Do you know what she said to me while she died?
That I was a pitiful person.
How dare she, so rudely! Without recognizing a predator like me!
What?
You horrible...
The commercials are ending soon. Which direction should we take this broadcast?
Is that what's important right now?
- Did you track his phone?
- It's a burner cell.
We're trying to track his location, but not yet.
Exactly what kind of punk is this?
Where are you going?
There's something bothering me, so I need to go confirm it.
Hey, Sim Bo Gyeong. Sim Bo Gyeong!
Oh, Taek Soo, are you out on patrol right now?
It's good you're close by. Can you check something for me?
Huh? He's trying to kill Yook Dong Sik? Not the other way around?
What should I do? I don't like things getting complicated.
- Should I call the police?
- No.
Text me the location and leave.
Nam Seong Cheol!
Nam Seong Cheol isn't home right now. I think he left his car.
What's is the situation right now?
That Nam could be the culprit.
What? No way! He even tried to kill himself!
That. Tell me in detail.
He said he lit up charcoal in his car or something. Anyway, he's really not the one.
By chance, what if it wasn't an attempted suicide but a test run?
There's a good chance charcoal will be used in a car, too, for a forewarned murder.
- What? What kind of ...
- Let's talk later.
Show-off tendency.
If he called the broadcast station in person and even forewarned about a murder...
he'll probably want to watch
the police who are panicked and confused about what to do.
He's close by.
I dozed off for a sec!
Where is this place?
Hyungnim, are you sleeping?
Hyung—
Hyungnim!
Oh!
What do I do?
Like years ago, just like how I used to do it.
One, two...
As expected.
Hyungnim! Hyungnim!
Hyungnim!
Seriously... Oh!
B-Breathe. What do I do?
M-My lips are precious, too.
It isn't what you think, Hyungnim!
Are you coming to your senses?
S-Sim Bo Gyeong.
010-0362-0896
This is Corporal Sim Bo Gyeong.
Yes, Corporal Sim Bo Gyeong. Someone lit up charcoal to kill my hyungnim.
- Who did?
- Whoever it was...
I didn't get a good look, so I'm not sure.
- Where are you?
- This is
the rooftop of a parking structure.
And it looks like it's near the TNN TV broadcasting company.
Where this is exactly, I'm not very—
Hello. Hello?!
Where are you? We just got the location. It's within the 300-meter perimeter of the broadcast station.
I think it's Nakyeon parking structure.
I'll head over there, so please send backup.
I have to quickly finish this off.
I guess you wanted to copy me,
but to be honest, talking about being a predator and whatnot,
while hurting the weak, I've stopped doing that.
It's not fun, and it made me feel like I was becoming a loser the same as them.
So, I was going around looking for bastards like you.
Human trash who deserve to die!
No way. Are you really... the Predator Murderer?
I am. It's true.
I told you, didn't I?
How could you do something like that? When you were treated kindly!
I am... sorry.
Your wife, I meant!
I... just want to be like you.
I thought you'd understand.
No.
Even a psychopath like me
doesn't do something so... What did she ever do wrong?!
How agonized must she have felt?!
She was by your side her whole life and trusted you til the end!
How could you?!
I can't forgive bastards like you.
Never.
I'll show you... what a real predator looks like.
That's...
This is the proof that I'm the real deal.
You... It's you.
That's right. It's me.
You... What are you?
What are you, really?
You're laughing?
Old Boy
I have something to tell you here!
No!
You're making a mistake right now!
Farewell.
Dong Sik! Are you here?!
Don't move! Dong Sik, are you okay?
Please save me!
That's not...
It's the rooftop! I've caught him trying to commit murder!
It was done by Nam Seong Cheol, as expected.
Are you okay?
Back up is coming, so stay right here.
Hey, Detective Jo, take the guys and go up, and Detective Lee and the rest of you, come with me.
He knows too much about my identity. I can't let him get caught.
Before that happens, I have to kill him.
He's there! He's there! Follow him!
Where did he go? Let's split here.
Half of you go that way, and Detective Lee and the rest, come with me.
Hello? Is anyone there?
Hello!
Psychopath Diary
Are you okay?
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
Here, take the road to the suburbs.
The police, in order to arrest Nam, who escaped,
mobilized a large-scale military police force
and have installed checkpoints on all connected roads.
They have asked for the citizens to stay inside and to report Nam as soon as they see—
Damn it.
The news just now, that's you, isn't it?
That's right, so if you make a foolish move, know that you'll die.
Did you do that because someone told you to, or did you do it alone?
Shut up, and just drive.
I was just curious.
Look at this bastard. Do you think this is a joke right now?
I'm telling you I'm that Predator Murderer.
What... are you?
Ah, my apologies. It because I'm so scared.
But, if it's not something you did because someone told you to,
why did you do such thing?
It’s a welcome drink. You want some?
I knew you would come find me.
Yes. Yes, Mister Dong Sik, I think I'm almost ther— Oh!
Oh what a scare!
Hello? No no.
Whereabouts are you?
Mister Taek Soo. Here.
Right. So where is here?
Here!
Mister Dong Sik?
Yes. Here.
Mister Dong Sik!
Mister Dong Sik, why did you go in there?
Dong Sik, grab this!
Grab this! One, two!
So, in order to meet me,
you even killed your wife?
It's for you that I killed her.
Do you remember? That homeless scum you tried to kill but failed to do so.
He came to the hospital where that wench worked, you see.
What?
He came because of his smashed head and a broken arm, saying that someone tried to kill him,
that after stamping a blood print in the diary,
he was in so much fear that he told everything!
Even if it was the words of a drunken bum, she must have thought that something was weird.
So that wench promised to contact the police,
but in the short time that she was away, he disappeared, she said.
Over there, the second bed.
When you work in the emergency room, there are all sorts of people,
so she didn't think much of it and let it go, but then saw the news...
If I had spared that wench's life, she would have told the police everything.
That's why I killed her!
- For our sake.
- Our?
I felt it when I saw the news articles about you. Someone had the same exact thoughts as me.
The world is full of insect-like bastards who make you want to vomit
just for the mere fact that they breathe the same air as you.
You can just kill them! Why didn't I think of that?
Thanks to you, I had a huge realization.
So me too, I took the resolution to become a predator just like you.
It's very moving.
If I followed exactly the things you did, I could meet you one day.
I did have that thought. But this fast?
As expected, the original is different.
You don't know how many things I want to ask.
Perhaps, about those murder dates,
KOSPI 300, inverse futures, I'm right, aren't I?
I've got a deep connection with that stock, you see.
The amount of money I lost—
What happened with Yook Dong Sik?
Oh, right!
I forgot to tell you that story! The funniest one.
That homeless guy said so, apparently.
That you were trying to kill him, but someone was hiding and watching,
and they ran away with the diary.
So the one who took the diary was not that homeless man, but—
I'm telling you it was that guy!
And do you know what he said? He said the diary is his!
And said that he's the real predator! That nutcase!
It must have been a lie.
A lie with some kind of intent.
No. It didn't seem like a lie.
Now that I think about it, that punk really is crazy!
He didn't even know I was trying to kill him and acted up like a fool!
Who does he think he is to call himself a predator?
Get off.
Everything is good, but you talk too much.
I ... I'm on your side.
I'm telling you I'm also a predator.
Really?
Then prove it.
If you flee by crossing here, I'll acknowledge you.
At night ... the highway?
Among the weak, there is one kind that I hate the most.
The weak ones who are delusional and think they are strong ones.
Isn't that sickening?
Don't tell me. You're not one of those, are you?
Who are you?
Why aren't you saying ...
Hyungnim! What happened?
Wh-What's wrong with your leg?!
- That is ...
- I took him out of a manhole he fell in.
M-Manhole?
- I have an urgent matter, so I'll go now.
- Oh no no, Mister Dong Sik!
What urgent matter, when you just almost got killed by a murderer? Get treatment,
and you should make a statement as well.
- It's really urgent.
- You can't.
Wait wait wait. Oh, oh!
Yes, Sunbae! Ah, Mister Dong Sik, I—
What? Nam Seong Cheol?
What is it?
She said he died from a car accident.
How is your body?
I said you could get treated some more before coming.
Even if I'm still a bit dizzy, if I rest a bit, it'll be okay.
I told you to stay out of it because it was dangerous.
Why did you meet Mister Nam?
That is ... Because he even made a suicide attempt,
so I thought I could bring him some comfort, yes.
It isn't that Mister Nam contacted you first?
Of course. He contacted me asking to see me. Yes.
As of now, you are the last person to have seen Mister Nam,
so your testimony is extremely important.
In your opinion, is Mister Nam really a predator?
That is ...
He said he is indeed a predator.
And he admitted to the previous six murders?
Yes.
What did he say, specifically?
Today wasn't even a date that matched with the stock pattern.
Also, it doesn't make sense that he suddenly killed his wife after killing an unspecified number of people he chose.
If Mister Nam is really our guy, seeing how he has a tendency to show-off,
I would definitely think he told you all kinds of things like this.
That is, uhm ...
All of a sudden, feeling dizzy, ah ...
Let's stop and take him to the hospital quickly.
Come with us.
Careful, careful.
Careful.
As he was fleeing, he crossed the highway and was hit by a car. What about the black box?
The verification results didn't find other circumstances beside the car accident.
And on the site, we discovered Mister Nam's burner phone that he used to call the broadcast station.
So are you sure that this guy is the predator?
From the search of Mister Nam's house, we found numerous cutout articles on the predator murderer,
and the blood print of his wife whom he killed by disguising it as suicide.
And evidence for the other cases?
It seems like it was destroyed as the investigation started.
But he performed details that were not disclosed to the public, such as the blood thumbprint.
And moreover, judging from how he confessed himself that he was the predator murderer when calling the broadcast station,
I think that it is certain he is the predator murderer we are chasing.
But... it is still too early to conclude.
- What is this about?
- Ah, that is...
We can't exclude the possibility that Mister Nam was a copycat.
He almost doesn't fit the profiling at all and—
Corporal Sim Bo Gyeong is just making personal presumptions.
Also, eye witness Yook Dong Sik, who was the last target,
testified that the culprit admitted the other cases were his doing.
If he is a copycat who yearns to be a predator, he could also have been lying.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
- Commissioner!
- The press is already making a fuss.
They say that the special team caught the serial killer and stopped additional murders.
The citizens who were insecure can now feel reassured and return to their normal life.
But you want to say that that guy is a fake, and there is another murderer?
It is only aggravating the anxiety of the citizens when you don't even have much basis.
Let's conclude it while we're at it.
- However—
- You all worked hard.
In a short while, the entire team will be given a reward,
so go somewhere today to fill your stomach and release your burden, alright?
- Good job!
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Bo Gyeong. It's true that we came all the way here thanks to you, but in the end, an investigation is teamwork.
If you get stuck in the profiling you made,
you end up disregarding the truth when it's obvious.
Yes.
You'll come with us, right?
Sorry. I have to go to Dad's hospital.
Not to the team dinner. I'm asking whether you have any thoughts of officially joining our team.
I'm not sure...
whether I have the qualifications to do so.
Cheongan Hospital
Ah B-Bo Gyeong.
Yeah Mom, where are you? Did Dad change rooms?
That is ...
We only followed the procedure.
"When the mental care patient is admitted at the request of the person who's responsible for his care,
"you have to receive consent from two people who are responsible for his care."
As for guardians, there are only my mom and I,
but I did not sign, I'm telling you.
Even if you ask us that—
You should talk with me.
As expected, it was you. Who let you decide to do this kind of thing?
I did it after discussing it with your mother.
That's enough. I'll take my dad away.
Last time, your father swung an injection syringe at you, didn't he?
You are a policewoman who received training, but what about your mother?
What will you do if he swings something even worse toward your mother?
There is no way my dad would do that!
Don't be stubborn.
What if a serious incident happens while you're somewhere else and only the two are together?
Then, truly, no one will be able to protect your mother.
Staying here will also be good for your father to receive treatment.
You can't close the coffee shop indefinitely and only stick by your father's bedside.
And you also need to think of your mother.
Staying in the hospital is bad for health. What are you going to do if your mother also falls ill?
Dad.
Dad? I'm here.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry.
Do you really like that woman?
Yeah.
Her looks aren't too bad, but are you sure you'll be okay?
More than anything else, her father is the problem.
Make sure he doesn't cause any trouble.
Oh. I see what you're saying.
If anything happens, call me right away.
The Predator Murderer who made many tremble in fear after his serial killings, is now dead.
Mr. Nam, who predicted his death on a live broadcast,
died during his escape in an auto accident.
The suspected murders that were disguised as suicides, committed by Mr. Nam
have been put to an end.
Around 5 pm last night, Nam attempted to murder 'brave citizen' Yook Dong Sik,
who played a crucial role in starting the official investigation.
Thanks to the work of the task force lead by Inspector Ryoo Jae Joon, Nam's forewarned murder was prevented,
and the team was able to rescue Yook with success.
Following, is the report by Park Cheol Mi.
Dong Sik, are you alright?
Dong Sik! I knew you'd do it!
Will you take a picture with me?
- Sunbae, are you okay?
- Well ...
Why do you keep worrying me? If you keep doing this, I—
Dong Sik!
I shouldn't have asked you to attend that funeral in my place. What if something had happened to you?
It's not like you knew something like this would happen.
No. As expected, my friend.
You're a pushov-likeable (both words begin with the same syllable).
Really.
Don't be so tactless, you.
Take the picture. Hurry.
Hey, Mi J-Joo
Ji Yoon, you should come too.
Should I?
In the middle!
I'm taking it. One, two!
Team Leader, won't you come too?
What are you doing during working hours?
I said what are you doing and not working during working hours!?
- Come over.
- Come.
I said what are you doing and not working during working hours!?
A 'Brave citizen' and now a victim who nearly died.
It's a little over the top, but perfect.
No murderer could hide his identity as well as I can.
The day after the Yuseong Biomedi incident, 13th of September.
Find out about Yook Dong Sik's whereabouts on that day.
Yes, sir.
Corporal Sim Bo Gyeong
Here is the fruit juice you ordered. It took a long time, didn't it?
I thought you would never want to see me again.
I'm sorry about last time. You were only trying to be considerate.
What's your relationship with Dong Sik?
Pardon? What do you mean by relationship?
No, it's just that... you wouldn't even tell me how you two met.
Why? Is it something I can't be curious about?
No, it's just that it's a long story.
I've got a lot of time.
Actually, I hit Dong Sik with my car while I was on patrol.
He wasn't hurt badly, but he lost his memory after the incident.
It must have been hard for him to adjust.
Memory loss?
Did that accident occur on September 13th?
Right, you two work together. Maybe I said something useless.
Oh, no. That's not it. It's just that he did seem a little different since then.
It seemed like he tried to hide it as much as possible, but it must have shown through.
He's such a pure-hearted person, that's why.
Please don't let Dong Sik know that I know about this. I'll pretend not to know either.
Wouldn't Dong Sik be more comfortable with that too?
Okay. I'll do that.
Seeing how Chief Park Jae Ho denies memory loss to such an extent,
I think it's true.
Director?
Ah, okay.
So he read my diary while having memory loss.
That's why that ridiculous...
Why is a young man like you driving like this?
I'm sorry, I must have lost my mind—
This man... how can you laugh in a situation like this?
No, it's not that.
I'm sorry. I'm—
What a crazy...
Here.
₩5 million
Take it before I change my mind.
Why won't people just readily accept money when it's handed to them?
What's the matter, is it not enough?
No, I thought it's too much actually.
I've included severance pay, that's why.
We've never met, and we will never meet again.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
Aren't you a real celebrity if the restaurant owner recognizes you and won't accept your money?
People I know are begging me to set them up with you!
What do you think? Want me to?
A blind date?
- No! Now that I think about it, they're not your type. None of them.
- None?
Did you enjoy your lunch?
Hello, sir.
I was looking for you, Dong Sik, actually.
Me, why?
I was thinking we could use your current image for the company's advertising.
From marketing ideas, there's one that suggests inspirations from the Aesop Fables.
Do you know the story "The Donkey in the Lion's Skin"?
"The Donkey in the Lion's Skin"?
Oh, that. I think I've read it to Woo Ri before.
You know, it's about a donkey that finds a lion's skin and puts it on—
- Oh, then the animals must have fled from him, thinking he was a lion, right?
- Yeah.
But doesn't he get caught by the fox later in the story?
The donkey, who got excited scaring other animals,
tries to scare even the fox by roaring like a lion.
But the fox notices right away that he sounds like a donkey.
Oh, I think I may have heard that story somewhere too.
But... to use it in an advertisement?
Is it not good? Then what if we change the ending?
To one where the donkey gets ripped to pieces by the lion.
Sorry?
A horror theme!
Anyway, I've realized your true worth, Dong Sik.
It's nothing, sir.
- Exactly.
- Pardon?
- Anyway, you should look forward to it
since I'm giving serious thought as to how I should use you.
Yes, sir.
Right. Did you hear the news about Bo Gyeong's father?
- Sorry?
- Oh, I thought you two were close.
Goodbye, sir.
Sir, you shouldn't do this.
I don't want to!
You need to receive the injection so you can go home soon.
Home?
Of course. Your wife and daughter must be waiting for you.
Okay, now.
Oh!
Let go! I don't want it!
Let me go home!
Hurry up and hold him down!
What are you doing? Get him!
I'm sorry, we're still closed!
Dong Sik!
I was just passing by.
I... decided to go back to the Patrol Division.
You're not continuing to work in  Inspector Ryoo's team?
I think I'm still lacking a lot.
I get emotional first, so I keep saying useless things.
Still, you're the one I'm the most scared of.
- Pardon?
Oh, I meant you seem very talented.
I'm not. Nothing of the sort.
Dad isn't well, so I think it's best for everyone for me to go back to where I was.
Oh, about your dad—
Just a second.
Yes?
Pardon? Dad disappeared?
Policeman Heo
What happened?!
We checked the CCTV nearby, and it looks like he headed to a nearby town.
I got it. Keep checking and let me know!
- What? Escape?
- Wow.
What is it he used to do? He suddenly used his strength, and his physical strength was...
Anyway, the hospital staff and the police are looking for him, so don't worry too much.
Where did he go exactly?
He couldn't have gone far, though. Let's go that way.
Just a minute.
Yeah. What happened?
What? The bus terminal?
Dad!
- Dad.
- Get away.
Dad, are you okay?
I have to go!
Dad. It's me.
Your daughter, Bo Gyeong.
- Daughter.
- That's right.
Me. I'm here.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm here.
You're okay, Dad.
Are you his guardian?
I mean, I was trying to talk to him nicely because he seemed pitiful,  but without warning, he...
How can you neglect a dangerous man like this?
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Seriously.
No!
Dad, are you okay?
I don't want it!
I don't want it! I don't want it!
I might be overstepping my bounds in saying this, but is him staying here the best thing for him?
My dad... holds a fifth-degree black belt in Tae Kwon Do, third in Judo, and fourth in Hapkido.
A total of twelve.
Since most criminals were no match if they challenged dad,
it's dangerous. You saw earlier, too.
He wasn't that bad before. Why did he suddenly...?
I don't know why he's doing that.
Maybe we didn't realize his condition was getting worse.
If we had known a little earlier, things wouldn't have gotten this bad.
Oh, it's not your fault.
Still, it's a good thing we found him before he got on a bus.
If he had gotten on the bus and went all the way to Gwangju in Gyeonggi Province...
Gwangju in Gyeonggi Province?
Yes. Earlier, the driver...
- What is it?
- I told you once, right?
That he ended up in that state after an accident while investigating eight years ago?
Where we found him at that time was a hospital in Gwangju that had closed down.
By chance, could he have been trying to go there?
No way. Suddenly?
I mean... you said that he's started behaving strangely just recently.
He could be doing that because he thought of something.
Like he left something there.
Notice of Closure
He was found fallen there,
barely breathing.
A hospital in Gwangju, in Gyeonggi Province,
an officer is hurt. An emergency situation has happened!
Requesting 119 assistance!
Maybe someone pushed him?
I also was suspicious of that, but there weren't any clues leading to that.
At the time, the criminal was caught at a completely different place,
and the location being where it was, I thought he fell during while investigating.
But you said the investigation notebook wasn't on him when he was found?
Right. He used to keep it with him at all times, but he didn't have it.
I didn't think it was odd at the time since I couldn't even think about that kind of thing, given the situation.
What is it?
Nothing.
What's the matter? It's like you saw a ghost.
Seriously, in the middle of the night, in a closed hospital like this...
why would there be a ghost?
Oh, my god!
What's the matter?
I was looking at my feet and walking...
- The feet?
- Something brushed past!
I think there are mice.
There's nothing much, so let's go now.
Stop! What if you see a dead mouse or something?
I mean, I touched something solid.
Could this be
your father's notebook?
That's it.
It's good. Although the culprit was caught a while ago,
it's meaningful for both your father and you.
What's the matter?
It's almost the same.
The profile that Dad wrote eight years ago.
Huh? What's that about?
Back then, Dad, at the hospital room earlier, had discovered the scene of a murder.
Damn it.
"Based on the blood on the floor, the murderer killed the victim here."
- "I don't think  he was experienced in killing."
-  I don't think he was experienced in killing.
He may have watched the person dying.
And the bloodstain on the bedsheet
appears to be the victim's right thumbprint.
(Son Ji Min; Sunam Girls' School)
I don't think it happened accidentally. The fingerprint is so clear,
it appears to be the result of a desire to collect.
"And the bloodstain on the bedsheet
appears to be the victim's right thumbprint."
The b-bloody thumbprint. Why is it turning up there?
Perhaps the murder of the girl eight years ago was his first.
He erased all the evidence my dad had found
and he was dormant for a long time,
and he reappeared as a more sophisticated and terrifying predatory killer.
I-I am sorry.
No way.
What the heck is happening? This is ...
There's nothing about what happened eight years ago.
Detective Inspector Profiler Ryoo Jae Joon arrested a 17-year-old...
If what is written in the notebook is true, the true culprit was not arrested then.
Was that me again?
It can't be.
The detective's case book? Are you kidding?
If it was eight years ago, I was very ordinary.
If it was during the winter eight years ago, you ran away.
You are saying I ran away from home?
Brother-in-law, you did something like that?
Yeah.  You said the president ( Dad ) made you so worried.
When did I ever?
A grown man needs to experience the world. You're talking nonsense.
Why in the world did I run away?
I'm not sure.
Ah. It was after your discharge from the army and you couldn't decide whether to go back to school
or what path to follow, and you were bumming around, probably.
Don't you happen to know where I was or what I did?
You don't know?
This is tasty. It ripened up well.
Mom, give me more rice.
Oh, our Dong Chan's appetite is back.
Dong Chan is ...
Why are you picking at your food? Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Eat a lot, Dong Chan.
Our Dong Chan even asked for more rice.
Officer Sim
So you're saying, the culprit from eight years ago hasn't been caught.
And that guy is the predator.
Then, what about Nam Seong Cheol?
When I looked into it, eight years ago, Mr. Nam was working overseas for a construction company.
He has nothing to do with that case.
Ah yes. But he definitely told me he was the predator.
He probably wanted to be.
The predator we're after is a very skilled killer.
But Mr. Nam was an amateur.
Even when he tried to kill you, he tested it out and almost died.
I don't know how he got his information about predators,
but it's highly likely he's a copycat.
So based on the notebook you found, you're going to start investigating the predator murderer again?
Yes.
I'm going to go back to the origin, assuming that the case from eight years ago was his first murder.
I'm going to investigate everything again.
Thank you. This is all because of you.
Ah, no.
I won't need to help with anything, right?
It just so happens that I was going to ask for your help.
So where are we going right now?
First, I was going to go show him, the owner of the notebook.
Visiting Sim Seok Goo?
Yes. During our visit, are we allowed to go out for a walk?
If the doctor approves ...
Oh, Sim Seok Goo already left for a walk.
What? My mom is at home.
Who is he with?
Director Seo.
Dad!
You two came together.
The weather was nice so I brought him out for a walk. I used my doctor connections.
Thank you.
Dad, how are you feeling today?
Dad, I found your old case notebook.
Take a look. It hasn't changed.
Dad, look carefully.
You don't remember?
What is that?
The legendary Detective Sim's case notebook.
She thought it might be helpful for her dad. You don't need to worry about it.
Case notebook?
Dad.
The culprit you were chasing, I promise I'll catch him.
Dad, we're leaving.
Ahjussi, your daughter keeps doing dangerous work. You must be worried.
She has no idea the kind of guy she's running around with.
That friend has killed six people.
Was it seven?
Oh, that's right. He's also the one who made you this way.
What did you say? He's not?
He is.
I'm going to make it that way.
Your daughter may also be murdered. She should be careful.
I guess you can't speak.
Psychopath Diary
This may be my last diary.
Hyungnim, a man like you is turning his back on the world!
Tomorrow at 4 pm.
Get an undertaker ready and go out near the Kang River bridge.
How does he know? Who exactly?
Eventually he will become a real predator.
He will be arrested by your daughter.
I've received a text message from an unknown number.
He wants to give me a tip as to the identity of the predator killer.
Then, this time my trophy will be...
I think I like you.
Is that alright with you?