(Guidelines were strictly followed
when filming with children.)
(Episode 66)
What's going on?
I told you the designer
wouldn't be making an appearance.
Well, the thing is...
Stage management team,
please bring the models backstage.
Stage team!
What is this?
I thought Holly wasn't coming.
How would I know?
Is Holly here or not?
What is this?
What's going on?
- What?
- Go and find out what's going on.
- What is this?
- Yes, sir.
My goodness.
Holly.
Please show up.
Please.
- Holly!
No way.
I don't believe this.
- Holly!
Oh, look!
What is going on?
What is Gu Dan Soo doing up there?
Thank you all for joining us today
and enjoying the show.
I'm Holly, the designer
in this collaborative project.
Holly, please look here.
- On your left.
- Look here.
- Over here, Holly!
- Please look at the camera!
- Over here.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're Holly?
I'm sure I told you I was Holly,
Ms. Maeng Gong Hee.
Holly, why did you keep
your identity a secret?
Why did you suddenly decide
to reveal yourself?
What was the reason you decided
to collaborate with Jayce Fashion?
The collaborative project
and this fashion show...
were all Ms. Maeng Gong Hee's ideas.
All I did was respond
to Ms. Maeng's sincerity...
because she knows...
she's not alone.
Does it make any sense
that no one knew Dan Soo was Holly?
Min Gi, why do you think
I had you stay by Dan Soo's side?
It was to become your eyes
and to watch Dan Soo from close by.
So, how could you miss
such an important thing?
Did you not know?
Or did you not report it to me
even though you knew about it?
I didn't know either.
From what I've found out,
he entered a contest
while studying abroad...
and has been working as a designer
named Holly since then.
I should ask Dan Soo myself.
Have him come to the office
this instant.
He disappeared
after the fashion show,
and he won't answer his phone.
What on earth is going on?
I didn't even know that
and kept nagging him so much.
I thought he was neglecting
his business management training...
because he was busy wandering around
with a guitar on his back.
But he had been building such a career
even without my help.
You must be very happy.
Congratulations, ma'am.
Yes.
I guess I feel confused
because I'm so overjoyed.
I should hurry up
and announce him as my successor.
I knew it.
He was just hanging around,
but he had this vibe about him,
like he wasn't just slacking off.
Something like a genius.
I felt that about him.
Gu Dan Soo,
you're a man of many secrets.
He's smart, handsome,
and multitalented.
What is a man like me
supposed to do?
Gosh, but it's so weird.
Why do you think he kept it a secret
all this time?
I know how that feels.
Freedom.
That's what geniuses want.
What's so good about
letting the whole world know?
They don't need money or fame.
All they want is freedom.
That's it.
How do you know so well?
Well, a genius can relate to
a fellow genius, you know?
Is that right?
That must be why
you seek freedom so badly.
Oh, my. Director Lee!
Are you acknowledging me
as a genius?
- Thank you.
- What in the...
Well, anyway...
Thanks to him, Gong Hee
will become a permanent employee.
Oh, I'm so happy.
By the way,
didn't Gong Hee and Dan Soo say...
they had been friends
since childhood?
- Oh, gosh.
- Look where you're going.
I'm sorry.
I came back after cleaning up
the fashion show venue.
Gong Hee. You knew, didn't you?
That Gu Dan Soo was Holly!
I really didn't know either.
Come on. Really?
Did you never even suspect him?
No, I still can't believe it.
The chairwoman's grandson is Holly,
and I didn't even recognize him.
My goodness.
I didn't make
any other mistakes, did I?
Pardon?
What?
Oh, no! It's nothing.
You know
we're in emergency mode now, right?
We're having a meeting in an hour.
Since the real Holly has shown up,
we will revise
our entire marketing strategy!
What? Another meeting?
When can we go home, then?
What?
(Daycare Center)
Hello?
What?
My gosh.
Can we have
some more pickled radishes?
Oh, yes. Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Two mixed dumplings, please.
- Here it comes.
- Great.
- Enjoy. Oh, dear.
- Yes, thank you.
Mom, it's me.
Go to the daycare center quickly.
No Ah is sick.
What? What's wrong with him?
He has a stomachache.
Hong Dan is busy
because of the fashion show today.
Can you go instead?
And aren't I busy?
Mom, I have to consult
on a case today,
so I have to go
to the university hospital.
Do me this favor. I love you!
I love you!
Goodness, you only love me
when you have a favor to ask.
By the way,
where has this man gone now?
We're so busy now.
Detective An will stay by your side
and protect you for the time being.
You don't have to do that.
I don't have much to do these days,
so it's fine.
Don't feel burdened.
Just go where you want to...
and do what you want.
Then, this guy will take care
of everything.
I won't do as you wish anymore.
I won't move aside just like this.
Even if I end up leaving,
I will see my son before I go.
Then, Detective An.
I'll depend on you
for just a little while.
You got it.
Why won't you pick up
after making such a mess?
Reporter Park? What happened?
This isn't what we agreed on.
Aren't you the one
who isn't sticking to her word?
I had everything planned,
thinking Holly wouldn't show up.
What on earth is going on?
Still, how could you
just stand there...
to get an interview
with the person in charge?
That's not why I gave you
this information beforehand!
Everyone is going crazy
because of Holly right now.
I have to get to a meeting
because of that too.
Don't call me for the time being.
My goodness.
Hello?
Everything would've been fine
if Holly hadn't shown up.
Then Gong Hee's promotion
and everything else...
could've been taken care of
all at once.
Gu Dan Soo was Holly?
What kind of joke is this,
Gu Dan Soo?
(Sunny Daycare Center)
No Ah.
No Ah, are you okay? What's wrong?
My gosh. Hello, ma'am.
No Ah.
You're here.
I called No Ah's dad too.
How long has he been like this?
It's been a while.
He said he had a stomachache
and has been like this ever since.
He didn't want to go
to the doctor either.
No Ah, wake up. No Ah?
Gosh, this won't do.
I'll carry him
and go to the hospital. Come on.
You...
What are you doing?
I'm pretending to be Dad
who stays in bed all day...
on the weekends.
Oh, boy.
(Sunny Daycare Center)
(Director Lee)
Yes, Director Lee.
Why aren't you coming
to the meeting, Ms. Genius?
I'm sorry. I'll be right there.
I thought geniuses wanted freedom.
Why don't you just quit your job
and become free?
Well, I said I'd be there soon.
I...
Gosh, seriously.
This is driving me crazy.
What's up with you?
Did you do that
to pull a prank on me?
I didn't call you, lady.
What?
I thought you asked for your mom
because you were sick.
I asked for my mom.
My mom who's in the US.
Your mom is in the US.
How can she come here?
Why, that...
Hey.
Why are you yelling
at a kid who's sick?
- Grandma.
- Hey.
All right. Where does it hurt?
Oh, my sweet baby.
Mother, why are you here?
Gong Boo called me.
How did you leave the office?
I got the call at work
and hurried over, but he...
He was pretending to be sick.
Goodness, he's just a kid.
I'm sure he had a reason
for pretending to be sick.
What reason can there be
for pretending to be sick?
If you do that again,
I'll really scold you.
Neener.
Oh, my...
Mother, I have to get back to work.
Tell Gong Boo to pick up No Ah.
It's okay. Mommy is just busy.
She's not my mom.
What?
My mom is Lee Soo Yeon.
She's a doctor,
and she's in the US.
Oh, dear.
Goodness, what will we do with you?
I made sure Holly's interview
won't be released for now.
Until he shows up in person
and makes his position clear,
we will observe the situation
and see how it goes.
What did the chairwoman say?
Until we decide
on our marketing direction,
she wants to keep the media out,
and she said
we should all keep our lips sealed.
But the collaboration
will continue, right?
Yes. In addition
to Holly's appearance,
all the pieces at the show
got amazing feedback.
I'll be in charge of the project
with Holly going forward.
What? Gong Hee started the project,
so we should let her wrap it up.
Besides, Gong Hee
will soon become a permanent employee,
so she's more than qualified.
Anyway, the show was a success
thanks to Gong Hee's hard work.
Let's give Gong Hee
a big round of applause!
Gong Hee, you're amazing.
Well done.
Thank you.
My gosh.
The meeting is over.
You just got here?
Well, the thing is...
I see. "The thing is."
Thanks for your explanation.
What? Wait.
What was decided at the meeting?
For now, we'll focus on calming the storm
after Holly's appearance.
My gosh. I hope someone
can calm the storm in my life now.
Gong Hee, shouldn't you
go on a vacation or something?
You need a vacation.
No, I'm good.
Don't you get it?
Or are you just playing dumb?
Are you excited
to become a permanent employee?
Try all you want.
You can't stop us
from getting married.
Congratulations in advance
on your wedding.
(Bubble Up Laundry)
Mom, I'm home!
I came so late, didn't I?
Where is No Ah?
He's asleep.
I have to take him home.
Just let him sleep here tonight.
Well, Hong Dan called me.
My gosh. He feigned sickness,
just like I used to.
Have you wondered
why he pretended to be sick?
- What?
- He said he missed his mom.
You think he's okay
because he's not sick physically?
He's heartbroken.
Well...
He can't see his mom now
because she's in the US.
What on earth is the matter
with Hong Dan?
She took him,
saying she'd raise him well.
I don't expect her
to think of him as her own,
but she should
at least act like she cares.
Gosh, it's so cold.
Why did you come home alone?
What about No Ah?
Oh, Mom wanted
to let him sleep there tonight.
No Ah said
he didn't want to come home.
What? He didn't want to come home?
I guess he misses his mom.
You know, when I was little,
I missed my mom,
so I always told my kindergarten teachers
that my tummy hurt.
Clearly, he takes after me.
Goodness.
I get that he takes after you,
but he even got
his malingering skills from you?
Anyway,
why did you have to spank his butt?
Don't you feel bad for him?
When did I spank his butt?
Did No Ah say that?
My goodness. That rascal...
even accused me
of something I never did?
Forget it. That's enough.
Let's eat. I'm hungry.
You didn't make dinner?
Me?
Yes, who else?
Oh, well...
You didn't prepare dinner?
What do you want me to do?
So, you want me to take care
of housework, go to work,
deal with No Ah
and everything at daycare,
and make dinner too?
I'm pregnant too.
Hey, is Ssook Ssook not your child?
I should've had dinner
at Mom's place.
Why did you only leave No Ah there?
You should live there too!
Darn you.
Come on, Hong Dan. Let's eat out...
Unbelievable.
I'd rather enlist
than deal with this. Yes.
The army is
a hundred times better than this!
Hong Dan is scarier...
than any senior military officer
I've met.
Honey, did you hear that?
Darn you.
That immature kid was
the mysterious fashion designer?
Is that really true?
Because of it, Chairwoman Hwang...
seems to think differently
of Dan Soo now.
My goodness.
In the past, she treated him
like a clueless, reckless child,
but things will change now.
Work harder
to assist Dan Soo well at all times.
Work is very busy now,
but my wedding...
will happen as planned.
Yes, of course.
Just because the immature Dan Soo
is actually a famous designer,
it doesn't mean your wedding plans
should be affected.
Nothing can or will stop you two...
from getting married,
no matter what.
The meeting with Ji Na's family
has been scheduled.
You should be there too, Dad.
My gosh.
My son really is getting married.
My goodness.
How do you plan on telling
Chairwoman Hwang about it?
I'll tell her
as I invite her to my wedding.
She'll be livid.
You'd better be ready.
What? Why would she be livid?
Just tell her
we'd appreciate a big cash gift.
Seriously.
Good grief.
Ji Na didn't say anything else,
did she?
You're hiding something from me,
aren't you?
What?
If there's something you're hiding,
just tell me.
Ji Na has been acting weird too.
Weird, how?
She seems to be on edge and...
Oh, don't worry about that.
All women get like that
before their wedding.
There's a term for it, you know.
Pre-wedding blues.
You know.
You're sure you're not hiding
anything from me, right?
Yes, I am sure.
Why do you keep asking me that?
Here. Eat up, okay?
Only trouble awaits
if I don't step in now.
I must act quickly.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're Holly?
I'm sure I told you I was Holly,
Ms. Maeng Gong Hee.
I still can't believe it.
Snot Face Geon is Holly?
The fashion designer I had admired
for so long was Gu Dan Soo?
My goodness.
Because she knows she's not alone.
This is considered cheating.
How could you do this?
And you disappeared again.
You won't even answer my calls.
There are so many things
I want to ask you and tell you.
So many things.
My gosh.
No Ah doesn't want to go to daycare.
What should we do?
Goodness, I know.
What can we do?
We should send him to daycare.
He kept saying he didn't want to go.
I felt bad after making him go.
I feel bad for you, Myung Ja.
You'd be sighing nonstop
even if you had...
no one else to worry about
except for your children.
Now, you even have to worry
about your grandson. Oh, boy.
I think you'll end up raising No Ah
at this rate.
Oh, dear.
My goodness.
Why are you here again?
Has your daughter
still not told you?
Why do you keep bringing up
my daughter?
What is it?
Go on and tell me.
What has happened to my daughter?
Fine, I'll tell you.
I must tell you for her own sake
as this is wrong.
Your daughter is...
pregnant.
Hey, what...
What on earth are you saying?
I even visited her OB-GYN clinic
and checked.
Your daughter...
is pregnant.
No...
(Pregnancy Journal, Maeng Gong Hee)
Oh, no.
My goodness.
Oh, dear.
(Regular Checkup Notes)
(Next checkup: January 9, 2025, 5 p.m.)
Oh, my.
- My gosh.
- What?
Hey, what's wrong? Myung Ja.
Help me up.
Okay, here.
Get up. Come on.
Goodness,
you're as white as a sheet.
What's wrong?
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
The hospital. Yes, I should go.
Right now. Immediately.
What?
The car. Drive me. Hurry!
What? But...
Hey.
My goodness. What is up with her?
Gosh, what's going on?
What?
Why is this...
(Pregnancy Journal, Maeng Gong Hee)
Why is Gong Hee's name here?
Hello, how may we help you?
Maeng Gong Hee.
She has a checkup today.
Ms. Maeng Gong Hee?
How do you know the patient?
She's my daughter.
Where is my daughter right now?
Oh, she just went
into the doctor's office.
Do you hear that?
The baby's heart is beating well.
You can't come in here
when I'm with a patient.
Mom!
You!
Why are you...
What are you...
doing here?
(Pregnancy Journal, Maeng Gong Hee)
(Saechorok OB-GYN Clinic)
Mom, please listen to me. Mom!
Fine, tell me.
Why are you here,
being treated like an expecting mom?
Mom, I tried to tell you, but...
My gosh.
Dad.
My goodness.
Oh, dear.
(My Merry Marriage)
Your baby...
Is Ssang Sook's son
the father of the baby?
Tell me the truth.
What are you planning to do?
What will you do?
You said he was a customer.
It's Detective An.
I knew this would happen.
You have some flour on your face.
Congratulations, Ms. Maeng Gong Hee.
Thank you.
Gong Hee, take a look at this.
What on earth is this?
The person
you will be greeting today...
is my grandson, Gu Dan Soo.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)