(Guidelines were strictly followed
when filming with children.)
I feel like
there's this tangled mess...
sitting in my heart.
Where do I begin to untangle this?
Or should I just leave it as it is?
I'm not sure...
about anything.
What...
should I do, Gu Dan Soo?
When you're making clothes,
you come across those knots.
They get all tangled up...
that it seems impossible
to untangle them.
But they eventually get untangled
in the end.
You just have to undo them
from the middle, one step at a time.
You know that too.
But right now,
I can't even tell
where the middle is.
You're in the middle.
Start with yourself,
whatever it may be about.
Hey, you're a simple-minded girl.
Just think about yourself.
Don't try to understand
other people so much.
And what if I don't understand them?
What am I supposed to do?
You know what you're good at.
Throwing punches out of nowhere.
Charge at them,
throw them on the ground,
and kick them.
Hey, am I a thug or something?
You kicked me all the time.
That was because
you were asking for it.
Will you really not tell me...
what this is about?
I was just complaining about life.
Thanks for the ramyeon.
Hey, wait.
I don't know what it's about,
but you're blaming yourself again,
aren't you?
Stop doing that
and just blame other people.
It's nice. Just live comfortably.
My goodness.
Crying and laughing.
You know that's cheating, don't you?
I'll be going.
Maeng Gong Hee.
What on earth can't you tell me?
I'd rather have you lean on me...
and cry your eyes out.
Why were you tearing up?
Why?
- Mom.
- What?
Hey, when did you get here?
Why didn't you call me?
I came because I wanted your food.
Oh, no. But it's too late.
Have you still not had dinner?
Well, someone cooked for me,
so I had some food.
But you should have a proper meal
at home.
You haven't been eating well,
so I was worried about you.
Let's go inside.
I'll fix you dinner quickly.
No, I eat just fine these days.
I should go home now.
I'm happy now that I've seen you.
Gong Hee, spend the night here.
No, I should get going.
My in-laws will be waiting.
Just spend one night here.
Stay with me, okay?
This is my daughter
that I gave birth to.
I can tell
just by looking at her face.
Something is worrying her,
but she can't talk about it.
She's trying to smile more
on purpose.
"The chocolate I received from you."
"Splendid fireworks."
"They will burst in my heart
and become a handful of ash."
"They will become love."
("Leaves in Your Heart")
It's so romantic.
Mr. Ryu, your poems melt my heart...
like these sweet chocolates.
Your poems always...
light up my heart,
but I have nothing...
but these small chocolates
to give you.
No.
Hang on.
Just as your poems color my heart,
I hope these chocolates...
will also color your day...
with sweetness.
Good.
Oh, my.
Darn it.
Let me say this first.
I hope you won't ruin my mood now.
I'm preparing chocolates
for Mr. Ryu.
- Don't jinx them...
- Just go to bed if you're sleepy,
and stop spewing nonsense.
What is this about?
Gong Hee will sleep here tonight.
I'm just letting you know.
That girl runs off to see you
whenever...
I can't believe this.
Both the daughter and the mother
will just do whatever they want.
My gosh.
Oh, my.
Did you two fight?
What?
She said she'd spend the night
at her parents' house.
Did she discuss this with you?
Or did she go there
without telling you?
Well...
She told me at work that
she was going to see her parents.
Is that so?
But today isn't a special day.
Why would she do that,
all of a sudden?
It'd be nice for her
to get some rest there.
The person you have reached
is unavailable. Please leave...
All of a sudden, without a word...
(1 unread message, Ji Na)
I met with Maeng Gong Hee earlier.
At my house.
What do you mean by that?
Why would Gong Hee go there?
Didn't she tell you that we met?
She didn't come home.
She must've been shocked...
from hearing
that we used to live together.
Then, what?
Did she think
things weren't serious between us?
Are you telling me
you actually said that?
It's funny.
We have so much history between us.
You can't just ignore that.
Isn't that right?
Why did you say that?
Why do you think I told her?
I have to correct what's wrong.
You felt it too, Min Gi.
You're regretting it in your heart.
It can't just be over like this.
Am I the only one who thinks so?
I'm hanging up.
Let's talk at work tomorrow.
I didn't know either.
That I'd need you this badly.
I can't even take a sip of water
without you. What can I do?
Come back.
In the end,
the one who will shine by my side...
is you, Seo Min Gi.
"If you rub
the magic lamp like this,"
"a genie will appear
and grant a wish..."
Hey, my hand isn't a magic lamp,
No Ah.
Why do you keep rubbing my hand?
Your hand is rough.
It's fun to rub it.
It's like playing with sand.
What?
Hey, what's wrong with my hand?
My gosh.
Goodness.
Oh, I'm sure I put my hand cream
somewhere here.
Where did it go?
Oh, no. My goodness.
My skin feels so moist.
Hey, Mr. Q.
Come on, baby.
"Hey, Mr. Q?"
What is that all about?
You're a quack. So, you're Mr. Q.
Look, there are kids listening.
No Ah and Ssook Ssook.
- What?
- Explain this first.
But why did this come out of there?
You were working with big hospitals
and whatnot.
I guess that brought in
some pretty decent money.
Oh, that was from Grandma
to give to No Ah.
Is that for me?
- Yes.
- My gosh.
- Are you going to lie?
- What?
Why do you keep racking up
bad karma?
Come clean before I count to three.
One, two...
Fine, you're right.
It's from the time
when I worked as an advisor.
I withdrew the money
to keep it as an emergency fund...
without getting caught.
My gosh. I can't believe this.
Is there more?
Are you suspecting me now?
I'm innocent!
Innocent, my foot.
You've stabbed me in the back
so many times.
Look, the back of my head is
becoming flat from all the stress!
- It was always flat...
- Hey!
Listen up. If there is more,
you need to tell me now
to maintain peace in the family.
I swear, there is no more.
Look at my innocent eyes.
If I find more,
you'll get a beating
for every dime I find, okay?
Come on. For every dime?
Get with the times.
You need to consider
the inflation rate.
Fine. For every cent, then.
- No Ah, let's get rolling.
- Let's get rolling!
- Search him. Stay still.
- I swear, there's no more. Wait!
Stop, hold on.
I'm very ticklish.
Your arms will hurt.
You can stop now.
The wrist pain during pregnancy
will last for life.
You've been running around
all day every day to find Grandma.
I can't go
and look for Grandma with you,
so I should at least do this.
I know you have bad knees.
I'm still strong and healthy,
so don't you worry.
Come and lie down here. It's fine.
Okay.
Mom, it feels so nice
to be lying by your side like this.
It feels so warm and cozy.
Goodness. It's nice to go to sleep
next to your mom...
when you have a husband?
Who says that
in their honeymoon phase?
Don't you also prefer to go to sleep
next to me than to Dad?
Be honest with me.
When your dad and I were newlyweds,
we got along so well.
Even when my mother-in-law
was so mean to me,
my resentment melted away
the moment I saw your dad's face.
Although, it's all in the past now.
Really? You and Dad were like that?
All your emotions become dull
with time, no matter the kind.
To maintain the relationship,
you need a happy memory or two.
Should I just skip work tomorrow...
and go with you?
Goodness. No, don't.
I just want you to live a happy life
without worries.
Stop worrying about me.
That's how you can help me.
Okay, without worries.
Without worries.
Mom.
To tell you the truth,
I'm having a hard time.
It's so hard.
Hello, have you been well?
How shameless of you to come here.
With your head held high.
I heard you liked mangoes.
Dan Soo told me.
Dan Soo asked me to pay you a visit.
As Dan Soo's mom,
I'm going to be brave...
and make an effort.
"Mom?"
You're his mom?
Have you no shame
to call yourself his mom?
Dan Soo was practically an orphan.
I was the one who took him in,
fed him, clothed him,
and helped him
get to where he is now.
It wasn't you. It was all me,
Hwang Ik Sun.
Even if you keep doing this,
you can't change the fact
that I am Dan Soo's mother.
And you can't change the fact
that you were the one...
who got Hae Joon killed.
If you're going to
keep being stubborn like this,
I won't stay quiet.
Must you...
tear me and Dan Soo apart?
Then do you expect me
to just sit back and watch...
as he goes down the wrong path
because of you?
You want me to accept
a mere thing like you as my family?
For Dan Soo's sake,
could you please put the past
behind you...
and take a step back?
Please...
stop hurting Dan Soo.
How dare you lecture me?
Who do you think you are?
How dare you tell me
to stop hurting Dan Soo?
Fine, wait and see.
Find out
what will happen to Dan Soo...
if he turns away from me
and decides to side with you.
Keep your eyes wide-open
and see it for yourself.
You can come to me
and beg me on your knees then.
But just remember...
that you won't be leaving here...
in one piece then.
What if...
I really end up ruining Dan Soo too?
What if I ruin Dan Soo's life too?
Then what am I going to do?
What should I do?
I must intervene.
My dear Dan Soo...
I can't let him go on like this.
Honey.
Detective An and I went to Myeongwol
and checked some places,
but we couldn't find anyone
with Mother's name.
Did you check all the care homes
in the area?
Did they really all say
she wasn't there?
There are only a few care homes
in the area,
so we checked
every single one of them.
The thing is, Detective An
did find a similar name...
at one of the care homes he visited.
The name was Bok Yi.
"Bok Yi?"
Does the name ring a bell?
There was a lady
whom everyone called Ms. Bok Yi.
"Bok Yi?"
I feel like
I've heard the name before.
Detective An and I will go
to Chungcheong Province today.
Don't worry too much.
Hang in there, all right?
Bok Yi?
Bok Yi...
Oh, boy.
Goodness, you scared me.
Hey, I'm working now.
What's that?
It's Valentine's Day, you know.
I prepared this special gift
for you, Gyeong Bok.
My goodness.
What? Aren't women...
supposed to give gifts to men
on Valentine's Day?
Well, what matters is that
you express your love.
Then I shall accept this
with a grateful heart.
What is this?
What? Aren't these
dried radish greens?
At the poetry workshop, you talked
about dried radish green soup,
so I thought...
This is nuts. My goodness.
You got me dried radish greens
instead of chocolate?
My heart is all dried up now,
like these dried radish greens.
Do you like my gift?
Detective An, were you too busy
catching bad guys to watch dramas?
What man gives a woman
dried radish greens as a gift?
Seriously.
My gosh.
Oh, it's busy today.
My gosh, Mr. Ryu. You're here.
Yes, hello. I was in the area,
so I wanted to stop by.
You didn't come
to the workshop today.
We're dealing with a family issue
at the moment,
so I don't have time
to write poems now.
I see.
You're here too.
By the way,
what's with the dried radish greens?
Oh, he bought me
those dried radish greens...
for Valentine's Day.
He said he bought it for me
because I wrote a poem...
about how much I missed
dried radish green soup or whatever.
I see.
Valentine...
is the name of the Roman saint,
who was the patron of love...
even in the midst of persecution.
He officiated weddings
for soldiers in secret...
when they were forbidden to marry.
He was the patron saint
of love and romance.
Valentine's Day was created
in memory of him.
Oh, my.
Goodness, I didn't know about
the meaning behind Valentine's Day.
This day suits you very well.
Please accept this.
Oh, my.
Is it okay for me to take this?
Of course.
Here.
Every time you eat one,
please think about me too.
My goodness. You're making me blush.
Oh, my.
Detective An. What are you doing?
Why are you still here?
Let's get going.
I'm going to leave a little later.
What? Hurry up and come along!
That's right. Hurry along.
I have something to talk about
with Mr. Ryu.
You should get going, okay?
Detective Dried Radish Greens.
- Why...
- Come on.
Hurry up, man.
- Let's go.
- Mr. Ryu, please have a seat.
- Okay, thank you.
- Let's sit.
Oh, my.
Did you wrap this yourself?
- Well, that is...
- My goodness.
Hey. It's me, Myung Ja.
Hey, Myung Ja.
Did you hear anything about Mom?
Oh, not yet.
Didn't you hear anything?
I asked some of my doctor friends
working in hospitals,
but I guess care homes
are a different matter.
It's not easy to find her.
I'm just going around
to random places for now.
I went to Mom's hometown too.
There wasn't anyone
under Mom's name,
but there was someone named Bok Yi.
Bok Yi?
Are you sure it was Bok Yi?
Do you know that name?
Yes.
It's Mom's older sister's name.
The one who passed away
when Mom was little.
Mom used to mention her to me
from time to time.
That she remembered her sister,
Bok Yi.
Hey.
I think I can find Mom.
I'll call you back later.
If you keep acting
however you want like this,
I have no other way either.
And what if I don't act
however I want?
What else can I do?
Kang Ji Na.
You're bound by
that useless sense of responsibility,
so I have to do something.
I can't just sit by and watch.
So? What are you planning to do?
First, I just let her know
that we used to live together.
But Maeng Gong Hee had come
to confirm something else.
Something else?
She wanted to confirm...
if you and I were together
the night before last.
I bet you wanted to get past that
by lying.
You must've thought
Gong Hee would believe you,
being the simple girl she is.
But do you think Maeng Gong Hee
really bought your lie?
No, she just pretended
to fall for it.
She doesn't believe you, Seo Min Gi.
That was why she came
all the way to my house to check.
Why did you have to
mention us living together?
You didn't have to say it.
It's the truth that she has to face.
She knew everything
before you got married.
That Kang Ji Na is the person
Seo Min Gi loves.
Still, she made this choice.
What did I do wrong?
What is it that you want?
Where do you want to end up
by doing all this?
Get divorced.
What?
Divorce Maeng Gong Hee
and come to me.
That's only right.
This was the wrong path
to begin with.
It's fine. I'll fix things.
You should just do as I say...
My gosh. I can't take this anymore.
So, are you saying...
you shamelessly let
your current wife find out...
that you and your ex-girlfriend
used to live together?
Gu Dan Soo.
This isn't your business.
Is that right?
But even
your ex-girlfriend is involved.
Why can't I get involved?
This is about my wife and me.
Then get your act together.
I told you.
Don't you dare
make Maeng Gong Hee cry.
It must be nice
to be Maeng Gong Hee.
She even has a friend
to step up for her.
Is this situation funny to you?
Or are you proud?
I knew you were a bottom-feeder
to begin with,
but if you're this fine
after seeing someone's heart break,
you're the absolute worst,
Ms. Kang Ji Na.
Hey, Maeng Gong Hee. Where are you?
I'm in your office. You said to
bring the documents for you to sign.
No, you can't do this!
She is my mom!
Please let me see her just once!
Her family is here.
Why won't you let me see her?
Please just let me check, at least.
Please!
But the patient doesn't want it.
She said she wasn't your family.
We can't help it either.
But she is my mom.
What kind of person
would get a good night's sleep...
after losing their parent?
Please.
I'm human too.
I'm her child. I have to find her!
Oh, my.
Are you okay?
Myung Ja!
(Myeongwol Nursing Home)
Why do you keep trying to find me?
You're wearing yourself out!
Mom.
Is that you?
Is that really you, Mom?
I told you not to find me.
Myung Ja!
Mom!
Myung Ja.
What are you doing here, Mom?
I looked everywhere for you.
If you hide like this
without even saying a word,
what am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to live?
How am I supposed to live
without going mad?
I didn't want to burden you.
That's why
I tried to be apart from you.
Why did you keep tiring yourself out
to look for me?
This was tiring,
but it was even harder
not to have you around.
A world without you...
is too scary.
I can't live without you, Mom!
I can't live a single day
in my right mind.
Why would you, Mom?
Why would you hide?
(My Merry Marriage)
I made a choice.
I want to be comfortable here...
until my time is over.
Dan Soo, help out...
- with the Heirmez project.
- Me?
I warned you.
You will regret it.
And I warned you too.
If you make Maeng Gong Hee cry,
I won't let you off the hook.
Are you going out again?
It's an important call.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)