Why did you want to meet at my shop?
I suggested we meet here.
Besides, it'd be nice
to help boost your sales.
Why should we meet
at an expensive restaurant?
We all know that
you can't afford it anyway.
Am I wrong?
Hey, it's not like you know
how much I have in my bank account.
Calm down.
She sure has a knack
for making everything sound so mean.
Gosh, stop.
Today should be all about me.
My son is...
finally getting married.
- My gosh. Congratulations.
- Let me see.
Oh, my. I know he recently passed
the civil service exam.
And he's getting married right away?
Congratulations.
I should be able to tell you
some good news soon too.
About what?
Are they already talking
about marriage after the blind date?
No, he turned down
the blind date after all.
Why?
Didn't he break up with the daughter
of the department store family?
You asked me
to set him up with someone.
My goodness. Is that true?
Oh, dear.
You bragged about it nonstop.
Actually, they didn't break up.
You know how young couples get
when they fight.
I guess I read the situation wrong.
Things are going well again
between them.
Are you sure about that?
Aren't you just deluding yourself
into thinking that?
She says
she can never forget my Min Gi.
So, what can he do?
To be honest, I don't like her.
I can't break them up when they say
they can't live without each other.
You kept bragging
about your future daughter-in-law...
from a powerful family.
Right. You bragged about it
in advance, so if it falls through,
it'll be so embarrassing.
Your daughter got her hopes up.
I feel bad for her.
Hey, what do you mean
my daughter got her hopes up?
Your son led her on.
Every evening after work,
he called her...
- and took her out for dinner.
- Every day, he called her and...
Are you sure
he wants to get married?
If he really does, he's a weirdo.
Hey, there's nothing weird
with my son.
I know you're heartbroken
because your daughter,
who's a mere intern,
got her hopes up,
but that's your problem.
I'm heartbroken? "Heartbroken?"
I am relieved. So relieved!
- Hey!
- What?
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
Did you think I'd leave you alone?
You took Hae Joon away from me.
Was that not enough for you?
I took Hae Joon away from you?
Who was the one
that took my son from me?
Leave at once.
Don't show up in front of me again.
If you want to live, that is!
Do you think you can hide the fact
that I'm Geon's mother forever...
by doing this?
You even changed Geon's name.
Of course, I had to get rid...
of that ugly name
you'd come up with.
Did you think
I'd let him keep that name?
Don't tell me...
you met Dan Soo.
No, she didn't.
I've already checked, ma'am.
If you hover around Dan Soo,
I'll carry out
the terms of our agreement.
Don't forget that
this is your last chance.
Live the rest of your life...
as if you're dead.
I won't run away anymore.
I've been running away
my whole life. I will never...
Think about your despicable parents.
Your filthy blood.
Do you want it
to ruin Dan Soo's future too?
The money I gave your father!
- Mr. Seo.
- Yes, ma'am.
I assume you showed up again...
because you were ready
for the consequences.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, I'll never show up
in front of Dan Soo.
Please let me watch him from afar.
Please just let me
watch Dan Soo from afar.
Please, have mercy on me.
I beg you.
Please give me some time. Please?
Please, ma'am.
- Please give me some time.
- Don't do this!
- Ma'am, please...
- Don't do this.
- Don't do this!
- What are you doing?
- Please...
- Please get up. Don't do this.
I'll help you up.
Hold on. Please get up.
Please... Please help me.
Help me.
- Please leave.
- Are you all right?
You two, please leave. Now!
(Oh J. Eun)
You should get going, ma'am.
I'll come back here
and take care of it.
Do not let her go like this.
We absolutely can't let her
show up in front of Dan Soo.
Ma'am, you should go home
and get some rest.
Your health comes first.
You two should really reconcile.
Will you two keep fighting forever?
She's right. I feel so anxious
every time I meet you girls.
Stop fighting, you two.
Myung Ja always provokes me first.
You girls know that too.
Then don't make me provoke you.
Hey, Ssang Sook put her scarf
around my brother's neck.
What?
Does that make sense to you girls?
I told you. His neck looked cold.
I was worried he might catch a cold.
What are you, a doctor?
Why do you care
if my husband catches a cold?
It's none of your business.
Before he became your husband,
we were close friends who grew up
in the same neighborhood. Why?
"Same neighborhood?"
Hey, did you live
in the same neighborhood?
No. We lived in Seoha-dong,
and she lived in Dongsang-dong.
You. Should I go ahead
and tell the girls...
what you did to my husband?
Forget it!
I won't come to your shop anymore.
Don't come!
We won't sell anything to you!
- My goodness.
- You're always welcome here.
- Get home safely.
- All right, bye.
- Bye.
- See you soon.
All right. Thanks for coming.
No problem.
My goodness.
You get so angry
whenever you see Ssang Sook.
And you keep getting feistier.
Whenever I see Ssang Sook's face,
my blood boils. What can I do?
Gosh, whatever.
I'm sick and tired of acting
as your personal firefighter.
But I was worried...
that Gong Hee might like her son.
I'm so relieved
that it's not the case.
Yes, I couldn't be more relieved.
If you two became in-laws...
My gosh.
Just thinking about it
gives me a terrible headache.
That's why I told Gong Hee
not to even dream of it...
to prevent it from happening.
Right, you made the right call.
Oh, right.
We have a group reservation later,
but we've run out of green onions.
What? Already?
We've been pretty busy, you know.
Hold on. Should I run to the store
and get some now?
No. I have them stocked up at home.
I'll run home and get some.
Okay, go.
Oh, boy.
Ssang Sook, that girl.
Look at this fluff. Is she a cat?
Did she have to wear that fur coat?
Goodness.
What are you doing?
You didn't come home last night.
You should've come straight
to the shop.
What are you doing here now?
Porridge.
You're making porridge?
What for?
I told you. Detective An is sick.
If he's sick,
his wife should take care of him.
Why should you make porridge
for him?
Well, his wife is sick too.
He gave it to her while kissing her.
Funny, right?
I don't want to know
whether or not they kissed.
Then you could've just asked me
to make some porridge for them.
Why are you doing this?
It's so unlike you.
Come on. I can do this much.
Suit yourself.
Goodness.
When your own wife is sick...
Forget porridge.
You never even take anything
out of the fridge for me.
This upcoming fashion week
is all the rage already.
Everyone says the company that gets Holly
will generate the most buzz.
It's already the talk of the town.
I know.
So, go and get Holly.
I'll contact the agency and try
to negotiate with them again.
Negotiate with them again? How?
Come up with a solid plan!
So...
instead of the agency,
what about making
a direct offer to Holly?
I think
Holly has lived a lonely life.
I believe Holly wants
to comfort those...
who are lonely just like her
through her designs.
How about I try sending an email?
Know your place.
I'm in charge of this.
Try it.
Director Lee.
We desperately need this.
We should do something!
Gong Hee, you send Holly an email.
If you get a response,
let's plan things all over again.
Let's meet at the cafe
in front of the office after work.
I'll be waiting.
Let's hear why he didn't come...
and why he didn't even call.
You're meeting Seo Min Gi today,
aren't you?
Hey.
What if someone hears you?
Did you do something wrong?
Why date someone
if you're going to keep it a secret?
That's because
it's an office romance.
After you meet him,
call me.
Why?
Just do as I say.
Why are you so reckless?
It's the same with Holly.
How could you say you'd do it
without any plans?
What?
What's wrong with him?
Oh, my.
Goodness.
- What...
- Ma'am, let me check your IV.
My gosh. Where did she go?
Wait.
(Registration, Cashier)
Goodness.
(General Ward B)
Oh, excuse me.
There's a female patient
who was admitted last night.
She's pretty tall
and strongly built.
Her hair comes down
past her shoulders.
- Ma'am, she's not here.
- Haven't you seen her?
I think she has run away.
I'll see where she went
and go after her.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Goodness. Where has she gone?
Oh, dear.
Audrey.
Why are you sitting here like this?
Please... Help me.
Hae Joon's family
won't leave me alone.
If they know
that I'm living near Geon...
I can't get caught.
Mr. Maeng. Please...
They're scary people.
- Help me.
- I will help.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Oh, please...
They say...
they can't allow anyone
besides her guardian...
to check the security footage.
So? Are you saying you lost her?
I'm looking for her
in every way I can.
We don't know what she might do.
Dan Soo...
If my Dan Soo were to find out...
Ma'am, you must get some rest...
How could I get any rest?
How on earth did she find out
that Hae Joon had died...
and come here like this?
She was hiding quietly for 20 years,
but all of a sudden?
Does she have money issues?
I'll look into that too.
She must want something...
to suddenly show up like this.
The likes of her never let go
once they've got their grips on you.
That vermin.
If I can control her with money,
I'll do that.
If not, I will make her afraid.
She is...
a dirty secret weighing me down
all my life.
I will never let Dan Soo meet her.
Miss.
You should smile.
If you smile brightly
with a wedding dress on,
the groom will be blown away.
As if.
The man out there
probably won't care that much.
Whenever he says anything,
he just has to mention my age.
Does he think he won't get older?
Am I the only one
who gets older each year?
Come on. Any man would be overcome
with emotions in this situation.
And even the most stoic groom...
will be moved to tears...
to see his bride
in a dress like this.
Then, he'll start acting
like a photographer...
and take 100 or 200 photos.
You just can't stop them.
Will he...
really act like that?
Here comes the bride.
What's with his reaction?
It's not like him to be so touched.
Oh, my.
This is seriously incredible.
Does it look that nice?
How does it cover it up so well?
What?
Cover what up?
How does it cover up
her belly fat so well?
This isn't just a dress.
It's the result of modern science.
The shape of the torso covers up
your chubby belly perfectly.
Who is the designer?
Is it a scientist?
No...
That's enough.
And this isn't just belly fat.
This is...
It is proof that
our Ssook Ssook is growing well.
Yes, I'm an ob-gyn.
I've seen so many women's bellies
in early pregnancy.
Your belly right now...
is exactly
100 percent pure belly fat.
Hey! Shut your mouth.
Unbelievable.
It's a wonder of the world!
This design is a miracle.
I told you to shut your mouth.
Why? Turn around.
Let's see
if your love handles are poking out.
You punk!
No, miss!
I think I heard something...
This is all your fault.
Whatever.
I'm sorry.
Were you waiting for a while?
Compared to how long I waited
in the park,
this wasn't that long.
Gong Hee.
I actually have something
to tell you.
What is it...
that you're hesitating so much?
Let's...
break up.
Pardon?
I'm sorry.
Is that...
What do you mean...
Why?
At least give me a reason...
There must be a reason.
I don't think
I can tell you the details.
I think that would be better
for you too.
I don't understand
anything you're saying right now.
It just happened.
"It just happened?"
Do you know
when I heard that before?
When my parents made me...
quit going to a study hall
to pay for my brother's tutors.
When I was taken out
of the school's scholarship list...
because of
a professor's favorite student.
That's what people say...
when they don't even have
a good reason to give.
"It just happened."
"I can't bother to tell you,
so just understand."
That's what that means.
Please know this, though.
I was sincere in every moment...
I was with you.
If you were sincere
in every moment...
(Ji Na)
Well...
That was an urgent call.
I should get going.
So,
that's it?
I know I'm not allowed
to say the word "sorry."
But still, I'm sorry.
I'm really...
sorry.
As of today,
Seo Min Gi's time is mine.
Would you marry me?
You blindsided me.
I didn't put a ring inside a cake.
What will you do if I say no?
Then we'll fight like crazy again.
What should I break this time?
Not the vase.
I'll break the TV or something.
I was going to
propose to you properly again.
For a man like you,
I don't care
if I have to propose first.
All you have to do
is give me your answer.
Why do you need to hear my answer?
You already know my answer.
Sorry about that!
Have some.
You know, I'm not a good cook.
I'm not sure if you'll like it.
You help me out every single time.
Eat up so that
you can get your strength back.
You didn't tell Myung Ja, did you?
About Dan Soo.
It's not that I don't trust her.
But if she finds out,
Dan Soo might find out too.
I'm just scared.
I didn't tell anyone.
Put your worries to rest.
Am I being too greedy?
Leaving this place is probably
the right thing to do, but...
Don't leave.
Stay by Dan Soo's side.
You regretted your decision
in the past.
Don't do something
you'll regret again.
Life is too short for that.
I'll help you.
But if I stay by Dan Soo's side...
Can I really do that?
He may resent you,
but you are still his mother.
Embrace his resentment...
so he won't have to
keep it bottled up inside...
and feel miserable anymore.
Hurry up and eat.
You need to get your strength back.
Hurry up and recover.
Once you pull yourself together,
I'll tell you everything.
If you tell me
to get down on my knees, I will.
If you want me to beg you,
I will.
I'll give you the ring
and confess...
everything to you.
My gosh.
Why? What is it?
I've never tasted
porridge like this before.
I can feel every grain of rice
moving around in my mouth.
Oh, no. Goodness.
I'm sorry. Oh, boy.
Goodness. Let me see.
- It wasn't like that earlier.
- Here, I'll finish it.
But I gave you a lot.
That's okay.
Tell me the truth.
What is going on between you
and Ssang Sook's son?
What do you mean, what's going on?
You two.
Nothing's going on, right?
Can I trust you on that?
You need to be careful
when men just want to play you.
Don't be naive
and get betrayed later on.
Mom, what are you talking about?
He wasn't trying to play me.
Then what was he doing?
He's engaged.
What? He's what?
Ssang Sook
couldn't stop bragging about it.
She said she'd be able to tell us
some good news soon.
Apparently, his fiancee is
from a powerful family.
My goodness.
No way. You must be mistaken, Mom.
No, I am not mistaken.
She kept bragging about it nonstop.
She looked like she'd give out
wedding invitations soon.
Mr. Seo Min Gi...
is getting married?
Yes, I told you. What is with you?
Mom, tell me more.
What more do you want to hear?
Don't tell me
you had a one-sided crush on him...
without knowing
that he had a girlfriend.
No, it's not that.
Hey, forget him.
You should never fall for a man
who is nice to every woman.
Do not fall head over heels
for a man like that.
Why would I? I would never.
My goodness.
I guess she really liked him.
Hey.
I told you to call me
when you were done. Why...
Maeng Gong Hee.
What's wrong with me?
Tears keep rolling down my face.
How strange.
Are you all right?
(My Merry Marriage)
Hearing this
might make you uncomfortable.
Could you help me
so I can see Dan Soo often?
Don't you think Gong Hee and Dan Soo
are more than just friends?
Not Gu Dan Soo.
Gong Hee should date someone better.
I wanted to check something
with you.
Are you getting married?
Is that why you broke up with me?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)