I...
I'm going to tell Dan Soo.
What?
I must tell him...
that I'm his mom.
What kind of mother does this?
He is my child,
but I can't even tell him
that I'm his mom.
I have to keep living in hiding.
At this rate,
they'll make a move first.
Before someone else tells Dan Soo,
I want to tell him myself...
and beg for forgiveness.
No, it's fine
even if he doesn't forgive me.
I want to embrace
his resentment too.
I am his mother.
I'll help you.
(Episode 55)
It's been a while since she vanished
from the hospital.
You still haven't found her?
Well, ma'am.
You found her, right?
Where is she now?
The thing is...
What?
If you have a child too,
you must know...
how any parent would feel
in this situation.
Please understand
and give me some time.
I promise you I'll leave
before Chairwoman Hwang finds out.
Give me just a little more time.
Please?
I think we lost her.
It seems that she has left Seoul.
You should've made her promise
that she'd never come back.
Will you let her come and go
as she pleases?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Mr. Seo.
How long has it been
since you started working for me?
Now that you're getting older,
you're losing your touch.
Perhaps,
you should consider retiring soon?
Yes.
I was frustrated with the situation,
so I called her here.
You can go.
Yes, ma'am.
Why did you want to see me,
Ms. Hwang?
I figured we should talk.
Please have a seat.
Ms. Kang came to see me and said...
she had decided
not to marry Dan Soo.
I beg your pardon? Ji Na said that?
No way. Why would she do that?
I guess she didn't consult you
before coming to see me.
Of course, she didn't.
Had I known about it,
I would've stopped her at all costs.
My gosh.
It must've really upset you.
There must have been
some kind of misunderstanding.
She says she has decided against it,
so what can I do?
Let's forget
we ever discussed this marriage.
My goodness, ma'am.
Please don't be like that.
Please don't be mad.
Ji Na is my daughter.
I know that girl better
than she knows herself.
I'm sure it was because
she got overly ambitious about work.
If it's because of
her ambition for work,
I will be sure to give her
everything she wants.
I have no intention of keeping her
holed up at home.
Of course, I know that.
Goodness,
why did she do such a thing?
Don't worry, ma'am.
I will be sure to talk to her.
Can I really leave it up to you?
Of course, ma'am.
You should set a lucky date
for their wedding,
and please wait for Ji Na.
Hey, it's tteokbokki.
You should eat while you work.
What's up with her?
Excuse me.
Yes?
How can I help you?
Oh, well...
Some pain relief patches, please.
My dad has a bad back.
That'll be four dollars.
Oh, please give me
some artificial tears too.
- That'll be seven dollars.
- So...
And some moisturizing cream.
Your total is 15 dollars.
Right.
Well...
A pregnancy test...
(Easy Pregnancy Test Kit)
That's five dollars.
- Do you need folic acid?
- Pardon?
Pregnant women must take folic acid.
Oh, I'm not pregnant.
Well, since you were buying
a test kit...
This isn't for me.
It's for a friend.
Okay.
You're home early.
Oh, yes.
Hey, what are you looking for?
Oh, some digestive medicine.
Gong Hee must have
some digestion issues.
She does?
But that has never happened before.
I think it's because
she's been stressed at work lately.
Even if that's the case, Gong Hee...
has fallen over,
bumped into things, and gotten hurt,
but she's not one to get sick
over small things like indigestion.
Well...
Then I should go
and prick her finger for her.
That's a quick cure
for a case of indigestion.
I see.
Please.
It can't be.
I'm sure I'm not.
I can't be.
No way.
I am...
pregnant?
Here, let me see.
- Go on.
- What...
Why are you all here?
Oh, I went downstairs
to look for digestive medicine,
but your mother and grandma
got worried.
Yes, have a seat.
A prick in the finger is
the best cure for indigestion.
You'll feel better soon.
Hey, why did you do such a thing?
I'm fine, Grandma.
As if you are.
You're as white as a sheet.
- Grandma has magic hands.
- Right.
We should prick your finger
to get your circulation going.
Well...
You should have a seat too.
Goodness. Hey, give me your hand.
You'll feel better soon
after I prick your finger.
I went and bought some medicine.
I'm really okay, Grandma.
Are you sure you're okay?
Have you ever seen me
get an upset stomach?
My stomach is no ordinary stomach.
I've trained it rigorously,
you know.
Sure, you're right, but...
It's no big deal. I have to work,
so you should get going now. Go.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Goodness, I wish
you'd just let me prick your finger.
I'm totally fine.
I'll take my medicine.
- Go on.
- All right.
Are you really okay?
Please, just stop!
Can you stop caring about me?
Why do you go out of your way
to worry...
and get my family involved? Why?
Do you not know why I'm doing that?
I don't want you to be sick,
and I want you to be okay.
I don't know. I don't want to know.
And I don't want to know
how you feel either.
I don't feel comfortable
around you anymore.
Seeing you morning and night...
is uncomfortable and awkward.
So why do you keep
crossing the line?
Does that mean...
I can't even take your side anymore?
I'm not a little kid.
Please just leave me alone!
Gosh, seriously...
This is between Mr. Seo and me.
Take this back.
Goodness. Gu Dan Soo.
Hey, what's with the suitcase?
Are you going somewhere?
Oh, yes.
Where are you going?
It's time to eat soon.
I'm going to go back home now.
To my grandma's house
where I used to live.
Goodness,
will you go back to her house?
Right, don't say that
you'll give me back my rent.
I gave it to you upfront
because I wanted to.
By the way, have you told
Gyeong Tae and Myung Ja about this?
They didn't seem to know.
I'll tell them some other time.
Goodbye.
All right. Oh, dear.
Goodness.
Oh, boy.
I've missed this so much.
Not bothered by anyone else,
and just being alone with you.
We can enjoy it for our whole lives.
Don't get tired of it, okay?
You'll have to think about it
starting right now.
I'm the type that gets easily bored.
Really? But seeing how
we've been doing this...
for over three years,
- I don't think that's true.
- Well...
That must mean I'm addicted to you.
My goodness.
I knew it.
Is it you again?
You should've backed off quietly...
when I explained things nicely.
You had to go and cause trouble?
Mom.
What are you doing right now?
And what about you?
Get your act together, will you?
I can't believe you've been seduced
by some lowlife.
Please speak with me.
I was going to go and see you.
How shameless of you.
Do you think I'll even meet
with the likes of you?
Ji Na and I...
will get married.
We won't break up anymore.
What do you think you're doing, Mom?
Do you want to see me die
from humiliation?
"Humiliation?"
Is this humiliating to you?
You're even more humiliating.
Why must you waste your time
with this good-for-nothing?
Tell him to leave this instant!
We will not break up.
What is this,
the love story of the century?
Shall I wait and see
when you'll let that hand go?
I will never let her hand go.
If you're not going to kick him out,
I'll go ahead
and say everything right here.
Can I do that?
Are you just going to
stand there like that?
If you won't end it...
until he sees you
at your lowest point...
Sure, okay. Let's do that.
Go home.
I'll call you.
Ji Na, you...
It's nothing.
And you shouldn't step in, Min Gi.
Just give us some time.
The two of you have no choice
but to break up anyway.
How far will you push this?
Do you want to see me
hit rock bottom?
"Rock bottom?"
You'll hit rock bottom
if you stay with him.
Do you need a wake-up call?
How far...
do you think you can go with him?
Mom,
if you're going to keep doing this,
I will cut all ties with you.
You'll cut ties with me?
Then how will you support yourself?
Both Min Gi and I have come this far
on our own.
You think you did it on your own?
Do you actually think
you've come this far...
without the help of Dodo Group?
Wake up.
Do you think
you can keep your job...
after breaking off the engagement?
And what about other companies?
What if Chairwoman Hwang makes sure
you can't get a job in the industry?
Then you'd have to do things
you don't want to do...
and curry favor with your superiors
to earn money.
You'll have to live
in a small rental apartment...
and struggle each month.
You want to live like that?
You can't,
because that's not how I raised you.
You can't live like that.
If that's something I have to endure
to be with Min Gi,
I will do it.
Is that so?
Then what about his family?
Do you think
his mother will be okay with it?
his family will welcome you...
even if you're not the daughter
of the Dodo family?
That's right.
His chauffeur father
will get fired too.
Fine. Then go ahead
and take care of his entire family.
Go ahead and live like that!
Mom!
I want to marry him. Can't you
please support my decision?
You do not want to do this.
You don't even know
what you really want!
My gosh, Ji Na...
Even if you do end up marrying him,
you'll split up
in less than three months.
Then you will...
blame me for not stopping you.
You'll lash out at me.
I know you very well.
Well, just wait here.
I'll go and get him.
Thank you,
for letting me use this space too.
I sent Gyeong Sol somewhere,
so don't worry. Just wait here.
(Oh Pine, You Verdant Pine)
It looks like me.
Looking lonely,
standing there all alone.
I couldn't even stop him...
because he looked so upset.
I don't think it's a good thing
that he's moving back home.
He should've at least waited
to say goodbye to us.
Will he be okay there?
He eats two bowls of rice
at every meal.
He'll have to
walk on eggshells there.
He said he'd visit us later
to say goodbye.
What are you talking about?
Someone moved?
Who?
Dan Soo. He's moving back home.
He already packed up and left.
Hey, Dan Soo.
Earlier,
I was dealing with something,
so I was on edge.
It's not your fault.
It had nothing to do with you.
It's just...
I'm just going through something.
That's all.
Hey, are you listening?
Gu Dan Soo.
What is this?
(Oh Pine, You Verdant Pine)
He's not coming.
He won't come.
Who'd want to see
such an awful mother?
Don't cry for me
Don't be sad for me
Don't look at me like that
You look like
you've lost all meaning to life
That look on your face
Don't love me
It's too late
Don't wait for me with bated breath
Our love has come to an end
Why did you
Just let me leave
Had I known
I would regret it once again
He refused to come, didn't he?
His awful mother...
I'm such an awful mother.
Dan Soo moved out.
What?
I think he went back
to his grandmother's place.
Then it really is all over now.
As his mother...
and as a neighbor too.
I'll never see Dan Soo again.
How could this happen?
How?
I met him again after 20 years,
and we have to be separated again
like this.
How could this happen? How?
How is this possible?
Even so,
how could you ditch me and leave?
How rude.
Since when did you listen to me?
Where are you, Dan Soo?
How much time do I have left?
Well...
If you just control your temper,
you could live to be 100.
Mr. Seo.
We should find a new doctor.
All he knows...
is to say sweet words in my ear.
This man is getting old too.
I should get Dan Soo
to do his part...
and hand over my position to him.
I've been in this position
for too long.
My position as the chairwoman.
You will be all right, ma'am.
Forget it.
Don't let on to Dan Soo.
Pretend you know nothing.
I'll tell him in due time.
Grandma, I'm home!
- Go.
- Yes, ma'am.
What is this?
Why isn't anyone coming?
Weren't you waiting for me, Grandma?
Oh, goodness.
What brings you here at this hour?
You told me to come home.
I, Gu Dan Soo, am back as of today.
I came to grant Grandma's wish.
Where is she, by the way?
I want to tell her in person.
Oh, she just fell asleep.
Even if someone
were to shake her awake...
or carry her away,
she wouldn't know.
Oh, that's fine.
What?
Of course. You wouldn't go anywhere.
Hey, did you...
It wasn't him.
Yes, this is it.
A bed should be big and cozy,
indeed.
It was such a bother...
to get up and turn off the lights
each time too.
Civilization is a great thing.
Oh, good.
I'm comfortable, for sure.
So why am I like this?
Will Gong Hee be okay...
on her own?
(My Merry Marriage)
Grandma, we will bow to you.
Live happily on your own.
- Gosh, of course.
- Oh, my.
If you get divorced twice...
Why are you saying
such a ridiculous thing?
Who are you?
How could you leave like that
without saying anything?
Why would you skip work too?
There's someone I don't want
to run into for the time being.
Who on earth is it
for him to act this way?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)