Why don't you...
just stay here?
Oh, I haven't seen that ring before.
Oh, this.
It's a meaningful ring to me.
But I had a bit of a situation,
so I couldn't wear it.
I guess
someone gave it to you as a gift.
Yes, someone.
Someone who is very cool...
and has a big heart.
Dan Soo.
You remind me of that person.
I remind you of that person?
Then he must be very handsome.
May I ask you who this person is?
Dan Soo, you must be really popular
among women.
Is it that obvious?
My gosh.
My popularity knows no bounds.
But why is it
that she won't fall for my charms?
To be honest,
I didn't come here
to talk to you about my grandmother.
I told Maeng Gong Hee
how I really feel about her.
My gosh, really?
She rejected me without hesitation.
So, she's awkward around me now.
She keeps avoiding me.
That's why I'm even more torn.
Maybe I really should move out.
Dan Soo.
Don't be like that.
Just wait patiently.
They say
there's a right time for everything.
Some are destined to part ways,
while some are meant to meet again.
Everything is predetermined,
but everyone struggles
because it's not the right time yet.
Dan Soo.
Your time will come too.
I'm sure of it.
Do you think so?
I hope you're right.
Yes.
For you...
and me both.
The right time will come. Trust me.
Gong Hee gave it to me
and said to use it...
to help you
with your wedding expenses.
I think it's about 2,000 dollars.
Oh, my. Everyone is so kind to us.
How modest.
So modest.
And this right here.
I terminated my insurance.
But it's not much.
I gathered
all the money I could get.
It's about 3,500 dollars.
My, I will gladly accept this.
How little and precious.
So little.
Thanks.
He was greatly hurt
by his first marriage.
I never thought
he'd want to get married again.
I'm truly grateful you helped him...
change his mind.
I had a lonely life.
I'm really happy that
I finally have a family, Mother.
I will also consider you
as another daughter of mine.
Thank you.
Even so, you're not allowed
to barge in on us whenever you want.
Gosh, stop it.
If you want to drop off food for us,
there are many ways you can do it.
Leave it at the security office,
or use the delivery service.
Stop.
Hong Dan, don't worry.
I'm not the type of mother-in-law...
who visits without any notice.
Oh, I'm not worried.
My goodness.
Visit us without any notice?
You surely shouldn't do that.
I get that it's not a lot of money,
but she won't even thank me?
And what's wrong with me
visiting my son's place?
I brought it up
without thinking much.
She could've just told me
to visit anytime.
It's a good thing
that she's not pretentious,
but it won't hurt to act coy
at times.
I don't like her one bit.
Gosh, Mother.
I don't plan to live...
under the same roof as my in-laws,
with a once-married man.
Let's live as far away...
as possible from each other, Mother.
This is nice.
- Goodness.
- What are you doing?
(Goho Wedding Hall)
Hi.
Ms. Eom!
Hey!
What?
What is it? What's wrong?
It is you, Ms. Eom!
I thought I had come into
the wrong bridal room.
How stunning!
Stop it.
It's not too late to marry me.
You're too good for Maeng Gong Boo.
Shall I do that?
Will you hold my hand...
and run away with me?
My goodness, Ms. Eom!
You look like a real bride
in that dress.
They say every bride is beautiful.
It must be true.
I'm jealous.
You should get married too, Yoo Ra.
Oh, remember you promised
to catch my bouquet today?
You have to throw it to me
at pinpoint, okay?
I'm dead serious about it.
Weren't you busy?
But you still came.
Your dress is so old-fashioned.
It's not my cup of tea.
Gosh. You just have to spoil things
to feel better, don't you?
Seriously.
(Goho Wedding Hall)
(Groom: The son of Maeng Gyeong Tae
and Kang Myung Ja, Maeng Gong Boo)
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Goodness. Congratulations!
Hey, you. You made it.
You came too, Aunt.
Gong Boo! My goodness, you punk.
I can't believe
you're getting married again.
Congratulations.
You've done this before.
Are you still nervous?
You can really crack a joke.
Thanks to you, I'm relaxed now.
Holding a wedding
at breakneck speed isn't proper.
Well, I understand...
she got pregnant
before marriage, but...
Goodness. Stop saying useless things
on such a happy day.
- Let's head inside.
- Let's go.
- Go on in.
- Hold on.
- Come now.
- Take them to their seats.
- Goodness.
- Give them corner seats.
Wait, Gong Boo.
(Korea OB-GYN Association)
- Myung Ja!
- Myung Ja.
- Congratulations.
- Welcome.
- We haven't seen you in ages.
How long has it been?
- Gyeong Tae.
- Isn't this Sam Seok?
Hold on. Excuse me for a minute.
Gyeong Tae is the same as always.
And you've gotten prettier,
Myung Ja.
It's because
I've got makeup on today.
My knees ache and such
because I'm getting old.
You said you had to stay
at the hospital and couldn't come.
Well, I couldn't miss this day.
I'm happy to see you smiling,
Myung Ja.
Have you seen Mom?
- Oh, Mom?
- Mom?
I'm right here!
- Mom!
- Oh, my.
- Mom.
Aren't you two busy?
I'm surprised you could make it.
I took the morning off
to see you, Mom.
You know we haven't seen each other
in a while, right?
Of course, I know that.
I had to look after my in-laws
in the hospital, but I came here.
Aren't I such a good daughter, Mom?
Yes, you are.
My, gathering all together
like this...
is truly nice, Myung Ja.
Gong Hee. Escort your grandma
and aunts to their seats.
Okay. Grandma and aunts, follow me.
- Let's go.
- You've gotten prettier, Gong Hee.
- That's not true.
- Slow down.
Myung Ja. Congratulations!
It's a relief that...
your eldest son is getting married.
Thanks.
I didn't invite you.
Why are you here?
I came because of Gyeong Tae.
Gyeong Tae's eldest son
is getting married.
Of course, I should be here
as his sweet friend.
"Sweet friend?"
Did you invite her, honey?
It's a happy occasion
for Gyeong Tae's family.
Must I be invited to be here?
That's so cold.
Gyeong Tae.
Aren't you happy to see me?
She must've lost her mind.
Stop being silly.
Leave after the meal.
Do you have to ruin this happy day?
Hey, am I some evil spirit or what?
- Enough. Let's go inside.
- Gosh, come on.
- Goodness. Cut her some slack.
- What's her problem?
Gyeong Tae. I'm here.
- My gosh, Detective An.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks for coming.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations, Myung Ja.
- This really is no joke.
- Is it?
I'm all over the place.
Once is more than enough.
- Finally, he's getting hitched.
- That's right.
Oh, my.
What?
It's good to see you.
- What?
- You scared me.
Hey, what's with your face?
Did you put on something?
No, nothing at all.
My skin has always been fair
like a peach.
And my cheeks are always rosy,
you know.
Gyeong Tae, aren't I right?
No.
You look sick, in the head.
It was a long way here, right?
Have you been well?
- Thank you.
- Dan Soo.
- Oh, hi.
You made it.
Isn't this job tough?
You may not believe me,
but I used to handle big money.
Someone upright like me
should handle money.
Why do you look so pretty today?
Stop being silly.
When will they be here?
The wedding ceremony
will soon begin.
Guests, please take your seat.
The bride and the groom
will enter now.
Bride and groom, please enter.
How pretty!
If I lose my footing and stagger,
you have to hold me tight, okay?
Why is the almighty Eom Hong Dan
so nervous?
I didn't think I'd get nervous.
But I'm a nervous wreck right now.
By the way,
do we really have to get married?
What are you saying now?
I had another nightmare last night.
It was about serving
in the military twice.
Would you like to get beaten up
by your bride at your wedding?
Can't you just hold my hand tight?
Before the groom walks down
with the bride while holding hands,
let's have him shout...
how happy he is today.
Shout with all your might!
I want...
to go back!
What was that?
- Seriously.
- Nice one.
He's in trouble now.
- Goodness.
- What?
Good grief.
What was that about?
What was that?
That little...
- That fool.
- Go back, where?
How embarrassing.
- It's okay.
- No, don't mind him.
Doors are closing.
(We're getting married.)
"One. Maeng Gong Boo will only love
Eom Hong Dan forever."
"Two. Maeng Gong Boo will obey
Eom Hong Dan no matter what."
"I, Eom Hong Dan,
sternly warn Maeng Gong Boo..."
"that he will not be forgiven
if he violates any of the above."
"And I, Eom Hong Dan,
promise that I will do my best..."
"to protect our love
and our marriage."
"From time to time, I will cook
your favorite dishes for you."
"I will do my best to make sure
that you can end your day..."
"with a smile on your face."
"Your forever life partner,
Eom Hong Dan."
"I, Maeng Gong Boo,"
"will love and respect
Eom Hong Dan..."
"in plenty and in want,"
"in joy and in sorrow,
in sickness and in health."
Here are my additional vows.
"First."
"I will quit drinking
and start exercising regularly..."
"to improve my strength
and stamina..."
"so that we can enjoy
some passionate nights!"
Nice!
- Very cool.
- Go for it!
Let's see
how long you can keep up with it.
- "Second."
- Good luck!
- "Three times a month,"
- That fool.
"I will take care of
all the house chores..."
"so my bride can fully rest."
"For three days of each month,"
"I will be her faithful servant."
I am at your command, ma'am!
How romantic!
"I will keep these vows
deeply engraved in my heart..."
"and will always stay..."
"by Eom Hong Dan's side."
"Together, we will build..."
My gosh. Did I eat something bad?
Why do I feel so queasy?
Bride and groom.
Put your marriage
before anything else.
Even before your parents
and children.
Your spouse comes first.
"You're always right."
"Oh, my. You look so dashing today."
Like this.
Listen up.
Give compliments
to boost each other's confidence.
- He's funny.
- That's my advice for you.
Last but not least,
here's my advice for the bride,
which is like my gift to you.
Bride, even if your husband...
does something silly
from time to time,
don't scold him harshly.
- I'll be right back.
- As I've always said to you,
try to nag him...
in a polite manner
to help and guide him.
(Restroom)
Why are you out here
instead of watching the ceremony?
I was collecting cash gifts
for them.
It looked like I'd already missed
all the important parts.
Anyway, why did you
suddenly run out of there?
I thought something happened.
Oh, it's nothing.
My stomach is a little upset.
I thought you could digest anything
and everything.
Well, should I step out
and pick up some antacids for you?
No, it's fine. I'm okay now.
Gong Hee.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Seo.
Of course, I should be here.
Can you give us some privacy?
Am I...
crossing the line...
by just standing here now?
Are you all right?
You don't look so well.
Are you feeling sick?
I believe
showing interest like this...
is inappropriate if you only
think of me as a co-worker.
Thank you for rooting for me
as my co-worker,
but please do not show
too much interest.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
Come to think of it,
it wasn't solely your mistake.
I misunderstood your intention,
so I made a mistake too.
Stop looking at me
as if you pity me.
It makes me so uncomfortable.
I'm doing great.
Thank you again for coming today.
Applause!
Darling, I love you
My love
- You are
- Only you!
The only one for me
I love you, honey
- Oh, my.
- A life without you
What a lovely couple.
- Is completely
- Nice!
Meaningless
It is so odd.
I'm talking about Ji Na.
Why do you think
she suddenly changed her mind?
Look into it.
Find out
if she's seeing another man.
When a woman changes her mind
like this,
it's always because of another man.
But we can't be sure
that she has another man...
There's another man involved.
I'm sure of it.
She's smart.
The reason she suddenly lost...
her rational thinking
and is being like this.
She has another man.
It's the only reason.
We should be expediting
the wedding...
and making sure
Dan Soo moves back home,
but Ji Na is causing trouble now.
I must know
why Ji Na is doing this...
and who this guy is.
Find out.
I will teach them a lesson.
Yes, ma'am.
All right.
We'll take the picture now.
Sir, could you move closer?
Yes, that's better.
I see that she's ready
to catch the bouquet.
All right.
When the bride tosses the bouquet,
- please give her a big hand.
- Okay.
Okay, throw it
on the count of three.
Catch it.
One, two, three!
- What?
- Gong Hee caught it?
- What happened?
- Hey, Gong Hee caught it.
- Nice.
- She should get married.
- Hey!
Oh, no.
What is this?
Gong Hee,
I can't believe you caught it.
Well, I guess my sister-in-law
is getting married next.
What?
- We can collect cash gifts again?
- What?
Hey, Dan Soo. We'll need you
at the cash gift booth again.
No way. I won't do it.
Find someone else.
Okay, we'll take it again.
Look at the camera.
Honey, what is it?
What?
One moment.
Where are you going?
We have to take our picture!
(Groom: The son of Maeng Gyeong Tae
and Kang Myung Ja, Maeng Gong Boo)
(Groom Maeng Gong Boo,
Bride Eom Hong Dan)
Was I mistaken?
Yes, there's no way she came.
Maeng Gong Boo.
What are you doing here?
You must be flustered
since you never invited me.
I came to congratulate you.
Congratulations.
I can give you a hug, right?
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, sorry.
It must've gotten caught
in my button.
How did you find me here?
I can find out anything
if I set my mind to it.
Hey, you...
Who attends
their ex-husband's wedding?
That's why I'm leaving quietly.
But you chased after me.
Oh, right.
I'll soon send you a gift...
to congratulate you.
I don't need a gift.
How have you been?
You blocked my number
and broke off all contact.
All I heard was that
you transferred to a local hospital.
Your wedding isn't over yet.
Am I wrong?
Go back inside.
Your bride must be waiting.
You two are now in the same boat.
Paddle hard together, okay?
It's a small boat that will wobble
if even one side misses.
Make sure to work together
to paddle forth. Got it?
Okay, Grandma.
Thank you.
Gosh, my sweetheart.
Goodness.
Everyone, thank you.
We'll have fun.
- Have a safe trip.
- Yes.
Enjoy, okay?
Always be safe
and take care of yourself.
Yes, and have
the most romantic night.
Of course.
We'll have a steamy night.
- My goodness.
- Oh, dear.
- Steamy hot.
- You, come with me.
I'll make your back
as hot as highway blacktop.
I was just giving him a massage.
Does it feel good?
You had a long day.
- A massage.
- I see.
She gives me a message
every single day.
It's hitting the spot.
Goodness.
The wedding was too small in size.
But the ceremony was fun.
You call that fun?
It lacked class.
Mother, we chose
this wedding hall at a hotel.
Would you like to have a look?
Gosh, why would I?
It's your wedding.
It's yours to look at.
But you have great taste, Mother.
And this wedding isn't just for us.
The family elders
will make the venue look classier.
Is that so?
My goodness.
Will it be held at a hotel?
Of course.
Only then is it not embarrassing
to invite guests.
That's what I'm talking about.
You're fine with it, right?
Mother likes it too.
As long as you two
are happy with it,
I'm in.
I rarely say this,
but don't you think...
Min Gi would make
the best husband in the world?
I only approved this marriage
because it's you, Ji Na.
My son is so amazing.
Anything less than this...
does not meet our standards.
Luxurious.
Gorgeous.
It's right up my street.
Oh, boy.
It really isn't easy
to marry off your children.
People come in crowds.
There are many important guests
to take care of.
Goodness.
At least
you got a load off your chest.
She's right.
Now that Gong Boo is married,
you've got nothing to worry about.
Remember you said the same thing
when Gong Boo...
- married Soo Yeon five years ago?
- Right.
I thought I'd be done
once he got married.
Gong Boo will do better, Mom.
Don't worry.
Gong Hee is right.
The wedding went well.
I'll go home tomorrow.
How come, Mom?
Leave after you see Gong Boo...
when he comes back
from his honeymoon.
No, Grandma.
Stay a little longer, okay?
Please do that.
If you leave,
Myung Ja will be really upset.
I don't need to see them again.
I already saw them at their wedding.
Why do you think about leaving...
the minute you're at my house, Mom?
You don't need to work
in your garden anymore.
Come on, Mom.
My goodness.
Myung Ja has changed.
The older she gets,
the more stubborn she becomes.
I take after you, Mom.
Was the meal at the wedding hall
a bit greasy?
Auntie. Do we have
soy sauce marinated crab?
- Soy sauce marinated crab? We do.
- Yes.
I was craving it too. Hold on.
Is Dad having dinner over there?
He didn't have to take...
the family elders to Uncle's place.
Dad must not want to part with them.
And he must've wanted
to treat them too.
She's right. They congratulated
Gong Boo on his second marriage...
because Gyeong Tae...
takes such good care of them.
But they get into a fight
whenever they get together.
I wonder
if they'll let him off easily today.
I can't help but feel anxious.
Here. It's soy sauce marinated crab
that I, Maeng Gyeong Bok,
- made with all my heart.
- Yes.
Would you like to try it?
Let's have a look.
- Ta-da.
- Oh, my.
Nice.
(My Merry Marriage)
Gyeong Tae. Your mother said,
"My son is suffering..."
"because he married
the wrong woman."
You had crossed the line back then.
You shouldn't have made
my mother-in-law...
get down on her knees!
What did you say?
You're amazing, Gong Hee.
You're in contact with Holly?
I'm going to tell Dan Soo.
I must tell him that I'm his mom.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)