Subtitles brought to you by The ♥ to Heart Team @Viki
Over here! Over here!
OVER HERE!
Here...
OVER HERE! OVER HERE! OVER HERE!
Ko Yi Suk! Ko Yi Suk!
Ko Yi Suk!
Episode 6
It has not been long since I replaced it.
How can we have a defective bulb in nowadays?
It is all because of you! You bring misfortunes.
You have to increase my self-esteem. Why are you discouraging me?
For a while, don't expect nice comments from me.
It's all done.
Here you go. Give me the new one.
Here.
Your bruises are all better now.
What are you doing?
Just because. I want to know how it feels.
Are you joking with me?
Really...
Stop touching me.
I think I liked it.
That time...
I keep thinking about you.
I feel weird when I see you.
I really like Detective Jang.
Really. I really like him.
I liked it as well. You, that day.
Our bodies get along so well.
What?
People say that sex is important for the marriage as well.
You are shameless.
What do you think you know?
I was once a stay-home-loner. What do you think I did alone at home?
Porno?
This and that. I've read your book, too.
Why did I read that book? I got the wrong message that you are a nice doctor.
People have to know the truth.
Truth about me?
What is the truth about me?
You are alcohol.
Like cigarettes, drugs, something bad.
Something that is addicting.
What? What are you saying?
I am what? Like alcohol, cigarettes, and drugs?
- Come here.
- Don't!
- I'm going to fall.
- I am alcohol, cigarettes, and drugs?
I am an alcohol and cigarette?  Come here.
Come here!
Don't do it.
I am going to get you addicted to me. Come here.
- Come over here!
- Aish!
Aish, aish?
Com here! Ah, feels good.
- What are you doing?
- Can you massage your doctor?
Massage my shoulder.
Aigoo, aigoo.
Seriously...
What is it?
Excuse me.
I came here because I was worried about how you were out of reach.
It's good that you look all right.
Ko Yi Suk must be a talented doctor.
I think it is my first hearing you laugh.
I went to your house worrying that something happened. You didn't pick up your phone.
I couldn't find your scooter either, so here I am.
I am talking to myself again.
I guess you have decided to consult with Ko Yi Suk again.
I will go now since I know you are well.
Please do your treatment well.
If you have any good news...
No.
I hope you have a good result.
Hong do, it is cold. Please get inside.
♫ Even if I'm lonely and young, if we go together ♫
♫That soft touch and voice ♫
♫ That moment that I can't go back to, ♫
♫ If I can feel you...♫
What if there is a good news?
Then, what?
Where are you?
January 23, the journal. I want to cook a lot.
I also want to do knitting a lot. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it.
I miss [subject unknown].
What does she want to do?
Aish!
It irritates me the more I look.
Look at the writing. Terrible.
Hey, why did Detective Jang come?
Why would he get mad when she is not even his?
Detective Jang has twisted mind.
It's like he doesn't want it, but he doesn't want to give it to anyone else either.
Why does he care if I sleep or live with her, when she's not even his?
What rights does he have to step in?
What are you talking about?
Giving what? What does Detective step in?
It just...
It's something he would know one day.
I didn't make a story that didn't happen.
I told him that we slept together.
You shouldn't have hope about how Detective Jang followed you here.
Man knows man. He came here because he was angry at me. He doesn't like you.
What did you tell him?
Hey! Cockroaches!
Come fast and kill it!
Die! Come, come fast!
Hey!
Come, come quickly!
Die! Kill it!
Kill it!
How, how could you say such thing?
How could you say that so easily?
How? So easily!
You are a bastard!
You are really a jerk!
Aish, I have to kill the cockroaches...
I think my head is bleeding.
I am going to get you addicted.
No, we're having dinner after work.
Cha Hong Do and I slept together.
Stop!
Detective Jang, I like you.
This is my last gift.
Thank you very much for everything.
Ow!
Stop, stop!
Stop!
Hong Do, do you have anything to say to me?
I am using it well.
Thank you.
I have a favor.
I want you to be careful.
Miss Hong Do, I want you to cherish yourself more.
Think about yourself more dearly.
I am sorry.
About what?
Whatever happened, there is nothing to be sorry about.
So, you don't have to look so guilty.
Then, I'll be going.
Take care.
Are you sleeping?
I am going to stay here for 2 minutes. Just 2 minutes.
How did I sleep the whole night, hugging her?
Grandma, are you going or not?
Yes.
Sleep is sleep. I need to work to survive.
In Western proverbs, a person's personality
reveals from monologue.
What did you just say?
No, no! I just said that I should work hard.
Look at this.
There is something that I just passed by once.
Some of them, I went back many times because I liked it.
These are all memories, right?
I want to put them all together to publish a book.
Old pictures.
Wow,
When you were young, you looked very handsome!
You must've been popular.
Well, it is not just about the past.
In the book, you should put some old pictures and your past memories.
Then, you should introduce nearby restaurants.
The concept should be bike road.
I actually thought about that once.
Then, have you checked internet cafes (forum) or bike clubs?
Popular bike roads could be easily found at those websites.
Internet cafe?
Why would you ride a bike at a cafe?
We should get you registered in a cafe first.
So old-fashioned.
I am not making stuff up.
What's so special about Detective Jang finding out?
Did I go too far?
Why is she not answering her phone?
If she goes to a not-answering-phone contest, she might win.
- Welcome!
- Is the store open yet?
You have to wait a little till the bread is done.
I will wait.
Oh, sorry. I just saw the text.
You already arrived?
Ok, I will be there soon.
Hey, Da Yeong. Sorry, were you waiting?
What's wrong now? I was surprised.
Drink some water first. You must have run.
You've never seen me like this, right?
I want to say I have no make-up on, but I put on some BB cream.
I put it on very fast so I might look weird.
No, you look like you have no make up on.
I like this new look. It's so natural.
You know I really like this side of you, right?
But, we should re-think about our marriage.
Da Yeong, did anything happen at the Ahn Dong?
Aunt called and told me that you did well.
I was having a really hard time.
There was piles of bean squares when I went there.
It's seriously the first time I've seen that since I was born.
I thought it is okay to have 12 family rituals per year.
But, it turned out it wasn't okay.
I have to take care of the people in my family who are living, not only the ancestors.
I was eating lunch after making the bean paste. I prepared rice for 26 people.
I am sorry. I should have stopped you from going there.
At night, if you called me and asked me if I was all right, then everything would have been all right.
Sorry. I didn't think that far.
Do Soo, have you ever been in love with someone before?
Real love.
If I felt the true love from you,
I would not have been reluctant about the marriage.
I thought it was simply your personality. But, that's not true.
My words aren't wrong, right?
What now?
I am Ko Yi Suk. Can I see you now?
Since you didn't tell me when I asked you before, just tell me now.
I don't like to come here either.
Since it was difficult decision to show up here, you have to tell me the address of Hong Do.
I need to talk to her. I am asking you based on name of her personal doctor.
I thought you lost your name as a doctor by yourself.
Okay, I got it.
I just stopped by before heading to personal detective services. Then, you go ahead with your thing.
Stay away from Hong Do.
Detective Jang, when was your wedding again?
I'm thinking about going with Hong Do.
I'm going to say this again, stay away from Hong Do.
Why do I have to? Are you mad I got her first?
You were looking for a chance to have her for 7 years
and I took her so you're disappointed?
Qualified or what not, whatever I do or don't with Cha Hong Do, stay out of my business!
Even if I had to live with her and take her in, I wouldn't give her to you.
You're going to take her in and live with her?
To you, is a woman someone without a heart, a toy, that you play with and get sick of and throw away?
Find someone else, just not Hong Do.
If you keep bothering her...I won't stay put.
Acting like you care for her...
It's like you have two personalities. You should go to the hospital for that.
I told you to leave Hong Do!!
Let go.
If you wrong her in any way, then you'll die by my hands.
This damn...
What's wrong? What's wrong with you?
Is something wrong?
It's all right.
- No.
I thought you were going to break it.
You have one new voice message.
It's me. Even if you didn't learn how to socialize, this isn't right.
Frequently cutting off contact and having unexcused absences whenever you don't like something. It's a really bad attitude.
Call me right away, or I'm going into your neighborhood and ringing the bell of every door to find you. You think I can't do it?
I already called Detective Jang and nagged him to give me your address.
Are you really going to be like this?
If you have a problem, you have to think about how to solve it! It doesn't make any sense to hide behind closed doors.
If you don't want to live alone in the world, come out and fight. Let's fight, woman!
Why did you look for Detective Jang!?
Ah, this psycho! I'm going to kill him today!
Eat some of this.
I'm not having a good day today.
Does it make sense to have a divorce at 60?
My Mom said she can't live with my Dad anymore.
Man, I've only heard of such cases...but it's happening to my family.
I thought their relationship was good, so why?
It was unstable.
I saw another side of you for the first time earlier.
I thought you were going to break the bending machine.
I don't think I can get married.
That's why I told you to propose!
Having someone like you and living with them is a really hard thing to do.
This is why I choose not to date.
It's because you're choosing not to? It's because you can't.
I'm choosing not to.
Why did you go to Detective Jang? What did you want to talk to him about?
What are you that you go talk to Detective Jang?!
I'm already embarrassed and apologetic to death. Did he commit a sin or what?
Why did you go and bother someone who had nothing to do with me? Why? Why? Why?
Give me your home address. Then I'll stop contacting him.
Hey! If you throw that, I'm going to file a report with the police.
Sit over there.
I have nothing to say to you. From now on, don't contact me again.
Hey, why did you sleep with me?
Stop bringing that up! I'm already dying of regret!
It just...happened that way.
You didn't know about the reason and neither did I.
At that moment, we bonded and were attracted to each other.
I told you to stop, dammit! Is that something to be brag about?
Talking to Detective Jang about what we did was like that too. At that moment, it just suddenly happened.
I didn't do it on purpose.
That doesn't matter now. Everything ended anyways.
Hey! Wait a minute!
I'm sorry, okay? I did wrong.
I really did wrong, okay?
I didn't ask how you felt about it.
You wanted to keep it a secret, right?
I admit that I did it out of my own way without considering your thoughts. I'm very sorry.
I don't know what is true anymore. It all seems like a joke.
You don't trust me?
Then how can you receive the treatment?
I'll think about it.
Hey, what are you?
What are you doing there? Come out.
I came for counseling. What about it?
I did a search on "Ko Yi Suk", and you're quite famous.
There are some bad rumors about yourself too.
Well, I thought you'd be better than Professor Uhm, who's a frustrating ajumma,
so I switched. Counsel me.
You can't just decide to switch on your own. Get out.
I was taking my last exam and during it...
Hey, don't talk. Hurry, get out.
I asked you to just listen. On the exam paper, I...
- Hey, you're not getting out?
- I won't get out.
I have to be here for an hour. Should I go out and go off the rails? Are you going to take responsibility?
You can go to your counselor Professor Uhm!
About the exam, people say that I ripped it to shreds and ate it.
I don't remember anything.
Where are you going?
He's frustrating too!
Why is she in my room? Did you tell her to leave?
She fired me. She wants to be counseled by you.
Why do you attract so many women? Anthrophobic patient,
a grandmother, and even a middle schooler.
What kind of combination is it?
Sheesh, just because a kid wants to switch, you switch?
I can't do this anymore.
It doesn't even show that I'm volunteering for free.
Is anyone even going to acknowledge me for treating people in this rural village?
I've stuck it out this long, so it's enough. I'm declaring my freedom now.
Can you see a patient alone?
Is your phobia gone?
Sheesh, you can't even see patients by yourself. How are you going to declare your freedom?
Then there has to be a good excuse at least, such as giving counseling for free.
Like seniors living alone, or poor people.
But that girl, is she the head of her household?
Everything she was wearing was designer.
She's my friend's daughter.
I should have known.
It's going to be extremely uncomfortable.
I guess I'll need to so some free volunteer work.
For the sake of our Professor who hasn't even gotten married while her friend's daughter is so grown up.
You little... stop talking nonsense.
What happened with the girl who you're working with?
You guys are so easy. After sleeping together,
how can you just work together like nothing happened?
It's because you're so conservative,
that you haven't been able to marry yet.
Get out! Get out!
Here!
That...
lazy brat.
Hey, take your helmet off.
What's wrong with her? Is she sick?
Her face is red.
Is it that you want to be counseled by me, or do you just dislike Professor Uhm?
"Do you like your Mom or your Dad?" Those kinds of questions that require making a choice,
You make me choose a side.
Do you think I looked at Dr. Uhm and thought that I wanted to be counseled by her?
But, if I answer that I hate Dr. Uhm, and you know her and my mom are friends,
so you'll think, "Ah, she has problems with her Mom." That's childishly simple.
You're so good at asking questions cleverly.
You're really smart huh?
But, why did you come here?
To pass time and relieve stress.
Hey, go. Go, go. Okay?
I don't intend to help you kill time, so go.
Is she a doctor too?
That Unni can counsel me.
She's not a doctor. Leave.
There's a reason.
Counsel her. A doctor shouldn't be picky about their patients.
Yes.
Damn.
Breathe in...
Hey, kid, what are you doing?
I heard you came in wasted a few days ago, carried on the back of a policeman.
What? Carried on his back?
That person said he carried me on his back?
How dare he lay his hands on me.
You're talking crap.
Hey, you better not start hanging out with strange guys because you're going to auditions and such.
I'm shipping you off to America!
This is my life, don't worry about it.
I'm learning about all the dirty experiences and bitter experiences in life.
Now I can't trust the police.
What, did you drink because you were upset about something?
No.
I was practicing acting. I was acting drunk.
Your acting practice sure is wild.
Hey, should I get you some water?
Sparkling water, please.
If it was 1947, then let's see...
Aigoo, it's 68 years old!
It's an elder. Elder.
How much did you buy this for?
Well, back then...
It was the price of a sack of rice.
Back then, the price of it was 2,800 won (about $2.80).
It was a luxury item in my time.
My son learned to ride bicycles on this guy, and my grandchild did too.
Oh my! His Grandfather is the Chairman of a bicycle company,
but why didn't he ride a new bicycle instead of this old thing?
There's a side to him that's like that.
Since he was young, he would never get sick of
whatever he was working on.
Even if it was just a dirty rag, once he's touched it,
he wouldn't even throw it away even if it was covered with oil.
He washed it and used it again and again.
But, do you know how to ride a bicycle?
- No.
- What have you been doing instead of learning that?
Ah it's...it's because you don't know how to use a smart phone.
What? Smart phone?
Thing thing on your nose.. clean it or something.
Did I get something on there?
Oh dear, what should I do? What should I do?
What kind of manner is this!
You know she has a counseling session today, but you took her out?
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- You should have at least called.
Is my time worth crap, you damned bastard?!
I should have contacted you earlier. It's my fault.
I really committed a terrible sin, Professor. Please forgive me.
No, it's all right.
Then how about a warm cup of coffee?
No, no. It's all right.
Even though I don't look it, I make an amazing hand drip coffee.
If you don't taste it, you'll regret it. Please come in.
What the heck? That person, seriously...
How can he touch there?
You know that your Mom didn't take her medicine, right?
If I see you today, you're dead!
I understand. I'm sorry.
My son is really handsome.
Oh.
It's a number I don't know.
Yes, hello?
Yeah, Honey. It's me.
What, Mom?
It's your father.
Yes, hello. What is it?
Then, I'll see you the day after tomorrow, Chairman.
I'll be going now.
Yes. Go safely.
It's late.
I'm just going to get changed quickly.
Do you really have to go Mom?
Are you ready?
What are you doing home at this time? You didn't go to work?
Mom's not in a good condition right now, so you can't handle it, Father.
Just listen to me today and go next time.
Is that your advice as a doctor?
You became a psychiatrist because you wanted to cure your Mom, didn't you?
But your Mom is still going up and down, so what happened?
When did you start to concern?
You don't know, you rascal.
Pull up the zipper for me.
Okay.
Mom, let me come with you. Huh?
Why would you go to that meeting? Aren't you coming?
Yeah, we should go. Let's go.
See you later.
Madam Oh, get in. I'll take you home.
I can take the bus.
I'll take you home. Please get in quickly.
No, no!
Oh my, Madam. Why are you so fast? Whoa!
Oh my, Madam, oh my.
You'll fall! You'll fall!
Madam, come here quickly.
It's slippery, it's slippery.
I'll take you at least just to the bus station..
- I told you I'm fine!
I can get there fine!
Come here, hurry.
It's covered with ice everywhere!
If you fall, your bones will be crushed.
Hurry, hurry. This way.
It will take you over an hour to get to the bus station.
Let me just take you there. It's warm in the car.
It's cold. Here, here.
Here.
Get in.
I see, you prefer the boss's seat.
It's a bit uncomfortable riding in a stranger's car right?
You don't talk at all.
Usually, elders.
Typically grandmothers talk a lot.
Left turn here.
Oh, sorry.
Aigo. I should have told you first.
Where in Soo Suk Dong? I go there often recently.
How's with my grandfather? Difficult, right?
Even still, he did get a little easier.
I guess it's just because he's getting older...
I seem to be really talkative today. Should I turn on some music?
How is it?
-You're going to go there now?
-Yeah. Tell me if anything happens.
Have you seen a police station where nothing happens?
Your household must be quite powerful.
With the grandpa fainting only from hearing the news of the canceled marriage.
Where my grandpa would by perfectly fine even if I tell him I wanted to have a divorce.
- Work hard.
- Go and come back.
I'll drop you off at your house.
I'm fine, thank you.
-Where's do you live? It's cold outside so I'll drop you off at your house.
-Just stop the car!
Wait a moment.
Oh, Se Ro, I'll call you later... What about Mom?
She's crying right now?
Where did Father go? Huh?
- What about Father?
- I don't know. He hasn't called.
I got talked to the butler who got in contact with our father, and
He found mom alone in a hotel room.
Because of Mom's illness, she couldn't resist her impulse.
Why is she like that, when she was the one who did it?
It's not like she slept with some stranger.
Is this a matter where we can do something about?
-Did you talk to mom in that manner?
-Yeah.
Kid, I'll see you later.
What happened to his mother?
Where are you?
Come out. I want to see you.
It's cold, so get in.
I'm not cold.
Did you think about it? About whether you're going to continue meeting me or not?
I trust you as a doctor...even though I can't trust you as a man.
Get in right now. It's cold.
That's why I decided only to be consulted.
Hey, what are you doing? Sit in the front.
Let's have a consultation.
Doing whatever you want...
Am I just supposed to be talking about myself?
My mom passed away. I don't know about my dad.
My mom was a single mother.
I was under my Grandmother's care at age 5.
She lived with another man and died in an accident.
And my grandmother was from Jeolla Province.
While working as a housekeeper,
She fed me, clothed me, and sent me off to school.
When I was in high school, I got bullied a lot.
So I would always stay at home.
I received a call from the hospital saying that my grandmother collapsed.
So that morning the last thing I said to her was "I will come back".
That's all.
How were you feeling that time?
You said you couldn't go to her when she fainted. How did you feel then?
I was sad. I was sad.
But I became mad.
She knew that I can't do anything by myself.
What should I do? She should've brought me with her.
I was angry like that.
And I was sorry.
Because I felt so sorry. I felt so sorry that
my whole body felt like it was ripping apart.
My grandmother...
She died while working hard to take care of me.
I can
forget about everything else,
but my grandmother's coarse and thick hands...
I don't think I can ever forget that.
You did well.
What now?
What do you want to ask about?
Do you want to go out with me?
There's something with our relationship
I know you feel it too. Aren't you curious about that?
Even just a while ago,
I felt like a bomb was going to explode inside of me and
It felt like fireworks were going off my head,
but after seeing you, I feel fine.
I'm curious if our relationship
is really love, or if it's just some simple chemical reaction--
I don't want to.
- You didn't even think about it properly how can--
- I seriously don't.
Think about it seriously!
Hey, so you're saying I'm nothing to you?
Of course. Correct, we are nothing.
Hey! Where are you going?
How can he talk so easily
about dating?
That crazy bastard, seriously.
Ah, seriously, who did I just get rejected from...
Ah, this girl is a reversal.
I'm dumbfounded.
Grandpa refused to receive treatment at the hospital,
and as soon as we led him to his room, he quietly passed away.
I'm sad he couldn't see you. Go on safely.
Hello!
- Hello!
You, really! Hey, Cha Hong Do!
I'm consulting someone. You're not even going to greet her?
I held in for a week, but I can't any longer.
You said that he's nothing, but why are you mad for a week?
And, the person that I was rejected by you is me.
What? You asked her to date? But she rejected you?
Daebak!
Eun Ho.
Hello.
It's my mom.
Is that person a doctor as well?
Oh, no. That person is not a doctor or a nurse.
The reason why she's here is because she's some sort of a security camera.
Your daughter can attack me.
You can't joke around with my mother like that.
Really?
I wanted you to consult my daughter because Professor Uhm suggested you.
Last time during consultation, I saw that my daughter downloaded a movie.
If I pay for something from my phone, I forgot that my mom will get a text message.
That's right... She watched a movie during the consultation.
The kid is very rude.
I think we're done with our conversation. Let's go. Get up.
Mom or daughter, they are the same.
What did you say?
Eun Ho, do you know why she failed the finals?
Do you know why Eun Ho watches a movie during the consultation?
I know my daughter better than you.
Hey! Why are you like that?
Cockroaches.
Good job. We have to kill all of them.
I'm a bit late.
Sleep well, Hong Do.
Can I see you for a second? I'll wait for you in the bakery.
What is this?
♫ I still, I'm gonna still ♫
♫ I'm gonna still, I'm going to fly ♫
Doctor
What is it?
-  Hey, can you come over here quickly?
- Hello?
I think the hospital is on fire.
What? Where are you right now?
What kind of fire? There are sprinklers there.
You are kidding, right?
Hey! Come here quickly!
Did you call the 911?
Is the firetruck coming right now?
Hello? Hello?
What is this Ahjussi?
What is this? No way...
I feel dirty. What is he saying?
How can I put out the fire?
Was he saying the truth? He must be.
He must be saying the truth!
Excuse me, excuse me!
Here!
Here! Here! Here!
Ko Yi Suk Ko Yi Suk!
Ko Yi Suk!
Ko Yi Suk! Ko Yi Suk!
♫ My soul, my savior ♫
Ko Yi Suk!
Why? Did you think that I'm dying?
You should have closed the door for all the cockroaches to die.
I'm seriously going to dry up those rascals.
Hey, am I still nothing to you?
You went out of your mind while you were running for me.
You should have realized how important I am to you.
That's enough. Let's go.
I will buy you a meal, since you actually got shocked.
Let's go!
Hey! Why are you like this? What are you doing?
Ow! Hong Do! Cha Hong Do!
What are you doing?
♫ I'm in love with you ♫
You only proved one thing. You are a crazy psycho!
Oh, really. I must be crazy. I did not keep my promise with Detective Jang.
Why did he cancel the marriage because of me? He must be crazy.
Hong Do! You didn't wear your helmet!
Wait a moment. I wanted to see you the whole day.
Detective Jang is not getting married.
Is she a player or what?
What I hate the most is when you are with that doctor bastard.
Why isn't she coming? Did you have a change of heart?
Chairman!
I think I dropped my earring.
You are the first, Detective Jang.
I must be crazy.