Timing and Subtitles are brought to you by the 🎤 ~You're My Melody Team~ 🎹 @ Viki.com
Since the last day I saw him, not a day goes by that I don't think about him.
If I had stuck by his side through it all,
would he and I be looking at the sea together now?
[Happy Merry Ending]
[Original webtoon "Happy Merry Ending" of Bomtoon by Dorae]
Ugh, seriously?
Did you sleep well?
Sleep in your own house, will you?
You don't sleep well on your own. I moved in upstairs so that I could be near you.
I'm late…
[Villa de GD]
[GD Convention | GD Party House | GD Wedding Mall]
- Was it difficult to get here?
- Oh my god!
Congratulations. You look gorgeous.
- So pretty.
- Thank you! Let's take a picture.
Okay. One, two, three.
- Have you heard from him?
- I'll take the photo now!
- N-Not yet.
- One, two, three!
But it should be fine, right?
Of course not!
What on earth is going on?
Did you really not hear a single one of my alarms going off?
You are late anyway, so come back to bed. Let's sleep some more, okay?
You turned off the alarm, didn't you?
No.
Where are the black socks?
In the laundry basket.
I told you not to wear mine.
Or at least wash them.
Where's my jacket?
Look carefully. It must be somewhere.
It might be at my place…
Why is nothing where it's supposed to be? Damn it.
Hey, Seung Jun!
What?
You're lost without that, right?
You're a lifesaver. Thanks.
- Do you have everything?
- See you later.
Oh, I'm so nervous!
Don't be! You are the prettiest one here!
- Really?
- I have to go.
- See you later.
- See you.
Ladies and Gentlemen, may I have your attention, please?
The wedding ceremony will begin soon, so please come into the ceremony hall and take your seats.
Are you kidding me…
Team Leader,
he's not answering his phone.
What if he ran away?
No way.
Why is this happening?
Excuse me.
Yes?
How much time do we have left?
Oh, the time! About five minutes.
He should be fine, right?
I can do it!
I got this!
Let's hope that the bride and groom will have a bright future together.
And with your best wishes, please give them one more big round of applause!
Who's that? Is he blind?
What's with the sunglasses?
Now we will hear the long-awaited song in celebration of the bride and groom's everlasting union!
♪ Though the heart cannot be heard ♪
♪ Or seen ♪
♪ Somehow we're standing here facing each other ♪
♪ What is love? ♪
♪ Does it last forever? ♪
♪ I still can't give you an answer ♪
♪ But I will tell you my true feelings ♪
♪ Can I stand by your side now? ♪
♪ Maybe we are destined to be together ♪
♪ A dream we've been hiding for so long ♪
♪ You are mine, and I am yours, us together ♪
You still play well.
Of course, I do. I have been playing the piano for years.
You should work here part-time. It's so hard to find an accompanist.
I can't leave the shop on weekends. That's when we have the most customers.
But I'll drop by to see you from time to time.
Anyway, who was that earlier?
- Who?
- The one with the sunglasses.
He was hilarious.
Seung Jun? He's the singer here.
I've known him for a long time, but he's still a mystery.
Here he comes.
This is Lee Seung Jun, the pride of our wedding hall.
And this is Song Jae Hyeon, our substitute for today.
Jae Hyeon!
Ah… Yes…
Hi, I'm Song Jae Hyeon, and I will be working with you from now on.
I look forward to working with you.
Ah, yes.
You are an amazing singer.
And you're really good-looking without the sunglasses.
He's a little shy.
So you're taking the job, right?
I told you, I have always wanted to do this.
We are a family now, so why don't we go out for a company meal together?
Is that all right?
Sounds good to me.
Sorry, I have to go now.
Okay.
What? How could he just leave like that in the middle of a conversation?
You should give up now. Seung Jun is a tough nut to crack.
Even we have never had a meal with him.
I will bring him with me! Can you make the reservation?
What?
Seung Jun!
Come join us. Please?
Do you have an important appointment or something? It's not like that, is it?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Seung Jun, you've never been to a company dinner before, have you?
It's basic manners to at least show up.
Just sit with us for half an hour.
Or just ten minutes?
Five minutes?
Great work today, everyone!
Now, now! We have a new member with us, and it's Seung Jun's first time joining us.
So a toast is in order. Let's go with the usual.
- Here's to our...
- Romantic weekends!
The vibe at our get-togethers has never been this good.
This is all thanks to you, Seung Jun. You should join us more often.
Yes, we've worked together for more than two years, and we've never even had a meal together.
I never mentioned it, but it hurt my feelings.
I practically had to drag him here.
Really? I wish I could have seen it!
Let's get together more often!
- That sounds great!
- I know, right?
Seung Jun,
can I ask you something?
Why do you wear those sunglasses? You are so handsome.
I'm not quite comfortable with people staring,
so when there's a crowd...
- He was just taking care of you because he felt sorry for you…
- Get yourself together, for God's sake…
- Don't you think it's too late…
- Do better!
- Aren't you ashamed to see the other members?
- Well, too bad! Looks like he abandoned you…
Don't flatter yourself!
Seung Jun, Seung Jun…
Seung Jun!
Are you all right, Seung Jun?
Ah… I am sorry.
I… I have to go to the bathroom.
Did I… do something wrong?
No…
He was always a bit strange, but we didn't know how serious it was.
- Don't worry about it. We were all curious, right?
- Right.
[Antidepressants]
Seung Jun!
Put your feet parallel to each other, like this.
If you push the paddle forward, you go backward.
If you pull it backward, you go forward.
If you want to stop,
put the paddle away here.
Teacher! Over there...
You never drink like this.
- What's up?
- I just wanted to get a little tipsy.
Exactly...
Why did you go to the get-together when you have panic disorder?
I'm in trouble.
What do you mean?
I downed two bottles of soju...
and I don't remember anything after that...
You…
came back at around 2 a.m.
Around 2 a.m.?
[Park Jong Hyeok: Bye, guys. (22:55)]
[Lee Min Gyeong: I had so much fun today!! (22:57)]
[Team Leader Lee Hyo Rim: Get home safe, Guys! Please take care of Seung Jun! (22:58)]
But based on the group chat, it ended at 11 p.m.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I had to open the door for you because you were pressing on the wall and making beeping sounds.
[Song Jae Hyeon: Are you feeling a little better? (09:00)]
What's wrong?
- Song Jae Hyeon?
What's going on?
What do I do?
Is it really all right for us to go?
Of course. It's getting late. You guys should really be heading home.
Okay, then we'll leave him to you.
- Bye!
- Don't worry. Have a good night.
- See you.
- Yes.
Ugh...
I...
I'm not usually like this.
It's all because of...
that asshole.
Asshole!
More...
- What?
- I want more, please.
Just a second.
Put your shoe on.
Which direction do we go from here?
We're here.
Thank you, Mr. Driver.
Leave a message at that number,
and I'll transfer the payment to you.
I'm... not going anywhere!
I live there. It's the house with the black door.
[Vocal Trainer | Lee Seung Jun]
I see you also give vocal lessons.
Then instead of the taxi fare,
- can I get lessons from you?
- Sure!
I'd love to! I will... I will...
I swear I'll give you vocal lessons! I will!
Promise!
Promise! Promise...
Good night.
Here you go.
Never mind... I'll just take you home.
Be careful! Watch where you're going!
Watch it.
[Café Simjeong]
Your Einspänner is ready.
(T/N: Viennese black coffee with whipped cream)
Can I get some napkins?
I want more, please
More?
Yes, much more.
Enjoy your drink.
You're seeing someone, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I'm not seeing anyone!
You've been smiling since this morning.
Right! We have eyes, you know.
I have not.
I wonder how long it will last this time.
Did you guys finish the things I told you to do or not?
- Of course we did!
- We did!
Then what's the mess here?
Those just came in, so we were just about to start!
[Rhythm J]
♫ I'm going crazy ♫
♫ Even when you're not doing anything ♫
♫ You have that power ♫
♫ From head to toe, whenever I see you ♫
♫ I think I'll go crazy ♫
♫ Come on! We won't give up this time ♫
♫ Wow ♫
♫ We won't give up this time ♫
What are you watching so seriously?
Teacher!
Don't you know Kim Chan Wu?
He's all over the Internet and the news.
Take a look, he's the talk of the town.
Later. Let's start class.
Did you do your warm-ups?
No, not at all.
Teacher, is it true that they'll be attending our academy?
I don't know.
What? I got my hopes up for nothing.
Why doesn't our academy have any idol stars or trainees? So many other academies do.
Scales first.
Okay.
[Song Jae Hyeon: Seung Jun, are you busy?]
[Song Jae Hyeon: Are you feeling a little better? Seung Jun, are you busy?]
[Vocal Trainer | Lee Seung Jun]
Hyeon Ji, I'll head home first. Can you close up for me?
What? Already?
I'll open tomorrow. See you.
Umm... Okay, see you tomorrow!
Is he going on a date?
It seems a bit different this time...
I'm betting it'll only last for a month.
Two weeks for me.
[Song Jae Hyeon: Seung Jun, you haven't replied to my texts, and I'm getting worried. Is everything all right?]
No, I'm just…
No.
Taking the meds...
It's a bit much, isn't it?
Seung Jun!
Why are you here...
You're on your way home, right?
I'm just on time.
I noticed that your academy was quite close to the café.
I was worried because you didn't reply.
I wanted to properly apologize.
I'm sorry for asking rude questions yesterday.
It's fine.
I'm the one who made a mistake.
I was just trying to get more friendly with you.
I hope there weren't any misunderstandings.
Of course.
Then...
Wait...
Hyeong!
Why are you so surprised?
You finished late today.
Did you wait for me?
Yes.
Have you eaten? Let's go get something tasty.
Ah... I'd love to, but I have to go practice.
- I told your manager that you'll be a little late.
- Pardon?
I said that you had an important meeting to attend, so don't worry.
What are we having?
Come on.
Do you want to have dinner together?
I'm sorry.
The guy who made me such a mess...
I became defensive in both social and romantic relationships after I met him.
He left a stain, and the more I tried to rub it away, the more it spread.
I'll drive you home, let's go.
Seung Jun!
What do I do?
Are you really going to drink more?
That asshole.
He's been nothing but a nuisance in my life.
Why did I think of him at that moment?
Maybe he looks like him.
Not at all.
Neither his looks,
nor his personality.
There's probably something similar about him.
Your first love has an impact on you.
If your first relationship was with a younger person, you'll find yourself drawn to younger people.
If it was with some trash, you'll probably be attracted to another piece of trash, even if you don't want to.
Ugh! Just thinking about it makes me mad again.
Hey! Where does that little creep live?
Do you want me to teach him a lesson?
Why did I make such a stupid mistake?
Why do you care so much about him, anyway?
You don't have to see him if you don't want to.
I… We work at the same place…
So…
So? What happened? Did you end up sleeping over?
- That was it.
- And you just came home?
What's up with you?
Hey! He just doesn't feel the same as other people.
If this was a game, he would be the final boss.
Like an otherworldly difficult level.
Who the hell could make Song Jae Hyeon into this mess?
I don't even recognize you.
I know, I don't even recognize myself.
He's the complete opposite of me.
And his walls are sky-high.
But so are your attacks.
Or are you not as good as you used to be?
Why aren't you leaving? I thought you had plans.
They're having this huge party at that new bar.
Hey, you should come with us.
I won't go.
Go by yourselves.
Hey! Song Jae Hyeon! Seriously?
Ugh… Fine…
Leave him. Let's just go by ourselves, come on.
If you start seeing someone now,
you'll definitely think of him again.
You're getting much better, you know.
It's okay to wait with starting a new relationship
until you've gotten over it completely.
Relinquish your feelings for him for now.
Why are you in my head?
Oh! Teacher...
I… Uh…
- You should have just said it.
- Right...
Oh... Wait, was I that obvious?
Here.
What?
Ah, I didn't mean...
Oh my, Chan Wu Oppa.
Excuse me, where is Teacher Seung Jun's room?
Over there.
And where is that?
Why would you ask m─
Ch-Chan...
Chan... Chan Wu Oppa?
Oh, yes, I'm...
I'm Kim Chan Wu.
Your face is really the size of my fist.
I'm such a huge fan, I've been a fan since your debut.
Ah, thank you.
Where's the vocal room?
There.
You look familiar. But...
Don't I?
Have you been in one of my classes?
No.
O-Or... a different teacher?
I'm Kim Chan Wu.
I see, I'm Lee Seung Jun.
No, I'm... Kim Chan Wu.
Okay… I'm... Lee Seung Jun.
Oh! You're... You're a bit hot, right?
[Café Simjeong]
It's him again.
Again?
Doesn't he have anything better to do?
Who is he?
You know, that guy who's hitting on Hyeon Ji.
- He kept calling her up and even went to her house.
- What happened?
She used to hate it so much, but they ended up dating.
- Has it been a month now?
- Twenty days.
Boss, I have to go out for a minute.
He's here because he misses me.
All right. Go ahead.
I'll be right back.
Does that actually work even when they're not interested?
I think it depends on the person.
If he seems fine, then it does paint the person in a different light.
Hyeong, why are you so curious?
- Are you... interested in Hyeon Ji?
- No!
Don't even say that as a joke!
Sorry!
Oh! I have to go!
Hyeong. Hyeong!
I'm the only one actually working here.
I don't know what's gotten into me lately.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
What was your group's name again?
One Point!
I'll make sure to check out your performance clips.
Oh! How... sweet of you.
Remember to review what we talked about today.
Of course.
My singing is a bit lacking because I'm the dancer on the team.
But the company promised me a solo if I improved.
You'll have to work harder then.
But won't you be lonely if you switch from a group to being a solo artist?
No... Not at all.
I can't wait for my solo debut.
Okay, good work today.
Thank you!
What genre do you think I should do for my solo debut?
I'm so torn between dance and ballad.
You need to practice first.
What song do you want to practice?
Seung Jun!
Who's that?
I…
Oh! I better get going.
No! You don't have to! Stay a little longer.
Someone from my company is here to pick me up.
I'll call you later.
It's… over, isn't it?
Hello, CEO.
Oh, here you are.
Thank you.
Well done.
You can lean the chair back and relax.
It's all right, CEO.
It's an expensive car, so it's spacious.
Thank you for coming to pick me up.
I'll pick you up every once in a while.
Really? Thank you!
Oh, right! How was class today?
Teacher Seung Jun is really sweet.
Yes?
Would you…
like to sit for a moment?
Yes…
I thought about you all day, Seung Jun.
How I must have made you uncomfortable by that sudden visit.
And how I'm sorry for making you go to that get-together,
when you don't even like those things.
And also that I asked you all those unnecessary questions.
All those things…
It has been...
bothering me, too.
Are you free tomorrow?
I'm a bit busy nowadays.
Vocal lessons, remember?
Don't you owe your driver something?
What?
"I swear... I'll give you vocal lessons! Promise"
Don't talk about that.
All right, I'll give you the lessons.
You promised.
I will…
It's really close by car.
You don't have to accompany me.
Do I make you uncomfortable?
I'll just watch you get on.
I…
It's here…
How quick...
Do you want to get the next one?
No, I'll just get going now.
Seung Jun!
See you tomorrow.
I'll make sure to practice.
Bye!
Relationships are not for me.
But... maybe we could be friends?
[Chan Wu]
Yes, Chan Wu?
Teacher Seung Jun, I was just talking about my practice song with the CEO, but...
Seung Jun!
How have you been?
It took me so long to find you.
See you soon.
♪ I'm in the woods ♪
♪ In the rugged valley ♪
♪ The twittering ♪
♪ Of the birds... ♪
♪ In my ordinary, daily life have become ♪
♪ You're like an angel from heaven ♪
♪ Everything feels like a dream ♪
♪ It feels like the perfect love that others only talk about ♪
♪ Is now here for me ♪
Thank you.
CEO, I'm really full.
I think I ate at least four servings by myself.
I'll get scolded by my manager if I gain weight.
He shouldn't tell people to lose weight when he can't even lose his own.
He's been on a diet since he entered the company, and he's still gaining weight.
- Really?
- Yes.
Seung Jun.
Yes?
You don't have to speak formally when we're alone.
I couldn't possibly...
It's fine, really.
I heard that you've lived at a relative's house from a very young age.
You must have been lonely.
Think of me as an older brother.
Okay...
Ju Won... Hyeong.
Cute.
I am quite cute.
Do you want to catch a movie after this?
Oh! Yes! I'd love to!
Let's watch that new horror movie. I heard it was terrifying.
As someone without a family, the only person I trusted.
Hyeong!
What... was that?
I thought you had gone home.
I asked you what that was.
What?
How could you do this to me?
It has nothing to do with you.
Let's go.
I'll drive you home.
Well done. You've really improved.
Thank you.
Hey, Lee Seung Jun!
Are you really not going to practice?
Pardon?
Do you really think you can debut like this?
Are you going to keep holding the other members back?
I'm very sorry.
Aren't you ashamed to face them?
All of you, out.
Get yourself together, for God's sake.
Hey, you have to do better.
He was just taking care of you
because he felt sorry for you.
Well, too bad.
Looks like he abandoned you.
Hyeong.
Why are you doing this to me?
Did I do something wrong?
Please, I'm sorry.
Seung Jun.
You think you're something, don't you?
But you're nothing without me.
Don't delude yourself.
Hyeong, please don't do this to me.
I'll do better.
Don't you think it's a little too late
for this to be a matter of doing better?
Think about it.
Hyeong!
Have you always been this kind of person?
Did you get kicked out?
I left.
Hey, your suitcase is so heavy. Carry it yourself.
Are you good at cooking ramyeon?
My mother's ramyeon is terrible.
You're a bit late today.
You should have told me if you were going to be late. I've been waiting up for you.
Ho Yeon.
Sleep at your own place tonight.
Is something wrong?
Please.
Good morning.
I slept at home yesterday.
I just dropped by before work. Look! I've even gotten changed.
Okay, have a nice day at work today.
What are you doing today?
Why?
Can I not even ask?
You know, you should eat something nice when you're down.
Let's have dinner together.
All right.
Seung Jun. Good morning.
Hi, Seung Jun! Have you eaten?
Seung Jun.
I'm Song Jae Hyeon, and I'm here for the lessons.
Did you leave something behind?
Hello—
Are you free tomorrow?
I…
Today is my day off.
I see... Seung Jun, don't worry about me and take your time getting ready.
Just a moment.
Okay.
Is it all right if we do this at my house?
Not there, here…
Try to clench up your lower stomach and breathe like you're pulling something.
Pulling…
I don't get what that means…
Oh… It's like…
Is it like this?
Here… Here?
Not bad, right?
This is my first time…
but I think I'm catching on really quickly.
Yes.
Seung Jun, is it too hot in here?
Your face is red.
Oh, yes… A little.
Do you want to open the windows?
I'll... I'll do it.
Why is the sofa here?
Do you want to call it a day and get some beer?
Why are you laughing?
It's a technique that students often use when they want the class to end.
Oh… Is it?
Then... would you like a beer at home?
Oh... Yes, I'd love that.
What are you doing after work?
Me? I have plans for dinner.
I'm sure you do.
Are you hiding a lover at home?
What are you talking about?
Please take care of your poor older brother, too.
It's not like that.
You'd better not get caught, I'll make you regret it.
Let's go some other time. I'll buy you something good.
Fine.
I really wanted to get vocal lessons, but we have a lot ahead of us, don't we?
It will take time, but I think it's possible.
How much time?
I don't know. I guess it depends on how much you practice.
I want to learn from you for a really long time, Seung Jun.
I'm just kidding.
Should we speak comfortably?
What?
I think it will help us get more comfortable with each other.
Right...
"-yo."
(T/N: an ending added to make a phrase more formal/polite in Korean)
Take your time.
Okay.
Why do you want to learn to sing anyway?
I've always wanted to sing a song for my lover at the altar.
Not that I know who it will be.
- I can write the song for you when the time comes.
- Can you write songs too?
I was a trainee since I was in high school.
I learned everything from singing to dancing, and composing.
I can't imagine you dancing.
You would have made a great idol. Why did you quit?
How could I sing with sunglasses on?
Get up.
Quickly.
Imagine that this is the wedding hall.
I'm sitting at the piano as your accompanist.
Huh?
Focus.
A beautiful melody fills the hall.
And you meet my eyes before you start singing.
And…
Imagine that there's only you and me there.
What is that supposed to mean?
You never know. You might sing better when I'm the only one you can see.
Now try it.
No.
Try it.
I just cast a spell on you.
I said no.
Come on, just once.
Just this once!
- I said no!
- Just this once!
Just once. Hm?
Hey, Ho Yeon!
Who's this?
This is Song Jae Hyeon, who will be taking classes from me starting today.
I mean... he's Jae Hyeon Hyeong.
Hi, I'm Song Jae Hyeon.
- Okay.
- And this is my friend, Im Ho Yeon. He lives upstairs.
I see.
I didn't realize it was so late.
Seung Jun, I should get going.
See you again, Ho Yeon.
Yeah, hurry home safely.
Yes.
You finished early.
I'm relieved to see that you look happier than you did a while ago.
- Good night.
- Are you going home?
Let's eat together!
I already ate.
[You must be busy. When can we meet?]
Why is he looking for me?
Seung Jun!
I've been calling you for a while.
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
Let's go in.
- How are you feeling today?
- I'm good.
Next up is a song to celebrate the bright future of the bride and groom!
Please give them a round of applause.
♪ Your smiling face keeps appearing in my mind ♪
♪ One day, suddenly, you became a part of my daily life ♪
♪ I imagine the things I want to do when I meet you ♪
♪ And by doing so, even a typical boring day ♪
♪ Becomes special ♪
♪ Ever since I met you, ♪
♪ All the moments in my ordinary, daily life have become ♪
Did you like my sunglasses?
I almost made a mistake... Please don't do that again.
It's nice to see you smile.
I shouldn't have said that.
There's that startled expression again.
It's just that it's really nice to see you smile!
You don't have classes today, right?
I'll drive you home.
Seung Jun.
- Seung Jun!
- What?
Why are you staring at your phone?
Are you waiting for a call?
No.
But there is someone I hope never calls.
I have to stop by some place.
Where is he?
What the...
Are you up?
Why did you come here?
Something is troubling you, isn't it?
But you wouldn't tell me even if I asked.
So I'm just going to stay with you.
I'll keep this with me for a while.
Should we take a walk?
How is it?
This is nice.
No more complicated thoughts.
I like it, too.
Do you come here often?
Yes.
When I'm frustrated...
When I want to listen...
When I wonder what you're doing.
When I miss you.
That is why I come to see you.
Why are you being like this...
to someone like me.
I've never done anything like this before, either.
But I just want to stay by your side...
and protect you.
I can't resist anymore.
Can I kiss you?
♫ Can I stand by your side now? ♫
♫ Maybe we are destined to be together ♫
♫ A dream we've been hiding for so long ♫
♫ You are mine, and I am yours, us, together ♫
Where the hell is he, and what is he up to?
This guy has been calling for a while. Are you sure you don't have to pick up?
Yeah, it's fine.
Who is it?
The man who made me like this.
It's been so long since I felt this peaceful.
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
- See, I told you it doesn't work!
- Wait. Move, move.
- Is it okay?
- Yeah.
How is this?
Wow! It suits you!
♫ One day, suddenly, you became a part of my daily life ♫
♫ I imagine the things I want to do when I meet you ♫
Ducks!
- Where?
- There! Ducks!
That's cute.
♫ Ever since I met you, ♫
♫ All the moments in my ordinary, daily life ♫
♫ Have become ♫
Wow. What is it?
I made it.
- You made it yourself?
- Of course!
- Try it.
- I want to try it.
Go ahead.
How is it?
It's good, right?
Really good.
I can make it for you every day.
- Really?
- Of course.
Chew before you swallow.
And remember to relax your lips when you practice.
Yes!
Hm... But why isn't this coming off...
Thank you very much!
Yes, good job today.
Chan Wu.
Why don't you try taking another teacher's class?
What?
Why?
I don't want to. I like you.
The CEO told me he likes you, too.
Dance songs aren't really my area of expertise.
And I was planning on getting some time off from the academy.
Oh, I see.
That's a shame.
I'll see you out.
Get back safely.
Teacher, does that mean we won't be seeing each other?
It's not like we will never see each other again if we don't meet here anymore.
You can call me if something happens.
Oh! Thank you, Teacher.
Can I call you often?
Not too often.
Okay.
Oh! It's the CEO! Sir!
Chan Wu, can you wait for me in the car for a little while?
Yes.
How have you been?
What are you doing?
What does it look like? I'm just picking up my trainee.
Did you send him here on purpose?
Isn't Chan Wu nice?
I thought you two would get along.
He is a lot like you.
You must be having a hard time. Your face looks rough.
My little Seung Jun, you used to be so nice when you were younger.
If you don't have anything to say, I will leave now.
What's the rush?
I have a proposal for you.
Do you want to come work for my company?
What?
Your composing skills must have improved by now, right?
You know we don't accept just anybody at our company.
I can hire you because I'm the CEO.
I want nothing to do with you.
Think carefully.
No matter how much you agonize over it...
you'll eventually come running to me.
I'll be leaving now, since Chan Wu is waiting.
Why... Why is he doing this to me?
What have I done so wrong?
Hey, Seung Jun!
You haven't done anything wrong.
He's just crazy. What other reason would he need?
I just...
I'll just stop everything and live a quiet life,
so it would be nice if he could just leave me alone.
Aren't you going home?
Oh, I have to finish something. You go ahead.
Okay, I'll get going.
- I'm going to clock out now.
- Bye.
[Song Jae Hyeon: Why aren't you answering my calls? Call me when you read this. I'm worried.]
[Villa de GD]
[GD Convention | GD Party House | GD Wedding Mall]
- Nuna!
- Oh! Jae Hyeon!
Is Seung Jun done?
Didn't he tell you?
- He quit last week.
- What?
We barely managed to get a substitute in time.
I thought I knew him, but apparently not.
Did... Did he say anything?
He just told us that he needed time to rest.
He already made up his mind, so I couldn't stop him.
Oh... I see...
Why? Do you have something to tell him?
It's nothing...
Did you stay up all night again?
I bought some porridge, so heat it up and have some.
I will be back soon.
[Kim Chan Wu]
Hi, Chan Wu.
Teacher,
they're kicking me out of the company.
I worked so hard for the album, and we were supposed to start recording next week.
I don't understand why they're doing this to me.
Please help me.
Think carefully.
No matter how much you agonize over it...
you'll eventually come running to me.
It's about time for him to show up...
[Lee Seung Jun]
I'm on my way now.
Well done, Chan Wu.
CEO,
does that mean I can debut?
Of course! Chan Wu, you deserve a debut.
Your vocal coach shouldn't quit in the middle just because he's busy,
right?
Thank you.
Did he break up?
You go!
No, you go!
Please, go...
Boss, do you... want me to set up a blind date?
I know someone really nice. I think this person would be perfect for you.
I don't know...
She's really pretty, really!
Hyeong! Do you want to go out for dinner then?
It's on me!
The two of you should go.
Come on, let's go. You know how stingy he usually is─
It's now or never.
It's not easy to work alone.
You made the right choice.
I didn't come here because of that.
I came because of Chan Wu.
Oh, Chan Wu?
What about him?
Chan Wu has potential.
I'm here to ask you a favor.
And what makes you think I will grant it?
You sent Chan Wu to me.
Aren't you still interested in me?
Yes...
There was no one quite like you.
Weren't you the happiest when we were together, too?
I don't think anyone would have been as nice to you as I was.
No.
I wasn't happy then.
It all crumbled down at that moment.
So much that I wanted to cut you out of my life.
You never liked me.
You just needed someone to toy with.
What are you trying to say?
Chan Wu.
He may rely on you now,
but he will realize it soon enough.
Before that happens...
I'm giving you a chance to be the person he thinks you are.
Having no one beside you...
That's a lonely thing, isn't it?
You're all grown up,
talking to your hyeong like this.
Please.
Wait, Seung Jun.
Okay, I understand.
I will do what you say if we get back together.
Seung Jun, I can do better.
Don't lie to me.
I won't fall for it again.
Hey! Lee Seung Jun! Hey!
I'll see myself out.
- See you tomorrow.
You don't have to take me home.
Do I make you uncomfortable?
No... Not uncomfortable.
I'll just watch you get on.
It's here...
How quick...
Do you want to get the next one?
No, I'll just get going now.
Wait!
Having no one beside you...
That's a lonely thing, isn't it?
The words may have been aimed at him, but they also hit me.
What on earth happened?
- Seung Jun!
- Hey, Seung Jun!
Let's go!
Let go!
I said let go.
It's my turn now, and I'm not letting you go.
Seung Jun!
Stop this.
If you don't come with me,
he's not going to come out of this in one piece.
He said no.
Who do you think you're putting your hands on?
- Son of a...
- Stop it.
I don't know what it was like before,
but now I'm not letting him go.
Don't ever come near Seung Jun again, or...
I'll make you regret it.
Hey! Lee Seung Jun!
Do you think he's any different? Hey!
You should go now.
I'll leave after I see you go inside.
- Do you know why Kim Ju Won is doing this to me?
- What?
Do you know why he stayed away all this while
and decided to appear out of the blue?
It's because you kept getting closer to me.
I don't want to see either of you,
so just go away.
You shouldn't be alone right now.
Why would you even want to be with me?
Out of pity?
Do you feel all grand and mighty when you're with someone like me?
- It's not like that.
- Then what is the reason?
I want to be there for you.
That asshole and you are more or less the same.
- You both make my life difficult.
- Seung Jun!
Please.
Leave.
Leave me alone for God's sake.
All right.
I'll go.
Showing him this side of me...
was worse than seeing that jerk again.
I tried so hard to become a different person after that.
Hello. I'm Lee Seung Jun, the composer.
I sent you an email, and I was wondering if you got it.
Please make sure to forward it.
Yes.
Hello?
Are you Lee Seung Jun?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Hello, this is Grim Music. Thank you for sending us your song.
Can you come for a meeting tomorrow?
Yes, yes, I can do it.
Thank you.
And I began to change.
♪ But even if I reach out my hand, I can't touch you ♪
[One year later]
♪ I hope we can meet again outside of what exists in my memories ♪
Yeon Oh! I think it's done.
- Already?
- Yes, we've got it.
You can come out.
Thank you.
- Isn't it good?
- It really is.
Right?
Was it okay?
- This song is going to be a total hit.
- Thank you.
No, no, it's all on you.
Hi, hello, hi.
- Chan Wu!
- Hyeong!
Congratulations.
Are you done recording already?
I knew you'd make it!
It just ended. Thank you.
Are you all right?
I'm... good, I guess.
I love working at the same company as you.
I can breathe easier, you know.
I knew that asshole Kim Ju Won was going to go down.
I mean, he shouldn't have messed with kids.
I know, right? This is why you shouldn't judge a person by physical appearance alone.
Well, it all worked out.
Ugh... Just thinking about him makes me lose my appetite.
Yeon Oh? Do you want to get some beef?
Sorry, I've got plans.
Okay.
Im Ho Yeon,
I'll take care of the rest.
No, it's all right.
Your lover is here... Go see him.
Come on! I told you we are not dating!
- Get this cleaned up.
- Okay.
How is work? Is it fun?
I'm still getting used to it, I guess.
You should thank me for everything.
Yes.
I'm most grateful to you.
Seung Jun!
Buy me dinner sometime...
Okay.
I wonder what he's doing now.
Who? Song Jae Hyeon?
He's probably having dinner.
If you miss him so much, you should go see him.
Will he want to see me, too?
Sometimes I can't tell if you're really clueless... or just pretending.
Wait, no.
You are definitely clueless.
Go get him.
Before it's really too late.
Hello.
Would you like to order?
One hot Americano, please.
Okay.
Excuse me, Sir.
We are about to close.
Would you like it in a to-go cup?
No, it's okay.
Without him,
all this would have been impossible.
I started singing again so I could be confident in front of him.
Are you nervous?
You'll come with me, right?
I dropped everything for you. Hurry up and get ready, we're going to be late.
Now, it was terribly difficult to get this person to join us.
But you guys know us, and we finally made it possible.
It's his first time meeting the audience.
Are you excited, Guys?
Yes!
That's nowhere near enough! Let me hear it! Are you excited?
Great, there are so many fans waiting here.
We now have around 26,000 viewers watching.
And we have 20 lucky fans here who have been picked to join us.
I think we ought to stop stalling, before we get cursed out.
So let's get down to it.
Here's the masked singer, the man from the video with 10 million views!
I give you Yeon Oh. A big round of applause, please.
Oh! Hello!
Louder!
Yeon Oh, hi!
It's your first time meeting the audience, so please say hello.
Hello, I'm Yeon Oh, a singer and songwriter.
Yeon Oh!
Forever!
Your fans shouted, "Yeon Oh forever."
Here! Please take a seat.
Now, we can see your song was released at 10 a.m. today,
and it has shot up the charts quickly.
Yes, I can barely believe it myself.
I heard that this song was based on your own experiences.
Yes, that's true.
Now, a lot of people, myself included, must be wondering about that.
Could you tell us your story in more detail here?
When I had a severe panic disorder,
I met that person for the first time.
Wait...
Do you want to have dinner together?
I'll... I'll do it.
Why are you being like this... to someone like me?
I just want to stay by your side and protect you.
Please.
Leave.
Leave me alone for God's sake.
All right.
That person must be really regretting not holding on to you right now, right?
Now that we have you here, we have to listen to your new song.
- Yeon Oh, are you ready?
- Yes, I am.
Here's Yeon Oh's new title track, "Reaching Out to You."
A big round of applause, please!
♪ Quietly my two lips come together ♪
♪ And call out your name ♪
♪ Before I knew it, my empty days became filled ♪
♪ With you and memories of you ♪
♪ When I close my eyes, when the wind blows ♪
♪ It feels as though you are right in front of me ♪
♪ But even if I reach out my hand, I can't touch you ♪
♪ I hope we can meet again outside of what exists in my memories ♪
[Closed]
Cheers!
This is really it.
Hyeong.
Aren't you sad?
I am, but...
You've got a job, and Hyeon Ji needs to go back to school.
There's no point in doing this by myself.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know...
I suppose I'll try everything that comes to mind.
Learn to sing.
Travel more.
Oppa, worry about yourself.
He can get along just fine without having to work.
- Do you spend the whole day worrying over me?
- What?
Don't... You might fall for me.
You are ridiculous.
They say a strong no actually means yes. Are you interested in me?
Wow... No!
Don't you dare start. I'm going to kick you so hard.
Just eat some of this. It's good, right?
Yes, thank you for the wonderful song.
The performance was perfect.
It was really good.
Thank you. I'll be off now.
Since the last day I saw him,
not a day has gone by that I haven't thought about him.
If I had stood by his side through it all,
would he and I be looking at the sea together now?
I didn't think Seung Jun would be so successful...
If I had known, I would have treated him better.
It's going to be so hard to see him now.
It has always been hard.
Right?
Oh! Good job, Jae Hyeon!
Jae Hyeon, look at this. Okay?
Are you doing well?
I wanted to sing this to you in person.
But I guess this is how I can sing it to you now.
Thanks to you, I've been able to sing like this, and I've grown a lot too.
Hey! Song Jae Hyeon!
Can I go in just for a moment?
I'm afraid you can't.
It will only take a second. I know Seung Jun personally.
We have no way of confirming that, and it has already started, so I can't let you in.
Please, it will only be a moment.
He's an acquaintance.
Ho Yeon.
Long time no see.
It just started, so go in quickly.
Thank you.
♪ When I close my eyes, when the wind blows ♪
♪ It feels as though you are right in front of me ♪
♪ But even if I reach out my hand, I can't touch you ♪
♪ I hope we can meet again outside of what exists in my memories ♪
You meet my eyes before you start singing.
♪ Even if I call you softly ♪
♪ With all of my heart ♪
♪ The only thing in front of me would be a silent space  ♪
Imagine that there's only you and me there.
♪ It would be just another foolish sigh  ♪
What is that supposed to mean?
You never know. You might sing better when I'm the only one you can see.
♪ It would be just another foolish sigh  ♪
♪ When I close my eyes, when the wind blows ♪
I just cast a spell on you.
♪ It feels as though you are right in front of me ♪
♪ But even if I reach out my hand, I can't touch you ♪
♪ I hope we can meet again outside of what exists in my memories ♪
Thank you for today.
- Thank you.
- Oh! Can I get a picture, Yeon Oh?
- Oh, of course…
Yes, take a photo of us, please.
One, two, three!
Ho Yeon!
Good job. You were great.
Where is he?
He just left. I thought you guys had a talk?
I'm sorry, Ho Yeon. I have to go.
Hello!
We have met before, right?
Oh, yeah... Can I see the owner?
It's been a while since I took over...
Thank you.
Hello?
How are you?
Seung Jun.
Why did you just leave earlier?
Didn't you come to see me?
I did see you...
You looked busy, so I left.
Where are you now?
Me?
Um... I'm just
walking around...
Do you...
want to meet up?
♫ Quietly my two lips come together ♫
♫ And call out your name ♫
♫ Before I knew it, my empty days became filled ♫
♫ With you and memories of you ♫
Did you wait long?
No... I just...
I can breathe now.
♫ It feels as though you are right in front of me ♫
♫ But even if I reach out my hand... ♫
I thought you didn't want to see me.
It's not that.
I was afraid you would be disappointed in me and leave.
I didn't want to get hurt.
I was also worried Kim Ju Won would hurt you.
Let's never part ways again.
Can I hold your hand?
You've never been in a proper relationship, have you?
You can do much more than that.
Get up.
If we are late, we'll get pushed back.
What time is it?
Ten o'clock.
I'll wash up first.
Shall we shower together?
No.
Come on, really?
Let's shower together...
No.
Why not?
I'm going to take a shower.
Oh, come on, I'll just brush my teeth then.
Just my teeth... Come on!
Come in then.
Yay!
- Let's shower together.
- Get out if you're going to be like that.
I thought you wanted to take a shower together?
♪ Your smiling face keeps appearing in my mind ♪
♪ One day, suddenly, you became a part of my daily life ♪
- Let's eat.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
- It looks delicious, doesn't it?
- I know, right?
♫ Ever since I met you, ♫
It is amazing!
♫ All the moments in my ordinary, daily life ♫
Seung Jun!
Yes?
♫ You're like an angel from heaven ♫
♫ Everything feels like a dream ♫
Seung Jun!
Hyeong, you look good today.
Are you done for the day?
- Let's go.
- Where to?
Thank you for today.
I'll be off.
Hyeong, isn't this the way to the wedding hall?
What?
Yes.
No one is going to be there since it's a weekday.
I wonder how everyone is doing.
Let's go see them.
Now?
Hyeong. What are you doing?
Thanks to all viewers for watching this show with us! 🎤🎹
Many thanks to our channel manager:
flowersnacc 🎤🎹
Huge thank you to our segmenters:
valneijr (Chief) & hapgood 🎤🎹
And a big thank you to our English editing team:
mindmuse & keiratc (Translation), flowersnacc (General), hhnike (Chief) 🎤🎹
Special thanks to our language moderators and their teams for their hard work. 🎤🎹
We hope you enjoyed the show! 🎤🎹
♪ By the time the sun sets and the skies fade to red ♪
♪ And I watch our shadows grow longer ♪
♪ Even if there are no expressions or words left to say ♪
♪ I hear a familiar voice ♪
♪ Do you know that the day you came to me ♪
Put your shoe on.
♪ The day you both cried and laughed without anyone knowing ♪
I swear I'll give you vocal lessons! I will!
♪ I gathered all of it in my heart ♪
Promise.
♪ And it grows inside of it ♪
♪ So that at some point, my heart will look like yours ♪
♪ Because I grew it just for you ♪
I got too nervous.
I swear I was better when I practiced.
Timing and Subtitles are brought to you by the 🎤 ~You're My Melody Team~ 🎹 @ Viki.com
I understand you now.
I can't resist...
♫ And it grows inside of it ♫
♫ So that at some point, my heart will look like yours ♫
♫ Because I grew it just for you ♫
♫ You're always there whenever I look back ♫
♫ Just as consistent as the sun that always rises again ♫
♫ Even if you are far away ♫
♫ Everything you touch becomes warm ♫
♫ I gathered all of it in my heart ♫
♫ And all of it connects us ♫
♫ I'll only look at you. I'll only live for you ♫
♫ Even now, as I think of you ♫
♫ The light that you carry calls out to my heart ♫