You told Mr. Mu, right?
You said I was an arrogant man.
I cancel all those
and cancel the trip.
Little Su, don't ask me.
I can't tell you.
Alright.
I won't ask you what it is.
Then tell me.
Why can't I?
Because if I tell you,
you wouldn't be surprised?
It turns out that someone
to make a surprise for me today.
That's enough.
For everything.
Tell you everything?
You're so straightforward
and a one-track mind?
You can't hide anything.
Let's go home and take a look.
What surprise
mr. Mu made for me on earth?
But I'm really fine.
You are nothing.
My sister-in-law won't be able to
follow this arrow
to find the wedding dress and shoes
then my brother
took the ring out
out with the ring
kneel down and propose. Perfect.
Hey,
Is it too obvious
a little too obvious?
Kind of.
Right.
Is too easy to find.
My sister-in-law must think
It's not challenging.
Or put it in the dressing room?
No. No.
Put it in the dressing room.
What if she can't find it?
Hurry up.
Your brother
to hate to marry him.
He didn't want to waste even a second.
You two, look at me.
What?
How is it? Is it OK?
Brother, I've already asked you
for the first time
for a hundred and one times.
Hurry up!
She will be there soon.
It's too late.
Be careful
you're so anxious they're getting married?
I didn't know
forgive her sister-in-law?
Mr. Mu,
all the information you requested
are all here.
I've checked it.
Su Jin's alias
Instead of Su Ji Shi.
Su Jishi is her
her twin sister?
She has been studying in S Country before
a doctor of geology.
Doctor of Geology?
According to investigation, she returned to China
three months ago.
Which is the period
changed drastically.
A Doctor of Geology
In my opinion,
as an actress.
So interested in
In a company's mineral resources?
And knows everything.
Change someone.
It's working now.
Sorry, Mr. Mu.
What did you say? I didn't hear you.
It's none of your business.
You've done well.
The money will be credited to your account tonight.
But you must remember this.
About tonight...
Knows what happened tonight.
You know
don't worry.
OK.
I'll leave now.
You can call me
If anything happens.
Dear, what are you looking at?
You were so engrossed in it.
The company's files
none of your business.
You still hide them?
You and I still have secrets.
Tonight?
I have an important meeting.
Not eat with you?
Not with me again?
My brother
they are so happy.
Do you have any
other thoughts about us?
What is it?
Bro, it's for Second Uncle.
Put it there first.
What did you just say?
Nothing.
Let's hurry to decorate.
Mr. Fang, I'm so nervous.
You're not the one to surprise me.
Why are you nervous?
I'm nervous for Little Su.
Do you think Little Su will be nervous?
Don't panic.
We are all familiar
grand scenes.
I'll start taking photos
taking photos.
I'll open the door.
Alright.
Xiao Xia.
Please check
how my makeup is now.
Should I freshen
my lipstick again?
Very good. Perfect.
Really?
Come on.
Open the door!
It's a surprise!
Where is she?
I thought you said it would be a surprise.
Didn't Mr. Mu say that he would
to propose to Little Su today?
Mr. Mu isn't the kind of guy
to drop the ball halfway.
But I heard that many people
have pre-marital phobias.
This kind of last-minute change
changed at the last minute.
What nonsense are you talking about?
If you think Little Su
I believe that Little Su is capable of such things.
Mr. Mu isn't that guy.
Little Su.
I was just saying nonsense.
Don't take it seriously.
I didn't care about it.
Why do you care about it so much?
Alright. It's late.
Go back and have some rest.
I really logged the whole day.
I'm so tired.
Hurry up.
Get out of here.
Call us
give us a call.
-Bye. -Do you go now?
- Take care. - Bye.
But how can I suddenly
how am I supposed to accept this all of a sudden?
My sister-in-law
from an actress,
who is a female doctor in geology,
with her name and personality.
She has completely changed.
It's too sudden.
Lower your voice.
Let's talk in the car.
What does it mean?
Second Uncle.
You also know that
xiaoman is a novelist.
Her ideas have always been wild.
Maybe the story
Is the material of her novel?
Second Uncle, you're...
To record that?
I've got a lot of free time recently.
You deserve to be the president of Mu's Group.
You're indeed a good talker.
Alright.
Then help me explain
whose material
whose materials are these?
What a steal.
I was just an actress.
How could she know
about our mining project?
And she also has
a doctor of geology?
I underestimated her.
If I release these things
on the Internet,
will it blow up?
Fooling the audience
It is enough to ruin
a small actor.
Let's talk about it.
Since you took the stuff,
they came to me first,
not the media.
This means
you don't want to destroy Su Jin
or the group.
What I want is simple.
Vacate Mu's position
the president of Mu Group,
give up all your shares
have you got a big appetite?
You have three days.
If you can't do that,
I'll do it for you.
Gao Ling consult the accountants in private.
Check Second Uncle.
You want to check his accounts?
Make a guess.
You're tired today.
Finally, knock off.
Where's my phone?
She's with me.
Has anyone called?
No one.
From last night till now,
mr. Mu hasn't called
every time.
Is he right?
He really regrets it?
This is too strange.
He only speaks nonsense everyday.
Boss has been so strange these days.
In the office the whole time.
Since she opened the door.
Secretary Gao is inside too.
Something serious
something big is going to happen?
Is there a financial crisis?
Hello, sister-in-law.
Are you in the office?
Yes, I am.
Is your brother at his office?
He's here too.
Xiaoman.
I hope you can tell me the truth.
Is there anything wrong with your brother?
It's impossible.
Xiaoqin, why do you ask this?
My brother is an adult.
He's an adult.
He didn't come out last night
and up to now,
you haven't replied to my messages
for a day and a night.
He didn't even call her.
Gao Ling told me that his company
has received several big projects recently.
So, he was probably a little busy.
You know that
he is a workaholic.
He never had day or night
there's no day or night.
Xiaoman.
I hope you don't hide it from me.
No matter what happens,
I hope
you can face it with your brother.
Sister-in-law, let me be honest with you.
If he really had an accident,
and it's very serious.
I was so worried.
Wait, what exactly happened?
You've been busy today.
Let's go home.
Why are you here?
Sent you a message.
They all fail.
So I had to come over.
I haven't seen you for only two days,
you've turned into a wild man.
What savage?
Touch your stubble.
It hurts so much.
You are the worst!
What?
My stubble can affect you
your image
In your heart.
No, that's not good.
Are you tired?
It wasn't at first.
Now I feel tired
after you came here.
Let me massage you something.
Xiaoman has told me everything.
Sorry.
I dragged you into this.
What do you care about that?
It's about the agreement
the agreement between Su Jin and me.
With the agreement.
Can we not talk about this?
I'll keep you company.
Alright.
Look at this.
Found it.
I sent it to you. Did you see it?
Alright.
He's in bad debt now.
He doesn't dare to threaten you again.
No matter what,
part of the reason why he did it
was for the company.
That's it for now.
Alright.
Would you like to have breakfast?
How about we watch the sunrise?
Honey?
I just shot all night,
and you asked me to come here.
It's only 7 a.m.
So early?
So early in the morning?
You know what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking that
you have to follow me.
Because
I will give you a foothold
In the entertainment industry.
Why?
From tomorrow on,
I will be
the group's new president.
Really?
What about Mu Hurun?
It has nothing to do with him anymore.
How come you like him?
That's impossible.
I'm your sweetheart.
That's me.
Envy Su Jin sometimes.
Mr. Mu worked very hard
to her back then.
Yadan.
Keep this in mind.
You are my girl
don't envy anyone.
If Su Jin has it,
you will have
then...
What about my new movie?
Your new play?
Secretary Gao,
the resignation letter of Xiaolan.
Resignation letter?
Mr. Mu,
we have found
we have a big financial problem.
I've sent you the relevant evidence
the relevant evidence to your email.
Oh, right.
Mr. Mu asked me to tell you something.
The day he resigned
Is the day you go to jail.
Think it over.
I'll hang up now.
What's up
Is that Mu Huron?
Up to now?
In fact, that day
I saw the information
on the two sisters.
The current Su Jin.
Not the real Su Jin.
How about
expose her to the press.
That way, Muhurun
mu Huron will never recover.
Scram!
I'm doing this for your own good.
Xu Yadan!
I know your thoughts.
Your aim is to harm Su Jin
but I warn you,
this information is the best.
Before this.
If the company fails,
I will not spare you.
I once went
when I was on a field trip,
I watched sunrises and sunsets.
But this sunrise today
Is the most beautiful one I've ever seen.
Do you know why?
That is because today
I will watch it with you.
You are still
the same narcissistic as before.
You haven't changed at all.
Why not?
We can.
If Su Jishi
don't you know
you are really special.
I know.
You're full of yourself.
As soon as you appeared,
you disrupted
all my plans in life.
Sometimes I feel that
you are so like a kite.
Free and free.
And I
Is like the string
that's pulling the kite.
The more I pull you,
the higher you fly.
But sometimes I am so scared.
I'm afraid that somehow one day
the string will break.
I'll never be able to find you again.
That's why...
I'd rather
to become a kite?
Will you take me with you?
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
You answer it first.
Hello?
I am busy.
Can't you come back
can't we talk about it later?
Something happened to Mr. Mu.
It was exposed.
Got it.
Wait for me upstairs.
I'm already downstairs.
Don't worry.
It will be properly handled.
I'll go up first.
Contact me later.
Alright.
Today it's disclosed that
the popular female artist Su Jin
the hottest actress, Su Jin
It was played by
by Su Jishi.
The more surprising thing is
su Jin and Mu's Group
the President of Mu Heulen
and their relationship
resorted to trickery?
To fool the audience.
Please show us
the picture ahead.
Hello, Huron.
I'm near your company now.
Let's go camping together tonight.
Alright.
Don't get caught.
Why do you suddenly come to camp?
This is the first time
to camp out alone.
To camp alone.
Mr. Mu, you're
you're very skilled now.
It's a must.
Think about it.
I thought it through.
I will help you.
You
are a survival expert in the wild.
As for me,
the tent is not bad.
When we have time
when we have time,
you can
have a good adventure in the wild.
Don't take so close photos.
Come on, Mr. Mu.
OK.
Alright.
It's done.
Come. Have a look.
Come, sit down.
It's so beautiful.
My hands are cold.
You know
It's perfect for a song.
What song?
There are horns on my head.
What are you doing? Are you interviewing me?
Alright.
Reporter Su.
Mu Huron.
Yes, My Lord.
I'm Mu Huron.
It's...
Are you happy being with me?
Very happy.
How happy!
So happy?
Mu Huron.
Do you love me?
Love.
Love me more.
This much.
Will you always love me?
You don't have to answer.
Why are you so dull?
I'm not here.
What's the matter?
Am I too pretty?
That's enough.
From today on,
I'm your man.
So no matter where you go,
you can't leave me behind.
Can you promise me that?
Hello, what's wrong?
You've finally picked up.
Check out the live broadcast link
I sent you.
Dear all,
this is the site of
held by Su Jin.
We will broadcast it live
the press conference.
Su Jin will be on stage soon.
To release her official explanation
about the stuntman incident.
Hello, Mu's Company.
Sorry
we'll take care of this.
Hello. Mu's Company...
Sorry
we can't respond now.
We'll give the public an explanation later.
Sorry, sorry.
Hello. Mu's Group.
To solve this.
Please rest assured.
Please trust us.
That all the terms are valid.
For the moment,
to answer for now.
Don't worry. This is standard procedure.
The company will
the company later.
Brother.
Mr. Mu, this is the document for you.
Hey.
Huron.
The board of directors all hope
to draw a line between
stay away from Su Jin as soon as possible.
The netizens are criticizing Jin Xiu and his wife
are fake couple
you have deceived many netizens.
Some people even said
mr. Mu dared to
to make profits for the company
to make profits for the company.
Could it be that Mr. Mu can't hold on anymore?
Will the company be okay?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Mr. Mu must have a way
a solution.
Don't worry.
High altitude.
It's urgent. I need to leave.
Come with me.
Okay, I'll go drive the car.
Xiaoman,
call Fang Jie
ask about the current situation.
Call me if it's urgent.
Alright, got it.
Hello, Brother Fang Xie.
Alright.
What's the latest news from here?
Will keep up with you, Xiaoman.
See you later.
Hi, could you please
can you update
keep up with the news?
We will have
an official announcement.
By then,
miss Su.
Well, why are you
why do you come out?
Where are you going?
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go inside first.
Miss Su,
I know you're in a bad mood.
But if you just say something,
no wonder I'm not used to this.
Fang Xie, you should
you've never called me
called me Miss Su before.
Little Su, let's stop here.
Without telling Mr. Mu?
Are you really alright?
You can't always let him take the responsibility.
He's exhausted
these two days.
Hey.
I'm about to finish the paper.
Have you got a venue
of your product launch?
Miss Su, open the door first.
I have something to tell you in person.
What brings you here suddenly?
Just open the door.
Sis,
jin.
I'm sorry, Sis.
I'm really sorry.
You are finally back.
Sister.
I'm sorry.
These past few months,
you've suffered.
Stop crying.
Look at that.
You're about to use up the tissue.
It's only a few months ago.
I thought
have passed the five ice ages.
So during this time,
during this period?
Every time I sent an email,
they only said you're very good
I was worried.
I went to Africa.
Originally, I just wanted to
travel alone.
Then
then I met a charity organization
that protects elephants.
Mum once told me that...
Elephants were her favorite.
So I took a lot of pictures
photos of her.
Tell me something.
You took so many nice photos.
But you didn't know to send me any.
I just wanted to be alone.
That's why I cut off
with the outside world.
Later, I met a volunteer
domestic volunteer.
He's a fan of mine.
He told me that
su Jin is still active in China.
I knew that.
It must be you.
Then I saw
some negative news about me,
and I rushed back home.
I'm sorry,
I made you suffer.
Don't say sorry anymore.
I'm fine now.
So you and mom
with mom?
Sister.
Mom, she...
Mom.
Sister, you are here.
Sister.
Mother?
When did she leave?
One year ago.
My mom suddenly got sick.
I wanted to tell you that
but mum said you're going to graduate soon
she was afraid that you would worry.
He wouldn't let me tell you.
Mom's illness
deteriorated rapidly.
Target drugs one by one
one by one.
Until one day...
I was doing a scene.
I suddenly panicked.
Then I received a call from the hospital.
Miss Su,
cherish your time.
Mother.
Sister,
we don't have
without a mother.
Mom knows that
your favorite noodles.
She couldn't wait for you to come back.
So she taught me how to make the noodles
how to make the noodles.
I must learn it.
And cook it for you.
Over the years,
has changed.
Was your sister
she was the same as you.
When she was little,
she was often picky about food.
But she
she loves the noodles
the noodles I made for her.
It's been years.
I miss her.
She must have
she must have forgotten
the smell.
Maybe
that she doesn't want to mention it anymore.
She is 8 years old,
so your father
take her and leave us.
I know.
She
she's still angry with me.
Mom said that
she didn't grow up with you over these years.
She feels sorry to you.
I'm the one
who should apologize.
Sister.
Have some water.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Little Jin, since you're back,
let's get everything back on track.
What is your plan?
Dear all,
this is the temporary
held by Su Jin.
Our channel will broadcast
live streaming the entire episode.
Su Jin is about to make
her explanation
regarding the stand-in incident.
Sir, please drive faster!
They're getting out.
Miss Su,
are you sure you've made up your mind
you really want to do this?
Mr. Mu has been
recently, Mu's Group has suffered
over the past few days.
He shouldn't
should not be borne by him
and his company.