Stop urging me.
I know there's an activity.
I'm downstairs
downstairs now.
Dear,
hurry up, right?
There is a huge explosion over there.
You are so late.
I thought you
why would you
to stand you up?
Sorry
I didn't expect to
I have so many messy things
messy things in my house.
Don't you think
you owe me an explanation?
What?
Don't play dumb.
You mean that day?
I told you that day.
I can't make it because of something.
Sorry.
I didn't come here today
not to listen to
to make yourself vague.
What do you want to hear then?
The truth?
As long as it's true,
no matter how absurd,
I believe whatever you say.
It doesn't matter.
How ridiculous.
Right.
Just tell me
actually, that day,
I fell into a novel
a novel about the entertainment circle.
And realistic.
Alright.
My garden is on fire.
I'm putting out the fire.
Be more sure about it.
I'm lost.
The way to meet me is too complicated.
I got lost as I walked.
You once told me
wherever you want to go,
even if there isn't a way,
you will find a way out.
That's right.
But are accidents always going to happen?
For example, you chisel for a long time
and you find out
my neighbor's road.
It also says
no mining is allowed on this road.
When I take a closer look,
protected area?
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Why can't you
tell me the truth?
I checked with Fang Jie.
You didn't go anywhere that day.
You didn't travel through time.
And your house isn't on fire.
You're not lost, either.
You were at home.
You even wore makeup.
But you didn't come.
Mu Hurun, is it enough?
You are only Party A to me.
You are my boyfriend in the agreement.
What makes you
to interrogate me about these now?
And you know that
these are only excuses.
Why do you still want to ask?
Alright, I'll tell you now.
I have no reason to
I'm willful.
I just don't want to go, OK?
I want to get off.
Are you and Mr. Mu...
Don't mention his name
that's his name.
Ms. Gu, you're pretty.
That's enough
-Go! -Go away!
Little Jin.
Who's your younger sister? Why are you qualified?
I was wrong before.
I'm sorry.
From now on, we'll be in the same trade.
We still have a long way to go.
We should take care of each other.
Grow up together. Isn't that better?
Right?
How do you want to take care of each other?
I know.
You're the host today.
I arranged dozens of interviews
dozens of interviews
for group interviews,
I can cover it for you.
You know that
I'm very good at group interviews.
I think you're working so hard.
You can take a rest.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I don't want to steal it.
For your media resources.
Thank you for reminding me.
Fang Xie,
to inform all
from the press conference.
I will arrange a time
give them half of the time
of the interview.
No matter how late it is,
please wait for me.
Alright.
What a pity.
I'm not used to
towards Plastic Sisters.
The clothes came undone.
Threads?
That Su Jin is so mean.
Sister, don't be angry.
Wait and see.
That's too much!
You know what?
Looks an honest man.
Your personal life is such a mess.
But my love for you is worthless.
I almost forgot.
Sister-in-law is live-streaming today.
Today, our investors
mr. Muthulen
also arrived at the scene
this movie is about
a magical note
triggered by this book.
Everyone knows
our heroine,
where is Miss Su Jin?
She has had
are really thriving in both career and relationship.
I'd like to know
have you two
you were in love,
did you write letters
or diary entries?
Nothing.
Anyone still wants to ask
what is the secret
to keep love fresh?
No need to be kept fresh.
What does that mean?
It seems that the two of you
very close indeed.
Right?
And never quarreled.
It's so enviable.
There's nothing to be envious of.
Because we didn't
nothing to fight over.
Please.
That's because
before we had a fight,
before we have a fight.
You are such a
you really keep me in suspense.
Mr. Mu has been
In the investment.
I'd like to know if Mr. Mu
your expectation for
after its release?
First of all,
I definitely hope that
this movie can be a big hit.
But for me, personally,
I hope that
to see Xiao Jin's progress and growth
through my help.
We didn't expect to see
they caught us off guard.
What about Xiao Jin?
We hope all the viewers
can enjoy the movie.
Besides, Mr. Mu doesn't need to worry.
With me every day.
I can do it well myself.
When two young lovers
flirting with each other.
When you flirted with me.
Alright.
Thank you for accepting
for this short interview.
Next, let's welcome
of the film
to the stage.
Let's wish Mystery Note
the Mysterious Notebook is a box office hit.
Su Jin, I love you!
What are you doing?
Come closer.
Why is he standing in the middle?
Sweetheart.
She was bullied again today.
When are you going to comfort me?
Miss Su.
What's going on then?
You've been hostile today.
Originally, the film
for your couple effect.
Because of your couple effect.
It's a joint interview.
The hosts were flexible.
I originally thought
your popularity is very high.
It seems that
a very close relationship.
A famous romantic complex
approached her.
I was thinking
should I pick it up?
Stop.
If you don't want to continue,
to clean up more mess.
I advise you to give up your idea.
In addition to the content
to be performed.
I don't want to
to see him recently.
I don't want to see him for now.
Miss Su,
mr. Mu is actually
out of kindness.
Whether it's funds
channels and connections,
Is all out.
What's wrong with you these days?
And you want to know
If you believe me?
Send a tweet now!
I mean Su Jin,
from the entertainment circle.
I'm sorry.
OK.
Miss Su, shall we go back first?
I'll buy you fried chicken, okay?
Come on.
Su Jin!
Let's see how arrogant you are.
Mr. Mu.
Mr. Mu wants to discuss with you
the mining in Yiliang Mountain.
I'll go to the company right away.
Huron is
our group's mines
our group's mine is almost at full exploitation.
The mining work in Yiliangshan Mine
be imperative
second Uncle.
My father didn't explore this mine back then
I am sure you know
that my older brother
Is stubborn.
Walking into a thing.
You can't even get through it.
But it's been so many years.
With no result.
Research on new minerals takes years
or decades.
Once the results come out,
huron.
Don't you think the stakes is a bit high?
Over ten years.
So much manpower and material resources
and made no noise.
What's more,
I also have
wrong about me.
About the test?
After the test report
when the test report comes out.
Huron.
We are doing a company,
not a research institute.
If you keep wasting time like this,
the actual situation of our company
than our company.
Huron.
Listen to Second Uncle.
And think about it.
Second Uncle.
Please give me more time.
Mr. Mu.
Say it quickly. I'm not in the mood.
Don't be fierce.
I have good news for you.
There's news
and Mu Hurun.
Do you want to know
what news?
Why did you lock the door?
Fang Xie,
you'd better give me
a reasonable reason
to be mad in the morning.
There are reporters downstairs.
Why?
Other than cooperation,
to be performed.
I don't want to
to meet him recently.
I thought
your popularity is very high.
It seems that
a very close relationship.
A famous romantic complex
approached her.
I was thinking
should I pick it up?
Stop.
Do you believe that I can now
I'll post a tweet.
Su Jin,
farewell to the showbiz.
Is this...
That day in the basement?
I don't know who took it
and cut it like this.
Now everyone is posting articles,
that you have cheated the audience.
Miss Su.
I'm really sorry.
Can you hit me? Scold me?
I said those words with you.
And I'm the one who lost your temper.
You can't take the blame.
How's the situation now?
All the media downstairs
are waiting for you
to take your first-hand account.
We'll try to
be low-profile.
I've discussed with the company.
To cancel all the announcements.
Stay at home
stay at home as much as possible.
Leave the rest to me.
Thank you for your hard work.
If there's anything,
please tell me right away.
Then I...
You can do anything
as long as you don't go out.
I'll take care of it.
Will it be me
will it be ruined by me?
In addition to the cooperation,
to be performed.
I don't want to
allow me to see him.
This is clearly
and making rumors.
The purpose is to
to draw attention.
How about this?
Find an identification team.
Once we find the source,
request the lawyer to send a letter.
Such a matter cannot be tolerated.
Alright.
I'll keep in touch with Fang Fang.
But their voices
In the recording.
I'll see if they
If they can provide some clues
to find the source.
Then go on.
By the way,
how about this?
Call Fang Jie again.
Tell him all the arrangements
all the arrangements and processes
and process.
And tell him
If he encounters any troubles,
and that is hard to deal with,
you can come to me.
OK. A hundred percent.
Although I don't know
what happened to you recently,
but if there's anything
If you need help,
you can call me anytime.
If it was Xiao Jin,
how would she handle it?
The life we have now
Is like a mask
a mask glued to the skin.
Closely
repeat myself with all these hypocrites.
And depressing memories
have been bonded.
Now in retrospect,
since I signed the agreement,
special feelings
have taken root
♪ And rooted in my heart ♪
Why haven't you replied?
Mu Hurun, is it enough?
You are only Party A to me.
You are my boyfriend in the agreement.
What makes you
to interrogate me about these now?
And you know that
these are only excuses.
Why are you asking me that?
Hello, Miss Mo.
The revision of the paper.
Hello?
Hello, Brother.
Are you busy
what's up
do you know where Gao Ling
where Gao Ling is now?
Gao Ling.
What's the matter?
It's about work.
We might be in
at the bar we often went to.
What was it about work?
You can just ask me.
No, I'm fine.
You don't have to trouble yourself with such an inferior question.
I have to go now.
Hold on.
What?
What...
I...
I have a customer.
The client, friend.
Right. A friend of client's.
A friend of mine
the thing is,
he has
with his girlfriend.
And then
our relationship became awkward.
And asked me what to do.
You know
how can I understand this?
So I want to ask you
If you have any opinions.
Are there any conflicts?
I think so.
The wife has a secret she doesn't want to tell.
But I will
that client friend of mine
already knows.
He cheated on her.
Hey.
Pregnant and run with the ball?
What are you talking about?
Then what's the reason?
You don't talk about the problem,
then how can he suit the remedy?
In short,
It's hard to express the specific name.
Anyway, I don't know
the details.
Your friend is so dramatic.
Hypocritical.
He asked someone to chase his wife
when helping me with my wife.
Please wait.
It's done.
I've given you the usual secret method
the contract.
Transfer it to him.
I really have something to do.
I'll hang up now, bye bye.
Hey. Hey.
Xiaoman.
They prefer cold war.
And the Cold War.
Mr. Gao,
how are you going to
why so late?
I have something to do. I got off work later.
Cheers!
That's right.
Great. I will catch you red-handed.
Mr. Gao,
do you remember the girl
the girl you talked about last time?
Dear.
Xiaoman.
This is Xiaoman.
I'm Gao Ling's girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
No, I won't.
Little boy!
These are the interns
for internship.
Who's a kid?
It's you.
Don't make fun of her.
This might be
this could be your soul mate.
Hey.
Go home and sleep.
Mr. Gao, are you going to order more wine or not?
Other tables are waiting for me.
Then
the same bottle as before.
Please.
Give me a bottle of
your most expensive wine.
I want to be alone with my
with my darling.
No problem. You two can have a chat.
My dear ancestors,
brother Gao Ling.
I think your soul mate
Is to talk
to talk about money with you.
You are mine
you won't leave!
What are we going to do to the lady?
Sister, I've brought you
what you want.
Those reporters downstairs
downstairs
fang Xie didn't follow you, right?
She's not here.
But Ats...
Why do you need a wig?
Isn't this exactly the same
exactly the same?
Exactly the same.
Is that Su Jin?
Su Jin has the same hairstyle.
I've seen this outfit before too.
It must be her.
I also think
can it be?
Let's go and have a look.
Mr. Mu, here is some important information.
Mr. Mu Xiuren.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I heard that
about geology here
were donated by you.
Right?
Is it true?
Mr. Mu.
I'm afraid you might get attacked.
How have you been these days?
Pretty good.
Regarding the recording,
about the recording.
It was my fault.
It's my fault.
That day,
It's really impolite
to keep pressing you like this.
Sorry.
Say it one more time.
Mr. Mu, were you apologizing
sorry to me just now?
I didn't hear clearly just now.
Say that again.
Listen carefully.
Over the past few days, I...
I had trouble eating and sleeping.
To eat or sleep.
My ears can't work well either.
Sorry.
Now I hear it.
Then our cold war
so much.
What cold war?
Nothing.
By the way,
according to Fang's explanation,
because of your trick,
he's apologizing to the media
to the media one by one.
That's right. I still have something to do.
If you go downstairs now,
no doubt you'll be recognized.
Follow me.
This library
has a deep collaboration with Mu's Group.
No one will come to the second floor.
I'll send you
I'll send you an account of the internal website.
You can investigate whatever you want.
You can stay until the museum is closed.
This place is secluded.
Thank you.
Go back to your work.
It's my pleasure.
Paparazzi.
Are you doing?
Usually, you expose
speaks the truth.
You really have to keep an eye on someone?
Who got lost in the community.
You don't know?
Sorry, Mr. Mu.
We didn't do our job well.
Sorry doesn't help.
Hello
who are you?
And the people who are paying you,
a decent egg comes and goes.
If we can't find Su Jin and Mu Hurun,
what about the people around him?
Such a big thing happened.
Didn't the people around them
knew nothing?
That's right. You're right.
Also,
continue to keep an eye on Su Jin's house.
As long as she shows her face,
we must make new contributions
okay, don't worry this time.
Is there a problem
with the methods?
It seems Gaoling won't accept
won't accept these tricks.
Search the places you don't understand.
He will attack.
Tough flirting?
Are not reliable.
The story on the website is good.
It's so touching.
Just follow this.
Write a love letter first.
And then make an accident.
For a innocent and tragic start.
That's it.
Write a love letter.
How to write a love letter?
There's finally one thing
smoothly.
It's so late.
I've finished my work.
Why are you still here?
Make do with the special period.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm just reminding you in a way.
You still owe me dinner.
When I finish this matter,
I promise you that
no matter what the result is,
I'll return
return the dinner.
It's a deal
hello?
What's so important?
What?
Got it.
What's up
a group of reporters
who doesn't know the address
and now she's waiting in front of my mom's house.
She tripped.
How is Aunt Hua?
I heard that she's fine.
I need to go back now.
Go now.
When you're home,
when you're home.
Call me if you need anything.
I'm too willful?
Affect people around me.
Why didn't you tell me
If you had gone to the library?
Because you had Xiao Xia pretend to be you.
Those unscrupulous marketing accounts
I don't know how many gossip articles
published gossip articles.
I don't want to blame you.
Of course you have something to do.
I found that
you are not yourself recently.
Be careful
on your way back.
The number of paparazzi never decreases.
Don't be hurt by them then.
Tell me if you have to.
I'll pick you up.
Miss Su,
we're protecting you. Don't be afraid.
Sister, when are you coming back?
Have you finished your things?
Don't worry about the useless things online.
Did you eat today?
I wonder how Aunt Hua is.
Aunt Hua, are you all right?
I'm sorry that you got hurt
because of me.
Aunt Hua.
It's Xiaojin.
I'm fine.
I sprained my foot
I sprained my ankle.
Don't blame yourself.
Look at Huron.
She shouldn't
how can I talk to you about such a trivial matter?
It's you
these days,
those rumors outside
and the
on the Internet,
It's all your fault, my son.
How's your relationship with Huron?
About you and Huron?
Right? It's fine.
Listen to Aunt Hua.
Eat well and take good care of yourself.
The next time you go home,
you can't be thinner.
Got it?
All right, aunt Hua.
I won't tell you anymore.
On Weibo the other day.
Half an hour.
See you downstairs.
You've been here for days.
Ask your questions.
And then go home.
In the past few days,
why didn't you explain yourself
why didn't you explain it?
As actors and actresses,
our works speak for ourselves.
As for my personal life,
I fully understand your curiosity.
But I won't follow the rules.
Those who make up stories
the vulgar taste of a sneak peek.
I also want you to know that
artists have their own privacy.
Harass and hurt my family and friends.
I will get to the bottom of it.
I also hope that
can be watched
learns to be responsible
for your actions.
Secretly filmed,
and malicious editing.
Someone who tries to speak up for me
then one day,
the law will speak for you, too.
So you mean that...
Those online are just rumors?
The fool follows the crowd, and the wise will distinguish themselves.
Any other questions?
If not,
please go back and rest.
Please answer me directly.
Is your relationship
was it true or not?
Did you really love each other?
Will you really marry
each other?
Really
really
please answer.
Please answer directly.
Mr. Mu and I are
certainly.
Mr. Mu is here.
Miss Su Jin and I
no matter what happens
or encounter in the future,
our relationship
will never change.
How can you prove that?
That's right. How can you prove that?
Trust me.
Since you two are so in love,
then the public notice
online exposed,
what is your contract
you mentioned?
Right.
Yes. That contract...
The contract?
That contract is nothing but
Is about a love variety show.
I didn't expect that
there would be such a huge misunderstanding.
I'm really sorry.
Are you planning
do a variety show together?
Right.
We think
we can do it
meet everyone
to meet everyone.
I'll follow you later.
I hope you can look forward
by then.
Where is the hammer?
They're watching.
Good Muhurun.
How dare you play this trick on me?
Sorry.
I took the initiative just now.
The reporters downstairs
won't leave for a while.
Don't thank me.
I know. I was
naturally.
It's too natural.
Why did you agree to
on behalf of me?
You don't have to agree.
But if you don't agree...
There will be more trouble later.
I'm not used to being protected.
What's more,
there's no requirement
mr. Mu should be worried about this.
I think you'll have to
get used to it.
Remember to close the door.
You called me to the company headquarters
very early in the morning,
what do you want?
Miss Su,
this is the best value
see? Even if we record in 12 days,
how about airing for two months?
The exposure and topicality
are going to be incredible.
It can't last 12 hours.
The press has released the statement.
It's bad if I don't go.
Mu Hurun promised.
Ask him to find a solution.
That's what you were talking about?
That your contract with Mr. Mu
needs you
to meet the needs of party A.
Right?
Threatening me with this.
I can memorize every detail of
the new cooperation.
Chapter 8, Article 17
Any event
attend any event,
a joint appearance
requires approval of both parties.
Neither party
to make a decision
he is arranging a twelve-day date
for me without permission.
To sue him without any lawyer,
to sue him.
However,
fang Jie, whose side are you on?
This is not your turn.
You have to do this.
Either you or...
Either you hammer it with a hammer
hammer me to death.
That's good. Fang Xie.
You forced my sister
force my sister back then, right?
It seems that I should judge
why my sister left.
She left?
Sister, where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
Sis,
I know you work hard in acting.
You don't have enough to eat or warm clothes.
You need to wear suspenders in winter,
In the summer, you should wear coats.
This reality show
I'll tell him on your behalf.
We won't go.
Brother Fang,
stop forcing Miss Su.
Xiao Xia, you heard wrong.
I don't want to leave.
I heard it wrong.
That might be because
I have been too tense recently
and always worried about something.
That's good.
Have some coffee to warm your hands.
Thank you.
I'll leave you two alone.
I'll go organize the report.
Just go.
The thing between me and my sister
to Xia all the time.
To hide the truth.
You find the right time
to tell her, right?
Miss Su, I know that
you've greatly helped me
to stay back this time.
During this period,
I have been forcing you to do
things that you don't like.
Actually, I feel guilty too.
Forget about it.
Fine, then.
I'll handle the rest.
Thank you, Fang Xie.
Breakfast for me.
You put so much effort into it.
All the reporters downstairs have left.
After the breakfast,
please clean the dishes.
And leave my house.
This breakfast
to thank you for helping me out.
Don't even think about love.
I won't participate in our cooperation
I won't participate in it.
Hey.
Hello, Mr. Mu.
To edit and record.
Of the editing and recording.
And I've handed it
to the relevant departments.
As you expected,
he admitted.
Was ordered by your second uncle.
So,
we need to inform them,
they need to be taken care of.
I can't.
Didn't she promise to
In front of the camera yesterday?
With such a popular show,
other artists are hoping to
be the next flying guest.
Su Jin thinks that
that she can be self-willed
and be willful now?
President Chen.
Su Jin has been under great pressure recently.
She has too many appointments.
You need to be clear.
That you live on commission.
You have your own performance.
If you don't want to be the manager,
there are so many who want to be it.
That's right.
You are right.
I'll think of another way
I'll think of other ways.
I won't hold the company back.
But this love affair
I can't.
Why did you come back?
You left the car key there.
Are you all right?
What can it be?
Don't forget that
I am the manager who made
of the national flower Su Jin.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
Fang Xie,
maybe we should go together.
That was a joke.
Nothing. Tell me.
You can go to
really?
This is strange.
Since you're so kind to invite Prince Yu,
would I dare not go?
Okay. See you later.
See you later.
Xiaoman.
Who are you talking to?
Having a date?
Or an insider?
If you're too ambitious,
that's good.
Now you know
I'm dating someone.
Then stop thinking about it.
Gao Ling, wait here.
What are you doing?
Having a date.
What?
Aren't you going to see
your date?
I'd like to see that.
That can make you refuse?
That my girlfriend
which stage?