Dating is not limited to holding hands.
Hug and physical interaction.
To stay overnight at home.
Miss Su, are you trying to
want to terminate the contract again?
This kind of cooperation
Is definitely not to
urging me to get married.
I think he wants to use
to cash Su Jin's money
for your own benefit.
What's so complicated?
Hey.
Sister.
Deep-Fried Chicken with Chili Pepper
he sends us
to live stream.
Fried chicken.
The most popular fried chicken chain
In the whole network.
Their live-stream studio
only invite the hottest stars
with the hottest celebrities
to try out new products.
The popularity of our anti-proposal
Is too great.
So they want us to attend it.
Got it.
That looks so delicious.
Miss Su,
you are right.
The one invited by the live stream
to be with Mr. Mu
and were broadcast live under the name of Splendid China.
As for the fried chicken company,
the investor behind the scenes
Is Mu's Group.
They really want to
to make money by using Xiaojin.
Forget it. Let's reject it.
Not really.
Not only will I go
but also to renew my contract.
Right now,
Is drafting a new contract now.
Take back all the things
that should be ours.
Have I
make yourself clear, right?
You should have
to make it clear to her earlier.
She has a good temper.
Lively and outgoing.
I also like that.
To marry you?
Alright.
If the two of you
are having a fight,
I'll be relieved.
After you get married,
the property
will have to be redistributed
according to law.
I need to check the Company Succession Law.
I'll leave you two alone.
The trending topic.
How did Su Jin propose?
Why is no one
about this script?
She told me
Is because of my career transformation.
What's that for?
Do you believe that?
Come on. Look at me.
When a girl
who suddenly starts to
to change herself.
That must be
you have a crush on someone.
She's into you.
To catch your attention.
Who is your sweetheart?
My heart
this is it.
Hey.
It's over.
In the future.
All right, young lady.
I have a meeting.
I'll leave now.
Brother Gao Ling.
See you later.
Join Su Jin and you will broadcast live
live selling fried chicken.
If you continue fooling around with Xiaoman,
you'll have your year-end bonus deducted for three months.
This time, I didn't.
This company
of this company.
They said
If you show up together,
their profit will double.
When did I invest in this company?
This company.
Three years ago,
I ordered fried chicken for you.
You said the sweetness of their tomato sauce
the sweetness of their ketchup.
And let me support you.
Then I'll help you
one million yuan in the capital.
Now they are
a nationwide chain
and it has become an internet celebrity.
Reject it.
High altitude.
Please remember.
I never eat
never eat sweet fried chicken.
I remembered it wrong.
Miss Su,
confirmed?
Mr. Mu is too busy
and cancel this live stream.
Why?
The reason isn't important.
The important thing is
that we can do
do a couple's live streaming,
to be a couple?
No, it's not.
Then I should be more active.
If he doesn't come,
I'll still be able to make a scene.
That I'm worthy of his contract renewal
that I deserve him to renew his contract.
Of his renewing my contract.
Right?
However,
enough.
I know what you're worried about.
You're worried
exposing my identity
will Su Jin's image
will further collapse?
Fang Xie,
I did promise you
I can play Su Jin
but you have to remember
I am not Jinqing.
I would never be able to act
the Su Jin that you created.
Sister Su.
Then I...
Youyou, lunch is here.
Alright?
I'll check the process.
Xiao Xia,
we have another?
There are.
Pick whatever you like.
Nothing else but these.
Youyou,
I thought you only had salad
for lunch?
That's why I didn't prepare anything else.
Don't worry. It's your fault.
I don't have an appetite today.
I won't eat now.
Shan.
Refine your makeup.
Everything is arranged accordingly.
I don't even have the freedom to eat.
And the company works like crazy.
No wonder you're tired.
Don't worry.
I'll pay you
I'll earn it for you.
Sis,
be happy.
I'll have fried chicken
during the live stream later.
Shan.
How about we change
for a new makeup today?
Come. Stop a moment.
Come here, everybody.
Our live guest
has changed.
The live streaming proposal has changed.
Let's go and get familiar with them.
Are you sure to ask these questions?
What if she gets angry
she is angry?
Su Jin is famous for her good temper.
How can she be angry?
Brother, Su Jin is here.
Are you sure it's a sweet white flower?
Hi, everyone.
This is Su Jin.
The hit live studio.
Sent here.
Right, I forgot to tell you that
their headquarters
Is on the 20th floor.
Su Jin will be there for the live broadcast.
Not interested.
You can get off work now.
Alright.
Su Jin,
I asked you to go and check
xiaoman's situation.
What?
You've got the result now
and report it to me now?
See you
childish!
Wow, it's amazing.
The first batch of purchasing vouchers
were all sold
the daigou coupons.
This is live streaming.
Thank you all
Isn't it awkward?
Little Jin.
Look at the machine in front.
Yes, that's right ahead.
Hi, everyone.
We originally
not only Xiao Jin,
she also invited her boyfriend
to come with her.
But unfortunately,
In the end,
mr. Mu couldn't be here
could you please reveal
the reason?
He's too busy.
I'm sorry
I let you down.
I'll bring him here
I'll take him here next time.
Brother.
This anchor asked.
Was different from
as what we wrote in the playscript.
Before this,
was in the trending topic
In the trending topic.
We are all curious about
why Xiaojin made such a choice
such a choice?
Xiaojin seems very anxious.
Why is it me who proposed?
First of all,
the fact that I raised this issue
It already shows
you set a frame
for your ideas.
What makes you propose?
It has to be the man.
We shouldn't label men
being active or passive
active and passive.
I think two people together
they have to explore
an emotional mode
of their own.
They're comfortable being together.
To be together?
After all, in this era,
to meet someone
that wants you to propose.
That wants you to propose
to have a crush on him.
Right?
The shy president's brother.
Hey.
Does it seem naive of me
am I too childish?
What Xiao Jin said is very good.
I really agree with you.
Su Jin,
your transformation
be based
the collapse of my image?
No way!
I'll show them
what truly
the true glamour of men.
How can I lose?
With Xiaojin recently.
We're going to
the real theme
the real theme today.
As the taste of
taste new products today,
the fried chicken,
please bring the fried chicken
please serve the fried chicken.
It seems that Xiao Jin is very happy.
More than talking about your boyfriend.
Of course. This is
I'm looking forward to the most today.
I can't wait another second.
What's up
why did my brother
going to Su Jin's live streaming?
Come here. Hurry up.
Come on!
Come here.
Mr. Mu, what are you doing here?
Can rest assured.
Let me handle the business here.
Can you do that?
Certainly.
I fried chicken for the first few rounds.
All seconds left.
You can't.
What do you mean?
Everyone, you can see this.
I'm as excited as you are.
Come on, Mr. Mu.
Hurry up and greet
to my family now.
Alright.
Hello, everyone. I am Mu Huron.
The fiancé of Miss Su Jin.
Hold on.
My hair is stuck.
That's much better.
What an impressive acting skill.
He's had a mouthful of dog food.
That's so happy!
Our fried chicken
Is ready.
Now, please
try our new products.
And then give our babies
our babies.
Alright.
Here, I can help you.
I heard that
eating fried chicken
with your beloved,
you'll be happier.
Come on.
I'm coming.
Female artist.
You can't eat fried chicken like that?
Look how delicious it is.
Slow down.
I rubbed my mouth.
Come on.
Is that so greasy?
Brother.
I'm gone.
It seems
unlock other new attributes
you unlock other new attributes.
Me too.
And I have been holding
for three years.
As an entertainer,
please take care of your body, okay?
I can't watch this live stream anymore.
Su Jin must have put on a lot of weight recently.
Why don't you feel that?
You are so fat.
He ate so much even in live stream.
I've become
laugh and grow fat
but I think that everyone should
don't live with the labels
the labels that were put on you.
You should never live up to
other people's taste.
If you want to eat,
the most important thing is to be happy.
Mr. Mu, do you agree
of Xiaojin?
Certainly.
You can eat whatever
want to eat.
After all, being healthy
a good health is the most important.
Right?
He's here again.
That's right.
He must be so strong.
What about us?
(Don't be afraid)
I'll get fat from eating fried chicken.
The right amount of fat intake
Is essential
to your health.
Such as fried chicken.
It won't gain weight,
It speeds up metabolism
and burns body fat.
I will recommend a tip
that won't get fat.
For example,
when we eat fried chicken,
In your mouth,
chew it for 30 times before swallowing.
In fact, just now everyone
didn't notice that.
I secretly
to swallow it
to swallow it, right?
Come, sweetheart.
Show us
the whole thing is yours
you can chew it for 30 times.
It's more disgusting.
Who can't?
You win.
Babies can also try
brother Gao Ling.
The novel I wrote.
How could they
change the script without permission?
Maybe we should
we're going to talk about your situation.
What happened
you, a little boy,
when do you learn
secretly dating someone?
I know it.
I know you lied to your brother.
With me?
You're busy with work.
I can't bother you
I won't bother you.
You've really grown up.
You know how to protect the one you love.
That's for sure.
To protect each other.
Is the first rule of love.
Haven't I done with the comments?
We're trying to add the keyword
to block them.
But to be honest,
the netizens are free to comment.
What's going on?
The fried chicken is sold out.
He even reserved one for next year.
The task has been completed.
Goodness.
Babies, you just can't believe it.
An anonymous user
already bought all our fried chicken
our fried chicken.
This fan said
he likes Little Jin very much.
He is a fan of Xiao Jin
and very supportive of you.
He said it was hard for Xiao Jin to do the live broadcast.
Let's all
thank you, Xiao Jin.
Thank you this fan.
We sold out the fried chicken
sold out in advance.
We have to end
ends early.
Have you not had enough?
Then Xiao Jin should
would like to say a few words.
First of all,
thank you, my friend.
However,
I must tell you this.
"Consume sensibly."
Don't waste food.
Don't do that next time.
Stop eating.
Thank you, Mr. Mu
for taking time out of your busy schedule to come here.
The live data
will be perfect.
There is still one month left.
How to manage Su Jin well.
I hope you know about this.
That's right.
Brother Fang!
Little Su is missing.
I've looked for her everywhere.
Yes
with the fried chicken?
Go find her.
One piece of fried chicken weighs three kilograms.
Hurry up.
Go for it.
We won't win.
Turn the tables.
Little Su.
Sister Su.
Ancestor.
Where are you?
You can't stop eating fried chicken.
Mu Xiaoman,
come here.
Brother.
Calm down.
I'm a university graduate.
You can't expect me to follow your lead
the same as you.
I...
You mentioned that
the sudden change in style
probably because she likes me.
You have a fever.
You actually know how to use
maybe the word
In the form of questions.
To prove that a girl
If she likes herself.
Su Jin can reach
reach such a level.
Tell me what
what happened?
Otherwise you are really hopeless.
It seems she's really something.
She's very beautiful.
Then I suggest you
find another boyfriend.
I'll just follow your advice.
She suddenly changed her appearance
and faced me with a new style.
He probably just wanted
to attract my attention.
There are so many ways to change your image.
And he chose
and the weirdest one.
It's not strange.
It's not good to see a girl who is too thin.
It's okay for her to be like this.
Aesthetic problem?
Doesn't mean I will...
Have any feelings
that kind of girl.
Get to the point.
In order to
to attract my attention.
She started to break my rules.
She won't let go.
Then propose to you
and marry you in public.
She's too scheming.
Is not that cheap.
What she's using now
It should be psychological
drawbridge effect.
My brain mistook fright
as affection for a woman.
Your heart was beating so fast.
How could it be possible
see that I wasn't hooked?
She decided to
all her previous actions
transform and make the most of
develop their commercial value.
The comments
to arouse my desire for victory.
Led me to the scene,
then she...
And then?
What happened after the live stream?
Nothing.
Brother.
It's obvious.
Su Jin is really
has fallen in love with you.
She's doing everything
to attract your attention.
Whether it's to draw my attention
I'll find out the truth
to find out the truth.
Why does it feel
my brother is acting weird today?
At this time,
your face is too sideways.
We have to pay attention
keep in relationship with the camera.
She's the best at 30 degrees.
Do you know
the netizens are
a brainiac.
The look in my eyes
was clearly
to tell Mu Huron
brother, stop acting.
Why did it become
to a show of affection?
Are you really
attentively?
What I said just now
you'll need these
to work.
Although this live streaming
Is really good,
we can't become
we must not become arrogant.
OK, got it.
Next,
It's time for serious business.
What business?
Settle Mu Huron.
And continue to work with him.
Mr. Mu,
I wonder if you are busy.
Little Jin.
And wants to see you.
The sooner the better
you want to see me?
I'm there to renew our contract.
Business cooperation.
Why are you trying to
dressing me like this?
What the heck is that fuzzy?
Even if it's a private trip,
your current
with the public.
Everywhere
wherever you go.
Watch your manners.
This is not show business at all.
This is clearly
the Truman Show.
Miss Su,
I put this lipstick
In your bag.
Remember to eat
eat it.
Replenish your energy.
Eat more.
What are you talking about?
This...
What's this?
Give it to me.
Dress like this.
Why wouldn't I bring my boyfriend
to protect you.
Your boyfriend?
I'll keep it carefully.
Miss Su, have a nice date.
Don't be impulsive!
Humph!
Do you think
only a hammer?
Miss Su.
Mr. Mu will be here soon.
He told me to take an order for you.
Alright.
What shall we order?
Australian lobster transported by air.
Give me the best
a dozen Iceland oysters.
Two Norwegian salmon.
King crab, deep-sea shrimp.
I think
you'll find a match.
Mr. Mu is rich.
Okay. One moment, please.
Mr. Mu is here.
To the point.
It was Mr. Mu
agreed to attend the appointment.
It's within the rules, right?
Compliance is the foundation.
But that doesn't mean it's valuable.
Tell me what you want.
Alright.
Then let's talk about
something valuable
look, our cooperation
for three years.
Has been going smoothly.
Is there still
one month is due.
You should consider
the continued collaboration?
Miss Su made such a big noise
made such a big noise before.
It's fine that I didn't hold her accountable.
You still want to carry on?
Are you kidding me?
I can talk with confidence
because I'm irreplaceable.
Tell me about it.
Your Mu's Group
all these years,
because of our cooperative relationship,
to our cooperation.
Especially this one.
Of your company.
How good
Is presented directly.
Mr. Mu, you read it.
More clearly than me.
Judging from your words,
I could
any of
any other celebrity
to cooperate with us.
Female stars are many,
but look at people from
your age and background,
you can't find anyone better than me.
I can also find
other outstanding women
to cooperate with me in dealing with my family.
Why should Miss Su tell me
you're the best fit.
You got to the point.
Our cooperation
Is only one month left.
At this moment,
you suddenly arrange to
the proposal.
There must be a reason
to do this.
For example,
to cope with the urging of your parents to get married.
If we stop
stop working with them,
mr. Mu will have to face
the troublesome scene
another troublesome scene.
You two.
Because your dad passed away early,
and bullied me.
Son,
you are the most devoted and filial child.
I only know
to threaten me?
Objective analysis of advantages and disadvantages
In summary,
and continue to cooperate.
It's good
and me.
Of course, this time
I offered to cooperate with you.
I will take the work
I will definitely take it seriously.
Miss Su. Miss
It must be three years
for three years.
But I feel that
It seems that
to know the real you.
She said
that's my work image.
What do you want?
I hope that we can make some adjustments
to the contract extension.
Except for the resources,
I want the company's shares.
The way of dividend should be discussed by both parties.
I have already worked out
the detailed rules.
Fang Jie will send it
secretary Gao to read it?
But you need money.
Right.
That's all.
As much money as I can.
It'll be easy as long as there's money.
As for the cooperation,
I've considered that.
So you have long prepared
a new agreement.
In which some new
to them.
In order not to waste this date,
have a look.
This guy is actually
come prepared
If he dares to add
strange terms,
don't blame me for touching the hammer.
The rules
about dating,
and the number of dates
why not?
We pretended to be a couple.
Things that waste
that wasted your time.
You should be happy.
As for the dividends
you've mentioned,
after I read
when I read the specific terms
will draw up
a new agreement for you.
Alright.
Mr. Mu, that's very generous.
Since...
We're done here.
After we talk about it.
I'm starving.
Cook for me every day.
I haven't eaten meat for a long time.
By the way, Mr. Mu,
I recently changed
my contact information a while ago.
Let's friend each other on WeChat.
I'll add you as my friend.
Alright.
Doctor Su.
That's only because
I love that.
As the saying goes,
an apple a day.
An apple a day.
The doctor stays away.
I like apples very much.
That's why I called Dr. Su.
Everyone should eat more apples.
You should eat one too.
You're welcome. Here.
Healthy.
Let's go then.
There are reporters outside.
Let me send you off.
Well, how long
how long will they follow us?
On a reality show,
miss Su Jin should be
should be more abundant than me.
It's not impossible.
Mr. Mu.
Pull over ahead.
Brother.
Is Su Jin
coming towards us?
How could it be?
Since when does she
directly communicate with me?
Well, Ling Xiao, look.
She is coming.
Sister Su Jin.
What a coincidence.
You followed me.
This...
How is it possible?
Take it easy.
Today, I am here
to tell you
an exclusive.
My boyfriend and I will
will drive to a field.
Let's see if we can take it.
To see
whether you can catch up with me.
What are you doing?
Mr. Mu, sit over there.
I'll drive the rest.
According to the file,
you don't know how to drive?
That's really character setting.
Mr. Mu, rest assured.
Leave it to me.
I'm a grown man.
I still need you.
Protect what?
Cut the crap.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Get in the car.
Don't stand there.
Sit still.
Brother, did we lose him?
Oh no. Where is this place?
All right
we've lost them.
You can drive on.
Alright.
I told you many times
I hate accidents the most
the most.
Wow.
Mr. Mu, come and take a look.
It's so beautiful.
Meteorite.
Most people call it a meteor.
I know.
But I like them
not because they...
About the wish wish.
But the meteorite.
Once it falls to the ground,
It will bring
to the Earth.
What do you mean?
Do you know what a meteorite is?
It's like glass.
There are blue and green.
How does she know these?
It's the one
the hot temperature of the meteorite
melted the target on the ground
and then cooled and solidified to form
he even studied geology
he even studied geology.
Fang Xie,
gave me
about geology.
In the play,
say yes and mean no
stop acting.
Luckily, I'm smart enough
I almost got caught.
Are you referring to
was first found in the Modawi River
In the Czech Republic.
So it is also called
the Modawi Stone.
Because each one
of each one
that's why they have
are different.
But no one knows.
What kind of meteorite
the next meteorite will bring?
Well
they are
that's unique to us.
There's no rush anyway.
We'll watch the stars before going back.
I knew you had ulterior motives.
It's really too cold.
Get in the car.
Brother,
let's have a good meal tonight...
Find our way back?
Shut up.
Where's my hammer?
Here it is.
There are no paparazzi now.
I won't walk you upstairs.
Mr. Mu.
The draft
our new contract.
Next time, can we
at home?
At home
more private.
In case you tell me
no need.
I think our cooperation
to continue.
What?
I don't usually say it the second time.
But considering your feeling now,
this is the last time.
Our cooperation is over.
Gao Ling will ask you
gao Ling will ask to see you.
It's one month and three days left.
Next,
I need Miss Su's cooperation.
Merry meet, merry part
In that case,
what else do I have
that need your cooperation.
For example, you rejected a proposal
and then counter-proposed.
The consequence that
caused by
I hope you and your team
to give me
the perfect solution.
Otherwise,
what compensation?
You should have known that
also,
I hope that
Is a person who believes
that doesn't affect
our company.
To this problem.
The atmosphere is always good.
Where is the problem?
Congratulations to Miss Su.
To show
the highest-level celebration.
Tell me what you want to eat tomorrow.
I'll go and buy it for you.
He refused.
Seriously?
I can't be more serious.
Come on.
Why not?
Didn't you just say that...
The atmosphere is good.
We can win her.
To get a raise?
I don't know.
Working in such an atmosphere
are problems.
Miss Su,
tell us the truth.
If something happened
Is there any reason
that we don't know?
It's personal.
I don't understand
why you can't renew your contract.
First,
she repeatedly violates our agreement.
Second,
the matter of opposing the proposal
caused a series of
a series of troubles.
The third and most important part is
work is work.
There's no emotion whatsoever.
Otherwise, it will become
uncontrollable variables.
I never work with
with a woman who likes me.
Why are you sighing?
You don't agree with me?
I agree with you.
Right. See?
That's a great partner.
But it's just gone.
What to tell mom?
To her?
How to answer my questions?
In your relationship?
Please tell me.
What to do.
What to do?
Cold scrambled egg.
I'm about to start now.
Right away.
What should we do now?
About...
To renew it.
But I want Murhurun to continue.
He begged me to renew it.
Let me hear
what is the plan of the perfect student?
Since I was little,
I have never dropped the ball
at all times.
Do you know the last person
who doesn't want to work with me
the consequence?
Of your
of your geological hammer.
And suffer more.
Than to die.
She's five years senior to me,
and he hasn't graduated yet.
Everyone is here.
Then let's
and get straight to the point.
Next season,
our top priority
to promote
the largest
the largest porphyry Copper Mine in the country.
The M & A of Qiduo Copper Mine
If the acquisition is successful,
this will mean
mu's Group will
will take an absolute lead
In the mining industry.
At that time,
the other business of the group
must make way for the acquisition.
I think other than M & A,
we have to maintain
our existing business domain,
we can also
to the new energy field.
The civilian market
high-nickel batteries
Is the limelight
the coolest new energy source.
Is like the fuel car.
The electric vehicle can't live without fuel.
Electric vehicles need electricity.
The amount of Ni in the battery
determines the capacity of the battery.
Mr. Mu,
for the storage battery area.
Don't welcome
the involvement of private capital.
We can take a step forward
before we can do it.
To produce intermediate nickel products,
which are electrolytic nickel and nickel sulfate.
Huron?
To launch a new business.
Is not as simple
as you think.
First of all,
It needs to introduce new equipment and talents.
Second,
the company's existing businesses
needs to be adjusted and restructured.
Third,
just as Mr. Ma said just now,
the problem of nickel ore resources
Is full of high risks.
But high risks
represents a high return.
Over ten years ago,
state E was trying to revive its industry
the export of laterite
of laterite nickel ore.
In recent years,
the window was reopened.
To allow some companies
to invest in E State.
With very strict conditions.
And recently,
I have taken down a few mines
and bought a few factories.
I object.
If the company advances rashly,
we may lose the territory we once had.
That's too risky.
I also disagree.
The development of the company
to develop
to get where you are today.
Enough.
Everyone's attitude
Is clear.
As for Mr. Mu,
he's still young.
They still need
to know more about the company.
When it comes to new business,
let's not rush to
to make a conclusion now.
We need to wait
the detailed report
of Mr. Xiao Mu's team.
I have
I have a dinner to attend.
To have a dinner together.
Together.
Huron.
Come to my office
come to my office and talk privately.
Alright.
These old fogies
and only do things conservatively.
New-type enterprises
Is developing so quickly.
The project is already
this project.
It's just a technical method
can't be solved.
We've prepared
the food is ready.
The food is on their lips.
They didn't know.
Open your mouth.
A new project
In the new project.
Since the parent company won't allow it,
we should invest in
to start new companies.
Right.
Don't be envious of us
jealous of our making money.
Now,
you should make more choices
that are suitable to invest in
to invest in and acquire.
Alright.
Got it.
I have something else to do.
Recently, the company's directors
are not satisfied with you.
Seeing Second Uncle's look.
Going on like this
to keep going like this.
No rush.
One day,
I will prove my ability to everyone
with the results.
Is it that message of Xiaojin?
Call her back at once.
She wants to rest.
Let her rest.
I know her.
After she adjusts herself,
she'll come back.
That's right.
You can take a horse to the water but you cannot make him drink
those who force to stay can't stay long.
Come on.
This is it?
The information
since his childhood.
From his upbringing
to hobbies,
to company information,
It's all here.
Great.
If there's anything you don't know,
and I
the dictionary?
The words won't be found.
Welcome to me.
Actually, I've always wanted to ask you
what made the opportunity
that prompted
the collaboration between Jinqing and Mu Hurun
It was his sister Mu Xiaoman
was actually his sister, Mu Xiaoman.
Where's Mu Huron?
Her company is getting better.
She needs a companion
to various occasions.
That's why I found Jin Qing
when I arrived at her house,
I realized that
the reason was partly
he wants to promote
his popularity.
The other half
was Mr. Mu's mother.
Forced him to find a girlfriend.
All these years,
mu's Group
aside from its
Its own established businesses,
It has also invested
many other industries,
like the entertainment industry,
the internet industry,
because of Su Jin,
brought more people
know about Mu's Group.
It is also more convenient for me to do so.
To break into the young market.
The more outstanding your sister is,
the greater the benefits
to Mu's Group.
So for coal bosses
to him,
presenting the data is the most intuitive.