♪Overcoming the boundary of confusion♪
♪Holding onto my life
in the face of death threats♪
♪I look into this dark night♪
♪Never once has my soul
been extinguished♪
♪With this passion♪
♪My spirit is growing
to reach full swing♪
♪Slashing the mountain
and the ocean apart♪
♪Answering the true call on a sword♪
♪I'm the chosen one
in this turbulent world♪
♪Keep my distance from the world♪
♪Who can understand my loneliness?♪
♪A single thought, looking down♪
♪Blades unsheathed,
frost flies everywhere♪
♪A belief that cuts through the world♪
♪Soaring towards the sky,
the sword reigns all♪
♪Striding across the land
with a drunken gait♪
♪I will protect the people
whenever I'm needed♪
♪Atop the summit, you and I shall
battle for the world's best♪
[Directed by Chen Zhoufei]
[Dashing Youth]
[Based on "Zhou Munan's
Juvenile Martial Arts Series"]
[from fanqienovel.com and bkneng.com]
[Episode 27]
Take a look. Which one do you like?
This is nice, right?
Let's buy this.
Ye, wait for me!
Ye, you are so kind.
Ye,
can you be my big brother?
I don't need Master anymore.
Ye.
Elder Wangyou,
you have been living in Mount Muyun
and observing Tianqi City.
I have something
to ask you.
Are you trying to ask
the whereabouts of your companions?
Right.
I wanted to ask Prince Langya
but I couldn't swallow my pride,
so I didn't.
Afterward, I tried to ask around
during the journey,
but then I realized
no one knew
about the bride snatching
as if it had never happened.
As for your friends,
Luo Qingyang was taken away
by the Shadow Sect
and locked up.
Nevertheless, he's the sect leader's
proudest disciple
as well as a future imperial guard
appointed by the Emperor.
Once everything quiets down,
Mr. Yi
probably would release him.
It's just that maybe
he might be given
some agreements to comply with.
As for Baili Dongjun,
his father, Baili Chengfeng,
brought him back to Qiandong City
and grounded him,
alongside
Sikong Changfeng.
However, as of now,
Sikong Changfeng
has already left Qiandong City
and is roaming around for training.
I thought you would only know
what happened to them in Tianqi City.
To my surprise,
you are even well aware
of their whereabouts afterward.
It's birds on the trees told me.
That's true.
Master speaks to birds.
No.
Not just birds,
but also fowls, beasts,
insects, fish, flowers, and weeds.
Master can sit down
and converse with them
the whole afternoon.
He lies to you.
Nonsense.
Master never lies.
Except
when he says
he will buy me candied hawthorns,
everything he says is true.
If the big commotion we caused
in Tianqi City
could be completely suppressed,
does that mean Wenjun
wouldn't know what happened,
that I came,
and even
that I had already charged into
Prince Jingyu's Mansion?
I'm telling the truth.
Master can
speak to birds.
Quiet!
Master, Here he comes again.
Why is he always
suddenly lashing out at me?
It's because
what he will do in the future
might bring tremendous trouble,
and he doesn't want to
get people around him involved,
so he pushes everyone away.
I still don't get it.
What exactly does Ye
want to do?
A mere thought could foment evil.
Here you come again.
How much longer
will it take?
I'm exhausted.
We might arrive in three days.
But why are you exhausted?
You took naps
after every few hours of walking.
I doubt
you are tired.
Well,
let's say I'm not tired.
Thank you for carrying me, Master.
Not me.
It was Mr. Ye.
Ye?
Ye! Hey!
You are so kind to me.
Ye, you are too good to me.
Get off of me.
Ye is a big softy at heart.
Ye is a big softy at heart!
Why is he smiling so happily?
It's because he is not attached.
Young Lady.
Qixuan.
Qixuan, is that you?
Yes, it's me.
Qixuan,
Qing said
Baili Dongjun headed to Tianqi
to help Ye Dingzhi
rob the bride but failed
and then he disappeared.
Is that true?
Young Lady,
you sure know quickly.
That's right.
A few youngsters
tried to rob the princess consort
at the imperial wedding.
They indeed played out of their league.
Is he...
Is he all right?
It seems
you truly like him, Young Lady.
Don't worry.
From the news I received,
he has returned to Qiandong City
and been placed under house arrest
by his father, Baili Chengfeng.
Qixuan,
thank you.
give me a moment.
[I need to leave]
Young Lady.
All right?
To me,
every word you say
is an order I cannot defy,
so you don't have to ask.
Qixuan,
I'm sorry.
You thought you were careful enough
to conceal your trace.
However,
concerning our years of friendship,
do you think
you can deceive me?
You want to stop me?
Lord Wuxiang ordered
to lock Young Lady up for three years
to reflect on herself.
If you go back now,
I will pretend
nothing has happened.
Lord Wuxiang, you say?
Qixuan.
Zi Yuji,
to whom do you pledge your loyalty,
the Yue Family or Lord Wuxiang?
Young Lady, please return
and reflect on yourself.
Young Lady, go.
Qixuan, but you...
Now!
I have never thought
that one day you would draw your sword
against me.
I have
also never thought
that one day
I would point a sword at your face.
Now, put your sword down.
Let's bring Young Lady back.
I will pretend
nothing has happened.
Yuji,
we grew up together.
You know me.
I can't do this.
Yuji,
let Young Lady go
and bring me to Lord Wuxiang.
I will bear all the responsibility.
Get lost.
Qixuan,
you are right.
We grew up together.
Of course I know
you won't betray Young Lady.
But do you think
I will betray you?
I also serve Young Lady,
and you are my best friend.
Young Lady, we should be on our way.
If you keep on waiting,
the sacrifice of the White-Haired Deity
would be in vain.
Young Lady.
It's the White-Haired Deity.
Qixuan.
Young Lady, you should leave now.
Are you not leaving with us?
No.
But
you helped me.
You can't stay
in Sky's Beyond anymore.
The martial arts world is vast enough
to accommodate me.
Young Lady, no need to worry about me.
You should leave now.
Qixuan...
Please go.
♪Let me see you one last time
before you leave♪
♪Hoping♪
♪Hoping that all your dreams
will come true♪
♪My memories well up♪
♪How much love and attachment there is?♪
Take care.
♪In the end, fate refuses to show mercy♪
You too.
♪I will live and die without saying
a word of grievances♪
♪Looking forward♪
♪There is no cause and effect♪
♪There's only a thin line
between the living and the dead♪
♪Why am I afraid to close my eyes?♪
♪I can't bear♪
♪To see you alone in this world♪
♪By the window♪
Come in.
I let Young Lady go,
so I'm here to face my punishment.
Do you know
what punishment will you face?
I do.
News from Nanjue says
something has happened
at our base there.
You will go and handle it.
On your command.
Lord Wuxiang,
didn't we already plan
to abandon Nanjue's base?
Our enemies have ambushed it.
Sending our men over
equals digging our graves.
Since he can't be of use anymore,
he might as well die
as a discarded pawn.
[Yahan Temple]
Greetings, Elder Wangyou.
Elder Wangyou, this way, please.
Mr. Ye.
Elder Wangyou,
I can lodge at an inn
in the city.
Mr. Ye, are you going to live in an inn
for the coming two years?
Who owns that crop field?
Our sect owns it.
May I?
By all means.
Mr, Ye.
If so, I will build a hut
by the crop field.
Why bother?
I have owed others too much,
yet I haven't reclaimed anything.
I don't want to feel indebted anymore.
[Three months later]
Ye!
I brought you candied hawthorns
from Gusu City.
I pleaded with Master so hard
to buy them.
Master was so unwilling
when he coughed up the copper coin.
There you go.
I don't eat them.
You can have them.
Are you not eating?
If so,
I'm eating.
They are yours.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot something important.
Master says
he can't always
stay by your side.
He has a family sword technique.
Long-term practice
may help purify your mind.
Master's assigned me to teach you that.
Did you see how I did it?
Without missing a move.
That's amazing.
Are you very skilled
in wielding a sword?
Curious?
I'm going to throw these leaves
into the air.
Can you aim all the pieces?
Try me.
Here you go.
Candied hawthorns.
You call this candied hawthorns?
[Prince Jingyu's Mansion]
Her Highness is spacing out again.
Yes, she is.
She receives the most favored
of all consorts in this mansion.
Yet, she pulls a long face every day.
She is simply dull.
Sir, please wait here.
Thank you for your trouble.
Your Highness,
the imperial physician is here.
Let him in.
Prepare a handrest and a handkerchief.
Yes.
I will take your pulse, Your Highness.
What else can you diagnose?
It can only be a cold.
Your Highness,
have you often vomited
and lost your appetite recently?
Yes.
Is there any problem with that?
Your Highness,
your pulse feels like a slippery bead.
Strong and dynamic.
Quick and agile.
It's a pregnancy pulse.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
- Congratulations, Your Highness.
Pregnancy...
Pregnancy pulse?
Your Highness, please be very careful
with your body these days.
Your Highness, please don't.
Tell me.
Why does Heaven
do this to me?
Your Highness,
pregnancy is good news.
Mr. Ye, your inner evil is persistent.
Why don't you give up on practicing
Demon Deity Sword Techniques?
Elder Wangyou,
does Demon Deity Sword Techniques
trigger my inner evil?
Ye,
I didn't allow you to watch it
because this is
a sword move
one wields at the last moment.
This devastating move
is used during the final moment
to destroy everything.
Master...
Master!
If I can't leave
with her,
can I trade this lethal move
for her freedom?
Mr. Ye.
Elder Wangyou,
thank you again.
Don't worry.
I won't launch
this lethal sword move.
Because
one will only be enlightened
at the moment
they need it.
Since there is a path of living,
why walk the desperate one?
What is a path of living?
Let go.
No.
Elder Wangyou,
get rest early.
Who's there?
It has been a while, Ye Dingzhi.
You were stalking me again.
What are you doing here?
Of course, I'm here to mock you
for overplaying your hand.
That being said,
I'm also here to congratulate you
on returning from Tianqi
alive.
I just didn't think
that after this failure,
you would come and crouch
in this place.
What a wimp.
Why are you
still holding up so stubbornly?
I can't believe
that old geezer advises you to let go.
In the end,
even if he's not Prince Jingyu's man,
he's loyal to the Tianqi royals.
Not only do I not advise you to let go,
but I will also help you reclaim
what you want.
I will reclaim what I want
by myself.
You should leave.
After all, we are not the same kind.
Who is your kind, then?
In the far west,
there was once a person who was my kind.
Unfortunately,
I landed him into trouble.
I wonder
how Yun is doing now.
Hopefully,
Ruofeng can keep him safe.
A guqin score?
Did Master leave this?
Young Lady,
after waiting here for days,
he's finally playing the guqin.
Right.
It's just that he stinks.
It seems he has discovered
the score you secretly left.
Greetings, Young Master.
I knew you came here.
Master has already died,
and you are free,
so you don't have to
call me Young Master.
Master saved
our lives before.
We swore
we would serve
both Master and you for life.
However, you never summon us,
so we daren't show up.
That's why we could
only follow you in secret.
We may not be skilled in martial arts,
as long as you need us,
we will risk our lives
without hesitation.
We will risk our lives
Fine. Get up.
I summoned you
for a favor.
Please command us, Young Master.
I'm worried about someone.
Can you
sneak into Tianqi
and ask around
if she is doing well.
[Nanjue]
Why are you
here?
After this ambush,
we repaid the kindness
of Sky's Beyond
for raising us.
[Prince Jingyu's Mansion]
Butler!
Prince Langya has arrived.
Your Highness,
Prince Jingyu left for Yindu.
He's not at home.
We didn't expect that to happen.
Your Highness,
only you can help me now.
Tell me on the way.
What happens now?
The Princess Consort
is so skilled
that we can't enter the room.
Hence, we can't know
what's happening inside.
I told Ruojin about it earlier.
Wenjun, be careful.
Who are you to call me that?
Why didn't you dodge?
Couldn't Mr. Li's best disciple
dodge my palm attack?
If I take this attack,
will you be happier?
Besides, now...
Did you come here
to ask for a beating?
I was told you are pregnant,
so I came to pay a visit.
I'm not the only pregnant woman,
yet you especially visit me,
Prince Langya.
You are worried
I would go out of my mind
and kill
the child in my tummy
out of anger, aren't you?
Wenjun,
marriage
and having a child
are different.
Knowing that you haven't gotten over it,
I must pay more attention to you.
You may leave.
I'm not
as stubborn
and weak as you thought.
Will you give birth
to this child?
At least,
I won't kill it myself.
However,
if he has to leave
by fate,
I hope no one will stop it.
Scram.
Now!
Thank you, Wenjun.
What a nice brother he has.
Sorry about that.
Come in.
Second Young Lady.
Any urgent news?
Lord Wuxiang sent one over.
[Yi Wenjun is pregnant]
Yi Wenjun is pregnant?
Look how loyal she is!
You care about her so much,
yet she is bearing a child
for her beloved husband.
What a steamy night
they must've enjoyed.
This is hilarious.
Hilarious, indeed.
This score left by Master
is something else.
It hides martial techniques
within the notes.
As expected of him.
Clouds tumble in a westward gale.
Mighty protection spans the seven seas,
returning home in triumph.
By just reading the scores
for a few days,
I'm so well-enlightened.
Why am I
so intelligent?
You are shameless.
As long as I could make you smile,
why not?
What brings you here?
I came here...
Did you miss me?
I came here
to teach you martial arts skills.
So you left the score here?
That's right.
However,
I'm having some regrets now.
How so?
On my first day in Ruochuan Inn,
it was full of guests.
Only one room was left.
But today
when I left the inn,
it was empty.
Do you know why?
Someone died in the inn?
No.
It's because you stink
at playing.
Everyone couldn't bear it and fled.
The innkeeper
wanted to complain at the yamen.
By the time he and his men arrived,
the yamen was heavily guarded.
The guards
all looked
as if they were suffering
something unbearable.
Hence, the innkeeper gave up.
Do I stink that much?
This is one of the four best guqin
in the world,
Empyrean Guqin.
Wind gusts and thunder strikes
in the empyrean domain,
where a dragon lies
in a millennial vernal slumber.
As the Scholarly Deity of Western Chu
roamed the martial arts world
in a white robe
with a guqin and a sword,
countless pretty ladies
were enamored by him.
I have never seen him,
but I would love to.
Was Master really that charming
back then?
Out of 64 unparalleled courtesans
from 32 music parlors in Tianqi City,
40 of them were madly in love with him.
What do you think?
So girls
like this type of man?
A guqin
with a sword concealed inside.
The sword unsheathes
as the guqin sounds.
No lady
would not be fascinated
by such a gentleman.
All right.
For what you said,
I'm going to learn to play the guqin.
What did I say?
To make all ladies fall for you?
That's not necessary.
Only you are enough.
But...
But?
A young man playing less skillfully
with his eyes closed
can be charming too.
Strike gently.
Stupid sword skills.
Stupid man.
Today, I heard
an interesting story
happened in the imperial city of Beili.
I wonder
if you are interested, Mr. Ye.
I'm not interested.
You said you were not interested
even before listening to it.
What a heartless man.
Have you already forgotten
your past beloved
in just a few days?
I thought
you would be very interested in this.
What are you getting at?
Instead of describing it as interesting,
I would say it's good news.
Beili is truly blessed.
The Emperor begets a prince,
while the prince
begets an imperial grandson.
Generations upon generations,
the monarchy flourishes.
What does that mean?
That means
the daughter of the Shadow Sect's leader
whom you hold so dearly
and the new secondary consort
of Prince Jingyu,
Yi Wenjun,
is pregnant.
Are you insane?
I know it.
You went insane
because you were so loyal to her,
while she couldn't endure
the lonely nights
and enjoy a great time
with her real husband
to bear his child!
Shut up!
I won't!
She seduced another man
when she was already married.
And you know she's married,
but you are still hung up on her.
A couple of cheats and harlots!
Drop.
[No animals were harmed
during the filming of this drama.]
[Some animals were created
using bionic props and 3D effects.]
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪