♪Overcoming the boundary of confusion♪
♪Holding onto my life
in the face of death threats♪
♪I look into this dark night♪
♪Never once has my soul
been extinguished♪
♪With this passion♪
♪My spirit is growing
to reach full swing♪
♪Slashing the mountain
and the ocean apart♪
♪Answering the true call on a sword♪
♪I'm the chosen one
in this turbulent world♪
♪Keep my distance from the world♪
♪Who can understand my loneliness?♪
♪A single thought, looking down♪
♪Blades unsheathed,
frost flies everywhere♪
♪A belief that cuts through the world♪
♪Soaring towards the sky,
the sword reigns all♪
♪Striding across the land
with a drunken gait♪
♪I will protect the people
whenever I'm needed♪
♪Atop the summit, you and I shall
battle for the world's best♪
[Directed by Chen Zhoufei]
[Dashing Youth]
[Based on "Zhou Munan's
Juvenile Martial Arts Series"]
[from fanqienovel.com and bkneng.com]
[Episode 26]
You're protecting
a traitor's descendant.
Ye Xiaoying, are you trying to rebel?
When the traitor's descendant
broke into Tianqi City,
you didn't show up.
Now that he's injured,
you're coming one by one.
It's really interesting.
Your Highness.
Go back and tell him
that for the sake of the stability
of the imperial court,
I can go against
my former friend
or force a couple to break up.
I'm not afraid of
what the world will think of me.
But just because I can do it
doesn't mean I agree with it.
Ye Dingzhi's life and death
is my bottom line.
I don't agree to his death.
Unless
I die first.
Get lost!
Retreat.
Your Highness,
they're
your brother's men, aren't they?
Xiaoying,
am I
being annoying like this?
To be honest,
you're doing it for the greater good.
In my opinion,
there's no difference
between your brother, Prince Qing,
and the First Prince.
Though it's not pleasant to hear,
I have to tell you.
Your Highness,
why not be a dragon
if you can reach the sky?
You know
we'll assist you.
Your Highness.
You may leave now.
Yes.
Guard.
Your Highness, what can I do for you?
Go to Imperial Academy of Medicine
and find a medicine for the Princess.
A medicine
that can make a person unconscious
after falling asleep.
Yes.
Lord Wuxiang.
You're back, Your Highness.
Beique has vanished for years.
Lord Wuxiang,
you don't have to address me
as Your Highness.
There's a lot of meaning
in that statement,
Your Highness.
It seems that you
have already heard about it.
I'm sure you
have a lot to say to me.
But I don't want to hear it.
Your Highness, please
think it over here.
Wuxiang,
are you trying to rebel?
Betraying Beique
is the true rebellion,
no matter what your identity is.
I hope
you'll figure it out
in these days.
Young Lady.
Qixuan.
Is that you?
Young Lady,
sometimes, I really
don't understand you.
Are you smart or stupid?
You can just talk some sense into me.
I'm not well-educated,
and easy to fool.
Why did you try
to talk some sense into Lord Wuxiang?
If you lose the argument,
you'll be punished.
If you win,
you'll be locked up.
You're wrong.
This time, I got locked up
before I could say anything.
Are you still in the mood
to joke with me?
But I have
to come back eventually
so that I can have a clear conscience.
If so, do you feel sorry for me?
I have to find a way
to get you out of here again.
Qixuan,
you don't have to risk your life for me.
Where is that brat?
Where's that brat
enjoying himself now?
I guess
he's in Tianqi City now
to meet his seniors.
He, the liquor addict,
is probably drunk again.
[Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion]
Sir.
Where is Dongjun?
In the carriage.
But he's tied up
with the Sky Dragon Lock
by order of the Heir.
Unlock the Sky Dragon Lock now.
Yes.
Young Master,
the Marquis is waiting for you.
Dongjun,
You've suffered.
Grandfather.
This time,
your father had no choice.
I promised him
that I'd let him decide
everything
in the Mansion from now on.
Your father said he'd lock you up
until he got back.
Do you feel aggrieved?
I don't feel aggrieved at all.
I'm at the mercy of you and Father.
I have only one request.
Go ahead.
I don't want to be locked up
in the backyard
of the Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion.
I have another home
in Qiandong City.
Please lock me up there.
As for my friend,
please send him away from Qiandong City
when he recovers from his wounds.
All right.
Thank you, Grandfather.
I'm sorry for the trouble
I've caused you.
No trouble at all.
Get up.
Come on.
I know
all about you.
I don't think you did anything wrong.
If I had
the courage of youth like you,
Ye Yu
might still be alive today.
Dongjun, don't worry.
I'll take care
of everything.
I won't be like that fool, Ye Yu.
If anyone tries to hurt my family,
I won't let them go.
Grandfather.
[Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion]
Master,
I'm back.
♪The wind blows
through the window lattice♪
[Zhuanmengsheng]
♪It's raining in the martial world♪
♪And the stars are flitting
in the mist-covered waters♪
♪How many people in the world♪
♪Can know what's on your mind?♪
♪We're all friends when we're gathered♪
♪I'll ride my horse in the wind♪
♪And I'll go wherever I please♪
♪The road ahead is like a mystery♪
♪But feelings have gone far away
on the wind♪
♪It's a wonderful moment♪
♪The horse's prancing,
causing fumes of dust♪
How long
will the Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion
lock up Baili Dongjun?
This is our family affair,
so we don't have to tell you,
Mr. Sikong.
[Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion]
Mr. Sikong,
you'd better mind your own business.
If you don't leave Qiantong City today,
you won't
get the chance tomorrow.
I've heard
that the Marquis of Zhenxi
was so gallant on the battlefield
that he was feared.
Now I see
he's nothing more than that.
Baili Dongjun just
drew his sword for his buddy.
First, he didn't kill anyone,
and second, he didn't rebel.
Why put him under house arrest?
Is the meritorious Marquis of Zhenxi
afraid
of Prince Jingyu?
You impertinent brat.
Get lost!
Get lost, my foot!
I dare you to curse one more word.
I...
I'll be back
when I've become
the Spear Deity in your mouths.
[Baihua Pleasure House]
Mr. Zhao,
it's been a long time
since you've been here.
Zi,
Miss Feng
still won't come out
to play the guqin today?
Second Master Tu,
you ask me this every day,
and I feel ashamed to answer you.
Miss Feng is not in the mood
these days,
so I'm afraid you'll have
to wait a little longer.
How uninteresting.
Baihua Pleasure House
is getting less and less interesting.
Are you
Second Master Tu of Qianjin House?
Yes, I'm Tu Wan.
My young lady wants to see you.
What?
I...
Say that again.
My young lady wants to see you.
What is this called?
It's called "Nothing is impossible
with sincerity."
Everybody,
I'm happy today.
I'll pay all the bills
in the house.
Thank you, Second Master Tu.
Miss Feng.
I'm Tu Wan.
Second Master Tu, please sit down.
Have some tea.
Second Master Tu,
that's a tea leaf.
Miss, I'm sorry.
Why did you want to see me
all of a sudden?
You're the vice manager
of Qianjin House.
I seldom go out,
but I've heard a lot
about Qianjin House.
That's for sure.
We are
very rich.
If you want,
I'll buy Baihua Pleasure House
and give it to you.
That's not necessary.
I just think
that Qianjin House
is so powerful
in Tianqi City
that you should know
something that others don't know.
You want to get
some information, don't you?
Not really.
I heard
that a few days ago,
some people were galloping
in Tianqi City.
They said
it was Baili Dongjun,
a young disciple of the Academy
who traveled with Mr. Li.
He was accompanied
by a young man with a spear.
But the next day,
no one saw them again.
You want to know
what they did on this trip,
especially about the nerd
with the spear,
right?
No, I just don't see
what's so great about him.
It seems you
still can't let go of that young man.
Second Master Tu,
will you tell me?
If this secret
is spread,
it's a capital offense.
But if you ask me,
of course
I'll tell you everything.
From now on,
reserve a seat for Master Tu
when he comes to listen to music.
No need to arrive early.
Miss,
I have one more request.
Please go ahead, Second Master Tu.
After all, it's a capital offense.
I can only whisper in your ear.
How dare you!
No problem.
I am sorry to offend you.
Do you know who I am?
Miss, he's here to rob the bride.
Don't worry, he's fine.
He's just a little injured.
Please make sure
you reserve a seat for me.
What a jerk.
You came back
to rob someone else's bride, huh?
It seems that the Dragon Transformation
still needs the sea to work.
[Muyun Abode]
I'll
come back when I've become
the top martial artist in the world.
[Elder Wangyou]
Whether it works or not
depends on a single thought.
You're being too profound.
I'm not well-educated,
so I don't understand.
You're a man of wisdom.
How could you not understand?
I was thinking
that if Ye Dingzhi
ever becomes
the top martial artist in the world,
it will be many years from now.
What's the point
of him going to Tianqi City
to look for her then?
Wuchan, we have to go now.
I'm coming.
Master, don't rush me.
[Wuchan]
It's not that I want to rush you.
It's just that if we're late,
we won't be able to make it.
Are you leaving?
Well,
see you.
Let's go.
See you.
Master,
why are you walking so fast?
Wait for me.
Let's go.
Xiao Ruofeng really keeps a close eye
on Ye Dingzhi.
Not only does his trusted man guard him,
but he even sends
an old man to follow him when he leaves.
Second Young Lady,
it seems
it's not the right time
to take Ye Dingzhi away.
Send someone to follow him
and see where he's going.
We can take our time to plan.
There's nothing I want
that I can't have.
Master, I can't hold on any longer.
You can't hold on
with such a small bag?
Master, I can't bear
the thought that I'll have
to walk hundreds of li
with this bag on my back.
Are we practitioners
afraid of this?
We practitioners
can't eat this
or that,
so why must we suffer this?
Do you think I'm going to stop
after what you've said?
You're more stubborn
than that big black bull
down the hill.
If you say you're going, you're going.
Then why are you still complaining?
Can't I just express my thoughts?
Wuchan,
do you know
there's a Gusu City under that mountain
we're going to?
So what?
Can it compare to Tianqi?
I've seen a lot of fun
in Tianqi City.
Although Gusu City
is not as big as Tianqi City,
it's much more interesting
than Tianqi City.
In spring, there are flower selling
in the streets, shrimp fighting,
board jumping, and juggling.
Everything you like is there.
Besides,
candied hawthorns there
are especially good.
When we get there,
I'll buy you two skewers,
one to eat and one to watch.
What do you think?
Say no more.
Master, let's go now.
Quick!
[Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion]
Yu.
You'll have to get a hold
of yourself later.
Don't worry, Father.
I won't go too far.
Father, I'm back.
My dear!
Dear!
Dear, please talk nicely.
Tell me.
Should I
punish you with Three-inch Ash
or kill you?
Dear, please spare my life.
Didn't you say
you wouldn't go too far?
I let you attend the wedding banquet
in Tianqi City.
Did I tell you to beat up our son?
Did I tell you
to bring our son back here
and lock him up?
What's wrong with him robbing a bride?
If you hadn't robbed a bride,
would you have him now?
No.
Didn't you always say he's no good?
He's following
in his father's footsteps,
and you're not satisfied?
Now, go
and release him.
No way, Dear.
It's important to keep him locked up
for a while to help him grow up.
He's not a kid anymore.
Fine.
Then I'll let you grow up too.
Three... Three-inch Ash.
Dear, don't act rashly.
You two can settle this
between yourselves.
I'm waiting to talk to Chengfeng.
I don't want to see you fight.
I'll wait for you
in the backyard tonight.
I... I'll sleep in the barracks tonight.
Fine.
Then you'll
stay in the barracks
for the rest of your life.
It really freaked me out.
Father, why didn't you do something?
She almost
killed your son just now.
Dongjun's temper
is all because she's spoiled him.
And me, too.
Regarding the bride snatching
in Tianqi City,
is the man Dongjun helped
really a descendant of Ye?
I've spoken to Prince Langya in private.
His identity is confirmed.
He's indeed
the little Yun who escaped
from the extermination of the Ye family.
He's changed his name now.
He's called Ye Dingzhi.
Ye Dingzhi.
What a good name.
I didn't expect Ye to
have a descendant
after he passed away
for so long.
Yes.
Heaven knows what's in store for us.
Is he safe now?
Prince Langya said
he had sent him
out of Tianqi in secret
and promised me to keep him safe.
The words of the imperial family
are not to be fully trusted.
I think we need
to get someone to protect him in secret.
After all, we couldn't
save Ye back then.
At least, we need
to protect his lineage now.
I understand.
However,
I tell myself
that Xiao Ruofeng
is trustworthy.
He can be trusted,
but what about Xiao Ruojin?
Father, as you said,
he's a member of the imperial family.
Prince Langya is a man of great talent
and virtue.
But usually, such people
don't wish to be an emperor.
Only someone like Prince Jingyu
is eager to seize power.
We must be careful.
Yes.
Shouldn't we
go and check him out?
It's the first time I've seen Dongjun
stay in one place for so long.
Forget it.
I don't think he wants to see me.
If you didn't do anything,
he and Yun would be dead.
You
should at least tell them,
let them know.
They're kids.
They won't listen.
Kids?
I think I heard someone say
he's not a kid anymore.
You...
Wuchan,
do you remember everything
I just told you?
I don't listen to a turtle chanting.
I'm a turtle
and you're a little turtle.
Master, you don't even have a map.
If we just walk like this,
can we make it to Gusu City?
No rush. We've got
some important things to do.
It's him.
Isn't he the one
who's been living in our yard
for a few days?
I heard
that he's going to be killed
if he's caught.
What a coincidence
that you're here too, Mr. Ye.
Since we've crossed paths,
let's travel together.
Crossed paths?
That's a nice way of putting it.
Elder Wangyou, I've heard that
you're a profound practitioner
who doesn't care about worldly affairs.
When did you
become the accomplice
of the imperial family of Beli
and start stalking me?
You've been stalking me
all the way here.
So it's time to stop, isn't it?
Mr. Ye, that's not true.
It's because
I don't like Tianqi City
that I'm leaving.
It's just that the journey is boring
and I don't know martial arts,
so I'd like
to travel with you.
I hope you
can take care of us.
Master,
you didn't say
we were going to traveling with him.
Shut it.
But why should I
travel with you?
That's scary.
How interesting.
The master doesn't know martial arts,
but his disciple
is a future martial expert.
Mr. Ye, you must be joking.
I don't need any companions.
I'll walk
my own path.
Mr. Ye, be patient.
How dare you say
you don't know martial arts?
Mr. Ye,
I really don't know martial arts.
I can only dodge, run
and...
What else?
As expected.
Bore Bell of Heart, drop.
I can trap people.
Master.
Mr. Ye,
you'd better travel with me.
Why
is this happening?
Demon Deity Sword Techniques
are the ways of the demon after all.
Before, you had a firm heart,
so there was no harm.
But now you can't get
what you desire,
so your mind is unstable.
If your mind is unstable
and the barrier is broken,
the demonic thoughts
will penetrate your body
and this is the result.
That's why I insist
on traveling with you.
It's only for two years.
After two years,
your mind will be stable
and you won't be afraid
of the demonic power's repercussions.
Why are you helping me?
Aren't we practitioners
supposed to help people in need?
I meet you
when you happen to be in trouble,
so I help you.
What reason do I need?
To be honest,
I have no destination in mind
adn don't know where I'm headed.
I thought
I could take her away from Tianqi
and we could go back to Nanjue together.
I have a hut there,
surrounded by bamboo,
mountains
and a river.
We'll live
a carefree life together.
There's a mountain outside of Gusu City.
It's
perfect for hermits like us.
That's where
I'm going.
Gusu City is good,
and so is the mountain.
Since you
don't know where you're going,
why don't you
follow me there?
It's far away from Tianqi City
and no one will disturb you.
It's only for two years, right?
Two years, tops.
After two years,
my Demon Deity Sword Techniques
won't have any more repercussions?
Not only will it not have repercussions,
but it will also advance
to a higher level.
All right.
Master,
so you're really good.
I can't believe
you made a big bell out of no where.
Master, can you make
a candied hawthorn skewer
out of no where?
No.
Qing,
you're back.
Yes,
I am.
But why are you here?
I...
I heard them say
you were going to give up
on the restoration.
You lied to me.
You've betrayed us.
Qing,
I...
Yao,
you're so heartless.
Have you forgotten
the death of Mother?
I haven't.
It's because
I saw the death of Mother
and experienced
the pain of separation
that I don't want this
to happen to anyone else.
War
requires countless innocent lives
to pay for it.
Our country is history.
Why don't
we rebuild a new home?
It's only because
you're in love with Baili Dongjun.
You're doing it
for your own selfish reasons.
Don't make yourself
sound so great.
Yes.
I am in love with Baili Dongjun,
but that has nothing to do
with my decision.
You expect me to believe that?
In your heart, is love,
such a vague feeling,
worth trusting with your life?
Yue Yao,
stop with the jokes.
To him, you're a liar.
You're just
an enemy of his nation.
Of course our relationship
is worth trusting with our lives.
Qing,
that's because
you haven't encountered it yet.
So what if it's worth trusting
with your life?
In the end, there's nothing
you can do about it.
What did you say?
Baili Dongjun
helped his good friend, Ye Dingzhi,
to rob his bride.
But they failed in the end,
and his whereabouts are unknown.
Perhaps he's already dead.
Dongjun.
No.
If only I had someone
to keep me company.
Why don't I play the guqin
Master left me first?
What? Can't you stand it anymore?
You sound like
you just woke up.
Sir,
you're here to laugh at me, aren't you?
I'm curious
to see you accepting your punishment
without saying a word
and staying here.
Have you learned your lesson
or are you trying to challenge me?
Now it seems neither.
You're just hiding out here
to slack off.
Who's slacking?
I've been practicing
my guqin and sword.
If you're so capable, come in
and let's have a fight.
Who wants to fight with you?
I'm here to ask you
if you've thought
about why you've been locked up.
Because I was robbing a bride
for a friend of mine,
and the one I was robbing from
was the Prince of Tianqi City.
My surname is Baili.
I can't just think for myself.
I have
the entire Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion
behind me.
Rubbish!
I think what you learned from Mr. Li
has been for nothing.
Yun is your childhood friend,
and your friend for life.
when you grow up.
It's not wrong for you
to help your buddy
to rob his bride.
Even if the entire
Marquis of Zhenxi's Mansion
is implicated, as you said,
you're still not wrong.
If we live in the world
just for fame and fortune,
and have no regard for integrity,
then what kind of men are we?
What's wrong with you
is that you overestimated yourself.
Overestimating yourself
is when you do
something you can't yet do
and can't bear
the consequences of your failure.
However,
you're not bad for being my son.
I also robbed a bride before
when I was young.
Back then, I wanted
to marry your mother,
but her father refused
because he had already betrothed her
to the eldest son
of the Xu family in Lingnan.
So on their wedding day,
I went to rob the bribe.
Your grandfather
didn't support me either.
Your grandfather had an army
of thousands of soldiers,
but he let me rob the bride
by myself with a sword.
But that's fine.
From the eldest son of the Xu family,
to the head of the Xu family,
to the Xu family's altar,
they all fell under my sword.
I was able to take your mother
not only because we were in love,
but also because
I am capable of doing so.
Do you think
you are competent?
That's the real reason
why I've grounded you here.
You also know
that today's Emperor Tai'an
is no longer
the same buddy who fought
alongside your grandfather
and General Ye Yu.
The righteousness of the past
can't stand up
to a heart hardened by power.
That's why your grandfather didn't want
you to get involved
in this complicated matter.
But since you chose to get involved,
you must be prepared.
There's no sentiment
in the imperial court,
but we have to have it.
You can leave here anytime you want.
But...
How?
Tell these soldiers outside the door
you're ready.
There's only one chance.
I'm not a man of leisure.
I don't have time to come here
and talk to you all the time.
Anyway, remember,
if you want to get out early,
have someone pass me a message.
I expect
to see
what you're truly capable of
when you come to me.
Sir.
You brat, stop calling me that.
I'm your father.
Baili Chengfeng.
You brat, I...
Father!
Thank you.
Thank you so much
for saying that to me.
Enough, you brat.
Keep practicing.
He just likes to talk tough.
[No animals were harmed
during the filming of this drama.]
[Some animals were created
using bionic props and 3D effects.]
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪