♪Overcoming the boundary of confusion♪
♪Holding onto my life
in the face of death threats♪
♪I look into this dark night♪
♪Never once has my soul
been extinguished♪
♪With this passion♪
♪My spirit is growing
to reach full swing♪
♪Slashing the mountain
and the ocean apart♪
♪Answering the true call on a sword♪
♪I'm the chosen one
in this turbulent world♪
♪Keep my distance from the world♪
♪Who can understand my loneliness?♪
♪A single thought, looking down♪
♪Blades unsheathed,
frost flies everywhere♪
♪A belief that cuts through the world♪
♪Soaring towards the sky,
the sword reigns all♪
♪Striding across the land
with a drunken gait♪
♪I will protect the people
whenever I'm needed♪
♪Atop the summit, you and I shall
battle for the world's best♪
[Directed by Chen Zhoufei]
[Dashing Youth]
[Based on "Zhou Munan's
Juvenile Martial Arts Series"]
[from fanqienovel.com and bkneng.com]
[Episode 36]
- Tianqi City is famous for
- Greetings, honored guests.
- the courtesan and Lord Vermilion Bird.
- Please, this way to your seats.
He's a total playboy.
Precisely.
The courtesan traveled a thousand li
just to meet him.
What a great love story.
Come.
Sir, your liquor is here.
It's Uncle Sikong.
Mister, give me some paper and a brush.
I need an envelope too.
All right.
What are you up to?
I'm going to write to Changfeng.
Changfeng?
Is your uncle,
the so-called Lord Vermilion Bird,
named Sikong Changfeng?
Senior, have you heard
of his name before?
Seems like that brat
has made a name for himself.
Sir, please.
[Changfeng]
During my travel,
I heard that you won
your beloved's heart.
Congratulations.
I shall return soon.
No need to hurry
with the wedding banquet.
You have to wait for me.
Add something for me.
Tell him to wait for me too.
First Senior, are you going
to join in the fun as well?
We did encounter each other
in an abandoned temple.
Write it this way.
There's a scholar who,
in pursuit of academic success,
hopes to ask for a few cups
of celebration liquor.
All right.
I'm just worried
that he might be too impatient
and hold the wedding banquet
in an instant.
I've never attended the wedding banquet
of a junior yet.
Yun.
I couldn't make it to Yun's wedding.
I can't afford
to miss out on Changfeng's wedding now.
Let's head back
when you've recovered.
Yao,
sorry for the trouble these few days.
Let's rent a boat
and depart this afternoon.
All right.
[Dongji Port]
Be careful.
Guys, everything is ready.
We may depart now.
Junior,
I will stop here.
Now that we're parting ways,
I don't know when we'll meet again.
First Senior,
thank you for everything
you've done for us.
Take care.
Uncle Junyu, take care.
Stop looking.
May you still be
the same old vigorous Baili Dongjun
when you return.
♪The wind
blows through the window lattice♪
♪It's raining in the martial world♪
♪And the stars are flitting
in the mist-covered waters♪
♪How many people in the world♪
♪Can know what's on your mind?♪
♪We're all friends when we're gathered♪
Yao.
♪I'll ride my horse in the wind♪
I'm fine.
♪And I'll go wherever I please♪
I was just reminded of Father.
♪The road ahead is like a mystery♪
♪But feelings have gone far away
on the wind♪
Dongjun.
♪It's a wonderful moment♪
I was separated from
my parents since young.
My impressions of my father
are very blurry.
I only remember
that during festive occasions,
when I wanted to admire
the lanterns in the streets,
Father and I disguised ourselves
as commoners
and blended in with the people
during the lantern party.
He would carry me on his shoulders.
♪One's childhood name was called upon♪
His shoulders were broad.
They were warm.
♪Drinking under the moon alone♪
♪Embracing one's joy and sorrow♪
♪It takes courage to be alone♪
My reunion with my father
was too short-lived.
♪And I'll go wherever I please♪
It was just like a dream.
♪The road ahead is like a mystery♪
Say,
had I opened the door earlier...
♪But feelings have gone far away
on the wind♪
could I have persuaded
my father to stop?
Yao.
♪The horse's prancing,
causing fumes of dust♪
I'm sorry.
I should have considered
your feelings.
♪Wait for me
to reminisce about the past♪
I suppose all of us
will blame ourselves.
However...
♪But the code of chivalry
demands travelling♪
We still have to move on eventually.
♪Hiding one's old flame in one's heart♪
♪Swallowing the farewell♪
♪Facing the martial world with no rest♪
♪Leaving one's sigh in a dream♪
We've arrived.
Yao, look.
A dazzling star has risen
in the eastern sky.
It's Alkaid.
That's Sovereign Lord.
Alkaid at the east
and Sovereign Lord at the west.
The undercurrent has stopped.
Penglai Island,
I'm finally here.
This feels sentimental.
Elder Mo Yi.
Long time no see.
You're still
as dashing as always.
Elder,
just look at you.
You're already in your forties.
Even so, you still
look like a teenager.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Why don't you ask
your master that question?
He's already over 100 years old.
Even so, he still looks like a teenager.
Isn't he embarrassed?
Kid, you're not kind at all.
It's no wonder
you've lost all of your powers.
Elder, you do live up
to your title as a deity.
You could tell at first glance.
How did you lose your powers?
It's a sad story.
Let's not bring it up.
Youthful still,
what's the cause for such sorrow?
Baili,
what was the internal strength technique
you practiced?
The Autumn Water Technique.
When autumn floods swell,
rivers pour into the Yellow River,
and its waters become so vast that
making it impossible
to distinguish cattle from horses
on the banks.
That's an impressive
internal strength technique indeed.
But it's not enough.
Elder, please enlighten me.
The Scholarly Deity invented
the Autumn Water Technique
after being inspired
by the water in autumn he witnessed.
But that was
his enlightenment after all.
No matter how good you are at it,
you'll never be as good as
the Scholarly Deity.
Moreover,
"When autumn floods swell,
rivers pour into the Yellow River."
is not good enough.
Come with me.
Where's your master?
He went on a journey.
I don't know when he'll return.
I'm afraid
it'll be difficult for him to return.
Elder, what do you mean?
Your master went to the north.
He went to the far northern land.
Why did Master go there?
Why do you think I'm here, then?
Elder,
I've lost all of my powers.
You should stop talking
in riddles.
You only lost your powers,
not your brain.
There is always
something greater beyond.
The way of the martial arts
is limitless.
Therefore, what you can achieve
is also limitless.
The stronger you are,
the heavier your responsibilities are.
The icy plains in the north,
the desert in the west,
the boundless sea to the east,
and the endless mountains to the south,
these four directions are
guarded by four saints.
One day,
you'll guard one of them too.
Me?
But that's all in the future.
Once you go beyond the stone monument,
you can see
a spectacular view.
[Boundless Sky]
Boundless Sky?
My predecessor wrote
Bound Sky alone.
But in my opinion,
it's only bound
because there's an end to our vision.
The sky is boundless.
Therefore, I changed it
to Boundless Sky.
Over there,
it's a different world.
Go.
This place is...
According to
A Record of Mountains and Seas,
at the end of the sky
lies a bottomless cliff.
The swirling clouds and mist
gather there,
yet they flow like seawater.
The rapid flow causes sparks,
dyeing the sky with a crimson shade.
Another ancient manual,
Heavenly Wind Chronicles,
states that at the end of the sky,
whenever a prosperous era is dawning,
deities will come
and Buddhas will do their prayers.
It's a place where deities live.
I assume the authors
must've visited this place before.
It's because what they said
was true.
What's behind the clouds and mist?
I don't know either.
Maybe you'll find deities
and Buddhas there.
Maybe you'll find out
that it's only a fantasy.
Or, maybe
you'll reach the end of the sky.
It's not what
we can seek out.
Now, do you understand why I said
the Autumn Water Technique
wasn't good enough?
"Sea of clouds
cascading from above."
That sentence alone
reminds me of the magnificent view
where thousands of horses
tread upon the plains.
Even if this were an endless sea,
boundless and stretching far and wide,
with the fastest ship
traversing a thousand li each day
for years,
it would still be impossible
to explore the entire realm of clouds.
The world is full of vibrant
and wondrous experiences,
with countless sights
and things yet unseen.
That's why you said
"Rivers pour into the Yellow River"
wasn't enough.
Indeed.
When the autumn waters come,
the River Deity may be proud.
Yet before the vast sea,
he can only lament
his own insignificance.
Not to mention the sea of clouds
we're looking at right now.
But in the presence
of such a magnificent view,
nothing matters that much.
With your internal strength gone,
just train anew.
It's nothing major.
You can always turn back
as long as you're not
at the end of the road.
You can always turn back
as long as you're not
at the end of the road.
The Scholarly Deity invented
the Autumn Water Technique,
a profound internal strength technique,
after witnessing the autumn rain
flowing into the Yellow River.
Now, you've witnessed
a magnificent sight as well.
Don't you think it's time for you
to invent another technique
that's more profound than his?
Are you saying that one can invent
an internal strength technique
by admiring this view alone?
It's more than just
a view you're admiring here.
There's also the Way of Heaven.
For the days to come,
you can ponder upon
your internal strength
behind the stone monument.
Elder,
are you serious?
Of course.
All things have their principles.
Now, you can train in the presence
of the Way of Heaven.
Not everyone
gets an opportunity like this.
You should cherish it.
Elder Mo Yi.
What were you doing?
I was observing the sea.
The tide rises and falls,
just like life.
When my father was young,
he was gentle and polite.
My sister grew up together with me.
She was once naive and carefree.
Maybe it's because
our lifespan is too long.
As we continue on our path,
we get distracted and confused.
When we live as humans,
we might be searching
for what we desire all the time.
Even if you don't know what you desire,
that's fine.
However, you must know
what you do not desire.
Once you cast away
the things you do not desire,
everything will become
clearer.
Elder, why did you
suddenly turn into
a scholar of philosophy?
I'm not used to it.
I'm getting older.
I can't stop myself
from sharing my experience with them
when I see youngsters I like.
Just let it go.
Yun?
Yun!
Let it go.
Ye Dingzhi?
Ye Dingzhi!
Ye Dingzhi.
You're finally here.
You told me to come, didn't you?
Speak. What's the matter?
Release me.
Can you please release me?
Ye Dingzhi!
If not, you should kill me!
Do you think I intend to spare you?
Everyone who participated in the plan
has been killed by me.
To protect you, Zhong Feili said
that you had nothing to do with the plan
before his death.
He took me for a fool.
If so, why are you...
It's because
I need a puppet.
More importantly,
I realize
that you're suffering from this.
You had fun
when you played hard-to-get, right?
If so, you should enjoy this process.
Enjoy the fun.
Ye Dingzhi!
Ye Dingzhi, come back!
Come back! Release me!
Come back!
Ye Dingzhi!
I am the ex-Left Guardian
of Sky's Beyond,
Zi Yuji, Marquis Purple Robe.
I am the ex-Right Guardian
of Sky's Beyond,
Mo Qixuan, the White-Haired Deity.
We implore to be allowed
to return to the sect.
Don't you guys fear me?
I was supposed to be dead.
You were the one who saved my life.
I have nothing to fear
even if you wish to take my life!
I've never saved you before.
After Qixuan and I betrayed
our former sect,
we escaped to that bamboo forest
and found that shack.
We found this
in the shack.
Back then, I was seriously wounded.
I only managed to survive
thanks to your medicine.
And,
I also received the help
of Miss Yan Lingxia.
Although you had no idea,
Qixuan and I
were still indebted to you.
And?
And,
you're strong enough.
Only those who are strong
can lead us out of these icy plains.
We only believe
in the power of one's sword.
You two wanted
to return to the sect, right?
Why are you two still here?
Thank you, sect leader.
It's all just a game.
If one isn't strong enough,
they'll end up as pawns.
That's why my father was
accused of treason
and his entire clan was executed.
That's why my wife
was taken away on numerous occasions.
I could never live in peace!
From now on,
I no longer want to be a pawn.
I will be the chess player
who controls the pawns.
A game.
A pawn.
I'm sure you're not doing this
of your own accord.
Even if I'm stuck in the game,
I'll finish it my own way!
No.
I won't let you go.
Why are you doing this?
If you don't let go,
your inner demon
will keep pestering you.
You'll never get to move on
or be released from this torment
as long as it pesters you.
I've told you I won't let go.
It's already been so long.
You keep thinking about that day.
But that day has already happened.
Everything is already set in stone!
What's the point in holding on?
Who said everything
has been set in stone?
It's not over
as long as I think the path
I'm treading upon
isn't over yet!
But my path has already ended.
I chose this path
of my own accord.
You should stop dwelling on it.
It's pointless.
Just give up.
No.
Why would you tell me to give up
if giving up doesn't make a difference?
Yun, come back.
Farewell.
Yun!
Come back!
You're not allowed to leave!
Not bad at all.
[One year later]
Elder Mo Yi?
How did it go?
For one year,
my dantian was empty.
But today,
internal strength
is gushing out of my body.
My body is filled
with internal strength.
You've done visualization training
for one year.
It's not strange for you
to achieve this feat.
Have you straightened out your thoughts?
I'm going to head back
and bring him here.
What if he doesn't agree
to leave with you?
If so, I'll reason with him.
I'll persuade him
and bring him back.
Good. At least you have an aspiration.
Elder Mo Yi,
why did it sound like
you were mocking me?
However,
there's no rush.
Compared to finding him,
I think I prefer
to take a bath first.
This is exhilarating!
Elder Mo Yi, you said
the autumn rain isn't satisfying.
Now, even the sea of cloud
isn't satisfying for me.
What's satisfying for you, then?
The sky!
Only the vast sky will satisfy me.
My internal strength technique,
is called
Hanging Sky.
Come.
Who said you could
grow a mustache?
Yao,
when I went beyond the stone monument,
I lost the concept of time.
It's already been over a year,
yet it feels like
it's only been a few days.
Only my mustache
can tell the truth.
But I did gain something out of it.
I invented my
internal strength technique.
It's called Hanging Sky.
Isn't it great?
Yeah, yeah.
It would be better
if you shave
your mustache.
Don't move.
If not, I might cut your face
by accident.
♪Cold breeze ceases♪
♪Sparrows dart through the woods
in faint chirping♪
♪Mist covering someone's eyes♪
♪Like a dream yet to awaken♪
♪It's supposed to be marvelous scenes♪
♪Traveling alone only to witness♪
All done.
♪The changes of the world♪
♪Until a red maple leaf♪
♪Lingers in the past♪
♪That reminds people of romance♪
♪The joy and sorrow are like ephemerals♪
♪Silently passing by each other♪
♪With a glimpse♪
♪A sudden wind tugged
at the heartstrings♪
♪It's hard to tell what I see
and what I feel♪
♪It's like coveting
the moon in the mirror♪
♪The frost in my palm♪
♪Looking for a pair of eyes♪
♪Acting vigorously♪
♪Knowing that the time can be slow♪
♪It's hard to let go of love♪
♪It's like a thousand knots in my heart♪
♪When the moon is bright♪
♪You'll come as promised♪
That brat Baili Dongjun,
actually
entered the Roaming Mystical Phase
for a second just now.
That was interesting.
It's a shame
that it only lasted for an instant.
Elder Mo Yi,
it's time for us to leave.
Once I bring Ye Dingzhi
back from Sky's Beyond,
I'll invite you to Xueyue City
to try the liquor I brew.
See you then.
I hope we won't see each other again.
People say that deities
transcend emotions and feelings.
Elder, you're heartless indeed.
If you do see me again,
you'll regret
what you said today.
Initially,
I was worried as Ye Dingzhi
had absorbed all
of your internal strength.
I never expected you
to recover your powers this soon.
And, you became stronger.
But the thing I'm happiest about
is that you look as vigorous as always.
Senior, what about you?
How have you been
for the past two years?
It's been great
and not that great.
What do you mean?
It's a long story.
Let's talk inside.
Is that guy outside Baili Dongjun?
If so, I'll take
a good look at him later.
Luoxia.
I went to Riverside Manor
with your token.
I've become your master's disciple too.
From now on,
you cannot call me Luoxia.
You have to call me Junior
according to seniority.
Luoxia,
you should stop teasing me.
It's fun to tease you.
Mr. Baili, I've long heard of your name.
I never expected
my name to be that famous
in the martial world
even though
I've been away for two years.
I'm ashamed.
It's not about your name, you know?
It's about...
Luoxia!
Master.
Have a seat.
Senior, what did you mean by that?
Did you encounter any trouble?
It's the guy
that you wish to avoid the most.
Was it Ye Dingzhi?
That's right.
Half a year ago,
a sudden force emerged
from the northwest of Beili.
They unified all the sects
on the icy plains.
They were unpredictable and ruthless.
People call them the demonic sect.
They kept harassing
the borders of Beili.
Therefore,
Beili sent out
some expert martial artists
to fend them off.
None of them were their match.
As we have no idea
about their background,
we dare not act recklessly.
Until last month,
three veterans
of the martial arts world
infiltrated the demonic sect.
They intended to take down
the sect leader of the demonic sect
to leave them leaderless.
They were prepared
to sacrifice their lives
to achieve their goal.
But no one expected them to...
None of them died.
All of them came back alive.
Before the martial arts world
of Beili could celebrate the occasion,
they realized
that these three veterans
had lost all of their powers
even though they were still alive.
They said the person
who did this to them
was the demonic sect's leader.
His name
was Ye Dingzhi.
Dongjun, what's on your mind?
I'm thinking about Yun.
I'll bring him back.
[No animals were harmed
during the filming of this drama.]
[Some animals were created
using bionic props and 3D effects.]
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪