♫  Overcoming self-doubt and finding purpose  ♫
♫  Enduring the trials of life and death  ♫
♫  As I gaze into the dark night  ♫
♫  My spirit has not been broken  ♫
♫  And unleash this passion  ♫
♫  My spirit will only grow stronger  ♫
♫  Splitting mountains and parting seas  ♫
♫  Answering the sword's call and entering the Martial World  ♫
♫  I'm the chosen one, fate in this turbulent world  ♫
♫  Keeping my distance from the world  ♫
♫  Who can understand my loneliness?  ♫
♫  A single thought, gazing down  ♫
♫  With swords drawn, frost flies through the air  ♫
♫  With faith that conquers the world with one strike  ♫
♫  Soaring through the sky, the sword reigns everywhere  ♫
♫  Breaking through the waves, dancing drunkenly everywhere  ♫
♫  Protecting the people, no matter the cost  ♫
♫  Atop the peak, you and I shall battle all out  ♫
Baili Dongjun.
Let's talk.
We haven't met in over a year and you walk away when you see me.
Because you're not worth my time.
Because I stopped you and your best friend from snatching the bride.
Why are you silent?
Baili Dongjun, tell me. Am I right?
Yes. Because I can't stand what you have done.
I rushed from Qiandong City to Tianqi not just for martial arts skills,
but also to learn about principles.
Jixia Academy is the best academy.
Among all the principles I have learned, none of them says power can trump a person's will.
However, my senior allowed that to happen.
I have to wake up early tomorrow morning.
Please excuse me, Senior.
If that's the case, why didn't you ask your senior if there is a principle
that teaches one to trump another's will with their power?
Your senior will tell you that kind of principle never existed.
Never in the past, present, or future.
Yes, I thought about that afterward.
If you hadn't interfered, perhaps Brother Yun could have gone further.
But he also might have lost his life.
Nevertheless, to me, my senior will stop such unfairness from happening.
He definitely will.
Right.
About this, your senior is...
very disappointed in himself.
Dongjun, I know you may never believe in me anymore.
But there is something I must tell you now.
Your grandfather will not die this time.
Not on the journey or in Tianqi
unless I die first.
Dongjun.
Yao'er, you are here.
How is it?
Are you not coming with us?
My identity is sensitive.
I'm afraid my appearance would strengthen the rumors of the Marquis's treason.
You have a point.
I will come to you once everything is over.
It's just that your trip might be dangerous.
Dongjun, are you ready?
Some Shadow Guards of profound phase, along with Ruofeng's guards,
will protect my grandfather.
I do blame Ruofeng for what happened to Brother Yun,
but I won't question any promise he makes to me.
Pofeng Army of the Baili Family bids farewell to Your Lordship!
Farewell, Your Lordship!
Prince Langya, let's depart.
Is something wrong with that old man? He accepted this order.
Su Muyu.
Hey, Blockhead Su!
I'm doubting whether you have a heart or not.
We are going to kill Baili Luochen,
the well-known Marquis Zhenxi whom that old man admires.
And we are going to kill him. Don't you feel excited?
- You are wrong.
- Why?
On the list, aside from Baili Luochen...
there's also Xiao Ruofeng.
How boring.
You are my best friend, but working with you is simply no fun.
Have you decided on a plan of action?
Since you put it that way, it means you did.
Xiao Ruofeng is the key to our mission.
We will arrange for twenty killers from the Su Family
to break the horse formation and wipe out the vulnerable Jinwu Guards.
While I go ahead and tie down Xiao Ruofeng,
you will charge the carriage and kill Baili Luochen.
Lastly, both of us join hands to kill Xiao Ruofeng.
A simple and clean kill.
It can be done in an hour.
This is the biggest order Dark River has had in nearly 30 years,
but you make it sound so easy.
Killing has always been easy, no?
It's you.
Senior, who are they?
They are Dark River, the most mysterious assassin organization.
So you are Prince Langya?
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Su Zhe.
Don't be nervous.
I didn't come here to kill.
Dark River is blocking our way but doesn't plan to kill us?
You must be Mu Nuan, right?
What a nice face.
What about yours? Why do you hide it?
I'm already old.
Unlike you. Many years have passed and you still look so lovely.
Have you been doing well all these years?
None of your business.
It seems you've had a great time.
Good to know that.
We were the only two survivors in the battle back then.
I didn't expect to meet you here today.
Since when did you start speaking so pompously?
I beg your pardon.
I would like you to see the countenance of the Marquis.
Forget about that.
Why don't you see the countenance of Mister Li?
Master, you...
Long time no see.
Old friend Su Zhe, we also haven't seen each other in quite some time, right?
Oh, it's Mister Li.
It has been a long time.
This man is the world's top martial artist, Li Changsheng?
If I kill him, I can take his place.
If so, you will be the world's top idiot.
Do you still want to see the countenance of the Marquis?
I don't think so.
I have seen what I should see.
Changhe, Muyu, let's go.
- Master, you—
- We will catch up after reaching Tianqi.
Let's go.
Send a message to the first client.
"Mission failed because of Li Changsheng."
Send a message to the second client.
"Mission accomplished because of Li Changsheng."
How was it?
How do you feel when meeting an old acquaintance after so many years?
What I went through still gives me the jitters.
That man named Su Zhe was once the top martial artist of the Su Family.
I know. He's the Conical Hat Ghost.
But don't worry. You are no longer part of Dark River
so even if it's the Conical Hat Ghost, they can't catch you.
Since he recognized you he probably figured out that we used a mask.
Fortunately Su Leng's imitation was convincing.
It was worth my effort to tell you about Master the whole night.
I do blame Senior because of Brother Yun, but I won't question any promise he makes to me.
The thing is...
What is it?
I have my plan. Come in.
Greetings, Mr. Baili.
This is Su Leng, one of Grandfather's bodyguards.
His father went on an expedition with Grandfather.
His father was the best spy in the army.
- A spy?
- They are good at impersonation.
They can convincingly play a peasant or a merchant.
This older sister is adept at the Art of Disguise.
She creates face masks that are so flawless that they can pass as real.
Sister, I would like to ask you to create a face mask for me.
Who would you like to be disguised as?
Him.
Who is he?
This is an exact duplicate of my drawing.
Dark River is prudent. They wouldn't dare take the risk.
Old Su.
What brings you here from the main hall?
Something urgent of course.
Something urgent?
What's it about?
After you two left, Soul Reaper Hall received its new orders.
New orders?
One order is to kill Baili Luochen, while the other one is to save him.
Old Su, Dark River never accepts orders with conflicting interests.
Once we accept a client, no matter how hefty the price the second client offers,
we won't renege.
What changed that old man's mind to engage in such unethical business?
First, killing Baili Luochen is no easy task.
Of course that's not the most important thing.
Most importantly, the second client has a more dignified identity.
Your Majesty.
How was it?
It succeeded.
Very well.
But something went wrong.
What went wrong?
Mister Li showed up again.
As long as the second client is determined enough,
the first client will wind up dead.
Li Changsheng?
Why is Li Changsheng back?
Even so, why is he with Baili Luochen?
Why are they all in my way?
Just why? Why?
Your Highness, please calm down.
Calm down? How can I stay calm?
Your Highness, I have an idea.
Then say it straight away.
His Majesty is wary of Li Changsheng.
This time he showed up together with Baili Luochen.
Isn't that a chance for us to take care of them in one fell swoop?
You are so clever.
I'm just easing your burden.
Ease my burden, my foot!
Your Highness.
Do you know who Li Changsheng is?
To take care of them in one fell swoop, you say?
Even if all the experts in the palace and the State Preceptor join forces, they are no match for him.
And you want me to kill him?
Do you want to get killed? Or do you want me to get killed?
- Get lost!
- Yes, Your Highness.
Top Leader thinks there's no harm in taking money from a dying person.
Li Changsheng?
Didn't he claim he wouldn't return to Tianqi City?
I don't believe it was him.
Look into this.
Yes.
Dongjun, I need to return to the palace and report for duty.
You check in at a relay station first.
I mustn't be seen with you, so I can't come this time.
All right.
Well, Censor Zhang... You keep pacing back and forth, I'm getting dizzy.
What's the point of wringing your hands?
Just take whatever comes at you.
Oh, my. You are actually in a mood to drink even now.
Censor Zhang, how could you say that?
This is Diaolou Tavern.
Since you're here, isn't it a waste if you don't taste the nice brew?
Come on and drink.
His Majesty ordered the Imperial Censorate to send someone to interrogate the Marquis Zhenxi.
How about you go?
This...
That won't do.
I can have a drink here. But I can't do the interrogation.
What good are you?
I thought you had gotten used to the fact that I'm an idler in the Imperial Censorate.
Censor Zhang, I have had enough liquor today.
I will leave you alone here with your troubles.
- Well, I...
- You!
I shall take my leave.
Goodbye.
This is a nice brew.
Luckily, I didn't drink much today. Otherwise...
I would be done for if my dear found me reeking of liquor.
No sooner had I stepped out of Diaolou Tavern than I entered the Baihua Hall.
I sure have enjoyed both brew and beauties today.
However, I have an uninvited guest.
Censor Hu, cheers.
I have seen you before.
On the wanted list.
Censor Hu, you are funny.
Do you really think I'm being funny with you?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is...
my sword is faster.
Yes, it's funny.
General Ye was my father's acquaintance.
How could I arrest his son?
That's impossible. Not a chance.
My friend, how can I help you?
I have heard a lot about you, Censor Hu.
I came here with a favor to ask of you.
I'm afraid I can't help you with that.
You haven't even heard what it is.
The Marquis Zhenxi is now a sensitive matter.
I still want to slouch in the Imperial Censorate for some more years.
Censor Hu, are you really that kind of person?
Why not?
I am.
I have a good friend named Baili Dongjun.
He is the grandson of the Marquis Zhenxi, Baili Luochen.
I know.
I suppose you know his name
not because he is Baili Luochen's grandson.
Instead, it's because of his Seven Starry Nights
winning Qiulubai in Diaolou Tavern, right?
What are you getting at? Just speak.
He's here.
Don't you want to have a few drinks with him?
Well people, to hide their true intention to help,
always look for some indecent excuses.
Marquis, someone seeks an audience.
Bring him in.
Greetings, Marquis.
Did you steal this uniform?
Dongjun, don't be rude. This is Censor Hu Bufei.
Three generations in his family have been in service.
They are the pillars of the nation.
Marquis, that sounds rather ironic though.
Oh, it's the Censor.
Why? Are you going to interrogate us on our turf?
Well, I... I wouldn't dare.
I heard that the genius brewmaster
who defeated Qiulubai with his Seven Starry Nights in Diaolou Tavern is here.
That's why I came to ask for a drink.
I have two cups of liquor here, a pleasant one and an unpleasant one.
Which one do you prefer?
Marquis, the young master is quite different from what I heard.
Seeing him today, he has some hard edges which resemble you back then.
He is my grandson.
Shouldn't he resemble me?
Please have a seat.
This is the finest Biluochun tea.
Use the tea fragrance to cover your liquor smell.
Otherwise you will have a hard time when you get home.
Your wife can be quite fierce.
Marquis, you still remember her.
Well, since you are willing to have tea with me,
I shall obey you.
Grandfather, have you met him before?
You both seem quite familiar.
His father is the principal academician of Longyun Pavilion, Hu Cheng.
Back then he was my classmate.
Academician Hu once held you when you were little.
An academician?
How come he doesn't take after his father?
Are you not going to tell me the business of the Imperial Censorate?
What business?
Has the Imperial Censorate ever had any serious business?
Funny lad.
That sorry bunch in the Imperial Censorate dare not come to me.
They see me as a sensitive matter so you were sent here.
But you are a spoiled brat who lives off your father's reputation.
You came here to interrogate me.
Surely you won't find out anything, good or bad, from me.
Marquis, you are insightful.
However, the Imperial Censorate underestimated me.
You don't question me, but I want to tell.
I'm not listening. No, I'm not.
Do you want me to twist your ears open?
Yes, please, Marquis. I'm jotting it down.
The brush you are holding demands lives.
Marquis, I hope you won't talk too much.
I'm old and I talk a lot.
How about this? Dongjun, you will speak on my behalf.
The Marquis Zhenxi's Mansion has 100,000 soldiers guarding the west gate of the country.
We never intend to disrupt national safety.
This trip to Tianqi is led by the Heir, Baili Chengfeng, with the Pofeng Army.
The Heir is a martial artist and is impulsive.
However, he has been instructed to keep the army in check and not to act rashly
no matter what happened during this trip.
The Marquis Zhenxi's Mansion believes
that the Seven Imperial Censors inspects all officials judiciously
and that they will clear the name of the Marquis Zhenxi.
If necessary, the Marquis Zhenxi is willing to confront the accuser in court.
I hope you will relay this wish to His Majesty.
The Marquis Zhenxi's Mansion will be deeply grateful.
Is that too much?
No, not at all. Young Master Baili, your words carry much weight.
If you say anymore words, I won't be able to continue with my trembling hands.
Leave if you want. I'm not keeping you here.
Dongjun, see him off.
Young Master, given what you said just now,
it conveys only a message: You don't intend to rebel.
But if someone wants to kill you, 100,000 Pofang soldiers
are ready to charge into Tianqi City.
I'm so impressed.
My friend said Seven Starry Nights
- defeated Qiulubai.
- That's right.
I want to drink it.
If you can prove my grandfather's innocence,
I will give you seven jars of it, not just seven cups.
Young Master, I will take your word for it.
I'm having this liquor for sure.
Have the Seven Imperial Censors reached a verdict?
There is no proof of the Marquis' guilt.
Who are the Seven Imperial Censors to accuse him?
Young Master, rest assured.
The marquis will be safe.  It's just that...
What is it?
Young Master, you ought to be careful.
Of course. I came here to keep my grandfather safe.
I won't allow anything to go wrong.
I mean you have to be cautious of the danger to yourself.
The danger to myself?
All right Young Master, the Imperial Censorate is two streets away.
I will head back myself.
Night roads are treacherous. Please be extra cautious.
I'm leaving.
Young Master.
Tell us what Baili Luochen told you and we won't kill you.
- Get lost.
- You!
You don't want to make this harder.
Why do you people always threaten me? So boring.
Let me tell you this. I don't give a fig for what you will do.
I only want to drink what I crave.
Don't waste your breath on him. Take him away!
Thank you, General Ye Jr.
You saw this coming didn't you?
Could you have handled this without me?
That's impossible. I... I'm nothing but a frail scholar.
Setting aside the older generation's matter, I saved your life today.
Thank you so much, General Ye Jr.
Tianqi City is a place of chaos.
You should leave soon.
All right. One last question.
Commander Luo from the palace seems to not be in Tianqi City.
I think Commander Luo has been sent out on a mission,
but I don't know the details.
- About my friend...
- They will be safe.
- I will take your word for it.
- I bet my life on it.
Speak.
First, when Li Changsheng and Baili Dongjun left Tianqi on a journey back then,
the former disappeared midway.
Therefore, that Li Changsheng should be a fake.
Second, I sent a message to Jin Xian and others.
Judging by the dates, they should arrive in Tianqi in no time.
May I?
Yes, please.
Mister, give me exactly what he's having.
All right.
Nice sword.
Shen Jingzhou, Wind and Snow Sword.
Ye Dingzhi, an unnamed swordsman.
I heard about you.
You are the disciple of the Sword Deity, Rain Demon.
Back then the Sword Deity brought you to Nanjue to challenge a couple of experts.
It was awesome.
I was mesmerized when I heard that.
I heard about you too.
An immortal from beyond with a sword summoning wind and snow.
The merciful killer, Shen Jingzhou.
I didn't expect to run into the best young swordsman here.
My pleasure.
We should have had a drink over this fortunate encounter.
Sadly, there is no liquor here.
Why don't we replace it with tea?
I hope you don't mind.
Since you have heard about me, you should know my other identity.
I'm Ye Yu's son. The wanted criminal of Beili.
I also know the real identity of Shen Jingzhou who owns the Wind and Snow Sword.
You are the direct disciple of Grand Eunuch Zhuoqing in the palace.
We are outside Tianqi City.
Since I haven't entered Tianqi, I'm a martial artist.
So I'm only Shen Jingzhou.
And you are only a friend I met by chance, Ye Dingzhi.
Very well.
Brother Ye, until next time.
Brother Shen, you should roam the Martial World.
Why confine yourself to Tianqi?
Master summons me back urgently. I have no choice.
I see.
Until next time.
Your Majesty, this case is hard to judge.
Please enlighten me, Your Majesty.
The Xiao Family governs the country with national laws.
The Imperial Censorate supervises all officials according to the national law.
There is no case you can't judge and no one you can't investigate.
Yet, you are kneeling here and want me to clarify for you.
If I can decide who is guilty or innocent, why do we need the law then?
And what do I need the Imperial Censorate for?
Zhang Chengzhong, you have become a dotard.
Your Majesty, the Imperial Censorate is responsible for supervising all officials.
But the Marquis has 100,000 elite soldiers.
Any verdict made would probably cause a stir in Beili.
I dare not make a decision.
Zhang Chengzhong, can the case file in your hands convict him of treason?
It's difficult to say.
Hu Bufei, yesterday you went to interrogate him.
Answer me.
Your Majesty, I believe the Marquis Zhenxi didn't commit treason.
Look at him.
Your Majesty, uh...
Like I said, judge according to the law
if he isn't found guilty of treason.
As for those who harbor rebellious thoughts, you might go and ask my sons.
They all harbor such thoughts.
Your Majesty.
Zhang Chengzhong, you have served two emperors.
You are the pillar of the nation.
How come you are so useless?
Your Majesty, since this problem has been resolved, there is another one.
Your Majesty! This is too much, Your Majesty.
I'm saying that you are a disposed good.
You good-for-nothing!
You are right, Your Majesty.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Creating discord between the Prince and the first-ranked Marquis
is very detrimental to the long-term stability of the country.
It's best to downplay the issue and resolve it quietly.
Prince Qing's name mustn't be mentioned.
Just say the Emperor has punished the accuser.
As for the punishment,
a deduction of two years' salary in private will be enough.
You said you didn't know how to judge.
Haven't you just clearly explained everything in detail?
Since you have figured out how to judge and do, just go ahead.
Is it indeed possible?
Get lost already!
Yes, Your Majesty.
I shall take my leave, Your Majesty.
What a relief.
Zhuoqing.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You will leave the palace with me later.
Aren't you curious about where I'm going?
There is no one in Tianqi City worth your personal visit.
You know me well.
Initially, I wanted you to approach the second prince
and persuade him to collect the evidence against Baili Luochen.
But in the end I pardoned Baili Luochen and put the second prince on the spot.
Do you know why?
That's not my business.
I only do what you say.
The second prince is ruthless and impatient.
He hasn't been behaving lately so I decided to teach him a lesson.
You are right, Your Majesty.
Zhuoqing.
Did you think I wanted to name Prince Qing as the heir?
It's windy today.
I will have the servants prepare a cloak for you.
♫  A gentle breeze intentionally stirs the heart  ♫
♫  Moored by the lake, ripples spread, feet covered with spring mud  ♫
♫  The branches softly whisper secrets in the wind  ♫
♫  In the moonlit night, I trace the outlines of your unfinished story  ♫
♫  As if destined by fate, I gaze upon your quietly graceful figure  ♫
♫  Restlessly searching for you  ♫
♫  I'll follow you until sunset and late afternoon sunshine  ♫
♫  Listening intently to the soft drizzle, accompanied by a lone shadow  ♫
♫  Who am I with at this moment?  ♫
♫  Roaming the world together in harmony  ♫
♫  Two hearts cherishing each other  ♫
♫  A red letter becomes a boat navigating our love  ♫
♫  A folding fan sways among the stars and clouds  ♫
♫  In this perfect moment  ♫
♫  I met you  ♫
♫  A gentle breeze intentionally stirs the heart  ♫
♫  Moored by the lake, ripples spread, feet covered with spring mud  ♫
♫  The branches softly whisper secrets in the wind  ♫
♫  In the moonlit night, I trace the outlines of your unfinished story  ♫
♫  As if destined by fate, I gaze upon your quietly graceful figure  ♫
♫  Restlessly searching for you  ♫
♫  I'll follow you until sunset and late afternoon sunshine  ♫
♫  Listening intently to the soft drizzle, accompanied by a lone shadow  ♫
♫  Who am I with at this moment?  ♫
♫  Roaming the world together in harmony  ♫
♫  Two hearts cherishing each other  ♫
♫  A red letter becomes a boat navigating our love  ♫
♫  A folding fan sways among the stars and clouds  ♫
♫  In this perfect moment  ♫
♫  I met you  ♫