♪Overcoming the boundary of confusion♪
♪Holding onto my life
in the face of death threats♪
♪I look into this dark night♪
♪Never once has my soul
been extinguished♪
♪With this passion♪
♪My spirit is growing
to reach full swing♪
♪Slashing the mountain
and the ocean apart♪
♪Answering the true call on a sword♪
♪I'm the chosen one
in this turbulent world♪
♪Keep my distance from the world♪
♪Who can understand my loneliness?♪
♪A single thought, looking down♪
♪Blades unsheathed,
frost flies everywhere♪
♪A belief that cuts through the world♪
♪Soaring towards the sky,
the sword reigns all♪
♪Striding across the land
with a drunken gait♪
♪I will protect the people
whenever I'm needed♪
♪Atop the summit, you and I shall
battle for the world's best♪
[Directed by Chen Zhoufei]
[Dashing Youth]
[Based on "Zhou Munan's
Juvenile Martial Arts Series"]
[from fanqienovel.com and bkneng.com]
[Episode 38]
As expected.
It's a spirit screen slope.
Will this route lead us
to the formation's core?
Precisely.
This Lone Void Formation
originally belongs to the military art.
It mysteriously helps
channel the fortune to one's side,
thereby overwhelming the enemy.
The demonic sect
lays the Ghostly Formation,
but the solution to break it
is quite similar.
The art of Ghostly Formation
relies on concealment.
Naturally,
the formation's core
lies in a place that gathers abundant qi
in the mountains.
On the northwest side of the mountain,
there is a boundless graveyard,
burying Han Xuan
and the entire Han Army.
Han Xuan's rebellion failed,
leading to his death.
Isn't that Ye Dingzhi
wants to do the same?
Soldiers have their qi.
As time passes,
their qi accumulates,
and the mountain
becomes a natural place for it.
Very well.
Will you continue to use your sword qi
to clear a path for me?
My pleasure.
This is indeed a nice sword.
What's its name?
Principles in life are written
into a tome of a thousand volumes.
So it's called the Thousand-Volume Tome.
With such a fine sword
to clear the path,
victory is assured.
I'm joining you.
No.
If you go,
no one will keep an eye on Xie Xuan.
His sword
is clearing the path for me.
If enemies come,
he might die here.
You just wait here.
Once I break the formation,
head eastward
to stop your friend.
But you
are all alone.
Don't worry.
Before we meet,
I was on my own.
I'm off.
No need to worry.
In Beili, the sword is favored,
while in Nanjue and Man State,
the blade prevail.
Only a few in this world use spears.
That's why people have forgotten
that the spear is the king of weapons.
What demonic beings fear most
are spears.
During my stay here,
the place has been unusually cold.
Turns out
it's because of the soldiers' graveyard.
Sleeping
beside this military tomb every day
was indeed quite disrespectful.
I, Sikong Changfeng,
am a wandering martial artist.
As I drift here
and see all the heroes,
I have no incense to offer.
Instead, I present this long spear
as a token of respect
to honor your noble spirits.
Darn it.
I forgot to ask that darned scholar
what to do
after finding the formation's core.
There are so many graves here.
Do I have to
dig them all up?
Lost Spirit Grass?
Why do I see
the stone of the formation's core
flickering?
Someone is approaching
the formation's core, Elder.
Never mind.
So what if they approach it?
They can't break the formation, anyway.
I have to rely on myself
in a situation like this.
The King of Medicine once said
that Lost Spirit Grass
grows among the graveyards
in the wilderness
where the soil is well-fed.
The area where all qi converges
should be flourishing with it.
I have a spear technique
named Dragon Transformation.
It was taught by my master,
Li Changsheng.
But I won't use it today.
I also have another spear technique
that when executed,
can stir up a commotion.
I won't use that either.
I have a daughter.
She has a lovely name.
It's Sikong Qianluo.
I miss her very much,
so I created
a new technique
named Qianluo.
Fellow soldiers,
watch closely.
Elder!
Whose spear strength is this?
It's continuous and tremendous.
I, Sikong Changfeng,
hereby offer my 1,000th spear move
to return all soldier spirits
to their homes.
Fall!
The formation is broken.
Charge!
I'm bushed.
When I meet Baili Dongjun
and Xie Xuan later,
I must tell them
I used only one move,
not a thousand.
Sikong Changfeng!
I'm still breathing!
Mission completed.
I should get going.
Thank you.
Don't disappoint me!
I will not.
[Mount Wangcheng]
Yuzhen, where's my mule?
Over here, Yixing.
One moment.
Be quick.
I won't be able to leave the mountain
if I'm late.
I asked you to pack my baggage.
You could've just
packed it casually.
Here you go, Yixing.
Let me see
what you packed for me.
I grew these peaches myself.
I don't like peaches
as much as you do.
Besides, are these peaches
really for me?
What are you talking about?
Give them back if you don't want them.
You can't take the peaches back
after giving them away.
All right, I'm leaving.
Wait, Yixing.
Forget about it.
You're not coming with me.
Just stay on the mountain.
Those who want to go can't,
while those who don't want to go
are forced to.
How irritating.
Getting back his own wife
is only right and natural.
But why must we
get involved in this?
Well,
it's all because of our sect's rules
that forbid marriage.
A bunch of stubborn old geezers
with no sense of romance
and ruins others' relationships.
What a sin.
Yuzhen, don't learn from them.
If you ever meet a girl you like
in the future,
marry her
even if you have to fight.
You can't go down.
I'm afraid that chance is gone.
Yixing,
are you going or not?
Right. Yes.
I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
Yixing, take care.
Come back soon.
This mountain marks the boundary.
Don't think you can overstep it,
you demonic sect.
Like we'd ever listen to you.
I think
it is up to us.
I didn't expect the lands
beyond the northern borders
to have so many skilled martial artists.
Most importantly,
they came in large numbers.
They came batch after batch.
It's not that they are in large numbers,
but you are too soft-hearted.
You injure them instead of killing them.
They go back to heal up in a day
and then
attack you the next day.
That's why
they came batch after batch.
Who's there?
It's you,
The Dark River.
Exactly.
I wonder if we are welcome here,
my righteous friends.
They are dropping like flies.
I see no reason they would push us away.
Changhe was right.
You so-called righteous sects
are simply hypocritical.
They are coming for your lives,
so you should retaliate.
If not,
they might think
you are idiots.
You!
I don't think the Dark River
came here
just to tease us, right?
Of course not.
Although the Dark River
used to kill solely for money,
this time
our first act
that has nothing to do with profit.
It's because our Top Leader said
the invasion of the demonic sect
into Beili
wouldn't do us
any good
and might affect
our already struggling business.
Hence, we were sent here
to help you.
What gimmick are you up to?
The Dark River
may be an assassination organization,
but deep inside,
we value our country.
Su Changhe,
the Undertaker of the Dark River.
Su Zhe,
the Conical Hat Ghost of the Dark River.
Isn't there still one missing?
I remember he was
always inseparable from Su Changhe.
Do you mean him?
He has become the Kui.
Of course he's not with me.
But don't worry. He's coming.
And he's the main force.
The Kui of the Dark River.
Judging by this lineup,
are you planning to kill us off
after helping us?
Take it easy.
We won't kill our own
unless someone pays us to.
Jinxuan,
have today's military reports arrived?
Your Majesty, they just arrived.
Read them.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Xiao Ruofeng]
"All towns occupied by Nanjue's army
have already been reclaimed
by the Langya Army.
Though Nanjue's army hasn't retreated,
they cannot achieve anything more.
We won."
The current attack from Nanjue
is merely a bluff from the beginning.
Besides, with Ruofeng
personally leading the army
to repel them,
it's an easy feat.
[Baili Chengfeng]
"The West.
The vicious mob in the Western Regions
has been suppressed.
There have been a few skirmishes
with wandering rogues,
but they won't develop
into a big threat.
We won again."
Sending the Pofeng Army
to suppress these wandering rogues
is indeed a waste of their talents.
[Lei Mengsha]
As for the North...
Keep it as short as possible.
Yes, Your Majesty.
"The army of the northern tribes
is extremely terrifying.
Though their numbers
are fewer than Nanjue's,
they are ten times
more ferocious.
They are a force to be reckoned with.
Fortunately,
thanks to the valiant Langya Army
and some great help,
so please rest assured, Your Majesty."
Great help?
According to the military report,
his name is Junyu.
He's from the Academy
and a disciple of Mr. Li's.
Mr. Li?
Even though
the top martial artist, Mr. Li,
has disappeared for so long,
his influence remains.
What about the Northwest?
What about that place?
We also received news
from the Northwest.
We sent martial artists
to keep the Northwest in check,
but this Wushuang City,
being a martial city appointed
by the founding Emperor,
has the responsibility
to defend the country.
How come the missive is so informal?
Your Majesty,
this isn't sent from Wushuang City.
It's from Sikong Changfeng
of Xueyue City.
I see. It's the Lord Vermillion Bird.
That explains it.
What does the missive say?
Here's what it says.
"The army of the demonic sect
has been intercepted,
but only one person broke through
and is heading to Tianqi City."
"We are asked to guard the imperial city
and protect Your Majesty."
Does this person
have the nerve to come here
to assassinate me alone?
What a joke.
This person
is called Ye Dingzhi.
Your Majesty.
Jinxian?
Why are you here?
You seem anxious.
Did you receive the news
that someone is heading here
to assassinate me?
Please take shelter
in the Heavenly Sword Pavilion.
No.
Your Majesty...
Jinxian,
how long do you think
until the assassination attempt?
I'm afraid it will be today.
Lord White Tiger and Lord Azure Dragon
are waiting
at the Azure Cloud Terrace.
Very well.
Let's meet him
there.
Since he wishes to kill me,
let him try.
[Pingqing Hall]
He's approaching quickly.
The Heart Sword has a soul within.
Is it in fear?
No, it's excitement.
Your Majesty.
It's dangerous here.
Please hurry and leave, Your Majesty.
It's too late.
The successor of Heart Sword
from Swordheart Grave.
Nice sword.
What a great sword core.
That's powerful.
Which phase is he on now?
Truth be told, he's not inferior
to Mr. Li.
You know I came to kill you,
why didn't you hide?
Such audacity.
I have done nothing wrong,
so why would I be afraid
of a thief like you?
A thief?
Who is the thief
that stole someone else's wife?
Consort Xuan has long been married
in Prince Jingyu's Mansion.
It was you who fooled and abducted her.
How am I the thief?
Consort Xuan?
Yi Wenjun is my wife.
We were betrothed before,
and we have always been
in love with each other.
Xiao Ruojin,
you coerced her into marrying
into the imperial family.
Beili
has made her a sacrifice
of your power struggle.
You!
Mr. Ye,
I would hate to fight you.
But given that
I'm right here,
I can't just stand by
and watch you kill the Emperor.
So bring it on!
I don't want to say this,
but I have to.
Ye Dingzhi,
do return to the correct path!
Nonsense!
There is more
than just one path.
My path
is to safeguard
the little hut outside Gusu City.
Your hut is ruined!
But she is still around.
As long as she is around,
I can rebuild the hut.
Xinyue!
That's enough.
Ji Ruofeng,
you're proficient
in martial arts of all schools.
Ye Dingzhi
is so powerful now.
Has he attained
the Roaming Mystical Phase?
No.
Only martial artists
who follow the correct path
are classified into four phases
of the first stage.
He has strayed into the Sly Path,
which is beyond the four phases.
Judging by his power,
he should be in the Malevolence Phase.
Who else will stand in my way?
Transcended the suffering world of Yin
without manifestation of immortality.
Held no name in the Netherworld
nor among the Three Deities Mountains.
He's already above
the Sovereign Sky Phase.
In a sense,
it's equivalent
to the Roaming Mystical Phase.
It's just that he has deviated
into the Sly Path
due to his obsession.
He may seem powerful,
but he's filled with heinous qi.
Those I have seen
who fell into the Sly Path
have lost their sanity.
How come Ye Dingzhi
looks so sober?
He may seem so,
but is being trapped by his obsession.
Hadn't the State Preceptor
left Tianqi for a long journey,
his obsession
might have been dispelled.
However, that wouldn't happen.
Your technique
can suppress my internal strength.
I didn't know
that someone in Beili
practiced the Xunian Art.
You are mistaken.
The Xunian Art is passed down
within Beique.
The one that remains in Beili
is the Xuhuai Art.
Both arts originated
from the same source.
They mutually reinforce
and restrain each other.
Your zhenqi is damaged,
giving me the upper hand.
You have lost.
They mutually reinforce
and restrain each other?
It only happens
when our phases are equal.
You've only just started your ascent,
while I
am already among the clouds.
You are way too far
from your master, Zhuoqing,
who is locked away
in the Imperial Mausoleum.
Back then,
Yue Fengcheng and Baili Dongjun
inserted their internal strength
into my body,
I fully absorbed it.
Who are you
to think
you can compete
with my internal strength?
You stole my inner strength,
yet you are boasting about it.
Who is that?
Don't worry.
It's the grandson
of the Marquis of Zhenxi,
Baili Dongjun.
You are here.
Long time no see.
Not longer
than the ten years
I thought you were dead.
Even though
you weren't with me in those ten years,
our hearts were still together.
But now,
we are against each other.
So,
are you finally going
to draw your sword against me?
Do it, then.
Baili Dongjun,
when you followed Ruofeng
to Tianqi back then,
you were an immature lad
when I saw you from the rampart.
Now,
you do seem
like the young master
from the Marquis's mansion.
Do not step over this sword.
Leave Ye Dingzhi to me.
Yun,
mend your ways.
All people killed by the demonic sect
did nothing wrong.
Yun.
I don't wish to fight you.
When I grow up,
I want to
be the White Feather Sword Deity.
When I grow up,
I want to
be the Green Feather Liquor Deity.
When I grow up, I want to...
be free and fight bad folks.
focus on brewing liquor
- and roam the martial arts world with you!
- Roam the martial arts world with you!
Nineteen years ago,
the apricot blossoms were
just as beautiful.
Back then, you were fond of the cool,
so you changed into a lighter robe.
Unexpectedly,
a late spring cold brought you down.
I promised that once you recovered,
I would take you and Wenjun
to watch the apricot blossoms.
It's a shame
that everything has changed.
We lost the chance.
This is my regret.
Now is the perfect time.
Let's go
and watch apricot blossoms
as promised.
Yun,
think about those innocent people.
Mend your ways.
Dongjun.
I want to live for myself just once.
I'm sorry.
All right.
If so, I will fight you
until you change your mind.
We have known each other for years,
yet we haven't
had a real duel.
I heard
that after you
lost all your cultivation,
you encountered a great opportunity.
Well,
I would like to see that.
What an imposing internal strength.
It's more powerful
than the Autumn Water Technique.
I created
this internal strength technique,
called Hanging Sky.
Very well.
Who's there?
Qingyang.
Wenjun.
It has been a long time.
I was told
that after I left,
you requested to be sent
to Muliang City.
Why?
Someone wrote me a letter.
Qingyang.
I think I heard
the sound of the Luminous Jade Moon.
It's him, isn't it?
Yes, it's him.
He's back.
I will take you to him.
To think that two young geniuses
show up at the same time.
If they didn't oppose each other,
the martial fortune of Beili
would've surpassed Nanjue's
by a hundred years.
The duel between them
may seem confusing,
but Ye Dingzhi
has distinctly gotten the upper hand.
If Baili Dongjun fails,
we have no choice
but to fight to the death.
No one can get away with this.
As of now, they are still
testing each other.
They haven't resorted
to their strongest moves yet.
The showdown between two experts
requires no more than one sword move.
And I'm waiting for it.
This liquor is named Xuyu.
I made it when I first entered
the martial arts world.
Ye Dingzhi,
as its name implies,
life and death are
as fleeting as a thought.
Attack and retreat
are decided by a thought.
The world comes into being
within a thought.
This sword move
inherits the divine aura of my master.
Do watch closely.
My sword move
is the final move
my master launched at Dongyue Lake.
Neither deities
nor demons,
only death can cease it.
I have never seen
such a desperate move.
Is this Ye Dingzhi's strongest move
you mentioned?
[No animals were harmed
during the filming of this drama.]
[Some animals were created
using bionic props and 3D effects.]
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪