♪Overcoming the boundary of confusion♪
♪Holding onto my life
in the face of death threats♪
♪I look into this dark night♪
♪Never once has my soul
been extinguished♪
♪With this passion♪
♪My spirit is growing
to reach full swing♪
♪Slashing the mountain
and the ocean apart♪
♪Answering the true call on a sword♪
♪I'm the chosen one
in this turbulent world♪
♪Keep my distance from the world♪
♪Who can understand my loneliness?♪
♪A single thought, looking down♪
♪Blades unsheath,
frost flies everywhere♪
♪A belief that cuts through the world♪
♪Soaring towards the sky,
the sword reigns all♪
♪Striding across the land
with a drunken gait♪
♪I will protect the people
whenever I'm needed♪
♪Atop the summit, you and I shall
battle for the world's best♪
[Directed by Chen Zhoufei]
[Dashing Youth]
[Based on "Zhou Munan's
Juvenile Martial Arts Series"]
[from fanqienovel.com and bkneng.com]
[Episode 11]
[Day of the Academy's Final Examination]
[Between Heaven and Earth]
I thought you hated occasions like this.
I assumed you wouldn't appear
after the preliminary examination.
You'll know why soon.
Lei.
Who do you think will impress everyone
in the final examination?
Ye Dingzhi? Yin Luoxia?
Or that expert
in Qimen Dunjia?
Why are you not
on the list?
If so, I can't make my choice.
You're indeed a good friend of mine.
Let me rephrase it.
Who do you think will impress everyone
in the final examination?
Ye Dingzhi?
Yin Luoxia?
Me?
Or that expert
in Qimen Dunjia?
Ye Dingzhi.
What is wrong with you?
I'm just telling the truth.
You want
to impress everyone?
You're not capable enough.
You two are early today.
Without me,
it sure is awkward between you two.
It must be true
that you two have nothing to talk about.
Mhm.
They stood next to each other
for almost an hour,
and they only exchanged one line.
That's normal.
Worry not.
Just
let me
host the event later.
They are so boring.
If you ask them to explain the rules,
the candidates will die from the nerves.
But it's
different with me.
Of course.
You'll blabber from day till night.
They'll get sleepy,
instead of nervous.
That's right.
All right.
All 16 of you here
are
the candidates of the final examination.
According to our rules,
you will
be divided into teams of four.
There'll be four teams in total.
All of you will be given a hint.
Use the hint to find
the object.
Whoever finds it first
will be recruited into the Academy.
And Master
will pick one
among the four winners
as his last disciple.
And that one will be our junior.
But of course,
to find the object with one hint
is not going
to be easy.
If you can collect all four hints,
the answer will be obvious.
Therefore,
defeating other teams
and snatching their hints
are crucial to winning.
How do we form a team?
By drawing lots?
Pick your own teammates.
We pick?
But we don't know each other.
How about let's form a team?
Are you sure you don't know each other
after all this time?
Who's good with sword techniques?
Who's good with toxin?
Who's good with qinggong?
Who's the strongest foe?
Haven't you
done your research?
As for your name,
origin,
and other information
no matter if it's traceable
or not,
don't you have an idea
about those already?
All of you are sly foxes,
so don't play dumb here.
Instead of
making
a fuss,
you'd better
select your ideal teammates
as soon as possible.
After all, there's no time to waste.
Zhuomo.
You gave them too many tips.
You have an hour,
and it begins now.
Make way.
Ye.
Move.
Move aside.
Let's team up.
Yes, let's team up.
Can I join?
Ye Dingzhi is pretty popular.
Several days ago,
Ye Dingzhi
stopped an armed fight in the city.
His martial prowess is known
throughout the city.
And you aren't aware of it?
Is that so?
Miss.
Would you like to team up with me?
It's him.
While I have never seen
his face before,
this person here knows Qimen Dunjia
and carries a similar scent.
It must be him.
If he's here,
things will be troublesome.
Why?
Do you have another plan, miss?
If I say yes,
will you oppose it?
Of course not.
I hope we are striving
toward the same goal
and I hope to see you
at the destination.
How troublesome.
It seems like your friend
is more popular than you.
In that case,
why don't we
team up?
We?
Miss,
in fact,
when I first met you,
I wanted to ask
if we
had met before.
Is that why you chose me?
Don't overthink it.
I chose you
because you are handsome.
And good-looking people
are supposed
to team up with each other.
It's the law of the universe
since time immemorial.
I looked around
and thought you looked the most dashing.
While I agree with that,
I...
Mr. Ye, think about it.
Do think about it.
Mr. Ye.
Ye.
Please make way.
I am very flattered,
but I already
have a teammate in mind.
Mr. Ye.
Thanks. I pick...
- Mr. Ye.
- Ye.
Mr. Ye,
I can't believe you'd choose me.
Please move aside.
I pick you.
Why me?
Because you're handsome.
Fine.
You're charming too.
I overheard you
saying that good-looking people
are supposed to team up with each other.
Zhuge Yun
is quite handsome.
But unfortunately,
he's not one of us.
What do we do next?
I am Xiahou Mengding.
I'd like to join your team.
I am Zhao Yujia.
I'd like to join your team too.
I know you.
You are the one
who did the Face-Changing.
I can tame animals.
I am famous in Tianqi City.
I can tame animals too.
My skill is unrivaled.
Are you
doing this on purpose?
I'm just telling the truth.
Let's have a competition, then.
Taiyi Lion Secret Arts.
He's from Mount Wangcheng.
It's my first time
seeing that technique.
It seems like there are lots of talents
hide among these candidates.
Even an expert of the Xuan Sect
is here to attend the examination.
It seems like the Academy
is famous now.
So?
Do you still want to compete with me?
No.
Farewell.
Uhm, I can...
Facing-Changing is not
the only thing I know.
- Farewell.
So it's you.
Zhao Yujia.
I'll leave if you're not picking me.
Stay.
I think
you're decently strong.
You must be one of us.
So we have
a team now.
Wait.
Miss, while you're pretty,
I'm not so sure
if I want to recruit you.
What's in your mind, Mr. Ye?
It's an important examination.
We must be cautious.
Baili,
test her out.
Me?
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
Your qinggong is exceptional.
You are faster than you were that day.
It's not the ordinary
Three Flying Swallow Moves.
I invented this myself.
It's called Drunken Slide.
A sword in her sleeves?
How ingenious.
The Instant Kill Sword Arts
sure is lethal.
I don't mean to kill.
It was just
to test you.
You had a dream?
I dreamed of Dongjun.
What did you dream of?
I dreamed
that he mastered
the Instant Kill Sword Arts,
and even improved upon
the Three Flying Swallow Moves
into his own moves.
That does
sound like a dream.
Mr. Baili,
have I impressed you
with my sleeve swordplay?
Like I said,
I was just testing you.
You'll have to ask him
if you pass the test or not.
Miss,
the final examination
will be a dangerous one.
Naturally, I want
strong teammates.
Don't take it to heart.
From now on,
we are a team.
The four of them actually formed a team.
The strong band with one another.
They are more likely to win now.
You think so?
I think this is even worse.
Master will only recruit one disciple.
If that team wins,
who do you think Master will pick?
Ye Dingzhi
or Baili Dongjun?
Master only recruits
the most interesting candidate,
not the strongest.
You
are an exception.
You're boring.
You're so extremely boring
that it becomes somehow interesting.
That's why Master took you in.
Do you think
you're a very interesting person?
I do.
I think Ye Dingzhi
is more interesting than you.
Quit it.
Time's up.
Have you found your teammates?
Well,
where is
the next arena?
Master.
Your next arena
is
the entire Tianqi City.
The entire city?
When does it start?
Now.
Mr. Baili here is very eager
to drink Qiulubai which comes out
once per month
after the examination.
How do you know?
I went
to Diaolou Tavern just now
and got the last pot of Qiulubai
of this month.
Oh, no.
You might not be able to enjoy it.
You old man,
I might just snatch it off your hands.
Mind your manner.
It's fine.
The young are bold.
Isn't it great?
All right.
I'll wait for your return.
He won't
let us catch a break at all.
As the saying goes,
the silk is white like snow,
braided it into two carps.
To know one's real thoughts,
retrieve the notes
inside the carp's tummy.
I...
In a word,
the hints are inside the fish's tummy.
They contain
the hours of Wei, Shen, You, and Xu.
In a moment,
send a representative here
and draw lots.
You will depart
on the hour that you draw.
Before you leave,
Mr. Mochen will give you
a pouch.
Oh right.
If one team
finds the final answer,
the golden bell on this stage
will toll.
When that happens,
please gather
in the Academy.
Understood?
Well, let's do this then.
Why do we depart
at different times?
Because each team
will be given only one pouch.
The hint is inside the pouch.
So there are four hints in total.
The ones who leave first
can act first.
They can either hide
or solve the riddle as soon as possible.
The ones who leave later
can pay attention
to where the ones leaving first go.
They can either find them
or wait for them.
If we all leave together,
then there's no need
to have this competition.
We might as well fight here.
The winners
will walk away with all the pouches
and find the answer.
How smart of you.
You sure know
our rules very well.
Enough talking.
Send someone up.
King of Gambling.
That will be me.
The ones who get the hour of Wei
will leave first.
The ones who get the hour of Xu
will leave after six hours.
The answer might have already
been found in six hours.
So the competition starts now.
The hour of Shen.
Not bad.
The first ones to leave
will be targeted.
Leaving at the hour of Shen
might be a better choice.
You live up to the name
of King of Gambling.
Good job.
You do know how to butter someone up.
You must be single.
Shut up.
Which team do you think
will depart first?
Well...
There.
The hour of Wei.
The hour of You.
The hour of Xu.
The first team may leave now.
What a formidable foe.
This is worrisome.
Why are you worried?
You're not sitting for the examination.
The winner
will be our junior.
I don't want
someone like him
to be our peers.
You have put up with me
so far.
I am your senior.
Fine, you're my senior.
I am.
Self-appointed senior.
Per your request, I have delivered
the message to Ye Dingzhi.
To join my wing,
one must pay a price.
Only by being responsible
for the death of Baili Dongjun,
will Ye Dingzhi be willing
to serve me loyally.
[Prince Jingyu's Mansion]
Ruofeng,
[Xiao Ruojin, Prince Jingyu of Beili]
who do you think will be your junior
in the examination?
Since when are you concerned
with the Academy's affairs, Ruojin?
Many in the imperial court
have vested interest
in the Academy.
I know
you are on the Academy's side,
so I never ask you about it.
However,
among the candidates,
someone
will work for Prince Qing.
Whoever that person is,
once recruited into the Academy,
they will be a member of the Academy.
Ruojin, you lost.
When it comes to weiqi,
I can never win you.
How is Wenjun?
I have taken her into my residence.
We're waiting for the day
Father mandates our marriage
to get betrothed.
[Yi Wenjun, Daughter of the Leader
of the Shadow Sect]
[Luo Qingyang,
Head Disciple of the Shadow Sect]
Qingyang,
it's crowded today.
Today is the final examination
of the Academy.
Is that so?
Yes.
They can live freely.
I envy them.
If I
could live like them,
would I also be free
and happy?
Wenjun.
It's so quiet on the street.
I don't see anyone here.
It's the final examination,
so they cleared everyone out.
Anyway,
the pouch says,
"You do not witness
the existence of Black Tortoise."
Black Tortoise...
What is Black Tortoise?
It wouldn't be the final examination
if it was an easy riddle.
Xuanwu...
Maybe Black Tortoise Parlor?
Black Tortoise Parlor?
Yes.
It's one of the most famous
sword armories in Tianqi City.
It's under the Academy.
There are sword armories in Tianqi City?
That's incredible.
How come I've never heard of it?
Sir,
you must have been living under a rock.
My family has strict rules.
Very strict.
Let's go.
Everyone has left.
If we don't go now, we'll be too late.
[Kill Baili Dongjun]
[Xuan, Baixiao Hall]
The four of them actually formed a team.
How quaint
and interesting.
More importantly, they have
intriguing backgrounds.
Any updates?
Yin Luoxia,
the daughter of the previous
King of Gambling, Yin Shunshui.
She is the current King of Gambling.
Her mother
is the only daughter
of Marquis of Luoyang.
Being unable to live
with the wandering gambler Yin Shunshui,
she left him.
Yin Luoxia
has been living with her father.
Half of her martial prowess
comes from her father.
The other half
comes from his father's
three other friends.
Together, they are the Four Vices
in the martial arts world,
Glutton, Drunkard,
Philanderer, and Gambler.
Yin Luoxia has no notoriety.
She hardly leaves her father
after they have lived in seclusion.
Furthermore,
she has never contacted anyone
from Tianqi City.
She's the real Yin Luoxia?
She was still a child
when she last appeared publicly.
But according to the information
gathered,
she is quite likely Yin Luoxia.
What about the rest?
Ye Dingzhi,
a nobody in the martial arts world.
In one specific record,
he was first spotted
in Nanjue.
He has been wandering ever since.
However, he should be a Beili citizen.
In fact, he is likely the youngest son
of General Ye Yu,
whose family was sanctioned
to death because of treason.
He survived by being swapped out.
When he was spotted in Nanjue,
he was following around someone else.
That person is his master.
Who is his master?
The strongest individual in Nanjue,
Rain Demon, the Sword Deity.
The disciple
of Nanjue's strongest individual
wants to be Mr. Li's disciple?
Looks like he aspires
to be
the strongest individual in the world.
From what did you infer his relationship
with Ye Yu?
Just his surname
and the timing of his appearance alone
are not convincing enough.
The case of General Ye Yu's treason
was an unjust case.
The one who sabotaged him
was Prince Qing,
who only obtained his title that year.
Ye Dingzhi and Prince Qing
were seen talking briefly.
Therefore, he must be Ye Dingzhi.
However, this is yet to be confirmed.
What about Zhao Yujia?
Nothing on him.
Nothing?
In that case,
there are only two explanations.
He either appears out of nowhere
or...
He's using a pseudonym.
Zhao Yujia
is an expert in mystic arts.
While we failed to identify him,
we found
the best mystic artist,
also the Chief of Mount Wangcheng,
Lyu Suzhen. His youngest disciple
is Zhao Yuzhen.
It was alleged that he was
a rare prodigy in Mount Wangcheng.
He has never left it
after he entered the mountain.
So you're saying that Zhao Yujia
might be Zhao Yuzhen?
How interesting.
Zhao Yujia is also recommended
by someone.
You're bringing it up now,
which means
the one recommending him
must be someone very important.
Like Xiao Ruofeng?
Zhao Yujia is recommended
by Mr. Li himself.
Oh?
This is intriguing.
And Zhuge Yun?
The settlement of the Zhuge Family
is still unknown.
However, evidence seems to suggest
that the Zhuge Family
has been wiped out.
But perhaps
some of them
survived.
We wanted to ask
the Elder of the Academy
who has recommended Zhuge Yun.
However...
What's it?
He is dead.
Dead?
Yes,
killed by Zhuge Yun.
He was killed
on the way to the region
that is out of the North.
But the Academy
hasn't received the news yet,
so they are not aware of the situation.
And I was only
informed of this moments ago.
Relay this to Xiao Ruofeng.
Noted.
The region...
that is out of the North.
Zhuge...
Right.
Anything else you want to add?
This information is very important.
I'll need extra money for it.
Lord Wuzuo.
They are tricky foes.
I'm here.
What are you afraid of?
Then the other Lord...
I have arranged accordingly.
Wucheng.
[Zhuge Wucai, Zhuge Wucheng,
Twin Lords Wuzuo, Sky's Beyond]
Please deal
with those pesky candidates now.
Qixuan.
You'll come with me
to find Young Lady and the others.
Zhuge Yun.
We're teammates.
We should help each other!
Why?
Who... Who exactly are you?
Isn't the Zhuge Family
known for its chivalry?
How...
How come you're this cruel?
[Black Tortoise Parlor]
Is there
anything what we're looking for
in there?
Let's check it out.
This is suspicious.
Please exercise caution.
Don't stray too far from me.
Be careful.
Be vigilant.
Hold on.
It's the coiled thread
from Honglu Temple.
Coiled thread is made from thin iron.
It's so thin
that eyes cannot discern it.
There aren't many weapons
as discreet and sharp as this one here.
Why are you standing there?
It's not as sharp as you said.
You're using a Celestial Level Sword.
And this
is the most common coiled thread.
Is there any other type
of coiled thread?
You'll have to ask
Mr. Xia from Honglu Temple.
Let's go.
So this is the Sword Tower.
How splendid.
That is
a real Celestial Level Sword, right?
I'm afraid only a deity can wield it.
Are the swords not worth
anything at all?
No one guards them.
Are they not afraid these swords
might be stolen?
They might pay with their lives.
We're already here.
What do we do next?
Our hint is just a line of a poem.
What are you staring at?
The jade on the sword hilt
looks like an eye.
Did you see that?
Or am I hallucinating?
You're right.
I saw that too.
The jade on the hilt
just blinked like a normal eye.
Why don't I slice it
to see what's inside?
Kiddo.
That sword is worth a fortune.
If you destroy it,
you have to pay for it
even if you become
the disciple of the Academy.
Who's there?
I am Xinyang,
the sword of a Sword Deity.
I am the sword of Fufeng Fairy.
I am Mingyue.
I am Qixiao.
I am the master of the Sword Tower.
All swords return to me.
I'll command all swords!
Just a trick of the eye.
Show yourself!
You have not seen the thousand swords
of Xuanwu.
How can you challenge all the demons?
It's that poem.
We're at the right place.
No,
you're at the wrong place.
Two pupils?
It's said that the servant
of the Yellow Emperor,
Cangjie, has four eyes.
So someone
with four eyes exists in this world.
A mortal with four eyes
is half a step away from godhood.
A sage with four eyes
can rule the Heaven.
Who are you?
I am your judgment.
You're
here.
If you want the final answer,
you'll have to go through me.
You work for the Academy?
Like I said,
all swords return to me
and I'll command all swords!
What gibberish.
Careful.
Our enemy lurks in the dark
while we're in the open.
It's pitch-black in the hall.
We can't see him
and he can't see us.
Those with two pupils
see light with one
and see darkness with another.
He has full vision
at the moment.
And we are the blind ones here.
I've practiced locating someone
with sounds for years,
but I can't
locate him at all.
That's right.
He seems to be everywhere.
We have no time.
If this place
has nothing to do with the final answer,
let's not stay here.
Let's leave.
Oh, no.
We can't get out of here.
I have an idea.
That costs a fortune, you said?
Then I'll
shatter it.
Insolence!
Run!
[No animals were harmed
during the filming of this drama.]
[Some animals were created
using bionic props and 3D effects.]
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪