♫  Overcoming self-doubt and finding purpose  ♫
♫  Enduring the trials of life and death  ♫
♫  As I gaze into the dark night  ♫
♫  My spirit has not been broken  ♫
♫  And unleash this passion  ♫
♫  My spirit will only grow stronger  ♫
♫  Splitting mountains and parting seas  ♫
♫  Answering the sword's call and entering the Martial World  ♫
♫  I'm the chosen one, fate in this turbulent world  ♫
♫  Keeping my distance from the world  ♫
♫  Who can understand my loneliness?  ♫
♫  A single thought, gazing down  ♫
♫  With swords drawn, frost flies through the air  ♫
♫  With faith that conquers the world with one strike  ♫
♫  Soaring through the sky, the sword reigns everywhere  ♫
♫  Breaking through the waves, dancing drunkenly everywhere  ♫
♫  Protecting the people, no matter the cost  ♫
♫  Atop the peak, you and I shall battle all out  ♫
Here it comes.
Dragon Transformation, transform!
We've already used five groups of people as a diversion.
We're sure that they didn't catch up to us.
Is our mission considered complete, then?
If that's all there is, that means we only helped a couple get together
and annoy Prince Jingyu.
Of course, it's more than that.
Isn't this Feili, the Soul Official?
Leave the rest to us.
Esteemed envoys, we dare not trouble the two of you for such dirty deeds.
Does that mean the two of you are going to act together?
You guys should stop asking questions.
Instead, you should return to Tianqi as soon as possible
and continue to lie low while planning for the grand scheme.
Great.
But Feili, you mustn't let us down.
Finally, I got everything sorted.
Brother Ye, what's with all the trouble?
Isn't it better to live directly in the mountains?
This place is pretty good too.
Isn't it lonely to live alone?
You're a young boy. Do you understand the meaning of loneliness?
Brother Ye, you have some guests.
- Young Master.
- Why are you all back?
Young Master, we were supposed to lie low within Tianqi City
and inquire about Miss Yi under your orders.
But a benefactor showed up a few days ago.
He gave us access to an opportunity.
Young Master, I'll leave the two of you to it. I'll tell you the details later.
♫  Even as the time passes quickly between spring and autumn  ♫
♫  I will never see the face of my old friend again  ♫
♫  Beautiful years have passed, but dreams in my heart are still unfulfilled  ♫
♫  Love and resentment are entangled, and I'm still frozen in the past  ♫
♫  Allow me to see you one more time before I leave  ♫
♫  Longing, Longing for karma that won't come  ♫
♫  Balancing on a thin line, why am I afraid to close my eyes  ♫
♫  What I can't bear most  ♫
♫  Is that from now on you're alone in this world  ♫
♫  By the window  ♫
On the day of your wedding,
I was there.
I know.
I heard you.
I went there with your senior.
We managed to reach the mansion's entrance.
I was even inside the mansion. I gave it my all.
I've tried my best to improve my martial arts since leaving Tianqi.
This way, I can go and pick you up once I can defeat them.
♫  Hoping that my dreams will still be fulfilled  ♫
♫  Memories seep into my mind, filling it with love and longing  ♫
If I have to wait until then, will I be old?
♫  Alas, sighing at a fate that is so sorrowful  ♫
♫  Because of you, the gratitude and grievances stir yet remain unsaid  ♫
You'll never grow old.
♫  Longing, Longing for karma that won't come  ♫
♫  Balancing on a thin line, why am I afraid to close my eyes  ♫
♫  What I can't bear most  ♫
♫  Is that from now on you're alone in this world  ♫
♫  By the window  ♫
Mister Qin.
May I ask where Young Master Feizhan is?
My name is Feili.
Are you two brothers?
We don't look alike, do we?
He's full of despair, while I'm a dashing gentleman.
Young Master Feili, you're such a jokester.
We were able to complete the task, all thanks to Young Master Feizhan's help.
I'm not done yet.
Although we're brothers, we do opposite things.
He saves people while...
I kill.
But why?
It's because all those who know about us have to die.
Did you say a woman
came looking for Ye Dingzhi?
And he was happy about it?
He was more than just happy.
It's just like...
It's just like me when I see candied hawthorns.
What does that woman look like?
Just like the goddesses we see in portraits.
People say that the women of Gusu City are beautiful.
But compared to that lady,
they're way inferior.
Isn't that Uncle Qin's zither?
Young Master, after our brief encounter, I have to head back in advance.
Someone is pursuing us.
The four of us will proceed southward and lure them to Nanjue.
Young Master, we'll come and see you again once everything has settled down.
We were able to leave Tianqi together with Miss Yi
all thanks to the help of Deputy Commander Luo and General Ye's old acquaintances.
Deputy Commander Luo helped us to escape Prince Jingyu's Mansion
while General Ye's old acquaintances escorted us out of Tianqi until we reached Gusu.
Now, we've parted ways.
Each of us is leading our pursuers to different locations.
But we should be reunited someday.
Young Master, please don't worry.
From Qin Yuehan.
Senior Luo and Father's old acquaintances.
Brother Yun.
Wenjun.
You're awake.
Good morning.
Master.
Tell Prince Qing that he can begin his operation soon.
Your Majesty, Prince Qing seeks an audience.
Summon him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Summon Prince Qing.
Greetings, Father. Long live Father.
Spare the formalities.
Thank you, Father.
What do you need?
Tell me.
Father, although Prince Jingyu's mansion has suppressed the news from the public,
there are no undiscovered secrets.
In my opinion, Ye Dingzhi isn't capable enough to take Yi Wenjun out of Tianqi.
I'm sure someone aided him.
Tell me about it.
I dare not do so.
Just speak your mind.
If we think about it, of all the officials in the court, only Marquis Zhenxi is able to help Ye Dingzhi.
And Baili Dongjun once helped him when he tried to steal the bride.
He also escorted him out of Tianqi.
Father, if Baili Luochen's subordinates are able to enter the capital and abduct the princess consort,
they might be able to storm the palace and steal the throne in the future.
It's not about whether he can do it.
It's about whether he wants to do it.
Xie'er.
Yes, Father.
I'll leave that to you.
Yes, Father. I won't disappoint you.
It's late at night. What are we doing?
Censor Zhang?
You see, it's midnight. Why has His Majesty summoned me to the court?
I have no idea either. Let's hurry.
Well...
- Is my hat tilted?
- Yes.
Last night, the Seven Imperial Censors were summoned in the middle of the night.
It seems like something huge is going to happen.
Brother, do you think we're their target?
I'm sure it's related to Prince Qing seeking an audience with Father.
Prince Qing's largest foes are us.
It's hard to say.
Logically speaking, it's most likely that Prince Qing is targeting us.
However, I have a feeling that something else is happening.
What is it?
By the Mandate of Heaven and the Emperor's decree,
Baili Luochen, the Marquis Zhenxi, is accused of treason.
Effective immediately, the Seven Imperial Censors
are ordered to jointly investigate this matter.
Thus ordered.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
What is it? Why are you panicking?
Eunuch Li is here. He also brought an imperial edict with him.
So what? I'm Prince Jingyu. Imperial edicts are nothing special to me.
Your Highness, although the imperial edict was delivered to Prince Jingyu's Mansion, it wasn't for you.
Eunuch Li.
Greetings, Prince Jingyu.
Greetings, Prince Langya.
Eunuch Li, what do you mean by that?
What do you mean when you said it was delivered to my mansion, but it wasn't meant for me?
Seems like the imperial edict was for me.
Indeed, Prince Langya.
Both of you are always close to each other.
Just now, I went to Prince Langya's mansion, but I couldn't find you there, Your Highness.
I knew that you would be in Prince Jingyu's mansion.
Your Highness, since I've found you, you should now receive the edict.
Your Highness, this is a secret edict.
Although His Majesty sent me here to deliver the edict, I have no idea what the edict is about.
Your Highness, you should read it yourself.
Eunuch Li, this edict is quite troublesome.
Although I don't know what the edict is about,
I do know that His Majesty was frowning when he wrote it.
He was pondering for a long time.
Eunuch Li, your words are making me even more nervous.
If so, I shall take my leave. I won't trouble you any longer, Your Highness.
Brother, what did it say?
According to the edict, there are already 600 Jinwu Guards waiting outside Tianqi City.
Waiting outside of Tianqi City?
What is Father up to?
He ordered me to depart for Qiandong today.
I am to bring Baili Luochen, Marquis Zhenxi, back to Tianqi City.
Yao'er, whose letter was that?
My maidservant wrote to me that the emperor is summoning the Marquis to the palace.
He was branded with the crime of treason.
You mustn't go.
If I don't go, what should you do, then?
Father, I—
Dongjun, what are you doing here?
- Who is this lady?
- Grandfather, we can talk about that later.
- I heard that—
- Baili Dongjun, head back.
I won't.
I'll say this again. Head back.
Didn't you say I could come out once I defeated you?
Heir Apparent, today I'll show you the meaning of defeat.
Come, show me how much you've improved over the past year.
You transformed sound to sword energy.
That's right.
Miss, how should I address you?
My name is Yue Yao.
Yue Yao?
If so, who is Yue Fengcheng, the city lord of Beique City, to you?
He's my father.
I knew it.
To Beili, I'm a fugitive from Beique.
Marquis, will you capture me and hand me over to the emperor of Beili?
I'm too old for this. I don't care whether you're a fugitive or not.
As long as you're someone Dongjun likes and he brings you back,
you're part of this family.
Marquis.
Using zither as your weapon, huh?
It's an excellent technique indeed.
I've never seen such sword techniques before.
However, you lack training.
You should head back and train.
Is that so?
You brat.
Heir Apparent, what do you think?
You were taken by surprise by your Instant Kill Sword Arts.
Grandfather, I'll show Yao'er around.
Let's go.
He has grown up.
Look at that brat.
In the past, whenever you poured me the liquor you brewed, you would always show off.
But today, you've grown mature.
You've grown up.
Grandfather, if you wish to listen to my prattle, I should gladly oblige.
Dongjun, since you were young, your father kept you in check.
Your mother kept you in check.
The only person who spoiled you was me, your fearsome grandfather.
Do you know why?
It's because you don't want me to be like you and Father.
You don't want me to lead a tough life.
Grandfather, you wanted me to be carefree.
You're too intelligent.
Once we grow old, we'll think about the many things that we missed out
when we were young.
But I want my children and grandchildren, especially you, to have what I missed out on.
But Grandfather, there are two different ways to be carefree.
They're different.
How are they different?
I love to be carefree indeed.
But not as a carefree noble heir of the Marquis.
I want to be a carefree martial artist.
- A martial artist?
- Yes.
I want to draw my sword for my friends, for love, and for injustice.
Although I'm carefree, I still have a sense of duty.
Although I don't obey the rules, I have my own principles.
Grandfather, now, the Baili Family is in trouble.
And I, your grandson, am ready to face the trial.
Come.
Sir, do you want to buy some?
Please take a look.
Have you heard? The Marquis Zhenxi has plotted a rebellion.
That's impossible.
Of all the times to do it, why would he do it when the state is this peaceful?
You're right.
Thank you, Miss Yi.
Elder Wang You.
Elder, do you need anything from us?
It's nothing major.
Miss Yi has been here for some time.
I happened to descend the mountain, so I came to check on both of you.
Thank you for your concern.
Since both of you are doing well, I shall take my leave, then.
Wait, Elder.
What's the matter, Brother Yun?
To be honest,
I heard people saying that the Marquis Zhenxi has plotted a rebellion.
His Majesty has sent an envoy to capture him in Qiandong.
Elder, is that true?
That's right.
The rumor I heard was incomplete. Elder, can you tell me the details?
I don't know the details either.
I can only make assumptions.
The Marquis Zhenxi has long been stationed in the state's west.
He has a strong foundation there.
And it's very far from Tianqi City.
The emperor wishes to intervene, yet his reach is limited.
Over time, he became a thorn in the emperor's flesh.
And regarding Miss Yi's escape from Tianqi City,
although Prince Jingyu's Mansion has suppressed the news
and prevented them from reaching the people,
those who are keeping Prince Jingyu and Prince Langya under surveillance,
right under His Majesty's nose, will definitely find out if they want to.
This event gave those who harbored sinister intentions an opportunity to act.
They could twist the facts and influence the emperor
by saying that the Marquis Zhenxi played a role in her escape.
It must be Prince Qing.
It's all because of me.
Miss Yi, don't blame yourself too much.
Even if you hadn't escaped,
they would still find other excuses to topple Marquis Zhenxi.
Moreover, that was just my assumption.
It might not be accurate.
Elder Wang You is right.
Wenjun, don't blame yourself for this.
If so, I shall take my leave first.
- Thank you, Elder.
I suppose you've made up your mind.
Yes.
Actually, I've made up my mind when I heard the news.
But everyone in Tianqi City is out to get you.
There are plenty of people in Tianqi City whom I wish to kill as well.
You mustn't be impulsive.
Don't worry.
I'm only heading to Tianqi to help Marquis Zhenxi overcome this ordeal.
As for Prince Qing, as long as Marquis Zhenxi is fine,
he'll be utterly useless.
All right.
Wenjun, since I'll be heading to Tianqi,
do you need me to accomplish anything for you?
Wenjun?
Wenjun, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Well, Brother Yun,
if you see Senior when you're back there, please send my regards to him.
All right.
The imperial edict has arrived!
Marquis, the imperial edict has arrived.
Such audacity! Why aren't you kneeling upon seeing the imperial edict?
You should head back to Tianqi and ask the one who drafted the edict why I'm not kneeling.
Why haven't you withdrawn yet?
The Marquis Zhenxi has rendered countless military merits. He received His Majesty's grace a decade ago.
He may bring his sword with him to the palace and not kneel in front of His Majesty.
What do you know at your age?
- Even so, his son still needs to kneel.
- Shut up!
So, it's you, Eunuch Cheng. It's been a long time since we met.
Years ago, I had the honor of making your acquaintance on several occasions.
I never expected you to still remember me. I'm honored.
Qiandong City is located in a remote region. It's very far from Tianqi.
As I recall, I haven't received an imperial edict in ages.
Eunuch Cheng, I'm sure the imperial edict is heavy to hold.
You may announce it.
Yes, Marquis.
By the Mandate of Heaven, the Emperor decrees:
The Imperial Censorate has submitted a memorial accusing Baili Luochen, the Marquis Zhenxi,
of conspiring with traitors and attempting to rebel. This is a grave act of treason.
Considering his past contributions in quelling the rebellions, he is not to be detained at this time.
Effective immediately, he is to follow the envoy to the capital for trial.
Thus ordered.
Excellent. Interesting.
This is interesting indeed.
Captain, which army is this?
How dare they ride their horses in Qiandong City?
It's the divine bird flag. They're the Jinwu Guards.
Marquis, you should receive the edict.
Father, should we receive it?
Eunuch Cheng, what did he mean by that?
If they don't, does that mean they're going to start a rebellion?
If so, can we still leave this place alive?
Chengfeng.
Receive the edict.
The Marquis Zhenxi thinks he's a big shot, huh?
We're envoys from Tianqi. How dare he make us wait this long?
Even if he ignores the fact that we're envoys of Tianqi,
Baili Luochen should come out and receive you, the Seventh Prince.
Silence.
He's a marquis. Why is he wearing a red robe?
Is he in a hurry to be married off?
The Marquis Zhenxi had plenty of nicknames back then,
his most notable ones being "God Killer", and "Bloody Robe Marquis".
When he's wearing his red robe, it means he doesn't wish to kill.
Of course, he doesn't mind dealing with small fries either.
Smart people wouldn't want to offend him when he's in this state.
We're envoys of Tianqi. Don't tell me he dares kill us?
I've heard that the Jinwu Guards were a bunch of useless fools.
Now that I'm seeing you all in person, the rumors are certainly true.
Marquis Zhenxi.
Prince Langya, let's talk inside.
Your Highness, I still remember that my son
had a pleasant chat with you
in Tianqi over a year ago.
I never expected things to end up like this.
The imperial court and its situation are ever-changing.
Your Highness, last time you took my son away from me here.
This time, you're going to take my father away.
Last time, I returned your son to you in one piece after bringing him home.
This time, I'll surely do my best as well, as long as the Marquis Zhenxi didn't do it.
If I had done it, Your Highness, you would have been dead by now.
Marquis Zhenxi, when do you plan to depart?
Tomorrow.
Thank you, Marquis Zhenxi.
Brother Yun.
This will be a perilous trip.
Don't worry. Just wait at home.
If you need anything, go find Elder Wang You.
Take good care of yourself. I'll return soon.
Take care.
Wait for my return.
I assume Prince Langya has received Marquis Zhenxi by now.
Excellent.
This time, I'll make sure that old Marquis Zhenxi
and that despicable Baili Dongjun stay here forever.
♫  A gentle breeze intentionally stirs the heart  ♫
♫  Moored by the lake, ripples spread, feet covered with spring mud  ♫
♫  The branches softly whisper secrets in the wind  ♫
♫  In the moonlit night, I trace the outlines of your unfinished story  ♫
♫  As if destined by fate, I gaze upon your quietly graceful figure  ♫
♫  Restlessly searching for you  ♫
♫  I'll follow you until sunset and late afternoon sunshine  ♫
♫  Listening intently to the soft drizzle, accompanied by a lone shadow  ♫
♫  Who am I with at this moment?  ♫
♫  Roaming the world together in harmony  ♫
♫  Two hearts cherishing each other  ♫
♫  A red letter becomes a boat navigating our love  ♫
♫  A folding fan sways among the stars and clouds  ♫
♫  In this perfect moment  ♫
♫  I met you  ♫
♫  A gentle breeze intentionally stirs the heart  ♫
♫  Moored by the lake, ripples spread, feet covered with spring mud  ♫
♫  The branches softly whisper secrets in the wind  ♫
♫  In the moonlit night, I trace the outlines of your unfinished story  ♫
♫  As if destined by fate, I gaze upon your quietly graceful figure  ♫
♫  Restlessly searching for you  ♫
♫  I'll follow you until sunset and late afternoon sunshine  ♫
♫  Listening intently to the soft drizzle, accompanied by a lone shadow  ♫
♫  Who am I with at this moment?  ♫
♫  Roaming the world together in harmony  ♫
♫  Two hearts cherishing each other  ♫
♫  A red letter becomes a boat navigating our love  ♫
♫  A folding fan sways among the stars and clouds  ♫
♫  In this perfect moment  ♫
♫  I met you  ♫