♫  Overcoming self-doubt and finding purpose  ♫
♫  Enduring the trials of life and death  ♫
♫  As I gaze into the dark night  ♫
♫  My spirit has not been broken  ♫
♫  And unleash this passion  ♫
♫  My spirit will only grow stronger  ♫
♫  Splitting mountains and parting seas  ♫
♫  Answering the sword's call and entering the Martial World  ♫
♫  I'm the chosen one, fate in this turbulent world  ♫
♫  Keeping my distance from the world  ♫
♫  Who can understand my loneliness?  ♫
♫  A single thought, gazing down  ♫
♫  With swords drawn, frost flies through the air  ♫
♫  With faith that conquers the world with one strike  ♫
♫  Soaring through the sky, the sword reigns everywhere  ♫
♫  Breaking through the waves, dancing drunkenly everywhere  ♫
♫  Protecting the people, no matter the cost  ♫
♫  Atop the peak, you and I shall battle all out  ♫
What a bunch of weirdos.
You're awake? Come and have breakfast.
What happened to me?
What happened to you?
You passed out a few days ago. My uncle saved you.
You're lucky to know me.
My uncle doesn't save just anyone.
Why is Little Thing still here?
Do you have a death wish?
My cuties.
Come. Come over here.
Be good. Be good.
Uncle. That's kind of disgusting.
These disgusting things saved his life.
I...
Thank you, Sir. Have I recovered?
No. You... have been poisoned by me.
- What?
The reason I don't always save people
is because I use poison to combat poison.
To suppress your old injuries, I gave you the Gut-Shattering Five Poisons.
But I don't have an antidote.
Wait. Then what do we do?
He can't just die.
Go to the place marked on the map and look for someone called Xin Baicao.
I claim that no one can escape my poison,
while this fellow claims to cure any poison in this world.
Go and show him your poisoned body.
Naturally, he'll know I sent you there.
He'll do his best to cure you to prove he's better than me.
Once the poison is gone and your old injuries flare up,
he'll think it's a trick of mine and will save you again.
Does... Xin Baicao, the King of Medicine, really exist?
Can he... really heal Changfeng?
How would I know?
I poison others.
I'm not a physician.
Go on now. You have 10 days left.
10 days?
After that, the Gut-Breaking Five Poisons will take effect and you'll be dead in less than four hours.
It starts eroding your guts. It's excruciating.
Thank you, Senior.
No need to thank me. Your life is still at risk.
I'm better. I used to think I'd die quietly on an unfamiliar road.
Who would've thought that Heaven would show me mercy.
To have met so many heroes before my life ends.
Even if I die now, it's worth it.
Sikong Changfeng, my uncle went to great lengths to bring you back to life.
Don't jinx yourself. Stay alive and wait for our next encounter in the Martial World.
You're right. I must stay alive.
With a steed, a spear, and a pot of liquor, I'll roam around freely.
You too. Go further, see more of the Martial World,
and fulfill your promise to the girl you like.
Of course.
Take this.
Until next time.
Stay alive, Sikong Changfeng!
He's the type who should die honorably in the Martial World.
Uncle, do you think I should die honorably in the Martial World?
What are you talking about?! Of course not!
Quick, peh, peh!
(TN: word to ward off bad luck after a curse)
Peh, peh? Then how will I end up?
You'll die pathetically from your parents spanking you.
Uncle, let's make a deal.
- No.
- I haven't said anything yet.
Let's go!
Ye Xiaofan, it's time for lunch!
So noisy.
What do we have today?
Quit touching my head.
My sister said I can't grow tall if you keep touching my head.
She's lying to you. I can examine bones.
- I can tell you won't grow tall, it doesn't matter if I touch you or not.
- Peh, peh, peh!
If you say that again, your big bun will become mine.
You sleep all day and don't find a proper job. You won't get a wife in the future.
Little brat, you talk like a mother.
Is getting a proper job that important?
Of course, it is!
Fine, then. I'll do what you say.
It seems it's time to find a proper job.
However, I'm afraid this job can't be found in the village.
It's time to leave.
You have to return to Qiandong City.
If not, your mother will poison me.
Can mother's poison beat yours? I doubt it.
I can't stand it when she acts spoiled.
It's not that I won't go back.
I just want you to show me around the Martial World on our way back.
Not doing it. No time.
You're not busy. Why not?
Not busy?
I'm the Bodhisattva of Poison! I'm busy!
Besides, after four years, the Forest of Swords is about to start.
I don't want to miss it.
Forest of Swords? What's that?
It seems you're in a hurry. Is it a great assembly?
Swordsmen from all over the Martial World wait in the wings for four years
just for the opening of the Forest of Swords.
Tell me, doesn't that sound grand?
Uncle, you dote on me the most.
You're the best.
I'll brew some liquor for you.
Go away. Save it.
Let me ask you this. Has your mother taught you any martial arts skills?
No. But she got me a master to teach me fist techniques.
That's enough. Come back.
What master?
His name is something like Wangba?
- Yes, it's an interesting name.
- Oh.
Wang Batian, the Fist Conqueror?
Right, right, him.
He's someone to be reckoned with.
Exactly. My mother thought he could teach me well.
He was working so hard, so I treated him to some liquor.
He said he had never had such a wonderful brew in his life.
Then I told him he could drink it every day as long as he stopped teaching me.
So, my mother drove him away three days later.
Did you have other masters?
Later she thought male masters were unreliable, so she found a female master.
She was so beautiful. I still remember her name.
Su Muqing.
Miss Su? She's indeed pretty.
Not only that, she taught me diligently for three days.
- Luckily, it was only three days.
- Why's that?
Because my father came to my backyard for three consecutive days.
You can imagine what happened.
You only learned superficial skills.
So, what are you actually good at?
Look at me.
What do you think?
Even you think that's terrible, right? Let's go.
Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle. Where are you going?
Back to Qiandong City. That route is shorter.
You can't be serious.
That wasn't amazing?
Wasn't that your father's qinggong technique, Three Flying Cat Moves.
Three Flying Cat Moves? It's Three Flying Swallow Moves.
Don't underestimate this. It's a great fleeing skill.
Don't go, Uncle.
I was being mischievous before, but I've changed now.
I swear, I'm serious this time.
It's true, I didn't like practicing martial art skills before.
First, I thought fighting was boring.
Second, as you know, General Ye and Brother Yun have died.
Grandfather didn't want me to suffer the Ye Family's fate.
However, when I encountered the Eight Young Masters of Beili,
and witnessed that bloodshed...
I asked myself whether I could protect my friend when he was in danger.
Could I be like the Eight Young Masters of Beili, draw my weapon, and fight alongside him?
Uncle.
Who do you admire the most in the Martial World?
Needless to say, it's Mister Li.
Which Mister Li are you referring to?
Speaking of Mister Li, it must be that person.
The One-Sword Deity, Mister Li.
When I was 19, I was fortunate to witness with my own eyes
the Darting Sword From Beyond in Tianqi City.
Five invincible swordsmen from Nanjue challenged Mister Li to a duel.
They planned to tire him out by fighting one after another.
However, Mister Li defeated them with only one sword.
From that day forward, no one from Nanjue ever challenged someone from Beili to a sword fight.
Naturally, Mister Li triumphed in the Martial Rankings that year.
Unexpectedly, he tore the Martial Ranking apart.
"The lowly Martial Ranking isn't entitled to judge a deity."
So cool. No wonder people said Beili wield swords while Nanjue hold blades.
Turns out they don't dare practice swordsmanship anymore.
Everyone in Beili practices swordsmanship.
I learned it when I was young.
You did? Don't you practice poisons?
I applied poison to the sword.
What? Have a problem with that?
No.
All right. I've made up my mind.
I want to practice swordsmanship.
You practice swordsmanship? Do you even have a sword?
Forest of Swords. How can I not find one there?
I see. I didn't see this coming.
Xiao Baili.
All right. It's time to get you a fine sword.
Really, Uncle?
Uncle, you've grown more important to me than my father.
Like you respect him much to begin with.
You can't say that.
Mount up. Let's hit the road.
Xiao Baili, keep up!
Coming!
What? Didn't you ask me to get a proper job?
Now that I'm going, why the long face?
I'm not. You're wrong.
It's true. You're capable and can become a military officer in town
and earn enough to buy noodles every day.
Then all the village elders will love you
and bring their daughters to propose marriage.
You can choose the prettiest girl and marry her.
By the way, Ye Xiaofan, who do you think is the prettiest girl in the village?
Maybe Madam Chen. She's elegant and graceful, plump too.
I'm saying a girl. Madam Chen isn't a girl anymore.
She's married.
You choose one for me then.
What do you think of my sister?
All the teachers in the village say that my sister will become a beauty.
Do you know what "will become a beauty" means?
What does that mean?
It means she isn't yet a beauty.
- Besides, I'm engaged.
- Oh.
What? You're engaged? When did that happen?
It was when I was little that we got engaged.
I'm of age now, yet I'm still wandering outside.
I wonder if she... has met someone else already.
Why don't you go and find her?
I will.
It'll be after I finish what I need to do first.
Very soon.
All right, stop here.
Ye Xiaofan, though you're only going to a nearby city.
You're leaving the village, after all.
You should have one the last meal with everyone, and bid farewell.
I'm not going to a nearby city.
Not a nearby city? Where are you going?
I'm heading somewhere I've been wanting to go, to retrieve something.
After that, I'll go to a place I must go.
A place you must go? Where is that?
A faraway city called Tianqi.
Tianqi? Isn't that the capital of Beili?
It's a great distance away. I've only read about it in books.
Ye Xiaofan, why are you going there?
I'm going to Tianqi to achieve something big.
Perhaps I might meet a long-lost friend there, and her.
Ye Xiaofan, what are you thinking about?
How about this?
Stop calling me Ye Xiaofan from now on.
Call me Ye Dingzhi.
Ye Dingzhi? Why this name?
Because I want...
to wander the Martial World with my sword, and challenge Tianqi.
Practice the sword techniques I taught you.
After a few years, you'll be able to protect the village.
Ye Xiaofan, don't go yet!
How will I find you later?
When I become famous, and you enter the Martial World,
tell everyone your name is Ye Xiaofan, and I'll come to you!
All right!
Fragrance sachets for sale!
As expected of Shenjian Town.
(TN: means Divine Swords Town)
Everyone here holds a sword.
Even a dog has one.
Uncle, could this be the legendary sword dog?
(TN: 'sword' and 'nasty' are homophones)
No name-calling.
Sorry about that.
A sword dog?
Uncle, you still haven't explained what the Forest of Swords really is.
Forest of Swords, as its name implies, gathers swords to form a forest.
At first, there were swordsmen thrusting swords into this land where the Sword Deity perished
to show their resolution in swordsmanship.
Later, whenever a famous sword is forged, or an elite swordsman perishes,
the new swords and the deceased masters' swords would be kept in the Forest of Swords
to await the fated one to claim them every four years.
Why does... this person look so familiar?
What an aroma.
Mister, what liquor is this?
Sword Liquor.
How can you come to the Forest of Swords and not taste Sword Liquor?
Sword Liquor?
Mister, fill it up.
All right!
Xiao Baili, you only introduced your martial arts masters.
Why don't you tell me something about your brewing master?
I didn't need someone to teach me that.
This is a natural talent, you know?
Coming! Sirs, your liquor.
Please enjoy.
That's intense. It cuts my tongue like a sharp blade.
It truly lives up to its name. Nice brew.
Don't drink too much. You'll get drunk.
Uncle, we've been walking for a long time.
I still see no end to this forest.
It's becoming foggy too.
Uncle.
Uncle?
- Uncle.
- This is Qimen Dunjia Arts.
It's the outside area around the Forest of Swords that's accessible on regular days.
But here is the place, which opens only every four years, the Forest of Swords.
How magnificent.
Two great sects forge swords, Sword Heart Tomb and Famous Swords Manor.
It seems Famous Swords Manor
is in charge this year.
Speaking of which, you have connections with Sword Heart Tomb.
What connections? Why didn't I didn't know?
Lei Mengsha's wife is Sword Heart Tomb's Master, Li Suwang's daughter,
Li Xinyue, the heir to the Heart Sword.
The Martial World is big, yet small too.
Since all of you came here to claim swords, I won't keep you waiting.
Please play the music.
The first-level sword is the Mountain Sword.
Everyone, you may start.
Uncle, shall we?
Not yet.
There are four sword levels.
First, the Mountain.
As high as a mountain, a place ordinary swords can't reach.
Second, the Ocean.
All rivers converge into the boundless ocean.
Only by merging one hundred Mountain swords can you form one of these.
The Ocean swords. Everyone, please.
Third level, Cloud Sky.
Above the ocean, soaring in the clouds, the Nine Heavens overlook all things.
Only one in every 10,000 swords is one.
Fourth level, Celestial.
Beyond the Nine Heavens, a celestial palace resides.
It's truly a sword from beyond.
Whether or not it will emerge in the Forest of Swords depends on your luck.
If so...
Given my swordsmanship skills, claiming an Ocean one isn't a problem.
You should at least get a Cloud Sky sword.
In that case, I need to use poison.
See any sword you like?
I only know Cloud Sky lies above Ocean, and a Celestial one ranks highest of all.
Needless to say, I want the best sword. Otherwise, how else can I gain fame?
Well said.
Who are you?
I'm Wang Yixing from Mount Wangcheng.
Lu Suzhen's disciple.
Setting aside whether he's eloquent or not,
his naive ambition to rise to fame keeps making it difficult for me.
Mister Wen, with all due respect, he should claim the sword himself.
Mister, what did you say? Who's claiming the sword?
I'm saying that it's better if you claim the sword yourself.
Look at him. I'm sure he'll get beat up in two or three strikes.
Are we really going to return empty-handed?
Don't worry yet, Mister Wen.
I think this young man might get a fine sword.
- Bravo!
You aren't drunk, are you?
The Mountain sword and the Ocean sword have all found their owners.
The next sword is of Cloud Sky level.
I named it Divine Fire.
It's a shard of the fiery sword, Grand Mysterious Sun, used by the Kunlun Sword Deity in battle.
To be more precise, it's born out of the Grand Mysterious Sun.
It belonged to the Celestial Palace, but fell from the Nine Heavens.
What a waste.
- I'm down.
- Me too.
I'm coming!
Hands off my sword.
Didn't you call it a waste? You hypocrite.
It depends on who owns the sword.
Swords have no levels, it's their owners that determine their value.
Why is the sword... flying?
This is the Sword Wielding Arts from Mount Wangcheng.
Not just wielding arts, it also contains Mount Wangcheng's secret technique.
With such cultivation at this age, he must be the top among all current disciples.
You truly are drunk.
This is Sword Liquor. It's different from ordinary liquor.
Mount Wancheng's Leader, Lu Suzhen's principal disciple, Wang Yixing, will claim this sword.
Everyone.
This is the only Cloud Sky level sword. Why isn't Wushuang City involved?
Could it be...
I'm not interested in swords of a higher level.
This sword is a perfect gift for my junior brother.
Everyone, thank you.
He mentioned "swords of a higher level."
Exactly. Wushuang City hasn't moved yet.
Is there really a fourth-level sword?
The fourth level, Celestial Level Sword.
Celestial being, please grant me this sword from beyond.
Xiao Baili, look. Celestial.
It smells great.
It's the fragrance of lotus.
I forged this sword and named it Dustless.
I ask for a peerless gentleman to come claim it.
Hopefully, this fine gentleman will journey the world with this sword
and let it triumph in the Record of Famous Swords.
This is a great sword. I want it!
You fool. Do you want your uncle, who uses poison, to be surrounded by all the swordsmen?
I, Song Yanhui of Wushuang City, wish to claim this sword.
Who will be my rival?
Who would dare compete with Wushuang City?
I will.
Who is he?
You are...
Ye Dingzhi.
Ye Dingzhi?
I've never heard of this name.
He's probably some rash young man. He dares challenge Wushuang City?
This time, I bet he'll die here.
This guy... looks... like...
I can't recall it at all.
Such agility.
A natural swordsman.
You're indeed strong.
But I am stronger.
Uncle, are they powerful?
Given what they've shown, they're both in the Hard Phase of Mortals.
However, the difference is that the man from Wushuang City
is already out of his depth,
while Ye Dingzhi hasn't fully exerted his strength.
He possesses such strength at this young age. That's not easy.
-  Wushuang City actually lost.
-  Unbelievable.
How did this happen?
I concede defeat.
Thank you.
Hold on!
Xiao Baili!
I... want that sword too!
May I ask your name?
Baili Dongjun.
Baili Dongjun?
Do we... know each other?
No.
We don't.
Then why did you...
You want to claim the sword, right? But where's yours?
My...
Right.
Mister, I'll lend you this one.
Such an embarrassment. What a disgrace.
I have one now.
He's just as silly as before.
Hold on. I remember it now.
Why do I-I think you look familiar?
Baili Dongjun, are you trying to cozy up to me?
You came to the wrong place.
He's incredible.
Are you not drawing your sword?
I don't know any sword techniques.
Young man, come down. Just surrender!
-  Exactly.
- Exactly.
Just quit and come down.
Don't get hurt. Stop fighting.
It seems that you're no match for me.
This fool must be slacking off during practice like he did back then.
Sword?
Can I... wield a sword?
Master, is this another illusion of yours?
No, this is a sword technique.
Pay attention. I'll only demonstrate once.
I have an unrivaled sword technique.
Why is it unrivaled?
On this earth, from past to future,
no one with this technique will ever emerge again.
If someone does, it will only be from the Baili Family.
I have recalled it.
I know swordsmanship.
That's...
♫  Overcoming self-doubt and finding purpose  ♫
♫  Enduring the trials of life and death  ♫
♫  As I gaze into the dark night  ♫
♫  My spirit has not been broken  ♫
♫  And unleash this passion  ♫
♫  My spirit will only grow stronger  ♫
♫  Splitting mountains and parting seas  ♫
♫  Answering the sword's call and entering the Martial World  ♫
Xichu's Sword Song.
This truly is Xichu's Sword Song.
It truly lives up to its reputation.
How carefree and spontaneous.
Words has it that it only consists of three moves.
I was fortunate to witness it once.
It was exactly the same as Mister Baili's.
♫  Soaring through the sky, the sword reigns everywhere  ♫
But his moves are complete.
How does Baili know Xichu's Sword Song?
♫  Atop the peak, you and I shall battle all out  ♫
I remember everything now.
Sword Song.
But why are there only sword moves and no song?
It's a shame that the singer is already dead,
leaving only the sword moves, Heaven's Path.
Back then, Gu Chen, the Scholar Deity of Xichu sung
and Gu Mo, the Sword Deity, wielded his sword.
In Xichy's last city, at the gate of Luosang City
with a sword and a song, they battled 9,000 Pofeng soldiers until their very last breath.
Finally, Luosang was raided and Xichu was brought down.
This complete sword technique became a lost art.
That's my nephew.
My nephew.
I didn't expect that Marquis Zhenxi's Mansion
would be much bolder than I imagined.
I thought I only came here for a sword and to gain fame.
Never imagining,
I'd meet you and such an interesting sword technique.
Liquor. Where's my liquor?
Catch!
It must be a fine brew.
You enjoy it so much.
Friend, lend me your liquor.
- Cheers!
Awesome!
Across the Nine Heavens, I travel on my sword.
There's indeed a song.
Going afar, never to return.
Amidst the clouds I sing in wild jubilation.
Drinking from 30,000 jars.
I bear a free spirit within and here ends my song.
♫  A gentle breeze intentionally stirs the heart  ♫
♫  Moored by the lake, ripples spread, feet covered with spring mud  ♫
♫  The branches softly whisper secrets in the wind  ♫
♫  In the moonlit night, I trace the outlines of your unfinished story  ♫
♫  As if destined by fate, I gaze upon your quietly graceful figure  ♫
♫  Restlessly searching for you  ♫
♫  I'll follow you until sunset and late afternoon sunshine  ♫
♫  Listening intently to the soft drizzle, accompanied by a lone shadow  ♫
♫  Who am I with at this moment?  ♫
♫  Roaming the world together in harmony  ♫
♫  Two hearts cherishing each other  ♫
♫  A red letter becomes a boat navigating our love  ♫
♫  A folding fan sways among the stars and clouds  ♫
♫  In this perfect moment  ♫
♫  I met you  ♫
♫  A gentle breeze intentionally stirs the heart  ♫
♫  Moored by the lake, ripples spread, feet covered with spring mud  ♫
♫  The branches softly whisper secrets in the wind  ♫
♫  In the moonlit night, I trace the outlines of your unfinished story  ♫
♫  As if destined by fate, I gaze upon your quietly graceful figure  ♫
♫  Restlessly searching for you  ♫
♫  I'll follow you until sunset and late afternoon sunshine  ♫
♫  Listening intently to the soft drizzle, accompanied by a lone shadow  ♫
♫  Who am I with at this moment?  ♫
♫  Roaming the world together in harmony  ♫
♫  Two hearts cherishing each other  ♫
♫  A red letter becomes a boat navigating our love  ♫
♫  A folding fan sways among the stars and clouds  ♫
♫  In this perfect moment  ♫
♫  I met you  ♫