♪Overcoming the boundary of confusion♪
♪Holding onto my life
in the face of death threats♪
♪I look into this dark night♪
♪Never once has my soul
been extinguished♪
♪With this passion♪
♪My spirit is growing
to reach full swing♪
♪Slashing the mountain
and the ocean apart♪
♪Answering the true call on a sword♪
♪I'm the chosen one
in this turbulent world♪
♪Keep my distance from the world♪
♪Who can understand my loneliness♪
♪A single thought, looking down♪
♪Blades unsheathed,
frost flies everywhere♪
♪A belief that cuts through the world♪
♪Soaring towards the sky,
the sword reigns all♪
♪Striding across the land
with a drunken gait♪
♪I will protect the people
whenever I'm needed♪
♪Atop the summit, you and I shall
battle for the world's best♪
[Directed by Chen Zhoufei]
[Dashing Youth]
[Based on "Zhou Munan's
Juvenile Martial Arts Series"]
[from fanqienovel.com and bkneng.com]
[Episode 20]
Ye,
do you still remember what I said
before we embarked on this journey?
Which sentence exactly?
Observe every strike I make carefully,
except for the last strike.
Otherwise,
it'd all go to waste.
I don't want to miss that strike.
My silly disciple.
Amid the trickling rain
and ethereal fog,
here I come treading on water.
[Yan Lingxia,
The Blade Deity of Nanjue]
Rain Demon.
You're here after all.
Chunshui,
what kind of person
is the Rain Demon like?
Is he going
to lead Yun astray?
During our journey,
I've heard a bunch
of martial artists talking about
how he's traveling to Nanjue with Yun.
The Rain Demon
had a nickname when he was young,
the Rain Maniac,
because he was maniacal and arrogant.
During his younger days
roaming the martial arts world,
he had defeated many people
who were actually stronger than him,
simply because he was a maniac.
Unfortunately,
he would eventually
encounter Li Changsheng.
And what kind of person
was Li Changsheng like?
He's far more maniacal and arrogant
than the Rain Demon was.
Can you stop flattering yourself
in such an obnoxiously indirect way?
You rascal.
Am I flattering myself?
I'm flattering Li Changsheng.
As I said,
in this life, I want to be
a genteel scholar,
an elegant young man.
I shall steer clear of worldly affairs
and I shall only
appreciate beautiful ladies.
You're over 180 years old,
and you're thinking
of appreciating beautiful ladies?
You're too old to do that.
Chunshui.
The Rain Demon
used to be a handsome man.
But when he was mastering
the Demon Deity Sword Techniques,
something happened,
and he turned into a beautiful woman.
See?
Unlike you,
he doesn't care much
about romantic affairs.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
traveled all the way
to kill Yan Lingxia.
Chunshui.
What's the deal about Yan Lingxia?
Beautiful.
She's beautiful.
You really don't care if it's too old
to appreciate beautiful ladies.
Five li from here
is a town
called Qianyue Town.
We'll spend the night there.
Rain Demon,
we shouldn't have met today.
What a nag.
Master, do you think
the Rain Demon
is any match for Yan Lingxia?
I can't say for certain.
I thought you knew everything.
What are you uncertain about?
If he's doing this for himself,
I guess they'd probably
end the fight in a draw.
But, if he's doing this
for someone else...
You mean for Yun?
The Rain Demon
may be called a demon,
but to me,
compared to most people, he's...
He's what?
Kinder than anyone else.
I have lost,
but you're about to die.
You shouldn't have gone all out
just to pursue a title
as useless
as the top martial artist of Nanjue.
I have never sought for such a title,
even if the whole world
believes otherwise.
Let them believe what they want, then.
Ye.
I told you not to watch my last strike,
but...
You saw it, didn't you?
Master.
Ye,
don't be sad.
Don't avenge me either.
I have been practicing
the demonic art for so many years,
and my health
has already almost depleted.
Even if I don't die today,
I'd have less than six months to live.
Throughout this journey,
I have launched 13 strikes.
Every strike
has been a lesson for you.
As your master...
this is
all I can do for you.
Ye.
I didn't want you
to see the final strike
because I hoped you wouldn't
follow in my footsteps.
But...
Since you saw it,
you will have to bear
the legacy of my sword fighting.
I have left you a letter.
There's an address on it.
Head to the address.
Master.
I have left a present for you.
Thank you, Master.
There's an old geezer in the north
that I have never been able to defeat.
Make sure you train hard
and defeat his disciple.
I will remember that.
I shall not
disappoint you.
Farewell,
Ye.
No one knows where I, the Rain Demon,
comes from.
I also do not wish for anyone to know
where my final resting spot is.
Master!
Chunshui,
what are you looking?
I can sense
an old friend departing somewhere.
Not bad.
You can already take three hits from me.
Sikong Changfeng, let's talk.
Sure.
All this time,
I've been meaning to ask you this.
Baili Dongjun
is from the Marquis's Mansion
and he has a noble status.
His father is the Marquis's son
and his mother is
the young lady of the Wen Family.
Right now, he's also
a disciple of Li Changsheng,
the top martial artist.
He's lucky to have a good life,
but you
have been wandering since young,
without a place to call home.
Usually,
a rich kid like him
would be someone that you'd detest,
but why are you friends with him?
When I met him,
I didn't even know
he was from the Marquis's Mansion.
Back then, all I thought was
that we happened to meet by chance,
and it's good to travel
around the martial arts world
together.
Even after
I knew that he's from
the Marquis's Mansion,
I realized
that even someone
from the Marquis's Mansion
could be like him.
Like how?
I have seen
many people from noble families.
Most of them
may look decent outside,
but they have a dirty heart.
But Baili Dongjun is different.
His heart is as pure
as a youth's.
Nice answer.
Moreover,
I think that both of us
are of the same kind.
He's lucky to have a good life while I'm
lucky to not get killed easily.
He and I
will reach our end goals eventually.
That's a marvelous answer.
We've been training for several days
and you've probably heard some rumors
that I might take you in as my disciple.
Wait, sir.
Those are just rumors.
I'm already glad that you're willing
to give me a few pointers.
I wouldn't dare to dream
of becoming your disciple.
I will not take you in as my disciple.
Because I'm not qualified.
There's someone
far more formidable than me
who wants to take you in
as his disciple,
but it's not the right time yet.
That day will come soon, though.
He's also waiting
to meet you again
somewhere in this martial arts world.
Meet me again?
Life is like a dream.
Meetings and partings come and go.
Are you leaving already, Mr. Xie?
As we have met, so must we part.
I have finished reading,
so I have to go.
Sikong,
I hope we can also
meet again somewhere.
Martial Uncle.
Sir,
I think it's also time for me to go.
When are you leaving?
Right now, then.
You're so eager to leave, too?
Since I feel like venturing now,
why not?
It's a big world outside.
May we meet again, sir.
I'm off!
This martial arts world remains the same
because of these youths
that continue to come
generation after generation.
We're here.
This is it.
[Qianyue Smithy]
Chunshui.
Have you been here before?
What do you need? A hoe, a spade
or a plough?
A blade.
A good one.
Who are you?
An old friend.
What's your name?
Nangong Chunshui.
Your surname isn't Li?
You look exactly the same
as that man when he was young.
You're not his son?
Why?
Does he look like
a playboy to you?
Of course.
That pompous brat.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he's got a bunch of grandchildren.
Pompous brat.
Hush.
That's not nice of you
to describe an old friend like that.
Well, don't just stand there.
Come in and we'll talk.
So,
who are you?
I'm Baili Dongjun,
a disciple of Mr. Li from the Academy.
I'm Yin Luoxia,
Mr. Liu Yue's disciple.
Liu Yue's disciple?
No wonder you look so pretty.
As for you,
you look like
a mediocre martial artist,
but you have a nice sword.
So we've got
two random boys
and a lass in the Sturdy Phase.
How bold is he
to let you guys
approach me like this?
I wonder how powerful
you are
to look down on those
in the Sturdy Phase?
I'm not looking down
on those in the Sturdy Phase.
I'm just looking down
on you.
That's because
I'm also in the Sturdy Phase.
Kid,
if you want to provoke me,
[Luo Sheng, The Military Deity]
try again in another 30 years.
You're the one who's provoking me.
Dongjun,
this is the man I told you about.
He's one of the top three
weapon makers,
Luo Sheng, the Military Deity.
Sir.
Those herbs are exceptionally rare.
Do keep them properly.
Also, please send
my master's regards to Mr. Xin.
Rest assured.
These herbs
concern
both the patient from the Mu Family
and my life.
Thank you, sir.
I'm off.
Safe journeys.
[Qiulu Apothecary]
Check these.
Do come again.
[Baihua Pleasure House]
I love the new score
that you're playing!
Come on!
Take this.
How long has it been
since you last came?
Come often.
We've missed you.
Should I see her?
My brother
could play this score as well.
I mistook you for him.
Actually,
I'd love to have a little sister.
You...
How dare you tease me time and again?
You may meet many people
throughout your life,
but only befriend a few.
I believe that true friends do exist.
Your guqin and my leaf
resonated together.
I will be back.
He's gone?
Linglong,
Mr. Sikong is back.
Miss.
He... He's back again.
[Baihua Pleasure House]
Mr. Sikong.
It's been a while.
What brought you here?
I...
Actually, I have been
thinking about you all this time,
but
I dared not bother you.
Then,
why do you come today?
I'm leaving Tianqi soon.
I'm here to bid you farewell.
Farewell?
We met by chance, after all.
You didn't have to come
to bid me farewell.
You flatter me.
I know
that to you,
I'm just
a nobody.
But to me,
you are special.
I have to leave now,
but I will be back
when I have truly
mastered spear techniques
and when I can truly
protect you.
Oh my.
How silly and naive of him.
Cut to the chase.
So, why are you here?
I'm sure Li Changsheng
is about to give me
a problematic task.
Mr. Li wants you
to forge a nice blade
for this young man here.
I won't.
I've just received
an important order,
and I've got no time for him.
How important is it?
Why don't you take a look
at what Mr. Li is offering you?
Well...
It's hers.
Mr. Li searched for it for a long time.
Kid,
you already have
a Celestial Level Sword,
and you still came here
to get a blade from me?
Looks like Li Changsheng
is ready to teach you
his ultimate moves.
What ultimate moves?
The Double-Handed Blade-Sword Technique.
That's right.
His Double-Handed Blade-Sword Technique
is forceful
yet elegant.
A perfect balance of light and heavy,
and it was invincible.
I see that your sword
is on the lighter side,
so I'll give you
a heavier blade.
Looks like Mr. Luo
has some leftover stock.
A few years ago,
someone gave me
a piece of meteoric ore.
I forged a sword and a blade with it.
That sword is meant
for the order I mentioned earlier.
As for the blade,
it needs to go
through the final forging stage
for another three days.
The one who placed that order
must be as important as Mr. Li.
And more decent, to add.
At least
that person came here
with real money,
instead of offering me
a piece of stone
for a mythical weapon
like that person did.
Remember,
don't disturb me
for the next three days.
Nice blade.
What's its name?
Unlike those fellows
from Swordheart Grave,
I disassociate myself
from the weapon
as soon as it is made.
Whatever name it is,
it's up to the owner to decide.
It's been so long,
and you still won't pass up a chance
to poke fun at Li Suwang
from Swordheart Grave.
I'm not.
I just don't like
his pretentious and genteel personality.
A sword is a sword.
What's the point of giving names
like that
"Listen to the Rain and Watch the Snow"
or "Smell the Wind
and Look at the Flowers".
Phooey!
How disgusting.
Fine,
since my sword is called Dustless,
I'll call my blade...
Maybe...
Unsullied by the dust
of the mortal world,
a pure heart lies beneath the cinders.
Why don't you call it Cinderless?
Alright, we'll call it Cinderless.
Good.
Now that you have a blade,
as Mr. Li said,
you can stop practicing
the 19 Embroidery Sword Techniques.
You can start practicing
the blade techniques.
What technique should I practice?
Take this.
[Five-Tiger Cliff Blade Technique]
Five-Tiger Cliff Blade Technique?
But, Mas...
But, Chunshui,
I've seen this technique before.
Even the guards at my home know this.
Don't underestimate this technique.
I had a friend
who used this...
He used this technique
and became famous, right?
You're making stories up again.
I don't believe you.
You can believe him
because the friend he was talking about
is me.
If you're not convinced,
why don't we have a spar?
Sure.
You believe me now, don't you?
You can use ordinary weapons
and ordinary techniques,
but the person who wields the weapon
must be more than ordinary.
Mr. Luo's
Five-Tiger Cliff Blade Technique
is actually weaker than Xiao Yi's
19 Embroidery Sword Techniques.
I understand.
I will train harder.
Good to see you being so humble.
Yun... Yun?
Yunyun?
Should I call you
Dongdongjun?
What brings you here?
To take my sword.
Is this
where Mr. Luo lives?
Who are you?
I'm Ye Dingzhi.
I have come to collect a sword
as my master's command
It's you.
Come, have a seat.
The sword is ready.
Your master has already paid for it,
so you can collect it anytime.
Thank you, Mr. Luo.
How is your master
doing lately?
Who are you?
I'm Nangong Chunshui.
Mr. Li has entrusted me
to bring Baili Dongjun here
to collect a blade.
Dongjun is here too?
He got wiped out
by Mr. Luo's
Five-Tiger Cliff Blade Technique,
and he's resting in there.
I'll see him tomorrow, then.
You haven't answered my question.
My master...
He has left.
Young man, you knew my master?
I guess
he was a good friend.
So you're the owner
of that sword.
What a coincidence.
What's its name?
And what's your blade's name?
It's called Cinderless.
I named it.
Then, I'll call my sword
Pavilion Moon.
Pavilion Moon?
Nice name.
Now, we have
matching weapons.
Alright, now that you're done talking,
it's time for us to leave.
Yun, want to join us?
I need to return to Nanjue
to handle my master's affairs.
I can tag along for a while, though.
Why?
Are you leaving?
Yes,
or else we won't make it in time.
Make it in time?
Make what in time?
Are we rushing
to go somewhere?
Why do I feel like you're not
rushing anywhere all this time?
We're not heading there directly.
We're stopping by somewhere
and it might take some of our time.
Where?
The Tang Sect.
Why are you going to the Tang Sect?
I've heard there's
a Poison Convention there,
so we're going to check it out.
I guess we're not
going to see each other again
in this lifetime.
Use your weapons
to their fullest.
Hopefully, one day,
I can hear legends of them
in this small town.
I wonder
where that kid is now.
When we received that letter
from the Ninth Prince,
I thought even the Academy
had enough of that troublemaker,
and had expelled him.
That made me happy for a while.
Our son
may be naughty on the surface,
but it's good for him
to follow Mr. Li
and travel around the world.
Well,
do you think
they'll pass by Qiandong City?
Probably not.
Mr. Li avoids trouble like the plague,
and meeting
the famous Marquis of Zhenxi
is the biggest trouble he could have.
I know you miss him,
but at his age,
he should be
broadening his horizons.
Don't you miss him?
No, I don't.
Why would I miss that rascal?
Chengfeng.
I keep worrying
about something.
I'm afraid that Dongjun...
Don't worry.
Mr. Li is with him.
Nothing would happen to Dongjun.
If you're still worried...
My brother will become
the next head of the Wen Family,
so stop torturing him.
That depends on
what he perceives
as true torture.
Planning to head out for fun again?
I have to stay at home
and concoct poisons every day.
It's so boring!
We've got so many poisons.
It's enough to poison
half of Beili's residents.
Two days ago,
we received
an invitation from the Tang Sect.
You mean
the Poison Convention?
That's right.
Everyone knows
that the Wen Family's poison
is the best in the world,
but the Tang Sect is now claiming
to have the best poisons.
I'm afraid they're planning
to compete with us.
Now that they're inviting us
to the Poison Convention,
we'd better not lose.
Is Father
really allowing us
to attend that convention this time?
He said
that we don't even need to compete.
For centuries,
if we claim to be the second best,
no one would dare
to claim that they're the best.
However,
we're not afraid
of having a competition.
If anyone tries to outshine us,
we'll just poison them.
Awesome!
I've always wanted
to show Tang Linghuang
from the Tang Sect
who's better at using poisons!
When do we depart?
Tomorrow.
I said tomorrow!
Go.
To my disciple, Changfeng,
I am going to the Tang Sect.
Let's meet there.
The Tang Sect?
Mr. Luo
may have a fiery temper,
but he's quite a nice person.
Before we left, he gave me
the liquor he brewed himself.
How does it taste?
Rough but strong.
I can feel the passion in him.
He's actually
a pretty loyal guy,
but he's not good
at expressing himself.
Otherwise, he wouldn't
have lost the chance
to be with that wild lass.
That wild lass?
You mean the owner of the jade pendant?
Yes.
Later, she married
Li Suwang from Swordheart Grave,
and then
they had a baby girl.
You know her.
Li Xinyue.
Second Senior's mother-in-law?
But she's quite old now.
Look at you,
and you're calling her a lass?
She will always be a lass.
She was just 25 years old when she died.
That's how old a lass should be.
She's gone?
Luo Sheng has always blamed himself
for her death.
But actually
it had nothing to do with him.
Later, he adopted a new identity
and moved to this town.
He swore he would never
get involved
in the martial arts world again.
So Mr. Luo
created a mental cage
and locked himself inside.
Who wouldn't do that?
To me,
I'm caged between Heaven and Earth.
I can never grow old
or die.
It sounds interesting,
but sometimes,
it can be pretty boring.
Chunshui.
You're getting too full of yourself.
Wen Buping.
[*Lit: steady pace]
Just like your name,
you sure have a steady pace.
I'm about to fall asleep
in this carriage!
Can't you go faster?
What can I do?
The Wen Family
is different from other sects.
If the other sects arrived first,
the Tang Sect would welcome them
with open arms
and do the honors.
But if we arrived first,
they'd be wary of us,
and vice versa.
Don't worry.
I did my calculations.
It's best if we arrive
in the last minute.
Fine.
You're just too cautious.
You're reckless and I'm mild.
This is
how our family gets better.
What's wrong now?
We're not even moving now?
Your messenger is back.
Well?
Have you found them?
We've found Young Master Dongjun,
but Mr. Li is nowhere to be seen.
Young Master is traveling
with two young men
and a young lady.
A young lady...
Mr. Li isn't with him?
Where are they going, then?
It looked like
they were heading to Jin City too.
The Tang Sect?
They're going to the Tang Sect too?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Did Dongjun
get separated from Mr. Li
and get abducted by those three...
I need to go first.
Enjoy your slow ride!
Dongjun.
Who exactly is
Chunshui?
You can think of me
as Li Changsheng's reincarnation.
I don't know
whether humans do reincarnate,
but I know
they just don't reincarnate
as adults.
Still,
the way you bluff and exaggerate
does resemble him.
Right, Yun.
He is Mr. Li.
What?
You might just
become my disciple.
Yeah.
Something happened that night.
You can take him as your master today.
I went to Tianqi
and took the Academy examinations
just to see
what my master's lifelong rival
looked like.
I've never thought
of becoming your disciple.
And now,
this is even more impossible.
When it comes to apprenticeship,
perhaps your master
was better than I am.
A thought just came to me.
What is it?
The martial arts world
is supposed to be dead.
But as we martial artists
fill it with stories,
the world has come alive.
Cheers!
[No animals were harmed
during the filming of this drama.]
[Some animals were created
using bionic props and 3D effects.]
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪
♪A gentle breeze♪
♪Intentionally touching the heart♪
♪Moored by the lake, ripples spread♪
♪Feet covered by spring mud♪
♪Branches softly murmur in the wind♪
♪Whispering secrets♪
♪Drawing your silhouette under the moon♪
♪As if destined,
gazing at your graceful silhouette♪
♪Restlessly searching♪
♪I stay with you even if the twilight
turns to a clear evening♪
♪Listening closely to the drizzle
in the shadows♪
♪Who can I lean on now?♪
♪Roaming the world together
like a pair of lovebirds♪
♪Deeply in love,
two hearts in perfect harmony♪
♪A red note as our boat,
we navigate with heartfelt devotion♪
♪A folding fan swaying
among the stars and clouds♪
♪In this perfect moment♪
♪To meet you♪