♪I don't want to hear you
nagging nonstop♪
♪Can't you just give me the result♪
♪Don't think being older
makes you so much greater♪
♪Just bring it on♪
♪Watch how I'll handle you♪
♪Hey, I'll just keep on nagging♪
♪Keep on nagging♪
♪You're annoying; do not get me mad♪
♪I'm always the one
taking the blame for you♪
♪Don't be afraid to speak;
I might hold a grudge♪
♪No. 132♪
♪357, what do you want♪
♪Stop right there♪
♪In this noisy, rowdy world,
fate is so amazing♪
♪When we go crazy together,
joy is always with us♪
♪We'll party till dawn♪
♪Laughing, jumping, with no worries♪
♪You're clearly so strange♪
♪I'm clearly so cute♪
♪Even if they don't get it,
it doesn't matter♪
♪Even if it's always crazy and weird♪
♪I still need fresh reasons for myself♪
=Hilarious Family 2=
=Episode 14=
The bed in a rich family feels so good.
What are you doing here?
You're awake, huh?
I'm not.
What do you want?
This is what I want to ask you.
Without saying a word,
you came over to me.
A mother needn't say anything
before visiting her daughter.
It makes sense.
When you left your daughter
to travel around the world,
you didn't say a word, either.
I didn't?
I didn't say a word?
Are you out of money again?
Don't say that.
This time, I really missed you.
I really did.
You missed me?
Come on.
Your...
Your sweetheart.
Mr. Guo, right?
Where is he?
You said he was one in a million.
What happened?
Did you break up?
Guo...
He's a nice man.
But he isn't romantic.
Instead of hairpins or tassels
that are sold everywhere,
he bought me a pair of socks.
People want their lives
to be romantic and exciting.
Don't you think so?
Look at you.
You look really plain.
How could you come out like this?
Have you never tried
rouge, makeup powder,
or eyebrow paint
since you were born?
How is that possible?
Look at his. And this.
What are you trying to say?
Give me some money.
I'll buy them for you.
Mai Youyou.
Let me make this clear.
I'm no longer doing
the inn business.
I have no money for you.
That's good.
You've married a rich man.
Don't always stay out there.
How did you
meet Mr. Jing?
Don't be so curious.
I'm not curious.
I'm caring for you.
What was your bride price?
Nothing.
Don't lie to me.
I think you only care about money.
I only care about you.
Or why didn't I ask others
about their bride price?
Let me say something intimate.
Have a baby soon.
Then you'll stick in this family
and I'll be relieved.
Right.
Good idea.
I'm going to have some babies now.
Where can I have breakfast?
In Yushi Chamber.
Yushi Chamber.
You.
Yes, you.
Yes. Come over here.
Who are you?
Let me introduce myself.
I am
Jing Kan's mother.
Here's the thing.
You're a maid here, right?
Yes, huh?
Later, go to the South Market
and buy me two fruit-stuffed jelly cakes
and sugared ice cream balls.
Remember. Two spoons of sugar.
A bit more or less isn't fine.
Western sugar, please.
Besides,
if there is extra rouge, makeup powder,
and eyebrow paint,
give me some.
If there isn't, buy me some.
Thank you for that.
Is that the place for breakfast?
Forget it. It's nothing.
I'll make my way around.
Bye.
Jing Kan's mother?
How many mothers does he have?
Madam.
Chief,
I've found out what Jing Kan cares for.
What is that?
A man.
Who?
Oh, my head hurts.
Ruan Ling.
It's all over the tea plantation.
Because his subordinate
gave Ruan Ling a few more bowls of food,
Jing Kan flew into a rage.
What does that mean?
It means...
Get to the point.
It means they have a thing
with each other.
What thing?
Anyway, he cares for Ruan Ling.
Why would he care for Ruan Ling?
Because he's flattering.
Ruan Ling
is rather smooth-tongued.
He always flatters people.
So, he is...
A pleaser.
Shouldn't he be a flatterer?
Everybody knows this word.
I want to be the man
who surprises people.
I can't believe
Jing Kan hit me so hard.
Then I'll make him
care more about the man he cares for.
I'd like to see
what's special about this guy
he's caring for.
Somebody come.
Bring me the pleaser.
Yes.
Mr. Jing wanted to see you.
I'm not going.
If he wants to talk,
he can come here.
Get him.
What are you doing?
Plenty to do, huh?
It's really a lovely room.
Chief, here he is.
Where's your master?
Master?
Don't tell me it's Jing Kan.
You're showing off.
Oh, look. Your intention
is quite obvious.
Yes. We'll mess with Jing Kan.
But sadly,
you have no time to inform him.
There must be some mistake.
If you want to mess with Jing Kan,
just go ahead.
If you want to slap him,
I can even do that for you.
He's trying to warn Jing Kan, right?
You don't seem to listen.
He's a perfect pleaser.
Pleaser?
A man who pleases people.
Why did you slap me?
Because we don't like Jing Kan.
Then you should slap him!
As his pleaser,
you have to pay a price, too.
Don't call me that!
This is too much.
It really is.
How about this?
You let me go
and I can help you
to lure Jing Kan here.
Try to get a helper, huh?
Fine. You need your master.
How about this?
If you bark like a dog several times,
I'll go get your master.
Isn't it funny?
It's so humorous of you.
Did I say you could laugh?
Go ahead.
Bark.
I...
- You...
- Ruan Ling.
Bark.
His master is here for him.
What are you doing?
Slapping your servant.
You're being humorous again.
That's going too far!
Sit back.
We sit too close.
Sit back there.
I don't want this.
Sit back.
Let me stay away from him.
Just sit back.
You used to be fierce, huh?
Quite impressive.
Ares of the Privy, right?
Previously,
you made a fool of me.
I'll chop off your hand each.
Is it too much?
Take both of my hands.
But let him go.
Are you insane?
Wait a minute.
Did you figure it out?
Chief, what do they mean?
I'll kill both of you, then.
What's the noise?
Who was that?
I don't know.
Go lock the door.
Alright.
Don't move.
- Head in hands!
- Squat.
I'm talking to you.
Don't move. Head in hands.
Get down.
Behave.
How dare you keep weapons illegally?
You think I'm dead?
We're saved.
Take all these guys away.
Take them away.
Don't move!
Are you blind?
We're the victims!
It's you again.
Sir, we were just joking.
Don't worry.
I'm here. You're safe.
- Alright.
- Come on.
- Mr. Jing.
- Thank you.
Come, please.
- He's still there.
- Let's go.
Mr. Lei.
I'm still here!
Behave!
Mr. Lei.
Don't touch me!
You're the pleaser!
Sir, untie me, please.
Here, Mr. Jing.
Thank you for helping me out.
I didn't do that for nothing.
You're the eldest child
of Jinyu Tea, right?
Yes.
I've been in this field for a long time
and had many friends
in the tea business.
They have a lot of fancy tea leaves.
The quality is guaranteed.
They just don't know how to sell them.
I'm wondering if you can sell the tea
in your own shop.
Give it a name as you wish.
The profits will go fifty-fifty.
No need.
I'll take 20 percent.
Please buy better food
for the workers
in this tea plantation
with the other 30 percent.
Impressive.
Impressive, indeed.
Since you agree to sell the tea,
you'll be contributing.
I'll reduce your time.
You can leave tomorrow.
I can leave tomorrow?
Why would I lie?
The tea leaves can't wait.
Supervisor Lei,
I have another condition.
Not on the price.
No.
I want to take Ruan Ling away.
I don't know
how Jing Kan is doing there.
Come on.
Be careful.
Come on. Put it over here.
Right over here.
Alright. We should go.
Whose halter tops?
Why are they here?
Who do you think owns them?
You?
Your mother.
Your...
My mother?
Where is she now?
In Yushi Chamber.
She got herself a welcome banquet
and invited everybody over.
Sixteen dishes.
Two menus, actually.
Come on. Move aside.
Let's drink.
This is a family
of widows.
Mother, what are you doing here?
What's the fuss?
Greet them.
Grandmother. Auntie.
I'm terribly sorry.
This is my mother, Mai Youyou.
She always
talks very casually.
Sixi,
you and Jing Kan
have been married for so long.
We didn't see your mother until today.
It's your fault.
Yeah.
Sixi, your mother
is insightful from traveling around.
And she's humorous.
Let's have a deal.
Without my permission,
you must not leave.
Come on, My Lady.
I can't stay at my son-in-law's place.
That's not appropriate.
Now sit.
You're well prepared.
When have I ever
disgraced you?
You must be Jing Kan's mother.
Who's she?
I'm meeting you at last.
Fine.
- Come on.
- Alright.
- Be seated.
You don't have to do this.
We haven't met before.
That's Madam's spot.
It doesn't make a difference.
Come on.
She must be your personal maid.
She's really diligent.
You've trained her very well.
Ms. Luo,
I should drink for our first meeting.
Oh, Mother.
I suddenly remember
I have something to deal with.
I'll take my leave.
What could be more important
than meeting Sixi's mother?
- Yeah.
- Sit down and drink.
Sit now.
It's fine. She doesn't have to drink.
Just make yourself comfortable.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Come on. The two of us
and this younger lady
shall wish Old Lady longevity.
Raise your cup.
Who's the younger lady?
You.
Wow, you think I'm younger?
No one else has ever seen it.
I thought you were younger than me.
Others think I'm older
because my husband is the eldest son.
Come on.
Here.
Let's wish her
a harmonious and prosperous family.
Glad to hear that.
I feel so good.
You're Sixi's mother-in-law.
They wouldn't exist without you.
They should respect you.
And we should
take good care of you, My Lady.
Mother,
in this family,
there are always rules.
One must behave
very properly.
I'm sorry.
Put them back.
On my shoulders.
Someone can finally drink with me
and we can finally laugh.
Does it bother you?
Ms. Luo,
another toast to you.
Thank you
for raising Jing Kan.
He's a great son-in-law for me.
Oh, I remember.
I have something important to handle.
Mother, enjoy the food.
I'll take my leave.
What's wrong with her?
Jing Kan isn't her biological son.
You should have told me.
Ignore her.
Let's drink.
- Come on.
- Let's enjoy ourselves.
Cheers.
Do you feel happy?
I do.
(Vast and Clear)
Drink slowly.
Auntie,
this is the amber bracelet
from my mother.
And this is the treasure pot
from my father.
This is the black-dragon incense
from my grandparents.
And here's some goat-milk pastry.
Who is it from?
It's from me.
Don't worry. No lard is in it.
My mother finally told me
you didn't eat anything with lard.
Why didn't you tell me before?
It was an old habit.
I occasionally eat some now.
You can just tell me
about something like this.
Don't endure discomfort.
Aji,
you had a long trip.
Go back for some rest.
Off you go.
Alright.
Am I interrupting, Ms. Luo?
You must be Jing Kan.
I'm not.
So, he's your son.
You look alike.
Don't be ridiculous.
This is my auntie.
What a woman.
Aji, have a good rest.
Go check
if his room is ready.
Yes.
I...
I really thought it was your son.
The two of you look alike.
What do you want me for?
Ms. Luo,
I talked carelessly
and offended you.
Don't take it personally.
I'm here to apologize.
It's nothing.
But remember.
Aji isn't my son.
He's my nephew.
I'll keep that in mind.
I'm just straightforward.
Anything else?
If you don't mind,
please leave.
Ms. Luo, we'll be friends.
If anything bothers you,
let me know.
I'll comfort you.
Nothing bothers me.
But you, Ms. Mai.
When you have time,
you can go out for a stroll.
You don't need
to be stuck in this house.
I get it.
Cuiying, see her out.
She isn't even here.
Why did you call her?
I'll see myself out.
You don't have to playact.
Bye.
What an ignorant woman.
What's wrong with you?
You can't even buy a ticket.
My Lady,
too many people were there today.
So what?
I'm old, all right?
How many more times
can I watch Yunzhu's opera?
My Lady.
There you are.
What's going on?
I was sent
to buy a ticket for Yunzhu's opera,
but I failed.
Yunzhu?
The opera singer?
Yes.
Don't laugh.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
Youyou,
where have you been all these years?
After we rowed a boat on Shigui Lake,
I lost contact with you.
In these dozen years,
I've been thinking of you.
Youyou,
who is this?
The owner of Huichun Opera House.
My Lady,
I'm Chen from Huichun Opera House.
Chen.
Let me be frank.
Try to get some tickets
for Yunzhu's opera.
But...
Youyou, to be honest,
it's really hard
to have Master Yunzhu sing
at my place.
So, the tickets...
Fine.
The door is over there.
You may leave now.
Youyou.
Let me think.
Oh, I remember.
I do have one ticket.
I had planned
to keep it
for Magistrate Meng's daughter.
I'll give it to you, then.
Alright.
No.
I need two.
Two...
Will you let her
go there alone?
She needs
a companion.
Fine.
I'll find another way.
Besides,
the seats must be adjacent.
If you get the tickets ready,
come here for lunch tomorrow.
If you fail,
you won't see me ever again.
Don't.
Fine.
I will try hard
to have lunch here tomorrow.
I'm on it now.
I'll take my leave, My Lady.
Mingzhen.
See...
Chen.
See Mr. Chen out.
This way, please.
Youyou.
Why is he so obedient to you?
You can totally
manipulate him.
Impressive, indeed.
We were friends years ago.
It's not worth telling.
Don't worry
if he offers no tickets.
We'll go straight to Yunzhu.
Who?
Yunzhu.
You even know him?
Do you really adore him that much?
I do.
Look, I'm old.
I love his operas most.
I want this house to be lively.
Don't laugh at me.
I won't.
You're just trying to be happy.
Oh, look.
It's so sweet of you.
Since you like Yunzhu that much,
I'll invite him over for lunch.
Are you sure?
My Lady,
we need some fun in the house.
Think about Ms. Luo.
She always pulls a long face.
Doesn't it upset you?
You mean Zhusi?
It upsets me.
So, I don't look at her.
Do you know why she does this?
Because she looks down on people.
I don't like it
when she remains domineering.
You're wrong, My Lady.
Think about it.
She's no longer young
and has lost her husband for years.
No man is around her.
Nobody could be happy in this condition.
I don't care.
My point is,
she needs to see a man.
(Jing Residence)
Ms. Luo,
you need feeding up.
Men like women with rosy cheeks.
Look at your face.
Sallow, indeed.
Who would like you?
What are you talking about?
I don't need feeding up.
You should eat more.
Besides,
my face isn't sallow.
Zhusi.
Youyou is right.
You really need
feeding up.
You should be more open-minded.
We're all single women.
Life can be comfortable.
But as time goes by,
you may feel uncomfortable.
What do you mean by that?
Have you thought about it?
You've been sad all the time.
If you have someone
to care for you,
won't you feel better?
Youyou, you have a point.
It makes sense.
It really does.
This is Chen.
I forgot to introduce him.
He's the owner of Huichun Opera House.
He also owns two private banks.
We've been friends for a dozen years.
I know him very well.
Why don't you get acquainted?
Oh, he's Mr. Chen.
He's obviously a nice guy.
Mr. Chen.
A very good young man.
Alright. Today is a good day.
You two should get acquainted.
Alright.
Chen,
let's get acquainted.
Where do you live?
How old are you?
Are you married?
- Youyou.
- Are your parents alive?
Do you have any children?
Youyou, this...
This should be a banquet.
Why do you make it a blind date?
(Blind date? You don't deserve it.)
You...
You can't have preconceptions.
Don't assume anything.
Get along with her.
If you hit it off, great.
If you don't, just be friends.
- Right?
- Fine.
Get along with her.
If you hit it off, great.
If you don't, just be friends.
It's no big deal.
Just get along with her.
How can I?
She's bad-tempered.
Her face is sallow.
And she isn't young.
I can't...
Who do you mean?
Her, right?
Old and sallow-faced.
Youyou,
you need feeding up.
Men like
rosy cheeks.
Mother, I'm full.
I'll take my leave.
You guys get along.
Keep having a nice time.
(I think you make a perfect match.)
How could she be so impolite?
Shut up now.
Come on.
Let's eat.
- Enjoy the food.
- Let's eat.
- Youyou, eat.
- Come on.
Get me some braised pork.
Madam, you invited Young Madam's mother
so early in the morning.
I've never seen you
have a friend in this family.
She isn't a friend.
Don't be ignorant.
She isn't?
But yesterday, I saw you
talk nicely to her.
Come on.
You've served me for years.
Why haven't you been smart yet?
Then why did you invite her over
in such a hurry?
Sixi's mother
appears to be straightforward.
But actually, she's shrewd.
She has realized
Sixi's mother-in-law
is a difficult woman.
So, she is
clearing obstacles for her daughter.
She's trying to marry Zhusi
to someone.
That's hilarious.
I thought she was just enthusiastic.
Don't bother to think.
You won't understand.
But Ai Sixi's mother
isn't smart enough.
I should remind her.
(Vibrant and Splendid)
It's a really nice chamber
for tea tasting.
Of course.
We're the supplier
of tribute tea, after all.
Take your seat.
Have some tea.
Mingxia, go get some snow water.
Yes.
Snow water?
What for?
For making tea.
Different kinds of water
are used for different types of tea.
You're even
so meticulous about tea.
Sixi is so lucky
to have married Jing Kan.
As the saying goes,
destiny brings people together.
We're destined
to be a family.
Think of Zhusi.
Sometimes, she's moody
and oversensitive.
But think of Sixi.
Sometimes, she behaves
without manners.
So, just as you can see,
she and Zhusi...
I'm quite worried.
I'm saying this
because I take you for a real friend.
I know.
So, Ms. Xue, I request you
to watch over Sixi.
If she behaves improperly,
criticize her.
I will.
She's like my own child.
Indeed.
Youyou.
You know what?
As for the blind date for Zhusi...
I totally support you.
We're on the same page.
Think about it.
A woman like her
needs a man.
When restrained,
she may behave better.
What do you think?
You're right.
Then tell me.
Who can be her man?
Don't be mad at what I'm going to say.
Last time,
Mr. Chen...
He's hopeless.
He can't attract Zhusi at all.
What kind of man fascinates her?
Someone like Kan's father.
Literate and talented.
Literate and talented?
That's not hard.
But if Ms. Luo
marries someone,
the burden of this family
will fall on you.
Won't that be too hard?
No, no. Not at all.
It won't be hard.
It's my responsibility.
By then, I'll ask Sixi
to share your burden.
She's like my own child, you know.
I won't rely on anyone but her.
I'm relieved
to hear that.
You may rest assured.
Have some tea.
Let me introduce him.
This is Master Yunzhu.
You don't need to.
Everyone here
knows him.
Please be seated,
Master Yunzhu.
Master Yunzhu,
please take that seat.
Close to Zhusi.
You can talk, then.
Where's Youyou?
Here I am.
Yunzhu,
how did you meet Youyou?
I used to sing Kun Opera
in a small town
and I wasn't very famous.
There was one time
when Youyou traveled to Songxi County
and heard me warm up
by the river.
She then recommended me to Mr. Yang
of Jiayun Opera House,
Anning Prefecture.
That's how I've come this far.
So,
Youyou not only helped me
but also improved me.
In this case,
you were discovered by Youyou.
You flatter me.
He was really competent
and talented.
He was hard-working, too.
Just like you,
I like operas.
He can sing really well.
So, I recommended him to my friend.
Let me introduce her.
This is Ms. Luo.
She's in charge of Jinyu Tea.
"Graceful businesswoman"
is a perfect word for her.
Why do you
keep nagging like that?
Master Yunzhu didn't ask at all.
I just want them
to communicate more.
Yunzhu, make yourself at home.
Help yourself.
Nice to meet you, My Lady.
Nice to meet you, madams.
My Lady
and Youyou,
thanks for inviting me over.
You're welcome.
Wow, he looks handsome
and he's so polite.
Don't you think so, Zhusi?
- Why?
- Muyun,
you have been babbling
all the time.
Master Yunzhu
is Mother's honored guest.
Save more time
for Mother
to talk with him.
Yunzhu,
will you sing a bit
to get us excited?
Great.
This is great!
Mother,
let him eat something first.
Perfect timing to sing before eating.
Terrific.
=Hilarious Family 2=
♪Your smile♪
♪Like spring when new leaves grow♪
♪Passing through endless time♪
♪Still longing♪
♪For gentle, tender memories♪
♪She emerges from all things♪
♪So quiet and distant♪
♪The breeze blows softly♪
♪Scattering at the end of time♪
♪May every blossom here♪
♪Never be forgotten♪
♪Facing away
from the old windmill at dusk♪
♪Stirring your heart♪
♪You once said you'd sing in the wind♪
♪The breeze blows softly♪
♪Scattering at the end of time♪
♪May every blossom here♪
♪Never be forgotten♪
♪Facing away
from the old windmill at dusk♪
♪Stirring your heart♪
♪You once said you'd sing in the wind♪