♪What a surreal story♪
♪Life teases you♪
♪Pulled by gravity, tiding♪
♪I can't help but be stirred♪
♪I fell in love, though not by choice♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪Because of my overconfidence♪
♪I'm willing to be confined to♪
♪Affection♪
♪I got disturbed and orientated♪
♪To let you get something on me♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪More sophisticated than you♪
♪But beaten by your false affection♪
♪I finally figured it out♪
♪As fate would have it♪
=The Love We Couldn't Keep=
=Episode 9=
I've got a full schedule today.
I can't spare you much time.
Sorry.
I'm not here for some chats.
Check your WeChat.
(Order: Some Requirements)
I think I can challenge the leader,
taking over his place.
What is this?
A big order.
Gengdi is about to be in China.
They want a local brand for co-branding.
Gengdi?
Absolutely true!
That's great!
If we can cut a deal with it,
it'll help Qingyu gain much visibility,
also good for our internationalization.
Exactly!
But, a competitive bidding is needed.
Their requirements are very simple.
To emphasize Chinese characteristics.
Director Tang,
are you confident to take it?
You've done your part quite well.
How could we not seize the chance?
Counting on you.
Amy, Gengdi came here yesterday
for the details of the collaboration.
Did you know that?
Vivian, my friend told me that
Gengdi went to their place
for some details of the collaboration.
Alright, and we don't force things.
I need to confirm it.
Okay.
Hello!
Liliy!
I heard about your company...
Do you know who handled the Gengdi issue?
Who is that guy?
Doukou!
Doukou?
Are you sure?
If it were Doukou,
we definitely have no chance!
Yesterday, people from Gengdi
went to Doukou for a face-to-face talk.
I want to go home and catch up on sleep.
There's no chance left for us!
Exactly!
What do we have to compete with Doukou?
Making a wedding dress doesn't count!
Not even making sure before bidding?
Isn't it wreaking havoc on us?
Yes, exactly!
Enough.
What are you afraid of?
I know she has a young lover.
Li Shu.
We have been in contact with Gengdi.
(Doukou (Business))
But unconfirmed.
Yesterday, Gengdi's men went to Doukou
for a good conversation.
As long as there's no contract and payment,
we still have a chance.
Set up a meeting with their business team.
Try to meet their boss,
having a face-to-face talk.
Alright.
I'm really impressed.
Our leaders
are all like hidden talents.
They still want us to work overtime for
projects that were predetermined long ago.
So annoying!
Qiu Wan'er from PR should handle it!
She's in charge of it, and
now there's such a big mess.
She can't shrink from responsibilities.
She's so good at seducing.
Didn't you see, at the last cocktail party
President Jiang from Jiang Media
couldn't take his eyes off her?
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
I'm tired of this nonsense!
I'm telling you that
they must have an affair with each other.
Or, why did Jiang Mi make it so fast?
She should be chosen to do it.
Send her to seduce the boss and then
wouldn't it be solved, would it?
Do you think Gengdi's boss is desperate?
Were you just talking about Manager Qu?
We just had some chats.
It's about whoever takes it personally.
Okay.
I was recording what you spoke of.
I give you two choices.
One,
you should quit yourselves.
And give me your words that
you won't spread rumors.
Two,
it's about defamation.
I will hire the best lawyer
to ensure you're gonna rot in prison.
Vivian, we were just joking!
Yes, joking. And don't be like that!
Choose one or two.
Sorry!
We'll quit tomorrow.
Where did your usual arrogance go?
I'm sick of arguing anymore.
We have so many members here.
Can I really shut each of them up?
Such a big heart?
But I'm in charge of PR.
And it's my daily routine.
If I were really that fragile,
one person with a mouthful of spit
could drown me!
(Meet and discuss the collaboration)
Tang, Gengdi's boss, wants to see us.
Really?
That's great!
My high performance can be delivered.
General Manager Fen.
Just leave me here.
Your proposal is very bold.
And also very innovative.
I like it very much!
But for the final result,
it'll depend on your bidding.
Thank you for
leaving us a chance to bid.
As you said,
we'll definitely give it our all!
Looking forward to working with you!
Thank you.
Then we'll take our leave.
I brought our previous design drafts
and went to Gengdi.
The boss over really favored our style
and granted us a chance to compete with
Doukou for the final co-branding rights.
- Yes.
- You're amazing!
You're impressive!
By the way, Li Shu,
you'd put all of our design drafts
together during this period.
I'll make some adjustments.
- Okay.
- Tomorrow at 10 AM.
Wait in the meeting room for you all!
Why are you following me?
I'm on the way.
On the way?
I'm your new neighbor.
I just tidied up half of my house.
It seems like that's the case.
But I'm not usually this messy.
I can see it through.
It's indeed quite rushed.
I'll buy something
to make dishes for you.
Then,
I shall accept your offer.
Wei...
This...
It's dirty, and I haven't wiped it yet.
So you like wooden sculptures, huh?
Yes!
I played with it when I was a child.
I saw it as an apple of my eye.
A gift for your birthday.
Brother,
come on, I've been in college!
You're still my younger brother.
You'll have it every year from now on.
Okay.
Did your ex-girlfriend give it to you?
My brother.
Do you have another brother?
I've never heard you speak of him.
He
passed away.
I'm sorry.
- I...
- It's okay.
Why don't you eat first?
It'll get cold soon.
Alright.
♪What a surreal story♪
♪Life teases you♪
♪No one else but you♪
♪Broke into my heart♪
♪Pulled by gravity, tiding♪
♪I can't help but be stirred♪
♪I fell in love, though not by choice♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪Because of my overconfidence♪
♪I'm willing to be confined to♪
♪Affection♪
♪I got disturbed and orientated♪
♪To let you get something on me♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪More sophisticated than you♪
♪But beaten by your false affection♪
♪I finally figured it out♪
♪As fate would have it♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪Because of my overconfidence♪
♪I'm willing to be confined to♪
♪Affection♪
♪I got disturbed and orientated♪
♪To let you get something on me♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪More sophisticated than you♪
♪But beaten by your false affection♪
♪I finally figured it out♪
♪As fate would have it♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)