♪What a surreal story♪
♪Life teases you♪
♪Pulled by gravity, tiding♪
♪I can't help but be stirred♪
♪I fell in love, though not by choice♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪Because of my overconfidence♪
♪I'm willing to be confined to♪
♪Affection♪
♪I got disturbed and orientated♪
♪To let you get something on me♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪More sophisticated than you♪
♪But beaten by your false affection♪
♪I finally figured it out♪
♪As fate would have it♪
=The Love We Couldn't Keep=
=Episode 8=
Promise me that
you can't fall for anyone else!
Weiwei,
why you hit people?!
Mother,
why are you here all of a sudden?
With the help of Jiang Mi this season,
our firm has turned around completely!
What does 'turn around' mean?
It's about a return to the peak,
sweeping the nation.
If there were no more bonuses, it'd be unfair!
Absolutely unfair!
By the way, Li,
you can secure your job for sure.
When you're in,
never forget to have meals with us.
Alright.
As for where to eat, it's all up to you.
Li is truly the most
worry-free intern I've ever had.
Li, what did you take?
It's a home-made thing.
I just thought I'd have it for lunch.
Li, I never thought
you can cook yourself!
It seems you've made quite a lot!
I brought a share for the Director, too.
Li, I have high hopes for you!
Sure!
I'm leaving.
I'm heading out now.
(How could this happen)
I've texted you.
Besides, you didn't even close the door.
Although there are two guys at home,
it may not be safe.
Hello, Auntie.
What are you talking about?
It should be more affectionate!
For example, like auntie,
or mother...
Mother!
It's not your turn!
I just saw everything.
About what happened,
that was just an accident.
It's all my fault.
I lost my patience.
A misunderstanding.
I've gone through it.
I can see it through that
have you quarreled?
Relax, and I'll stand up for you.
Okay.
Weiwei,
you've never been taught to hit people.
How can you do that?
I...
Boy, you
look quite pretty.
Are you one of our natives?
Auntie, you said it.
I'm an intern under Weiwei.
You must be much younger than her!
Yes!
But the age issue doesn't matter.
Come on, add each other on WeChat!
Of course, yes.
Director, time to eat!
Director, it's time to eat!
I'm not hungry.
Get it out of here.
Your mother will be concerned if so.
Please have a bit.
He worked hard to cook.
You need to have them all.
Come on, have more.
Come and have a taste!
Thank you.
No need to do it since tomorrow.
Why?
I was told by your mother.
She knew nothing!
And many guys are watching us here.
Both of us will be framed.
Alright.
I understand.
By the way,
on top of work stories,
you can't get in and out as you wish.
Did I do something wrong?
Or,
you're sick of me now?
No!
Director!
Why did you get him upset again?
I...
It's not the way you look at it.
Because I failed her.
You can't blame her.
Then, you guys keep going.
Never forget your meal.
For a newcomer,
he's already doing very well.
Don't be too strict with him!
Director.
Sing it!
Brother...
Can you fix an appointment with Li Shu?
I want him.
Do it yourself!
I failed, so I came for your help!
He's unwilling to see you, that means
he really doesn't want you!
I...
I know that.
I chose to team up with Qingyu because
I could take more chances to see him.
I never thought
he's so businesslike!
(Dinner tonight?)
He didn't care!
You're a fairy-like girl.
You should know when to give up.
Negative!
I must face the challenge!
Brother, please!
When you were in college,
I asked him to take care of you.
I made a mistake.
Yes.
So you should hold me all accountable!
Li Shu is determined.
He won't fall in love with you.
Is it the way you treat your sister?
(Qu Wan'er)
Give me your phone.
- Why?
- Give it to me.
(Qu Wan'er)
Brother.
It turns out you love Qu Wan'er!
Why don't we work together?
I can do it myself.
Yes, you can!
I'm sure you'll have no
life-long companion!
When did you block me?
I never thought the decisive Tang Weiwei
could be disturbed by an intern.
Now, my mom is getting involved, too!
It becomes more complex.
I think you do have feelings for him.
If so, just give it a try.
You can't just because of a bad past,
staying single for a lifetime!
Let's talk about it later.
(The Additional Clauses)
Mr. Jiang wants to amend it.
Did I offend him before?
Why won't he let me go in this life?
Do you think Mr. Jiang
has feelings for you?
Negative, and don't curse me!
How can this be considered cursing you?
Mr. Jiang is the CEO of Jiang Media.
About the immense wealth,
when it comes, you better catch it!
I don't. Whoever wants it can have it.
Weiwei,
I really
really love you!
As long as you're willing to admit it,
I can forgive.
Admit what?
You're absolutely ridiculous!
You don't believe me, do you?
Alright.
Let's break up!
Break up?
It was your fault.
But you want to break up with me?
My fault?
Truly unreasonable!
(Attraction, Trust, Like, Love, Destruction)
(Tang Weiwei hates thunderstorms)
Why are you here?
I...
Thunderstorms frighten me!
Come in now!
Alright.
I haven't apologized to you about
what happened before.
What?
We're not a couple.
But I kissed you in advance.
It's okay.
It's a thing of the past.
I know that
a five-year age gap lies between us.
Sometimes, you think I'm too young and
are sick of my immaturity.
But I really love you.
I... I also really love you.
I don't want to deceive myself.
But we can't be a couple.
Sister, do you love me?
Why can't we be a couple?
I haven't figured out how to tell you
about some things yet.
It's okay.
I'm willing to wait till you figure it out.
♪What a surreal story♪
♪Life teases you♪
♪No one else but you♪
♪Broke into my heart♪
♪Pulled by gravity, tiding♪
♪I can't help but be stirred♪
♪I fell in love, though not by choice♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪Because of my overconfidence♪
♪I'm willing to be confined to♪
♪Affection♪
♪I got disturbed and orientated♪
♪To let you get something on me♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪More sophisticated than you♪
♪But beaten by your false affection♪
♪I finally figured it out♪
♪As fate would have it♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪Because of my overconfidence♪
♪I'm willing to be confined to♪
♪Affection♪
♪I got disturbed and orientated♪
♪To let you get something on me♪
♪Why do you push me any harder♪
♪More sophisticated than you♪
♪But beaten by your false affection♪
♪I finally figured it out♪
♪As fate would have it♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)