Famosperosis means Nowadays Beneficiaries
Deliberation is everywhere
It's unbearable
When there's trouble, you'll hide behind your parents
I shouldn't have agreed to a interview with Hong Yifeng.
He'll get his revenge sooner or later.
Besides, his show is so popular now.
You should be thankful too.
Come in.
Director General, the chairman's wife is here. She's on the phone.
I'll go out for a bit.
It's okay. Don't bother.
Chen Xiaowen.
Where is Li Xianhong?
Madam, we're also in touch.
Today, the stock price dropped by 27 yuan at the opening.
I don't care how he'll do things outside.
But as the general manager, you're dealing with a crisis.
We should be responsible for the investment.
Who agreed to an interview with Hong Yifeng?
It's all my call.
You won't think about the consequences?
Li Xianhong failed to come back to you.
You think he'll quit his job?
You don't understand this?
Xiaowen, thank you.
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
Who are these people?
How could the chairman get together with them?
There was no problem when they were interviewed yesterday, right?
I don't know these young people either.
But I'll try to figure it out.
I'll report to you later.
I'll go out now.
Hi, Yifeng.
What's wrong?
Why are you looking for me?
I'm just wasting a little time.
It won't be long.
You should know why I'm here.
How would I know if you don't tell me?
I'm here to see you.
I see.
Or is this what Li Xianhong taught you?
I didn't think that I would be so easily fooled.
But I chose to believe you because of my professional respect for you.
But the fact proves that I'm too naive.
I know he's not perfect.
But he's not a bad person.
He didn't take advantage of Taiwan's resources to go to the streets.
He's not fair to the general public for using his image of a business demon.
Besides, you're causing a controversy.
It's not good for Taiwan.
Don't be so high-profile.
Why don't you just tell me that my news has caused a lot of damage to your image?
Maybe I'll respect you more.
Don't you think that when the media uses Facebook content,
they need to make a real assessment?
Every word in the film was said by Li Xianhong himself.
And the fact that he argued with his husband was also a fact.
I don't think we're misleading the audience.
Or should we first go through the review of the Zhe'er Cultural Group?
Here, the real deal.
Don't blame him.
I forced him to bring me here.
I didn't mean to avoid the people in the office.
Boss Fan, to be honest,
you don't have to reply to the messages on the Internet.
Do you want me to remain silent,
let them slander and attack me?
The communication between generations is different.
I sincerely suggest that we should go back to the traditional media.
That's our familiar battlefield.
Isn't it better to give up the Internet and communicate with the young?
Besides, most of our customers are young people.
If we only go to the traditional media, we'll be far away from them.
I understand that.
But traditional media can let everyone get the same message at the same time.
Although everyone has different views, it doesn't matter.
But at least we get a chance to make it clear.
This may also cause a bigger argument.
Do you think it's good?
Is it really good?
Here, have some hot soup.
Drink it first. Don't be so serious.
The messages on the Internet are very unreasonable.
Even if we explain them one by one, it may not be clear.
They are all behind the Facebook.
We don't know who they are.
They are using the image of profit and loss on you.
It's a wrong confrontation.
I'm not a person who doesn't want to fight.
I know you are not.
But boss, please give me a chance to make it clear.
Okay. What are you going to do?
Lin Xianhong is an individual.
And the people in the battle suit and the community are a group of people.
Individual statements and public opinion shouldn't be put in the same news.
Besides, you have never seen a bad news.
So you want to discuss the news theory with me now?
Then I think we don't have to waste time.
You can go up the elevator and find the senior in the TV station.
Thank you, boss.
If you tell others that you have a relationship with him,
will everyone give you a big question mark
in the professionalism of this news?
I hope you will go to Hong Li Fang's live broadcast again.
You still believe him?
He came up with this.
He created two generations of controversy.
I think it's the best way to solve this on his show.
I'm afraid he won't handle it on his own.
And Xiao Wen is still the general manager of the group.
I have reminded him that if his past love history is dug out,
I believe...
Okay, stop talking.
It's decided.
You arrange it.
Thank you, boss.
It's a long time ago.
Do you think it can still work?
But you're not the reporter from a long time ago, are you?
Hong Li Fang's live broadcast.
What do you want?
Give him a chance.
Let him go on my live broadcast.
This is a win-win situation.
You will earn your income.
And he got a chance to make up for his own mistakes.
But I need you to promise to keep your loyalty.
Can I ask you another question?
I'll go get some water.
Okay.
I wonder what the spirit girl has to do with you.
I'm sorry.
Patrick, let's eat.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
Friends.
Good morning, Ms. Sun.
Good morning, Mom.
You're early.
I just got here.
You just kicked me out.
Why don't you want to see me?
What are you saying?
I'm the most relieved when you're here.
I brought you your favorite jade flower.
I put it on for you.
Look, it's pretty.
Is Hong okay?
It's okay.
Shanghai's base is well-established.
Hangzhou is also very promising.
Everyone is looking forward to it.
Mom, you look good today.
I'm getting better.
My brain is getting less and less important.
It's okay.
You just have a good rest.
Just take the medicine that Dr. Zhao gave you.
Why are you saying the same thing to him?
I told him.
I can't drag it like this.
Let me die.
Mom,
if you're gone,
no one can be with me.
Mom, do you know that...
when Hong was doing an interview,
he couldn't stop talking about you.
He said he remembered when you were little,
you drew and wrote homework with him.
You gave him all the achievements he could get today.
I read the news.
Why did they say that about him?
It's okay.
Don't look at those things.
It's just a temporary trend.
Don't look at those things that are not there.
Why did he fight with those kids?
He's always been a bad temper.
Mom, don't worry.
No matter what happens,
I'll be with him.
Xiaowen,
I'm sorry.
I know you love him.
But...
he can't give you a name.
I'm really sorry.
In my heart,
you're my daughter-in-law.
I want to thank you.
Really.
Can you move the coffee to the front?
This one?
Yes.
The chocolate one?
How about this?
Okay.
Hello.
Lily, I'm looking for you.
One coffee, please.
Thank you.
You've already investigated me.
What else can you do on Facebook?
What's the matter?
Do you like Li Xianhong?
It's none of your business.
I was thinking,
if you were there that day,
why didn't you stop her from fighting with your classmate?
And,
did you know that someone was secretly taking pictures that night?
She's an adult now.
Do I have to agree to anything?
If you love her, why don't you protect her?
Do you like Xianhong?
I knew her when I was in senior year.
I was her first job in the society.
I've been with her for ten years.
You haven't answered my question yet.
I'm sorry.
Was she with you last night?
I'm her personal secretary.
It's my responsibility to understand her.
She's not the type to respect others.
She said her mother wanted to leave,
hoping that she could respect her.
She must have done it.
I've told you so much.
How long have you known each other?
Two months? Three months?
I'm not your rival.
I don't have a crush on her.
I'm not her rival.
Does she know that you like her?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Hello, official global.
How can I help?
Hi, my name is Jay.
I'm an old friend of one of your doctors.
Dr. Deleterious Garon Takis.
I have his full cell phone number,
but it seems like he doesn't use that number anymore.
Right, let me check.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Right, let me check.
Okay, thank you.
Hi, Jay.
Sadly, the record states that he's no longer with us.
He was deployed at the Kandas Trauma Center in Afghanistan
when an unfortunate incident occurred,
an airstrike.
Sorry, could you check that again for me, please?
Jay, I'm afraid we only have one doctor by that name,
Demetrius Garon Takis.
Prior to Afghanistan, he served in Anchorage and Phuket, Thailand.
I'm really sorry if he's your friend.
Thanks for everything.
You know, in the Talmud it says,
whoever saves a life saves the whole world.
We'll see each other again.
I hope so.
Take care of yourself.
I could look at that smile all day.
Hey, man, don't you have an old lady waiting for you back home?
Hey, Jay.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just took my bed off.
You homesick?
Nah, I'm alright.
Cheers.
Where are you from?
Taiwan.
Taiwan?
I don't know.
I don't know where that is.
Let's go over there.
Sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I just got here.
I didn't wait long.
The work hours during the meeting are not always good.
Especially when the hair loss is getting worse.
Like the recent hair loss conditions, it's really dangerous.
You're hungry?
No, we can just eat whatever we want.
How can we? Take it.
Where are you going?
Just take it.
Hurry up.
Yong-bae.
You're here.
I haven't been here for so long.
Of course you have.
Did your husband come to pick you up?
He's been here since I was little.
What's wrong with you?
You're so stubborn.
You're still not going to stop?
Yeah.
What do you mean? Hurry up.
Yong-bae, have some soup.
Okay.
I'm going to have some too.
Look at us.
We've been here for a few days.
It's like this when you're in your early years.
You're so busy.
I don't know what you're busy with.
What are you looking for me for?
Nothing.
I just want to see you.
I can't find you, can I?
I can tell you're busy.
Hurry up.
You're so stubborn.
Why are you so fussy?
Hurry up.
This morning, the news station called me.
They asked if I could go on their live show the day after tomorrow.
One of the guests is Li Xian-hong.
Are you going to deal with Li Xian-hong?
He dares to go on the show?
Maybe.
So I want to ask you.
Do you think I should go against their generation
or against Li Xian-hong?
What do you want to achieve?
I want to let everyone know
that we young people in this generation
are not willing to become a loser.
The point is, in the face of the current situation of the two sides,
the competition we are facing is so fierce.
The ruling party
has lost the opportunity to have a fair competition.
I think
you should tie Li Xian-hong
with the ruling party.
Isn't Zhe-Rong-Hua Group
opening a new stronghold in Shanghai?
You can start with this as a conclusion.
How is it?
Not bad.
These financial groups have been eating up in Taiwan.
They are shamelessly
planning to go to China to make money.
Yong-bae.
I'll cook the pork soup.
You young people
are not easy to deal with.
Hurry up and eat.
I'll continue to cook when I'm done.
Thank you, Yong-bae.
I'll go to the kitchen first.
It's not hot.
It's so sweet.
It's delicious.
Senior Si-Jie.
Hey, Shou-Mei.
Have you finished reading the information I sent you?
Yes. But I have some questions for you.
Please go ahead.
The Guai-Nai-Zhe-Gan-Shi-Zhu-Zhen-Chao
can compress the
amount of nuclear waste into
more than 10,000 news.
I checked it.
It should be fake news.
Because the nuclear waste has already been
compressed into a little bit of news.
At that time, it became a subjective feeling.
The truth became clear.
Maybe we
always believe what we are willing to believe.
The only way to reach the objective
is to
admit your own subjective feeling.
Listen to other voices
and cross-examine.
However,
an original conflict
was started with careful arrangement.
It proved the existence of the conflict.
Three, two, one.
I am Huang Li-Feng.
Welcome back to the show.
We just talked about
the young generation
who think that the five-year-old
have taken over Taiwan's resources
and deprived many young people of opportunities.
What do you think about this, Mr. Lee?
How do we
deprive them of opportunities?
The problem is that they don't work hard.
They have to fight for it.
That's because you, the five-year-old
are still standing in the position of decision-makers.
How can we not?
Mr. Lee, listen to me.
How did you get wealth in your generation?
By plundering.
Yes.
You can plunder Taiwan's natural resources
with this cheap manpower.
The worst thing is that the profit limit is limited.
Okay, Mr. Lee, let me interrupt.
I think we are in a fight.
You are right.
The problem is that
the young generation
think that
the environment is changing.
It's a matter of time.
If we put our efforts
and talents in the society,
there may be no competitiveness.
But actually,
the young people are not worse than us
or even better than us.
Why can't they
like you, Mr. Lee,
when you ask this question?
You should ask the young people in the country.
I totally agree with what Mr. Lee said.
In this age of intellectual explosion,
the doctors from Liu Me and Liu Ou
are everywhere.
I believe that any president like Mr. Lee
has a lot of experience
or background.
Even in this age,
it may not be considered as one thing.
That's right. The times are really different.
The young people in Taiwan are really hard.
Because what you have to learn
is the competition of the world.
To be honest, it's really hard.
Zheng Bang, how many years ago did you come back from Jianqiao?
What do you think?
First of all, I want to respond to
what Mr. Lee said earlier.
I think the most serious problem
in this age of five-year-olds is
that you don't want to hear
the voice of the young generation.
You are the ones who call them strawberries.
You are the ones who hate iron and don't make steel.
Zheng Bang, listen to me first.
Listen to me first.
This is why
I'm here today.
Isn't it?
We are a democratic society.
The best way to eliminate misunderstandings
is to come up with and discuss together.
I think it's really interesting. Mr. Lee
will now put the democratic society at the front.
I want to ask you, when you were in China,
did you dare to say that?
Do you have double standards?
How do you make the people
happy with such standards?
I don't think you need to say so much.
The point is that
the Zhe Ren Group is occupying the national resources
and is going to lick the CCP.
I'm asking you.
Do you have feelings for this land?
This land is for you.
Do we not know
what kind of position
the Zhe Ren Group is behind?
What you are doing now
is like a human being's heart.
What else is the core value?
What is said is
that the businessmen have no motherland.
Yes, I think the Zhe Ren Group
has always been
the benchmark and model
for the cultural companies in Taiwan.
But now
there is such behavior and expression
that really hurts the hearts of the Taiwanese people.
We hurt the Taiwanese people.
We are building
Chinese culture for the Taiwanese people.
But you, as a public figure,
are also the cultural industry of the local companies.
But you have neglected the core
of speech and freedom of publication.
Because of the need and taste of the catering company,
the slogan of the cultural creation
is actually the interests of a small number of people.
Mr. Li, do you want to respond?
Okay, I won't be polite.
Yifang.
I have some internal news here.
Look here.
The Zhe Ren Cultural Authority
has been operating in Taiwan for several years.
It is no longer a secret.
Everyone, look.
They have been
in the Chinese market
five years ago in 2009.
Look carefully.
The Zhe Ren Cultural Authority
This news
is really shocking.
I remember that Mr. Li
said in the media that
he wanted to follow Taiwan
to support local companies
and create local employment opportunities.
But I didn't expect that he said it
and left for China.
Li Dong, are you unable to act
or you don't want to act anymore?
What should we do now?
Mr. Li, you're not recording anymore, are you?
I can't sit here.
We can't record anymore.
Lu Ma has left.
He didn't want to talk to us.
He wants to communicate with us.
We can tell by looking at him.
It's ridiculous.
But if we think about it,
at least the chairman
is sincere in communicating
with them face to face.
Maybe we can find
other companies' media...
Xiao Wei, take me to Lian Yun Street.
Fan Haorong is at the station nearby.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
The Jiu-er Cultural Group
has always been the symbol
and the pioneer
of the cultural industry in Taiwan.
But now,
such behavior and expression
is really like the Taiwanese.
We hurt the Taiwanese.
We are building
Chinese culture for the Taiwanese.
But you, as a public figure,
are also a cultural industry
in the local industry.
You neglected the core of the speech and freedom
by descending on our modifying public figure.
You neglected our
chinese culture.
You neglected the core of the speech and freedom.
But now,
you are the god.
You are the spreak of fortune.
You promoted our culture
and ped называется our culture.
You are the proof of everyone's buildup
does not represent the company's position.
Please believe that our management team
will not be affected by this public relations crisis.
Okay.
Stop it.
Stop recording.
Hey.
If you're here to care about me,
what will happen after I get beaten up by an egg?
Please rest assured that I'm not hurt.
Except for the egg, it's very stinky.
Have you read this book?
Bai Lu told me
that this matter had nothing to do with you.
In this show,
we will continue to focus on the latest gossip news.
Now, let's talk about
the chairman of Zhe Ren Group, Li Xian Hong.
Do you see that?
She looks great and she's a talented person.
But the fame of Li Xian Hong
is not a matter of one or two days.
Let's take a look at Li Xian Hong's past.
She's a real beauty.
From the first female celebrity, Shen Xiao Wen,
to the anchor, Hong Li Fang,
and the rich second generation, Liao Ya Ru,
to the current Lin Li Lian.
What about Wang Hong?
Do you feel very happy now?
I'm very happy.
Now, look at her Facebook.
Many people have been reprimanding her.
They all say that she's a shameless woman.
Wow, she really has been pushed by the public.
I thought that the case was not simple.
Look at the revenge of women.
This time, she abandoned Li Xian Hong
and ran back to her.
Yes, of course.
Do you see that?
All the audience should remember this.
At that time, Li Xian Hong
ran back to find Shen Xiao Wen.
But Hong Li Fang
was very sad.
She left the newsroom.
She had two years.
Everyone, two years.
You can have two children.
You can have three children.
But no one thought that
Li Xian Hong ran to marry Liao Ya Ru,
the rich second generation.
Why did she choose to be
a popular actress?
Because Liao Ya Ru
has a great financial status
in the South.
But Shen Xiao Wen is not easy.
Wang Bao Chuan was a singer for 18 years.
Shen Xiao Wen lost to Li Xian Hong for more than 20 years.
Everyone, more than 20 years.
She abandoned her.
How could she make such a choice?
Although Shen Xiao Wen
has been with Li Xian Hong
since she started her business,
she is always a beauty.
Look, you can't turn a blind eye.
Who is Zheng Dong?
Zheng Dong is still Liao Ya Ru.
So, who is the top three?
It's Shen Xiao Wen.
I think it's a small thing.
Maybe there will be a small five tomorrow.
Who knows?
Who is the small six?
Guo Yi Guo.
I think it's a big deal.
Lower than shadows
My ground is frail
You can't stand but be very still
All of this
Can be yours
If it's worth a thing
All of this
Can be yours
I don't have a plan
But all that is true to my way
This is my world
Yet I'm my world
My eyes are crystal
The rest is just pale
My songs are riddled
It's all my own thought
My words
My chest built thick walls
To ignore that it's hollow
My time is my own
And it's yours as well