Episode 13
Are you crazy?
What if you get into an accident?!
Do you hate it that much? Do you hate being with me that much?
Is that why you're trying to move to another company even though there's time left in your internship period?!
That's right. Then or now, surviving is important to me.
And I'm going to quit the company anyway. Isn't it obvious to grab onto a good opportunity when it's here?
And it's already too late for you to be paying attention to me.
Paying attention to me now is laughable.
Why? Am I pitiful?
Are you sorry? Is that why?
It's not like that.
Then why are you so concerned with every detail of my life?
I...
have "plastic flower."
What?
- "Plastic Flower," lovesickness.
What?!
I like you.
I really like you!
So don't go.
♫ I really love you, ♫
♫ I love you, ♫
I like you.
I like you, Ae Ra!
I...feel like it will explode here, so I'm going crazy.
Do you not know?!
So...
If only you like it, and your heart feels like it will explode,
you thought it would be the same for me as well.
What?
- I told you.
I like how my life is right now. I finally feel like I can live.
The CEO at Unified Shilla must have noticed me, starting with the buffet proposal.
I...
found out how happy it is to accomplish something on your own, and being acknowledged for it.
I found out what a happiness it is to stay up all night creating something.
I was so excited that I couldn't even sleep. Don't you get it?
Ae Ra.
I want to go to that interview.
It's true that it's a good opportunity.
♫ I really love you, ♫
I'll take you.
I want to go alone.
♫ I really love you, ♫
You're late because of me.
What's your reason for deciding to change jobs?
What's the reason that you're changing jobs, Ms. Na Ae Ra.
You didn't even prepare things like that?
What? I just thought honesty...
Honesty?
That you're quitting because you don't want to see your ex-husband's face?
An interview for people with experience looks at character over other things.
Since they know that the people who apply are good at their jobs.
Why are you changing jobs? Was there anything that was difficult while you worked?
Were there any troubles? Things like that.
For questions asking if it was difficult, if possible tell them that it wasn't,
and you can just show them your passion.
Since that's the truth, it won't be too hard.
Since you even postponed your birthday and worked overtime.
Well... although it was because I forced you to.
The CEO can't go home from work because of a mere intern!
Eat it or not.
You really do think of a person.
Did he know and buy this or what?
(Traditionally on birthdays Koreans eat a seaweed soup)
Na Ae Ra.
- Yes.
What do you think are your strengths?
I think it's that I do everything diligently.
That's not it, that's not it.
You have to be more specific when you talk about it.
You can show examples of them with the project we're doing.
Resilience, passion, ambition, and even spontaneity.
Since you were cool.
You're thankful, aren't you?
Yes. Thank you.
While you're thankful, I should quickly make a request.
After you're done with your interview, let's eat dinner together, Ae Ra.
I can't do that.
What's wrong? Are you ok?
What is it? Are you ok?
Pain...I have pain...
Why? Does it hurt somewhere?
Here...
Love... love sickness.
Don't joke around!
It's not a joke. It really hurts.
So, treat me with care since I'm a patient.
That's why...
Dinner.
They said I have love sickness...
They said it's an illness from my heart ...
Iron.
Iro...
It's not even fun.
The customer cannot answer the phone so leave a message...
Aiyoo, really.
These days, Miss is having a difficult time,
but with her problems,
the Chairman is having a very hard time.
He can't sleep at all at night,
and ... if you add the CEO Cha's woman problems,
I can't guarantee...
Chairman's health.
Why is our Ahjussi beating around the bush?
What is it?
I guess Father doesn't know about this.
You know why I brought these picture to you, right?
Since she's CEO Cha's ex-wife, we can look past that,
but I didn't think you would do that, too.
I don't know exactly
what kind of bewitching power this woman has that she can hold onto two men and shake them up ...
but these pictures...
- To Father,
continue to keep this a secret.
I'll take care of the rest.
It's time to go for your scheduled health check up.
I'm not going! I told you I'm not going! How many times did I tell you?!
Where did you work at?
I was at the Venetian in Las Vegas for four years.
I was at the Hilton in the US.
I was the Marketing Team Leader for five years.
I was in charge of the projects related to President Obama and other important U.S officials.
What about you?
Your experience.
I am ...
currently working as an intern with the Mobile Shopping Team.
Intern?
What is this?
Weren't they selecting people with experiences?
Oh my god.
Na Ae Ra... don't be discouraged.
You are here because you were scouted.
I like you.
I really like you!
How are you doing this interview?
Huh?
I really... can't accept this.
That a lowly intern is doing this interview.
What's with the unlucky 'tongue roller'?!
It can't be based on your abilities.
Seeing how you're pretty and all, I wonder if
you have a sponsor somewhere.
Excuse me!
I should take care of that one!
Oh my god.
Jolie Choi? What's Jolie Choi?
Are you an imitation of Angelina Jolie?
As I've always said, you should keep your manners, even when you're saying mean things.
My heart condition and mental condition are really sensitive today,
so don't bother me or I'll...
Oh my God.
- I could jump you, right now.
Ah, she's so ignorant.
Oh my god, you surprised me.
Jolin Choi?
Oh, sorry.
Jolly Choi.
Yes?
The higher-ups at this hotel would like to see you now.
Me?
Actually, the interview is just for formality.
The higher-ups have already...
They've already decided on Jolly Choi.
I knew it.
Should I go now?
-Yes. To the rooftop.
Rooftop. Okay.
I don't know if I should...
But, actually, this is a tip...
But the higher-ups at this hotel
are going to see if Jolly Choi
is going to take this elevator or if you're going to walk up the stairs
and make their decision based on that.
In my opinion, how it will be if Jolie Choi takes the stairs,
and show them your perseverance.
The rooftop...
is at the 20th floor.. and this is..
the 2nd floor. Second floor.
Okay. I got it.
Yeah!
Fighting, Jolly!
Fighting!
-You got it!
Jolie... wow...
What do you consider to be your biggest strength?
I... believe that the relationship between a company and an employee is like fate.
Therefore, I believe that each and every person is precious.
And there is no such thing as a project that isn't important.
Na Ae Ra! Where are you right now?
Is this dinner?
I just felt like eating something sweet.
I think I'm going to be sweet.
Do you want eat some of mine? It's sweet.
You got some on you.
Huh?
Over there.
Where?
Here! Gosh.
Did your interview go well?
Why are there so many?
This and that.
The result of the interview is coming out in
a couple weeks, and...
Ae Ra,
you really... don't like my company?
I do. I like the work and the people there.
But... just because of the situation...
If it's that, then it's fine.
What is?
There's something like that.
Let's eat dinner.
What is this?
I have to do this, so it'll be safe.
Where is this?
Just trust me and follow me. Because it's a nice place.
Are you there? I can't see anything.
I'm cutting the pork cutlet now.
Why isn't it working? Oh!
What is this?
Did it fly over here?
Where did it go? Stay still for a moment.
Where is it? Is it here?
-Where are you....?
Aigoo, is it here?
-Are you crazy?
What do you mean I'm crazy?
-Hey, Cha Jeong Woo!
Are you okay?
Wait, I think your string came undone back here.
I'll do it for you.
-Stop!
I said to stay still. Only I can do this.
-I'll do it!
Stay...!
Okay...
Don't laugh.
Don't laugh!
Ae Ra, are you mad?
No.
That's good.
Look...
I couldn't really see you because it was so dark.
I'm sorry.
It's fine. You can make mistakes.
You said that this was the fun of coming here.
Not just now.
Earlier.
From the time I caught you going on the interview until now.
I, actually,
couldn't see or hear anything because it was so dark in front of me.
But I think I can see things one by one now.
Things are clearer because I can't see.
Jeong Woo..
Your heart that must have felt wronged.
Your heart that must have felt resentful.
Now that I can see it,
I'm really a terrible person.
Ae Ra,
even so,
can't you watch
how I'll get closer to you from now on??
♫ The words that are too bitter to swallow. ♫
♫ To the depths of my heart I really love you. ♫
No lights allowed in this place.
Yes.
Mister!
Yes, yes, I apologize.
Find the light.
We're here.
Yeah...
But... is this the only place you can stay?
Even if he's a colleague, it's still a man's house.
I'm only living with Min Yeong, so it's fine.
This won't do, come to my place.
I told you I'd take care of it myself.
You need to be careful.
Of what?
Of everything!
Everything lingering around!
You're the most dangerous one!
Go quickly.
Go, quickly.
I'm really going now.
You'll fall. Walk properly.
Good night, Ae Ra.
How could you cut off all calls and go into hiding?
I felt upset.
That is...
You don't have to explain.
Wait. Shouldn't you be making excuses?
Normal lovers would nag each other in situations like this.
That's what lovers do.
Seung Hyeon, I'm grateful for how you feel, but...
I'm tired from waiting all day.
I'll go now.
Seung Hyeon...
♫ You won’t know, you won’t know ♫
♫ How much I'm longing for you. ♫
♫ I don't know, I really don't know. ♫
♫ Do you have to leave me like this? ♫
Diet
I'll have to start taking care of my body again.
Here.
Where did you go in the afternoon? I couldn't reach you.
I took care of something really important and urgent.
What was it?
A company's core human power almost got discharged.
I stopped it from happening.
But you can't lose the competition.
From now on, I'm in an emergency mode, so don't look for me even if you can't suddenly reach me.
I got it.
What?
I was saying that...you must have gotten over your illness.
What are you thinking of?
Yes.
What's going on this late at night?
And what's with this alcohol?
You came.
Stop drinking.
Let go.
I told you to not act like a teacher in front of me, didn't I?
Aren't you going to get a hold of yourself?
What? Are you saying that to yourself?
You're the one who should get a hold of yourself.
What are you doing in between 2 women?
That's what you're curious about?
Okay then, I'll give you an answer.
Think well before you speak.
I think I'm going to go a little crazy these days.
I...
am going to start over with Na Ae Ra.
Then...
what about my sister?
You're going to throw her away?
Since you've used her as much as you need to...
What? While saying you're sorry?
Shut your mouth.
So, "No comment" on that?
It's not that I don't know why you're like this, but
I'm not one to play around with liking a person.
So don't say this lightly.
There's a limit to letting go just because you're young.
Stop drinking!
Don't butt in.
I ... want to protect both ... you and Ae Ra.
And I'm going put in my effort to do that.
What if ... you can only choose one?
I hope that won't happen.
Please get a cab for him.
I'm going.
There's no need to look after me.
You should just take care of yourself.
Even so,
can't you wait and see...
how I'm going to get closer to you?
I like you.
I'm saying that I really like you!
D&T Soft Ventures' investment funds are blocked?
D&T Soft Ventures, who were looking for investors
with the development of a new game,
are hitting a road block with investments ...
What is that about?
It's an editorial blog.
The future looks bleak...
Are they the weather station?!
With whose permission are they to give an advanced notice?
Tell them that I'm going to sue them all.
For circulation of malignant rumors!
You used to not care about editorial blogs.
Why are you so sensitive these days?
I'm... I'm a patient.
Alright, alright.
You and your patient act.
This is an example of how we can combine messenger and mobile shopping service,
which was brought up at the company workshop earlier.
Let's take a look at it.
I am a little late.
Continue on, Team Leader Wang.
I'm thinking about making these points
to be used like cash at the shopping mall.
It sounds like a good idea.
For the launching luxury promotion event this time, you'll be going with a luxury appraisal show?
Na Ae Ra?
Ah, yes.
Since, we plan on selling the luxury goods
at a discounted price,
there are a lot of comments whether the luxury products
we're selling are fakes.
So we can provide information on
separating whether something is fake or authentic.
I'm wondering if we should proceed with an event to emphasize
that we don't sell counterfeit products.
You look pretty today.
It does sound okay,
but what's the estimated size of offline customers?
It's not likely to get all the customers in one place.
Ah, that...
What about linking it from our company's homepage
to the internet and broadcasting it?
Since the goal is to inform many people rather than having a big event.
Go ahead and proceed with it.
Promotion is fine,
but don't forget the importance of holding onto
your current clientele.
Yes.
You look pretty today.
What am I doing right now?
You've already drawn up a list of appraisers?
We just got it confirmed.
I drew it up,
ever since the event was first discussed.
Yes.
Just because it's your first meeting,
don't feel intimidated.
Excuse me?
Yes.
They're ultimate professionals,
if you let them push you around and be nice, then
our shopping mall will have to close its doors.
Shouldn't we do our best at a time like this when
our company isn't doing so well?
Yes.
If I get overzealous and run around,
Team Leader Wang, please hold me back.
Ms. Ae Ra,
you sure do run around a bit.
Even if you feel that way,
if you show yourself that easily,
then your opponent will see your cards.
For a woman having to live alone,
you have to be more strict with yourself.
Let's succeed in a big way again and celebrate with a party.
Hello, CEO.
What about this one?
♬ Mirror, mirror, who does this person like? ♬
♬ Heaven, heaven, who is he thinking of? ♬
♬ Guessing and curious about the look in your eyes♬
♫ From now, and you and I.♫
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ah, my hand had a spasm.
♬ Mirror, mirror, who does this person like? ♬
♬ Heaven, heaven, who is he thinking of? ♬
♬ Guessing and curious about the look in your eyes ♬
♬ From now on, you and I, ♬
♬ should we get to know each other? ♬
Of course, the atmosphere at the office is so-so.
If the investors back out, what can the CEO do?
The reports have already been passed around,
so it's obvious for the investors.
Me?
If I can, I'd like to stay here. There's nowhere else for me to go.
Okay, if something comes up, I'll let you know.
Oh, you startled me!
Manager Kang?
Is the company in a lot of difficulty now?
Well, truthfully it's in a crisis.
Our CEO is already infamous
for having excessive scuffles with investors.
Do you think they'll be easy on him when he's not on their good side? They'll say, "Try being in the hot water!"
But an intern like you doesn't have to worry.
Last time, there was a situation like this.
And the CEO and Director Guk were able to get past it.
So, with this, we'll have to trust them both again.
You came out.
I thought you'd be asleep because it's so late.
I got up from sleeping.
But what is it at this hour?
Just because.
What is it?
Did something happen?
Ae Ra,
can I hold you once?
Excuse me?
Seung Hyeon.
Please.
Just stay like this for a moment.
You...
might be...
really disappointed in me in the future.
Why are you acting so strange?
Because I became certain of how much I like you.
So I am never going to step aside.
Today's confession,
it doesn't matter if I'm the only one to like you.
I won't ever give up on you.
Sorry for waking you up.
Go back and sleep.
What is this?
The list of contributors
that can fund us immediately.
This isn't the kind of money we can use clearly.
You also said that this money is dangerous.
We're not in the situation to pick and choose.
This money
will end up holding our company down.
We can't.
Then do you want to release an article announcing our marriage?
In this situation,
isn't this the safest and reliable way to
get our funds?
You know that, too.
With just one line about our marriage in an article, a new investment is a guarantee,
and we can also block the investments from leaving.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Why?
-Because ultimately, it's deceiving the investors with lies!
There must be another way.
I'll find it, so just wait a while longer.
If you change your mind,
there is an easy way to avoid a crisis.
I don't want to use you for this.
It's not because of Na Ae Ra?
Are you thinking about remarrying her?
Is that why we can't release news articles about marriage?
I do not take care of business matters with personal feelings.
It's just that,
I think I'll have to say this.
I can't accept your heart.
I'm sorry.
So from now on...
-I think I need to say this, too.
The danger this company is in right now,
with the method that you have,
we can never overcome this.
I told you the best method that I can do.
The judgement... is up to you.
CEO, the Unified Shilla Hotel CEO has contacted you.
I was surprised after hearing from the secretary.
I knew that you don't usually invest in this field.
Yes, I don't.
There's too much competition there.
But somehow,
it turned out like this.
Let's just say that I came to trust you while looking at this project.
I'll invest as much as you need right now.
Whatever the reason,
I'm really grateful that you're investing like this.
I can't accept that money for nothing.
Soon, there will be a fresh project that the company will announce.
I can't tell you about it right now, but if we can announce it,
it's something that will make a big mark in mobile shopping.
Since Shilla is investing in it,
I'll see to that you get some profit.
It's interesting.
This side, that side.
Excuse me?
Never mind. I do have a stipulation.
Give us a small role in...
the management of the company.
That......
-We won't directly get involved in management.
But please let my delegate take my place.
Because I absolutely have my trust in you.
Just... it'll be fine if you can just think of it
as collateral.
Hey, I did it the way you told me to,
but what are you scheming right now?
What do you mean "scheming?"
But even if it weren't for you,
I think it was good to make an investment.
That CEO Cha has charisma
and is very reliable.
He's a person I really like.
What? What I just did,
is it a knife in the back, or a shield to block the knife?
Well...
I'm contemplating that.
Hey! Is dating all you're doing nowadays?!
I'm looking at your grades from Korea!
Of course!
I think I have to hang up now.
Son, I love you, I miss you, I'll call you again!
I think I was a bother to you...
No, no, it's not.
I was worried, so I wanted to hear my kid's voice.
Is there something wrong?
My tooth is hurting suddenly.
The company is up and down
and if it gets worse,
I'm afraid that my desk will be taken away (get fired),
so I can't leave the office.
Look at what I'm saying. I'm sorry.
Please sit.
Here.
I'll only accept it because of my tooth.
Is he your son?
-Yeah, he's my second child.
I told him to study, but why is he just dating?
But it's good to see that.
You have someone to talk to when it's hard.
Yes, I like that.
But it's not like we didn't have a crisis as well.
Crisis?
- Was it when my first child was three?
Ah...while I was raving about, trying to do my own business,
I blew all the money away!
Back then, my wife said she couldn't live with me and wanted to put a seal on it (divorce papers).
Oh, just the thought of it now...
Then, but how ...?
Oh...
because of our second rascal.
When we were fighting whether we should end it or not, my wife got pregnant with this one.
My wife said this back then.
"Even though it was difficult, what can we do?"
Just think that our second is our hope,
and to start over again.
Oh, to all parents,
their children are their hope.
Don't they live to watch their children?
You succeeded,
and even if you were to repay all of those debts because of it,
nothing would have changed for me.
Because that money
wouldn't have been able to revive our hope that disappeared.
Lost hope..
Hope...
Was it you?
I'm sorry..
Does it hurt? Are you okay?
Gosh, what kind of woman...?
Did you get trained in combative sport?!
It's because you grabbed me from behind.
Geez, you're always sneaky!
It serves you right!
I knew it would be like this.
Now I feel like I can live.
Isn't it really difficult?
I heard all the financial resources are cut.
You don't even have a penny?!
That's so like you!
I do have a penny!
Don't worry.
What do you mean worry ...
It's because I might not get paid.
And what's with your face? Why did you come here when you're having a hard time?
You being here is the hardest for me.
I'll go to Min Yeong's house tomorrow.
Don't misunderstand, because I am not leaving because of you.
My stress just got pushed away in one shove.
I have to go to the office.
I'll leave.
Good night.
Cha Jeong Woo!
You are okay, right?
Who am I?
I am the IT field's leader, Cha-Era ... Cha Jeong Woo!
I'll be leaving.
Ae Ra?
What?
Last time, on the rooftop...
Never mind.
Good night. I'll leave.
Are you alright?
I am alright.
In the afternoon, there was another call from Dr. Kim.
If you don't come to the regular check up this time...
I will take care of that.
Even then...
I told you I would take care of that.
Director!
Let go!
I told you to let go!
CEO Cha ... this bastard!
Luxury Emotion Show with D.
Check often on the internet live broadcasting screen.
If the connections come in too fast and the broadcast can't go out out properly,
immediately get the support of the server team that's on standby.
Yes.
Did you check the commentary?
- Yes.
Hello.
CEO, thank you
for coming all the way here.
I can't just let such an important event for the company pass by.
But why is it
that I don't see the person responsible on scene?
Oh, Na Ae Ra? She is in the warehouse.
She has to check on the bags that we'll use for the event.
Warehouse?
Warehouse.
Aiyoo, that warehouse is nice.
It's really dark and remote...
Excuse me?
Ah, it's nothing.
You're about to crawl into that bag.
You scared me.
I'm in the middle of doing some really delicate and important work here.
What is that?
What are you doing?
This is the real luxury product. Look at the buckle.
This is fake.
Although they look the same, there is a difference.
The length of the buckle on the real luxury product is...
a bit shorter than the one on the fake one.
The real product is exactly...
1.35 cm.
You didn't know, right?
I've worked in a luxury shop so I do have an eye for these things.
You know Company "C", right? There, the fake one is where the curve of the logo is wide at the angle.
And for the Company "D", you can differentiate by
whether the logo is engraved or not on the front button.
Isn't it hard?
Yeah, it is hard.
What are you doing? I explained it all to you.
I guess you have a lot of spare time.
No. I am really busy.
I came by here coincidentally.
You had your nose embedded in this bag so I came, just in case, you went into respiratory distress and died.
Aiyoo, you.
CEO, you were here.
Yes.
I came by here for a moment while I am on my way to the meeting.
Oh, is that so? Then, I guess you'll have to leave soon.
Keep up the good work.
Na Ae Ra has no time to waste.
Then please keep up the good work.
Then I will go work.
Okay. Please work hard.
Because it'll become your last work at this company.
Right, Na Ae Ra?
Can you please move?
Because I have to pass through.
Yes, Appraiser. Have you arrived?
Yes, I will go to the lobby.
Luxury bag sold by Don't Talk.
Yes.
The appraiser has arrived.
You've come?
You can just check this.
Yes.
What are you doing, not bringing the bags?
Yes. I've brought the bags.
Okay. Now it is all done.
Ok, here.
They're all matched up.
Are you nervous?
A bit, since it's my first time broadcasting like this.
There is no need to be nervous. Do you want to see the screen?
Why? Is there a problem?
It's 30 seconds before broadcast. You're all ready right?!
Yes.
What should I do?
How....
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute.
What is the matter?
Have you gone crazy?
The bag was switched.
What did you just say?
Oh my...
The bag was switched.
So how did it go?
They weren't even able to start. The internet message boards are a mess with all the commotion being raised.
What will happen to Na Ae Ra?
Hey, go find out what's happened.
No. No. I will go.
Hello.
Yes. Please have a seat first. Have a seat.
But Ae Ra, it was you...who was in the warehouse before the broadcast.
Think about it well. If you get blamed all for this...
Aigoo, aigoo, think about it well! Oh.
Secretary Kim...
Secretary Kim?
No.
Tell me again.
It was ordered by Chairman.
How could he do such a....
Are there any other people who know about it?
There are none.
The CCTVs from the warehouse onwards, collect all of them.
If it goes into someone else's hands (finds out),
it'll become a headache.
♫ What do I do? What do I do? ♫