Sleep, wake up, and go to work. That's what I do every day.
And that's all I do because I enjoy it.
If I do the same thing every day,
nothing good happens, but nothing bad happens either.
Another gray hair.
Center Morning! Here is our next segment.
It looks great and it tastes delicious!
- A curious collection of sweets.
- Time to eat.
Today, we'll visit a popular pancake house in Ebisu.
- The owner raises his own chickens.
- It looks good.
Their pancakes are always made with fresh eggs.
It seems more men are visiting lately, too.
Old men can't go alone.
I tried the pancakes as well.
♫ Can you feel the shakes in your body ♫
♫ When something is about to start? ♫
♫ Are you ready to love somebody? ♫
♫ Yeah, to love somebody ♫
♫ But, I'm having a hard time alone ♫
♫ I don't even know myself yet ♫
♫ What does it mean to “become an adult”? ♫
♫ I was thinking that you can stay ♫
♫ As you are now ♫
♫ I've touched your hand ♫
♫ At that moment, the one who was reflected in my eyes ♫
♫ Was you ♫
♫ You were the one for me ♫
[Old Fashion Cupcake]
Yes, okay. I understand.
[Episode 1]
I got it. Have a good day.
So...
The boat shipment will get there by 2 p.m.
I'm truly sorry, thank you for the help.
It's fine, feel free to rely on me.
What?
Bosses are only helpful in times like these.
Really, I'll carry you anywhere.
I could never, Nozue-san.
(T/N: San, honorific meaning Mr., Ms.)
And so, Nakamura-kun, can you help us come back from this?
(T/N: kun, honorific used to address men who are younger or the same age as the speaker)
Yes, of course.
I'll be in your care.
Yes.
Good.
Nozue-san, good work today.
You too, Togawa.
Department Head Kirishima called.
She wants to talk with you.
Oh, I wonder why.
You never stopped by after work.
Oh, I forgot.
Please don't forget.
Sorry, but it's all okay.
It's never important if it's after work.
Based on the timing, maybe it's HR-related.
Okay, I'll go see her in person.
Nozue-san is so cute today.
Like every day.
I would do an hour of overtime if it's for him.
Thanks to him, we don't need to work overtime.
Yeah, he works so fast.
But why is he single? He's so popular.
Now that you mention it, Kanda-san, from accounting,
is following Nozue-san around again.
She's fine with being second.
What? She actually said that?
To that extent? What did Nozue-san do to her?
He hasn't done anything, of course.
Just seeing him laugh tickles our maternal instincts.
We're so sinful.
Everyone.
Don't make him work overtime.
- Sorry.
- Of course.
I'll get back to work.
Again.
And how about Togawa-san?
You know what?
You can't avoid this forever.
Yeah...
You're so talented.
But I'm not department head material, so...
Geez.
Just think about it, okay?
That wouldn't change much.
I pushed for them to promote you.
At least help me save face by thinking about it for half a day.
Fine, only because we started here at the same time.
Geez, you never seem to want anything.
Oh right, are you free tonight? Let's eat some sushi. What do you think?
Sure, are you paying?
No, it's a Goukon. Takitani wanted me to invite you.
(T/N: Goukon, small gathering where men and women can meet)
- I'm not going.
- Come on, just consider it.
Bye then.
Shouldn't you at least want girls?
That's sexual harassment.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's you, Togawa-san.
You can't smoke here.
I miss our smoking room.
How about you quit smoking?
It's too late.
- Could you?
- Sure.
This was at your desk.
Sorry, I guess I left it out.
What did Boss Kirishima want?
Oh, she invited me to a Goukon.
What? That's it?
Yeah.
- Do I smell that much?
- Oh, sorry.
Are you going to the Goukon?
No, I'm not that young anymore.
Aren't you still 39?
I'm already 39.
If you're already 39, I want you to get promoted.
You should be in Kirishima's position.
No, I'm fine with where I am now.
That kind of competition is a bother.
You used to be hungrier for this.
Was I?
You're still 39, so don't say things like that.
Now I'm getting scolded by a 29-year-old.
I enjoy working with you.
That's not why I'm saying this,
but I want you to enjoy work too.
Sorry for stepping out of line.
No, not at all.
Actually, thank you.
It's nothing.
Oh right, Togawa-san, do you know any good places for dessert?
I know a few.
Can you show me?
Oh, sure.
Okay, I'll leave that to you.
Great, okay.
- Hello.
- Sorry for barging in.
It's fine.
It's not much, but as a form of apology…
- Oh, please. That call earlier was enough.
- Not at all.
Thank you. Please sit.
- Thank you.
- Please.
Nakamura is doing his best to make up for this. Please understand.
Of course. We plan to work with you for a long time.
Thank you.
Oh, right. I found a delicious shochu place recently.
(T/N: Shochu is distilled liquor)
Would you like to go together sometime?
Of course.
Came out for a smoke?
But you can't smoke here.
Right. Thanks.
Why don't you quit?
I heard that exercise helps alleviate nicotine withdrawal symptoms.
We could go to the gym together.
Are you listening?
It must be nice to be a couple of girls.
What?
See? Looks fun, right?
But a couple of guys can have fun too.
Guys, no matter how excited they are,
never become that happy.
Well, I guess so.
They take photos, wait in line for pancakes, and talk about love…
They laugh at silly girl talk
and have pure fun.
Are you jealous?
I am.
I mean, ever since we were young, we were never that lively.
Well then.
Let's take a lively photo.
No, that's not…
You're right.
But if I were a girl, I might've talked to you about love
and taken lively photos with you.
You're kind, so you'd play along, right?
Say cheese.
What are you doing?
Your pixel count is out of date.
I tried acting like a girl, taking a hot guy's photo.
Am I hot?
The girls in the office said it.
Those girls, huh?
Oh right, how long is half a day?
- Half a day?
- Yeah.
Twelve hours, I guess.
Or I guess, if you're only counting the hours we're awake,
it's six or eight hours.
That long?
Whatever, I'll be right back.
Hello, Kirishima?
Yeah, it's a bit early,
but after a lot of thinking, I'll have to turn down the promotion.
There are lots of more talented people.
No, I don't know what I'd be able to do,
and I don't even know what I want to do.
I…
I haven't accomplished anything until now.
So I don't know what I'd be able to do,
and I don't even know what I want to do.
That's not a good reason.
But what more can I say?
- You're like this every time…
- Hello?
- Keep this up and you'll never…
- Hello? Hmm, maybe it's my flip phone.
The reception…
- Hello?
- Hello? Wait, what?
Flip phones are convenient.
All right, let's head back.
Nozue-san.
Yeah?
Would you like to play pretend as a girl?
Play pretend? What do you mean?
Let's go.
Wait. Where are we going? Togawa.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you, this looks delicious.
Are you not eating?
I mean, this is…
It's a strawberry pancake.
No, I mean we stick out here.
We're in the middle of playing pretend.
Forget that you're a man.
But…
You're the one who said you wanted to be a girl.
I didn't mean this.
It's okay, those girls are just head over heels for your devilish charm.
No, they're not. They're staring at you, a hot guy.
Stop that. Eat before it gets cold.
Do you have someone you like, Nozue-san?
- Why so suddenly?
- It's girl talk.
“Girl talk"?
Do you like anyone?
I'm almost forty. I'm over the hill.
It's too late for love.
- You're scared, aren't you?
- What?
You're afraid of dating,
receiving new work from your promotion, getting more responsibilities…
Even eating pancakes here is scary.
You realized at this age that you've only worked your whole life,
but you don't know what to do or what you want to do.
Now that you're older, you're afraid you can't just say you don't know.
You're afraid of challenging the unknown and failing.
You're afraid of your 30s just ending like that.
You even regret that you've put all your passion into your work—
Togawa.
Yes?
I'm staying calm because it's you.
Say that to anyone else, and they'll hit you for sure.
I would only say this to you.
Also, I said that I was fully ready to get hit.
An out-of-shape guy in his 40s hitting a fit guy in his 30s?
Only my hand would get hurt.
Sorry for stepping out of line again.
Why bother even saying it, then?
Sorry.
Was I that obvious?
That right before going over the hill,
I was having an embarrassing midlife crisis?
It's not that. I'm the only one who noticed.
You're always the perfect boss.
Why couldn't I fool you?
- Because I like you.
- What?
I like working with you.
Oh, I see. Thanks.
I learned everything by watching you, day in, day out.
That's why I've grown into be such an outstanding subordinate.
Are you complimenting yourself?
I've watched you at all hours,
so I was even able to see the early symptoms of your menopause.
Wait, I have menopause? Isn't it a bit soon?
True, you're still 39.
It's still too soon even at 40.
Basically, you're still young.
I have my doubts.
Regret can lead to happiness and can be a fuel to your life.
Oh, I've heard those words before.
- I learned them.
- From whom?
I want to help you so you can burn that fuel and become happy.
I'm just your boss at work.
Would you like more coffee?
I'm good, thank you.
- Yes, please.
- Here.
Anyway, before your menopause gets worse,
let's think of countermeasures.
Are you talking about anti-aging?
Yes.
First, consume your fuel and temporarily increase your serotonin.
- Go ahead.
- Okay, I got it.
How is the taste of regret?
It's 100 times tastier than I thought.
Glad to hear it.
Yeah, that's good.
Togawa-kun.
Yes?
Thanks.
No problem.
- Let's take a photo.
- What? But…
When you play pretend as a girl,
this is important for anti-aging.
So photos are mandatory.
Here it goes.
With the pancake.
Was I in the picture?
Please finish it in five minutes. We'll miss the meeting.
Five minutes? I'm not a student.
Hey. Today, you were interviewed.
Are you okay?
- Thank you for today—
- You were incredible.
“I haven't accomplished anything.”
“I don't know what I'd be able to do.”
“I don't even know what I want to do.”
You were so honest.
Well, you obviously were desperate to get in anywhere.
But it is a strength to make excuses for yourself
and be able to regret it openly.
Lots of growth and emotions can only come from regret.
For example, for people who want to change themselves, like you,
regret can lead to happiness and can be a fuel to your life.
Our company is obsessed with burning fuel like that.
I've burned a lot of it, too.
So I'm pretty sure you'll be hired.
What?
Now then, want to grab a drink?
Um, well...
- Let's go!
- What?
Let's go.
Now I see.
What is it?
Hey, Togawa.
Yes?
Want to go grab a drink? It's been a while.
When you get a certain amount of experience,
it gets in the way of gaining new experiences.
You always predict negative outcomes
and don't let yourself do anything.
- There's a smoking area there.
- Oh, thanks.
But…
No, let's go to the station.
Are you quitting?
No, I'm thinking of cutting down.
I see, you're quitting, aren't you?
I never said that.
That's good.
I support your decision to quit.
Like I said, I never said I would.
Why are you laughing?
[Preview]
You're cute when you laugh, Togawa.
Nozue-san and Togawa-san got pretty close lately.
Acting like a girl and trying new things have amazing anti-aging properties.
Please act completely like a girl.
A girl should give a cuter response when hugged by a hot guy.
Nozue-san, are you mad?
I'm not mad.
Nozue-san.