Hi
Mei Mei
You still have more than two months left
It 's about to give birth
I want to come and see you .
Mom
I 'm fine
You don 't need to come .
I wanted me to come over
I can help you with that
I can do your laundry
Then cook
When you finish giving birth
Confinement is out
I 'll be back
Mom
I
I 'm fine .
You don 't use
I know
I 'm pregnant with this baby
You feel very uncomfortable .
Both you and my dad think
I lost your people
Right
Why are you here ?
You 're not happy when you come .
In my heart
Very uncomfortable as well
We don 't have to force it
Right
All right
Let 's just leave it like that
I 'm fine
2706712
Message
Born or not
When available
Call me back quickly
Please call more times
Thank you
Mom 's okay
Alright
Don 't fight .
The opposite side must be busy .
I 'm free
Kangqi will call back
That 's right
Don 't worry too much
It must be fine .
You haven 't had a baby and you don 't understand
Having a child
The dangerous person is in the delivery room
The panicked person is outside the delivery room
How dangerous is it
Only Time
I can 't persuade or stop
I watched
I can only look at her
Go into the dangerous area
If I could
Just stay with her .
All right , all right
Don 't think so much .
She would rather face it herself
You don 't want me to accompany you either
How much do you think she hates me
I 'll do it
Hi
Mei Mei
Susu
Lai Xiaoyan
Eat a poached egg
And your father
Grandma 's own
Xiaoyan
Give this soup bowl to Grandma
Grandma serves you soup
Jianxiong
Mom , I 'll do it myself
I 'm fine , fine
OK
Mei Mei , give me the bowl
This is so rich .
Mom is going to the market today
Buy a lot of things
Fortunately , we went to meet us .
Otherwise , it cannot be carried
Thank you for your hard work , Ma
No hard work
Take care of your own daughter
What 's the hard work ?
Xiaoyan that
Take grandma 's fish soup .
Drink it
Grandma is old
Gastrointestinal digestion is not moving
Thank you , Grandma
You 're welcome
Eat
Mom
This is more than just
Take care of Mei Mei
You took care of us
A family of all sizes
Do you want to eat the meat ?
I 'm eating .
That 's right
Mom
I have to give you the grocery money
Why is this family talking about money ?
This is a bit outsider
This is not
I have retirement pay
You cannot contribute money and effort at the same time
Mom , please accept it
I feel at ease after accepting him .
Transferred it to you
Eat Eat
Let Li Jianxiong eat quickly
Then I 'll accept it
More refund and less replenish
I got it for you .
This Susu
Mom
I brought you a red bean soup
I 'm afraid you won 't have enough .
I 'm full I
The old man
How much appetite can you have ?
I 'll put it here first .
Eat when I 'm hungry later
What are you doing ?
Bookkeeping
Mom
Let me discuss something with you .
We will unify the specifications in the future
They all eat the same food
Differential treatment is not good
Jianxiong snitched .
None
You
Eggs in the fridge
It 's different
You make two pots of fish soup as well
Who doesn 't think much about it ?
Then I 'm also for
Consider this family
Xiaoyan
That half - big boy will eat me to death
Right
The one on the table
The energy of eating
It 's pretty scary .
Like fleeing
You are now
There was no job just now , right ?
Susu Ma Now
There is no source of income for the time being
That 's not open source
Then I will calculate horizontally and vertically
I just thought about it
Then only throttling is possible
Mom
We 're not at home
Is the situation special
You just have a bowl of water .
Are you fair or not
Everyone is very sensitive
Li Jianxiong is not already
Did I give you living expenses ?
Anyway , we will
Just treat everyone equally
Wu Limei
What do you mean by that ?
Do you think
I feel sorry for my money
Then I skimmed them both
No No No
That 's not what I meant
What do you mean ?
I
I 'll say
You are always selfish
You said you eat eggs , right ?
That between Li Yan and Su Su
The food is different
Li Jianxiong and I eat
It 's not the same .
Then what if someone sees it ?
What do you think ?
People will be chilling .
This matter can 't stand thinking .
Then why do you think about it ?
You said
Still chilling
What you say is so unconscious .
That Susu is your daughter
Then I feel distressed
I feel sorry for Susu
Isn 't it just sorry for you ?
Is Xiaoyan not enough to eat
Yes No
From inside my mouth
Save food for him
I didn 't say
From his father 's mouth
Save it for him .
That 's right
My bowl of water is not even .
But if I 'm missing
I 'll make up for it .
You wouldn 't do it
What are you doing here
Raising a teacher to ask for crimes
Not
I 'm not fine
Talking to you
The problem is that you didn 't say nice things
Right
You said that
We can 't talk , okay ?
Then let 's not talk about it .
I was wrong
You two stop fighting here
Your blood pressure for a while
Up again
Don 't I serve you red bean paste ?
Eat or not
You try it
I don 't eat it
It 's delicious
Why are you wronged ?
Let me see
I don 't I don 't
Come on , let me see , let me see
I 'm so wronged
Don 't , don 't move .
It 's beautiful with pear blossoms and rain
Let me see
Whose old lady brings rain with pear blossoms
It 's so beautiful .
What are you doing ?
All right , all right , all right
Don 't be angry with her anymore .
I 'm not angry with her
She is pregnant
What 's there to worry about
Are you wronged ?
None
I keep accounts
Mom
You wander around
I can 't pee
You are melodramatic
Don 't lock the door
In case anything happens
I can break in
Don 't break into the door .
All right
You 're not that good .
In case you
You sit on the toilet
You suddenly stand up
My eyes are dark and I faint
If your feet are numb
You slipped on your feet
I can 't
Did you rush in with a stride
Don 't curse me , okay ?
Then at least I 'm out there .
I can give it to you
Delivery paper or something .
Row Row Row
Hurry up and hand me a piece of paper
OK
I 'll take it
I take
Mei Mei , you 're a shit
Still urinating
Mom
Is it big or small
This This
I 've gone all the big and small .
If you didn 't
What are you doing in there ?
Then this this
What are you doing here ?
You can 't drink water here .
Let 's go to the toilet now
Not
You need to be careful
What I told my mother
Mom can be a
Reasonable calculation
We can prevent it in case
So are you big or young ?
Before going
It 's not born .
Is it big or small
You 've been talking for a long time
You still didn 't tell me
Is it big or small ?
Are you thirsty ?
I just made a pot of tea
Mom
At this time
I usually don 't drink anything .
Tea at the door of this toilet
What 's this ?
Delicious
Delicious , delicious , delicious
Exciting
Mei Mei
You turned off the air conditioner
I didn 't turn it off
You closed it
Is it my mother ?
Impossible
The remote control is
I 'm here
The air conditioner in that house
Is a brand
The remote controller can be universal
Impossible
You think too much
Sleep , sleep
Mei Mei
You are
Fifteen minutes
I understand
Within 20 minutes
All is OK
Don 't work hard .
I 'm very gentle . Don 't worry
Mom , bring me a roll paper
Mom , I still want a cup of tea
OK , I 'll do it right away
How about
Shit
What is the form
Describe it to me
Very good Very good
It 's normal
The color is also normal
Come here for you
I have one thing to do now
It 's painful
You know that
Now I go to the bathroom every time
I have to look at the shit
It 's just me , I won 't go to see it
I can 't report it to you either
This is related to you
What about your physical condition ?
You have to take a look
If you are constipated
Then I 'll have to give you some more .
This green bean
If it is not formed
I 'm going to add red beans to you .
I don 't want to see it
You 're looking at your own
It doesn 't depend on anyone else .
Something to watch
What 's wrong
Turn on the air conditioner
Sleep
Wait , I 'm anxious
What are you doing
Mom made you do this
Jianxiong
You 're back
This This
Is she severely infertile ?
Vomiting and dizzy
I searched on the Internet
A folk remedy
Multi - pronged approach
Try
What is the effect of Mei Mei
Stop vomiting
This is pretty good .
What do you mean it 's ten o'clock ?
Ten o'clock
Turn off the lights and the book says you 're happy
Children are happy when TV is turned off
Turn off the TV
Don 't mention pregnant women in the book
Go to bed early and wake up late to take care of your health
Okay , okay , Jianxiong
You should learn to cooperate
OK OK
Fit
Yes , yes , yes , help her .
Okay , come on , slow down
Get Up
Go to bed quickly
OK
I drink black chicken and lotus seed soup today
What are you laughing at ?
I heard it
Someone has been angry recently
No wonder this anger is not good .
Mom , I 'll bring this over .
No need to wait
Mom
Didn 't I say everything ?
This is not the same as this
Can we all eat the same food ?
I worked hard
What are you doing for ?
And you picked it
Do you like to eat or not
Grandma , stop eating .
Okay , eat it
That
Poached Egg
Eat Eat
Mei Mei Ya
This is yours
Xiao Yan Lai
Let 's do it ourselves
OK OK
That Susu
You eat this of me
I can 't eat such an expensive egg
Come
Susu helps me serve soup
This is for your mother
OK
Mei Mei
This bowl is yours
Your
Let me serve it
Li Jianxiong , please drink my bowl
Not
Jianxiong 's bowl is here
I 'm in Sheng
All right , Mom
Yes Yes Yes
Let him drink this from me
I 'll just drink this .
This is yours
Jianxiong Lai
Xiaoyan
Did you give it to Xiaoyan ?
Let 's eat .
I I
I 'll go to serve my meal first . I 'm hungry .
I won 't eat it
Troubling everyone
Why ? No , no
What are you doing ?
I don 't want to eat it
That 's your real mother
Can you talk nicely
What attitude
I 'm still your mother .
Wu Limei , what are you doing ?
What kind of young lady temper are you doing
Then my grandma
The soup I worked so hard to cook for you
You didn 't eat a bite of the meal you cooked .
It really is
What kind of young lady temper do you have ?
I said I didn 't eat or didn 't eat .
OK OK OK
You come out and drink the soup
Line
It 's annoying
OK , sit down and eat first
You 're used to it
Eat a chicken leg
Grandma
Don 't take it too seriously .
You said you two
It 's been decades
This day of swords and swords
At this time
There 's no way to reverse it
Isn 't it the same with my mother ?
Between me and her
There are still many unsolved problems
She doesn 't appreciate it and I receive it
She doesn 't understand you
I understand you .
You and I are on the same side
Sweet mouth
But that 's how she talks
Not sounding good
I guess it 's also genetic
I still love you in my heart
Why don 't we talk about intergenerational relatives
I 'll kiss you
We 're good .
Ignore her
That
I 'll go in
I 'll bring you a thick dress .
Mom
I 'm fine
Go your business
Today
Mei Mei
Ever since she was pregnant
She 's quite picky .
Probably today
The chicken soup is a little too oily
That 's why she lost a little temper
It 's not a matter of oil or not
You saw it anyway
My little thoughts
I don 't want to hide it from you either
She thinks I treat you hard .
She feels sorry for you
That
There 's no harsh treatment ?
You are biased towards Susu
Slant to Meimei
That 's not
A matter of course
I 'm good to Susu
It 's also sincere .
No matter how good
Then more or less in my heart
That still has to be calculated for Li Yan
More
They 're all parents .
Na Na
Be partial to your own children
Isn 't that normal ?
Jianxiong I actually am
I really like you
I treat you like my own family
But Mei Mei
She is on me after all
A piece of meat that fell down
Mei Mei 's
I 'm sure I want the best for her
Of course I understand this
You understand that she may not understand
She also understands
Look at us all
Living in the same house
It 's difficult for her to be caught in the middle .
But she knew
How is she
You don 't really get angry with her
Really competing with her
Are you giving me a high hat ?
Then she is always
Trouble caused by progestogen
After Mom
Please be more bearable .
His own daughter
I can handle whatever I want
It 's you
You 're going to live with her for the rest of your life
You have to be more bearable
Then I should .
Lai Ma
Coming Branch
I , I , I
I don 't smoke anymore
You should smoke less too
This is the only one
The last one
I quit tomorrow
This second - hand smoke
You want to dye this hair inside
I smell all over my body
It 's not good to bring it in
Your room is quite warm
Did you go to our ladies ' room
Yes No
Yes , yes , that 's the expression
I just saw our ladies ' room
When you spoil me
This is my expression
One men 's toilet and one women 's toilet
It is agreed that the well water will not violate the river water
Why do you just
You have to waste it
Where 's our ladies ' room
Are you a dog
Did you learn the territory from a dog ?
Sorry
I just spoke
A little too much , isn 't it ?
I 'll go clean the toilet
OK
That won 't happen again .
I couldn 't fix that men 's room .
I 'll just say it
I 'll accompany you .
Leave it to me
The first time was a little uncomfortable
Just let me get used to it .
Is it OK
Can you do it
Can 't get in
Let 's not care about the toilet today
All right
Find someone to report repair tomorrow
I will pay the money
Leave it alone
I can 't stand it anymore
Grandma
Are you cold ?
My room is a little cold
Grandma
I want to pat
How old are you
You still need to pat
I want to pat
You 're not sleeping
Why are you ignoring me
You should go to bed early in the future
Do you know
Grandma , I want to pat it
Pat , pat , pat , pat .
It 's our Susu Hao
Susu Guai
What 's wrong
I think I heard something .
There is no movement .
Mei Mei
Meimei , what 's wrong with you
What 's wrong with you
This supper today is really
There 's nothing wrong with it
I 'm so uncomfortable
No
Everyone eats the same thing
We 're all fine
This is a pregnancy reaction , right ?
Is everything okay ?
It 's fine
You can only endure it slowly .
Here
Let me look over your side
And
Mom
Are you smoking ?
I didn 't .
On your head
It smells like cigarettes .
Mom
Do you know this second - hand smoke
To me and Xiaobao
How harmful is it ?
That means you are my mother .
If it is Li Jianxiong
I wouldn 't let him into the room .
I 'll go wash my hair
Mom
Come , come , come , come
Let me tell you
Mom
I 'm not here to settle old scores with you .
I 'll do it for a while .
I think
You took good care of me
Right
I reach out to my clothes
Open your mouth when you come with food
Have a good time
But don 't you feel it
Living habits of the two of us
It 's different
This person and his habits
is very important
Every day , you say
The more I 'm afraid of
The more you get
The more I care about
The less you do
I 'm worried every day
You know that
There isn 't a day that I 'm not afraid .
There isn 't a day that I don 't get nervous
I don 't have a day at ease
Mom
I just wanted to ask this
Why are you here
Take care of me .
Without you to take care of
Actually , I 'm doing fine
I can put myself
Very well taken care of
Why are you
You have to take care of me
Mom
It 's my fault
I didn 't mean to
Go in
I 'm holding you and watching the steps
Then you should go to bed early .
Mom
You fixed the toilet
Small Questions
Look at the bathroom
It 's so neat
I 'm sorry , this is
Then leave it
I 'll come , I 'll come
Mei Mei
Breakfast is ready
Rise and eat
Hungry will cause hypoglycemia
You can 't afford it
Su Su ah
Why
Grandma wrestled later
Grandma told you
Take up your time
I want to see you today
Your mother 's attending doctor
Dr. Xu
That 's right
I have to catch up with the draft today
In two days
I 'll take you there in two days .
No , it must be today
Tell you about Grandma
Delay Today Tomorrow
Tomorrow will be delayed
I have to go today
Did you hear it
I 'm going to get in there .
I 'm going to get in .
I did this myself
Replenishing Qi and Nourishing Body
I think you doctors
Stay up late
Suitable
Thank you , Grandma
But our hospital has rules
I can 't accept it
I 'm not
I don 't mean anything else
Dr. Xiao Xu
My daughter is older
I 'm worried about her pregnancy
I hope you can
Please take care of me
Grandma
The hospital does not allow admission
I gave him that last time
Extra delicious beef jerky
He didn 't want it .
Let 's do this
After all , it was made by my elders .
Why don 't you try some pieces
Is it a thought
Okay , then I 'll take a few .
Thank you , Grandma
I will do my best
How are you ?
Did your relationship with your mother ease ?
That 's what my mom and I do
Live your life
I was in front of Aunt Wu last time
I praise you
Which time ?
That time when you opened your five fingers to go to confinement
No wonder
You , mother and daughter
A lot of ease
It 's Dr. Xu .
You 're so understanding
None
Do you have a girlfriend
I don 't have a girlfriend
You see , I 'm really old and confused
You 're so good
It should be that
Married , right ?
Grandma
Let 's go now
Dr. Xu still has a job .
Not you
Add a WeChat message , you two
It wasn 't me , I wanted to
In case you say
There is an emergency at home
I I don 't know what to do
I 'm afraid of being blind
Is it convenient
Convenient
If it is convenient , then add
Add
Add WeChat
Let me scan you
OK
Dr. Xiao Xu
Did you get your friend application ?
You two know very well
It 's hard to talk about familiarity .
Isn 't it just about my mother ?
Can be familiar
Okay , I know .
I 'll make a good relationship
For your Mei Mei
I mean
Familiarity in all directions
Ms. Zhao
What are you doing
You red line
He came to me
You 're still worried about me
Please leave me alone
I 'm telling you I
We just broke up , right ?
This ex boyfriend
It 's not cool in my heart yet
From time to time
I can still remember
His voice and smile
Very sad
Don 't worry about it .
Be prepared
Whose is it ? Is it yours
Take a look
Yes , Dr. Xu
I don 't want to see it
Well , if you don 't look at me , I 'll help you
OK , OK
I see I see
Yes No
You 're so gossip . Let me take a look .
Yes
Good return
How to return properly
Grandma asked me to keep you on hand
It 's not early or late .
Lunch is just right
Come
That
Ma Su Su
Wash your hands
We 're serving
Jianxiong
You 're really good at crafting
I 'm relieved to have you taking care of Mei Mei
I 'll do it
Mei Mei
It 's time to eat
Rub it
I know
Mom
That is
This pig foot you braised today
I secretly tasted it .
Absolutely
She doesn 't like cooking
You have to pass this recipe to me
I 'll inherit it .
OK , I 'll give it a while .
I 'll write it down and send it to you
OK OK
Mom
What are you thinking today
I need to go to the hospital
It 's not like I didn 't see it last time
Doctor Xu
Then I guess I 'm going .
I have to meet someone else .
Visiting
Who is leaving
You 're leaving
Didn 't you say you would stay for a long time ?
You don 't take care of her when she is pregnant .
There 's something going on at my aunt 's house
She didn 't always want me
Take care of Zai Zai
So I thought I 'd just go over .
Go back and help your aunt
It also saves her from calling me partial
That 's also that 's also
Mom
Then when do you decide to leave ?
I booked tickets for this afternoon
I left this afternoon
What tickets did you book
Bus
Why do you book a bus ?
We 'll call you online ride - hailing
You refund your ticket
What is it called online car - hailing ?
How expensive is that ?
A few stops
We 'll be there in an hour .
Jianxiong
I 'm going to say a few words .
OK , you say it , you say it
First .
Mei Mei is greedy for coolness
You can 't let her blow the air conditioner .
Second , bend down
That big move
It 's really dangerous if you can 't do it .
Mom , I really can 't
Also go to the toilet and take a shower
Keep an eye on it
What if it slides or something ?
Don 't worry
Susu
If your Uncle Li is busy at work
If you don 't have time to cook
Learn to stew some rice
This pig 's claw
Grandma burned a lot
then you put it in the refrigerator
You can eat it for a long time
It 's best to learn how to stir - fry some vegetables
Meat and Vegetable Combination
Good
Clean
Can 't learn
You have to learn .
I really can 't learn
Are you gone ?
I 'll give you Mei Mei
Cook Instant Noodles Everyday
No
Instant noodles cannot be eaten
Then give it to her
Order takeout three times a day
I 'll call her in a different way
No
Then don 't go .
I 'm done .
Let 's eat
OK
Also
Actually , I 'm afraid you 'll be tired .
It 's also angry , right ?
Jianxiong
That moment
You 're going to give me a ride
Well , of course .
We must all go
I gave it to you
I won 't send you
Eat quickly
Serve some soup for Mom
Real fragrance
Someone will pick you up when you get there .
Your sister will come
All this time here
Thank you for your hard work
Go back and rest
Let my sister take good care of you
Jianxiong
I put that
Use the remaining living expenses
I 'll turn the way you came .
Mom
Keep this for yourself
You have worked hard during this period .
Big and small inside and out
You also supplement a lot
How can you
Suffering and paying money .
Didn 't we agree ?
Refund more and make up less .
That 's what I 'll say
If you want to worry more
Then I 'll put the others
I transferred it all to you
This
Okay , I won 't be wordy .
I accept it
Mom , let me say one more thing .
You 're still out of our minds
There 's no way to do that
This is my temper .
Be strong and competitive
Want face
Some things I 've done before
Some words said
A little ruthless and a little absolute
Hurt someone 's heart
I don 't know .
Now I 'm old
No time either
To correct and make up for it
Please bear with us
Grandma , what did you say ?
What are you saying ?
I think it will take a while .
Why don 't you stand in line first ?
I 'll take my grandmother to sit for a while
Okay , okay , go , go .
Sit with Grandma
Sit here
Okay , okay , okay
Almost done
Grandma
Do you have a whisper to me
Your mother has been losing her temper lately
Hormone causes
But in my opinion
The most important
Or does she have no idea in her heart ?
I had you last time I was pregnant
Originally held it in my hands
A good hand
Beat it up
Your mother was stubborn since childhood
You don 't like to discuss everything with me
You said it was hard .
Regrouping yourself after all the hard work
I 'm pregnant again
She doesn 't know either
Waiting for the rest of my life
What is it ?
Su Su ah
Be considerate of your mother
Don 't take everything seriously with her
Line
A baby with a mother is like a treasure
She 's amazing
Don 't worry
In the future
I 'm looking for your sake
Shall I give her three minutes ?
It 's too hard
Then it 's my fault .
I 'm so old
Small ones are awesome
You go this time
Can you come back soon
I will miss you
Grandma misses you too
But older
That 's useless
Sometimes in my heart
My heart is good
But some things I did
Sometimes it 's just not right
All right , all right
Always under one roof
You said it was rubbing around
It is inevitable that people will get annoyed
It 's not enough to listen to her for everything
I 'll tell you this time
Why do I have to leave
What did Wu Limei say
No , I 'll ask .
No , I asked her
No No
Let me tell you
That 's Grandma
I feel tired
I want to go back and rest
If I want real
If you fall down
Nah Nah
You , you 're waiting on me
When I serve you , I 'll serve you .
I told you that
Even if there is
Don 't blame her anymore
Don 't you say your mother
Do you rely on being a daughter ?
She 's used to being arrogant with me .
Didn 't you just say that ?
You said a baby with a mother is a treasure
Right
Mom
Ticket checked
Check - in
Hold things
Don 't forget things
That 's still a little time .
Let 's take a picture
My dress is yours
Gave it to me two days ago
Did I look good for the first time ?
You look good in everything
Hi Li Jianxiong
Come , take a picture for Mom
Hello , Hello
Can we stand here ?
Very good , very good light is okay
Come , come , come , come
Come and see me
Come
Look at me
Haolai
One Two Three
Another one
Come to Meimei and see here
Wait , wait , wait a minute
Wait a minute
What 's wrong ?
That paper is there
Paper Paper Paper No need No need
Take the dry , take the dry , take the dry
No paper No paper
Mom , don 't take the scarf , Mom
Good Su Su
Susu came over and blocked it
Don 't be wet
Don 't get wet Don 't get wet
It 's okay , it 's okay , Mom
I know what 's wrong
Take this
Wipe Grandma 's hands
What 's wrong ? What 's wrong ?
Are you okay ? I 'm leaking urine
It 's okay , it 's okay
It 's okay , Ma
I 'll go to the bathroom later
That 's fine
I know
Hurry
Send your mother home
I know I know
Hurry
Send Mom Back
OK OK
All right , I 'm leaving .
Let 's go
Goodbye , goodbye
Tell me when you arrive .
OK OK
Master
Please help my grandmother pick up her luggage
Let 's go
Su Su ah
You were with Grandma just now
What are you saying ?
Talking about stocks
The market rose today
Grandma
What can she say ?
Isn 't it just about you ?
What do you mean about me ?
Grandma
Spoil you
Treat you as a treasure
That 's not enough
She also wants us all
Everyone spoils you and loves you
They treat you like a treasure
How are you doing ?
Now Feel
It 's okay , it 's okay
Pregnant women are like this
Mom
What about you
Do you treat Grandma as a treasure ?
We 'll go this way
Isn 't it a little slow ?
Route given by navigation
Maybe there 's a traffic jam on the highway
I didn 't even bring my grandmother to the West Lake .