Big Sister
Director Su is here
Come , come , sit , sit , sit , sit
It 's okay , it 's okay
I 'm here to talk to Tong Tong
Say hello
Tong Tong Sitting
Come
Thank you , Sister Susu
Have you finished the puzzle from last time ?
I think you look good .
When will I be discharged ?
Come
Thank you
Mom
I have something to talk to Sister Susu
One said
Is it ok
Then mom , go get some water .
Then talk
Sister Susu
What 's wrong
I want to give myself
Have a funeral
I don 't want people
When I saw my funeral
Motionless
Lying in a large coffin
I want
Let them see me healthy
Happy appearance
I think
Happily say goodbye to them
Can you help me record it
Cut it into my film
This way
The last one left in this world
About my picture
It won 't make people sad .
Gu Yunsu
Why
You are whirling early in the morning
What are you doing
Did you mean it
I work
Work
Friday night
Which friend is speaking nonsense
I don 't want Qin Yuxuan anymore
I don 't want any work either
I don 't want anything .
After a weekend , I asked for it again
I have to go to work
Aren 't you going to Shanghai
Why don 't you get out ?
Get out , I 'll get out in the afternoon
Too much stuff
I 'll collect it later
During this time
Consider it ours
Breakup Cooling - off Period
All right
What about you
Experience it well
Work Life Without Me
Is it really what you want
Experience
I arranged these for you
Is it just that
You can 't accept
My hands are dirty
Refuel
Change it back before Friday
Look at this place
Yes
Come and I 'll send you
What does that mean ?
A parting gift
Didn 't you come to hand over the work ?
You 're Gu
Mr. Feng
I 'm Gu Yunsu
You can call me Xiao Gu
or Susu
Yes
Come to my office later
I will handover your resignation
General Manager Feng Su Su
Come to my office
Follow personal procedures
That verbal resignation does not count .
Sister
Resignation Application
The boss has signed it .
Fill in and remember to find a leader
Let me calculate it
This time you 're in trouble .
Don 't worry , I can hold it .
Thank you
You 're welcome
Boss , I promise you
I will guard against arrogance and rashness in the future
Prudent and Humble
Work hard
It was the dinner last Friday
My behavior is a bit gaffe
It 's not a bit of a gaffe
Very gaffe
Special gaffe
The Mouth Hi Thing
I 've already reflected deeply
Listen to me
The company needs someone like me
I compete desperately in my business
I 'm like a wolfdog
But passion for career
I 'm like a licking dog
My loyalty to the company
Definitely a watchdog
I just want to stay in the company
For You
I want to stay again
In the list I received
Without you
If you stay
Where to put you
It 's not suitable .
You can take me
Place in any location
As long as I can stay with the company
You didn 't earn it yourself
Not even
You said it , right ?
Qin Yuxuan and your company
You are all you
You guys aren 't shit
Now I have to stay
Why
Because
I don 't accept it
I think even without Qin Yuxuan
I can also work in the workplace
Find my own place
Mr. Feng
Could you please
Give me another chance
I have a
Project called Shimmer
That girl , Tongtong
I 've been with her for over two years .
I want to give her an explanation
I have to give her an account
The boss called me over .
To make me
With the transformation of the content department
The project tonality you just mentioned
And what I want to do
Content category does not match
Let 's do this
I put you
Go to Mr. Wang 's group first
Director Su
You 're here to see Tong Tong , right ?
Why didn 't you enter the door ?
I 'm just gonna go in .
Tong Tong
Sister Susu , why are you here ?
I miss you
Sister Susu
Have you met some
Unpleasant things .
No
Why do you ask that
I 'm embarrassing for you .
It 's okay
It 's actually not that important .
Tong Tong
I 'm here today
Mainly to
Talk to your primary doctor
Have a good chat
And there is another
Particularly important things
That 's who you want to invite
You want to put the list
Contact details
Will you tell me everything ?
OK
This little thing is really
You don 't believe it
Am I able to work ?
Not
You two are separated
You have no chance either .
Gonna go
Say goodbye
Goodbye
I 'm back
Limei 's daughter
Dad
Come on , come on , Dad
What is this ? This is
First Prize
First place
You 're still good .
The child came first
Or are you better educated
Don 't you go to social activities today ?
Not going
I made a lion 's head
Come to wash your hands and eat
Don 't , don 't , don 't , don 't , Limei
It 's this every day
Let 's change
Let 's go out to eat today
Is it good ?
Is it okay to eat out
What do I want to eat ?
Steak Pasta
Good Steak Pasta
Change clothes Change clothes
Steak Pasta
Here 's another piece for you
OK
Mom
Let 's take a picture
OK
Attendant
Hello
Help us take a picture
OK
Mom
Not ready for another one
One more
Okay , thank you .
Thank you
You 're welcome
Just give me your camera
OK
Who are we looking at ?
First Come First
Mom
None
This is just
The unprepared one
Come on , a little more
Why aren 't you sleeping ?
Why did you drink it by yourself ?
Is Susu sleeping ?
Sleeping
I 'll drink one with you too
What kind of wine is this ? It tastes so bad
Does it taste bad
When we get married
You said it was a good wine
That
Yeah
Of course it was a good wine at that time
There was no money at that time
It 's good to be able to afford this
Kangqi
I want to discuss something with you
I still want to go to school
I studied and graduated from school
You can find one in the future
Decent work
Li Mei
We 're both starting three soon
What other books to read
Which school can request it
And you don 't know
This is now working outside
Extremely hard to find
Yes No
You see me day by day
Exhausting
Do you remember
When you proposed to me
Did you say anything
You said you wanted to take me to Hangzhou
You said you wanted to take me to that place
A New Life
Do you remember
I remember it
I cashed it .
Then this room we live in now
House
Food and clothing
Aren 't we all new ?
Yes No
This is not what I want .
This wine still cannot be drunk
I 'm telling you this wine
I 'll get diarrhea if I drink any more .
I 'll ask Mineko later
Bring me two more cases of good wine
Can you drink it then ?
Don 't think about it .
Drink less this wine
Go to bed early
I 'll warm your bed .
All right
Sleep Sleep
Kangqi
What about last night ?
I thought carefully
Wait a minute , right away
Brother
What 's wrong
Yes , I understand
Give up
Kangqi
You 're back
You sit
I want to talk to you
I have a bit of a headache from drinking today
Let 's talk tomorrow
You drank too much
I had nothing to do with a drink
Gu Kangqi
I don 't want to be a housewife .
How nice a housewife is
When you stay at home , you have money to spend
No matter how many people envy them , they can 't envy them
Where is it ?
Why did I stay at home ?
I am busy from morning till night
I never stopped for a moment
So
You are indispensable in this family
Right
Without your rear support
How do I fight on the front line
You can hire a babysitter behind you
Please invite your aunt
Can the nanny be like you ?
Don 't think I don 't know
What 's your plan
That 's what you want to do with housework
Trying to use Susu to trap me at home
Think of me as an old mother
No , you 're so funny
Who said you 're a mother ?
Mommy looks better than you
Are you young and beautiful ?
The figure is still so good
Okay , I see what you mean
This way
This weekend
I pushed off all my work .
I 'll accompany you and Susu
Tao Zi said
We have a hot spring near here
It happens that you bought that swimsuit last time
You haven 't worn it yet
That big backless
You said you put that on
I told you we should go to the hot springs
I 'm afraid someone will abduct you .
OK OK
I 'll be with you this weekend
Okay , don 't be angry
I really have to go .
Wait , wait for me
Walking
It 's too late
Kangqi
I still want to talk to you
I want to find a job
I promise I 'll talk for the last time
I finished chatting
Never again
Come well
Let me listen
You see
You said you would bring me to Hangzhou
Brought me to this place
A special new day
I believe it
But I feel a new day
It seems that you are the only one who sees it
I don 't see it
I do housework every day
Daily chores
I take care of you
Take Care of Susu
I 'm stuck
In these things
My world looks like
Our family is so big
I don 't see a new life
I don 't know what it looks like
I don 't know my
Where is self - worth
I 'd love to achieve it
But I can 't achieve it
My life is just you and Susu
especially you
Because you are me
Obtaining external information
All sources
I depend on you
My life is very monotonous
Very boring
Yesterday the day before yesterday and the day before yesterday
Exactly the same life
Nothing to hope for
I 'm breaking down
It 's really crashing
Kangqi
I 'm beginning to conscious
Unconsciously pleasing you
I started catering to you
I flattered you
But I don 't like me like that
I don 't like it at all
But I can 't help it
I don 't even know .
What is my meaning
I don 't even know my worth
Where should it be reflected
This is not what I want
That new life
Do you understand
Gu Kangqi
Possible
You don 't love me anymore
But I have to love myself
I have to love myself
Give you a task
These invoices
Glue them all
Transfer to Finance
OK , no problem
Besides , I 'm at eleven o'clock
There is a meeting with the brand side
Is there anything I can do
Pour twenty cups of coffee
No problem
You need to rush by hand
Good hand rushing is fine
Page numbers are messed up .
Sister Ma , would you like a cup of coffee ?
Everyone who has tasted it says it is good
Xiao Su
Why are you making coffee now ?
You have to come in person
At least you used to be
Independent projects
The leader doesn 't like me .
It 's okay
I 'll treat it as a new experience
Live as an internship
It 's okay . Your attitude is quite good .
Sister
My project
I want to increase my budget
I have filled out the form
I 'll find you to stamp it later
Does it taste good
This cannot be approved
Why can 't it be approved
It 's not that I want to embarrass you .
What are you doing now
Working in Mr. Wang 's team
On this
It must be signed by Mr. Wang
I can only approve it .
Sister
Before this project
Mr. Qin has always led me to do it .
Now he 's gone
Please accommodate .
My project is particularly urgent
It will be filmed soon
Sister Ma
This trouble
Help me quickly approve it
Extremely anxious
All right
Thank you , Sister Ma
Sister You
Do you see it clearly
You signed it
She 's so anxious if she doesn 't say anything ?
As I said , I 'm very anxious .
You have to understand , too .
With your current situation in the company
You said if something goes wrong
I have to take the blame for you
There are old and young people here .
How dare I not be cautious
Eighty-seven
I haven 't got off work yet , my mother
Not
How do you walk
Silent
I 've been standing there for half a day .
Why are you so serious ?
You are blind
This is how I am
Is it like playing a game ?
So angry
Something must have happened
What to suffer
I don 't want to say anymore
I just recently found out
My popularity at the company
It 's worse than I thought
How utilitarian is that workplace
Go up and surrounded by good people
They should be happy now
It feels like beating a drowned dog .
You can 't keep thinking that .
Then you used to be with Lao Qin
Like a duck in water
More people are jealous of you
That eye looks
The new boss doesn 't like you
Why don 't you come here quickly and step more ?
I don 't understand you coming back either
Asking for trouble why
You also think I 'm in the company
With today 's achievement
Is it because of Qin Yuxuan
I 'm with you every day
Run content together
I don 't know how much you spell ?
But then again
If not
Lao Qin 's strong support
Our project is not possible either
Every time it goes so smoothly
Yes No
I heard you went to see me
What is it ?
Tongtong
I 'd like to add another shot
Tong Tong
I remember she wasn 't
After successful matching
Is the shooting over ?
She
She 's relapsed now
Optimistically estimated for more than two months
That 's unfair
What a good child
Can you go
It must be possible
I heard you 're over there
Busy
I 'll definitely squeeze out this space for you
You are me in this company
The only friend
Mr. Wang
Come in
Please take a look at this
Can you sign it for me
What is this
This is what I 've been following for two years
One item
We need to increase the budget now
You signed it here
I can apply to the Finance Department
This is what you were before
Items in the group
Now you 're in our group
There are still  in our group
So many plans
Implementation cannot continue
You do this stuff
This is definitely not as good as those
Brand Customized Videos
More commercial value
But this thing you say
It is the history of our company
First time as a long video
Doing public welfare projects
As far as I know
Your project
Followed the film for two years
That should be
Accumulated a lot of materials
Just cut it out .
No additional funding is necessary
Continue shooting
Right
Wang is always like this
The boss is actually
Very supportive of this project
Boss Support
Why don 't you go find your boss ?
What are you looking for with me ?
You are my direct leader .
If I want to request a budget
I definitely have to find you .
Now that you know
I am your direct leader
If it 's good , you have to be obedient
I won 't let you do it
Don 't do it
Don 't have so much nonsense
Do you have a problem with me ?
Still have a problem with this project
Both
Then don 't you think
because of your personal likes and dislikes
Affect your judgment on your work
This behavior is very unprofessional
Gu Yunsu
Whether you are convinced or not
Since you still recognize me as a leader
Then stop talking nonsense
There are only two ways
Obey
Or leave
I 'll leave
Gu Yunsu , what do you mean ?
You thought you were gone
Our department is not good
Yes No
After I told you you were gone
Our department will be better
Listen up , everyone
Overtime this evening
Don 't go home
Mr. Wang
I really can 't work overtime today
I will ask for afternoon leave
I 'm going for a prenatal check - up
Did I approve it
The task I gave you
Is it done
You think you 're amazing when you 're pregnant
Yes No
You can get pregnant as long as you are a woman
Don 't be angry , Mr. Wang
I want to ask you something .
What happened
I went to the mountains last month , right ?
That 's right
Who do you think it 's none of your business
Which restaurant is there in the mountain area ?
Eating so much money
five thousand eight hundred ninety-four
How to eat
I don 't know about our company
There is such a good thing .
Let you  every month
Buy a luxury item
20,000 yuan
Let me tell you .
Take care of what should be taken care of
Don 't worry about things you shouldn 't worry about
What is your attitude
Give you a chance
Let you explain it
What is your attitude
Great leadership
They 're afraid of you
Because
They are old and young
Mortgage to raise children
I have enough to eat alone and the whole family will not be hungry
What am I afraid of you ?
And Sister Qin 's fake
You 'd better give her an approval
Otherwise , I will go to the labor arbitration office
I 'll sue you
If you violate the rules , it is illegal
You can work overtime if you want us to .
Did you pay for overtime ?
You threatened me , Gu Yunsu
You 're threatening me
Dear Colleagues
This person in the future
I ask you to go to the dinner room
It 's best not to go
We signed a labor contract
It 's not a deed of sale
You don 't have to talk to those people at the wine table
Accompanying drinks and laughing
Your invoices
I have taken pictures and sent them to my boss
You 'd better explain to him
But it is possible
You don 't need to explain
You are such a useless person
Stay in the company for such a long time
You 're not a boss 's relative
It doesn 't even make sense .
Gu Yunsu , you are slandering
You are completely defamatory
Do you know if you want to go ?
Page numbers are messed up
If it 's messy , it 's messy
You can 't reprint a copy , can you
You insist on letting me stay up late to sort it out for you
Are you perverted ?
This is all right
It 's no longer messy .
Gu Gu Yunsu
I 'm your leader
Turn off your phone
Do not shoot
What do you mean by that ?
You sign the divorce agreement quickly
I 'm not talking about Wu Limei
Why are you messing with me ?
Your daughter doesn 't want it .
You divorced me
She doesn 't want me anymore
Do you like to sign it or not
I told you the court said
Automatic separation after one year of separation
Starting today
I won 't live in this home anymore
You you you
How old are you
You 're so naive you
You think you work outside
So easy to find
Do you think money is so easy to make ?
If money is easy to earn
I stay at home every day .
I 'm not going out either
Listen to me .
I 'm a little busy outside
I haven 't come back
But the money won 't come back
Why do we live without money
What to eat and drink
Start
You just don 't know
Society is so sinister , do you know ?
You 've been out of society for too long
You have no idea
How fierce is the competition outside
Did you know
Xing Wu Limei
You 're leaving today
I won 't stop you either
Go out for a walk , too
Think about my husband
Not outside either
So easy to find
Understand
Wu Limei , we 're not young , right ?
Can we
Don 't be so willful
How do you live if you go out now
Let me ask you
You 're wearing this
Contents of the box
Backpack
Which one I didn 't buy ?
What are you doing
I 'll give you my coat back
I owe the rest first
Get started , get started , get started , get started
Do you want me to get up ?
Jump from this
Have to go out
Where do you live when you leave ?
Do you have money ?
Stop flipping
I have money
Where did the money come from
Yours
I took 800 from you
I owe it first
Eight
I 'm not talking about Wu Limei
Are you going out ?
How many days will you stay ?
This dress is worth 500
I 'll only borrow 300
Give it back to me
Hello
Is there a larger size
A little cuter
Do you think this room is OK
It was just vacant recently
You can leave it to her
Let me have a look .
OK
Fixed Price
Three hundred yuan a month
One Pay One No Counter Offer
Line
Three hundred is three hundred
But big brother
Can the deposit be waived ?
When I just went upstairs
I saw it written
It may be
Can 't stay for long
Very good Very good
Thank you .
Yaoba of Chinese Department
My My
Take a look
No way , right ?
We now need experienced
See what you need here
I can do anything
You can learn
Call me if you have news .
You remember me , right ?
It looks like this
Where is Tongtong
There 's a farewell party this Saturday
Do you have time
Hello , hello , Teacher Huang
This Saturday
Tong Tong has a farewell party
Do you have time
Hello , this is Qing Han , right ?
Boss
What to eat
I want a fried rice cake with green vegetables
With or without eggs
Add an egg and a piece
No need
Walk and sit
Your daughter
Yes , this stall depends on her .
Tongtong , what are you looking at
Harry Potter
Your Favorite
Who is there ?
Hermione
She 's smart
Would you like help
No No
This is very light
Tongtong , please bear with it .
No pain
Soon
OK
Tong Tong is the bravest
Tong Tong
Come on , we 'll be ready soon
Later
Woolf said
Life is like a tree
Leaves always land
But slowly falling down
The leaves were once carried by the wind
Surrounded by light
Rotating
Flying
Mom
Thank you
Tong Tong
Will live a long , long life .
Mom
You need to laugh a little more
You look pretty when you smile
When you find one
Handsome Dad
Then
If you still have a child
That 's me
I am
Look at your face
Remember  when the time comes
Tong Tong does not cry
Mom doesn 't cry
Happy Birthday
Uncle Chen
It 's not my birthday yet
You will be discharged from the hospital
Thinking
Celebrate your birthday early
Let uncles and aunts
Would you like a bite of your cake ?
Close your eyes and make a wish
I want to be like when I was a kid
Go surfing with my mother
OK
Mom takes you surfing
Come
Three Two One
Happy Birthday Happy Birthday
Let 's take a picture together
Where 's Mom
Mom
Mom Mom
Mom is here
Let 's take another picture
Laugh a little happily , everyone
Tongtong , we love you
Tongtong 's departure
Telling many regrets of fate
But it also reminds me of love
Is the only meaning of life
Thank you for being there .
My short life
What about this film
That 's why I insist
Reasons for staying
It 's now done
I have no regrets either
Resignation Application
I 've handed it over to the personnel department
Work for this handover
The handover is completed .
Just before leaving
Still a little nervous
Because
Mr. Wang definitely won 't schedule the broadcast
But I think
Don 't worry
Give me this film
Although it doesn 't matter what I want to do
Content direction is inconsistent
But it touched me
I believe it will
Impress more people
I will do my best
Let more people see it
Thank you
I really don 't plan to stay any longer
I 'm a little tired from doing it
I want to rest for a while
Working
Sometimes other than money
We should find something else
But other times
Money
That 's the whole point
Director Wu , my resume
Wu Limei sits
Take a look
Just sent it
All of them are university degrees
You
Age is here .
Education : High School
I don 't have enough experience .
Or
What about you ? Introduce yourself
Just remove  from this resume
Specialties and Advantages
I 'll summarize as soon as I 'm ready
Report to the leader
Yes No
I
It 's okay , you tell me
Then go back and think about it first
Come to me when you think about it .
Come
I 'll put my resume here
Nana Line
Then walk slowly
Come to me when you think about it .
All right , all right
I 'm a single mother
I have to feed myself
With my daughter
I want to do my best
Bring my daughter to me
Live with me
I have no way out
No way out is my specialty
My trait
My biggest strength
It 's also my disadvantage
Try it for you
Thank you
I 've listened to Wu Limei since I was a child
Talking about dreams
But later
She started talking about money
At that time , I always felt
It 's cheesy to talk about money
I learned later
That cheesiness is in the bowl
Add the confidence of an egg
She wants it too
Proof of living with me
You can do it
That year
My mother is also twenty-eight years old
Despite our choice
Distinct
But I can 't tell where it is
We are just a little similar
Probably because
What we do about our lives
Sure enough
Doctor
Am I pregnant or not ?
None
The road is still long
Congratulations on the miss
The two of us
That 's it
Just
Gu Yunsu
Me
I really like you
I know
You don 't have to like it in the future
I
My young talent
I have a bright future
I go to bigger cities
There are better jobs
After I arrived in Shanghai
More and more beautiful girls
Like me
What about you
Boss , you 're not young .
You 're in ruins
What else do I like about you ?
I 'm in trouble
You 're right
It 's your lips this time .
No longer falling behind
I bluffed
I understand
Before I
It 's always bluffing
I can 't figure it out
What do you think we
We have come to this point
Probably because
That little love between us
It 's not enough .
It 's enough in Hangzhou
It 's not enough to go to Shanghai
Yes
Not enough
Although
Hangzhou is not far from Shanghai
But I arrived in Shanghai
You are all I have .
Just a little bit
Almost
The time for my move is set
Next Monday
I drive with the moving company
Go Together
OK
What about the house ? It 's due next week
Do you think I want it ?
Help you renew your lease for a period of time
No No No No
No , really no
What are you going to do ?
I 'll leave now
What about you
Both people and money are completely empty
Don 't talk about lovelorn and unemployment
And without me as a free landlord
Private vehicle
Long - term meal card
I 'm really worried that you can 't think about it .
Do something extreme
I decided
I 'm going home to my mom
Didn 't you two just finish your fight ?