What are we going to eat later
How about pizza
Yes Yes Yes Yes
He he he
So handsome
Li Mei
I only know your name is Li Mei
I don 't know your last name yet
Her name is Wu
What are you doing
This is for you
No need to pay me back
Mom
Actually , I think my father is this time .
You 're really serious .
Of course
It 's also because he 's old .
Restored
Your father 's heart
It 's different from others
What about others
What age is it
What kind of life , right ?
Your father is not
What age is your father
All have to pass
The day he wants
He couldn 't live ordinary days
You know that
Your father 's life
It 's a pity not to be an artist
I 'm different
I want to live an ordinary life
So I choose
Life like this now
Select such a person
What I 'm looking for now
I don 't regret it at all
I think
Uncle Li is
The kind of person I want
Ordinary and ordinary
But he is at ease
I support
In Love
Once unreliable
Never reliable
That 's so right
Mei Mei
Susu
Uncle Li
I 'm upstairs and downstairs
I 'm looking for you everywhere
You came here for a walk
Not tomorrow morning
Did we just switch ?
Your mother will be early tomorrow morning
Fasting Physical Examination
Several tubes of blood will be drawn
I 'm not at ease
I have to come early
Then you accompany me
I 'll draw less blood
Nah Nah Nah
Smoke as much as you need
Then you should feel at ease
All right , all right
Don 't worry
No, how can you  today?
This
Come this far for a walk
I am in a good mood today
I didn 't know you were coming here
OK
You know you feel sorry for me
Get better quickly
Yes Yes Yes
This time is more serious
After discharge
I must exercise well
No longer let you worry about me
Then let 's agree
Don 't heal the scar and forget the pain
Next time ,
I 'm exhausted
I really don 't care about you .
I don 't believe it
How can my wife ignore me
Then try
You parents
No matter how big the contradiction is
Not in front of children .
How much harm does it do to children
Comrade Police , you are right
Today I was really impulsive
This thing should be compensated
Will definitely compensate
Please come here
Police force wasted
I 'm sorry
Here
Signed
And he
OK
Sign this as well
This is your
This says
Husband and wife
Due to relationship breakdown
Reconciliation is no longer possible
You said this
How did this happen ?
Isn 't it good before ?
You said you wanted to come to Hangzhou before
I brought you here .
Married
With Susu
Then we
In this city in this Hangzhou
Reserved a home
I thought .
To make more money
We can
You can get better and better
Living
I gave my home away .
Okay , I 'll keep one , right ?
Take care of yourself
Signed
Susu is gone
Let me help you
Uncle Li
The bathroom is empty
Why did you go all the way out ?
All these expectant mothers
Use the bathroom at all times
Have to meet their needs
Uncle Li is really careful
My sister today
Physical examination with Aunt Wu
But there are exams in my school
Gotta get back
I called my brother - in - law over .
But he 's rude .
Can I trouble you for something ?
Take care of it more
Don 't worry about this .
Sorry for troubling you
It 's okay , it 's okay
Mei Mei
Get up
Let 's go early today
Catch the first batch
Check early and eat early
This empty stomach
How sad it is to be hungry
Mei Mei , it 's your turn
Come
Next
Give me the list
This is it
What 's your name ?
Wu Limei
Don 't think beautifully . Let me tell you .
It 's over
Results available soon
Wait here for a while .
OK OK OK
We 'll wait here for a while .
Yes , yes , wait here
Come
You just lied to me
That 's our baby
OK
Keep pressing it
There 's no one to accompany you .
I My husband is with me today
There may be traffic jams on the road
What 's up with you
Tell me .
Thank you
Next
The neighbors are here
OK
Give me the list
What is your name
Sun Yihui
She has no company
Her sister has something to do temporarily
How do you know ?
Her sister told me that .
You 're such a social butterfly
What 's going on ?
Is this okay ?
There 's a doctor here
Good , good , doctor , come , come , come , come , come
Do you hear me ?
Already gone Already gone
Already went to see it
Hi
Let me tell you
I 'm in the next bed
You and your wife fainted
Come quickly
We can 't live without our family .
Is it better ?
Much better
My expression slowed down
Much better than just now
Here , here , here
Thank you .
Special thanks
Wife
How is your health ?
Dead
How 's it going
Agreed
Little sister has something this morning
You want to accompany me for the prenatal check - up
Yes
It 's agreed but people
You said I was uncomfortable this morning
How many times did I call you
You didn 't answer any .
What about last night
Mr. Zhang
He insisted on letting me go over for a drink
I said I won 't drink when I go home
He said no
Are you there ?
He drank from that pot
Who can stand it ?
As a result , I drank too much Mei Mei
The prenatal check - up must be accompanied
Yes Yes Yes
It 's dangerous to have no one with her .
I know
Why don 't I hurry over ?
I know it 's not you yet
I 'm not drinking too much , right ?
This is a delay . Look , look .
How is your health now
Hate
You don 't eat either .
Can your body stand it ?
What do you think ?
Fortunately , there is one next door
Uncle and aunt take care of me
I just recovered .
I count on you
That uncle and aunt
Really giving it
I 'm sorry for your trouble
I 'm very busy recently
That aunt disturbed your rest
It 's okay to rest
I 'm fine
Uncle , thank you very much .
Not this
Look at my wife
I knew you were here today
We need to draw blood on an empty stomach
I specially put this chocolate
I 've already
I 'm ready for you .
You see
Eat a chocolate first
The couple quarreled
What 's interesting
Let me tell you
These two are unhearted
This one has an uncle
One Aunt at a Time
What are they doing
If I knew , I would have ignored them
I 'm from Susu 's generation
It 's normal to call me uncle and aunt
Enter
Dr. Xu
This is Wu Limei from Number 35
This morning 's test report came out
OK , thank you
Uncle Li and Aunt Wu
If nothing goes wrong
We can be discharged next week
Dr. Xiao Xu
You mean
I saved the child
The data is good
The height of the placenta has also increased a bit
To be on the safe side
We 'll watch for another week
If everything goes as usual
We can go home and have an abortion .
It 's not easy for us
We finally got through .
It 's not easy
Come , come , come , come
Now there is one thing to note
It is gestational diabetes
Except for fruit
Desserts and drinks
You can 't eat these high sugars
Need to control not eating or not
Don 't eat , don 't eat well
I want to write this down
What we know
For desserts
High sugar
After we go back
You can prepare one of these instruments
Monitor values every day
How to use this
After turning away
It 's this needle
It 's bleeding when it 's stuck .
Touch it up
It can display blood sugar values
Look , I 'll show you .
Is this the right thing to do ?
That 's it
Does it hurt
It hurts a little bit
But tolerable
But I can 't stand it
Six months after you
I have to get an injection every day
It 's for the good of our children anyway
Then
From now on , you will get every needle
I 'll take a needle with you .
That kid is also my kid
I have to do my part .
No need , Li Jianxiong
I 'll just measure my blood sugar , by the way
You don 't need to be so righteous .
What 's wrong
You really need to test it
The sugar content is too high
We often do this
Come
OK
Dr. Xu
How is my mom 's diagnosis ?
Why is it hot ?
You 're crazy
Hot
You know it 's hot .
Are you trying to burn me ?
You still want to piss me off
You are pregnant
I 'm not the same as you .
This belly isn 't big .
The temper is not small .
I have a big temper
You didn 't force it .
Who did you drink with last night
Is it with Mr. Zhang ?
Which Mr. Zhang did you drink with ?
Mr. Zhang , have you seen Mr. Zhang ?
Make it up for me again
You have this information
What is the King 's Canyon ?
With your friends
Drinking together
Everyone else is for this family
Running there for my career
What 's your name
You call that black
I 've worked hard .
You call that running around
You call that moving
Being a father can 't be so easy .
Complain in front of me every day
Say that you worked hard
Where did you work hard ?
You or you wouldn 't come
Sit there when you come
Your butt
It 's like a nail growing
You sit uneasy
You don 't want to
Tell me a few more words
I hold your broken phone every day
Not watching short videos there
It 's just playing games
You like mobile phones so much
Why don 't you use your mobile phone ?
These husbands
It 's not all there
Do you play with your mobile phone ?
How can I talk to my wife ?
Bed next door
The bed next door will not
I don 't know how others live .
I can 't control it either
But I look at the bed next door every day
I have only one thought
I feel like being your wife
I 'm embarrassed
Uncle
Give it to me
No , no , I 'll do it , I 'll do it
Don 't get your hands wet .
I washed it together
Thank you , Uncle
What are you thanking for
Thank you for bringing my mother .
So well taken care of
That 's my own wife
I 'm pregnant with my own baby
Isn 't it right to be nice to her ?
What 's there to say about this
Then I won 't thank you anymore .
Is there anything else you want to say
It 's okay , I just think
You said
If my mother could be young
I wish I had met you earlier
What about the fate between people
Pay attention to an opportunity
One second earlier is impossible
Not even a second later
Also
If I met earlier , I wouldn 't be there .
This screen
It 's very warm and touching
What are you talking about ?
Timing Emotion
Are you talking about the same topic ?
This donkey 's mouth is wrong
This chat is sometimes like this
One Meaning
I do have one
With timing and affection
If it 's all involved
Dr. Xu said it
I 'll be out next week
Yes
You have something to do with me
I heard my mom will be discharged next week
If nothing goes wrong
I want to talk to you
Change Place
Where to go
A place to eat
I 'll go eat first .
Xu Wenbin
Where have you been
I went to the canteen on the rooftop .
Isn 't it a place to eat ?
Didn 't you ask me for something ?
What 's going on ?
I
I want to say
What do you want to say ?
Or
Qin Yuxuan
What are you doing here
Why can 't I come ?
You are ill
I came to see you
Who is he ?
Who he is and what does it matter to you
What are you yelling about ?
Why has nothing to do with me ?
I can 't care about you .
Don 't shout , okay ?
Don 't shout
Why don 't you catch up first ?
I 'll go first
Xu Wenbin Xu Wenbin
I like you
I I like you
What I wanted to tell you just now
This is it
Do you have any
What you want to tell me
You guys should find out first
I 'll go first
We 've figured it out pretty well
I have nothing to talk to him
Qin Yuxuan
I don 't want to talk to you right now
What are you doing here ?
The lioness is in heat
It came to look for
Two male lions of the Super Pride
Why did you want him to come to me ?
Add fun
What to help
Let me tell you
I found something
Did you know
This male world
I especially like competition
Really
As soon as this little Qin appears
Have you found anything
This little Dr. Xu is very excited
How about
Is the fire fierce or not
You 're trying to draw money from the bottom of the pot
The fire is all out
How could the fire be extinguished
This animal world says
Mom , the man and the man
He 's a little different , right ?
What 's the difference ?
All the same
Right
Yes Yes
Push Tower Push Tower Push Tower
Hurry up
You can always trust the animal world
If the fire goes out
It must be your problem
Line My Question
OK my question
That 's right
How about
Let 's look forward to it together
Tomorrow 's Animal World
You will accompany me tomorrow .
Seeing the Animal World
OK
But today 's issue is not very good
It 's scary
You 're scarier than they are
I 'm doing it for your own good , you know ?
Not knowing good or bad
After Uncle Li 's work
Will go home to cook first
And send it over
It takes almost an hour
Make the sky visible
Let the white clouds hear
No one can erase it
The promises we made
But if you tell him
My mom wants to eat from Anita 's
Croissant Sandwich
He would stop by after work
And Anita Restaurant
Exactly between the unit and the hospital
You 're welcome , thank you
This way he will be better than usual
Arrive about an hour early
And this time
It 's pretty tight
Are you stupid ?
Yes No
Nobita is here
Arrived late
Lao Gu is here today .
Are you anxious for Mei Mei ?
Lao Gu , you wear a hospital gown today
What is the condition in the maternity ward
Just think of us
Are you wearing pajamas
We are in the same boat
Just wait .
Uncle , you came early today
Mei Mei said she wanted to eat Anita
She sent me a special WeChat message
I said from the unit
Why don 't you bring it here ?
So I want to eat Anita
A little earlier
I told Gu Yunsu that I
I want to eat Anita
You 're very sweet .
Yeah
I took your phone specifically
I sent a message to Uncle
I have more thoughtful things .
My mother loves watching Animal World recently
I 'll turn the channel later
Tuned to CCTV10
I heard that there was a lion fight today
It looks good .
What 's the fight ?
The winner is already decided
What do you eat , Anita
Try this
Then Anita has changed .
The cooks have been changed
Mei Mei said she loves to eat it
Chef changed
The taste has changed
I 'm not happy with this
Come , come , come , eat , eat , eat
Come to Su Su and open them all
The croissant is still hot
Don 't we have croissants ?
then why
You want me to buy croissants
My mom is pregnant recently
Mouth is tricky
My father gives her croissants every day
Every day
This croissant is not that croissant
Just love my bite
I can 't do it without coming
I said I 'll give it to you
Make so many nutritious meals
Why don 't you have any appetite
You eat croissants every day
That croissant is so high in calories
High fat stuff
It 's all butter
You can handle it
You the baby in your belly
I can 't stand it either .
What
What did you say
I said so high calories
High fat stuff
The baby in my belly can 't stand it
I understand
What baby
Isn 't it gone , baby
If you can 't control it
Where 's your mouth
Just take care of your legs
You can go out
Outside
It wasn 't abortion .
Raise yourself here
Then I got so angry
Conditioning and conditioning
You 're interesting .
Who told you that
Who did she tell me ?
She told me that too
That 's all told me
You are so interesting
Mei Mei , you told Lao Gu .
I didn 't say anything .
I accompanied my mother for surgery
What surgery is it ?
People flow
Misunderstood
Not
Then why do you still let me
Why did I come ?
That is
You let him come every day
It 's your wishful thinking
Is it wishful thinking
Isn 't it your love and my wish ?
Yes , you look at it
Are there so many dishes ?
You said we were eating and talking
What 's going on
Can 't be solved at the dinner table
Yes No
We 've reached this point
What else are we talking about
What are you sitting on ? Uncle Uncle
Please tell me clearly .
What do you mean ?
I 'm willing to love her
Or I love her
They all mean the same thing
Don 't you understand ?
Didn 't I want to tell the details ?
It 's the two of us reunited .
We 'll both be fine soon
Get up
What are you doing ? What are you doing ?
Figure it out now
It 's me and Wu Limei now
Legal husband and wife
You 're so blatant
My kidnapper
You 're shameless to poach me
Do you have a moral bottom line
I 'm shameless
Love is my morality
I have no bottom line
Let me tell you
Li Mei regardless of whether she has children or not
I 'm sure you 're the foot of the wall
I dig it .
I dug Limei
Can I dig it today ?
I dig when I dig
Repeat
I dig it .
Digging , digging , digging
Don 't you like it ?
Dig , dig , dig
Stop digging
I will
I 'll tell you
I think you are
Su Su 's biological father 's share
Give you one last chance
Apologize to me
Otherwise , my fist
It 's not used to it
You apologize to Li Mei
You apologize to her and you two
You guys no no no
You must be sorry for her
This opportunity is available
You apologize to her
What does this have to do with Li Mei ?
Hit me with your fist
Don 't turn on Wu Limei
I 'm afraid of you
I 'm for her
Born to block a fist
Gu Yunsu
Why don 't you stop them ?
I just knew that I was messing around here
Let go
So many pregnant women
If you want to hit , you will hit it
Get Out Out
Walk
Come on
Go
Where to call
Right here
Right here , right here
Is this fine ?
Yes
Come , come , come , come , come , come
What 's wrong
How to practice
Come , come , come , no corpse , no corpse
Don 't move
You can 't slap your face .
I have a meeting tomorrow
I 've had surgery here .
Be careful
You can 't afford to fight , you know ?
Then protect your crotch .
I 'm a military boxer
Stretch the crotch and push the elbow
Don 't you stop Gu Yunsu ?
What can be stopped
At their level
Who can beat who ?
Enjoy watching
Not touching each other at once
Hand pain Hand pain
Don 't be spattered with blood .
Don 't you feel too embarrassed
Alright
Nobody knows us anyway
Don 't even laugh .
This is a duel of men for dignity
Fighting for you
For Limei , for true love
I educated him
For Mei Mei , for my family
Come
Stop fighting
Will you two fight to the end ?
I haven 't stepped on this foot for half a day .
I can 't stand it anymore
It 's fun to watch
Push hard
I want to fight for Li Mei
You 're so heavy
Name
Wu Limei
Discharge
What
Which bed should you be louder ?
Thirty-five beds
Wu Limei
I feel embarrassed
What did I tell you ?
Don 't get burned , right
Are you endlessly funny ?
Interesting
Don 't you like it
Animal World
It 's on fire
It 's really hot
Put it away
Be careful I 'll beat you up
What is this ? This is
Wife - robbing
These two old men
One is still sick
Mental Disease
What psychosis
This is clear
is an old disco soul dancer
Don 't look at it
Are you okay ?
It affected my study
You 're disturbing my entertainment
Snatch it
Look at this action
It 's exactly the same as in the video
This is called bouncing the crotch and pushing the elbow
Bring it here
Stretch your crotch and push your elbow , right ?
Then let 's take a look .
This move bounces the crotch and presses the elbow
What are you two doing ?
What are you doing
Li Yan An Yiming
The classroom is yours
Chasing the fighting place
Teacher
Li Yan taught us military boxing
Li Yan , this is not you
What a shame
This is not you
Reasons for chasing and fighting
You come to my office after school
Take the time to study
What a blind spirit
Hello
Discharge Procedure Discharge
You can discharge from the hospital
Okay , keep this .
OK
Here is a list of payments
I need your signature
OK OK
Good health
Susu is gone
What to talk about
Attendant
Do you have any whiskey at home
Sorry
No wine is sold here
Hello , I want Australian white thank you
I want an American
Ice thank you
OK
Wait a moment , two of you
What are you talking to me about ?
You have to drink and strengthen your courage before you can say it
What bravery do I have ?
I gave you some for fear of your guilty conscience
What am I guilty of ?
You know I 'm in Shanghai
What kind of life did you have ?
I miss you every day
I 'm worried about how well you 're doing
How is it working
Did you get angry in that house
How is your relationship with your mother
What 's the result
You let me come back
What do you see
You saw it
I have someone I like now
I intend to
Starting my new life
What did you say you came back to see me ?
This bullshit
I think you are
Out of ex - boyfriend 's jealousy
Unwilling or even angry
Psychological Trouble
Once I can understand
But please do not do this again
Don 't say this again
If you are unclear
Did you disturb my life ?
I 'm disturbing you .
I I came all the way back
I traveled to see you
I 'm disturbing you
Then I Then I
Then let 's block off diplomatic relations , right ?
What do you say ?
I can do anything
We can also
Business exchange only
Live as an enterprise account of the other party
Yes .
Then let me talk to you about business .
Anyway , I am
Returning with a mission
Talk to you about escaping .
Your company decided to want it
A little complicated
Complex
Where is the complication ?
Tell me
Hello , excuse me
Your White
Thank you
Your Ice American
OK , thank you
You 're welcome
What 's complicated
Where is the complexity
It 's complicated
Branch level
Also divided into individual levels
Let me tell you first
On a personal level
That is
I found that
I can 't let you go
You are sick
I 'm sick
Me these days
I 've been thinking about this question
I just can 't figure it out
I 'm until that day
I saw you and
You and that guy
I 'm sure I don 't want to miss you
You 're not missing me
You just want to win
My mom is right
Always
Believe in the Animal World
What about the company level
Expand and talk
I don 't want to say
Why
I need to make it clear to you
Would you still like to see me
I 've planned it all .
What about me
Prepare to be here again
Stay an extra week or two
I 'm going to do it bit by bit
Infiltrate you in batches
Just wait .
Shameless
You are ruthless
Unreasonable
Brother Li
This is the document for the afternoon meeting
Take a look
How is Brother Li in recent days ?
Pretty good .
Why is it bad
OK
Good as hell
That 's fine
The afternoon meeting with Liu Chu
Can you change it to online
Change online
Then we have to talk to Liu
Discuss
Otherwise , everyone else will do as usual
Change it to online
It 's pretty good .
Good as hell
See you online that afternoon
This is discharged from hospital
Yes Yes Yes
Everything is fine
Is it all right ?
This is also clear .
Can 't stay any longer
It 's all like that .
When I went through the discharge formalities
He also walked with sunglasses .
You said that at such an old age
What are we doing ?
I 'll go back and churn .
No matter what , I can 't rest well .
My heart hurts .
Completely enlightened
I said I had to talk to you two .
Nobita
Nobita is not here
Not here . Such a coincidence .
It 's not so unfortunate
Then let 's talk .
What else is there to talk about
Just talk for two minutes
Three minutes Five minutes
Ten minutes
Fifteen minutes at most
To
Supplements
Nobita
You 're not at home , but I came in .
Change shoes
OK
No need to pour water
In the future , you
Don 't buy me anything
Not you
Tell me what you need
I 'll send you
I don 't need you
Do I need to
That 's it
It has nothing to do with you .
Don 't get me wrong
My purpose
The child is still there
I 'm not bullshit , am I
Your little life
Having a prosperous life
It 's too late for me to bless
Even if I had that thought
I have to stop if I don 't give up .
I just want to be nice to you .
Pure
Gu Kangqi
Can we set a rule ?
In the future
Except for birth , old age , illness and death Gu Yunsu
Between us
Don 't contact us again
So old
What other rules do you need ?
Not
Life and death are still far away
Let 's stop talking .
My illness
This is too old
It 's easy to figure things out
I 'm still thinking about the past
You said
Am I an asshole ?
I 'll just ask you
Am I still human
You had a big belly at that time
Pregnant with Susu
You just need me
How difficult is it for you ?
If I can 't help you , let 's not tell you .
I still don 't go home every day
I 'm hanging out .
Am I Human
I should be like
Thrown away like garbage
You should abandon me
I 'm thick - skinned , right ?
I came to your door again
I still want to be nice to you
Compensation Compensation
Is there a chance to think beautifully
I was wrong
I think
My mind is small
Right or wrong lies in my mind
I always
I always want to give you what you owed me before
I think you owe me .
I want to make up for it
You know that
So
But I know now
This is not appropriate for me to do
It 's not you
Where did you hear it
I 'm complaining about you .
I didn 't mean that .
I didn 't want you to say you were wrong
Where are you wrong
You 're right
If you have to say that
That means you have me in your heart
You have me again in your heart
It 's too late
We are more suitable
Your little life has been like this
Right
Nobita
Not your cup of tea
When will I say this ?
I have to tell you .
You shouldn 't have said that
My mouth is salty and my mouth is light
I love sour food and spicy food
I know it myself
I know better than you
It 's because you two are not suitable anymore
You two are not just
Isn 't this life ?
I 'm sorry for Nobita
Veteran Cadre Nobita
Be good
Let me become a celebrity
He doesn 't want to bring goods or anything .
Right
Strangely wronged
I 'll go to his unit to find him
Pay him a compensation
One yard is one yard
This is not a code
I think this this
You don 't have to be so particular
It 's also noon .
Why don 't we have a meal ?
Jiangnan Station
Remember again