CAPTIVATING THE KING
Your Majesty.
There must be a criminal
for an interrogation to take place.
Who is this spy you speak of?
Has Chu Dal-ha
mentioned the spy by their name?
I shall reveal the criminal's name
in the interrogation.
Forgive me for saying this,
but a crude handling of the matter
may place you in a precarious position.
What dares to make you say so?
Should your interrogation
to find and punish the spy
who colluded with the Qing
become known to Prince Rui,
he will become furious.
It may end up disturbing
the peace between the two nations.
Your determination to punish the criminal
may become a detriment
that endangers your reign.
That would constitute
their interference in our affairs.
The Qing have their hands
on our every affair.
Even the crumbling fortresses
of the borders
are being neglected because of the Qing.
Are you confessing the failings
of the Border Defense Council?
Then it seems I must abolish the Council.
Is Eunuch Kim outside?
Have you summoned me, Your Majesty?
The Border Defense Council's involvement
with this interrogation will be barred,
so order all its members to leave.
See if Inspector General Kim Je-nam
has come to the palace
and have him see me
with the Chief Royal Secretary.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Principal Director.
You may leave now.
EPISODE 14
When selecting the officials
joining the interrogation,
exclude all the members
of the Border Defense Council.
Mobilize all the royal secretaries,
the clerks, and the runners
to review all records
of the spy case from three years ago
and reports from the borders,
then report back to me.
Sixth Royal Secretary Kim Myung-ha
shall be excluded
as he was involved in the case.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I shall follow your command.
Your Majesty.
I apologize for asking,
but why have you decided to look into
the report of Chu Dal-ha
when he has tried to assassinate you?
It is because his report
aligns with my wishes.
Your Majesty.
Are you suspecting the spy
who colluded with the Qing
to be among the members
of the Border Defense Council?
Do you suspect it to be
Principal Director Park Jong-hwan?
Is that why
you commanded me to find a way
to abolish the Border Defense Council
and reform the court?
I have wanted to do that since long ago.
But I have yet to discuss it
with the court.
Then I shall report to you again
after coming up with a detailed plan.
That is correct.
But I could not abolish it rashly
as the Council's influence
had grown so much.
Your Majesty.
I shall carry out your command
as your devoted subject,
but the court will resist ferociously.
I am prepared for it.
The capital traitor
who joined hands with the Qing
and put this nation
and its people in a crisis.
I will find that vile spy
and have them punished for high treason.
I will have their disgraceful name
engraved in the records
so that the people of this nation…
will remember their crime.
My brother
was poisoned to death.
Who would have dared to commit
such an atrocious and treasonous act?
Tell me, who did it?
His Majesty
summoned all members
of the Border Defense Council at night
and then commanded us
to leave all of a sudden.
He should not treat court officials
in such a coarse manner.
There has been an attempt on his life.
That would explain his mood.
In my opinion,
he has some other designs in mind.
Summoning Kim Je-nam out of the blue
was a sign in itself.
It seems that he does not trust us--
Right State Councilor.
You are crossing the line here.
Are you suggesting that His Majesty
does not trust the Principal Director?
-That is not it.
-Enough.
That is enough.
Why do you think
His Majesty has decided
to look into the report of a traitor?
It is because Chu Dal-ha
will most certainly name another traitor.
And that traitor's name
will clear His Majesty's name
of being Prince Rui's spy.
Whoever is named by that man,
that traitor and their family
shall be destroyed
and all those associated with them
will be arrested
and executed for high treason.
When the interrogation begins,
there will be a bloodbath.
There is only one way
to stop that from happening.
We must prevent this interrogation
before it causes such chaos.
Go to the library with the runners
and get the Royal Secretariat's Records
and all the reports from the borders
from three years ago.
Yes, my lord.
My lord.
What is my duty?
You are to stay away for the time being.
As you were involved
in the spy case three years ago,
His Majesty ordered your exclusion.
Your Majesty.
Are you sure you do not need
a royal physician to tend to you?
Though you may not be seemingly injured,
I suggest that you be examined
just in case.
Morning examinations are enough.
However, Your Majesty…
Your Majesty.
Captain Joo Sang-hwa has a report to make.
Let him in.
With all due respect,
it is past your bedtime.
You can meet him tomorrow.
It is fine. Let him in.
Yes, Your Majesty.
How is Mong-woo doing?
She seems to be in shock
from Chu Dal-ha's arrest.
And it seems a man named Se-dong
has frequented
and shared the news with her.
Do not forbid him from visiting,
but report to me immediately
should anything happen to her.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Captain Joo.
Just how poor are you at your job?
I have never been on good terms with you,
but I have trusted you wholly
with His Majesty's safety.
However,
this incident was a bolt out of the blue.
An assassination attempt from a traitor?
You are right.
It is all my fault.
The biggest problem
is his visits to his private residence.
If you cannot stop his travels,
such an incident may end up recurring.
I concur.
However,
that is up to His Majesty to decide.
It is neither up to me nor you.
But Captain Joo…
I am back.
Did the Special Firearms Unit
not tell you off?
Master Choam
must have told them that I would visit,
as they did not stop me from entering.
What about the State Tribunal?
What will happen to Master Chu?
The King will interrogate him himself,
so he will be imprisoned
until he is transferred to the palace.
Then why did they arrest him like
they were going to kill him immediately?
That really scared me.
Please see to it
that he is well taken care of, Se-dong.
Do not worry about that.
Jeomine and I will take care of it.
Thank you.
-You may leave.
-All right.
Get some rest.
You should lie down, my lady.
My lady?
How come His Majesty
returned to the palace
without saying a word to me?
In my opinion,
I think he left in a hurry
in case you were troubled
by Master Chu's affair.
Could that be the only reason?
Your Majesty.
You are in good health today
and show no symptoms.
About that poison.
The poison that killed my brother.
Have you yet to find it?
Forgive me.
It was not found
in the herbal medicine he used to take
or the bowl that contained it,
but on the royal robe
he coughed up his blood on.
I could only confirm that he took poison,
but could not learn
what kind of poison it was.
I understand the difficulty of the task.
But do not give up and keep working on it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
His Majesty ordered me
to greet you on his behalf.
My heart almost stopped at the news
of the assassination attempt.
Why could he not have come himself
for such an easy task
as coming to greet me?
I apologize.
The interrogation preparation is keeping--
How is His Majesty doing?
Like always,
he did not express any discomfort.
I hope his health has not been affected.
Did the royal physician examine him?
He took his pulse early in the morning.
His Majesty is healthy as ever.
Having you by His Majesty's side
does ease my mind.
You may leave.
What on earth is happening in the palace?
Has the Principal Director sent word yet?
I apologize.
I will send word again
to the court conference room.
There is no need.
He will come without my calling
when it is time.
Your Majesty.
Chu Dal-ha attempted to assassinate you.
How could you hold an interrogation
over a report such a man made?
Please retract the order of interrogation.
The report from that traitor
must be a false one he concocted
to avoid punishment.
There is no solid evidence
proving the existence
of a spy who colluded with the Qing.
You must behead the criminal
and hang up his head for display
to show the gravity of his crimes
to the people
and let it serve as a lesson to all.
We implore you
not to dismiss our words of advice
and grant our petition.
-Please grant our petition.
I have seen you all
for a long time
since the days of the late king.
But every single one of you
remains the same
and eternally unchanging.
You act as if you care
for the nation and its people.
But do you truly think I do not realize
that your safety and personal gain
are your sole concern?
It is utterly appalling and disgraceful.
Compared to all of you,
Chu Dal-ha
is a thousandfold more loyal
as he risked his life
to report on the spy
who colluded with the Qing!
Your Majesty.
How could you
compare such a wicked traitor
to us court officials?
It is highly inappropriate!
Heed my words!
If anyone submits another petition
to go against me on this,
no matter who you are,
I shall consider that you are
attempting to hide the spy
and have you punished for high treason.
That was strange.
I felt the same way.
His Majesty
seems to have been
bewitched by Chu Dal-ha.
That is not what I meant.
Then what is it?
I have never seen
the Principal Director stay so silent
when His Majesty was this enraged.
You are right.
Whenever His Majesty was furious,
he would be the first to show deference
and soothe the King's wrath
to mediate the situation.
But he did not step in once today.
Earlier at the hall of governance,
I overheard the Left State Councilor
talking to the Minister of Rites
that His Majesty decided
to look into Chu Dal-ha's report
to clear his name
of being Prince Rui's spy.
It is all bygones now,
but three years ago,
I shared Lord Kim Jong-bae's suspicion
that Grand Prince Jinhan had sent a spy
to both the Ming and the Qing.
But to hear
that Chu Dal-ha had acted upon
the late king's command
and that there was another spy
who communicated with the Qing in secret.
This is pure chaos I cannot fathom.
So, tell us.
For what reason was your father
so convinced that His Majesty
was the spy back then?
Pardon?
Right, the reason was…
Why has His Majesty
summoned the Border Defense Council?
There has been a report
of a breach of the peace treaty
whereby a spy named Chu Dal-ha
was dispatched to the Ming
to communicate with them.
Did you just say Chu Dal-ha?
Do you recognize the name?
Recently,
I have seen him at a courtesan's house
that Grand Prince Jinhan frequents.
Are you saying you saw
the Grand Prince meeting with him?
That is correct.
I saw them clearly with my two eyes.
What is wrong, Myung-ha?
What insolence is this?
You bastard.
Do you have a death wish?
Yes.
I may as well kill you
and take my own life today.
What wrong did I ever do to you
that you would treat me thusly?
You clearly told my father
that you witnessed a meeting between
Grand Prince Jinhan and Chu Dal-ha
at Hongjang's courtesan house.
Did I say those words?
My father believed in your lies
and…
thought that Grand Prince Jinhan
was the spy who colluded with the Qing.
My father…
died because of you.
Let me go!
You should get your story straight
even in your raging state.
Lord Kim Jong-bae
died at His Majesty's hands.
So how is his death my fault?
All I ever did was tell him
what he had wanted to hear.
Even if it had not been for my lies,
he would have found a way
to accuse His Majesty as the spy.
Do you think His Majesty
would agree with you?
I will have you tied to the rack
along with Chu Dal-ha for interrogation.
Who knows?
He may even attest that you were the spy
who colluded with the Qing.
Please spare my life.
Please forgive me this once.
It is all in the past, is it not?
Does this mean you are forgiving me?
Just you wait.
I shall contemplate
how best to deal with you
to relieve my anger.
Principal Director.
What did you just say?
His Majesty is attempting
to sever his ties to me
despite my significant
contribution to his reign
and our bond bound by the heavens.
And why would he wish to do so
when you are his one and only uncle?
Do not tell me…
it is because of the suspicion
regarding the late king's poisoning.
It is for another reason.
But you assured me
there could be no other reason.
Back in the day,
I once told you that I had a plan
I had worked on for a long time
to secure His Majesty's ascension.
I was the one…
who secretly informed Prince Rui
that the late king sent a spy to the Ming.
Why did you do such a thing?
That is exactly it.
You must feign ignorance like so
to the King as well.
Tell him you did not know
and that the Principal Director
is not a spy.
I sincerely did not know.
Did you
truly not notice any oddity?
Did you believe
the Qing troops' timely invasion of Uiju
when Grand Prince Jinhan was in trouble
and the late king's sudden passing
were all mere coincidences?
It is highly unseemly
to depreciate my services thusly.
Do not worry.
His Majesty cannot dare to cast me away.
If he dares to bring me down,
he will crumble before I do.
I hear Chu Dal-ha's interrogation
is being prepared.
We are currently selecting the judges.
However,
the court is complaining
because the criminal has not been named.
There is no chance
that Chu Dal-ha knows their name.
This must be by His Majesty's design.
I am worried as he seems to be
rushing the case for some reason.
If the court's resistance grows stronger,
his safety will be put at risk.
Bollocks! You cannot!
I must go to the palace today.
I must see His Majesty.
I have to look into Master Chu's case
and inform the Sixth Royal Secretary
about the recent developments as well.
You cannot go to the palace in this state.
I will go instead.
I shall go to the State Tribunal
-and the palace--
-Jageunnyeon.
Jageunnyeon.
Stop calling my name.
If you call me like that,
I cannot dissuade you from going.
Thank you.
Why did you come to the palace
when you have not fully recovered yet?
I came as I had something to tell you.
Is it because
I arrested Chu Dal-ha without telling you?
How would I dare
to comment on your decision?
Nevertheless,
if you arrested Chu Dal-ha to protect me
when you knew
it was all my crime and not his,
I must say you still do not know me well.
I decided to take measures first
as I anticipated you would react this way.
Was it because I am a woman?
It is because you are my woman.
This interrogation
is being held
to find the treacherous spy of the Qing
from three years ago.
This is a quest I have long striven for
and a duty I must fulfill.
What could I possibly do
if I had you bound in ropes as a traitor?
The fear that you might get hurt
would paralyze and bar me.
I understand how you feel.
I know guilt weighs on your heart.
However,
this is also what Chu Dal-ha wants.
Remember that and return home.
Your Majesty.
Is the spy who communicated with the Qing
Principal Director Park Jong-hwan?
I looked back
upon hearing the news of the abolition
of the Border Defense Council.
Having the Grand Prince
accompany you to the gisinje,
the substitution of the Princess,
and the appointment of the Crown Prince
were all a power struggle
between you and the Principal Director.
Three years ago,
when my father was taken to the Qing,
when Hongjang died,
and when I was at death's door,
I took a vow before the heavens
that I would dethrone the captivated king
and bring justice to the world.
And that I would make you feel the pain
and suffer the indignity of being betrayed
by the person you trusted.
But in hindsight,
the one who was captivated…
was me.
I was blinded by the captivation
and failed to see the man you truly are.
In truth,
I still do not understand, Your Majesty.
Attacking the Principal Director
will only endanger your reign.
For what reason
are you taking such a high risk?
I was ashamed.
Even a powerless commoner…
risks their lives
to carry out their duties.
But I, their king,
have failed to do anything.
Hiding the crimes I have committed…
has been eating me alive.
Are you referring to the crime
that you mentioned to me?
The one that began three years ago
and still continues to this day?
You will turn your back on me
if you learn what it is.
You will spit on my face,
condemn,
and loathe me.
If it is against your wishes,
you do not have to say anything.
What more can I hide from you?
When the late king passed away,
he gave me his last words.
Find…
the one who harmed me
and punish them.
And see to it
that the Prince Royal
ascends to the throne.
I went against my brother's last words
and ascended to the throne.
The man standing before you…
is a criminal who usurped the throne.
Your Majesty.
You ascended to the throne
to keep the late king's last words.
It was to protect
the Grand Prince and the Princess
that you became a criminal.
For the past three years,
I have been wandering,
lost in the Underworld.
However,
you are still in the Underworld.
I will stay by your side every step.
I will endure it all with you…
and be of support to you.
My lord.
His Royal Highness summons you.
Your Royal Highness.
Master Kang is here,
Sixth Royal Secretary.
The King has barred
my involvement in the interrogation.
I was worried when you
disappeared from Banchon Village,
but seeing as you are well,
I strongly suspect that you and the King
may be on the same side.
Even if Chu Dal-ha
names His Royal Highness or me
during his interrogation,
I will not be shocked.
I can assure you that will not happen.
Do not worry.
Then answer me.
How come you are all well
when Chu Dal-ha is at death's door?
Where have you been all this time?
Are you not the one
who proposed to plot treason together?
Perhaps the King
already has full knowledge of our plot.
Answer me.
What on earth has happened?
Chu Dal-ha…
attempted an assassination and failed.
It was because I was captivated
that I failed to see
the King's real intention.
But now,
I am certain of what it is.
The interrogation…
is His Majesty's measure
to protect His Royal Highness.
Can you swear to the heavens
that this is not a lie
to relieve me of my worries?
I swear on my life.
Had you not sworn,
I just might have believed you.
My lord.
Let us…
-He is over there.
-Right.
My goodness, how awful.
Thank you.
-You have half an hour.
-Yes, of course.
Master Chu.
We are here.
My lady.
How is your wound?
It is bearable.
How are you doing?
It is bearable for me as well.
Goodness, when did you prepare all this?
He will not be able to finish it all.
It is not even that much.
This is Bun-yeong's regular meal.
It was indeed very pleasing
to see her down a meal, was it not?
Please take good care of Bun-yeong.
I shall try.
Goodbye, my lady.
You.
Have you seen me somewhere?
I am not sure.
It is my first time seeing you.
Is that so?
Wait, Se-dong, do you remember that man?
The Principal Director's servant
we met for Bun-yeong's matter.
Do you mean Mak-dong? What about him?
Do you remember how he recognized me
when I had never seen him?
That is true.
He did ask you
if you had ever seen him somewhere.
What are you talking about?
Do give us an explanation
so we can understand.
Who is Mak-dong?
Three years ago,
there was a man
who told the Qing of all my movements.
Mak-dong,
the Principal Director's servant,
just may be that man.
So it is not that
Chu Dal-ha remembered Mak-dong,
but rather Mak-dong
who recognized him first?
But that alone
does not prove that Mak-dong
tailed Chu Dal-ha.
Nevertheless,
his being a servant
of the Principal Director
cannot be a mere coincidence.
Please have him questioned just in case.
Principal Director,
I apologize for coming at this hour.
It is fine.
What brings you here?
I am here to ask your servant,
Mak-dong, a few questions.
It is on His Majesty's order,
so please hand him over to us.
Summon Mak-dong.
My lord.
He left early today
to visit his relatives in his hometown.
He will be back in a few weeks.
Did you hear him?
I understand.
I shall return then.
I apologize, my lord.
I did recognize his face.
But I only saw him so long ago,
so I could not recollect who he was.
At least you remember now.
Mak-dong.
Thank you for your work.
I will not
forget your kindness, my lord.
Stop right there!
Arrest him!
-Yes, Captain!
Good work.
Take this letter to Uiju.
A month from now,
the Qing's envoy, Jung Je-pyo,
will arrive with a document approving
the appointment of the Crown Prince.
Tell him that I have sent you
and give him this letter.
Yes, my lord.
Your Majesty.
Forgive me.
Mak-dong, Principal Director
Park Jong-hwan's servant,
was found dead with his throat slit.
If his throat was slit,
that means he was murdered.
This was clearly to silence him.
Chief Royal Secretary.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Summon Principal Director
Park Jong-hwan this instant!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I am not sure he will admit
his crimes of murdering Mak-dong.
I am not summoning him to question that.
Then for what, may I ask?
I must…
give my uncle his final warning.
His Majesty requests you inside.
Principal Director.
Confess your crimes and be punished.
I will not interrogate you if you do.
I am not sure which crime
you are referring to, Your Majesty.
Do you truly believe
your treasonous collusion with the Qing
can remain a secret?
When the interrogation begins,
all your crimes from murdering Mak-dong
to concealing your liaison with the Qing
to poisoning the late king to death
will be exposed.
Your Majesty.
With all due respect,
you cannot punish me
for the late king's death.
Even if a poisoning took place
and I gave out the order to do so,
you cannot expose those crimes.
If you punish me for them,
the people will think
that they were your doing.
And this will serve
as a pretext for treason,
which will then lead to your dethronement.
A pretext for treason?
A pretext for treason, you say.
The people believe
that I poisoned my brother
and my sister-in-law
to ascend to the throne
and committed depravity
by taking my brother's woman.
The people
condemn and point fingers at me
for being a pathetic king.
A king who lets
the Principal Director, his uncle,
take control of the court
and abuse his power as he sees fit
and also indulges himself in baduk
with the gidaeryeong,
a man whom he is attracted to
at Yeongchwijeong.
All my actions so far…
provided ample pretexts for treason.
That is why I am taking action now.
The king…
executing his own kin
who has recklessly wielded his power
will inspire the people more than ever.
Do not be concerned about treason.
All this is to prevent one.
I will give you one final chance.
Confess your crimes and be punished.
If you do,
I shall spare you from the humiliation
of being interrogated in the open.
What is your choice?
Allow me some time to think.
You have one day.
You will come here
at this exact hour tomorrow
and confess your crimes.
The spy who colluded with the Qing
that His Majesty is looking for.
That spy is you, is it not?
My lord.
Meet Kim Myung-ha.
Why do you suggest
that I meet him out of the blue?
Three years ago,
Minister of War Kim Jong-bae
suspected Grand Prince Jinhan
of being a Qing's spy.
The dispatch of a spy to the Ming
and the secret communications to the Qing
were all considered to be
Grand Prince Jinhan's machinations
to dispose of the late king
and ascend to the throne himself.
Back then,
I was impressed that Grand Prince Jinhan
had accomplished such feats.
That is why I abandoned Kim Jong-bae
and joined hands with him.
How interesting.
Continue.
After observing you closely
for a few days,
I realized that all those feats
were accomplished by you
and not His Majesty.
And it turned out the person
I wanted to serve
was not Grand Prince Jinhan.
It was you, my lord.
Watching His Majesty
state his will to punish the spy
who colluded with the Qing
filled me with fury.
If I were you,
I would have exploded in indignation.
After all your service to His Majesty
whereby you even put up with
the sordid business of being a spy,
His Majesty
fails to see…
Anyway,
what I wanted to say is
that a king who does not appreciate
a loyal subject is not worth lingering on.
Do you think Kim Myung-ha
would meet with me?
I shall act as your intermediary, my lord.
I told you to wait, did I not?
I came to convey a message
from the Principal Director.
So in other words,
the Principal Director is asking me
to join hands with him in treason.
What do you mean by treason?
We will ascend the Crown Prince
to the throne, his rightful place,
and liberate your father's soul
from his bitter resentments.
Park Jong-hwan
must be the spy.
Am I wrong?
It seemed you had a falling out
with the gidaeryeong.
Is that not right?
When the interrogation begins,
my name may roll off
of Chu Dal-ha's tongue,
but he could easily say yours.
He may end up naming both of us.
Therefore,
we must stand on the same side
as Principal Director Park Jong-hwan.
That is the only way
His Royal Highness, you, and I
can survive.
Why do you hesitate?
Do you not want revenge on the King
for your father's death?
Do think about it
and let me know by tomorrow morning.
Kim Myung-ha
wishes to join hands with you.
Words alone are not enough.
I need solid proof
that he will support me in this cause.
What kind of proof do you have in mind?
Convey this message to him.
Welcome, Sixth Royal Secretary.
What is going on here?
Father did not forget my wish
and gave me his approval
to play baduk with my master.
It has been a while
since I have seen you smile.
Do you think this is inappropriate
during my mother's mourning?
No, Your Royal Highness.
I was only happy to see you smile.
Is something the matter?
No, do not mind me.
Your Royal Highness.
Principal Director.
Sixth Royal Secretary.
Your Royal Highness.
Please forgive me
for my negligence so far.
I shall visit you more often
and make sure to be of service to you.
Thank you.
Your Majesty.
Principal Director Park Jong-hwan is here.
State your crimes, Principal Director.
I apologize, Your Majesty.
But I have none to state.
I have been your loyal subject thus far
and have never been disloyal to you.
I have always been prepared
to give you my life if necessary.
However,
not even a royal command
can force me to falsely confess
crimes I did not commit,
for a smear against my reputation
equates to one against the reputation
of you and this nation.
You adamantly…
refuse…
to state your crimes?
Yes, Your Majesty.
As I have no more to say,
I shall excuse myself now.
Chief Royal Secretary.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Please give me your command.
I will summon the criminal
and interrogate him tomorrow,
so make sure to prepare.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
With all due respect,
summoning the Principal Director
to the interrogation
without evidence or witness is risky.
The official's mistrust toward you
will only grow
and make it more difficult
to abolish the Border Defense Council.
In truth,
there is a witness and evidence
that I have been saving as a last resort.
Where might they be?
My lady.
Senior Court Lady Han is calling for you.
Lead the way.
Principal Director.
Why are you standing about?
Take it already.
Are you telling me to take my own life
now that you have no use for me?
How foolish.
Taking your life is a child's play.
I would not need this to do so.
Then what…
What would you do if I refused?
I shall report thusly
when His Majesty holds an interrogation.
"Senior Court Lady Dong
poisoned the late king to death for you,
Your Majesty."
His Majesty will not forgive you
for poisoning the late king to death.
If he forgave you,
he would become a depraved tyrant
who forsook the bond set by the heavens.
He will have you killed
to clear his name.
Do not be so foolish.
This is all for your sake.
Saving yourself
should always come first.
That is more like it.
Senior Court Lady Dong?
Are you all right?
Please wait.
Take it.
Stop acting generous
with that despicable face of yours.
You are nothing but a fraud
deceiving everyone
with your false appearance.
How you must want to boast
that you are His Majesty's only woman.
You have no chance.
You are neither a man nor a woman.
His Majesty's affection will not last.
I have no intention
to compete against you
for His Majesty's affection.
Of course not.
I do not care.
I am sick of everything.
I cannot…
carry on any longer.
Now,
I will carry out what tasks I can.
Your Majesty,
Senior Court Lady Dong is here.
You are the evidence
of my brother's murder
and the witness who bears knowledge
of Park Jong-hwan being the spy
who colluded with the Qing.
Chief State Councilor.
His Majesty urgently calls for you.
Did he also call for a Royal Secretary
and an official historian?
He only asked for you, my lord.
Are you suggesting
we send a spy to the Ming?
That is correct.
Last night,
His Majesty gave a secret order
to the Chief State Councilor.
Good work.
Senior Court Lady Dong.
Attend the interrogation
and confess your crimes tomorrow.
If you confess your crimes
and those of the Principal Director,
I will make a judgment
in light of your efforts.
You will be punished,
but not executed.
His Majesty will not forgive you
for poisoning the late king to death.
If he forgave you,
he would become a depraved tyrant
who forsook the bond set by the heavens.
He will have you killed to clear his name.
Your Majesty.
I shall follow your command.
In return,
please grant my request.
This is the final request…
that I will be making.
What is it?
CAPTIVATING THE KING
Even if I have to quash
all resistance from the court,
the interrogation will be held.
Bring an end to this case.
Enough!
Do you not see that you will be endangered
if you punish the Principal Director?
Answer my question!
You have held on so far
for this day to come, Your Majesty.
Treason? That is ridiculous.
Who informed you of such a lie?
The Emperor wishes
to play baduk with the gidaeryeong.
The Qing's envoy
must have caused you distress.
I do not understand these feelings.
I am afraid.
Subtitle translation by: Jea-heon Chung