(The following content may not be
suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(All characters, organizations,
places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Widows?
The assassins who tried to kill
the local functionary were women?
Yes.
I am certain that one of them...
was wearing mourning clothes.
Are you sure?
How could women...
I definitely saw them.
They were not
just regular assassins. They were...
Hey.
Where is Yun?
I was informed that he went
to a gisaeng house he frequents.
- A gisaeng house?
- Yes.
It is called Yeonhwa House
in Mudam Valley.
Okay.
Take care of the body.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Right. That is where the village
for widows is, is it not?
Pardon?
Come to think of it,
the village for widows
is next to the gisaeng house.
Welcome.
We are not here as your customers.
We need to search the place quietly,
so cooperate.
Okay.
Let us not complicate things.
Do not let Prince Yeongchang...
who is young and weak
take the throne.
Instead,
help me take the throne.
That is the only change
in your plan.
So you want to become a king?
Do you think you have
what it takes to be a king?
Is he one of them?
No.
If he is one of them,
he would not be dressed like that.
What are you doing?
This village for widows
is protected by the King.
Men are forbidden here.
You ought to be rolled
and taught a lesson!
Oh, my!
Are you here to catch
your daughter-in-law who ran away?
Then you should back off even more.
You are hiding something in there.
Goodness.
What are you doing to a weak woman?
What could I be hiding?
How may I help you?
Lord Heo Yun stopped
by the gisaeng house for a bit.
There was no one suspicious.
Good work, everyone.
You bought us some time,
so we were able to dodge a bullet.
When we were
after the local functionary,
she seemed to be good at fighting.
But I believe she is smart as well.
I think I can assign you missions
from now on.
I will do my best.
By the way, who is he?
Why did you bring me here?
Even you, the Chancellor
of Special Counselors,
can do nothing.
I had thought
you had the King's trust.
But he caught up to you.
Thanks to you,
Prince Yeongchang has died.
Even if the King finds out,
the situation
will not get any worse.
We have lost our purpose.
What do you mean?
Did you not hear what I said?
You must make me the king.
Why do you want to take the throne?
I have always wished
that our poor people...
would have enough to eat...
and live good lives.
Do you really need me
to say such things?
You need to deeply care
about your people!
I am...
going to become a king...
who is invincible.
And you can serve me.
Are you going to inform the King?
Will you tell him that you had once
considered betraying him?
Or...
will you tell him that his son,
who should have died
20 years ago,
is still alive?
Will you make a tearful confession?
Let me answer your question...
about why I brought you here.
Come in.
While keeping my eyes on you,
I had an unexpected gain.
When I heard that the Muweol Corps
was sent to an island,
I wondered what there could be.
I found some people...
who had been in hiding
for a very long time.
That was when I knew...
that the stories
my father had told me...
were true.
Were you not curious?
Why do you think
the King wanted to kill...
his own son and Jung Yun Jeo?
You are probably still alive...
since you were not curious
about that.
Are you...
Had I been the son of the King,
I would not have felt wronged...
about having to live in hiding
for all my life.
You must be Yun Jeo's son.
I will see to it...
that he becomes the king.
He is the only man
who will bring back everything...
that I have lost.
All right, then. What do you say?
Usually, sharing
such deep secrets...
would bring together
the individuals involved.
- You cannot come in here.
- No, it is okay.
I am allowed to do that.
What?
I can go wherever I please
and kill whomever I want.
I am allowed to do that.
What do you mean?
I have finally found out...
whom you have feelings for.
Are you talking about that again?
I told you that it is not...
If that is true,
will you be okay if I kill him?
I am going to leave soon.
I just used him.
I have always been sorry...
towards Lady Chun for taking me in.
But thanks to him,
the burden I had was lifted.
You used him?
Yes.
Just like how you are being rude...
solely because you found out
who I was,
I found his weakness
and used it against him.
So do not assume
such a ridiculous thing...
or make such heinous comments.
All right.
Leave this place and come to me.
Then I will be...
No.
I do not want to hear it.
Please leave.
What? What is it?
Why did you accuse
an innocent man of being a pervert?
Where and what were you doing
after that?
Why did you come here?
- I do not want to talk about it.
- What?
You said
you would tell me everything.
I thought you were not interested.
You told me not to ask questions
and to mind my own business.
On top of that, you are going to...
I am going to leave soon.
I just used him.
What were you going to say?
Forget it.
Finish your sentence.
Stop being so secretive
and answer my question.
Why do I have to be the only one
who tells you everything?
What about you? What is your story?
Why are you suddenly
asking about me?
We are talking about you
because you acted peculiar.
What does that have anything
to do with you?
You little...
- What...
- My goodness, that is enough.
My gosh. Seriously.
My goodness.
Are you guys kids?
Are you?
If you have something
to argue about,
you should calmly
talk about it like adults.
The day has just started,
but you are ruining the mood.
What? Hey, Aeng Du.
Can you ask her where she is going
without doing the dishes?
He wants to know
where you are going.
I am going to earn money.
And tell him that it is his job
to do the dishes.
She says it is your responsibility.
Do not go.
Do you...
Do you even know
what kind of guy he is?
I live with you, but I do not
even know who you are.
So how would I know anything
about him?
Anyway, do not go.
Do not go.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
Me? I am...
your mother. I am your mother.
My gosh, tell him he must be
very proud of himself.
You guys are driving me crazy.
You will not even
let me eat in peace.
But you finished your meal.
You guys are so immature.
I cannot stand this childish act.
Hey, where are you going?
I am on my way to see Lord Yul Mu.
Why would you go there?
I need to eat lunch...
now that I have finished breakfast.
My gosh, come on.
Darn it!
Where is Lord Yul Mu?
He must not have come.
He goes to dozens of gisaeng houses.
This is good. I can use this chance
to wash the dishes.
What about lunch?
What about my lunch?
He promised that he would
cook flower pancakes for me.
He also said
that he would take me on a picnic.
He told me
that flower pancakes taste best...
when we eat it outside on a picnic.
He promised me.
My gosh, I will make it for you.
My goodness, are you sure
you can make them taste good?
I am not confident.
How am I going to face His Majesty?
Just act normal.
He must be more suspicious now.
What should we do?
We are going to move the base
for the Muweol Corps.
Tell everyone to stop
going to Yeonhwa House,
and tell them they should
also be careful not to get caught.
How about we just accept
Grand Prince Neungyang's offer...
Everyone thinks
it is a good alternative.
Prince Yeongchang
is no longer alive.
So we must come up with a solution.
I will come up
with another solution.
He can never be the next king.
Tomorrow,
the Muweol Corps
will have to leave the village.
- What?
Make sure you do not leave
any traces behind.
And form a group of 3 to 4 people
and leave the village after sunset.
Let us all meet
at Aseowon in Hanyang.
Who gave us this order?
Is it Lord Heo's order?
Yes, I got a letter from him.
But did you forget
what happened yesterday?
Does he have
any power left in him at all?
Why is it that we always...
have to change
the people we serve?
Lord Yul Mu...
I mean...
Grand Prince Neungyang has been
planning everything all along.
Now that he has power,
we have no other choice.
If we refuse,
everyone will be put in danger.
However,
he is also someone
who can fulfill our wish.
The chancellor will soon
come to an agreement with him,
so we are not betraying anyone.
We just need to trust both of them
and follow their lead.
Neither of them seems any different.
I am going to meet
Grand Prince Neungyang tomorrow...
and settle the situation.
But I also think it is right
to move our base.
I will escort you to Hanyang.
I want you to stay here
and help the others leave.
Meanwhile,
Lady Kim can stay with me.
Okay.
Are you really going to go?
We are talking about the chancellor
and the King's cousin.
We should just stop here.
Let us go back to your father and...
And do what?
Are we going to hide
in the mountains this time?
My goodness gracious.
A group of high officials gathered
together to start a new world...
behind His Majesty's back.
Do you even know what that means?
A conspiracy.
You know that...
You know that and you are still
willing to go? What is your plan?
They are already doing it,
so that means my dad
is not guilty of treason.
I barely found their weakness
by dressing up as a woman.
I should use it to my own advantage.
If things go bad,
I will just report those traitors
to the police bureau.
My gosh.
I do not care
if I have to kill them or not.
I am going to put an end to this.
Then we will no longer have to hide.
My father, brother,
and...
I am going to leave soon.
And...
Okay.
We will continue to live with you.
We will stop hiding.
Let us do that.
Okay, let us do that.
Yes, of course.
I will live with you and Aeng Du.
Yes, without a doubt.
You are unbelievable.
You are supposed to use
glutinous rice powder water.
I cannot believe
you threw the soaked rice cakes...
right into the pot of oil.
I thought it would be similar.
Frying things in oil
are pretty much the same.
My gosh.
I am hungry.
Can you cook it for me?
I am busy. Forget it.
Lord Yul Mu would have
made them for me.
That is enough.
Let us get going soon.
- Go where?
You said that
you would make flower pancakes...
and go on a picnic with me.
When did I promise you that?
I told you that I am busy.
Lord Yul Mu would have...
Fine, let us go.
Eat up.
Are you protecting me?
Or are you keeping me
locked in this room?
I am keeping you here
so I can protect you.
I have no time to waste.
I need to find my sons.
I will ask my men
to do their best...
to find your firstborn.
If they cannot find his body,
that means he is hiding somewhere.
Please make sure
that you find him for me.
As for His Majesty's son...
If I happen to find him...
We will go to Ming.
If you want us to go somewhere
further away, we will do that.
We will go where you tell us to go.
You told me he grew up to be
a smart and righteous man, right?
Maybe he could be my alternative.
What do you mean by that?
No, it is nothing.
I will find him.
I just need you
to stay here quietly.
No one will get hurt,
so do not worry.
Why are you wearing a man's outfit
all of a sudden?
Why not? We climbed over the valley
and are far from the house.
This is great.
Look how handsome I look in this.
Here.
Handsome, my foot.
Forget it. You do not even know
how to fish.
Look who is talking.
You have not caught a fish
for an hour either.
So we should just head back.
Why did you drag me here?
Do you think
I wanted to bring you here?
Had you not started cooking
this flower pancake...
I said I would make pancakes.
I never talked
about going on a picnic.
Anyway, this is all your fault.
You should not have gone
to that kitchen, to begin with.
And why do you think I went...
And that jerk is the worst.
If he made a promise to her,
he should keep his promise.
If he could not keep his promise,
he should have not made it.
Goodness.
You two will end up getting attached
to one another at this rate.
Why do you keep fighting?
This is not that big of a deal.
It is because he has
a lot of secrets.
He said he would tell me,
but he never did.
It is because I do not wish
to lie to you. So what?
What?
I cannot tell you...
why I came here. Not now.
I will have to lie to you
if I tell you why.
And I do not wish to do that.
Happy now?
I am sorry to interrupt
your serious conversation.
You need to turn the boat around.
Gosh, I can breathe again.
Well, can you look for a leaf?
Find a soft one for me. Okay?
Hey, hey.
What? Where are you going?
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Hey.
Did you see that? I do not need
that darn fishing rod to catch...
Darn it. Hey.
Hey, what is wrong with you?
Come on. Darn it.
Why did you not tell her
that you lived on an island?
She never asked.
Darn it.
Aeng Du.
Eat this.
Eat it over there.
What?
Are you that dumb?
You should have dried
your feet first.
Forget it. Let us just go.
If your feet are cold,
you will catch a cold.
You will make my life harder
if you do.
There.
All done.
- I told you...
- Not to do stuff like this for you.
I will do whatever I want.
It is not like
you listen to me either.
It is not that.
I do not know your real name.
What?
When I thought that
you fell into the water earlier,
I could not call you...
because I did not know your name.
Do you want me to tell you?
I do not want to.
Is your name that precious
to share with me?
I will tell you later...
if you take good care
of Dong Dong and Dong Joo.
I will tell you once they grow
their cockscomb, lay eggs,
and become chickens.
Your answer is always "later".
Forget it.
I will tell you then,
so you should stay with them
and raise them well.
They need you.
You are their owner. Okay?
Promise me that you will do so.
I will keep addressing you
as a jerk then.
Hey, why are you always so harsh?
My request is not that hard
to comply with.
Promise me. You will not promise?
Gosh.
(The Muweol Corps must leave.
Do not leave any traces behind.)
The chancellor is indeed naive.
The only solution
he could come up with...
was sending the Muweol Corps
to Hanyang.
However, the King has his eyes
on this place.
So it will be dangerous for them
to stay here.
If you also visit our house...
I have been visiting
this gisaeng house every day.
Stop coming here
would draw more attention.
Then, what should we...
Follow the chancellor's instruction.
We will.
I will go to Hanyang
as soon as dawn breaks.
I have a few questions
for the chancellor as well.
I am going to ask him...
to follow the current.
I will provide guards and horses.
That is all right.
I will go to Hanyang with a widow
who just joined the Muweol Corps.
And I believe you have met her too.
I do?
Your Majesty.
I am the vice-curator
in charge...
of the village for widows
at Mudam Valley.
- My name...
- That is enough.
Tell me
about the village for widows.
Tell me everything even if
it does not seem suspicious.
You can only go home
if your answers satisfy me.
Yes.
I heard you joined the Muweol Corps.
They said they would pay me.
I heard
you are preparing to commit treason.
I am sparing your life even though
you ought to be dead...
because Dong Joo asked me to.
But it is getting difficult.
I am starting to want
to break my promise I made to her.
I am not intimidated
by a man who is all talk.
Well, do as you please.
Do not sway her.
I will make it brief.
Hey. I lost him because of you.
Who are you?
Wait. Are you not...
Thank goodness I did not promise...
that I would stay beside him
until the chicks grew up.
But I want to.
I want to stay by his side.
I am sorry, Mom.
Her belongings are still here.
It cannot be.
No.
What is this?
- What?
- How could you go without telling?
- Where have you been?
- You disappeared too.
Hwa Su asked for my help,
so I was at her place.
Do you think I did not check?
It looks like you are planning
to go somewhere.
Leave and let me sleep.
I will not ask you to like me.
You can use me if you want.
I am fine with that.
So...
Please do not disappear on me.
I am begging you.
Is it okay for you
not to be disguised?
Have you not heard?
Lord Heo is behind me.
What?
That is why it would be natural
to visit him like this.
We are here.
Are you leaving today?
Yes.
Are you hurrying...
because of him?
I am leaving because I am ready.
All right.
Let us go to Hanyang together.
I will go alone.
Please do not follow me.
Fine.
But I must check to see
if you have arrived safely.
Do you remember where the swing was?
Show me your face anytime
between 9pm and 11pm.
That is all that I ask.
If I do that,
will you not do anything?
Are you talking about him?
Yes.
Promise me that
you will never harm him.
And yet, you tell me
that you do not like him?
Even if I do, I will hide
my feelings.
I will leave without saying anything
and hurt him.
That way, he will despise me.
That will be better...
than my dying...
and his losing me.
I know very well...
how it feels to lose someone
you love so dearly...
and to continue on living.
I will not let that happen.
So you do not need to worry about...
You are crying.
And it is because of him.
You are not warning me.
You are confessing your feelings
for him.
Please pay me for everything
I have worked for you.
No.
I will pay you in Hanyang.
Do not be late.
Thank you.
I am alive.
A gisaeng house
provides for the village...
Bring in their boss...
and the widows
who are close to her.
If there is no evidence
bring in witnesses.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Has everyone escaped?
Yes.
They have.
And Lady Kim has left
with Lady Chun already.
So we are the last ones.
My house...
and my friends are all there.
I did those cold-blooded deeds
so that I could live there in peace.
We need to leave...
to keep our friends safe.
Let us go.
- All right.
- Pour me a cup.
This is nice. All right.
There he comes.
Let us move.
- Let us go!
Come on!
Why do you not...
yield yourself?
He promised that he would take care
of people like us...
who are powerless.
If so,
is he not better
than the current King?
I wonder if you will think the same
after seeing this.
This is Lady Min's...
We found her dead body
on the mountain behind the village.
And we have recently found out
who killed her.
Are you saying
Grand Prince Neungyang did this?
Why?
So he could dig up whatever
he needed to know about me,
find my weakness,
and eventually threaten me with it.
You think he will care for the weak?
He is a man who can kill anyone...
in order to get what he wants.
Grand Prince Neungyang is
provoking us to make the first move.
He is very much prepared,
so you must be careful.
Should we find him and kill him?
He did nothing wrong.
He had to hide and live on an island
because of his father.
Bring him back alive.
"An island"?
Are they talking about my brother?
Is it a bit uncomfortable
to be friends?
I thought it would be nice
for us to be friends.
I am sure we will
slowly become friends.
Yes, of course. We will be
working together for a long time.
Am I of any help to your plan?
I would not keep you around
if you were useless.
There is something...
I need you to help me with,
but that is not part of my plan.
Your younger brother... I mean...
I need to find His Majesty's son.
Are you going to kill him
if I find him for you?
Well...
I am thinking of killing him
because he is useless to me.
But what do you think?
I am also willing
to follow your opinion.
Hwang Tae.
How did you get caught?
Did you get hurt?
Are you okay?
You must have been through a lot.
I missed you, Hwang Tae.
How did you get here?
Well, it is a long story.
But I came to save you.
Let us get out of here.
No.
I am not here because I got caught.
What?
I thought you got caught
by Grand Prince Neungyang.
I thought you were running...
from the person
who tried to kill us...
We almost got killed
on the island...
because of you.
- Hwang Tae.
- Grand Prince Neungyang...
saved me right when I was about
to get killed because of you again.
What are you talking about?
The reason we had to hide,
the reason why my mother had to die
such a pitiful death,
and the reason why
we had to get chased all the time...
I found out why.
Was it because of me?
Yes, it was all because of you.
Never mind.
Forget it. You should go.
I will not tell anyone
that I saw you today, so get going.
Why was it my fault?
Why?
Tell me.
Tell me!
Do you really want to hear it?
Are you sure you can handle it?
Tell me.
Fine.
This is all because of you.
This is...
This is all because...
you are the son...
of His Majesty.
Do not kill him.
We need someone to go back
and tell Lord Heo...
not to waste his energy.
That is nonsense.
You expect me to believe that?
You expect me to believe
that I am His Majesty's son?
If you cannot believe me,
you should go ahead
and ask His Majesty yourself.
What is the matter with you?
I am your younger brother.
I am my father's son.
That is what I also thought!
That is why...
That is why I lived
such a difficult life.
Mother.
Hwang Tae! Come on in here!
- Mother!
- It is all your fault.
Had it not been for you,
my son would have...
My family would have...
I am no longer
going to live that way.
I am going to retrieve everything
I had lost...
because of you.
Hwang Tae.
Please do not do this.
Let us leave together.
You cannot abandon me like this.
What am I supposed to do now?
Run away by yourself.
This is all I know,
so do not come looking for me again.
Do not try to know anything.
Hide and live like you do not exist.
If you do not do that,
you will surely die.
Get out of here. Leave.
Leave right now!
Brother.
Do not call me that...
anymore.
Did anything happen?
The alcohol got me
feeling a little sentimental.
What is going on outside?
It is nothing.
It has been taken care of.
Do not worry, and rest.
I have another appointment.
Goodnight.
You are here.
But...
I could not find Lady Kim,
so I came here alone.
I needed to ask you something.
You could not find her?
Okay. Go inside.
I need to step outside for a moment.
Did you kill Lady Min?
Yes.
I killed her
in order to keep a secret.
I got rid of a possibility
that may cause trouble later.
Is there something wrong with that?
In case of trouble in the future,
you killed a woman
who risked her life to do her duty?
It is only natural for someone...
who has served her purpose
to disappear. Do you not agree?
In that case, you might abandon
the Muweol Corps...
and the village for widows
whenever you want.
You can make sure
I do not abandon them.
And as for the village for widows,
I have already abandoned it.
Let us go!
If you need a village,
I can build another one.
If you want a gisaeng house,
I will make...
the biggest and the fanciest one
in Hanyang.
Please do not tell me you thought...
taking the Muweol Corps
out of the village...
would solve this.
You must have thought
little of the King.
Please give me some time.
I will make sure...
no one becomes evidence
for the King.
I can move the whole village
somewhere else if necessary.
Why?
- Pardon?
- Why must I do that?
It is a hassle...
when I know a very simple way...
that guarantees what I want.
I understand now.
I am glad.
Wait for me in the room.
And tell Dan Ho to find Lady Kim.
Yes, my lord.
Did you catch him?
Who are you?
My father, my brother, and me.
Why did you try to kill us?
Who on earth am I?
Answer me.
- Are you...
- My lord! Lord Heo!
The village for widows is in danger.
Let us begin!
- Yes!
- Let us start.
- Oh, no.
- What?
- There is a fire!
- Fire!
Do not miss anyone.
- What is going on?
- Darn it.
There were rice cake and meat in it.
Anyway, it was really good.
I have never heard of a place
that sells that dish.
My gosh, this is frustrating.
I am certain this is the place.
I am certain of it.
Hey, just eat some food and go.
You will see a tiger later
if you stay out.
That is all right.
We can spend the night here.
With this, we can spend
10 nights here.
She is talking a bunch of nonsense.
Why did he tell her to eat something
that does not exist?
Gosh, this is annoying.
But she has a lot of money with her.
Kill everyone!
Kill all of them.
(Brewery)
That is our village.
Fire...
How dare you?
Lady Kang, what is going on?
I do not know.
Fire...
Kill all of them.
Dong Joo.
Stop it immediately!
What is that? Where are you going?
Tell him that I am sorry
that it is not much.
To whom?
Your brother.
What is his name?
Nok Du.
(The Tale of Nokdu)
Dan Ho. That jerk.
I cannot spare him any longer.
A group of robbers did this?
I will find and kill them...
no matter what.
Is this what you were trying...
to hide from me?
Hanyang? You must take things easy
for the time being.
There is a conversation
I have not finished yet.
Until when will you ride it?
I guess fate found its way to you.