♪Have you ever heard about♪
♪The cliff of a snow mountain♪
♪Once fascinated numerous people?♪
♪Legend has it that♪
♪There were treasures at the peak♪
♪But also there was a bottomless chasm
hidden over there♪
♪The smart, the fool♪
♪And the kind people♪
♪All are familiar to you♪
♪On the mountainside, on the cliff♪
♪On the cloud♪
♪And in the human world♪
♪Snowflakes are drifting profusely and disorderly♪
=Joy of Life Special Edition=
=Episode 14=
One more thing.
According to the information
sent from Beiqi,
my son was caught
because his identity was disclosed.
By secret agents from Beiqi?
No, not from Beiqi.
You mean from the capital city?
He was betrayed by someone
from the capital city.
Bingyun lurking in Beiqi
is a top secret.
Besides His Majesty,
only officials from
our Investigator's Office know it.
Can it be someone from our office?
Why not?
Head,
I think we should carry out
a thorough investigation right away.
No need.
It's a serious problem.
It ends now.
Never mention it again.
Yes.
The Investigator's Office has
been established for so many years.
Time passes so quickly.
It's time to replace some old stuff.
Dad, you want to see me.
You're back.
Come and take a seat.
The negotiation
in Court of State Ceremonials is over.
Be cautious at the Hall tomorrow.
You mean
the banquet tomorrow night?
What's wrong?
you're elegant and kind.
literary giants are all in Beiqi.
In earlier years,
scholars actually found it an honor
to pass
the imperial examinations in Beiqi.
Though things are better these years,
when it comes to scholars,
Nanqing is no match to Beiqi.
Now the Nanqing literary circles
have anchored their hopes on you.
I...
The literary circles?
Zhuang Mohan and his mission
"A thousand miles from home, I'm grieved at
autumn's plight" which you wrote a few days ago
is rated as
the No.1 Current Seven-character Poem
by scholars of Nanqing.
Many say in private that
accomplished at such a young age,
you can be better
than Zhuang Mohan in future.
I just wrote one poem.
They are too hasty
in drawing the conclusion.
One poem is not much,
but we've longed for a talented scholar
for so long.
We may even fight a losing battle.
Who will lose?
You, of course.
So tomorrow night,
everyone will watch me
meeting the literary giant
Zhuang Mohan.
You don't need to be amazing.
Just play it safe.
That's enough.
Will you go tomorrow night?
The banquet tomorrow
is especially set for
Court of State Ceremonials
and Board of Rites.
I'm the Assistant Minister
of Ministry of Revenue.
Why would I go?
Don't worry.
Just a little advice.
Respected as Zhuang Mohan is,
why would he actually
make things difficult
for a young man like you?
Fan Xian will also attend
the banquet tomorrow night.
Master Zhuang, please ruin his name.
You've hung up a red lantern.
Uncle, for all these years,
I've been wondering
whether you can see or not.
How come you know
I hang up a lantern?
And you even know the color.
It's hard for me to explain.
I can know everything.
But I don't see with eyes.
You see with your heart.
I don't know how to put it.
Uncle...
I find you mysterious all the time.
If anyone dares to piss you off,
he's definitely dice with death.
Take a seat. Take a seat. Take a seat.
Let's get down to business.
Tomorrow night,
the imperial family will hold a banquet at
the Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest.
The Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest?
How is Wang Qinian involved?
Who?
Wang Qinian,
Uncle,
besides being mysterious,
how come your thoughts
are so hard to follow recently?
Thoughts?
I don't think
the Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest
has anything to do with Wang Qinian.
Fine.
Let's get down to business.
The banquet tomorrow is mainly for
the celebration of finishing
the war against Beiqi.
It's kind of a big event.
Aren't you going to ask me
why I ask you over?
Aren't you going to tell me
if I don't ask?
You've made a point.
Fine.
After the banquet tomorrow night,
we'll break into the imperial harem.
Are you sure?
Everyone will relax
after a great event.
OK, the plan remains unchanged.
I'll lure Hong Sixiang away,
and you should sneak into
the Empress Dowager's palace
to find the key.
There's one last problem.
I don't know
where the Empress Dowager keeps the key.
It might take time to find it.
There's a secret compartment
on the bed board under her pillow.
All her important things are kept there.
How did you know
Your mom searched it before.
Why did my mom
search her secret compartment?
The old lady has lived in widowhood
for so many years.
Though she looks serious,
I wonder whether she keeps
love letters in private or not.
Those are the words
said by your mom back then.
So she searched the Empress Dowager's
secret compartment only for gossiping!
I've no idea
what gossiping implies,
but yes, you're right.
Didn't she get caught?
I kept watch for her.
Why are you laughing?
Words can't express
my feelings right now.
What feelings?
Just forget it.
Anyway, back then,
my mom had solved
the biggest problem for me.
Now,
as long as I know where the key is,
I feel quite sure of getting it out.
If we take the key,
the old lady might notice.
We'd better put in a fake one.
Without seeing the real key,
how could you
make a fake one in advance?
I've got an idea.
Good.
Wait for me here tomorrow night.
Someone's here.
I asked him over.
Seriously?
Your Excellency.
Come in.
It's quite late now.
Do you have anything for me?
I have a question for you.
Please go ahead.
Do you have anything to do with the
Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest?
I suppose not.
I think so.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Take a seat.
Your Excellency, thank you.
I might as well stand.
Your Excellency,
I heard
that by deterring the Beiqi mission
in the Court of State Ceremonials,
you've made great contributions
to Nanqing.
I will attend the banquet
tomorrow night.
Your Excellency,
charismatic and vigorous as you are,
you'll definitely be promoted
in the near future.
Is this for me?
Yes.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
next time you grant me a reward,
please grant me bank notes instead.
They are easier to hide.
I want to break into the imperial harem
at night.
Your Excellency,
pardon, please?
I said I want to
break into the imperial harem at night
and sneak into
the Empress Dowager's palace
to steal a key.
Of course,
for fear the old lady might notice,
I have to make a fake key overnight
to replace the real one.
That's my plan.
Are you kidding me?
Not really.
Are you serious?
Yes.
It's a deadly sin
which could implicate your family.
I suppose it is.
Then why do you
tell me about it?
I just told you
I have to make a fake key
overnight.
I have to find
the best locksmith in the capital city.
Since I'm not familiar with
the capital city,
I need someone with connections.
That's you.
If I'm involved,
I will also commit a deadly sin.
You just find me a locksmith
to make a key.
You know nothing else.
Right!
Then you should only ask me
to find a locksmith.
Right? Why tell me
the whole plan?
I also want to tell you less,
but I can't.
You have to wait for me
outside the imperial palace tomorrow.
Your Excellency!
Aren't you afraid
that I might tell on you?
Do you really want to
trust me
with your life?
Of course I do.
You're a wise man.
You should know that
you only need to
take a little risk by helping me,
but you'll get yourself killed
if you dare betray me.
Why do you say that?
You know how Chen Pingping
treats me.
The Head treats you like his son.
So this is the case.
If I tell on you
and get you killed,
the Head will definitely
cut me into pieces.
You're really wise.
Then why don't you ask the Head
to do you the favor.
It's inconvenient for big potatoes
to do such things.
What can I say?
The choice is yours.
I know a good locksmith.
Good. Ask him to
wait for me tomorrow night.
OK.
From tonight on,
I'll raise your salary
by another ten taels of silver.
This is something
that might get my entire family killed.
You only add ten taels of silver?!
Don't you think it's too little?
So you don't want it?
I want it.
Give me bank notes instead next time.
What time is it?
It's about 1:00 p.m.
Is the Hall of Prayer
for Good Harvest ready?
Yes, they started decorating
early this morning.
Find me a place for the night banquet.
It's only held
for Court of State Ceremonials
and Board of Rites.
It's no big deal.
Just do it.
Yes.
I can't wait.
I've asked.
As to the night banquet in the
Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest,
guests can take seats at about 5:00 p.m.
Your Highness, if you eat too much now,
you won't feel like eating
in the banquet
On such banquets,
there will be
a lot of drinking and praises.
How could I fill my belly?
That's right.
Such banquets
are merely a formality.
Your Highness really don't
have to go.
Fan Xian completed
his first task successfully.
I certainly should
congratulate him in person.
Hasn't Fan Xian taken the side of
the Crown Prince?
Who told you so?
If not, why would the Crown Prince
send him to
negotiate with the Beiqi mission?
Man like Fan Xian
won't follow the Crown Prince willingly.
I've only met Fan Xian a few times,
but I find him a bosom friend.
Just like me,
Fan Xian won't feel content
to occupy a position below others.
How long has His Highness stood there?
About an hour.
His Highness is afraid to
form folds on his gown.
What time is it?
Your Highness, it's about 5:00 p.m.
Let's go to the Hall of Prayer
for Good Harvest.
Yes.
Your Excellency Fan!
Your Excellency Xin!
What a coincidence!
Indeed!
Your Excellency Fan,
why not wear your robe?
It's just a meal.
I'm not some high-ranking official.
Well then. I'll have
more drinks with you later.
Your Excellencies, regular examination.
No edged tools
can be taken inside.
Who would bring edged tools
to a banquet?
Your Excellency Fan, listen!
The ritual music
is prepared by the Board of Rites.
Can I bring needles in?
Steel needles. About this long.
No.
Wait a moment.
That's all.
Your Excellency Xin, let's get inside.
I'm cautious
because I was assassinated before.
Yes, you should be.
It's right to be cautious.
Can I bring in poisons?
Poisons?
No! No! No!
Fan Xian,
Your Highness.
What's going on?
Don't touch it.
These are poisons made by myself.
I'm not allowed to bring them inside.
You're really Fei Jie's student.
Can they kill?
Of course.
Give me a bag.
No.
Why?
If anything happens to His Majesty
and the Crown Prince,
I won't be able to justify myself.
Right. Just forget it.
Fan Xian, you've rendered
meritorious services this time.
You'll definitely have a bright future.
Congratulations!
Thank you,
We can see each other more.
I might be able to
help in the imperial court.
I'm so flattered.
Your Highness.
You're from Court of State
Ceremonials. Your name is Wang...
Xin!
Xin... Xin... Xin...
Xin Qiwu.
I remember you're a follower
of the Crown Prince.
We're all couriers! We're all couriers!
If you feel dissatisfied
following the Crown Prince,
you can follow me instead.
There should be none left.
Now there's none left.
Don't touch them.
I don't have the antidotes
for some poisons.
Your Excellency Xin.
What're you thinking?
In your opinion,
why does the Second Prince
come to the banquet?
To draw talents like Your Excellency Xin
over to his side
of course.
Your Excellency Fan,
you're making fun of me again.
It's obvious that the Second
Prince was trying to win you over.
How could it be me?
Your Highness! Please believe me!
I'm definitely loyal
to Your Highness.
I will never follow others.
Your Highness,
Your Highness, I can prove that.
Just now, the Second Prince
did try to win him over,
but loyal as His Excellency Xin is,
he didn't take the offer.
Yeah! Yeah!
Your Excellency Fan,
thank you for telling the truth.
You're welcome.
Don't worry.
His Highness is open-minded.
Right! Right! Right!
Your Excellency Fan,
something's not right.
The Second Prince actually
said those words to win you over.
How come you become the one
to clear my name instead?
a few days later,
Your Excellency, it's not!
The Princess Royal is also here.
Brat, do you dare
to see me?
Who are you?
Unbelievable!
You're the one
who beat me on the street.
Now you actually pretend
you don't know me!
Young Master Guo!
Long time no see!
Your wounds are almost healed.
Good for you.
How dare you forget me!
Mind your words! Mind your words!
You sound like a whining woman.
You villain!
I'll never forget
what you've done!
You sound more like it.
Why are you here? Why is he here?
Well, he...
I am the Imperial Compiler.
My father is the Minister of
the Board of Rites.
Why can't I be here?
You can! You can!
The dishes will be served soon.
-Mr. Guo, please take your seat.
-Don't be smug.
Fan Xian, let me tell you.
Today, right here,
I'll watch you hit rock bottom
and ruin your name
with my own eyes.
Nonsense!
Father.
What's the occasion?
Go back to your seat!
Yes.
My son is so rude.
Your Excellency Fan, please forgive him.
Who are you?
This is Guo Youzhi,
Minister of the Board of Rites.
Minister, it's you.
Your Excellency, do feel relieved.
Your son is mischievous and lovely.
I'm not angry at all.
Well. Well. Well.
Come on! OK! OK!
Stop looking around.
Our seats are over there.
Come on! This way, please!
Let's sit here.
Come on! Have a seat!
Have a seat!
Your Excellency Fan, have a seat!
Your Excellency Fan,
Guo Baokun is also
a follower of the Crown Prince.
You'd better make peace.
I'm fine with that.
Just look at him.
Your problem will be solved gradually.
Your Excellency! Your Excellency!
Did you really beat him?
How could that be?
By reading the books of sages
since childhood,
I've always been denying self
and returning to propriety.
How could I beat others?
But you killed a martial arts master
from Beiqi on the street a few days ago.
Nice wine.
Right. Right. Nice. Nice.
Xin,
there are two seats left.
For whom?
Probably for the two masters
from Dongyi Town and Beiqi.
Beiqi has sent
the literary giant Zhuang Mohan.
Who has Dongyi Town sent?
As for Dongyi Town...
Your Excellency.
Are you OK?
How can he carry a sword
into the imperial palace?
Apprentices of Si Gujian
never leave their swords behind.
His Majesty
has made an exception for them.
Apprentice of Si Gujian?
He's the first apprentice of
Great Master Si Gujian,
Yun Zhilan?
Those two female assassins
you killed on the street
were his apprentices.
The Dongyi Town mission
is also sent here to settle that.
Does he sell wine?
I've never heard of that.
Your Excellency, why do you ask?
It sounds like a wine's name.
Really?
Your Excellency Fan,
the Princess Royal asks you over
to tell you something.
Come closer.
Don't let her
I've been waiting for you to kill me.
How come there are no surprises?
Your Highness, take it easy.
You'll be surprised at any time.
If you pledge allegiance to me,
I'll let Wan'er marry you.
I'll let you have
the financial power of the Neiku.
And I'll give you more
whatever you want.
What if I want to kick you out of
the capital city?
A great wish.
You should definitely try.
I won't fail Your Highness for sure!
Fan Xian and Auntie
are talking happily.
I wonder what they're talking about.
It's none of my business.
Your Highness wants to
win Fan Xian over, right?
Let's make a bet on
who will get Fan Xian in the end.
What shall we bet?
Life.
It seems I've made
an improper joke.
Your Highness, please forgive me!
Fine!
Zhuang Mohan is here.
You've never met Master Zhuang, right?
It might be fate
for Beiqi to have
such a literary giant.
After explaining classic texts and
annotating articles for decades,
he's got many works to his credit.
In some way,
he's even more powerful than an emperor.
Carrying the literary inheritance
all by himself,
doesn't he find it burdensome?
If the scholars heard
what you just said,
you would be accused of
disrespect of the saint.
Why would I admit
I said those words?
I heard some people
have anchored their hopes on you,
expecting you to become
a literary giant in future.
Your Highness won't hope so for sure!
Well, since Master Zhuang is here,
the banquet should start soon.
Go back to your seat.
I'm leaving.
I've given you the chance,
but you've thrown it away.
Here arrives His Majesty!
This way! This way! This way!
May Your Majesty
live ten thousand years!
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
His Majesty has arrived at the
Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest.
Have you checked
all the maidservants,
eunuchs and imperial guards
on shift tonight?
Yes, I have.
All of them
have a clean family background.
No one is suspicious.
Among those who entered the Hall,
have you found anyone suspicious?
Yes,
Fan Xian is.
According to
the Division of Imperial Guards,
he carried a dagger and poisons with him
when he arrived.
What about Zhuang Mohan?
Zhuang Mohan only took inside
a roll of old paper.
My men took the chance to check it.
There was nothing inside.
I think
Zhuang Mohan doesn't practice
martial arts.
He wouldn't be a problem.
Yun Zhilan went inside with his sword.
Right.
But Yun Zhilan is
an apprentice of Si Gujian.
He is not supposed to
know Zhuang Mohan.
If Yun Zhilan tries to
kill His Majesty with his sword,
who can stop him?
Eunuch Hong Sixiang
is right outside the Hall.
Serve the dishes.
Eunuch Hong, it's a night owl.
Chief Musician Fan.
Your Excellency Fan,
His Majesty is calling you.
Calling me?
What does His Majesty call me?
You're the Chief Musician of
the Court of Imperial Sacrifices.
That's the name
of your official position.
Your Majesty.
You've seen me a few times,
but you've never knelt down.
I thought
you would remain standing this time.
Then I would piss off everyone.
Look at your blurred eyes.
You must have drunk a lot.
Your Majesty,
On such a big occasion,
I can't help feeling nervous.
Yun Zhilan?
Your two apprentices
were killed by him.
I know.
Young as he is,
he's somewhat competent.
He's competent if he can kill me.
The apprentice of Si Gujian
is really proud.
I get that.
Fan Xian.
According to the memorial submitted
by Court of State Ceremonials,
you've done a great job this time.
The war was started because of you,
and it was ended by you.
I don't want to praise you in public.
Come on! Join me for a drink.
Chief Musician Fan, please wait.
Your Majesty, I have something to say.
Go ahead.
Besides being good at martial arts,
Fan Xian is also famous for
literary grace.
I'm amazed by his talents
in writing poems.
Recently, I've heard that
when negotiating with Beiqi,
Fan Xian handled it properly without
being too humble or too pushy.
He can be entrusted
with important tasks.
Just go straight to the point.
Why not put Fan Xian in charge of
the imperial examinations next spring?
Scholars going down in history
under the supervision of a youth talent,
it might become a much told tale.
Though Fan Xian is known for his poems,
he is inexperienced after all.
Your Majesty.
Though inexperienced,
he is really talented.
I agree.
to put Fan Xian in charge of
the imperial examinations held in spring.
Well...
How could this be?
There're still a few months
before the imperial examinations.
We'll see by then.
You may all leave.
Your Majesty.
Is this young man Fan Xian?
Master Zhuang,
have you also heard of him?
I've read his poem.
Young as he is,
he's talented in poetry.
Master Zhuang, you should guide and
support the younger generation.
I'm a minister from Beiqi.
I should not interfere with
the political affairs of Nanqing.
But the imperial examinations
held in spring
are of fundamental importance
to scholars around the world.
You should be cautious
when choosing the man in charge.
Master Zhuang, you're absolutely right.
When it comes to
the imperial examinations,
we can't be too cautious.
Master Zhuang, I admire you for being
well versed in the learning of
both ancient and modern times,
but I don't agree with
what you just said.
Though I'm a woman
with little knowledge,
I've read the seven-character poem
written by Fan Xian.
He's young indeed,
but this poem alone
can show he's really talented.
What you said just now
is secretly against Fan Xian.
Are you afraid that
this young man might surpass you one day
and gain a better reputation than you?
Everyone else present here
is either a trustworthy minister
or a learned scholar.
They certainly don't like to argue.
Ignorant as I am,
I'm willing to speak up for
our talent of Nanqing.
Are you referring to
that seven-character poem?
Exactly.
Master, have you got any poem
better than that?
Yunrui, mind your manners in the Hall.
Master Zhuang, you're broad-minded.
Please forgive her for being rude.
The wind so swift,
the sky so wide, apes wail and cry;
Water so clear and beach so white,
birds wheel and fly.
The boundless forest sheds its leaves
shower by shower;
The endless river rolls its waves
hour after hour.
A thousand miles from home,
I'm grieved at autumn's plight;
Ill now and then for years,
alone I'm on this height.
Living in times so hard,
at frosted hair I pine;
Cast down by poverty,
I have to give up wine.
What a fantastic poem!
I've written poems my whole life,
but none
can match that.
In this case,
you admit defeat candidly.
The first four lines are wonderful.
But people all say
the essence of the poem
is the latter four lines.
The latter four lines
are absolutely marvelous.
It's a pity that
they were not written by Mr. Fan.
So Fan Xian copied the poem.
Yes.
I also find it strange.
How could he
be so talented?
Fan Xian,
do you have anything to say?
Master Zhuang can say
whatever he likes
After all,
highly respected as Master Zhuang,
what he says counts even
if he has no proof.
Your Majesty,
I can prove that
Fan Xian wrote the poem
at the poetry gathering
held in Prince Jing's mansion.
Guo Baokun, the Imperial Compiler
was also there.
He can be a witness.
Is Guo Baokun here?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Did Fan Xian write the poem?
Yes.
In this case,
Master Zhuang is trying to
frame Fan Xian up on purpose.
He might be misled by others
to form such a misunderstanding.
What a coincidence!
The latter four lines of the poem
were written by my teacher
when he was visiting Tingzhou.
It should to be a good thing to see
such wonderful lines reappearing
in the world.
But Mr. Fan
actually made a name with other's poem.
Is that appropriate?
For scholars,
morality is more important than talent.
The first four lines of the poem
are remarkable.
Mr. Fan is definitely talented.
But why does he have to be so greedy
as to make a name
with other's work.
I was hesitant about
telling the truth.
But after careful thinking,
I feel that by telling the truth,
I might help Mr. Fan
and decided to
return to the correct path.
There's no making without breaking.
He can focus on moral cultivation
in future.
Mr. Fan,
I told the truth
because I cherish your talents.
I mean no harm.
Please be introspective.
Fan Xian,
feel free to speak your mind.
Master Zhuang,
is your teacher surnamed Du?
No.
Never mind.
Master Zhuang is known for
respecting teachers and honoring truth,
I suppose
he won't use his teacher's reputation
to frame up an innocent man.
But men are hard to predict.
He might feel unhappy
seeing a young man rising to his fame
and make all this up to
destroy his future.
If the Princess Royal
are you suspecting me of
framing this young man up
at the cost of my teacher's reputation?
I dare not.
It's just that unlike Beiqi,
Nanqing emphasizes laws.
If you want to accuse someone,
words alone
won't be enough.
Your Highness, you've made a point.
Look, it was written by my teacher
back then.
Could it be
the proof?
The lines are exactly the same.
Even without the handwritten copy,
we can see the truth.
The latter four lines of the poem
depict a desolated
and frustrated life.
Without going through
ups and downs in life,
how could anyone ever depict
such an artistic conception?
But Mr. Fan,
you're successful and famous
at a young age.
How could you be so sad
and desolated?
When a young man
tries to express sorrow,
he would normally go too far.
Your Majesty.
Fan Xian gains a reputation
by deception.
He's utterly shameless.
By doing so,
he has disgraced
all the scholars of Nanqing.
I beg Your Majesty to
deprive him of his official title,
expel him from the capital city,
and never recruit him
as an official again.
Young Master Guo!
Since I've disgraced
Nanqing,
why are you so happy?
Nonsense!
I'm just furious.
I feel ashamed to be your colleague.
When did you know that Master Zhuang
would argue about the truth on the Hall?
I just heard him of course.
Then why did you say with certainty that
I would be utterly discredited
the moment I arrived at
the Hall of Prayer for Good Harvest?
Either you're good at fortune-telling,
or you've hooked up with Master Zhuang
in advance!
Nonsense!
How could you use "hook up" to describe
my relationship with Master Zhuang?
Well,
At such a critical moment,
just forget about the choice of words.
Your Majesty,
my son doesn't get along with Fan Xian
all the time.
Their dispute matters nothing.
What's important now
is Fan Xian's poem.
Since he copied other's work,
he should be severely punished,
or the public anger
won't be quelled.
Minister, good for you.
You pointed out the heart of
the matter directly.
I just spoke my mind impartially.
Master Zhuang,
you're right.
I copied that poem from others.
He really copied from other's work!
Mr. Fan,
you're brave to admit your mistake.
After this, you're sure
to achieve great success in future.
Stop flattering me.
Master Zhuang,
I copied poem for myself,
and you copied poem for your teacher.
We're no different.
In fact,
you're not as frank as I am.
This poem
is written by Du Fu, the Saint of Poem,
who is also known as Shaoling Yelao.
It has nothing to do with your teacher.
Gaining fame for your teacher
by deceiving the public,
Master Zhuang is really a role model
of respecting teacher and honoring truth.
The Saint of Poem?
Which dynasty
was he from?
As the Saint of Poem,
did he go down in history?
We can't find him in historical records.
I see.
Because his poems
are from another world.
A world lasts for thousands of years
and is filled with splendid poems.
Is it the fairyland
existed in legends?
Feel free to laugh! Feel free to laugh!
It's definitely the fairyland
compared to your world.
Have you been there?
It's a picture scroll
left from my dream,
a memory left in my head.
Your Excellency Fan,
you mean
you've travelled to the fairyland
and recited a poem in your dream.
Your Majesty.
what Fan Xian said
is utterly ridiculous.
By making up such an absurd story,
he lied to Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I beg you to punish him!
Master Zhuang,
has your teacher written a lot of poems?
My teacher has written
many excellent poems.
Does he have many unpublished poems?
I've gone through all his works,
and that is the only poem
that remains unpublished.
Who told you
I only recited one poem in my dream?
Give me paper.
Give me ink.
Mr. Fan,
if you want to compose poems,
I'd like to write them down for you.
You want to
improvise more poems
to prove that you saw them all
from the fairyland?
you don't know
That memory
is literally carved
into my head.
Every word I saw
and every book I read,
I can remember them clearly
as if they're right in front of me.
Do you know what you're talking about?
I'm afraid he's so exasperated that
he starts to talk nonsense.
Don't you see
the Yellow River pouring from heaven,
rushing to the sea, never to return?
Don't you see, in the hall
the mirror is saddened by the grey hair?
Young and dark at dawn,
but at dusk snowy!
Ah, let's enjoy ourselves while we can.
"It's wrong to set goblets idle,
in the glory of the moon."
I was created by Heaven,
certainly not for nothing.
As for money,
it scatters and gathers as money should.
When will there be no more
moon and spring flowers?
For me who had so many memorable hours?
If youask me
how much my sorrow has increased,
just see the overbrimming river
flowing east!
I do not know in the celestial sphere.
what name this festive night goes by?
I want to fly home, riding the air,
but fear the ethereal cold up there.
The jade and crystal mansions are so high!
[*It's too high and too cold for me.]
Dancing to my shadow,
I feel no longer the mortal tie.
Though drunk,
we lit the lamp to see the glaive.
Sober, we heard the horns
from tent to tent.
Under the flags, beef grilled was eaten
by our warriors brave.
And martial airs were played
by fifty instruments.
It was an autumn maneuver in the field.
We wished to fly in heaven,
two birds with the wings of one,
and to grow together on the earth,
two branches of one tree.
On the road ahead
surely will be friends dear and true.
Throughout the land is there anyone
who knows not you?
My attic which last night
in vernal wind did stand.
A few plum twigs
at the corner of the wall
blossoming all alone, defying the cold!
Would you have me bow my head
before mighty princes?
On war-torn land streams flow
and mountains stand.
In vernal town grass
and weeds are overgrown.
Though I am white-haired,
still I'd sing and drink my fill.
Hating to part,
hearing birds breaks our heart.
We can't fly wing to wing
like a pair of phoenixes,
yet our hearts closely linked
beat in harmony.
Here's my precious horse,
here's my priceless fur.
Tell the boy to give them for the wine.
I want to fly home, riding the air,
but fear the ethereal cold up there.
Hear spring rain
falling in a small mansionall night!
Till mountains crumble, streams run dry,
thunder rumbles in winter,
snow falls in summer.
West of the Yangguan Pass
you'll see no more of mine.
I do not know in the celestial sphere.
Men are born sentimental and emotional.
Myriad footpaths
with no human traces shown.
For the long years,
to whom can I my grief convey?
Youth do not know real depression.
Time passes indifferently,
turning people from young to old.
Revived even if she be,
could she still know me?
Near a cottage a stream flows.
How panic-stricken I was retreating
before the Tartars!
Being a captive,
I lamented over my solitary confinement.
Who can avert his death
since time immemorial?
Let my heart remain true to
shine in the annals.
No ancients before me,
nor comers from behind.
Reflecting on
the infinite heaven and earth,
Alone, in a sadness sublime,
my tears come.
Is it over one hundred?
Mr. Fan, it's way over one hundred.
That'll be enough.
How could there be any fairyland
in the world?
If not,
where do all these poems
come from?
They must be written by himself!
Even if
he writes them all,
even if he writes thousands of poems,
it can't prove that
he didn't copy that poem.
He can recite marvelous poems
without thinking.
how could he
copy other's work?
Why should he?
When it comes to explaining
classic texts and annotating articles,
you win.
But when it comes to reciting poems,
I win.
For a literary giant...
...I'm not qualified.
But for a man,
you're not qualified.
Since I am drunk and sleepy,
you may go...
What's wrong, Master Zhuang?
Master Zhuang!
Master Zhuang, wake up!
Get the imperial physician!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Come on.
Put the sober soup on the table.
Put it here! Put it here! Right!
Plump the pillow
to make it soft.
He drank too much.
Make sure
he won't get a stiff neck tomorrow.
The plan remains unchanged.
Wait for me outside the palace walls.
No!
You're so drunk.
Let's make it another day.
He's here! He's here!
Mr. Fan, the poetic genius, is here!
You're here! Hurry up!
Put him on the bed! Put him on the bed!
Be careful! Be careful!
Slow down!
Cover him up!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Be careful! Cover him up!
Thank you!
You may go back and rest.
I'll take care of my brother.
There're a lot of servants here.
No need to bother you.
Save it!
Enough of that.
No need to make a fuss.
He's just drunk.
Do you know what your brother has done
in the imperial palace?
What?
He's a well-known poetic genius now.
His Majesty ordered
the imperial guards
to escort His Excellency Fan home.
His Majesty also said
to take good care of him.
Now,
he is the treasure of
Nanqing.
Of course not.
I mean it.
Your Excellency, you don't know.
Mr. Fan composed poems
out of drunkenness tonight.
Everyone in the Hall
was stunned and startled.
Many said in private that
he's really a poetic genius
sent from heaven.
Look at your brother Fan Xian.
He's such a promising young man.
Look at you! You only want to sleep.
Just learn from your brother.
Isn't he also sleeping now?
He...
Ask them to leave.
You are different!
Get up!
It's late.
Go back and rest.
I'll take care of my bother.
No need to rest.
He's become a well-known genius.
We should take good care of him.
Make some midnight snacks in case that
he wants something to eat
after waking up.
Go there now.
Hurry up!
Enough of that.
Just leave.
Brother needs to rest.
Go! Go! Leave now!
Let him have a good rest.
Be quiet! Be quiet!
It's time to go.
Let your brother have a good rest.
Leave now!
We should leave early.
Brother!
Brother, are you OK?
I'm fine.
Did Zhuang Mohan really spit blood?
Yes.
After tonight,
Fan Xian will be known
as a poetic genius.
In this case,
Zhuang Mohan has made a lie to
frame Fan Xian up.
His good reputation over seventy years
was ruined over one night.
He actually ruined his life
at such an old age.
After writing down so many poems,
your hand must be sore.
Now that there's good news
from our literary circles,
it's a happy event rarely seen.
Even if my hand would be broken
for writing down the poems,
I still feel happy
from the bottom of my heart.
Your Majesty, are you tired?
I just feel emotional.
Nanqing was founded
with military forces.
When it comes to civil administration,
we're far behind compared to Beiqi.
The late emperor
was deeply concerned about it at heart.
God blesses Nanqing.
Now we have Mr. Fan, the poetic genius.
Poetic genius?
Or may be a lost genius?
But the poems
are really good.
But I'm wondering
whether he wrote them or not.
Haven't you taken the medicine?
It helps to vomit.
Ruoruo,
some people in the imperial court
have conspired with Zhuang Mohan.
What happened today is a setup.
Who might they be?
The Princess Royal and Guo Youzhi.
If the Princess Royal
Didn't she defend you
all the time in the Hall?
You're a smart girl.
How can you fall for her trick?
I'll sneak into
the imperial palace tonight.
But brother, you're too drunk.
Because I'm drunk,
no one will suspect me.
Ruoruo,
guard the room for me.
Don't let anyone in.
I know.
As long as I'm alive,
no one can get in.
♪In the river of history♪
♪Time goes round and round♪
♪Memories about the former and present lives♪
♪Join each other in an endless way♪
♪In the long drunken Milky Way♪
♪One season follows another in a flash♪
♪And the wild geese are flying south♪
♪I just can't give up♪
♪To be with you for my whole life♪
♪I have been hovering in the dreams
for hundreds and thousands of times♪
♪I can't even say a word
when I watch the flowers falling♪
♪Year after year in the wandering♪
♪I count the remaining years♪
♪Even though we can't meet each other anymore♪
♪Even though we have ended up the destiny♪
♪I never feel regretful♪
♪In such a chaotic world♪
♪I still miss you as ever♪
♪I can't fall asleep under the moon♪
♪With a gentle heart♪
♪I cherish our remaining years♪
♪Even though we have to go through♪
♪All the hardships along the journey♪
♪You always stay by my side♪
♪Watching the falling flowers, speechlessly♪
♪Year after year in the wandering♪
♪I count the remaining years♪
♪Even though we can't meet each other anymore♪
♪Even though we end up the destiny♪
♪I never feel regretful♪
♪In such a chaotic world♪
♪I still miss you as ever♪
♪I can't fall asleep under the moon♪
♪With a gentle heart♪
♪I cherish our remaining years♪
♪Even though we have to go through♪
♪All the hardships along the journey♪
♪You always stay by my side♪