UNDER THE QUEEN'S UMBRELLA
EPISODE 14
Ik-hyeon.
You must…
survive…
at any cost.
Please…
stay healthy.
This is where it ends for us
as father and son.
Go now.
Thank you.
Not at all, Your Highness.
You must preserve yourself.
You will be seen by others.
Go on now.
Seung-seon.
Serve Her Majesty well.
Yes, Father.
Very well.
Let us go.
Who is the real father of Prince Uiseong?
Answer me. Who is the real father
of Prince Uiseong?
You already know.
He is the son of His Majesty.
Did you really think I poisoned this?
Your Royal Highness.
Prince Uiseong
is the first son
His Majesty held in his arms.
He is his firstborn.
"The Crown Prince passed away
in his quarters."
"The King and Official Historian
Park Jung-ho attended
as Royal Physician Yoo Sang-uk
conducted the autopsy
and Royal Physician Cho Guk-yeong
wrote the geomsimunan."
GEOMSIMUNAN: AN AUTOPSY REPORT
The record has been destroyed.
Official Historian Park Jung-ho?
My Queen,
what did you just say?
Please reinvestigate the cause of death
of Crown Prince Taein.
The death of our late Crown Prince
is too similar to his death.
Are you saying…
our Crown Prince was murdered?
Yes.
There is such a suspicion.
So I wish to look into the cause
of death of Crown Prince Taein.
I cannot dig into the past
based on mere speculation.
Do you know what it would mean
if Crown Prince Taein was murdered?
It would mean my enthronement
was nothing less than a rebellion.
I have been on the throne
for over 20 years,
but I am still surrounded
by those who threaten my authority.
Moreover, there was a suspicion
of Seo Ham-deok's rebellion.
I am yet to find out
who took part in this treason.
You should be
my biggest support, My Queen.
Why do you…
raise such a suspicion?
I am not here to raise suspicion.
I am simply trying to find out
how our son died.
If…
he was really murdered,
I need to know why he had to die
and who took his life.
I must know.
I will not allow it.
If the Crown Prince was truly murdered,
I will look into it in another way.
But I will not allow the reinvestigation
of the death of Crown Prince Taein.
Seungjeongwon ilgi was tampered with?
Yes.
The problem is, only the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein is gone.
It was suspicious enough
that all the records were destroyed
by the fire in the Royal Clinic.
But the record
in the Royal Secretariat is also gone?
I am certain someone tried to conceal it.
Who could it be?
Someone who is afraid
that the report will come to light.
It seems all the records of that day
are gone now.
No.
There may be remains…
of gajangsacho, the first draft
kept by an official historian.
GAJANGSACHO: THE FIRST DRAFT
OF SECRET AFFAIRS AND PERSONAL REMARKS
You know the name
of the official historian
who attended the autopsy.
Do you know of
Official Historian Park Jung-ho?
He is the father of Lord Park Gyeong-u.
Did you…
just say gajangsacho?
Yes.
Have you read the gajangsacho
left behind by your late father?
Back then,
did you leave me
because of that gajangsacho?
Did you summon me back to the palace
because of that?
What are you planning
to do about Prince Uiseong?
I shall let him live.
Do you know
why I let one of the children
of the deposed Queen Yoon live?
When your children die one after another,
and only one is left,
you live every single day
in complete anxiety and torment,
worrying that you may lose that one too.
What is more dreadful
than losing your child
is that you cannot kill yourself
because of the child you still have.
Therefore,
if I kill Prince Uiseong right away,
the pain will end
a little too early for Consort Hwang.
For now,
I do need to know
who the real father of Prince Uiseong is.
Look into that.
Do you mean there is no record at all?
That is right.
The evidence to prove
Crown Prince Taein was murdered by poison…
no longer exists.
Therefore,
we must stop our investigation
of the cause of his death.
Instead,
there is one thing I need you to do.
Find the poison
that killed my late Crown Prince.
It does not react to silver.
When taken orally,
it causes balban in the mouth.
BALBAN: BRUISING AND PETECHIAE
Pick out the most likely ones
and bring them to me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What happened?
The records of Seungjeongwon
were also damaged.
Damaged?
Do you think
it was also the King's doing?
The only hope we have left is…
to find the original draft of the
autopsy report of Crown Prince Taein.
It is not like I do not know that.
We searched through the Royal Clinic
and the home of Cho Guk-yeong,
but we were unable to find it.
The Chief State Councilor
may have it already.
Chief State Councilor?
Therefore, we must get him
to stand on our side.
Have you decided?
I cannot bring down
the King I enthroned myself.
So Prince Uiseong, you must stop here.
Stop here?
-I cannot do that.
-Prince Uiseong!
Lying around in a fancy residence
after receiving 180 gyeol of land
made me become even firmer on this.
I must return to the palace.
I said I will do what I can
to make it happen.
Do you still not get it?
Your influence in the palace
has also changed.
That may be true, but this is wrong.
Have you forgotten
how your mother raised you?
Your ambition could put her in danger!
She gave me her permission.
When your child takes the wrong path,
it is a duty of a parent to correct it.
You must stop Prince Uiseong
before things get out of hand.
It is too late.
Do you not know what happens
to the rebels if the rebellion fails?
I would rather die
than live in this humiliation.
Cho-yeon!
Prince Uiseong is not the son of the King.
What?
The Queen Dowager
also seems to be aware of this.
If the King finds out about this,
not only will my life be in danger,
but also yours and Prince Uiseong's.
Why did you wish to see me?
Have you seen the gajangsacho,
the first draft, your father put together
in the year of his death?
I apologize,
but my father did not leave
any gajangsacho.
So please,
I ask you not to call for me
over such a matter from now on.
Someone has tampered
with Seungjeongwon ilgi.
So…
the only remaining record of that day
is in the gajangsacho
your father put together.
I have
never seen that draft.
I heard your father suddenly passed
not long after he attended
the autopsy of Crown Prince Taein.
Do you think…
that is a coincidence?
Even if his gajangsacho is left behind,
if he chose to hide it even as he passed,
would it not be
the truth he tried to hide until the end?
What if it is
the record he tried to protect
at the cost of his life?
It has been a while, my lord.
Yoo Sang-uk.
How are you still…
Yes, I am somehow still alive.
I do, however,
look a bit ragged, thanks to you.
What is it?
Are you shocked that the man
whom you were sure you had killed
is sitting before you?
There is no reason
to bicker over the past.
Let us get to the point.
Very well, then.
Chief State Councilor, since you are here,
may I take it
as your agreement to join us?
Let me ask you before I answer.
Is the King you wish to enthrone
Grand Prince Yeongwon, Yi Ik-hyeon?
Yes.
You are right.
You must stop the interrogation.
Do not hurt him.
Do not tell him that you know.
Are you sure
we can trust him?
Prince Uiseong is not the son of the King.
Yi Ik-hyeon?
Is he not the younger brother
of Crown Prince Taein?
The fact that Physician Kwon
is in league with Yoo Sang-uk
means he is also tied to Yi Ik-hyeon.
I know Physician Kwon
was involved in poisoning Brother.
If your assumption is right,
Father might become…
their next target.
Who do you think Physician Kwon is?
Perhaps,
it may not be that Physician Kwon
was abetted by Consort Hwang.
He may be using Consort Hwang.
If Grand Prince Yeongwon
is the one you wish to enthrone,
why would he let me live?
If you provide useful information to him,
he may guarantee your safety.
When Crown Prince Taein passed away,
the current King was there.
If the rebellion succeeds,
can you testify to what you just said?
If you can guarantee
the safety of my life and the position
of Prince Uiseong in the palace,
then I will testify.
It looks like there is more
you want from me.
What do you really want from me?
I am sure you have a good reason
why you wish to bring me into this.
The autopsy report of Crown Prince Taein.
Give us the original draft of the report.
Why are you asking me for that?
We searched the surroundings
of Cho Guk-yeong
and all of the Royal Clinic
but found nothing.
So I figured you were the only one
who would have it.
I do not have it.
Cho Guk-yeong, that sly man,
would not have hidden it just anywhere.
He used to be a mere assistant to you.
How do you think he became
a minister-level official?
Cho Guk-yeong was the one
who killed Crown Prince Taein
on the orders of the Queen Dowager.
Why do you think
she let him live to this day?
I am sure he prepared
for what was to come to save himself.
Are you saying
the gajangsacho was left behind?
Yes.
However,
it includes content
I cannot show you, Your Majesty.
I ask you to just let it go.
I cannot do that.
If I let this go,
then the truth of that day
may disappear forever.
If
Official Historian Park Jung-ho passed
because of that record,
then the truth he wanted to leave
as a historian until the end
must be included in that draft.
Please,
tell me the truth of that day,
the truth someone tried to conceal.
Your Majesty.
There is a person and incident involved
that you cannot handle.
Do you still wish to see it?
Yes.
I need to find the truth
behind the death of my late Crown Prince.
So I must know…
the truth of that day.
I ask of you.
I have a request to make as well.
Do not tell anybody
what is written in the gajangsacho.
If you keep that promise,
I will show it to you, Your Majesty.
I promise.
His mouth is filled with balban,
bruising and petechiae.
What killed him?
I regret to inform you
that hyeolheogwol does not
seem to be the cause of his death.
What are your grounds?
There was balban in his mouth,
and his throat was severely swollen.
Also, the wounds on his chest
did not exist before,
and there are bloodstains under his nails.
He must have scratched himself in pain
after he was poisoned,
which caused these wounds.
Do you mean
that my Crown Prince was murdered?
There was no reaction to indicate poison.
The poison could be something
that does not react to beopmul.
BEOPMUL: TOOL USED
TO DETECT POISON DURING AUTOPSY
I cannot be sure,
but we cannot disregard
the possibility he was poisoned.
If you are not sure, then it is not true.
Do not look into the cause of his death.
Do not record anything that happened here.
The cause of death of the Crown Prince
is hyeolheogwol.
Right after the late King
left the examination,
he met with Prince Geumyeong.
And he was soon crowned
as the Crown Prince.
Prince Geumyeong…
is His Majesty.
Does this mean
His Majesty…
was aware that Crown Prince Taein
was poisoned to death?
Crown Princess.
Rumors say you are yet to consummate
your marriage with the Crown Prince.
Is it true?
I apologize.
I will bring you good news soon,
so please do not worry.
By any chance,
is the Crown Prince avoiding you?
Avoiding me?
He is just busy carrying out his duties
as the Crown Prince.
Bearing a son to succeed him
is the most important duty
of the Crown Prince.
Have I not told you?
I am worried about him
because he has not secured his position
as the Crown Prince.
He must be evaluated thoroughly
for everything he does
and tested every second
until he is enthroned.
If he shows any deficiency,
he can be replaced at any time.
That is the reality
of the position of the Crown Prince.
Why would he be replaced
when he was just crowned?
Even if he shows any deficiency,
please shield him, Your Royal Highness.
Crown Princess.
It would not be to his benefit
to shield him blindly.
There is a rumor in the palace
that he is infertile.
Do you not realize
how fatal that is to him?
I will put an end to that rumor.
Please let Her Majesty know
that I am here.
Your Majesty.
Please set a date for our consummation.
I have a plan,
so please wait, Crown Princess.
I have no time to wait.
What is the matter?
I visited the Queen Dowager just now.
The Queen Dowager was quite
inquisitive about the consummation.
I understand that she is worried,
but it seemed like
this could harm His Royal Highness.
And I wish to become closer to him.
After all, we are married.
However,
I have no way of fathoming
what is in his mind.
Could you tell me about him, Your Majesty?
In that case,
there are people
who can tell you more than I can.
Has His Royal Highness
always been brusque?
-Yes.
And does he rarely express himself?
Right, what does he like to eat?
I think he likes everything
that is made with meat.
No, he likes greens
such as bracken and bean sprouts.
I see.
So he is not a picky eater
and eats a balanced diet.
It will take some time,
but I am sure you two will become closer.
He may seem brusque and cold,
but he is actually
the most warmhearted among us.
He is right.
If you meet him more often,
you will grow closer sooner.
And if he keeps giving you a hard time,
just let us know.
We are on your side.
A crown princess who visits
the quarters of a grand prince
before she consummates her marriage
with the Crown Prince?
I am glad.
The more preposterous a rumor is,
the better.
However, Your Royal Highness,
other Grand Princes were also visiting
the quarters of Grand Prince Muan.
It seems like
something is going on with him.
Keep your eyes on his quarters.
Your Majesty.
I have bad news.
There is a rumor in the palace
-that the Crown Prince is a hwaja.
-What?
Hwaja?
A problem with his reproductive organs?
There is also an atrocious rumor
that the Crown Princess
cannot deal with her loneliness
and visits the quarters
of Grand Prince Muan.
That is absurd!
The rumor started from the Queen Dowager.
I cannot let this go on.
Court Lady Oh.
Summon the Crown Prince and Princess now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What about the baby?
Was there a rumor about the baby?
I heard a crying sound,
so I went over and looked.
There was a kitten crying.
So I grabbed it and brought it here.
Goodness, what are you doing?
-You surprised me.
-Did I?
Do not slap me.
Come in.
Greetings.
I am a nursemaid.
As of today,
she will help you two
through the consummation of marriage.
Your Majesty.
I will return your trust
with a result greater than you expected.
I am aware of who you are.
You have never failed once. Is that true?
Yes.
You can count on me.
We will implement an emergency system
until their consummation.
Do you understand?
-Yes.
The first day of consummation
is the day the energy of yang
fills the air
and even eunuchs have difficulty sleeping.
It is in two days,
the fifteenth of this month.
The hour will be midnight and the location
will be the quarters of the Crown Prince.
Crown Prince's delegate.
How well does His Royal Highness
know about sexual matters?
He is aware of the theory,
but he does not seem
to have actual experience.
And he does not show
much interest in women,
so his sexual desire does not seem strong.
Does he not have any physical problems?
He is completely normal.
I check every morning.
Crown Princess' delegate.
How well does Her Royal Highness
know about sexual matters?
She knows everything there is to know,
so there is nothing left to teach her.
Above all, she is fervent.
What is more important than fervor
is to awaken their instinct.
What is this?
People usually say eel, chive, peanut,
watermelon, raw octopus,
and tuber fleece flower
help fill a man's energy as aphrodisiacs.
But they are all useless.
This is all you need.
This is freshwater eel extract
made with water filtered with red clay.
Please drink up.
You drink it.
Your Royal Highness.
May I inform Her Majesty?
Soak all the way in the water
until you are saturated with the scent.
What is this? It smells delightful.
It is medicinal water with white daphne.
White daphne?
Yes.
Its scent is said to travel 1,000 ri,
so it is also called the 1,000 ri flower.
It reminds one of a flowery path
drenched in summer mist
and intoxicates them.
This is a way of training
the muscles in his lower body
between the lower back, thigh, and pelvis.
It helps with circulation
and awakens intrinsic instincts.
You must go down lower.
Hold out just a little longer.
Your marriage will be consummated
tonight at midnight
when the moon is full.
The lovemaking between a man and a woman
comes down to the mood.
Tilt the mattress a little more.
If you keep this on you,
you will give off a sweet smell.
Please lie down on the outside
to keep the energy of yang inside.
This is a wedding drink.
It will help
with the awkwardness and tension.
Prepare to receive His Royal Highness.
-Yes.
There is still
hansikgyeong left until midnight.
HANSIKGYEONG: ABOUT HALF AN HOUR
Yes.
What should we do until then?
This is a wedding drink.
It will help
with the awkwardness and tension.
Would you like to have a drink,
Your Royal Highness?
Although I get drunk easily…
Your Royal Highness.
I want us to be comfortable with each
other like how we were on Manwol Island.
Your Majesty.
What is the matter?
At the time of the Crown Prince's death,
Physician Kwon was imprisoned.
I am sure he used another way
in addition to the poison.
What do you reckon it was?
There is one thing I am suspicious of.
When the needle is inserted
deep into the gimunhyeol,
it can hurt the organ and cause bleeding.
My Crown Prince suffered from hyeolu,
where his blood did not clot properly,
so it must have been fatal.
His internal bleeding must have persisted.
In order to prove
all my assumptions are true,
I must find
the poison Physician Kwon used.
However,
do you think he will bring the poison?
She told me to bring her the poison.
It seems like
the Queen is suspicious of me.
You must be cautious.
Everything will be over if your identity
gets exposed, Your Highness.
So how did it go?
Your Majesty, the Crown Prince
and the Crown Princess
have spent the night together.
What a relief.
I can finally stop worrying about them.
It truly is great news.
I was quite worried.
Goodness.
They spent the night together?
What if
the Crown Princess gives birth to a son?
Would it not be difficult
to throw her out of the palace?
Did we really…
sleep together
last night?
We were together, and we slept.
No, that is not what I meant.
-Did we…
-Do it?
What do you take me for?
Since we were drunk…
I thought about it for a moment,
but I did not want to spend
our first night together that way.
But I did take a look.
Did you…
look at my body?
-Have you gone crazy?
-I checked because I am not.
Crown Princess!
There is a rumor that you are a hwaja.
I had to check if the rumors were true.
It is an important matter.
Other married people see and do
all kinds of things between themselves.
Why must we live otherwise?
Besides, I looked at something
I am allowed to as a wife.
Is that a problem?
Please consider it
a confirmation procedure as a wife.
I do not want to do it like this.
Then how shall we do it?
No married couple
exchanges permission to sleep together.
It happens when the sparks go off.
I must go.
Were you afraid you spent the night
with a woman you do not love?
I also do not want to be with someone
who dislikes me.
I do not dislike…
What did you just say?
Nothing.
What is it, Your Royal Highness?
Let us go.
Who?
There was a physician who came by
Consort Hwang's parents' home often.
And the young assistant of the physician
was Physician Kwon.
Did you just say…
Physician Kwon?
Yes.
How ridiculous.
The father of Prince Uiseong…
is a lowly physician?
Where is he right now?
He has returned to the palace.
The Queen summoned him back.
The Queen?
The first one is water boiled
with poison fire coral.
Next, highly saline salt water.
Lastly,
a poison made with dried
and powdered innards of blowfish.
I am sure the Queen will think…
that I will hide the poison.
Are you saying
you will expose the poison you used
on the late Crown Prince?
That way, the Queen will waste her time
finding the real poison.
Good work.
One of these may be the poison
he used to kill the Crown Prince.
Pardon?
Physician Kwon is a clever man.
So…
he may have brought
the poison he used
in order to rid himself of my suspicion.
Your Majesty.
Won-pyeong has arrived.
Come in.
Your Majesty,
there is something you must see.
You must hurry to Hyewolgak.
She took her own life
due to the grief of her circumstances.
The wounds on her chest
are very similar
to the ones you showed me.
In addition to that,
there are signs of balban,
bruising and petechiae, in her mouth.
What did she take?
Bring it over.
What is this?
It is gansu.
GANSU: SALTY AND BITTER WATER
THAT MELTS NATURALLY FROM MOIST SALT
Gansu…
DISINFECTED THE AFFECTED AREA
OF SKIN DISEASE WITH GANSU
This is it.
The poison that killed
the late Crown Prince.
It was gansu.
What did you just feed me?
This is the method you used,
Physician Cho Guk-yeong.
Have you forgotten already?
You are right.
I added some gansu.
It is clear my son was murdered.
Please trust me, Your Majesty.
His Royal Highness definitely passed
due to hyeolheogwol.
All I want
is the safety of my old mother.
By the way, Your Majesty,
his neighbors said
Physician Kwon
does not have an old mother.
Your son…
Where is the real Yi Ik-hyeon…
right now?
Where is the original draft
of Crown Prince Taein's autopsy report?
If you give it to me, I will let you live.
The autopsy report?
Yes.
I must retrieve it
to prove that my older brother
was poisoned to death by gansu.
Are you…
Have you finally figured it out?
I am the younger brother
of Crown Prince Taein, whom you killed.
I am Grand Prince Yeongwon.
Yi Ik-hyeon…
has killed my late Crown Prince.
Were you aware…
that your son poisoned my son…
to death?
I was not.
However,
even if I had known,
-I would not have stopped him.
-No.
You should have.
How many more must die and be sacrificed?
The Queen Dowager started this.
So why?
Why must I…
stop it?
Yi Ik-hyeon…
may not stop at killing the Crown Prince.
How are you alive?
I was dying to know
why my brother suddenly passed.
So I learned medicine
from Physician Yoo Sang-uk.
Also, a physician is the only one
who can touch the royal family.
Let me live.
Please let me live.
You know very well
that you will not survive
after drinking gansu.
Everything was plotted
by the Queen Dowager.
I only did as she ordered!
I am sure you only did as you were told.
So tell me where the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein is.
Now.
Then I will give you this antidote.
I hid it in the floor
of the archives of the Royal Clinic.
I have marked the place.
Please give me the antidote now.
I wanted to kill you…
the same way you killed my brother.
You…
Physician Kwon.
Are you looking for the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein?
Yes, I am.
What brings you here, Your Majesty?
You already know
why I am standing here before you.
I finally found out who killed my son.
Yi Ik-hyeon.
UNDER THE QUEEN'S UMBRELLA
There is not long until the rebellion.
How is this in your hands?
It has been a while.
Who do you think
will be next?
Tell Prince Uiseong
to remain in his residence for now.
Is there something wrong
with the Crown Princess?
Hand over Physician Kwon to me.
Once you have the autopsy report,
kill him immediately.
I see people do not change.
It is over, Your Majesty.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon