UNDER THE QUEEN'S UMBRELLA
I hid it in the floor
of the archives of the Royal Clinic.
I have marked the place.
Are you looking for the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein?
Yes, I am.
What brings you here, Your Majesty?
You already know
why I am standing here before you.
I finally found out who killed my son.
Yi Ik-hyeon.
From becoming a physician
to entering the palace,
did you do all of that
to get revenge?
Revenge was not my initial plan.
At first, I simply wanted to find out
how my brother died.
Then when did all this start?
A long time ago.
A very long time ago.
What is it you want to know?
Everything.
Tell me everything you know
about my son who died painfully.
Why did it have to be him?
Why?
Why did it have to be him, of all people?
When I found out he was
suffering from hyeolheogwol,
I thought it was destiny.
It was my chance
to learn how my brother died through him.
Are you saying
you killed my son
in the same way
Crown Prince Taein was killed?
I would have been caught right away
if that was the case.
I inserted a needle into his gimunhyeol
to cause his organs to bleed.
Then I repeatedly gave him a small amount
of gansu, salty and bitter water.
In the end, he died
after I stopped treating him.
I trusted you
with the life of my son.
So how could you…
How could you…
How dare you…
How could you dare kill
my child right under my nose?
My mother lost four of her children!
Seeing you in this state
reminds me
of how my mother grieved
over her innocent children.
I sincerely apologize
for taking the life
of the innocent late Crown Prince.
But do not forget
none of this would have happened
if the current king
had not usurped the throne.
As my brothers were killed one by one,
I lived
in constant fear
that it could be my turn at any moment.
You will never understand
the excruciating pain.
I was simply trying to get my revenge.
Shut your mouth.
You can claim all you want
that your fear and pain
justify your revenge,
but you are
nothing but a murderer
who killed my innocent son.
He did not deserve
to be brought down by someone like you.
He did not have
anything to do with your grudges!
Then what did my brothers do
to deserve to be killed?
As I watched my mother
bury the bloody bodies of her sons
holding back her tears of blood,
I swore to myself
I would find out
what caused my brother to die
and put everything in its rightful place.
The death of the Crown Prince
is only the beginning, Your Majesty.
I will never…
let that happen.
I will
put an end to everything.
I will make sure
that you, Yi Ik-hyeon,
pay for taking the life of my son.
-That way! Get him!
-Yes, sir!
There is not long until the rebellion.
As soon as His Highness finds
evidence of poisoning,
we will take action.
So be sure to check
where each of you must be again.
Arrest all of them!
Darn it.
Why are you telling me this now?
I have been suspicious of Physician Kwon,
but I did not know he was Yi Ik-hyeon
until today.
Do you have evidence
that he murdered the late Crown Prince?
Yes.
I have evidence
that he used gansu to kill him.
All we need now is his confession.
If what you say is true,
I will make him pay at any cost.
However,
he is a mere physician
who killed the Crown Prince.
A mere physician?
He is Grand Prince Yeongwon, Yi Ik-hyeon,
who pretended to be a physician.
No. He is not Yi Ik-hyeon.
The man who is living
with the deposed Queen Yoon
is Yi Ik-hyeon.
Your Majesty.
Who has the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein now?
How could you lose him in the palace?
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
He could not have gone far.
Find him at any cost.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Search thoroughly!
-Yes, sir!
No one is here!
The deposed queen has fled.
Search the area!
Who is there?
Reveal yourself.
How dare you?
You are a rebel
pursued by the palace guards.
How dare you show up here?
If you report me,
I will inform His Majesty
that you have been plotting treason.
His Majesty is in pursuit
of Physician Kwon?
Yes.
Their base in Seochon
was attacked last night,
and they were all arrested.
Prince Uiseong was lucky
to avoid being arrested with them.
Tell him to remain
in his residence for now.
And if you hear any news
about Physician Kwon,
please let me know.
You want my help?
Would it not be safer
for me to withdraw now?
We still have a chance.
I will reveal to the world
what the King did,
which will undermine his authority.
Then the autopsy report
will strengthen the legitimacy
of Grand Prince Yeongwon,
the brother of Crown Prince Taein.
And then?
We will crown a new king.
The new Crown Prince
will be you, as promised.
Is that right?
Can I see that autopsy report?
Physician Kwon.
Are you looking for the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein?
It is definitely inside the palace.
So we have no chance without it, do we?
I will find it no matter what.
All you need to do
is help me sneak into the palace.
Why did you not tell Father?
His Majesty must not know
where this autopsy report is.
That way, he will keep
Physician Kwon alive to find it.
By the way,
how is this in your hands?
I found out who recorded this.
Do you know where the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein is?
No, Your Majesty.
Is that so?
As you are the one who recorded it,
I assumed
you would know where it is.
Why…
are you looking for it, Your Majesty?
The death of the late Crown Prince
seems to resemble
that of Crown Prince Taein greatly.
So I think
the autopsy report
might help me reveal
how the Crown Prince really died.
By the way,
I heard the Queen Dowager
is in search of it as well.
If that autopsy report
was what had kept him alive,
I was certain he would want to check
if it was where he had hidden it.
And
the person who needs this
most desperately right now
is Physician Kwon.
No,
I mean Yi Ik-hyeon.
He has waited 20 years.
He will not give up like this.
Therefore,
when he finds out that I have the report,
I am sure he will come to see me.
It has been a while,
Royal Physician Yoo Sang-uk.
It has been a very long time indeed,
Prince Geumyeong.
If you want to live,
tell me where Yi Ik-hyeon is.
If I were going
to beg you to spare my life,
I would not have started this.
What did you see
during the autopsy that day
that made you do this?
You should know the answer
better than anyone.
You saw everything, did you not?
So please,
tell me what happened that day.
I have only endured all these years
so that I could someday dig out the truth.
So tell me.
Please.
Tell me how you poisoned
-Crown Prince Taein to death!
-Shut your mouth!
Am I the one who killed him?
Fine, I did look the other way.
Knowing my mother was killing him,
I pretended not to know.
But there was nothing I could do anyway.
No.
It is your greed that killed him.
Therefore,
you will never be free from that day
for the rest of your life.
For 20 whole years,
the death of my brother has held me back.
It made me work harder, and I managed
to make a prosperous kingdom!
I did all that to prove
that I deserved the throne.
"Prosperous kingdom"?
You live in anxiety,
surrounded by evil enemies.
Do you call that prosperous?
You deserved the throne?
Will you be able to say that
when it is revealed
that Crown Prince Taein was poisoned?
How do you think
history will remember you?
This is probably
how you will be remembered.
"Prince Geumyeong,
the traitor who usurped the throne."
Find the autopsy report
as soon as Physician Kwon is arrested.
And once you have the autopsy report,
kill him immediately.
Is Physician Kwon still missing?
Yes.
They searched the capital thoroughly,
but they have not found any trace.
Your Majesty.
His Majesty ordered
that Physician Kwon be killed
as soon as he is arrested.
What?
We need his confession to bring
the Grand Heir back to the palace.
We must find him before Father does.
Not just His Majesty.
Once his identity
comes to light,
the Queen Dowager
will try to kill him as well.
You must already know Royal Physician Cho
was poisoned to death by gansu.
I do.
Nothing that happens in the palace
ever gets past me.
In that case,
do you perhaps know
who killed him as well?
It was Physician Kwon.
And he turns out to be
Yi Ik-hyeon.
Yi Ik-hyeon?
Yes.
He is Grand Prince Yeongwon,
the brother of Crown Prince Taein,
who you have kept alive.
How…
How can Physician Kwon be him?
Then who is the man
living with the deposed queen?
He is an imposter.
You have been deceived
by the deposed queen.
Now that Yi Ik-hyeon killed Cho Guk-yeong,
who do you think
will be next?
It will probably be
the person who ordered Cho Guk-yeong
to kill Crown Prince Taein.
Why are you
so obsessed with the death
of Crown Prince Taein?
I need to find out the truth of it
so that I can find out the truth
of the death of my son.
Therefore,
I plan to reveal the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein.
It has already
come into my possession.
Are you out of your mind?
What is it that you want?
I want you to find Physician Kwon
before His Majesty does.
If you do,
I will hand over
the autopsy report to you.
But remember this.
You have to bring him to me alive.
Are you all right, Your Royal Highness?
Bring the man
who has been following
Prince Uiseong around right now.
Your Majesty.
The Crown Princess collapsed.
-The Crown Princess?
-Yes.
Why did she collapse?
Is there something wrong with her?
With all due respect,
I am having trouble checking her pulse.
What do you mean?
Your Majesty.
Her Royal Highness
has a slower pulse than normal.
Thump.
This is the usual speed of my heartbeat.
But whenever I see you…
Thump, thump.
It beats normally.
It means I like you.
She is pregnant.
Did you just say
she is pregnant?
Yes.
The pulse feels smooth
and disperses when pressed.
I am sure she is pregnant.
Congratulations, Your Royal Highness.
Congratulations, Crown Prince.
I feel especially grateful
for this great news
after the unfortunate events
that happened in the palace recently.
Crown Prince.
Leave the matter
regarding your brother to me.
No.
I will continue to assist you.
It would be more helpful if you fulfilled
your duties as the Crown Prince.
I will let you know if I need help.
So focus on looking after
the Crown Princess for now.
She must feel confused
due to the unexpected pregnancy.
It must be even harder for her
because she is unwell.
You should stay by her side
at times like this.
The Crown Princess is pregnant.
Really?
-She is with child?
-Is it certain?
Yes. A royal physician
just checked her pulse.
Oh, my goodness.
This will give
the Crown Prince a foothold.
Exactly. If a son is born,
he will have nothing to worry about.
That is right.
Why does Consort Hwang
want to have tea with us all of a sudden?
I have no idea.
It makes me feel uncomfortable.
Could it be that she has not given up
on making her son the Crown Prince?
The Crown Prince defeated
all his competitors.
It would be shameless of her
if she has not given up.
Goodness gracious.
The Crown Princess is pregnant.
After all the commotion,
I am relieved
the Crown Prince is producing an heir.
Her Majesty must be so relieved.
Should we go and congratulate Her Majesty?
Let us hurry.
You have woken up.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
What are those?
They are paintings that His Majesty sent
for the development of the unborn baby.
An unborn baby?
Is someone pregnant?
You are, Your Royal Highness.
-Me?
-Yes.
You are carrying a child.
How? When?
I guess it was the day
you consummated your marriage
after the nursemaid awoke your instincts.
All you have to do
is provide me with information
about Physician Kwon.
Your Royal Highness.
I am afraid I cannot do that.
It is not under my jurisdiction,
and even if I do know something,
I should not
leak such information personally.
So that was it.
When I heard you called for me,
I thought you wanted to congratulate me
on the pregnancy of the Crown Princess.
Her pregnancy
seems to have changed
your status dramatically as well.
Now that the Crown Prince
has gained a foothold,
I reckon many things will change
from now on.
Your Royal Highness.
If you have nothing else to say,
I will take my leave.
Your Royal Highness.
It seems Physician Kwon is hiding
in the residence of Prince Uiseong.
Is that right?
I will have them arrest him immediately.
No.
If we move rashly, he might flee.
I cannot hand him over
to the Queen so easily.
I will make sure
they suffer before they get killed.
Seeing that you know such a small gate,
you must know your way around the palace.
I used to play with my brothers
near the gate as a child.
Its humble appearance
makes it hard to believe
that it leads to the palace.
Do you have a family?
Yes.
I have an old mother and a son.
What about your wife?
I never got married.
Then who gave birth to your son?
She is with another man now.
Did you love her?
We may have lived
as an ordinary married couple
if we had not met the way we did.
When I ascend the throne,
I will grant you a wish.
Tell me what you want.
There is a house
where I lived with my brothers.
I want to reclaim it for my mother.
And I want to live there with her…
and my son.
That is my wish.
By the way,
when will the rebellion be?
It will take place
when the palace is most peaceful
and His Majesty is off guard.
"The plum blossoms
are bright and radiant."
"They look like waves in the moonlight."
"Adorned with white frost and snow,
the icy flowers…"
His Royal Highness
has always been brusque.
He likes meat.
No,
he likes greens
such as bracken and bean sprouts.
He is more warmhearted
than any of his brothers.
GIVING BIRTH TO SEVEN CHILDREN
THAT TAKE AFTER HIS ROYAL HIGHNESS
Looking around the palace
holding his hand.
Taking a stroll with him.
Eating and chatting with him.
Wishing upon a shooting star with him.
When will His Royal Highness
open his heart to me?
Were you afraid you spent the night
with a woman you do not love?
I also do not want to be with someone
who dislikes me.
Your Majesty.
Since you have your plate full,
leave the Crown Princess to us.
Yes, Your Majesty.
We will take good care of her.
I appreciate the gesture,
but I must decline.
Please do not be like that, Your Majesty.
We would love to do something for you.
She is still in the early stages
of pregnancy.
She needs complete rest.
I know that,
but all the preparations
for pregnancy care are finished.
That is enough.
Since no pregnancy care is better
than physical and mental well-being,
make sure she can rest comfortably.
You should leave her alone.
Yes, Your Majesty.
But I have everything ready.
You broke your promise.
You said you would visit me often.
I am sorry.
I missed you,
Uncle.
What is this?
It is in return for the book.
I appreciate it, Uncle.
But next time,
please bring me Gyeokmongyogyeol.
You should be grateful
that I bring you one.
You are quite particular.
By the way, Uncle,
can I really move back home
when I turn nine?
My mother told me
that I can go back when I turn nine.
Really?
Are you sure?
You have to keep your promise.
I will.
I thought Her Royal Highness was pregnant.
I know.
Why is a pregnant woman running around?
This is not the first time.
I saw her running yesterday too.
Oh, my.
Could it be that
she is pretending to be pregnant?
Announce her arrival.
Now!
Your Majesty, the Queen Dowager is here.
What brings you here?
Rumor has it
that the Crown Princess is not pregnant.
I need to find out the truth.
Your Majesty.
The Crown Prince and Princess are here.
I summoned them here.
She is not pregnant.
What do you mean?
Why has your opinion changed
since your last examination?
With all due respect,
the Crown Princess has an unusual pulse,
and it seems to have led
to a misdiagnosis.
A misdiagnosis?
If what you say is false,
you will not be forgiven.
Your Majesty.
He is only human.
He can, of course, make mistakes.
By the way,
what do you mean,
the Crown Princess has an unusual pulse?
Her heart disease
makes it difficult
to check her pulse properly.
Heart disease?
How could you send your daughter
into the palace
when she was suffering from a disease?
It is true that she suffered
from heart disease as a child.
But the symptoms have improved
and do not affect her daily life anymore.
There is more.
I heard
all the matchmakers
have avoided setting her up.
If she is avoided even outside the palace,
she is certainly not qualified
to be the Crown Princess.
You knew everything
from the beginning, did you not?
During the selection,
you gave her the highest score
knowing all of that.
Was it your plan
to expel her like this
using her flaws as an excuse?
I was also well aware of her reputation.
Due to her free and easy character,
she had a bad reputation
among the matchmakers.
However,
that is exactly what made me
select her as the Crown Princess.
The Queen should be
someone bold and progressive.
Since her disease
seems to be nothing serious,
I will make sure she is treated.
So
I ask you not to raise
any further issues regarding her health.
You do not want me
to raise any further issues?
Heart disease affects fetal movement,
which may lead to a miscarriage.
Do you still say there is no problem?
I will take good care of her.
So
you should stop worrying about it now.
No.
I will inform His Majesty
and have her deposed.
Deposed?
The Crown Prince
is the heir to the throne.
If the Crown Princess
cannot produce healthy offspring,
she does not deserve the position.
Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness.
Are you going this far
to acquire the autopsy report
of Crown Prince Taein?
Yes, that is correct.
Give me the report,
and I will keep the weaknesses
of the Crown Princess secret.
Give it some thought.
Between the autopsy report
and the Crown Princess,
what would you like to protect?
She is definitely pregnant.
If you want to live,
do not tell anyone that she is pregnant.
From now on,
you only have to do as I say.
Every day,
you pass by that place on your way
to your jugang, the daytime lesson.
I wanted to see you even from a distance.
And I could not hold back.
I think that is what started the rumor,
although I turned out
not to be pregnant after all.
I am relieved that you are not.
I heard pregnancy can be dangerous
for a woman with heart disease.
And it can be even worse after birth.
Do not let it concern you.
Nothing is more important
than your health.
Your Royal Highness.
We do not…
need to have a child.
Your Majesty.
The Queen Dowager beseeched His Majesty
to depose the Crown Princess
making an issue of her disease.
What?
This is unexpected.
I thought you would hold on to it
until the end.
I could not lose another Crown Princess.
You should give up now, Your Majesty.
Once Yi Ik-hyeon is dead,
everything will be over.
Do you think…
that is the only record from that day?
Hand over the gajangsacho,
the first draft, to me.
Are you going back on your word?
I only showed it to you
because you promised
not to tell anyone about its existence.
But Lord Park,
if we fail to find Yi Ik-hyeon,
the death of the late Crown Prince
will forever remain a mystery.
Lord Park.
The gajangsacho
is the only record left from that day.
With all due respect,
I cannot give it to you.
For I do not
have it any longer.
What…
do you mean by that?
You should get rid of it.
What did you just say?
I said you should
get rid of that gajangsacho.
If this record comes to light,
the dynasty will falter,
and the palace will be in chaos.
And its consequences
will be borne by the people.
If I get rid of this,
the record from that day
will be lost forever.
It is for the greater good.
So please do not hesitate.
Do you have anything on Physician Kwon?
I apologize.
We are searching by all possible means,
but we have not found any trace of him.
With both the autopsy report and
the gajangsacho gone, what shall we do?
Instead of Physician Kwon,
we should look for the deposed Queen Yoon.
He is a dutiful son.
I am sure he will visit his mother.
Search for Court Lady Jung,
who was expelled from the palace
along with Queen Yoon.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Why has Prince Uiseong
not reported Physician Kwon yet?
He must know
who his real father is.
How could you say something so absurd?
How disrespectful to the royal court.
Did you think your family would be safe
after turning Prince Uiseong,
the son of a lowly physician,
into royal blood?
Consort Hwang and Prince Uiseong
will face death.
Will you be able to prove it?
Nothing is true
unless it can be proven.
Chief State Councilor.
Did you forget
the family of the deposed queen
was accused of treason?
Evidence…
can always be created.
You have done it yourself.
However,
I intend to give you a way out.
Hand over…
Physician Kwon to me.
That is
the only way to save the lives
of Consort Hwang and Prince Uiseong.
We found the deposed Queen Yoon.
Where is Yi Ik-hyeon right now?
Why
should I tell you that?
Because if anyone else finds him first,
he will be killed.
You also
intend to do the same, do you not?
No.
I intend to spare his life.
I cannot find out
how the late Crown Prince died
without his confession.
So tell me.
Where is
Yi Ik-hyeon right now?
I will lure Physician Kwon
to the government offices
by haesi, the twenty-first hour.
Arrest him then, Your Majesty.
Wait here.
Those who will help you
will arrive at haesi.
There is no need to wait.
I can figure it out on my own.
What are you talking about?
What if you miss each other?
Then stay with me until they arrive.
By the way,
you are a mere physician.
So why do you risk your life
for Grand Prince Yeongwon?
What about you?
Why did you kill
the brothers of Crown Prince Taein?
I see people do not change.
Did you really expect me
to join you in that lousy rebellion?
Why did I kill his brothers?
It was to save my own skin. That is all.
Right.
So,
where is Grand Prince Yeongwon now?
If I tell you,
will you spare my life?
I will.
You can tell me.
You still have not found him?
Take one step closer,
and the Chief State Councilor will die.
Step back!
Put down your swords!
I said, step back!
Do you recognize me now?
Grand Prince Yeongwon…
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
You should run.
I will find you a hiding place.
You need to stay alive
to plan for the future.
I will not be able to leave
the palace alive anyway.
This is for taking the lives
of my brothers.
Mother.
The Chief State Councilor
has been murdered
while luring Physician Kwon
on His Majesty's orders.
Where is Physician Kwon now?
The guards are searching the palace,
but he has not been found yet.
He first killed Cho Guk-yeong
and then the Chief State Councilor.
His next target is the Queen Dowager.
In addition to killing my brother,
who was the Crown Prince,
you ordered the Chief State Councilor
to kill all my other brothers.
Following Crown Prince Taein,
my brothers were killed one by one.
I have chased your shadows ever since.
But for once,
I was ahead of you.
It was…
with Prince Uiseong.
I impregnated the concubine of your son
and made him raise my child as his own.
Your favorite grandson is my son!
How do you feel?
This chamber is surrounded.
You will not leave this place alive.
Are you really…
Yi Ik-hyeon?
Yes.
I am.
Did you intend to use me
from the beginning?
Did you ever think of me
as a woman even for a moment?
All I needed
was someone to takran my bloodline.
TAKRAN: TO LAY EGGS
IN THE NEST OF ANOTHER BIRD
It is over, Your Majesty.
Where is
Yi Ik-hyeon right now?
This is the blood
of the Chief State Councilor.
This is the blood of my father?
He should
pay for what he did, should he not?
No.
I do not believe it.
No!
Tell me it is not true.
Yi Ik-hyeon!
I am afraid I must kill you.
That is the only way
for me to live.
No…
I have failed,
but you must…
You must survive no matter what.
I am your father.
No…
You are…
the true heir to the throne.
Do you have a family?
Yes.
I have an old mother and a son.
When I ascend the throne,
I will grant you a wish.
Tell me what you want.
There is a house
where I lived with my brothers.
I want to reclaim it for my mother.
And I want to live there with her…
and my son.
That is my wish.
Yi Ik-hyeon
must have been killed by his son by now.
It is a shame that I could not witness it
with my own eyes.
Grandmother.
Rumor has it
that Physician Kwon coaxed you
into joining him in treason.
Physician Kwon
is Yi Ik-hyeon,
the leader of the rebels.
You still have a chance.
Kill Yi Ik-hyeon
with your own hands.
Only then,
will you be able to hide the fact
that you have been in collusion with him.
UNDER THE QUEEN'S UMBRELLA
You are indebted to me.
You have the gajangsacho.
This will be your last chance
to reveal the truth.
What do you think I should do?
I will sway the Queen
to bend the King's will.
You must cast them out from the palace.
It seems like the Crown Princess
has lost the fetus in her womb.
That is my way of protecting my son!
I will protect my husband in my own way.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim