UNDER THE QUEEN'S UMBRELLA
EPISODE 2
I hope I did not make you uncomfortable
by visiting you at this ungodly hour.
There is nothing
I enjoy more in this palace
than the conversations I have with you.
Please, feel free to visit me anytime.
You are indeed thoughtful,
but I have wronged you and your father.
During the Three-Step Selection,
you were the most favored candidate.
However, the late King, who wished
to keep his maternal relatives in check,
insisted on selecting a candidate
from a family with no roots.
As a result, you ended up
being a concubine.
Had you become the Queen
as you should have,
the status of Prince Uiseong would have
been very different than now.
It is all in the past.
"All in the past"?
To the east of the palace,
there is a large tree
that I have been especially fond of.
It used to look magnificent
and provided a pleasant shade.
It could not have been more perfect.
But one day,
the roots of the tree
began to rot and dry out.
It has become so fragile now
that even a gentle breeze
could make it fall.
What do you suggest I do?
It should be pulled out
if that is indeed the state it is in…
because it takes hundreds
of years for a new tree to take root.
By the way, you do not seem
to be interested in the cohort selection.
I do not think
the position suits Prince Uiseong.
Then…
what about the position
of the Crown Prince?
Hyeolheogwol…
I heard the late Crown Prince Taein
suffered from the same disease.
Was it the disease
that caused him to pass in the end?
That is what everyone says,
but I do not believe
that it was hyeolheogwol
that caused his death.
The royal physician even told us
that Prince Taein
had been cured of his disease.
Do you mean…
that there was something else
that caused him to pass on?
Is that you, Ik-hyeon?
It was as though they had foreseen
the death of the Crown Prince.
The current King was proclaimed
as the new Crown Prince,
my father was accused of treason,
and I was deposed.
It all happened rapidly in succession.
I would like to ask you this.
To my knowledge,
you had four other children.
Should not one of your other sons
have succeeded the Crown Prince?
Then let me ask you this in return.
Have you ever prepared
the other Grand Princes for kingship
apart from providing them
with the most basic education?
I have not.
Of course, you have not.
Such behavior may have made
the other Grand Princes
a threat to the Crown Prince.
That is what sets your sons
apart from those of the concubines.
And you must have done that
to protect your other sons.
However, the concubines have been
eagerly waiting and preparing
for the taekhyeon.
Do you mean the process
by which the wisest and worthiest
of the remaining princes
is chosen as the new Crown Prince?
Yes.
You are right.
Being polite, generous, loyal, agile,
and showing mercy willingly
are the five virtues
that lead one to a state of grace.
When none of the sons of the Queen
are worthy as the successor
or all of them do not qualify to rule…
One would be entrusted with more work
-…that system of taekhyeon
-and thus, achieve great things.
may justify the inauguration of a son
of a concubine as the new Crown Prince,
just as His Majesty
came to inherit the throne.
A wise man rises skyward
to reach truth and morality each day.
He is not concerned with
being acknowledged undeservedly
but strives to improve himself
in order to earn recognition.
OUTSTANDING
Congratulations, First Junior Consort Cho.
This is only the beginning.
Indeed. Now that we have someone
to succeed the title of Crown Prince,
it is time to expel
the Queen and the Grand Princes.
For it is you, Your Highness,
who should be Queen.
Therefore, you must prepare yourself.
If you fail to do so,
you risk not only losing the Crown Prince
but also the lives
of the other Grand Princes.
I, too…
did not understand this
until it was too late.
No matter how quietly we lived,
the mere existence of my sons
was deemed a threat
by those in power.
And just like that…
I ended up losing
the remaining Grand Princes
even though we had not been living
with any desire to reclaim the throne.
The only reason I am still living…
is because I still have
one son remaining
that I must protect.
You asked me
what I would have done
if I were to turn back time.
Although…
people may point their fingers at me
and ridicule me for being crude,
cunning, and shameless,
I would do anything necessary
to protect my children
if I was still the Queen
and still had the opportunity
to change the course of things.
Your Highness.
Why do you not inform His Majesty
of the condition of the Crown Prince?
Would he not be upset
if he were to find out later?
The more upset
His Majesty becomes, the better.
Pardon?
Nothing is more enraging than
something that happens unannounced.
So it has to be the Queen
who kept the condition of the Crown Prince
a secret from His Majesty.
Things will become interesting
starting tomorrow.
Wake up.
It is still the fourth hour.
"Between the third hour and the seventh,
the liver, bowels, and gallbladder become
active and stimulate the brain."
That is what is written here.
What book is that?
A book that holds the secrets
of the education of the royal family.
It was through these methods
that His Majesty ascended the throne.
Why do you think
the Queen Dowager gave this book to me?
It must be proof
that she recognizes your brilliance.
I have also learned a way to wash
our faces that makes us more intelligent.
We will begin washing our faces
using jisikbeop starting today.
JISIKBEOP:
A BRAIN DEVELOPMENT BREATHING METHOD
IN WHICH ONE HOLDS THEIR BREATH
IN SALT WATER FOR OVER 150 SECONDS
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven…
Mastering jisikbeop
enhances your concentration and patience.
Nine. Keep going. Ten.
Good job. You are doing well.
Twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four…
You can stop if you have to breathe.
Well done. We will go and have some meat.
You are not done yet.
I cannot hold my breath any longer.
The water is too salty.
And what if it is?
This will help improve
your inventiveness and creativity.
Even the Crown Prince
practices this each morning.
That is because he is the Crown Prince.
Why must I--
This is the 65th time.
The King ends his meal
with water that has been
boiled one hundred times.
It takes a lot of effort
but is said to extend one's lifespan.
The water must cool completely
before it is boiled again.
Only then will it be effective.
Partake in the cohort selection.
Do you not want to
put your abilities to the test?
What do you mean by that?
It is a chance for you
to prove yourself before His Majesty.
Just as you said,
the first son of His Majesty
is you.
Just enter the test
and leave the rest to me.
MULGWIWONJU: RESTORATION OF AN ITEM
TO ITS RIGHTFUL OWNER
I will return to you
what is rightfully yours.
From now on,
you may do away
with formalities in my presence.
Even when I enter
the room or stand beside you,
do not mind me
and focus on treating the Crown Prince.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
You may leave for now.
Physician Kwon.
I want you to search
the records of Naeuiwon, the Royal Clinic.
There should be records
of the treatment of Crown Prince Taein.
And find any other records
on the treatment of hyeolheogwol,
but do so discreetly.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Crown Prince.
His pulse seems to have recovered.
Your Highness.
You have yet to fully recover
so you should not strain yourself.
Crown Prince.
You should lay in bed
a little longer. It is still early.
Mother.
I am sorry to have worried you.
Why did you not tell me
of your illness and make things worse?
Were you afraid
that I would scold you for being ill?
As this illness could remind us
of an unpleasant past,
I hesitated to tell you
as I may have caused you grave worry.
Crown Prince.
With treatment, you will recover
and be able to return to your daily life.
So do not worry too much.
I will push them to do it.
Your Majesty.
-That may make things go awry.
-Why?
If you do so,
you might be met with resistance.
If more Grand Princes enter,
there will be a better chance
that one of them becomes the cohort.
I advise you to
persuade them, not force them.
-Persuade them?
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Please, refrain from
yelling at them and speak softly.
We will see.
I wonder why Mother
summoned us so urgently.
Why else?
She is not one to let such things slide.
Do you think this is about
the incident with Prince Uiseong?
What else could it be?
Do not be so pessimistic.
I am not being pessimistic.
I am being realistic.
Brother!
Are you on your way to the lesson?
Where are you going?
We are on our way
to being scolded by Mother.
Beg for forgiveness.
-Will do!
What could the Grand Prince Gyeseong
be so busy with these days?
You seem to be away all the time.
Hold on.
You are not hiding a girl
in the palace, are you?
Is she pretty?
Grand Prince Gyeseong.
Yes, Mother.
I heard that you are very interested
in learning foreign languages.
Which language
are you the most interested in?
I am interested in Chinese.
-Chinese?
-Yes.
I see.
Grand Prince Ilyeong.
You seem to be interested in
astronomy and divination.
Pardon?
Well, yes.
-Mother.
-Yes?
You are making us uncomfortable.
Please, scold us and be done with it.
You are making me extremely anxious.
Scold you? What is this about?
I was just planning to converse
with the Grand Princes
to learn what your interests are.
-Why all of a sudden?
-Seriously…
What do you mean? I just told you.
I would like to know
what your interests are.
Have you let the news
of the cohort selection get to your head
as it did the concubines?
Watch your mouth!
"Get to my head"?
Everyone is making such a fuss
to become a cohort so they can
join our brother at Sigangwon.
Well, I…
This is not about that.
You still must be curious.
Yes, I am.
And what will you do?
Are you partaking in it or not?
Tell me.
Never mind.
I order every one of you to partake.
Your Majesty…
Mother, did you not hear the announcement?
I did.
They said that we need to
partake in it of our own will.
PATIENCE
-I know that.
-Mother.
I have no intention of partaking.
Why not?
The evaluation process looks difficult,
so I do not want to.
-And what about you?
-Mother.
I am busy developing
a portable sundial these days.
I do not think I can make time
to enter the cohort selection.
What?
-You brats!
-I will enter.
If it has to be one of us,
I will gladly do so.
Yes, Grand Prince Gyeseong.
That is a great idea.
LEFT
The rest of you should reconsider.
Why should we?
Really? Give it some thought then!
Although I scold you
whenever you cause trouble,
have I ever nagged you to study?
THEY HAVE NOTHING TO SAY
But you see, even if you get married,
you should at least leave the palace
with some basic education.
Then allow me to get married
so that I may leave the palace.
Mother, I would like to get married too.
You good-for-nothings,
you bring His Majesty shame.
Mischief-makers who are all but a stain
on the history of the royal family.
Do you know who this is referring to?
It is what the people of the palace
whisper about the lot of you.
Are you not ashamed?
You seem to be very ashamed
of us good-for-nothing mischief-makers.
That is not the point.
I am suggesting that you restore
your tarnished reputation.
I am sorry.
We seemed to have missed the point again.
But what can we do?
We are all but a stain.
If the Crown Prince
fails to overcome this crisis,
the lives of the Grand Princes
will be endangered just for being my sons.
How could they be so oblivious?
Why not tell them about
the condition of the Crown Prince?
They are emotional and affectionate.
Even if I ask them to be discreet,
they will visit the quarters of the
Crown Prince day and night out of worry
and end up revealing his condition.
For now,
the best course of action
would be to keep myself focused
on tutoring the Grand Prince
who shows the most promise.
Your Majesty.
Why not ask Lord Min Seung-yun
for an objective evaluation
of all the Grand Princes?
Ask him directly?
Yes. There may be a Grand Prince
who might be much more capable
than we are led to believe.
We should speak with Lord Min first
and then try to have as many of them
as we can partake in the selection.
You are right.
I will use the cohort selection
as an excuse
to get as many of them
as I can to read books.
Your Majesty, you already had one today.
Your Majesty, please wait for me.
It must be the herbal medicine
that has made her so speedy.
Your Majesty, please.
Do you see that?
She is without any grace and dignity.
One might even mistake her
for a martial arts master.
She must be the fastest in the palace.
And she is supposed to be the Queen?
What a disgrace.
Prince Uiseong.
Did I not say
that I might end up killing you
if you spoke such nonsense
like that again?
Go ahead and hit me then.
Those fools may not be able to hear me,
but they will surely
see you take a swing at me.
You should not call
the servants of the court such names.
Who cares? They are just
lowly servants who work under us.
Go ahead and hit me.
I would love to see if the Queen's
martial arts training has paid off.
She is the Mother of the Kingdom.
Treat her with respect
both in and out of her presence.
Grand Prince Seongnam.
You know what?
The title of Crown Prince
should have been mine, not your brother's.
You should stop before you regret it.
If I ever end up inheriting the throne,
I will not keep the likes of you alive,
even as peasants.
I would have you all killed.
Listen carefully.
The throne will be my brother's.
If a bastard like you becomes the King,
I will see to it personally
that your kingdom lies in ruins.
What…
did you just say?
Excuse my bluntness,
but none of them
have a chance at becoming a cohort.
It is not that they lack intelligence.
It is just that they are mostly
lacking in determination.
If the Office of Royal Genealogy hears
that a prince has neglected his studies,
their name is then passed on to
His Majesty at the end of the season
and that prince will be classified
as a delinquent and punished.
All the Grand Princes are in danger
of being classified as delinquents.
But especially
Grand Princes Seongnam and Gyeseong.
If they miss a few more lessons,
they will end up delinquents
due to their truancy
and be expelled from Jonghak.
Hold on a second.
I can see how
Grand Prince Seongnam might be at risk,
but Grand Prince Gyeseong too?
Delinquents?
This must be a misunderstanding.
I have checked many times.
It is Grand Prince Gyeseong.
What will happen if he is expelled
from Jonghak as a delinquent?
It will end up proving
how unfit he is for kingship.
But is he not the Grand Prince
that you count on the most?
He still is.
We know nothing for certain just yet.
He has not been classified as one yet.
It is a possibility that he might.
I doubt he will ever end up
causing any serious trouble.
Your Majesty.
Is that not Grand Prince Gyeseong
over there?
Where on earth did he go?
Your Majesty.
I looked everywhere for you.
I thought you had
run somewhere far off to hide.
But I find you hiding here again
as you always have.
No matter how hard I search,
there is no place in this palace…
where I can cry out loud.
Did you cry to your heart's content?
A little.
Did you see that?
Yes.
So I was not seeing things.
What do I do now?
If someone else finds out,
that will be the end
of Grand Prince Gyeseong.
What should I do?
Your Majesty.
You should stop telling me your secrets.
But who else would I tell such things?
I had no one to turn to when I entered
the palace at such a young age.
I do not care if you serve
the Queen Dowager or anyone else.
You are the only person that I have.
What…
What am I to do now?
What will I do…
with my dear Hwan?
Do you wish to partake?
Master.
I did not come here for the fear
of being scolded by Mother.
But I am standing
at a crossroads right now.
I am asking you this in an attempt
to protect my honor as a Grand Prince.
Must you really
reveal the results of the exam?
I shall ask.
Then I would like to partake
in the cohort selection.
GRAND PRINCE MUAN
PRINCE BOGEOM
PRINCE UISEONG
PRINCE SIMSO
PRINCE YEONGMIN
PRINCE HODONG
No.
I do not have time to waste.
The cohort selection will begin soon.
I should go and check on
Grand Prince Gyeseong.
Your Majesty.
Do you intend to have him
partake in the exam?
What do you expect me to do?
I cannot just give up on him
just because I now know everything.
He is the only Grand Prince
who volunteered,
so how could I give up on him?
Perhaps the other Grand Princes
will apply as well.
Then I would be ever so grateful.
But did you not see that day?
When I brought it up with them,
they asked to be married
so they may leave the palace.
Give it some thought then!
Although I scold you
whenever you cause trouble,
have I ever nagged you to study?
GRAND PRINCE SEONGNAM
Have you completed the list?
Almost.
I will deliver it to His Majesty
as soon as you are done.
There is still half an hour left,
so why not take a seat while you wait?
If anyone has not submitted
their nameplates by now,
they surely do not intend to partake.
We must still abide by the rules.
I shall hand over the list
in half an hour.
I see. Yes.
As you wish.
Your Highness.
The Crown Prince wishes to see you.
Right now?
-Over here!
-Where are you?
-Where?
Where are you?
He has grown so big.
I hear he is already
in the Office of Early Education.
-He is giving his master a handful.
-Where are you?
-Over here!
-There you are!
He has no problems
understanding his tutor…
-Over here!
-…but never does as he is told.
Here!
-Where are you?
-Look how full of life he is.
He seems to take more after you than me.
Kang.
Do you remember our days in Seochon?
There was nothing I enjoyed more
than visiting you there.
I do miss those days sometimes.
When you returned
to the palace from Seochon,
I was happy as it felt like my younger
brothers had gotten a new older brother.
I was relieved
to know that you would have their backs
even when I am gone.
Could I ask you to do
the same for my son too?
Make sure he works hard
on the things he needs to do
and that he is not tempted
by the things he should keep away from.
Scold him if he drinks
or causes any trouble.
I want you to be like a father to him
as well as a friend.
Why do you say such things
as if you will be going away somewhere?
Will you keep me company as my cohort?
I miss the time we spent
in Seochon together.
Who are you?
Who said you could enter my house?
I am your brother.
Says who?
I do.
Brother. Are you good at fighting?
Brother, it is them!
-What do you want?
-I have a brother too!
Whatever.
You are dead meat.
My brother is an excellent fighter.
Come on, Brother.
You said you were good at fighting.
But why is your nose still bleeding?
You lose if you bleed from the nose.
It is okay.
We will land at least one punch
the next time we fight.
Take that!
I could not have been happier
when you returned
to the palace to live with us.
Well, it is time. Please hand me the list.
Master, am I too late?
Applications are still open.
Then I would like to apply.
GRAND PRINCE SEONGNAM
I knew you would come.
Your Majesty.
All of the Grand Princes have applied.
What?
All of the Grand Princes?
-All of them?
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Even Grand Princes Seongnam and Muan?
Yes. All of them have applied
to partake in the cohort selection.
My goodness.
How could they surprise
their mother like this?
Court Lady Shin.
Let us begin the preparations.
Your Majesty.
This is great news.
-It is indeed.
-I am so relieved.
I did not expect such great interest
in the cohort selection.
Is there a reason you wish to select
the new cohort through an examination?
The Crown Prince is bright in academics,
but he is much too upright.
I want him to twist, turn, and break
outside the box from time to time.
Therefore, I intend to select
a prince whose perspective
differs much from the Crown Prince.
I am your arithmetic tutor, Park Chi-un.
He was not satisfied
with his previous arithmetic tutor,
so I have brought someone new.
Is he qualified?
He came in first place
in the arithmetic examination.
He is second to none
when it comes to arithmetic.
Prince Uiseong
must make a strong impression
in the first two exams.
You can rest assured.
The literary exams will be only on
Jungyong and Seogyeong,
and I will teach him
only the lines that he will be tested on.
You must memorize everything up to here.
In Jungyong, you must make sure
to study Chapter 21,
"On Enlightenment Through Sincerity."
I have brought
all the textbooks used at Jonghak
and Sigangwon as you ordered.
I see. Well done.
Your Majesty.
Do you intend to read all these books?
I will not be able to
help the Grand Princes
unless I know what they will be tested on.
If you are asked how one should
go about putting men in office,
what would your answer be?
May we take a break?
I did not arrange
a private lesson with the top student
from Sungkyunkwan,
the Royal Confucian Academy,
just so that he could watch you doze off.
Mother, may I…
May I take a quick nap before we continue?
Do you know how much
this lesson costs per hour?
You have no idea how much it cost me
to convince him to come and tutor you.
Learn as much from him as you can
so that we get our money's worth.
I will.
You may continue.
In such a case, I should quote
Zi Lu's chapter of Noneo.
"The Master said, 'Raise to office
those whom you know--'"
Mother. My nose…
Please, continue.
Yes.
"He went on to say, 'As to those
whom you do not know,
will others neglect them?'"
EXPECTED QUESTIONS
Your Majesty, it is getting late.
Let me just finish this.
One would think you are the one
taking the examination.
The concubines even hired scribes
and private tutors to aid their sons.
-They did?
-Yes.
As the Queen,
I cannot stoop so low as to bring
learned academics as tutors.
What other option do I have
but to resort to gajeonggyohak?
GAJEONGGYOHAK: MODERN-DAY HOMESCHOOLING
Since you take herbal medicine
whenever you are under stress,
I am sure it will make you even healthier.
I need to stay strong.
Who else will protect my sons, if not me?
But you should not take
more than two pills a day.
We will see.
Court Lady Shin.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Do you know how
I came to be selected as the Queen?
You do not dare say it, do you?
I know. I have heard
the servants of the court gossip.
They say the late King selected me,
a woman of humble birth,
to keep his maternal relatives in check.
But I will tell you what.
That was not it.
It was because my abilities surpassed
all the other candidates.
If I lose…
I cannot sleep.
I will see you again next time.
Yes, Your Highness.
Hurry and leave before someone sees you.
-You startled me.
-Pardon me, Your Highness.
Did you look into it?
-Did you find out anything?
-Yes.
Grand Prince Gyeseong has been secretly
going somewhere as you expected.
Is that right?
Although she pretends not to care,
I know that Her Majesty
would not be standing by idly.
Could she have hired a scribe?
I have not found out that much yet.
Then what is it that you found out?
I know where the Grand Prince
goes and at what time.
I see.
I wonder who this scribe that Her Majesty
has gone so far as to hire is.
How can there be no medical records left?
The only record I could find regarding
Crown Prince Taein was a single line
stating that His Majesty passed
from hyeolheogwol.
It was the Crown Prince who died.
How can there be no other
records regarding this death?
All the records were lost in a fire
that swept the Royal Clinic.
A fire?
There still must be someone
who remembers what happened.
I asked around,
but no one seemed
to remember what happened.
What do you mean?
Some died in the fire,
and the surviving physicians
all left the palace afterward.
Then there is not a single physician
in the palace who knows what happened
except for Royal Physician Cho Guk-yeong?
Yes, Your Majesty.
The fire alone is enough
to raise suspicion,
so how is it that no physician
from then is still at the palace?
-How does that make sense?
-Your Majesty.
That is all I could learn.
Then who was the physician
who treated Crown Prince Taein?
It was Lord Yoo Sang-uk.
Yoo Sang-uk?
Court Lady Oh, ask around
about the whereabouts of Yoo Sang-uk.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It will not be easy to find him.
He is said to be missing.
His relatives and acquaintances
must know something.
-Hurry.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Summon the Grand Princes.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Mother, what are all these books?
These are the books you will be studying.
Do not be startled.
I picked out the questions
that are likely to be on the exam,
so focus on them for now.
Who picked these questions out?
I did.
-No way.
Do you not believe me?
It is not that we do not believe you,
but it is just that it is hard to believe.
I had students at Sungkyunkwan review it,
so begin studying them first.
I will also bring you more questions later
that may not have been covered here.
Mother.
Have you always been
this passionate about our education?
Of course. I have always been competitive.
All right. The exam is in two days.
I just want one of you to become
the cohort of the Crown Prince.
I see.
As you well know, Mother,
it will be fine as long as
he manages to keep up.
I will not repeat myself,
so listen carefully.
Focus.
There are five grades
that you can receive in this exam.
"Tong" means you did an exceptional job.
"Yak" means you did okay,
"Jo" means you need to do better,
and "bul" means that you failed.
Lastly, there is "bangoe,"
meaning you do not deserve
to be graded at all.
-It is the worst grade then.
-Exactly.
You never used to care
even if we got bad grades.
There is nothing good
about being a prince.
It just ends up tying you down.
You cannot always get what you want.
At least not while you are in the palace.
Mother.
Must one of us really go on
to become the cohort of the Crown Prince?
You must prepare yourself.
If you fail to do so,
you risk not only losing the Crown Prince
but also the lives
of the other Grand Princes.
Yes.
Is there a problem?
Mother.
We are terrible students.
We are the worst students at Jonghak.
So you should let go of false hopes
and be content
that we even applied
for the cohort selection.
-That way, you will be able to--
-Have you ever tried?
You can worry about that after you try!
And while we are on the subject,
you will also have to keep up
with your studies at Jonghak from now on.
You have changed.
What has gotten into you?
I do not want to lose.
Even mere concubines are actively involved
in their children's education at Jonghak.
I also have my pride to protect.
I…
am the Queen!
Also…
you will all leave the palace
once you get married.
Mother.
Then does that mean
we will be married sooner
if we do as you say?
Yes.
So before you leave the palace,
feel free to make your mother proud.
You never know…
what will happen in the palace.
Therefore,
I would like to be able to…
lay my hopes on you.
So please…
be on your best behavior
while you are still in the palace.
I am fine with all of this,
but I fear that you may hurt the other
Grand Princes by giving them false hope.
It may be more meaningful
to accept things as they are
and live to the best of one's abilities.
I am not giving them false hope.
I cannot let you know why just yet,
but this is a decision I made…
to protect all of you.
The Crown Prince has just
finished his jugang.
JUGANG: DAYTIME LESSON AT SIGANGWON
Will he be fine to continue
with his schedule?
Yes, Your Majesty.
He did not seem ill at all.
You can stop watching him
at Sigangwon for the time being.
We cannot let the others notice
I am keeping watch over him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I hope the Grand Princes
do well on their first exam.
How is Grand Prince Gyeseong doing?
I saw him head to his quarters.
What do you mean?
You should have kept watch
until you saw him go in.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I should go and check his quarters.
I cannot believe Her Majesty.
She always told us to be calm
while keeping up appearances,
but she even found a place
for her son to study in secret.
UNDER THE QUEEN'S UMBRELLA
Rumors are covered by rumors.
It might not simply end
with a cohort selection.
They are starting.
Are you confident
in making him the cohort?
It is time I face the true side
of Grand Prince Gyeseong.
What an unexpected change.
He must have been so scared.
I have done it once.
Who is to say I cannot do it again?
Starting from tomorrow,
the real battle begins.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim