♪If the world is ready♪
♪What can I do when it gives me a hard time?♪
♪Instead of hiding♪
♪I'll embrace the change♪
♪Thousands of falls♪
♪Will teach me how to jump♪
♪Thousands of burns♪
♪Will make the best fireworks ever♪
♪If I'm going to land♪
♪I need to have the guts to fly♪
♪So what if I hibernated?♪
♪Passion will give me the light♪
♪And the volume♪
♪To shout to the world♪
♪Don't hesitate♪
♪Run and run and run♪
♪I'm flying through the air♪
♪Don't be afraid♪
♪Jump and jump and jump♪
♪To feel the joy of weightlessness♪
♪There's resistance in the headwind♪
♪It's a favor from fate♪
♪At the end, a miracle will♪
♪Stand by me forever♪
♪Forever♪
[Ski into Love]
[Adapted from Jinjiang Literature City's novel "Ski into Love" by Qing Mei]
[Episode 23]
[Shan Chong]
[You're the best, Shan Chong]
Hello, everyone.
You're now watching
the 2025-2026
Snowboard World Cup
Men's Big Air
Final.
This year,
two Chinese athletes,
Shan Chong and Dai Duo,
are competing in this World Cup.
The competition consists of three rounds,
with the final score
being the sum
of the two highest-scoring runs.
Based
on the scores from the first two runs,
Russia's
John Huston
currently holds the first place,
followed by China's Shan Chong
in second.
Now, it's time for the third
and final round,
[BIG AIR WORLD CUP]
which will decide the champion.
Alright, the rider is on the move
in a regular stance.
He's approaching the jump.
Takeoff!
Not bad.
Backside 1440.
Weddle Grab.
Smooth landing.
An 1440 means
four full rotations.
Judging by performances
so far in this World Cup,
this trick isn't
considered particularly difficult.
It falls into the mid-to-lower difficulty range,
so it won't receive
a very high base score from the judges.
Keep your rhythm in this run.
You've got this.
His final score may not be too high.
Now,
let's look
at the replay.
Rider No. 2,
Dai Duo,
please get ready.
Let's go.
Good luck.
Good luck, John.
Control
your arms on the spin.
- Dai Duo is... - Stay balanced on the landing.
- stepping out of the lounge. - You've got this!
His face
still carries a trace of youthful innocence.
His teammate, Shan Chong, gives him a pep talk.
Dai Duo earned his spot in this competition
through the National Snowboard
Big Air Championship.
He's a rising star with great potential.
This is his first time
competing in a World Cup...
Kiddo,
nail this run.
I'll see you
at the podium.
If he can keep his cool...
See you at the podium!
He has a strong shot
at securing third place.
Best of luck to him!
Go for it, you little rascal.
How will Dai Duo
perform?
Let's find out!
Start is ready.
TV is ready.
Rider is ready.
And judges are ready.
Go, Dai Duo!
- Go, Dai Duo! - Go, Dai Duo!
There he goes!
[Dangerous stunts. Do not attempt]
He starts in a regular stance,
looking confident.
He's building speed.
And he's getting faster!
What trick will he go for?
He's approaching the jump.
Takeoff!
Good amplitude!
Very nice.
[Dangerous stunts. Do not attempt]
Weddle Grab.
He went for a Weddle Grab!
Landing!
Backside 1620!
Beautiful!
A flawless execution!
Kid,
you nailed it!
No mistakes!
He did it!
Even with his ranking
nearly secured,
he still went for a high-difficulty trick,
pushing his own limits!
The riders at the top are fired up too,
shaking off all the competition stress!
The judges are now scoring his run.
He's going to be in the top three, right?
Definitely!
Dai Duo!
What score will he get?
Alright, 82.25!
He's secured the bronze medal!
Nice!
Congratulations to Dai Duo!
Amazing!
Now, let's look at the replay.
Backside takeoff.
Weddle Grab.
What a
solid grip!
Great airtime, too. Landing!
No mistakes on that 1620.
A perfect execution!
Honey, come.
Come watch.
I rushed over straight
from the class reunion party.
I didn't even finish my meal.
- The crucial moment is coming. - China's Shan Chong...
Where's the competition at now?
Once this foreigner finishes his run,
it'll be Chong's turn.
He currently ranks No.1 in the FIS standings.
Based on the scores from the first two runs,
this round
will be a head-to-head battle for gold.
Alright, John is ready to go.
Regular stance.
He's approaching the jump.
Great amplitude!
Backside rotation.
Stalefish Grab.
An 1800! He nailed it!
He's good.
It was flawless!
Now, the pressure...
That...
- That was a high-difficulty trick. - Shifts to Shan Chong.
Is that foreigner really that good?
Why did the guy
say the pressure is now on Shan Chong?
Didn't you hear the commentary?
The foreigner
pulled off a high-difficulty trick.
There were so many spins in the air.
Shan Chong
has to land an even harder trick
to take the lead.
Right now, John's score is higher.
Got it?
Pay attention.
Well, I don't know the rules.
Shush.
A seamless execution!
Let's see
how the judges score John's flawless run...
Honey, I was wrong!
I'm sorry.
I got a little carried away.
Oh no.
An 1800
is already insanely hard,
and he did a flat spin.
Is Chong getting silver?
Well, that's okay.
As long as he gives it his all,
he won't have any regrets.
But he doesn't want second place.
I believe in him.
Are you sure about this trick?
You know how difficult
it is, right?
I do.
Throughout the competition,
Shan Chong has been a rock
for his teammate, offering unwavering support.
Coach,
I fought my way back
to the national team
for this moment.
I want that gold.
I want to represent China
at the Winter Olympics.
Alright.
I believe in you.
Go for it!
Rider No. 28, Shan Chong, please get ready.
Alright, folks.
Up next is the rider
we've all been waiting for:
China's very own Shan Chong.
Master!
You've got this!
He first stepped onto a snowboard at 3 years old
and joined the national team at 18.
After injuries forced him into retirement,
he fought his way back with unwavering determination
and record-breaking performances.
In the snowboarding world, there's a famous saying:
"Just put in the work.
Time will take care
of the rest."
This is
Shan Chong's
final run.
Can he handle
the immense pressure John laid down...?
Do your best.
What
high-difficulty trick
will Shan Chong and his coaching team go for?
Let's see what he brings to the table.
Go, Shan Chong!
[Hualing Junior Team Training Base]
From today on,
snowboarding is no longer
just your dream.
I like it!
Do you love it?
I love it!
It becomes your career.
Next time, I'll go for the gold.
It becomes your responsibility.
Master,
if you had the chance,
would you return to Big Air?
I dream about it every night.
He may be a king in hibernation,
but I believe
that one day, he'll wake up
and reclaim his throne.
[2025-2026 Snowboard & Freeski]
[Big Air World Cup Countdown]
Are you ready?
Yes.
[Shan Chong]
I never believed
that just doing my best
would leave me with no regrets.
I have to go
beyond my best.
Only then can I claim the glory that belongs to me.
He's off!
[Dangerous stunts. Do not attempt]
Shan Chong
is riding in a regular stance.
He's moving fast!
He needs a high-difficulty trick
to surpass John.
He looks
determined.
He's still accelerating.
He's approaching the jump.
Takeoff!
It's a frontside rotation!
Incredible, Chong!
Beautiful, Shan Chong!
Absolutely beautiful!
Frontside double cork 1800!
Indy Grab!
I've got goosebumps
all over!
Smooth, effortless, and stylish,
he nailed it!
From takeoff
to landing,
every part of this jump
was flawless.
And looking
at his landing,
it was even cleaner
than John's.
Just now, we clearly saw
he landed
between the second and third blue lines.
That means his air time was longer,
much longer.
He did it!
Master!
Look, Shan Chong did it!
A perfectly executed trick!
Now we wait.
What score
will the judges give?
As of now, based on the standings,
Dai Duo
has officially secured third place.
Now,
all eyes are
on Shan Chong's score.
That was insane!
Absolutely incredible!
No matter what,
you did it.
Let's give a huge round of applause
to all the athletes
for bringing us this Big Air spectacle!
Shan Chong,
the king, has returned!
You did it.
Hard work has paid off.
Effort has paid off.
Time has paid off!
Alright, the results are in!
In this World Cup,
Shan Chong
takes first place with a total score
of 184.50!
His third jump alone
scored
a staggering 95.25 points,
the highest score of the event!
Adding that to his first jump's 89.5 points
for a backside trick,
he surpasses John's 179.25
with a total score of 184.50
to claim victory in the Men's Snowboard Big Air
World Cup!
Congratulations to Shan Chong.
He's officially
punched his ticket to Milan!
♪Thousands of burns♪
♪Will make the best fireworks ever♪
♪If I'm going to land♪
♪I need to have the guts to fly♪
♪So what if I hibernated?♪
[2025-2026 Snowboard & Freeski Big Air World Cup]
♪And the volume...♪
Thank you.
♪A miracle will♪
♪Stand by me♪
♪Tomorrow will♪
♪Don't talk about giving up♪
♪Just talk about bravery♪
♪Don't hesitate...♪
Dai Duo!
You're the best!
Shan Chong!
Chong, I came here to see you!
Thank you for making my dream come true!
Both of them are my students!
Congrats.
What did I say back then?
You said
we'd stand on the world stage together,
representing China.
And win together.
And win together!
[One month later]
What did Mom say?
What do you mean, Mom?
That's my mom.
You're not trying to steal my mom, are you?
I wouldn't dare.
What are you thinking about?
I just can't believe your mom
accepted me
so easily.
Even now,
it still feels like a dream.
That's because
my mom loves me.
And?
And...
And because you're amazing.
And?
And...
And because you love me.
And?
And because I love you.
Hello, Chong. Where are you?
Just got to the lobby.
Hurry up.
I'm upstairs, waiting
by the elevator.
We're in the elevator now.
Okay. Got it.
Long time no see.
Yan.
Jiang!
Zhi!
You're here too?
Long time no see.
I've missed you.
Me too!
Really?
But I feel like
you're too in love
to even notice me.
That's not true.
You're always my number one.
I missed you.
Hey, Yan.
By the way,
where are Beici and the others?
They're on the slopes.
Then why are you here?
To wait for you guys.
Hello?
Look ahead.
Where?
Look ahead, you idiot.
Over here.
Why are you standing there?
Get over here.
Nope.
You come to me.
Looks like someone needs a lesson.
Let's go.
Alright.
Why did you make me
come over?
Shan!
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
Wouldn't that ruin the surprise?
Didn't you say you wouldn't come
until you finished those chapters?
Oh, Zhi, you have no idea.
I pulled three all-nighters so I could
come snowboarding with you guys!
That figures.
I'm so happy
we can all be together.
This is amazing!
Oh right, Zhi,
I want
to talk to you
about the comic...
Alright, enough.
Let's check in first.
Alright.
Let's talk later.
Let's go.
Are you up to something?
I have a question for you.
What kind of proposals
do girls
usually like?
Are you getting married?
Keep it down.
I knew it!
When's the wedding?
It's a proposal,
okay?
She has to
say yes first.
This is wonderful!
You're finally getting married!
Zhi is going to be
my master's wife!
Like I said,
she has to
say yes to my proposal
first.
Right...
You're right.
You're asking the right person,
though I've never been proposed to before.
But trust me,
for a girl,
the proposal matters even more than the wedding.
Because when you
take out the ring
and ask her to marry you,
that's the moment
she truly believes you mean it.
A proposal
should be a surprise.
It needs three things:
the perfect ring, roses,
and your sincerity.
One more thing.
- Whatever you do, don't... - Master, Huayan!
Keep it a secret.
Don't let him find out!
Look, I bought all this food.
Let's eat together.
- Sure. - I'm not hungry.
I'll go grab something to eat.
But, Master...
What were you two talking about?
I... uh...
I'm not hungry either.
I'll go take a shower.
Why are you both leaving the moment I get here?
Hua said
there's a game to play.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, didn't she tell you?
Nope.
Then why did you bring me here?
Huayan.
I'm here!
Hello!
Zhi, I won!
I want to play too.
I want to play this one.
I'll play with you later.
First, come smash a golden egg with me.
How did I miss it?
Try the one in the middle.
The middle one?
Oh, bad choice.
If you pick
the middle one,
you'll probably get nothing.
These ones here seem luckier.
Try one of those.
So which one?
This one or that one.
That one looks promising too.
That one, then?
I'll smash this one, okay?
Go ahead.
Okay.
So many questions.
Hua, you're amazing!
A dinner voucher for two!
Not bad.
But it's not the grand prize.
Who wants to go to dinner with me
Why didn't you guys call me for the game?
He...
Who's that?
Beici.
Beici...
I want to play too.
Don't...
- You're too late. - Who's playing with me?
Who's playing with me?
This egg looks pretty good.
Try the middle one.
Zhi, come play with me!
Come on!
- Why me? - Beici!
It's fine.
I'll play with him.
Beici!
I'll go watch.
Let's go.
I'm great
at playing games, you know.
You'd better not
go easy on me.
Don't worry. I won't.
Alright then, watch this!
No rush.
Take it slow.
Just imagine that's Beici's head.
Right.
And then smash it.
Actually, it does look like him.
Go, Zhi!
Take this, Beici!
Hah!
Ugh, you're so annoying.
My turn!
Alright, watch and learn!
Hah!
Why?
Beici!
It's okay.
You did well.
Better luck next time, Zhi.
When you play,
you should go all in, right?
Will you shut up already?
How about one more round?
You know the rule. Play to win, right?
Zhi?
Thanks. Congrats,
Beici.
Zhi?
Do you want to go again?
Nah, I'm done.
You guys go ahead.
Jiang Nanfeng and I
are hitting the buffet.
Let's go.
Zhi...
Well then.
I'll go smash some golden eggs!
Which one should I smash?
Come on, Master.
Someone had to lose, right?
Besides, Zhi
agreed to play with me.
Right.
Here, smash this one.
- Go ahead. - This one?
Alright.
Gosh.
A ring?
Don't ever let me see you again.
Chong,
he's sorry.
Master,
I messed up.
Give me a chance
to make it up to you!
I did some research
and read through
every proposal guide.
And?
And here's
what I've learned:
A perfect proposal needs three things:
the right time,
the right place,
and the right people.
Wow, mind-blowing insight.
Let me finish.
We need music,
lighting, and flowers.
Get to the point.
The point is,
I found the best place
in the hotel for a proposal.
The bar downstairs.
All we need to do is get Zhi there,
let her have a drink,
get her a little tipsy,
- and boom... - Hold on.
What exactly are you
suggesting?
He's saying
if Zhi isn't drunk,
you'll have no chance of getting a "yes."
Right?
What?
That's not what I meant!
If she gets wasted, will she even remember it?
Okay, fine.
Forget the drinking part.
But listen.
First, we decorate the place.
Then, when the mood is right
and Master gives the signal,
we bring out the flowers,
balloons,
and all that.
And finally,
Master walks up to Zhi,
takes out the ring,
and boom! She says yes!
Do you think
it'll work?
It sounds like a solid plan.
As long as Beici stays out of it.
Are you on a diet?
Yep, I am.
How disciplined.
Where are Huayan
and the others?
They just got back from the slopes.
They'll be here after they change.
I'll call and hurry them up.
No need.
Yan said they're on the way.
Thanks.
Here,
try the house special.
You try it first.
If it's good, I'll have some.
Look at you two.
Dating has made you both dumb, huh?
- What a disgustingly cute couple. - It's good.
You try it too.
It really is good.
I'm going to the restroom real quick.
Sit down already.
Master,
how's it going?
Is she here?
Yeah.
Chong, do you have the ring?
Yes.
Master,
look.
We're ready too.
You've got this, Master.
Just don't cause any trouble.
Don't jinx it.
It's definitely happening this time!
Let's go.
Today is
a very special day.
One of our guests
is proposing to the love of his life.
Someone's proposing?
Could it be Shan Chong?
No way...
Don't just stand there. Go!
Thanks, guys.
Go!
Is he really proposing?
Now, let's all give them
our heartfelt blessings!
This is so romantic!
Today is your birthday
and our 1,001st day
together.
I love you.
Will you marry me?
Say yes!
Kiss!
Was this
part of our plan?
Did we just get upstaged?
Seems like it.
So, do we still
go out there?
Someone just proposed, huh?
Yeah.
Guess we lucked out. Cheers.
It's nice
to witness something like this.
Raise your glasses.
Cheers.
Yeah, we're really lucky.
Is Master going to...?
What's wrong?
I...
Is there something you want to say?
Wei Zhi,
I want to tell you...
♪Let me stand under the snow♪
♪So that you remain warm next to me♪
♪Crossing stitches♪
♪To weave this moment for you♪
♪Let the snow keep my silence♪
♪As I fall with you into the depths♪
♪Shining like fireworks♪
♪Not as warm as holding you close♪
Time to leave.
Let's go.
Chong,
you were this close!
What happened?
Are you proposing or not?
You think I don't want to?
Didn't you already
go into her room?
Yeah.
She suddenly went to the bathroom.
I...
I just didn't get the right moment.
So you had time for a kiss
but not for a proposal?
How about this?
Let's ask someone with actual sense
for advice.
So you dragged me here in the middle of the night
just because
he wants to propose?
I can't help you.
Plenty of dating experience,
but zero proposal experience.
Besides, I have no plans to get married.
Master,
I have an idea.
No, you don't.
Listen, Master.
You should
make a cake for Zhi yourself
and secretly hide the ring inside.
She'll find the ring
while eating,
and with the right atmosphere,
you'll come off as both thoughtful
and romantic.
Chong, I think this
might actually work.
It's lame.
What if she swallows the ring?
Shan Chong,
there are a million ways to propose.
Creativity and surprise
are just the basics.
What matters most
is you.
Why are you proposing?
Where are you proposing?
What does this moment
mean
to both Wei Zhi and you?
Listen to your own heart.
The most important person in this is you.
Got it?
Hey everyone!
I'm Beici the Bear!
Welcome to Mount 2800!
Can you even walk
in those heavy pants and boots?
Romantic. So romantic.
Absolutely breathtaking!
It's stunning!
This place is unreal, Beici.
You nailed this vlog location.
Of course!
I picked it out just for Mas...
For my
world-class vlog!
So, Master,
are you satisfied?
Of course he is!
Come on.
Take some gorgeous shots for me.
Hold that up.
Alright.
Three, two, one.
Say cheese!
I'll take one for you.
Sure.
Alright.
Got it.
Take a look.
Beici!
Yan! Zhao Keyan!
Zhao Keyan!
Oh, you two.
They're fighting!
You two are such kids.
Don't forget
today's theme
is "Romance at 2800."
Right.
Alright,
now,
let's do some acting.
I'll be the director.
Let's do the first scene.
As for the leads...
Beici,
you're the male lead.
And Huayan,
you're the female lead.
Why not you two?
Quit messing around!
Come on, let's do this!
Now,
just follow
my directions.
- Let's do this. - Alright.
On this magnificent
snow-capped mountain,
Beici gently takes Huayan's hand.
This is dumb.
Come on!
Three, two, one,
action!
These two are hilarious.
My beautiful Huayan,
would you grant me the honor of this dance?
Huayan
gracefully walks to Beici.
The two of them start
dancing romantically at the snowy peak.
Alright. Now Huayan
twirls.
And Beici twirls.
Beautiful.
You just tripped me!
- That hurt! - I'm sorry...
Let's try again.
- It hurts! - Alright.
You two are out.
Worst actors ever.
Come on, one more chance!
Nope.
Please, one last shot!
Guess who's up next!
That would be Zhi
and Master!
Let me walk you two
through the scene.
Alright.
Once again, our leading couple
arrives at the snowy peak of Mount 2800.
Zhi is mesmerized
by the stunning view
and slowly walks
toward the edge.
Then,
Chong approaches
from behind and gently wraps
his arms around her waist.
Together, they take in
the breathtaking scenery.
Got it?
Any lines?
You can
improvise,
alright? Let's do this.
- Alright. - I'll give you a high-angle shot.
- Three, two, one. - I'm going up first, then.
Action!
Zhi slowly walks toward the edge of the mountain.
What a stunning view!
Now,
Chong
quietly approaches from behind.
Zhi waits in silence.
Chong slowly steps forward.
Now,
from behind, he...
♪Is locked in my heart...♪
It's so beautiful.
♪Let this journey drift as it will♪
♪From now on, I'll stay for you♪
♪Let me stand under the snow♪
♪So that you remain warm next to me♪
♪Crossing stitches♪
♪To weave this moment for you...♪
Why isn't he...?
You...
♪I'm not bright like fireworks...♪
Wei Zhi,
thank you for coming into my life
and for sharing your happiness
and dreams with me.
Meeting you
has been
the greatest joy of my life.
♪When you walk towards me firmly...♪
The snow witnessed our first encounter.
So right here,
in this place, I want to tell you...
♪With my dreams...♪
That from this day forward,
I want you by my side every single day.
♪As I bravely fall with you...♪
It's happening.
He wants her by his side forever!
Wei Zhi,
will you marry me?
Marry him!
Say yes!
- Say yes! - Say yes!
♪The hibernation dream is radiant as always...♪
Yes, I will.
I will!
Now get up.
Get up!
♪Stars in your eyes♪
♪They are gentler than the sky♪
♪I daydream with the light on my back♪
♪It's being emotionally moved. It's the night sky♪
♪A dream. A warm winter...♪
Kiss!
Come on!
♪Can only be opened when it's been fulfilled♪
♪Remembering it subconsciously♪
♪The love that remains unchanged♪
♪It's gonna be true love♪
♪It's gonna be true love yeah♪
♪I know you will be the one in the end♪
♪It's gonna be true love♪
♪There's no need to prove it with time♪
♪Every bit of joy is because of you♪
♪The name in my heart♪
♪Is it luck♪
♪Or destiny's art?♪
♪The memories we've come to share♪
♪And that perfect encounter there♪
♪Feel like a promise whispered in air♪
♪You're my one and only♪
♪It's being emotionally moved. It's the night sky♪
♪A dream. A warm winter♪
♪The song I hum. The blowing wind♪
♪I can touch it by reaching out♪
♪The tree hole with a wish made♪
♪Can only be opened when it's been fulfilled...♪
Gather around!
I'll set up the camera.
Master and Zhi, stand in the center.
Be careful.
Camera's set. Come on.
Come.
Stand over here.
Look at the camera.
Alright.
Strike your best poses!
Three, two, one!
♪It's gonna be true love...♪
- Let's do one more! - Can we think of a third pose?
Any ideas?
Do you want one more shot?
- One more. - Yes, one more!
Alright.
This time, you carry me.
♪Your love, I hold onto every second of it...♪
Alright, third shot. Three, two, one.
Up!
♪Afraid to miss a moment of new emotions...♪
Here, I'll help.
Let me give you a hand.
Alright,
one, two, three,
up!
♪Wanna feel me. That's a no♪
♪I'm always ready for you♪
♪It's gonna be true love♪
♪It's gonna be true love yeah♪
In the Kingdom of Comics, there lives a princess.
Her skin is as fair as snow,
and everyone calls her Princess Zhi.
In the Kingdom of Snowboarding, a king lies in slumber.
He is strikingly handsome.
[Tablet - DEF: 100, Pen - ATK: 100]
Armed with her weapons,
she slides her way
[Crystal Coffin]
to the Lone Tree.
Princess Zhi kisses the king.
The king awakes,
sees Princess Zhi,
[Places a veil over her]
and places a beautiful veil over her.
[King]
Must you write such silly stories?
[Princess]
To comic artists, that's romance!
Fine...
And so, the Princess of the Comics Kingdom
marries the King of the Snowboarding Kingdom,
and they live happily ever after.
[Comic, Snowboarding]
Congratulations on your wedding!
[In honor of the finale of "Half a Farewell Song"!]
["Ski into Love" - Ending with love and joy!]
[My dear lady, a happy ending at last!]
What's the most important thing in snowboarding?
Having fun!
No. It's learning to sideslip first.
[Wow]
As long as I'm with Mom and Dad,
every moment is fun!
I, Shan Xunyue, am the happiest kid in the world!
[Thank you for being with us on this journey]
[May love burn bright. May dreams never fade]
[Be your own light]
[-- Ski into Love]
[The End]
♪Secrets keeping in breeze when♪
♪Snow kissed the lonely trees and♪
♪Hold me, kingdom in snow we met♪
♪I stumble upon tides in the stillness♪
♪The paintbrush reveals a secret♪
♪I came close to you in the mirror of snow♪
♪And met you in the purest white♪
♪You're still hidden♪
♪In the pocket of my heartbeat♪
♪So bring me back to shiny ice♪
♪It's hiding in your eyes♪
♪Waiting for the snow to reveal our meeting♪
♪To wake up for you♪
♪So when your faith is burning bright♪
♪Echo in my light♪
♪So I whoo♪
♪Whoo♪
♪I finished the silver sequel♪
♪And searched for the meaning of tenderness♪
♪You are the answer to my riddle♪