♪If the world is ready♪
♪What can I do when it gives me a hard time?♪
♪Instead of hiding♪
♪I'll embrace the change♪
♪Thousands of falls♪
♪Will teach me how to jump♪
♪Thousands of burns♪
♪Will make the best fireworks ever♪
♪If I'm going to land♪
♪I need to have the guts to fly♪
♪So what if I hibernated?♪
♪Passion will give me the light♪
♪And the volume♪
♪To shout to the world♪
♪Don't hesitate♪
♪Run and run and run♪
♪I'm flying through the air♪
♪Don't be afraid♪
♪Jump and jump and jump♪
♪To feel the joy of weightlessness♪
♪There's resistance in the headwind♪
♪It's a favor from fate♪
♪At the end, a miracle will♪
♪Stand by me forever♪
♪Forever♪
[Ski into Love]
[Adapted from Jinjiang Literature City's novel "Ski into Love" by Qing Mei]
[Episode 7]
Come on.
[Filmed in a safe environment. Do not attempt]
Be careful.
♪Secrets keeping in breeze when♪
♪Snow kissed the lonely trees and♪
♪Hold me, kingdom in snow we met♪
♪I stumble upon tides in the stillness♪
OK.
Master.
Take that.
♪The next story dialogue♪
♪When the bonfire blooms♪
♪Exists because of you♪
♪So bring me back to shiny ice♪
♪It's hiding in your eyes♪
♪The deep, hibernating thoughts are buried♪
♪You are the only exception♪
♪So when your faith is burning bright♪
♪Healing my frostbite♪
♪So I whoo♪
♪Whoo♪
♪You are the answer to my riddle♪
Zhi.
We'll take you to the airport.
[Filmed in a safe setting]
Will someone pick you up in Nancheng?
I can go back alone.
I have a favor to ask.
What?
Could you leave a wish and a signature
on the last page of this?
[Half a Farewell Song]
This one?
My brother lined up to get this signed sketch for me
at the Nancheng Comic Con.
Before I got
this signed sketch,
I didn't expect
I'd be able
to draw and become friends
[To: Shan, wishing you could...]
with you like I am now.
I feel like
I'm dreaming.
Done.
Miss Shan,
now we
are in the same boat.
Zhi.
What's wrong with you?
I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.
Crying while laughing.
Are you out of your mind?
Maybe you are.
Did you
catch a cold yesterday
in the snow?
Seems like a little bit, but don't worry.
If I'd known, I'd have sent you back earlier.
Seems like a lot of fat
doesn't help.
Who's got a lot of fat?
It's weird.
You also watched the fireworks most of the night,
but why are you okay now?
I'm from the Northeast. I can handle the cold.
Fireworks?
What fireworks?
Did you two go out
for an event yesterday?
- No, I didn't. - So what...
Good.
Something happened
to you two.
What could have happened?
Chong, say something.
Say what?
All I can say is that you've lost your pocket money for the month.
Miss Zhai.
We're here.
Shan.
I'll miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
See you later.
Send me a message.
We must message each other.
Keep in touch.
Let's go. I'll go in with you.
See you later.
Bye, Zhi.
Stay with me this far.
Thanks.
Am I electrical?
You're venomous.
Remember to take your medicine when you get back.
And
have a safe trip.
Thanks, Master.
See you later.
[MissyJi]
Zhai drew it herself.
Master.
I'm glad I met you
in Hualing.
[Filmed in a safe environment. Do not attempt]
What's so funny?
Disgusting.
I think you two have a thing.
I think you need a spanking.
You're lucky
to have a relationship with a girl
as nice as Miss Zhai, okay?
If it were you, would you want the blessing
of that turtle cushion being broken by her?
You never say anything nice.
Let me show you something.
I took it.
It's a perfect match.
You look like a couple, okay?
You're smiling.
Something's happening
to you.
Who smiled?
I saw it.
I didn't.
I'll send a message
to Miss Zhai later.
How fast did they drive
that they came back so soon?
Madam.
Duo?
You can come anytime,
but do you need to bring so many things?
Come on.
It's not causing me any trouble.
Shan.
Shan, come on.
Look who it is.
Sir.
Duo?
Busy with cooking?
Let me help.
No need.
Sit down
and rest.
No need for help. We can handle it.
Go rest.
Let me know if you need my help.
We can do it.
Good smell.
Mom, we're home.
Duo?
Wash your hands and get ready for dinner.
Son.
You're back just in time.
Go wash your hands
and help your mom.
Don't bother Duo.
He's a guest.
I'm not, sir.
Now go rest.
Coming.
Why did you bring us
so much stuff when you came?
Just a side trip.
Yes. Wash your hands.
For me?
Is that awesome? I caught it myself.
You caught it yourself?
That's awesome.
I'll take you with me next time.
Then, let's catch some more.
You can catch as many as you want.
Are you and my brother at odds again?
We're not at odds.
Actually,
we're lifetime enemies.
Lifetime enemies?
That's funny.
What can you do?
After you come back to Hualing,
you guys still need to eat
at the same table.
Where's your coach? Why didn't he come?
He had some things to do,
but he's probably close by now.
Could be.
Aren't you guys training?
I'm going to Xicheng next month,
so my coach thinks...
Maybe he's still not giving up
on Shan Chong.
He's still not giving up?
Son.
Cut some cucumbers for me.
Actually, in the end,
it has nothing to do
with whether he's given up or not.
How should I put it?
It's hard to let go.
Hard to let go?
You seem to feel it
more than he does.
No, I don't. Don't disgust me.
I didn't.
You made me do it.
Coming.
Who is it?
Wang?
Mr. Shan.
Come in.
I brought you two bottles of good wine.
You just have to come
without bringing me anything.
How long has it been?
We must have a drink today.
Look.
It's good.
You don't need to change your shoes.
I'll stain the floor.
The smell is too strong.
You know me well.
Where's Chong?
Helping us in the kitchen.
In the kitchen?
Go now.
Chong.
Mr. Wang.
Leave me alone.
Chong.
We're frying fish. The fumes are too thick.
Here you go.
I'll fill your glass.
Now.
Try my specialty.
Thank you, ma'am.
It smells good.
Chicken with mushrooms.
Mr. Wang, have some more later.
Yes.
Chicken with mushrooms.
Son.
Drink with your coach.
Don't let your dad drink.
Come on.
Mom.
I can't drink much.
Let them drink together.
Okay.
Come on, let's drink.
Let's drink.
I came here to drink with you.
Okay. Come on.
Let's drink.
You're welcome.
How is it?
Is it strong?
It's good.
Come on.
Thanks, Mr. Shan.
Good.
Chong.
What have you been up to?
He seems to be busy with
teaching a rookie
sideslip lately.
Sideslip?
Even teaching this?
I mean,
I think it's good to teach sideslip.
It's safe.
After helping them get a good foundation,
he might be able to send a few talents
to your national team,
right?
Don't mention it.
Training and tournaments
at Xicheng start soon.
This idiot
can't finish anything.
I'm so anxious that I'm losing my hair
and my lips are swollen.
When Chong was there...
Right?
Chong.
Wang Xin.
Come on.
Thank you.
This dish I made
tastes so good.
Have some more.
Okay.
By the way,
is your kid going to take
the college entrance exam?
Next year.
Not that early.
And he doesn't ski,
so I can't teach him.
I can only let it be.
So Chong,
I...
I'll get a glass of water.
Come on.
Me, too.
Wang.
Come on.
Leave them alone.
Okay.
Let's go on.
Drink more.
Okay.
Come on.
Come on, Wang Xin.
Shan Chong, what do you mean?
My coach was having a serious discussion with you,
but as soon as he talked, you left.
I'm talking to you.
Chong.
Come back.
Shan Chong is here.
All right?
You're drunk, aren't you?
We all need you.
Come back here.
Okay.
Everybody misses you,
you know?
Sir.
Come back now.
Okay?
Let's go home.
Sir.
Come on.
Are you all right?
Be careful.
Okay.
Chong.
Sir.
Take Master back safely.
Wrap him up in case he catches a cold.
You don't have to remind me.
Think about it.
Who is he doing this for?
Let's go.
Duo.
We have to stick together, Chong.
Sir, let me do it.
Come back.
Okay?
Take care of him.
Don't worry.
See you, sir.
OK.
Be safe.
Don't worry.
I'll come back to you in a while.
OK.
I'll go wash the dishes first.
Are you going to Xicheng, too?
When do you leave?
Tomorrow's flight.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm not going to train.
Whatever you do,
be safe.
Dad, let me do it.
Let me do it.
Did you tell your mom
you're going to Xicheng?
Yes.
What did she say?
Nothing
except "be safe".
Do what your mom says,
you hear me?
Or I'll beat you up.
All right. Let me do it.
Let me do it, Dad.
Go get some rest.
Okay.
Don't help me. I'll be fine.
How can you be fine
after drinking so much at lunch?
What did I drink so much for?
Didn't I do it
to ask Chong back?
Who sent you a message?
Tell him and ask him
to come back to the national team.
We need him back now.
Sir.
Sir, are you okay?
Why don't you hold me up?
You didn't let me help you, did you?
Why do you obey me so much
when I don't need you?
If I order you to bring Chong back,
can you do it?
That really hurts.
Defense.
Here.
[Five years ago]
Give it to me.
Stop him.
Defense.
Nice.
Get the ball back.
Catch it.
Pass it to me.
Pass it.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
It's you.
Yes.
Why are you here?
I came to visit my brother.
If you come to visit your brother,
why are you waiting downstairs in the dormitory?
You could have met us
at the training ground.
Would you have waited here all day
if your brother had come back late?
I look like this,
so it's inconvenient for me to go over there.
The wheelchair is really quite inconvenient.
Get your sister fitted with prosthetic legs.
I've asked her.
Ask her for me.
Do you want prosthetic legs?
What does Uh mean?
Do you think wearing prosthetic legs
will make me look better?
Do you think your muscles won't atrophy
if you sit here all the time?
My dear brother.
I need to interrupt you in your busy schedule.
There must be some bad reasons for your sudden respect.
Are you in trouble?
I'm a little...
Probably... Maybe... Perhaps...
Stop if you don't know what to say.
Save me some money.
I'd like to try prosthetic legs.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
What's the prize money
for Beishan's training match?
A lot.
Do you want to participate?
Go out and train with me.
What? It's the middle of the night.
Why are we going out to practice?
I want the prize money.
Useful for me.
Wait a minute.
You've been working too hard lately.
Build on your strengths and win the championship.
Are you confident?
Yes.
Dare to fight?
Want to win?
Yes.
Very good.
Let's go.
[Dangerous Stunts. Do not attempt to recreate them]
[Surgery in progress]
Doctor.
Who's the patient's family?
How's my son?
Don't worry.
The surgery went well.
Okay, thanks.
He's fine.
The surgery went well.
Don't worry.
Hello, inpatient department.
Okay.
I don't want prosthesis legs.
Why not?
I can't ski anymore.
Even if I'm in a wheelchair for the rest of my life,
it'll be no big deal.
If he hadn't gotten me the money
for prosthetic legs,
my brother would have insisted
on participating in this race.
I...
I wish him peace.
Come on. Relax.
Breathe and match your breathing.
Breathe in.
Okay. Relax.
Shan Chong.
The doctor said you're still young
and fine.
As long as you keep up with your rehab,
you'll have no problem getting back
to your old self.
Have faith in yourself.
Again.
Okay. Hang in there.
It's good.
It's normal to feel pain.
Just hold on.
Again.
I can't tell him that.
He loves skiing so much
and is so talented.
How can you let him give up so easily?
Loves it?
What he loves
almost killed him.
He's all right now, isn't he?
He's all right?
He's got two cuts that big
on his shoulder and leg,
so how can he be all right?
Shan has become like that.
How am I supposed to live
if anything else happens
to her brother?
Why are you crying
while you're talking?
Okay. Don't cry.
[Retirement Request]
We chose six men
and six women from 1.4 billion.
Of these, you have the most points
and the best record,
but you're retiring now. What do you mean?
What do you mean? Tell me.
Means nothing.
What?
I mean
snowboarding means nothing.
Anyway, I've given you the application.
Shan Chong, listen.
If you leave, don't come back.
Warning!
My full brother,
Jiang Yiming, is coming to get you.
Zhi.
It's been a long time.
[HAPPY EVERYDAY]
I've got a big surprise for you.
No need.
Thanks, Yiming.
This is too much.
Marry him.
- Marry him. - Marry him.
It's weird.
Take these flowers.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Why are you picking me up?
Where is Jiang Nanfeng?
Jiang Nanfeng has a lot of work to do.
I'll do the small things
like picking you up.
Small things?
It's small for her,
but for me,
it's the most important thing.
Thank you for helping me with my luggage.
Let's go.
[Filmed in a safe environment]
Zhi.
Have you been busy lately?
Yes.
I've just returned
from Germany
and have been doing some paperwork
for my new job.
If you're not busy,
show me around.
Yiming, I want to ask you.
Aren't you also a Nancheng local?
Why did you ask me
to show you around?
Look. I've been abroad
for the past eight years.
From undergrad to PhD
and even my current job,
I've been busy as a bee.
How many times have I been back during that time?
Nancheng has changed
so much.
Anywhere has become unfamiliar to me.
See?
I even use the navigation when driving.
Zhi.
Over the years,
have you met
any new friends or boys
you admire?
Yes.
A lot.
Red light.
Ski video?
Yiming.
Why did you peek at my cell phone?
I saw it by accident.
I heard from Nanfeng earlier
that you were skiing together at Beishan.
How does it feel?
Pretty good.
I'm quite good at it.
That's good.
You know what?
When I studied abroad,
I also liked to ski
and was really good at snowskiing.
Snowskiing is good.
How to say...
Elegant.
Before I was
in the Alps ski resort...
I snowboarded.
That's better.
I can teach you to snowski.
Snowskiing is better than snowboarding.
Who said that?
It's different, okay?
That's not true.
Snowskiing is much faster
than snowboarding.
Let me quiz you.
Do you know what the top speed
of snowskiing is?
The record speed for snowskiing
is 252 kilometers per hour
while snowboarding only reaches about 200.
Skiing is not about speed.
It's about skill.
You have no idea how cool snowboarding is.
My master...
No wonder you like snowboarding so much.
It's because it's cool.
Snowskiing is even cooler.
And at the later stage,
the skill requirement of snowskiing is higher
than that of snowboarding.
You must be tired
after a long flight.
Take a rest first.
I'll remind you when we get there.
Thank you.
Why did you bring me here?
What's going on?
You didn't even ask me.
Now turn around.
Don't you want to go home?
But your mom
specifically told me
to bring you home
as soon as I got you.
She knows I'm back?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Zhi.
Ms. Wang.
Now that I'm here,
let me say hi to your mom.
Yiming.
On second thought,
I think I can just say hi
to her tomorrow,
Give me the suitcase.
It's too heavy.
Let me do it.
Don't worry. Give it to me.
Let's go together.
Don't forget our family will have dinner
together tomorrow.
Thanks, Yiming.
You're welcome.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Is my mom really home?
You're acting like a thief.
Didn't you see me?
Why don't you even say hello to me?
I didn't see you.
Mom.
I'll go change
and eat with you.
Sit down.
Did you get the clothes I asked Nanfeng
to give you?
Yes, I did. I've put them on.
Now have some soup.
How old are you now?
Why do you always make me worry about you?
You spend all day skiing or painting,
but you don't do anything serious.
And you often go out without saying a word.
Listen.
After you come back this time,
stay at home.
Don't go anywhere.
Got it.
[Mom]
Mom.
Wei Zhi, have you been behaving well?
I made a good friend
at school.
Her name is...
Where is she from?
Local or foreign?
Local.
Then get along with her.
Bring her home when you have a chance.
I'll let the nanny make you good food.
Behave well,
and I'll be happy.
[Short story]
[This is my path, so I accept failure]
Let's look
at this company's balance sheet
for 2021.
Here are the assets.
We explained that this
should equal that.
On the left are liabilities.
On the right is the owner's equity chain.
Here. What's
the net profit
it retains?
100,000.
So what's their
net sales margin?
Is that senior believable?
Is he serious?
He's the best at bragging.
Yes, he is.
Do you even believe him?
He's so unreliable.
I'm so nervous
about my interview this afternoon.
No. I'm so nervous.
I need to get a drink.
OK.
You guys go ahead.
All right. Just go ahead.
Wei Zhi, are you still painting?
I've been checking out a lot of companies lately.
Zhi, look.
Are my dark circles
especially obvious?
You seem to be a bit haggard,
but overall, it's okay.
You're still a lovely and quiet beauty.
You're so comforting.
The thought of going for an interview
made me so nervous,
so I stayed up all night.
In my next life,
I want to be a princess
like you.
I could have closed my eyes
and gone back to inherit the family business
instead of going to the interview.
But we found a couple
of pretty good companies.
Do you want to explore them with us?
No need.
I'd like to draw some more.
Okay.
You look really good
in a suit.
And when your bangs
are tied back, look,
they sparkle. So great.
Perfect.
Come on. Let me give you another suit.
Try another one.
This one's good.
Here you go. Try this one first.
Zhi, listen.
When you get to the office tomorrow,
familiarize yourself with the surroundings.
Then, come to my office.
I'll invite a few boys over for you
to check them out.
Why?
Don't you need a serious pick?
You know what?
These boys in the company
are pretty good.
I've asked around.
They're all
from Nancheng.
I'll be happy
when your marriage is finalized
and you get married
and even have children.
Mom.
I don't want to be an accountant.
What do you want to do then?
I have a career I like.
Leave me alone.
Where are you going?
My friend's house.
I don't want to stay at home.
Where are your friends?
My local friend.
This is my path,
so I accept failure.
Who?
Why did you come?
I just got back from abroad
not long ago,
so I haven't had time
to come and see your new house.
That's why I am here.
Zhao Keyan.
Don't run out.
I'm just opening the door,
not going out.
Go change your shoes.
You're so big.
I think it's fine.
Do you live alone in this house?
With a dog. Nice.
It's safe.
Didn't I tell you?
I took Zhao Keyan
when I was in college.
The first time I met him,
I was super into him.
Zhao Keyan?
That's a weird name.
What do you want to drink?
Anything.
Thank you.
Nanfeng.
Did anything special happen
when you went skiing
with Zhi?
What special thing?
Did Zhi meet a master?
A man?
Yes.
Was he better looking
than me?
What's it got to do with you?
Is it comparable?
How can it have nothing to do with me?
Zhi's business is mine.
After all these years,
you're still so pestered
about Wei Zhi.
Why pestered?
I am affectionate,
fascinated,
and obsessive.
From the first moment I met Zhi,
she lived in my mind.
Yiming.
This is my friend.
I told you about her.
Her name is Wei Zhi.
Wei Zhi, hi.
Thank you for coming
to my birthday party.
Yiming.
Happy birthday to you.
Turn this clockwork,
and you'll see the surprise.
I'm so deeply in love
that I've spent more than ten years
of my youth loving someone.
How romantic.
Why do you say pestered?
Then have you ever heard
that love doesn't allow
wishful thinking?
Don't blow me off.
Let's go.
I'll buy you dinner tonight.
I'm not going.
I'm on a diet.
I don't want to eat.
I'll treat you to a fat-reducing meal.
Tell me
about Zhi's master.
Really. Tell me
Tell me.
I'll buy you dinner.
Zhao Keyan, help me.
Zhao Keyan.
Shan?
Can I come in?
Yes.
What are you reading?
Is it interesting?
Of course.
Are you sure you can read this before you open it?
Right to left.
Stupid.
How could I not know this?
I just want to see
how it ends first.
Okay. Go on.
I just came to care about you.
Tomorrow morning, I'm going to Xicheng.
As for you,
take care of yourself.
Be happy.
Anything else?
You should also work hard
at your job
and do what your Miss Zhai says.
Work hard.
My?
My Miss Zhai?
Chong.
We're family.
Your schemes are almost
in your face, okay?
No wonder.
Normally, you never
read my comics,
but you did today.
So you're in love with someone.
Don't be ridiculous.
You are babbling all day.
I'm not.
When you go to Xicheng,
Dai Duo is also there.
Maybe you two will run into each other.
Why would I run into him?
He barks when he sees me.
I don't even want to talk to him.
Go to bed early.
Don't stay up late.
You either.
They're both in Xicheng,
so maybe they'll actually meet.
[Chong. WeChat Moments]
[Beishan, bye.]
[Snowy Classroom. Snowboarding Equipment Introduction]
Preparation for Snowboarding:
First of all,
in the inner part, wear a snug-fitting quick-drying suit
and socks
for warmth, breathability, and perspiration.
Next,
wear a hip protector,
knee pads,
and armor
to protect most
of your joints.
These are essential.
On the outside, wear a ski jacket,
which should be waterproof, windproof, breathable,
warm, and hard-wearing.
If it is colder,
you can opt for a thicker ski jacket with armor
or add some extra sweatshirt
or fleece items, etc. as a warming layer.
Face protection
will protect you from the wind, coldness, and the sun.
Of course, a helmet is also necessary.
Finally,
goggles and gloves.
Goggles protect against wind,
snow, and snowblindness.
As for gloves, make sure to choose
waterproof gloves with wrist protection.
Note
that the first thing you need when skiing is a good protection.
♪Thinking about you♪
♪And your future♪
♪Thinking of you♪
♪With words to say♪
♪Watching you♪
♪Take each step♪
♪Breathing deeply♪
♪Once again♪
♪Who truly understands you?♪
♪Who knows how wonderful you are?♪
♪My dear friend♪
♪Dear friend♪
♪I understand you♪
♪Once again♪
♪I listen to your breath♪
♪My dear friend♪
♪Dear friend♪
♪I understand you♪
♪Once again♪
♪I listen to your breath♪
♪My dear friend♪
♪You'll see if this is love♪