Customer No. 34, your latte is ready.
Customer No. 35, your iced Americano is ready.
No iced Americano
Hmm? I just finished it.
Maybe another customer took it.
Customer No. 34
Oh, it's me
Where's my coffee?
Excuse me, I'll make you a cup right away.
If no one steals
The coffee will stay there.
But if someone takes it
Are you kidding me? What is this?
The coffee won't be there.
I need someone to steal my destiny
Episode 2
All down, you know all down, right?
I just need to lose a ball
All fell down
I throw the ball, and the pins are like bowling pins
All fly out
Looking back, I really was...
Oh, Ji Won
If someone steals my destiny
That should be you.
Because you will only be happy if you take my things
Come here soon
minister
Hello, Minister
Minister, are you going on a field trip?
Agent Yang just said you won't be coming to work today
Oh, yes.
I have something unexpected this morning.
So that's it
Jiang Zhiyuan, are you working on your project plan properly?
If you do it badly again this time, I really won't tolerate it.
I'm trying to do
The section chief said
It feels like Ji Won is not working hard.
Our Ji-won works very hard.
Is this the delicious coffee?
Is it the one in front of the bus stop?
Look at you, you're lazy at work.
Leaving work to buy coffee during work hours
sorry
- I bought it on my way back from a field trip
- Women don't work anyway.
Just stuffing delicious food into your mouth...
-Agent Jiang
-Um?
Please come over here
Let's have coffee
Minister, would you like some drink?
I haven't drunk yet
Actually I didn't have breakfast
That’s why when I go out on a mission…
It's better to have breakfast
You drink it
I'm afraid you'll be embarrassed to drink coffee by yourself when you get home
That's why I deliberately asked you to come here to drink
Thanks
That's right
I don't plan to quit.
Do you want to see this?
This is what my dad gave me.
Every time my dad gives me pocket money
Draw a love heart
Even though I always ask him not to scribble on the money
But it still couldn't suppress his artistic soul
I am such a beloved daughter of my father
I plan to try hard
besides…
You said I was a capable person
Gave me a lot of strength
It allowed me to make up my mind, thank you.
Actually, it's been a long time since I last saw you.
I haven't been pursuing anything.
I'm just busy living
I decided not to live that kind of life anymore.
Good decision
Will you laugh?
I think it's the first time I saw you smile
Excuse me
Do you have any dates this weekend?
This weekend?
No
-So…
- I have made an appointment with Jiwon
We're going out together this weekend.
You've forgotten? That's so sad.
I have already made a reservation at Gusuting
That's a delicious barbecue restaurant.
Lonely Pavilion?
Yes, do you know that store?
I think I've heard
I see
I want to drink that delicious coffee too.
Let's go buy it together
Sorry, I'm a bit busy now
Why? I want to drink
I heard the sandwiches there are delicious too.
Kang Ji-won is so boring
The minister wanted her to work on the weekend, and I rescued her.
Can't you even drink a cup of coffee with me?
A model student who only knows how to work
So annoying
(Employee Search)
(Kang Ji-won)
(Name: Jiang Zhiyuan)
(Taeha High School, Korea University)
Hello? Is this Guseting?
I would like to inquire about group reservations for this Sunday
Busan Taeha High School Reunion, 6 o'clock...
Oh, is it half past five?
(Zhao Dongshuo)
Hello? Dongshuo
Can you help me find someone?
Yes, now
I'll call you back later
Minister, this is for you.
(Pain Relief)
This is a painkiller
I heard it's best to take it whenever you feel a little pain.
Have you eaten?
Your injury should hurt.
Oh, I'm fine.
You're well prepared, but take care of yourself first
You probably need this more than I do.
Thanks
Come out for a while
I must let Jung Soo Min steal my destiny
Wouldn’t you…
It's because of Liu Zhihe
Are you saying you want to break up with me?
What?
Liu Zhihe became a minister at a young age
You seem to think he has some background.
You only know one thing but not the other.
Half-witted vixen
I said that men should be judged by appearance and brains
Do you know?
What does that expression of yours mean?
You don’t have anything going on with Liu Zhihe, do you?
Minister, I'm sorry.
You are here because the minister asked me to buy an OK bandaid
That's why it's like this?
Did that guy ask you to buy a Band-Aid?
That crazy old man
He actually wants you, a person with an injured foot, to buy it?
I can't stand it
I will break up
Because I feel that between us
It doesn't seem to be the same as before
I don't know
I don't want to say it out loud
What is this?
You think I'm a little cold
Are you throwing a tantrum?
Um
I want a relationship that everyone admires
I hope you are that kind of
The kind that others would want to steal
Excellent boyfriend
What?
What does it matter what other people think?
It's enough that we are sincere to each other
Kang Ji-won, you little guy
I thought you were stupid, but it seems you are not.
Okay
I'll pay more attention
Let's reconcile.
-good
-Um
What? What are you doing?
Let's reconcile
Why in the company?
It's okay, no one will come.
-Yes
-Won't
Wait, there's a phone call.
It's my mom. She called and asked me to take medicine.
This won't work.
Oh, yeah
I untie this
I…
I know it's none of my business
But even if they are couples
You shouldn't force intimacy.
that…
I just remember that I used to
I regret it
You are a smart person
Don't make the wrong choice like me.
Did she come here specially because she was worried about me?
It's lunch time
Let's go eat
Agent Yang
Have you made a restaurant reservation?
Honey, what shall we eat?
I want to eat curry
Let's go to an Indian restaurant.
Sorry, I'm poor lately.
And today the meal in the staff cafeteria is spicy fried pork
Minhwan, why don't you take Xiumin out to eat curry?
No, if you want spicy fried pork
Then I will also eat at the staff restaurant today
Oh well
Then let's go to the staff restaurant.
Thanks, my other half
for you
It's not that I don't know
As long as it doesn't suit your taste, you will be scheming
Let's sit there.
Oh, really, you should be careful too.
Ji Won, are you okay?
what to do?
The reason why I endure
Because I thought you were my only friend
-sorry
- You should have avoided it, but you got splashed
what to do?
Let's sit there.
Ouch
hateful
Damn
Oh god, I'm sorry.
How are you?
sorry
Xiumin, I'm sorry.
Did you trip over my feet?
Honey
-Are you hurt?
- Really
Isn't this your favorite shirt?
Ossendic?
The whole thing is ruined
what to do?
Give me a napkin
Oh, napkins, ok
I won't be bullied anymore.
Excuse me
Is there anyone outside?
Are you calling me?
right…
Excuse me
Can you help me?
Do you need sanitary napkins?
right…
right
Please wait a moment. I'll get it for you.
Thank you, thank you so much.
Thank you so much
I just want to know who is this great benefactor
The one who saved my life, I didn't expect it was someone I knew
I will definitely treat you well once
No need to entertain, it's nothing.
Xiyan, don't move yet.
Excuse me
really
alright
How can you be so nice?
You are the one I thought didn't exist in this era
The Good Samaritan
Kind people who only exist in movies
And you are the light and salt of my life
My real savior
Is this your personality?
God
You look so pretty when you smile
Why don’t I know this?
Beautiful and kind
You are truly the best person in the world.
You are really exaggerating.
Others will surely do the same.
No, it's not.
There was another person who came in before you.
I really begged her.
But she just kept mumbling
I went to the toilet, washed my hands and left.
Thanks, my other half
Excuse me, have you eaten yet?
I haven't eaten yet
I came to eat without any preparation
The result was a crisis.
Yes
Looking back
We haven't had dinner together.
If possible, would you like to eat together?
You said you were going to get a napkin.
But he never came back, so I wondered what happened.
She's in an emergency, too.
What's going on?
Anyway
We've taken care of it ourselves
Very well handled
Is this handled well?
Park Min-hwan must be furious
He begged me for a year to buy him that shirt
I'm really sorry, Agent Park.
I'll buy you a new shirt
No
It's just a shirt.
You don't need to care
Isn't that a famous brand?
Shouldn't it be 1.5 million or 1.8 million won?
Not that expensive, probably around 1.2 million won
-Um…
-what to do?
I'm just a contractor, I don't have much money.
It's okay, don't worry about it, just eat.
Is it really okay?
As expected, he is Agent Park, very capable
-Super strong
-You're great too
I should go buy a shirt.
Eat, everyone. I have a lot of shirts at home.
Your heart is as broad as the sea
Today I was planning to try the spicy fried pork
It smells so good.
Agent Park is the best
(Weite Western Restaurant)
Always be careful with fire
Chop some more onions
Very good, continue
Hey, this is burnt.
If you leave it alone, it will burn. Redo it.
Thank you for visiting
The food is so delicious
Thanks
Chef Baek Eun-ho
yes
You graduated from Busan Taeha High School, right?
Yes, what's up?
Xiyan, you are really good at eating.
yes
Why do girls eat so much?
Whether male or female
To do great things, you must definitely eat more
This is what my grandfather taught me.
So did your grandfather do something big?
He is selling bean sprouts.
And tofu and sauce
It turns out that he runs a small vegetable shop.
Xiyan, you are blessed by your grandfather
That's why it's so energetic
Koreans just want to eat rice
Yes, well said.
I'm a picky eater, it's too bad
How are you supposed to work if you only eat that?
You eat too little
That is to say
I should be able to eat like Jiwon
Looking back
Ji-won has never had indigestion since she was a child.
Her digestive ability is so good that she can even eat steel.
-Isn't that right? Jiwon
-Um
Is that really the case?
I remember I used to eat pork soup rice with her
She's just like an uncle.
Eat generously
You uncle
Min-hwan, you can't say that.
No matter what, you have to love our Ji Won
like
Yes, love is important.
I envy you for having such a good friend.
Yes, Xiumin is so great.
Why are there no men...
Agent Jiang, let me pour you a glass of water
- Help me pour it too
-What? Why would I?
You have to pour water anyway.
- Help me too...
- You come to work in the company anyway
Would you like to help me with my work too?
this…
that…
That woman is so young, how dare she do that?
Don't call that woman.
This is the company
Although she is younger, her rank is the same as yours.
What?
oh
But I'll remind her.
Yeah, tell her.
Have her manners been eaten by a dog?
Min-hwan, you should finish eating with Soo-min before going upstairs.
You know she's a picky eater.
Ignore her, she doesn't eat much.
Very different from me
Yeah, okay
See you later
Hee-yeon, I'm sorry.
I recycled the plates for you.
You feel very unhappy, right?
Sorry, I should have held back.
I knew it as soon as I saw it
The person who just ignored me in the bathroom
It's Zheng Xiumin
Excuse me, the person who just came in
Could you please do me a favor?
I am not ready yet, I need help from others
It's troublesome
After our meeting, shall we go for coffee?
- It's my treat
- I said I'd like to invite you
Ji Won seems angry
Because I ruined your shirt
Ouch
You also know that Ji Won is not that kind of person
Just now she was worried that you ate too little
She usually cares about you very much.
Is this really the case?
Ji Won is so ruthless sometimes
I don't know how much I like her.
Ouch
It doesn't matter.
- Come in
- I want a ride too
Ouch
My hand...
Oh, okay
this…
What should I do?
Well, that...
No, no.
Excuse me
Sorry, can you lend me this?
You use
What perfume?
This is...
Good smell
Yeah, yeah
（Conference Room）
-for you
-Thanks
good
What are you doing?
What?
Chief, those are the meeting materials.
Didn't I tell you not to do that?
Um?
To be honest
I don't even need to read the business plan you wrote to know it's terrible
At least be sincere.
Will the atmosphere of the meeting be good?
Do you think this makes sense?
- You guys tell me
-Once a person becomes incompetent
They only make a big fuss about the little things they know
Oh, it does feel a bit insincere.
Hee-yeon, the staple
Be like this
Slanting nails
Staples?
That's right
Xiumin is really sensible
All reprints and repins
All?
This seems to waste a lot of paper.
I want you to realize
You've wasted a few trees.
Section Chief
I think Agent Yang understands what you mean
Ji-won, pour the chief a cup of coffee
Section Chief
Please help me look at the business plan I wrote
I have to be a full-time employee.
Should we go out for some fresh air?
Is that so?
Agent Yang, I'm sorry.
Because I don't know much
No
It doesn't matter
This really can't go on any longer.
Agent Yang
Would you like to have a cup of coffee with me?
I have to do what the section chief wants me to do.
It will be fine in a moment
You're a bit weird.
Next time
At least please take a look at this.
"One-person family"
Isn't this the project proposal that was rejected by the section chief?
What do you want me to watch this for?
Please take a closer look
If you're still not free, forget it.
Then I'll go first
Scare me
Where did you run back from?
Oh, that...
The meeting is over, wait till I go to the bathroom
Let's go to the lounge and laze around.
etc.
Min Hwan said he had something to tell me
I'll find you later
(Proposal for quick-cooking meal kits in the one-person household era)
(Pain Relief)
Hee-yeon, I have something to ask.
Got to go back to the office.
So you want me to finish eating this by myself?
I can't just accept the benefits you give me every time, right?
So this Sunday
Do you want to go on a date with me?
My treat
Sunday?
You're going to date me this weekend.
I found a delicious barbecue restaurant.
Guse Pavilion
I can't seem to do it on Sunday.
Do you have a date?
I have an appointment.
But I don't think I'll go
Can I not go?
What is the appointment?
Alumni Reunion
Of course I have to go to the class reunion.
Go see First Love
Then feel disappointed
This is the way to move forward and forget the past.
No one knows where my first love is
What are you doing?
I was actually very unpopular in school.
I need to go there
Looking back on my shameful past?
This is more appropriate, right?
If you don't go, it will just be a miserable past.
If you change it drastically
That will become a glorious history.
minister
yes
You asked me if I was free on Sunday.
If it's urgent, I'm willing to come to work
Don’t you have an appointment?
That's right
But it doesn't matter, work comes first
I think this is right
You are the priority
that…
I'm actually wondering whether I should go or not.
Go ahead
Although I hesitated
The answer will be different every time
But let’s try it this time.
You can go
Just remember that you owe me a favor.
What?
(Basic nutritional information of quick-cooking food packs)
Please take a closer look
If you're still not free, forget it.
Very well written
Agent Yang
Have you seen it?
Um
I have seen
very nice
Do you want to do it with me?
That's not how things work in the company
The section chief has a different point of view from us...
That person has not seen
-What?
- I saw
He pretended to read
But it's just for show
Not just this time
Including your report.
He vetoed everything.
This is something everyone knows.
Look at him, he's really outrageous.
Because he thought that was power.
Impossible
If you are controlled by emotions for too long, you will lose your objectivity
Regardless of other
Regardless of the section chief's opinion
What do you think?
Do you really think my proposal
Is that outrageous? Really?
Then I'll discuss it with the section chief.
Section Chief Kim Kyung-wook…
She's really annoying lately.
Scare me
Section Chief
Excuse me, have you had lunch?
The beautiful Xiumin in our group
I ate loach soup to nourish my body
What about you?
I had spicy fried pork in the staff cafeteria
It seems delicious.
Say
I have a secret to tell you.
secret?
You know I want a full-time job.
I have an idea, but I can't figure it out.
Of course I'll help you.
Really?
Thank you so much
No
Our group is
The yellow-faced woman and the ugly one who doesn't look like a woman
Because of the low mood in our group
We really need you to become a full-time employee.
The section chief is really
You are so humorous
You know he does whatever he wants.
So he always opposes what you say
Ever since he pursued you and was rejected
What are you talking about? That's too childish.
Jin Jingxu for seven years
I have been doing such childish things.
I know he can become a section chief.
Because he took your project plan
Submit it under your own name
As he did before
He used my business plan to get Zheng Xiumin a full-time job
He is my predecessor
In the company, people would always give away things made by their subordinates.
Use the name of your superior...
You never did that.
I am very confident in this plan
You know this is a good plan.
But the Chief...
On Monday I will submit the rejected proposals
Submit it again without changing the title
What?
Wait until you are sure he has not seen it before vetoing it.
Then…
Would you like to work with me?
I'm 100% sure he didn't see it.
No, maybe 99%?
I'm sure Kim Kyung-wook didn't read the project proposal
But if he remembers a chart or a picture...
(The Love Bible)
Don't be afraid, I'm right.
I know how lazy he is and how he doesn't do anything.
Chief, please take a look.
This is a new project
(Proposal for quick-cooking meal kits in the one-person household era)
(Table of contents)
(Pursue health)
(Product Overview)
（Nutrition Information）
Are you kidding me?
This is the same as what you gave me last time...
I'm speechless
It's worse than before!
I am this person
It's not that I haven't seen people who can't do things.
But this is the first time I see someone like you
How could you be so bad?
This is obviously cutting and pasting information from everywhere
If you don't want to work, don't do it.
Why do you want to torture me?
Chief, I'm really sorry.
This is the same one as last time.
I got the wrong one. Please wait.
This one is right, the green one
I'm sorry, Chief. I'm so sorry.
What? Didn't he realize that he had seen it?
Exaggeration, he really didn't do anything
It really lives up to its reputation
I didn't quite believe it.
He actually didn't know
The title is exactly the same, how could he not know?
I said he wasn't working.
Now we are the same team
Quick cooking packs will definitely be popular
Providing consumers with fast, simple and delicious food
good
Now I finally know why everything goes wrong for me
I can't believe it.
I've been working for this guy.
Are you two the only ones drinking coffee?
cheers
Chief Jin is exaggerating, how could he not know?
"Quick cooking meal for one person"
(Planning Purpose and Background)
(Basic nutritional information of quick-cooking food packs)
cheers
Why did you ask me out after get off work?
To tell you the secret I told you today.
The word secret
It's really exciting
Is it okay to eat pork belly?
Oh, that's right.
Did you say you had spicy fried pork for lunch?
Eating pork for two consecutive meals
Isn't this a bit bad?
Won't
I prefer Korean pork to Korean beef
You really know how to eat
(Pork: Imported)
Xiumin, you are such a nice girl
I'm not
The really nice girl is Ji Won
All I talk about is Kang Ji-won
Do you like her that much?
I really don't understand women.
Ji Won
Not like us
She graduated from a Korean university.
She is smart
and
Still a bit ambitious
What's so great about Korean universities?
The people who graduated there only know how to study, but they are useless.
The plan is full of unrealistic nonsense.
Ji Won probably doesn't think so.
She'll probably think you don't know talent.
No vision
You say I have no vision?
I think you have an inferiority complex about your academic qualifications.
Don't do this
University?
It's of no use at all
No
I mean, her idea might be good.
Although execution is another matter
That Jiang Zhiyuan
Always so rigid
So that's what she thought in her heart?
By the way, the one she printed wrong today
Quick cooking meal package project
It's terrible, but the idea is good.
You bring it over here
Develop with me
It might be a big seller.
With you...
-Together?
-right
Anyway, if Zhiyuan were to do it, she would definitely not do it well.
If you can rely on your experience, you can grasp the direction
I think it should be OK for me to get a full-time job.
I really feel comfortable with you.
It's like I'm chatting with my brother about work.
She just said
Am I like a brother?
Of course, yes.
The boss is my brother.
Come
Our Xiumin
Tell me more about the project plan.
us
Let's have a drink first.
cheers
Brother Chief, come and have some meat.
Well played
Why is she Kang Ji-won's friend?
I can't even try.
What does it matter?
I think she's in love with you too.
Just make a quick deal.
What's the deal? Are you selling used goods?
Are you kidding?
All down, right?
Too strong
Well played!
Shang Tsung
Do you know any nice girls?
I'm really going crazy
nerve
You are full of energy.
Where is your girlfriend?
Why does mentioning her make me feel cold?
She's just for marriage.
What is used for marriage?
Look
She is kind-hearted and frugal.
She works hard to make money but doesn't know how to spend it.
-how?
-Wow
She's the perfect wife.
She's super boring.
She will look at the company's outlook report
Have you ever seen anyone watching that kind of thing?
I guess she should be looking at materials in the company now
Like this
Rebirth means you can do anything
Although it's not a big deal
But I let Zheng Xiumin eat the turtle
Kim Kyung-wook too
I can do anything
These are couple earrings. You must wear them on Sunday.
Your everlasting love, Xiumin
Did you see the earrings she was wearing?
You've been so distant lately, I'm so sad
I'm not saying this because I'm drunk
I'm going to sleep at your house tonight.
We spent the weekend together and went to Guse Pavilion on Sunday
(Guse Pavilion)
Guse Pavilion
I am sure
(Guse Pavilion)
(Busan Taeha High School, 37th Reunion)
She really came
Ji Won!
Jiwon, you're here?
Let's go in quickly
What's going on?
Aren’t we both going to have dinner?
If I said it was a class reunion, you definitely wouldn't come
We are all over 30, let's forget the past
They are all very nice people.
- Let's go
- Xiumin, I...
It's okay.
I'm leaving, help me with my bag
Kang Ji-won is really amazing
No one who is familiar with her dares to come
She must be here to eat meat.
Looking at her dress, she looks very poor.
Why are you speaking in Seoul accent all of a sudden? So corny
By the way, why is she still playing with Xiumin?
Can't you tell it at a glance?
Xiumin, that innocent child, is so kind to her.
If Xiumin wasn't here, she wouldn't even have any barbecue to eat.
Drink milk!
Don't be like this.
Zheng Xiumin is so kind
We should take care of her.
Did you see the earrings she was wearing?
She should have learned how to wear it from Xiumin
You can tell it's a fake from 500 meters away.
When Jiang Zhiyuan was in high school...
Wisdom, etc.
What's wrong?
Jiang Zhiyuan was not at her seat just now
Hello, have you been here all the time?
Why are you pretending not to be there?
You are really insidious.
I won't go there
No, don't come over. Today I...
I'm going to your house today
After a drink, I want to see my lover
I'll be there in an hour
Do these two people think my home is a hotel?
them…
etc.
All right
There's no need to wait for something that's going to happen anyway.
You two love each other to death
I will help you get results quickly.
You go this way.
Thanks
Are you just getting off work now?
Yes, you just came back now?
I have something to do.
You've worked hard. I'll take my leave now.
etc.
This one?
This is the gift I received
That is...
Counterfeit goods
Those who understand will know it at a glance
That is...
Counterfeit goods
Those who understand will know it at a glance
Are you talking about me?
What's the meaning?
It's better not to wear it
I remember
He's said the same thing to me before.
I think he's being disrespectful.
Because I didn't know to go to the class reunion
What kind of humiliation will I suffer?
That's a gift from my friend.
Of course I think it's bad for him to say that.
sorry
no
Thank you
Do you want me to take you home?
What?
Because it's late
Oh, no thanks
There are also buses available, which will arrive soon.
I want to take you back
Thank you for your kindness
I have a date with my boyfriend
goodbye
Thanks, no need to look for it
What?
I was working overtime. I'll be back soon.
She is rushing back in the middle of working overtime?
Right, she is also a human being. She will definitely be hungry if she hasn’t eaten for too long.
There's beer in the fridge, have another one and wait for me
It's incredible
Jiang Zhiyuan, you are dead today
(whisky)
Will you get drunk if you drink this?
I love you, my other half
Be gentle with me
I love you, I said I like you
"Come quickly"?
There's not even an emoji, so cold
It's really too much
I'm not going
I'm not going anymore
You make my heart go up and down
Jiang Zhiyuan, you are dead today
How come he got here so quickly?
I'm not going, I'm not happy, I want to go home
I'm a little sad
What? Why isn't she here?
Honey, you're back.
You're here soon.
I thought you would be here in a while.
I'm eager to spend a hot night with you
So I took a taxi.
There's no need to do this.
us
Long time
there is none left
Right?
It's been a long time.
So we should talk...
Wanna chat?
Talk with your body
Let's put the clothes...
Now
us
unnecessary
Clothes
Come
Don't move
It suits you very well and looks good.
Turning the shameful past into a glorious history
People like me
It's not something that can change overnight.
I was bullied before.
She forgot how bad she was.
Fortunately, I met you, Agent Park
I'm coming, behind you
I used to like you!
I have someone I like.
Which woman did he fall in love with to do that?
Go and ask around
Translated by: Peng Xiangfen