Cold wind is not good
My dear Ji Won
You are still beautiful
If you leave me, I won't forgive you
Don't forget that I am by your side
You want to live with me for a long time
Thank you
I don't have good luck with my husband, but luckily I have good luck with my friends.
How can you say that?
Min Hwan is a very good husband
- That guy has another woman
-What?
He sent me messages saying he loved me and missed me
Then deleted it immediately
It must have been sent to the wrong person.
Don't be so sensitive
Do you want me to go talk to Min-hwan?
No need, I have you and that's enough for me
I only have you.
Just think positively, okay? My significant other
Ms. Jiang Zhiyuan, it's time to go to the injection room
This time the medicine doesn't hurt at all
You'll feel better after the fight.
Don't give up, never
(Anticancer)
(April 12, 2023)
I can't remember the last time
When do you feel happy?
Why do I miss you so much?
If we hurry, there are only six months left.
If a miracle happens, there are still 12 months left.
There will be no next time now.
Thank you for your hard work. You look beautiful today.
You are really beautiful
The wedding dress I picked for you is really suitable
Forget it, now you are married into the Park family
You are my daughter.
A distressing little thing
It's not your fault that you don't have a tutor.
Now, mom, let me teach you
Poor little thing
Our Min-hwan is the only son of the third generation of the Jinhae Park family.
Three generations of only son
How dare you cut off our family line?
sorry
I took in your useless thing.
Why can’t I have children?
What exactly can you do?
-Mom, please bear with it.
-Let me go
What a waste, sit down, why are you so angry?
(Duga Holdings)
What? You quit?
I want to invest in stocks
You remember Roy Gentar back then?
A few more bucks can turn your life around
I can't earn anything I can in order to work in a company.
This won't work.
We have to pay so much loan every month
Shouldn't you at least discuss this with me first?
Hey, are you kidding me?
Why should I discuss my affairs with you?
Mother
Mom, will I be successful? Will I make a lot of money?
Of course, my son is good at everything.
Is there something going on at home? Is it just you who has a family?
Everyone here has a family.
No wonder people say married women shouldn't work
What are you doing
sorry
You said you would fix the door lock today
I'm not playing
You think you work overtime every day?
Does it look like you are good at doing things?
That's because you're bad at work.
I'll be so busy that I'll be dizzy
You need to be self-aware
Didn't you hear the washing machine?
I put the clothes down to wash
- You should at least take out the laundry...
-hateful
Hello!
I've been working all day and I've just sat down
I don't care
Gastric Cancer Stage IV
The situation is not optimistic
So pitiful, what should I do?
My son
Why marry that kind of person?
So I can't recognize people clearly.
Now things are finally on track.
How could I be so unlucky?
Mom, Kang Ji-won has cancer
Who's going to cook for me?
Are you too kind?
Why worry about such a thing?
People need to work to overcome illness
Technology is so advanced now, nothing will happen.
Isn’t it?
Don't even think about telling the company, just work until you can't go anymore
Don't be so emotional over there, saying you are sick.
That's asking for trouble.
Can't we just cut it off?
Technology is advanced, nothing will happen.
Cancer is no big deal these days.
All the drips are done.
Episode 1
Don't mind your husband having an affair.
I'm older, it's better to not have a husband
If you are not feeling well, stop thinking about bad things.
Don’t you have a good friend?
She is so pretty and kind
Yes, I have a good friend.
She is smart and capable
I am the section chief of U&K.
That was the company I used to work for.
Actually, I have many shortcomings
Honey
Xiumin is the only one who stays with me
Now
It will be the same in the future
Ms. Kang Ji-won
that
If you continue treatment
Your family must come.
I want to pay the fee or take you back.
sorry
Please deal with it within today.
The number you dialed cannot be answered
Forwarding to voicemail...
Answering the phone
The number you dialed cannot be answered...
Did you get your house deposit back?
Answering the phone
Please answer the phone.
We've been married for less than a year and you quit your job
I haven't even calculated how much money I make to support my family.
You should at least pay for my medical bills.
Answering the phone
(Ping An Hospital)
(Taxi, empty)
Please take me to Hae Young Villa in Heungma-dong
Ouch, you seem very ill.
You'll be feeling better soon.
Isn’t spring here?
I won't get better
I will die
Ouch
You can't say it so badly.
The doctor said so.
That's not a bad word.
There's no benefit in living
How could there not be?
(Taxi driving license
Name: Choi Nam-hyun)
My dad passed away very early.
I don't have any brothers or sisters
There is a husband like no
No
It's better not to have it at all
So…
I wouldn't be unable to pay my medical bills and end up in debt.
The result will only be known at the end of the road
That...is not this road
I'll take you on a good path, trust me.
Come on, we're here
You see
The path you know is not the only one
There is another way
That road might be better.
(Hai Ying Villa)
(9,600 KRW)
Thanks
Please wait a moment
Miss
Today is my last day driving a taxi.
Just think of it as your dad giving you pocket money.
Keep it as a souvenir.
Then you will immediately become lively
Lively and make a lot of money
You will also encounter one
A good man who is willing to die for you
Live a happy life
No, no need to do that.
Oh, take it quickly.
The old man's hand is about to break.
Honey, you are really smart.
What made you think of buying cancer insurance?
Her father died of cancer.
I see she is getting thinner and thinner
I think it's time, so I'll buy insurance now.
Awesome, very well done.
One billion won?
Yes, if she died
I have received the insurance money for the diagnosis, and I have bought you a package.
Then invest the rest of the money in stocks
I plan to buy you a better bag
It's so kind of you
When Ji-won dies, we'll buy a house.
Buying a house is good
But that woman lasted longer than I expected.
I'm just afraid that she will do this, even if she is insured
I didn't ask her to see a doctor.
She's pretty tenacious.
Do you want me to take her out for some fresh air?
Push her secretly?
No, what if you fall down too?
How can it not work? I just need to push it gently.
No one will find out
What on earth did she eat to make her so tenacious?
Then you should eat with her.
I am strong without eating.
You two crazy people!
Ji Won
Honey, are you okay?
Spit it out
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine
You're committing insurance fraud.
I want to report you
Hello!
What are you doing?
Honey, are you okay?
-I'm fine
-Are you really okay?
-Um
-good
If you leave me, I won't forgive you
Zheng Xiumin
I'm going to kill both of you today.
I'm going to kill both of you!
Hello, Hello, Hello
Have you had enough?
Don’t you feel bored?
Ouch
hateful
Hello
What else can you do now?
Let's go
Get out of the way
Hello!
You really are
etc.
Ji Won
sorry
sorry?
It's done.
What can I do now?
The living must continue to live
You're going to die anyway.
Why do you always think only of yourself?
You really have it.
Won't you die?
Do you think you won't die?
- You will die too
-That's enough!
- Really
-Stop fighting!
Honey!
Hello
If you want to die, just die obediently, get out of here!
The happiness I desire is out of reach
And the familiar misfortune is right in front of us
Honey
She seems dead
She'll die anyway.
Does it matter how you die?
What should we do?
You be quiet
Anyway, she is a cancer patient and often faints.
She slipped herself
We are only seeing it now
I don't know what happened
Will we not be able to receive the insurance money in this case?
-Will it?
-what to do?
In short, six months
If a miracle happens, 12 months
I won't live as long as the doctor said.
I am dead
(April 12, 2023)
Honey, what are you doing?
Why do you look so distraught?
Why are you holding your glasses in your hand instead of putting them on?
Have you been to the doctor?
What did the doctor say?
Honey, what happened to you? It hurts.
it hurts
What's wrong with you?
Hello!
Jiang Zhiyuan, let me go!
Kang Ji-won, let go of your hands
Damn it, let me go!
Ms. Kang Ji-won!
Please wake up.
This is the company, what are you doing?
company?
How are you?
What's going on?
I don't know
Are you hurt?
Borrow it for a moment
Kang Ji-won
Ji Won
The living must continue to live
You're going to die anyway.
Get out of here!
Hey, Kang Ji-won
Don't run away
Can you calm down?
(Yeksam Station)
(Park Geun-hye was elected the 18th President)
(Dark New World)
(2013 World Baseball Classic
South Korea team was eliminated in the preliminaries)
(2013, Yazun)
(International superstar PSY releases new song)
(The first Korean singer to reach No. 1 on Billboard)
(2013 Spring Sale)
(Congratulations to Kim Yuna for winning the 2013
World Figure Skating Championships Champion)
What's going on?
Where is this?
You from the company
I ran nearly two hundred meters.
Mercedes-Benz
I guess I should ask what's going on.
what is going on?
(April 12, 2023)
(April 12, 2013)
Is there anything hot at home?
No, it's okay.
Do you have cash?
You probably didn't bring your wallet or cell phone.
(Agent, Kang Ji-won)
You take it.
There are always times when people need help from others.
Thanks
(Packaging date: March 17, 2013
Effective date: April 17, 2013)
(Effective date: April 17, 2013
Date of manufacture: April 10, 2013)
All in 2013
So warm
Now let me clarify
Am I dreaming?
If I am dreaming, where is the dream?
(April 2013)
Is it 2023 when he died at the hands of Park Min-hwan?
Or am I 31 years old again in 2013?
No, 2023 is not a dream
I…
I know who Minister Liu Zhihe is.
Minister Liu Zhihe, please say a few words
President Liu Zhihe in 2021
Promoted to U&K Representative Director
Complete control of the management rights of U&K Food and Finance
Completed the inheritance process
(U&K Group CEO assumed office)
(51st session in 2021
U&K Holdings Regular Shareholders Meeting)
Although no one knows now
But the Minister is...
I won't stop challenging
Expanding our company beyond Korea
Becoming a global lifestyle company
…grandson of Liu Hanyi, founder of U&K
This is my vision for U&K
He will start the succession process in a few years.
From what I know about this
Am I really going back in time?
That's right
Where is the money he gave me?
Here
Just think of it as your dad giving you pocket money.
Keep it as a souvenir.
Don't scribble on money.
dad
That's not graffiti.
That is love
It is love only for us, it cannot be like this
Okay, don't worry.
I should listen to you.
Do everything for you
I can't stand you, Dad.
That's Dad
(Name: Choi Nam-hyun)
(Name: Jiang Xianmou)
I will do it for you
Dad, I'll do it all for you.
dad
You should say hello to me.
Why is your face so swollen?
Come out, let's go eat something
Ji-won, what's wrong with you?
You haven't answered the phone since you rushed out of the company
I'm worried about you
I'm on my way to your house
I'm not feeling well
Don't come over. I'm with Min-hwan now.
Oh no
Hello, Hello, Hello
You are really ignorant.
Okay, you have mixed feelings, that's okay.
Although I don't quite understand
But other girls say that, okay, I know
I see
But why do you want to work in the company?
Is it so obvious?
Isn’t this quite right?
What good will it do you to make things difficult for me?
Can you explain it so that I can understand?
When exactly is it?
We haven't done it recently.
How did you get pregnant?
Is that my child?
What?
Didn't you say you seemed pregnant?
I remember
Because I can't eat these days.
So I thought I was pregnant
It's actually stress gastritis
Did it start from this time?
Not only does it keep putting pressure on me until I die
And I fucked with my friend
I'm kidding.
You don't have the ability to do anything with other men
Don't misunderstand me
I'm just saying you're not young anymore.
If you stop now
I can't work anymore.
That's a career interruption.
You love your work and you know how to do it
I don't want to become a yellow-faced woman, staying at home all day.
If you were to have a baby now
It's like cutting
The wings of the birds flying outside
If I didn't know you would quit your job and stay at home to rely on me
What you said seems to make sense.
Take it away
Surgery fee...
good
I pay half
-half?
- You're going to take it off anyway
Wouldn’t it be better for your health if you removed it early?
And I don't want kids
There is no benefit in raising children in this era
Our Min-hwan is the only son of the third generation of the Jinhae Park family.
How dare you cut off our family line?
I am not pregnant
It is gastritis
You are not pregnant?
Gastritis? It turns out it's gastritis.
Then why are you so sensitive?
Let's break up
-What?
-You have nothing to say?
Are you done?
You went crazy on me at work today
I thought you were pregnant, trying to understand you
But you said you want to break up?
Let me go
You guy
Hey, did I say something wrong?
Why are you mad at me?
-I forgot
-Are you crazy?
Park Min-hwan is a madman
It doesn't matter if I die
But you can't stand me saying I want to break up
Let me go.
Why do you want to break up with me? Why do you?
I'm going to kill you
Tell me, what right do you have? Why?
You say it
Do you think you can break up with me?
Why do you tell me you want to break up?
Tell me, why?
Tell me what you say!
Is anyone there? Help!
Help!
Please save me!
Miss
You can't call the police just because a couple quarrels.
It's not a couple's quarrel. He just said to me...
I know, I know very well
But most of the girls who call the police
Afterwards, I always ask why I did that to my boyfriend.
How helpless would we be then?
Mr. Police
Girls are always extra sensitive for a few days.
I apologize for her
You weren't interrupted anywhere.
I see your boyfriend is an employee of a large company
You can't just come to the police station because you're angry...
gentlemen
Is this the place where I need to break off to get here?
never mind
Can you at least take me home today?
This can't go on any longer.
(Balance: 718,916 KRW)
What to do?
(Balance: 718,916 KRW
Payee: Park Min-hwan)
At this time, I was already afraid of breaking up
Do everything according to his wishes.
I have given him a lot of money.
He also used the cash advance feature on my credit card
what to do?
Can't think of a solution
I have already received my retirement benefits.
I want to escape with 700,000 won
Can't even last a month
I'm sorry for yelling at you just now.
-But you're also very wrong
-What?
I really meant what I said just now.
So I plan to make a lot of money from the stock this time
I'm going to buy you a bag.
I got a tip that Roy Gentar was going to buy
madman
If this one goes up, we'll get married.
I want to invest in stocks
You remember Roy Gental back then, right?
Roy Gental?
How could I not have thought of that?
Roy Gental
The only successful thing in Park Min-hwan's life
I figured out a way.
Let's use this to get through this stage first.
Although I can't remember
Everything that has happened since 2013
But I know exactly what will succeed
Give it a try
This time I really want to live a good life
(Scanning progress)
You see
It is not necessary to take a photo
It's just gastritis
It's a little serious. You need to take medicine properly.
Don't be stressed
good
very good
I want to maintain my current health
(“If you want to quit your job, please read this book”)
minister
“There’s nothing wrong with retiring on stocks”
"You want to be a salaried worker until the end of your life?"
"If you want to quit your job, please read this book"
Are you planning to quit your job?
No
Is this
The injury you got yesterday?
Sorry, I didn't notice, what should I do?
If you feel sorry, buy me a meal.
I like to eat soup rice
What's wrong?
What?
You said you wanted to come to Tang Restaurant
I didn't expect it to be this kind of place
Are there any other kinds of soup restaurants?
No
I've never talked to him before, so I didn't notice.
He is very...
Thanks
Feels like a rich young master
Please use it
How about it?
Much better than I thought
You haven't eaten yet?
What are you doing?
I mean soup rice
Thanks
So he is this kind of person?
He is more handsome and considerate than I remembered, and...
Have you been to the doctor?
Yes, I just went to see it.
On the way back, I stopped by the bookstore.
Thank you so much for yesterday
You take me home
I also bought cup noodles and chamomile...
You feel very different from usual.
Do I have it?
Do you really want to quit your job?
I'm actually considering
I feel like I can't go on like this anymore
I feel like it's time to make some changes.
-Are you getting married?
-What?
Because you also bought the interior decoration book
I guess you might be planning to get married.
("Follow the experts to do interior decoration")
Oh, this is...
Indeed, this year I started preparing
Marry Park Min-hwan
I am also considering getting married
I would rather die than get married.
actually…
(Other half)
It doesn't matter
My dear Zhiyuan, please reply immediately when you see this
Why doesn't she answer the phone?
She caused such a commotion in the company yesterday
I only have you, Jiwon
Where is she and what is she doing?
Why don't you answer the phone?
The scars are exactly the same
sorry
I see you seem badly injured.
No
let's go
good
Thank you for the treat
Now you don't owe me anything.
One meal is enough
OK
besides
You are a very capable person.
Although marriage is good, family is also important
But it's a shame you left.
As a boss, I think so
Thanks
Then I'll take my leave first.
good
(Work, instant meal kits, skyrocketing stocks)
(quick cooking meal package)
You are a very capable person.
(Chamomile tea)
Because he always had a stern face before.
I'm afraid of him.
I didn't expect him to be such a nice guy.
How does he know that I am capable?
I forgot all
I am good at doing things
I have a lot of things I want to do in the company.
Things that no longer belong to me after marriage
Since I can't be stronger than Park Min-hwan
So the things that have never been fought for
What Kang Ji-won wants to do
(Kang Ji-won)
She really is
It makes me unhappy again
Why should I suffer like this for Park Min-hwan?
Let's start working quickly.
Ten minutes before work
You should be ready to start working.
I see it all
Work hard, you know?
Kang Ji-won
(Roy Gental)
(Quantity: Full amount)
(Cash purchase)
(Are you sure you want to buy?)
Oh my god, it's up again.
How much will it increase?
Ji Won
I thought you were going to call me last night
What were you doing yesterday?
Me yesterday?
Do you know the MODU community?
I'm looking at that website.
Marriage, husband's family, wife's family
I forgot the time when I saw it.
So that's it
There is a girl who is in the terminal stage of cancer
She saw her husband having sex with her bestie
Oh my god, really? That's crazy.
Crazy, right?
I think her bestie is more disgusting than her husband.
How could she do this to her best friend?
That is to say
She probably meant that her best friend would die anyway.
So it doesn't matter.
If I die, you can take everything I have.
But if you die, I will die with you
-Kang Ji-won
-exist!
When will your runaway brain come back?
Is my proposal that bad?
Is it bad?
It's too good to say that this is bad.
The whole mess
(Proposal for quick-cooking meal kits in the one-person household era)
This proposal was rejected at this time.
However
Zheng Xiumin handed over the proposal without changing a word
But the section chief praised it and implemented it.
Ji Won
This is really good.
How about I make some minor revisions and submit it again?
Zheng Xiumin thus became a full-time employee and was promoted step by step
Is this reasonable?
One-person household? Homemade meal kits?
Living alone, who can cook for themselves?
It's troublesome to fill water and turn on the fire.
But you want to vacuum pack the green onions?
Freeze dried squid?
It takes until midnight just to unpack the packages one by one.
Do you think this makes sense?
The development team will definitely say
"Be yourself and do it"
-What should I do then?
- Section Chief Kim Kyung-wook
He is a rude and incompetent scoundrel.
He's also a relationship expert.
Who is that?
He has a connection with a very famous high-ranking person.
Who am I talking to now?
Agent Jiang
what's on your mind?
Please tell me if there is anything wrong, I will modify it immediately
Women have this problem, they are so dependent
Do your own thing
When you come to work
We should also consider other people's eyes.
How can a girl dress like this?
Agent Yang is a married woman.
You are still a lady.
How can we men survive like this?
This is all because women didn't join the army
Our country should also allow women to serve in the military
Right? Agent Park
Yes, that's right, I will push it forward
Right?
You do it again
Although she is Jin Jingxu's right-hand man
So we hardly talked.
But she's a very capable person.
Because Jin Jingxu blocked her promotion
She was just a permanent agent until she left.
But as usual
She is more than qualified to be a section chief now.
-that…
-Agent Yang
Section Chief Jin is looking for you
Very good
- Let's talk
- I have nothing to say
I have…
hateful
Oh my god
careful
Are you okay? You suddenly ran out
What's going on? Just now it seemed...
I'm fine, I'm sorry.
sorry
I'm sure I feel the same
And it's the same place
No
This is impossible, what am I thinking?
Hello
Hello, Kang Ji-won, hey!
Hello, Kang Ji-won
How are you?
I was still injured after all
Injury in the same area
Although I avoided it, I still couldn't avoid it
Then I won't...
don't want
But my scars are gone.
I used to be afraid that I was pregnant and I was shaking with worry.
I knocked over the coffee pot and got burned.
What does this mean? I should be able to figure it out.
(Marketing Team 1, Park Min-hwan
Send a photo)
(Sell)
(Park Min-hwan, Roy Gentar)
(Roy Gental
Sold the day before: 81,415)
You sold Roy Gental?
Let's Talk
Are you ignoring me?
What kind of demeanor is this?
Hey, I sold my stock.
To pay you back
I have transferred the money to you, please confirm it
If TKU Technology surges
I will make more money, so I don't regret it.
But you have to remember that I sold the skyrocketing stocks for you
You are that kind of person
TKU Technology?
Regarding the so-called TKU list
Members of the ruling and opposition parties…
Even I, who don’t know much about stocks, know about TKU Technology
It is a famous hype stock.
After the company boss hyped up the stock
Flee abroad, stocks are delisted
He actually sold Roy Gental, which was skyrocketing
Bought TKU which will plummet?
Because I bought Roy Gental
So Park Min-hwan sold it
Marketing team came to the meeting
Remember to bring your new product survey information
good
Oh my god, it's up again.
Hey, I sold my stock.
What is supposed to happen will eventually happen
How is your injury?
But just let it happen.
No matter who it happens to
You're always getting hurt and that makes me worried.
I almost had a heart attack.
Are you listening to me?
Xiumin
I have trash to throw away
Can you help me throw it away?
What are you talking about?
Please
You are my other half
Okay
You're going to date me this weekend.
I found a delicious barbecue restaurant.
Guse Pavilion
OK, let's go
As long as you help me take out the trash
good
Agent Jiang Zhiyuan, clerk Zheng Xiumin, please come over quickly
You covet my garbage
Then you handle it.
Marry my husband.
I need someone to steal my destiny
If anyone stole my destiny, it should be you
Kang Ji-won is so boring
So annoying
It's not that I don't know
As long as it doesn't suit your taste, you will be scheming
Because you are very capable, Agent Park
What perfume do you use?
You're dead today.
You two love each other to death
I will help you get results quickly.
Do you have any dates this weekend?
You are the priority
Just remember that you owe me a favor.
You are here because of Liu Zhihe
Are you saying you want to break up with me? That crazy old man
I won't be bullied anymore.
Translated by: Peng Xiangfen