I used to...
Like you!
So
I…
Feel sorry
(Minister Liu Zhihe)
- Hello? Minister?
- Sorry for calling you on a weekend night
But I think I need your help
Do you have time to help?
It is about the group's publicity budget
I'm at the Winton Hotel
Hello? Agent Jiang?
Oh, okay
I should be there in 30 minutes.
OK, see you later.
good
Sorry, I really have to go.
Oh, okay
Can that
Can you tell me your phone number?
Wait
I'm leaving first
goodbye
Episode 4
The minister never seemed to come to me unexpectedly on weekends.
Sorry, I'm late
I'm not late, thank you for coming.
I'm sure this has never happened before
We walked and talked
Winner Planning is currently holding an exhibition
They proposed to convert the group's marketing expenses into
A considerable amount of money has been transferred to online marketing
- There will be a big change in the promotion strategy
- A very bold proposal
This means that the proportion of online marketing will increase.
However, the group's conservative
Many people think it's too early
How can I help?
Support my opinion
This is NurTV, it's amazing
This will become a
A platform used by all age groups
Wow, this...
I sensed an opportunity
But someone may have a different idea
Minister Liu, you are here.
Sorry, I'm late.
This is Agent Jiang Zhiyuan from the Marketing Team.
So at this time
U&K's whack-a-mole bully is still in the company?
Don't you know who I am?
Known as the whack-a-mole manager
Video of violence against flight attendant on plane
The post went viral on social media, causing quite a stir
What are you looking at? Is there anything good to see?
Good morning
It's amazing to see you here...
I mean it's an honor.
Minister Liu, you really understand
Hire such a beautiful female employee
It's fun to work, right?
I remember
Jin Jingxu's backer is the general manager of whack-a-mole
They really look alike.
For you, work would be boring.
I want you to be nicer to Ji Won.
Hello, are you really a contract employee of U&K?
Who said that? Ji-won?
Yes, Ji-won said you were a contract employee.
She is an agent
While we're on this subject, show us your business card.
Kang Ji-won is an agent, so what are you?
I'm just an ordinary employee.
Ji-won gets promoted quickly
- I will soon...
- Are you kidding?
You put her in the company.
How could she be promoted faster than you?
You were introduced to the company by someone you know.
But he taught me autobiography and interview skills
How about asking me to treat you to a meal?
You said that big companies have to go through
First, second and third round interviews
Each one has to deal with it differently
Even if these
But what about your past relationship with Eun-ho?
Eun-ho cannot be contacted
Why on earth did you come to the class reunion?
You guys are still talking about this?
That was when I was a kid.
We are both 31 years old now.
-Don't mention it again
- Are you kidding?
We have been fooled by your lies.
Did you really give Ji-won a fake item?
That's not Jiwon learning from you.
You gave her that
It's obviously fake stuff.
How come she even said something like that?
Have you been trying to frame her all along?
Why would I do that?
I'm Jiwon's friend.
indeed
Jiang Zhiyuan was scolded throughout high school
It's all because of you.
You said he coveted your man and imitated your dressing style
I want everything from you
You are the one who is whining there all day long!
I didn't ask you to scold her.
You guys bullied her yourselves, why are you blaming me?
Really creative.
Crazy Woman
I'm going to the toilet
- Really
-Oh my god
When did I ask them to scold her?
Why blame me?
A bunch of rotten people
(Other half)
The number you dialed cannot be answered...
hateful
Why did Bai Enhao show up now?
Ouch
Is this a joke?
Why should I pay you?
Do I have to see it before I can decide?
sorry
But this is quite…
Pretty good...
I haven't been to this site before.
What's good about it? It's all pornographic stuff
It seems that the target audience is set very accurately
That's called an algorithm
It's probably because this is your first time visiting that website.
What?
When I first visited the site
There was also "That Guy is Delicious"
I think it was to attract attention at the beginning.
That’s why I recommend more sensational content first.
After using it for a long time
We will recommend content that interests you.
That function is very useful.
You don't have to see things that you are not interested in.
Hello
You just need to stand there and smile, just be a vase
Why are you so arrogant and talkative?
Her name is not "Hey", she is Agent Kang Ji-won
What? Minister Liu
I want to hear from this promising employee
So I bring her here even on weekends
No, I...
Minister Liu is praising you
Yeah, this is the first time I heard him say that.
Minister Liu...
It's hard to get close to people, and I won't keep people around.
Of course, good people who can do things should be kept around
Were you laughing? Are you crazy?
Do you have a brain?
minister
Thank you for speaking well for me just now
Because you are a nice person
If it's not good, I won't say that.
You said you can get girls by going camping
sure
You can't even get your girlfriend.
After failing to seek love, Park Min went home and changed
What else? Is your wife any different?
My wife only thinks about me.
As long as I leave home
She would keep calling and texting me
Say something like "I miss you so much, what are you doing?"
"Have you eaten yet?" I'm so annoyed
Once upon a time
I really can't understand
I was only out for five minutes.
- She called me right away
- What is this? It's delicious.
-Isn't that delicious?
-Um
My wife prepared it for me.
She told me to stop drinking coffee and use delicious food to wake me up
very nice
It's different from your girlfriend who doesn't look for you.
hateful
I think your girlfriend has another man.
And keep you for marriage
You're not the only one who can do this.
You don't understand at all
She doesn't have that ability.
You figure it out...
Damn
You lunatic, why did you take them all?
Because it tastes good, I want to use this to pick up girls
-parking
- Really
Get in the car
No, it's okay.
It matters to me
You come to work on weekends
I heard nonsense that I didn't need to hear.
I even thought I should treat you to a meal.
If you keep looking at my face
We're going to have dinner.
What's wrong?
Because that's all you're sorry about.
Someone who is really mean to me.
But I don't feel sorry for me at all
Don't be too used to cooperating with others
good
I learned not to be nice to people who are mean to me.
But I will be twice as good to good people
Good idea
Now you just need
Just be able to recognize the eyes of a good person.
How do you know I don't judge people?
I thought I had, but I didn't.
It looks like that.
So what do you think I am?
Good Guy
It seems that I am not completely blind.
But
Is “That Guy is Delicious” good?
no
I just wanted to save face for the general manager.
But what you said feels very real
Tell me, should I watch it?
It's not like that, really.
I didn't watch it either.
So unfair
I think you should watch it carefully.
I'm really wronged.
I really haven't seen it
(Other half)
(Remind me later, one hour later)
(Reject call)
If you have an appointment, I can take you there.
No
Sorry, I said I would wait.
But I contacted you again.
Because I haven't seen you for a long time, I can't calm down
Looks like someone said something interesting.
A friend of mine
who?
He is my classmate
I went to a class reunion today.
We exchanged phone numbers after a long separation.
Seeing childhood friends I haven't seen for a long time
It will be fun for a while indeed.
Even though it's all in the past
I used to like him very much
He is my first love
that…
Seeing your first love again may bring back old feelings
But people say it's dangerous
So let the past feelings go...
Not that kind of feeling
I have a boyfriend now
(Park Min-hwan)
(Remind me later, one hour later)
(Reject call)
Agent Jiang
Um?
Recently, even cats and dogs are driving good cars
You shouldn't be able to see inside the car from outside.
No
I'm not because of that
-Don't you want to be seen?
-No, why wouldn't I want to?
Xiumin?
Park Agent
What's going on? Why are you here?
that…
What?
That...
What's wrong?
Um?
There seems to be something wrong
The password is the date when Ji-won and I started dating
Isn’t it?
June 22, yes
I'll call Ji-won to check.
She doesn't answer the phone
The number you dialed cannot be answered...
She's not usually like this.
It doesn't matter
I'll continue waiting outside
Don't be like this. I'm here to see Ji Won, too.
But this...
This is really...
Let's go get something hot nearby and chat.
Tell me what's going on.
Stop crying
So shall we go out?
good
The minister noticed that I was behaving strangely.
How should I explain this?
Thanks
Really delicious, and warm
Since I and Park Min-hwan are agents
They are recognized as office lovers
You probably have a lot of questions.
But this is my private life, I don't want to explain
That's it
Although I want to ask, but if you don't want to say it, don't say it
As long as you're making a decision that's good for you
That's enough
I can be sure of this.
I've recently realized something
I have always been cooperating with others
So I don’t know myself very well
So you know something about yourself?
I'm learning
I am also writing a project for a quick-cooking meal package
Quick cooking meal kit?
right
Show me when you finish writing.
No
I'm looking forward to it, better sooner rather than later
If that's the case
good
What else do you want to do?
I also want to...
I also want to do interior decoration
I also want to learn self-defense
Self-defense? You want me to teach you?
Do you want me to learn self-defense?
Why do you react this way?
No
It feels very different from your image.
Is it a long way off? I used to be a sports person.
Judo, Aikido, Special Martial Arts
Taekwondo, Muay Thai, Kickboxing…
Really
I've had this feeling since last time.
Would you consider wearing contact lenses?
(Dried pollack, grilled pollack)
Drink slowly, or you'll get drunk.
I don't know why things have become so complicated.
I'm so afraid that Jiwon will misunderstand
No
You also know Ji Won is not that kind of person
She's been a little weird lately.
I feel like she's getting farther and farther away from me
Our relationship isn't like that. It shouldn't be like that.
She is indeed a little strange
Wait, is there really something going on between her and Yoo Ji Hyuk?
Impossible
Kang Ji Won will like me
She understands a man's appearance and style
She must be busy with work recently.
She is a deadbeat.
Only think about one thing at a time
-Is that really the case?
-Of course
No one doesn't know
What's your relationship with her?
Should that be the case?
right
Fortunately, I met you, Agent Park
If it weren't for you, I would definitely be very sad today
Thank you so much
You are the best, so handsome
No
Not handsome
this…
arrive
Thank you for driving me back
- I'm in
-Do you want me to walk you to your door?
What?
No
Ms. Kang Ji-won
I think before getting married
Try to get in touch with more people.
You're more open than I thought.
I wasn't originally, but now I'm starting to...
wrong
I won't do this from now on.
I don't think you have to get married anyway.
You seem to be a non-marriageist.
No, I want to get married.
So what I want to say is...
that…
oops
Really
minister
It's nice to see you smile
Interior decoration proposal for the happiness of benefactors
She's so cute
If you want to do all of this, I recommend moving.
move place
This is also a good idea
(Other half)
(missed call)
I can't contact you
I really don't know about the class reunion
Why do students behave like that?
I know if I told you in advance that it was a class reunion
You won't come
I just want to find a way to solve it.
I think this matter should not be discussed via text message or phone call
We'll talk tomorrow
(Park Min-hwan)
Ji Won
Xiumin is crying now
It sounds like you guys have a misunderstanding.
Where are you?
Fortunately, you are with her.
Please take care of her and send her home.
I have mixed feelings and need time to think
-Are you okay?
-And you?
Well, I'm fine.
After all, I can't do this for a long time.
So you two should get married soon, please!
-Hello?
-oh
I'm not an impatient person.
But I still called you
Sorry, I got home late and couldn't call you.
Oh, no, it won't be late.
I'm a little anxious.
But it feels a bit strange to talk to you on the phone like this
Is that so?
Have we never talked on the phone?
Yes, you want me to stop following you...
fine
What's up?
No...No
Don't say
How many times are you going to say no?
Okay
You asked me not to talk to you anymore.
That's why it's like this
Hello! Kang Ji-won
What happened to me?
You really shouldn't do that.
Don't talk to me anymore.
What happened to him? I didn't say anything.
Sorry, Ji-won.
I told him you were interested in him.
Did I like him making him so unhappy?
That's because you rejected me harshly
I reject you?
yes
I still have that letter.
-letter?
-right
Your reply
I wanted to throw it away, but I couldn't.
So you wrote to me and confessed
And did I reply?
Have you forgotten?
I wrote a letter to confess to you
Stayed up late
Oh, forget it.
- Eun Ho
-Um?
Should we meet?
You can bring
Is my reply coming?
Why hasn't she come yet? She usually comes early.
Agent Jiang, what's going on?
I thought you were an artist.
What day is today?
No, that's not the case.
Wow, you are so beautiful
Actually, Xiyan and I went shopping on Sunday
So by the way...
well done
Right? You're so beautiful.
-Ji Won
- What's going on? Get out of the way.
Honey
Are you really my girlfriend?
I can hardly recognize it.
I want to give you a surprise
It scares me
Honey
You look like a different person without glasses, very beautiful
You talk like you've never seen it.
She doesn't wear glasses.
Ouch
How could I not have seen it?
It just looks different.
It's really different
What?
Feel sorry
Minister, I'll clean up.
I'll leave it to you.
Hmm? But...
Today you...
I don't look like I'm dressed for work.
What?
Oh, I...
Looks perfect for work, why...
Are you going to blame her?
Maybe I haven't seen her without glasses.
That's the feeling
Then I'm sorry.
Did you watch it yesterday?
What?
Yesterday was the weekend, and it was the first time I saw it at work.
I noticed you were wearing contact lenses too.
Oh, yeah
minister
That's much more handsome.
No wonder it feels a little different
Looks good…
that…
Do you guys go get contact lenses together?
What are you talking about?
Why…
Aren't you going back to your seat?
No
Don't do this
Agent Park, you are awesome.
We are discussing Agent Jiang
Agent Park, you have a really good eye.
No one knew that Agent Jiang was such a beautiful woman
You don't know, she is a beauty.
- I think you need to defend well.
-What?
Many people in our group said
Having a goalkeeper doesn't mean there won't be goals
Seo Jin-su
He has been talking about Agent Jiang all day today
That's right
Oh, no.
The ball doesn't like this.
That ball only has me in its eyes...
here
What's the matter?
I'm going out on a business trip later.
It doesn't matter for a while.
This is for you. Have some coffee.
Thanks
Did you take a break?
How are you feeling?
I was not good on Friday.
Attending the class reunion
Are you feeling better?
that…
Speaking of which…
What happened to you meeting with Liu Zhihe yesterday?
Oh, that one
I'm sorry for always taking advantage of the minister.
He has something urgent to ask me to come over
That's why I left the class reunion in a hurry.
That guy is such a jerk.
I see Liu Zhihe
Seems to be interested in you
That's not the case.
No, as a man I know
This is male instinct.
Regardless of whether it is urgent or not, why should he look for you?
He also had an issue with your outfit this morning.
Because you are so beautiful
It made him crazy
It's so annoying
Say
You are so beautiful today
You are so beautiful, a bunch of flies are staring at you
Makes me so angry
I should be the only one who can see it.
You are mine, right?
What's this?
There's something here
Oh my God, what should I do?
What should I do? Go to the toilet immediately.
Go to the toilet quickly.
My underwear is wet
Borrow
Ji Won
You wouldn't misunderstand me, would you?
I really don't know why they do that.
That was more than ten years ago. How naive!
How could I not believe you?
If I hadn't seen the ending, I might
Don't believe you?
I might have misspoken.
You know I often make mistakes.
Well, I was a little angry yesterday.
But after I thought about it, I found it strange
You have no reason to lie
Pretend you're dating Eunho
And I want you to break up with Eun-ho
Unless you want to bully me
Makes me look like a freak
But
It's crazy for anyone to do that.
Yeah, I can't do that.
Xia Ruizhi and his gang
In the past, he often bullied me with strange excuses.
Now it seems it's your turn.
Um
But I won't let it go.
We are not in high school anymore.
I want to meet with Enhao and ask him clearly
Are you going to meet Eun-ho?
Yes, he gave me his phone number yesterday and said he wanted to meet
Don't worry, my significant other.
this time
I really won't let it go.
good
But will Min-hwan be unhappy?
If you meet another man
Min Hwan is not that kind of person
He said I'm happy.
besides
The stock market has soared recently and he has made a lot of money.
Are stocks rising sharply?
He wants me to look forward to our new home.
very nice
It's been a while since you got off work on time, right?
Isn't that right? Agent Jiang
I haven't gotten off work early in a long time.
Anyone want to go eat fried chicken?
I have to pick up the kids.
I have to meet a client.
-I can…
- Really
The company should give Jiwon a bonus
You're the one doing the work
Excuse me
Feel sorry
This hairstyle really suits you
Everyone is talking about you today
Everyone said they envied Agent Park
No
Agent Jiang, you and Agent Park are a perfect match.
So envious
Agent Jiang
Yes, Minister.
Why are you dressed like this for work today?
Do I look weird today?
No, that's not the case.
It's ok, I shouldn't ask
Because you are considering wearing contact lenses
So I wore it today.
So I want to know if you are doing this for someone too
Or because of someone's relationship?
This makes me feel good.
This is the first time I dress like this, and I feel very happy.
And because I dress like this
Other people's attitudes toward me have also changed.
It's not that you shouldn't dress like that.
Has the attitude towards you changed?
That's right
But there are people like this
I want to deal with people like this
This is how it should be done
Start now
I won't be so foolish as to stick to just one form anymore
For myself
For yourself?
right
But you look really different when you smile
I hope you can smile more often in the future
besides
Although I still don't quite understand
But make some changes in clothing style
It should be better
I recommend you do this, then I'll take my leave.
right
Don't be so foolish as to stick to just one form
Hello? Where are you?
I'll leave it to you, Agent Jiang.
You can take the bus in front of the shopping mall
OK, thank you for your hard work.
Because you are considering wearing contact lenses
So I wore it today.
Liu Zhihe seems to be interested in you
Oh yeah, I bought it!
This is mine!
It's Hee Yeon
Oh yeah!
What's wrong with her?
Hee Yeon…
What are you doing?
-How did you do that?
- I'm very happy
Oh yeah, this is mine.
Okay, I know you are happy, stop making trouble
Thanks
I will never forget
You gave me this limited edition favor
I would also appreciate it if you could calm down.
-Please
-Wait a minute
Rumor has it that the Minister and Hee-yeon had an affair
(Personnel changes, staff Liu Xiyan)
Kim Kyung-wook claimed that they had an improper relationship
So she was transferred.
No wonder
That's why we always meet
Because Xiyan and I became familiar with each other
I didn't expect this.
Oh my god
It almost happened.
Park Min-hwan is a useless guy
What is male intuition?
Minister Hee Yeon
Are boyfriend and girlfriend
Sure enough, the heirs of U&K are different.
I always have to queue up to get in.
I went straight to the VIP room.
"What did you say you wanted?
Give her everything she wants."
That's what he said
- You are excited
-I haven't been this happy in a long time.
And he pretended to be uninterested in brand names
Really handsome, grandpa
There are always a lot of things I want to buy
I looked at clothes, bags and shoes
I want my brother to buy them all for me
I bought clothes, bags, shoes and coats.
Anyway, it's my brother who swipes the card
He bought them all for me, which is really cool.
I want to stay longer.
I'm sorry to leave so early.
It doesn't matter
-Hello, Director Lee
-Um
You stay with grandpa all day.
What should the Strategic Planning Office do?
Because he is my right-hand man.
No, I am grandpa's right-hand man.
Grandpa, please take care of your health.
I'll see you again
OK, come play again.
-The same to you
-good
-Brother, will you take me back?
- We're going in opposite directions
What are you talking about? Of course you have to give her a ride
It’s so late, you want her to go back by herself?
- Get in the car now
- Grandpa, I'm leaving.
good
Goodbye Grandpa
Have you asked about that woman?
I put the information in your study.
(Bomb me)
Brother Zhihe?
Hello?
Now?
If you want to teach girls self-defense
Is judo really the best?
You treat him like this
Is it to teach others self-defense?
Wait, that hurts.
You've worked hard
He's so ruthless
Every time my dad gives me pocket money
Draw a love heart
Yes, I know
I didn't expect it to be so difficult
But I can't tell the truth
Makes everything complicated
What would you do?
Should I tell Ji-won everything?
Tell her that Park Min Hwan will have an affair with Jung Soo Min
Then hurt her
No, if I were to say
I had to tell her
I'm living my second life
Will she believe it? I can't believe it myself.
I still haven't figured out what's going on.
(April 13, 2023)
Mr. Park Min-hwan, you are suspected of murdering Kang Ji-won
We're going to arrest you.
Ms. Zheng Xiumin, please come with us
What?
hateful
stop!
Why?
Why are you taking me away?
Why do you have to do this? Let me go
You can exercise your right to remain silent
Everything you say will be used as evidence in court
-Did you hear that clearly?
-What do you mean by murder? How could I have killed anyone?
How could I kill someone?
It was an accident, at most it was manslaughter!
Okay?
Anyway, if I leave her alone, she will die.
Anyway, you have this suspicion
Zheng Xiumin was also arrested as an accomplice
If you have something to say, please go to the police station.
-What?
-take away
Why are you taking me away?
I didn't, it wasn't me
Take it away
-I didn't, I didn't kill him!
-Let me go!
Let me go!
What's going on?
So Zheng Xiumin
Are you having an affair with Kang Ji-won’s husband?
It's really exaggerated.
But how dare she
You suddenly want us to come over?
To be honest, I came here because I felt bad.
Was that ten years ago?
We held a class reunion at Guse Pavilion
At that time, it seemed that we were too harsh on her.
Yes, Ji-won really wants Xiu-min
Break up with Bai Enhao?
- I don't know
-Ji Won
say what?
Eun-ho? Why are you here?
Hey, come here quickly, it's a mess here
What were you talking about?
Don't mention your ex-girlfriend Zheng Xiumin
-She conspired with Ji-won’s husband…
-etc
I have never dated Zheng Xiumin
Really?
You really haven't dated?
What I heard about Kang Ji-won's life that day
Leave me speechless
then
I regret everything madly
But…
I got a second chance
(April 19, 2013)
Looking back, I had a few chances.
But this time it's different
I am in a good mood indeed.
Ji-won, I tell you, men
All will cheat
Min-hwan, you need to take care of Ji-won
If something has changed
Things that weren't a problem before
It may become a problem
Where did you go after get off work? Tell me the truth.
I'm worried that Park Min-hwan will hurt you
Are you crazy?
minister!
Translated by: Peng Xiangfen