Kang Ji-won
Kang Ji Won!
Damn it!
Why did you hit me? It hurts.
You are the one who is wrong, how dare you lose your temper?
- Like a little kid. - What's wrong with me?
How dare you say that?
Why would you bring someone with such poor manners?
Jiang Zhiyuan was originally a very well-behaved person
She must have been possessed by some evil spirit recently, I don’t know what’s going on!
Ouch
You, the guy who got beaten by a woman, only has a mouth left
See the big picture from the small details
How many times have I said that family education is important?
You didn't listen to me and did this.
How are you going to deal with it?
-Ouch. - What are you going to do?
Oh, my god!
Oh, mom doesn't understand at all, damn it.
Jiang Zhiyuan is crazy, what can I do?
Jiang Zhiyuan, you are dead.
Jiang Zhiyuan, come out!
You don't think that things can just end like this, do you?
I am too tolerant of you, and you have no self-awareness to act insolently in front of me
I know you're in there, come out
Come out, come out!
Hello…
My benefactor, what's the matter with the way you are dressed?
Am I doing something wrong?
Are you going to punish me? It seems a bit wild
No, that's not the case.
I have something to return today.
Then this outfit is suitable
- So did you succeed? - Yes
This is my brother's first time visiting someone else's new home.
I told him that the housewarming gift should be toilet paper roll and laundry detergent
But I don't know when he prepared the flowers.
I like flowers
Oh my god, what?
Who is so rude to yell at someone's door?
Wait, here...
This is number 410, right?
-You are Ji-won's brother... -What are you talking about? Explain it to me clearly.
Oh, ok, hello
Sir, you are exercising.
This is my girlfriend's house...
I must have made a mistake.
girlfriend?
The former tenant was indeed a girl.
etc.
Former tenant?
This is just the right size for a new home.
But why rent it?
Agent Park clearly boasted that a man should have his own house
I heard you want to pay rent to my brother.
Don't pay
He won't know whether you have paid or not, he doesn't even check the account
Anyway, this was supposed to be my place to live.
These are two different things.
There are many houses in other places, why choose here?
It's too inconvenient to live in the same building with my boss at work.
Is this for the bedroom?
Yes, thank you.
Don't get too tired of organizing
-Goodbye. -Go carefully.
Goodbye, Hee-yeon
You go
Even if you were born in a position where you can't live your life as you wish
But I still think that political marriages are not right in the 21st century.
So when you cancelled your engagement with Oh Yoo Ra, I thought you were finally acting like a human being.
Was there any other reason why you called off the engagement?
Brother, I mean if
If you are someone very important to me
If you have ulterior motives...
What are you worried about?
Are you afraid of what I might do to Kang Ji-won?
that…
What can I do? She's getting married.
That's right, go home.
elder brother
I have nothing to do with Jiang Zhiyuan and I can't do anything
She's a good person and I really want to help her.
I also thank her for loving you so much. Are you satisfied?
You go
But it was the first time I saw him show that expression
hateful
Park Agent
What’s wrong with you?
-How was your weekend? -Very good.
you look beautiful
Hello, Kang Ji-won, you...
Are you crazy?
- What's going on? - Oh my god.
Why do you keep hitting me?
You really are...
Let's stop here, both of you.
When I was beaten, you didn't move.
Why are you so unfair?
Do you like fairness so much that you want to share your love equally between two women?
Agent Jiang, come out with me
Please wait a moment
What needs to be said about the cheating bastards
- What? - Underwear?
Who is this for?
I found it in your car.
How can you just flip over someone else's car?
How dare the cheating guy be so loud?
Park Min-hwan is so exaggerated
-He cheated on Kang Ji Won -Cheating?
You know Park Min-hwan, right?
Marketing Group
-I heard he cheated on me.-Is that true?
And still in the car...
What?
In the car? In the car?
Big news!
God
Has the news reached the HR department?
This is really great news.
Really
What should they do?
"A couple who had been dating for seven years, the man cheated on her
The woman threw her underwear and things got out of control.”
He was going to beat Agent Jiang
-Stopped by Minister Liu-Red Underwear
Ladies and Gentlemen, U&K Representatives
I'm back
Red underwear
This is a weekend drama.
I don't watch TV, this is enough
That's why Kang Ji-won treated my mom like that.
What should I do?
It's scary when a nice person goes crazy.
How come you can’t even take care of your underwear?
That's not mine
What?
Isn't that your underwear?
But I've only been with you in the car in my life
If that pair of underwear wasn't yours, how did it end up in my car?
How could such a weird thing happen?
What's going on?
Whose underwear is that?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Damn
I knew you'd take the bait, Park Min-hwan
Although it's not Zheng Xiumin's
But I picked out the style you like.
How are you?
What is going on?
Excuse me
Hello? Eunho
I am in the company
I'll call you later
good
I met my parents yesterday at Eun-ho's restaurant.
He must be worried about me after seeing me break up.
Yesterday?
So you knew this before you met the parents?
Is that why you dress like that?
You should tell us
You must be sad on your own
But do you know who the other party is?
This is unreasonable.
How could Kang Ji-won have found that pair of underwear if she didn’t take my car yesterday?
I'm going to ask her
Ask her where she found her underwear? Either way, you are a cheating man.
Damn it, really!
Stop shouting!
You just fell in love
Although it is wrong, it is understandable
People's hearts will change
She should be more attractive.
That's great.
Look who this is.
Isn’t this the excellent agent Kang Ji-won who takes care of all the company’s affairs by herself?
Section Chief!
Oh, Chief.
-Today is a good day for you to start over.-That guy is really...
Because of her appearance
-Only men can't stand cheating-Okay
Really
Men, they all look at women's performance
Even if I were to date a fox, I would never date a bear.
- That's a man. - Yeah.
good
haven't seen you for a long time
In this era, even if you get married, you will get divorced.
You just follow your heart
So don't care about other people's opinions.
We must not waver.
You seem to have made a mistake.
Zheng Xiumin
You are not suitable for marriage
Jiang Zhiyuan graduated from Korea University
I have saved a lot of money and I am very capable in living.
But what about you?
You are not only beautiful
Anything else?
Do you have it?
Sleeping with you? I admit, it felt good.
But realistically, I'm not in my 20s anymore and I'm not crazy
Why would I want to marry you?
You should be self-aware
What?
how?
Hello!
you…
You bastard!
What?
-Hey! -What's going on?
Section Chief
Chief, oh
How could you do this to Xiumin?
How could you?
How could you? Let go. How could you do this to Xiumin?
How could you do this to her?
Chief, come over here.
What's wrong with you? Stop it.
Xiumin
Let me go!
How could you do this to Xiumin?
Come on, Chief.
So the person Park Min-hwan cheated with was Jung Soo-min, right?
That best friend of Kang Ji-won?
Oh my god, it's like a jungle.
How can it happen in the company...
How? What happened?
-Big news-Come here quickly
What's wrong?
Park Min-hwan and…
- Jung Soo Min? - You know?
- You know? - Yes.
They have been good friends since junior high school.
Isn’t that too exaggerated?
Ji Won is so pitiful
U Food Cheating Legend
-That's what I mean-Underwear Park!
Underwear Park?
I really want to quit
Cheating Girlfriend
Pretending to work overtime to stay and have an affair
U Food Cheating Legend
The Other Half
Ji-won, have you moved?
I think we should talk
I'm at your house now
You don't believe what others say, do you?
You have to trust me
Liyou Foods Quick Cooking Meal Pack Tasting
This is a video footage shot by an on-site investigator at a supermarket last weekend.
But there is one part that worries me a little
So I want you to take a look
Is Liyou Foods holding a promotion for quick-cooking meal packs?
Should we set up a stall as well?
But where are our products displayed?
Didn't see it
Look
Like this, it's completely tucked in the back.
The results of the last food tasting were quite good. I thought it would be displayed at the front.
Park Min-hwan is the agent of Marketing Team 1, and Jung Soo-min is the staff member
U&K Bermuda Park Triangle's Shameless Behavior
Someone saw them pretending to work overtime and staying
Secret date in the office
I was scared to death!
How could you get into such trouble?
Even if you get into trouble, how can you hide it?
What? What is…
Joe's supermarket, because of not informing the allergens, there was an accident
Why didn't you report this?
How do you know?
Not only did you not apologize to Trader Joe's, you loudly accused their employees of being at fault?
Yeah, but that's the fact.
When we were gone for a while, the supermarket staff started the food tasting activity.
You two?
Why did both of them leave?
that…
The responsible persons are Park Min-hwan agent and Jung Soo-min staff
Dog mongrel
Really a bastard
No
What are you guys thinking about?
Ji Won
Park Min-hwan seems to be handling the customer part well.
The problem is that there is no report
that…
Girlfriend's best friend, cheating, beast
I'm doing that even during work hours.
Banned words: Park Min-hwan, Bermuda…
Now everyone also shares the marketing team's news through the company's email
So I will first put "Park Agent, Park Min-hwan Bermuda Park" etc.
Set as banned words
Oh, and "Underpants Park"
Company emails containing prohibited language cannot be sent
Messages cannot be sent
This should avoid being discussed within the company.
However
This protection will only take effect after you accept the department transfer
Department transfer?
In this case, it will be difficult for you to become a full-time employee.
Although the contract has not expired
The company has specially considered your situation and allowed you to work until today.
Do you agree?
Female staff lounge
Ji-won, answer the phone.
MODU Topics
Our company's B guy cheated on his girlfriend A's best friend C, and the two got into trouble again in Joe's supermarket
To be honest, men can't resist the temptation of women.
Why is everyone scolding me?
Why should they? They don't know me.
Ji-won and I...Ji-won...
The Other Half
How is this possible?
The company also has a system
How can I be the agent and Yang Zhulan be the section chief?
Agent Yang Zhulan is successfully carrying out the quick-cooking meal package project which might otherwise be idle.
She is a talent that the company is very grateful for.
On the contrary, in addition to the relevant cases, you are
Absenteeism, gender sensitivity and peer evaluations are very disappointing
this…
I have never read sexually sensitive publications in the company
This is a notification
If you don't accept it, I'll take it as your intention to resign.
Section Chief, Kim Kyung-wook
Damn it, hey, Yang Zhulan!
Please help me change my seat.
yes
Agent Yang
Printing room
You can't smoke here...
Oh, it's not
what are you doing here?
This is where I go when I want to be alone and think quietly.
A company is a place to work
This is not a place for you to think.
Didn't you come here just to be alone and think quietly?
You are not the kind of person who would go to the warehouse to pick up printed materials yourself.
You...
Pretend to understand
Do you care more about the other person?
The type who becomes colder the more he speaks?
U&K Talent Development Institute
I think I can recognize people quickly
People who judge others hastily
I personally really hate your type.
You don't look very happy about being promoted to section chief.
If it's because of Kim Kyung Wook, you don't have to care
Based on your performance, you should have been promoted to section chief long ago.
In the performance, the cooking kits should account for a large proportion this time, right?
This is a project that Kang Ji-won represented.
From idea, planning to execution
If someone deserves to be promoted to section chief based on this
That should be Agent Jiang.
After speaking it out, I feel much more relaxed.
Please use this as a reference for personnel decisions
Isn’t Jin Jingxu also…
Will you be promoted to section chief based on your business plan?
You are the type who suffers
I think I can recognize people quickly
People who judge others hastily
I personally like this type
If what they say is true
You are right.
I am the victim
It feels more comfortable to be a sucker
Why do you need to tell HR this?
We do the work together.
I also think you deserve the promotion.
I don't like the feeling of being sorry.
I always felt that it was awkward for me to be a team leader.
This project is yours
I'm sorry, when Chief Jin said he wanted to exclude you
I should correct him immediately.
After working with you, I realized
What a good person you are
And how much fun it is to work with good people
Although I don't know what decision the HR will make
But to me, you are the best
To me, you are much better
Agent Jiang
I think you should go to the first floor.
What?
Tell Jiang Zhiyuan to come out!
Why stop us?
I almost died
Who is Jiang Zhiyuan? How could she say such a thing?
I wonder if she knows what she's talking about.
Doesn't the fact that she disclosed that she is from the marketing team and used her real name mean that she is very confident?
- Then why are you stopping us? - Please calm down.
Hello
I am Jiang Zhiyuan, the agent of the marketing team.
-Oh- Are you Kang Ji-won?
Oh yeah
Hey, do you think we are playing dead just to get free compensation?
Do you think allergies are a joke?
We didn't say anything more if you guys didn't do your job well.
My husband almost died.
He almost died.
Excuse me, can I see your cell phone?
Hello everyone
I am Kang Ji-won, the key figure in the UK&K scandal
Since I am shaking, I will just explain
First of all, there is a misunderstanding about the triangle relationship.
It is true that the person I am going to marry falls in love with my friend
But my friend did not respond to his pursuit
She was a very charming person.
I'm trying to accept that this is inevitable.
The thing about Joe's supermarket is totally typical
The example of a bad customer who wanted free compensation
Eat the food you tasted without looking at it carefully
This is something that someone with severe allergies would never do, right?
My innocent friend is being blamed
It makes me feel very painful
Kang Ji-won
What on earth were you thinking when you uploaded this kind of article?
This is not the article I wrote
But the handwriting is mine.
Among the people I know
There is a person whose handwriting is exactly like mine.
Zheng Xiumin, stop!
Ji Won
I won't let it go easily this time.
You clean up the mess you made.
Wait, Ji-won
Ji Won
Why are you doing this? Don't
Don't forget how much you know about me
How much do I know about you?
MODU community, U&K Foods agent Jiang Zhiyuan
Why use someone else's name?
As an employee of U&K
I'm very sorry about this.
But someone else should apologize to you.
Wife
She is the girl from before.
Girls who are with Park Agent or someone else
So that was fabricated?
She stole her friend's boyfriend and used her friend's name to open an account to defend herself
Because no one would believe her in her own name
I'm really sorry
Due to the situation…
Going in a very bad direction
So I went too far in order to justify myself.
I definitely don't mean to scold you two.
I know you must be very unhappy, but I didn't think that far ahead.
It's all my fault. I was wrong. I'm sorry.
Miss
sorry
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
I really feel like I'm going crazy
I know I shouldn't do this.
But…
I've been having a lot of mood swings lately.
I know I'm a bad woman
But I'm afraid this will continue
I really can't think straight, so I do this
Ji Won
Ji-won, I'm sorry.
Can you please forgive me?
I…
I can't live without you now
Ji Won
I am pregnant
Pregnant…
I want to see it
Park Min Hwan…
Park Min-hwan is…
It's me
Kang Ji-won…
Going crazy
And Jung Soo Min...
My life is ruined!
Viper Cash Repayment Notice
Viper Financial Slaughterhouse
The pauper capital ultimatum
Not fun at all
Hey, do you also think I look like someone who got another woman pregnant behind his fiancée's back?
Yeah?
Oops, I seem to have been hit by a car
What is this?
What is this? Huh?
Who are you guys? What are you doing?
Brat?
I look pretty young, don't I?
Yes, you do have a baby face.
Right? I have a baby face.
What era is it now?
This is the Republic of Korea, you are...
I'm afraid something will happen to you. I'm afraid you'll be in trouble.
Where are you from?
Are you guys from Viper Cash?
Or someone from Viper Finance?
Where from?
Ouch
Are you still borrowing money from Viper Cash?
They don't beat people but cut them, right?
- Kill someone? - Yeah, yeah
-Here-Yes
-Is it still here? -Yes
Sir, I will pay it back! I will pay it back!
- What? - Be gentle.
Aren't you broke? Is there any way to suddenly become rich?
I have no money
But my parents have
As long as I get married, they will buy me a house
I'll pay it back in cash, right away, yes
They always have to see the coffin before they can have money
So when are you going to get married?
End soon
I have a daughter who is getting married...
I have a pregnant woman, yes, the woman who is pregnant with my child
I'll pay you back as soon as I get the house.
Big Brother
-Brother, you are here. -It is cold outside.
Why don’t you wait in the store instead of coming here?
I'm sorry to ask you two to do something weird.
As long as you need us, we can do anything
Is he the guy I went to get the fried chicken last time?
What's going on? He's in a lot of debt.
Brother, we're not done yet.
Let's go pack up and come back
We'll be back soon.
Very cold
Kang Ji-won will be happy
She will be happy
mom
Didn’t you say you would buy me a house when I get married?
Can you buy it for me now?
You only gave me red hygienic clothes.
Why should I buy you a house?
When you give me a grandson, I might buy it for you.
Mom, I'm not kidding now.
I'm in urgent need now
Do you believe me?
Don't you love me?
I am your son, Park Min-hwan, your only son
Where are you going, little brat?
Really
Oh my god, I'm so scared! What the hell?
Hey, why are you squatting there?
Hello
Hey, Jung Soo Min
what are you doing here?
I'm nothing special except that I'm pretty, so what are you doing in my house?
Why didn't you tell me you were pregnant?
Will anything change if I become pregnant?
Yes, I was a bit too harsh, wasn't I?
I really didn't mean that, really.
All men are like this, right?
It seems that there has really been a change
Kang Ji-won wasn't like this originally
Even when I told her I was pregnant she didn't want to talk to me
fool
You seem to be very smart
But in an unknown place, it's stupid
Your child is my child, of course she is hurt.
She likes me so much
Is that so?
I am pregnant
Of course
Although she is very cruel, she doesn't show it, but I know
Don’t you know that too?
She's fragile inside.
Since I found out about your relationship with me, I've been hurt and scared.
Plus you said you were pregnant
She must be in a bad mood.
is that so?
-Cheers-Cheers
Oh my god, this is really God's help
Agent Jiang, wouldn't it be terrible if you got married without knowing it?
Garbage should be thrown into the trash can
But the funny thing is that the garbage and the garbage can seem to hate each other
Did you see Park Min Hwan’s expression when he heard she was pregnant?
Pregnancy? Zheng Xiumin, what are you planning?
Park Min-hwan must have azoospermia
Is the meal to your liking?
Very delicious
Do you need anything else?
No, it's great right now.
Thank you
Very good
Have a nice meal!
But…
I thought Ji-won would stand by me in the end.
She's probably angry.
So just pretend you didn't see my message.
But when she saw that others were too harsh on me
I thought she would stand by me.
She has always been like this
Even if it's a little strange
Even if it's not quite right
Even if she is angry
But in the end
She still forgives me and understands me
I think…
Now it's my turn to be your person
You graduated from Kang Ji-won, right?
You're not in love.
Let's both let go of Kang Ji-won
Just think about the two of us.
us?
us…
Do you want to get married?
I said cruel words to you
I want to try not to like you
But I think I only love you
us…
Should we get married?
Our Family…
Our family will be better tomorrow than today
I promise you
Tomorrow will be better than today
family?
right
Incident reporting, personnel disciplinary notification
So Kang Ji Won has no problem
The problem is her fiancé and her friend?
right
But luckily the employee in question said she was pregnant
The customer forgave her and the matter came to an end
The relevant employees were also given personnel sanctions.
The investigation results of the quick-cooking meal package project are also the claims of Kang Ji-won, the agent.
It is common to steal the plans of subordinates.
So Kang Ji Won is the victim
I have to see her.
Come in
I heard you've been having a lot of trouble lately.
I told myself that what was bound to happen must be faced even if it was difficult.
It seems like you have a lot of difficult people around you.
There aren't many difficult people.
But there are still many strong people.
Am I included?
I think so
So what are you going to do in the future?
- Now? - Yes, please go over and take a look
-Grandpa- Ouch, you scared me
You'll scare the guests, little brat.
The president didn't say anything.
So you don't have to worry
I won't let this happen again, sorry.
Why are you sorry?
I feel so magical to be able to see the president so close
But he's not as unapproachable as I thought.
He should be hard to get close to.
I told him frankly
When I said my boss stole my project proposal
I once thought about whether I should just not care about it
But I don't regret it now
This is the answer my grandpa would like.
And he brought up my private life first
He said it wasn't my fault I stepped in poop
Second-hand market
Purchase two-line pregnancy test stick and ultrasound photo
Your article has been published
family
A new beginning
Park Min-hwan and Jung Soo-min seem to be getting married soon
You should have a new start.
oh
Um…
I can't feel at ease until they say they want to get married.
They will get married
Because if he doesn't get married, he has no money.
What does that mean?
I checked Park Min-hwan's financial situation.
The stock credit is very bad, and I also borrowed a lot of high-interest loans.
Therefore, he is under great pressure to repay his debts.
He has already paid off his severance pay.
Because of this incident, he was demoted to an ordinary employee and his salary should be reduced.
How did you check?
You once said
I'm a person who only does the right thing
Actually, it is not the case
My grandpa knows
I just...
Nothing I wanted before
Do you want to try shooting?
I'm a person with a lot of things to do.
Whenever I need to do something, I come here and pull the trigger.
When I thought the bullet had already flown
It's irreversible
Just do it, after thinking this
Even if you don't want to do something, you can still do it.
But now I can't help doing what I want to do
I am a person who can do many things
Now it has changed
I'm just doing what I can to help you.
Hold tight and lean against me
My benefactor, you are awesome.
It's really easy to make a quick meal.
I don't have a talent for cooking.
But this set is very simple
You don’t cook at home, do you?
Yes, I always order takeout when I'm alone.
This won't work. You have to eat healthier.
I once had a stomachache so I try to cook at home
It's delicious
You are really perfect
Benefactor, will you marry me?
I don't plan to get married
This won't work.
Even if you don't have that intention
Your ex-boyfriend feels like he lost when he gets along well with someone else first. It's annoying.
You have to be happier than them first.
Which type do you like? Do you look at the face or the figure?
I'm going to answer the phone
It's Bai Enhao calling.
No, don't answer it. I'll call him later.
Just take it
If a handsome guy calls me on Christmas, I will answer the phone.
Hello? Eunho
What?
-Hello. -Are you coming?
-Did you wait long? -No
-Hello. -Hello.
You drive very carefully.
oh
Because I seldom drive
After that, I drove for the first time
- That time? - My brother
We got drunk in his shop and he gave us a ride back home
This was the first time I encountered such a thing and I was at a loss. He saved me.
The minister was drunk?
And it was in Eun-ho’s shop?
If Kang Ji-won is the only one who wrote with his left hand
What do you think will happen?
Yes, he comes often.
Because my brother has such a sophisticated taste, the food he makes is delicious.
So what do you want to do?
Where are we going?
Aren’t you going with us?
Oh, Agent Jiang
Do I look like someone who doesn’t have a date for Christmas?
Let’s go, have fun!
All right
I'm the kind of person who doesn't have a date on Christmas.
But they look really good together.
Ouch
You're eating ice cream? That's a bit human.
I want to eat too
What's the matter?
Didn’t you say that her classmate should be a good man and asked me to help them get together?
I did super well.
What's wrong with the temperature? Is the heating off?
Does he seem like a nice guy?
Um
I think he might be a little bored.
But it's comfortable to get along with him. He's handsome and stable.
Although the benefactor appears to be very strong, he is actually often anxious.
And most importantly, his eyes are full of love
How? Why? Why don’t your actions match your words?
You said you have nothing to do with my benefactor and you can't do anything
You said you wanted her to be happy and asked me to introduce her to a good man as soon as possible.
You want me to eat like this?
I hope my benefactor can meet a good man soon.
She seems to dream of spending Christmas at home with her family.
Bright light bulbs and gifts under the Christmas tree
There are cakes and music boxes
And the decorations like Christmas hats and socks
Isn't it a bit cold? Would you like something hot to drink?
I'll buy it
Can I live this kind of life as long as the two of them are married?
Dinner is a popular time on a day like Christmas. I have to go.
Feel sorry
What is there to be sorry about?
Thank you for spending time with me
No
I really had a great time today
It would be great if it could make you forget some of your sadness
Then next time...
Eun Ho
You are a really good friend.
I'm really glad to see you again.
You really shouldn't do that.
I'm glad I don't have any misunderstandings about you anymore.
Don't talk to me anymore.
See the real you
I used to...
Like you!
Thank you
I will also be your good friend
good
Thank you
My first love
Come
The line you wrote with your left hand
It seems not me
minister?
Why don't you go in? What are you doing here?
I came out to get some fresh air
I'm planning to go back now.
You seem to have been breathing for a long time.
No
that…
minister
I have something to tell you
You want to come over to my house?
Or should I go to your house?
What would you have done if I hadn't said I had something to tell you?
I'll tell you I have something to tell you
Actually, I went on a date with Eun-ho today.
He is my first love
And he said he likes me
I heard
I stood there for a long time
But why did you reject him? He seems like a nice guy.
He's a very nice guy.
That's why I liked him before
But…
My heart doesn't think so
Do you remember that I asked you before so that I could be honest with you?
Please let me be honest with you sometimes.
I've never confessed my feelings.
This time I want to try to confess
When I was with Eun-ho
I keep thinking of someone else
I thought I knew it all
But people who don't understand
There are still many people I don’t understand.
But…
He is the only one I can understand.
and…
He is the one who knows me best
After hearing your thoughts
I guess that's why I came back.
I know you like Kang Ji Won
But I don't think you're the type to interfere with Park Min-hwan and Jung Soo-min
Whatever concerns Ji-won concerns me.
What went wrong?
minister
I'm not a person suitable for love
Because I want you to be happy
I want to help you collect the wedding money.
The man and family of Kang Ji-won
It's all mine now.
Congratulations on picking up my trash