The number one
Korean content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM MAY NOT
BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS INDIRECT
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING
MARRY MY HUSBAND
PRODUCTION SPONSORS:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS,
AND TOURISM, & KOCCA
THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL,
AND IS NOT RELATED IN ANY WAY
TO ACTUAL PEOPLE, PLACES, INCIDENTS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND SETTINGS
- Happy birthday to you!
I wondered why you'd have
such a fancy birthday party.
Was it to propose?
I hope today will be the best gift
of her life.
How was it?
You're so lucky!
This is amazing.
How did you come up with this?
I was a little surprised
by the drones and fireworks too.
Well, you know. I'd do anything.
You know, I would've still been happy
with a cheaper event.
Thanks.
SECOND HAND MARKET
Proposal...
PROPOSAL DECORATION
It's 39,000 won?
This is 50,000 won? This is insane!
Oh, hello.
The company will provide a villa
for Ms. Kang's birthday
to offer consolation
for what happened recently.
Consolation?
For what Mr. Kim did.
Oh, right.
It's for that.
But a villa for consolation?
Normally, a condo,
but they're more generous this time.
He's really in love with her.
It's true love!
But too bad. You clearly don't know women.
Ji-won only loves me.
Don't grab like that! You're crazy!
I'm sorry, sir.
This is a great opportunity.
Why don't we have the party
with everyone on our team?
She thought it was a birthday party,
but surprise!
I'm going to propose to her.
I'm going to marry Kang Ji-won.
Come and get your heart broken, punk!
I hate your guts!
You'll come too, right?
Of course.
I can provide other support too.
Well...
Congrats.
Have you...
still not forgiven me?
Ji-won, I'm sorry. Stop being mad at me.
Please?
I'm sorry.
Don't be mad.
Let's go back
to being good friends. Please, Ji-won?
I can't figure you out.
But what's important is
that I don't really want to.
Bye.
Ji-won...
Kang Ji-won!
You know I can't swim.
Guess what they say then?
What?
Carbonara.
Ji-won.
Are you cold?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Su-min's sleeping.
She must've been surprised.
What a relief. It could've been bad.
How did she fall in?
She didn't jump in, did she?
She slipped.
She seemed drunk.
Really?
I'm glad no one's hurt.
Su-min should be grateful to you
for the rest of her life.
You're her savior.
Thankfully, there's some hot cocoa.
It's hot.
Yeah, drink that.
Let's bring your temperature up.
I bet you'll have a good life.
The more accidents,
the more to reminisce about.
The proposal was nice!
Of course.
- Shall we clean up?
- What?
But it's only 11.
We need to talk and drink more.
The night's still young.
I'm pretty shook up, so I'm tired too.
Let's all rest.
Thanks for tonight.
Let's go.
Shall we go up too?
Go ahead. I'll go after I drink this.
Yeah, sure.
That was a textbook proposal.
It went great.
I could never do it again. No way!
Oh, my God! What the hell?
What?
You're quite late.
What are you doing here?
Get in here.
I proposed today.
And Ji-won's in the next room.
That makes it more thrilling.
You don't want to?
Are you drunk?
You look really happy.
Ji-won...
jumped in the water for me.
Now...
it's your turn to make me happy.
Come on.
Are you okay?
She jumped in.
She didn't slip.
Right in front of me.
Maybe I didn't know Su-min at all.
I thought it'd be easy.
That Min-hwan is trash
and Su-min covets my things,
so I just need them to marry
to become happy.
But I was wrong.
She dragged me down.
She grabbed my arm
and dragged me down deeper.
Also...
she was smiling.
Did I imagine it?
I wish that were true.
But no.
She tried to die for real.
As if dying in the water was nothing
and she didn't care about anything
as long as I died with her.
I want to show you something.
When I felt confused
and unsure of what I was doing,
I always came here.
Once I cleared my head here,
I felt I could take another step.
No one knows the future.
However,
we know more than other people.
So don't be scared.
You've gotten so much better.
You learned something new
about a friend of 26 years.
If Su-min showed you a side
she never had before,
it means you're not an easy target
to her anymore.
I truly wish you a happy birthday.
Thanks for the proposal.
It was the best first birthday.
MARRY MY HUSBAND
EPISODE 9
Ms. Kang!
- Hello.
Oh, my. What's that?
Ms. Kang, no way!
I'm engaged!
Wow! Is that a carat?
Wow, Mr. Park really did it.
It's so pretty.
I'm so jealous.
- It looks good on her.
- Yeah.
Why tell everyone if you'll call it off?
Because I'm going to call it off.
Park Min-hwan's life
will take a bigger hit
once everything's revealed.
You know, I've gotten a lot better.
What are you doing this weekend?
Come to Yuhan Department Store.
I'm going to milk him
for the first and last time.
It's a shame I have a trip to Japan.
You're going to miss out
on a big spectacle.
Min-hwan's face will be a sight.
I'll be rooting for you.
The family can meet on the weekend.
My mom has a cooking class
at the cultural center. There's no time.
Are you eating something nice? Buy me too.
Goodness.
You're so greedy, aren't you?
- I want...
- My God!
It's the printer.
It must be jealous.
Are you two planning another surprise?
I'm so jealous of Ms. Kang.
It's the least they can do.
Only the family dinner's left now.
You'll do something legendary again,
right, Mr. Park?
Even I can't wait.
Right.
I didn't know Min-hwan had
this side to him.
My expectations are so high now.
They are?
What do you mean by expectations?
Come on.
Good men buy women clothes, shoes,
and bags before the family dinner, right?
Wait, women run away
if you buy them shoes.
The best friend can buy them!
Oh, is that a thing?
So nice! I'll spread the word.
Yeah, sure.
What to sell second hand...
Just the frame.
I'll toss the rest. They're too old.
And the...
Who's that?
Ji-won.
I'll just give you this and leave.
Your birthday present.
These.
Aren't they pretty? Buy them for me.
As my birthday present.
Well...
And...
I want to give you something else
as a wedding present.
Is that okay?
You're getting married,
and you can't cook.
I heard Yuhan Department Store Cultural
Center has a good weekend cooking class.
I'll pay for it.
Let's take the class together.
Yuhan Mall's cooking class?
Make it just like this.
YUHAN DEPARTMENT STORE CULTURAL CENTER
SPECIAL COOKING CLASS
The class Kim Ja-ok was taking.
This never happened before.
I'm sure Su-min's evolving
because I've changed my attitude.
You don't like it?
That's not it.
Thank you.
I'm more grateful.
Ji-won.
I'm really sorry.
Thanks for the chance.
I won't disappoint you.
I'm going to become your real other half.
Someone you can really rely on.
I must have no talent for acting.
Because it's so hard
to pretend to be biting it
when I know it's bait.
This is great.
If the bad guys weren't bad enough,
I'd be hesitant to take revenge.
But they just won't give up
and continue to be so persistently bad.
Thanks.
Thank you so much.
YUHAN DEPARTMENT STORE CULTURAL CENTER
COOKING CLASS
I had to pay for parking last week.
I've been coming here for years.
That's not possible.
Your name and plate number?
Kim Ja-ok, 5780.
Ma'am, you parked
for over six hours last week.
We only provide two hours for the class.
- It's our policy that you must buy...
- No.
It's just a tiny parking spot,
but you make me pay?
I've never once paid!
Why are you making me pay now?
This is my spot.
Goodness.
Everyone pays for this class.
How are there assigned seats?
Look at this young lady.
I'm an adult, and I said so.
Move out of the way. Go over there!
I'm sorry. Let's just do what she says.
- We'll go.
- Don't say sorry.
Nothing's set here.
That girl knows a thing or two.
I swear, there will always
be rude, ill-mannered people.
They're everywhere.
I called and checked the quantity.
And the Jomart tasting evaluation.
There it is.
And the proposal for promotion.
Where is it?
Farm assessment form.
Oh, no.
I'm really busy...
Mommy.
Yeon-ji?
Mommy, it's Sunday. Where are you?
I'm hungry.
How did you call me?
Where's your daddy? Where is he?
Daddy? He's busy.
I'm hungry. When are you coming home?
Why is your daddy busy?
Is he not home? Where is he?
Sir, can you drive faster?
My five-year-old daughter
is home alone right now.
I'm sorry to hear that,
but I can't clear this weekend traffic.
This is insane.
YEON-JI'S DAD
Mommy!
- Yeon-ji!
- Mommy!
It's me. This is a video call.
Put it down and look at me.
- Mommy!
- Don't cry. Look at me.
Mommy!
Yeon-ji, I'll be there as soon as I can.
Just wait.
Mr. Lee!
Please help me.
Here. Thank you.
Sir, thank you so much.
Thank you.
Where did you go?
I had some work to do.
Do I play all day?
It's the weekend.
Noodles...
How could you feed her instant noodles?
Don't eat that.
So dramatic.
You feed her then.
Are you okay?
- Mommy.
- Yeah?
Why go to work on the weekend
to come back so early?
Your hands are quick and neat
for a young lady.
I love to cook.
But as for you...
How will she cook for her family
if she's that slow?
They won't eat tomorrow at that speed.
Maybe breakfast in two days?
No, lunch in two days.
What?
What was that?
My boyfriend loves cooking,
so he'll cook for me for the two days.
Men weren't even allowed in the kitchen
back in the day.
It's not that day now.
I'm happy with now.
What's your problem?
It's obvious what kind of family
she'll marry into.
- Ja-ok?
- Goodness!
Are you done?
Hello!
Why is she so annoying?
Sir, women who can't even cook
are signing up for this class
to try and seduce a man.
You have to be careful of them.
Yeah, I understand.
Goodness, Ji-won!
How did you make it so pretty?
Wow! That's amazing. You're the best.
Great job.
I was bad at cooking
around this time. But...
Peel that pear.
Yes, ma'am.
Not so thick. Thinner.
Okay.
Thanks for the hard training.
I love her cooking skills.
How could someone so rude...
Food shouldn't just look good.
It's hard to make good carrot râpées.
This taste...
It's the same as the teacher's.
Because you learned it here
and taught it to me, Ms. Kim.
I'm glad you think it's good.
When did you learn to cook?
I didn't learn. I just did it.
I wanted to make it pretty,
so I went slow.
I learned what carrot râpées were today.
Well, my dad taught it to me long ago.
Your dad...
He was a great person.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you. Let's go.
Let's go do some shopping.
Min-hwan!
He's buying me clothes
for the family dinner.
Want to join us?
But...
I didn't know Su-min...
would be here.
Babe, when are we meeting your parents?
What?
Well, we have to set a date.
I should go.
I have plans.
If I knew you were coming,
I wouldn't have made other plans.
You have plans?
Yeah, let's hang out next time. I'll buy!
We did birthday and wedding gifts.
Next time,
it's a gift for my savior.
Yeah, okay.
It's a date, then. Just the two of us.
Yeah, sounds good.
This is nice!
I'm really alive because of you.
Bye.
Do you need any duty-free items?
That's okay.
That's fine.
Wait a second.
Do you want to see?
Are you saying
he bought the same necklace?
No, it's a bit different. This one...
It looked quite expensive.
I want this one.
Hey, this is too expensive.
Are you newlyweds?
The perfect wedding gift.
I haven't met her yet,
but I hear his mother has high standards.
If that's the case,
you'll need that bag.
It's not just her.
We both work at U&K, actually.
Everyone's dying to see what he'll buy
for me. Even I feel pressured.
Pride controls his body.
Yeah, well...
I'm a legend at U&K.
We'll take it.
- Can I?
- Of course.
Show us a few more similar ones.
This would go well with pink.
- With this bag!
- What...
How could she buy all of these?
Are you going to wear
cheap clothes you bought online again?
I told you.
My mom has high standards.
We can't get married
if she doesn't like you.
I didn't want to spend his money
when he was struggling.
Why did I do that?
He would've bought it
for another woman anyway if not me.
It was no big deal.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Min-hwan, isn't this beautiful?
I love it.
I finally feel like
I'm up to par with your parents.
Getting a family is really great.
It's pretty. Yeah.
They're all pretty. All of them.
I realized yet again
that a woman should meet the right man.
Of course.
A woman needs to meet the right man.
We have to have our family meeting now.
We have to go somewhere to eat.
How shall we pay for the meal?
BAEK EUN-HO
- Baek Eun-ho?
- Yeah, go on.
The one running a restaurant?
- No.
- No?
Wait.
Hello?
Isn't this Ji-won's phone?
Yes, hello.
I'm Min-hwan, Ji-won's boyfriend.
I'm Eun-ho, Ji-won's friend.
I heard a lot about you.
She said you were a great chef.
Yeah, thanks.
But can I speak with Ji-won right now?
That's not important.
I heard you ran a fine dining restaurant.
What cuisine is it?
Is it French or Italian?
Or maybe omakase?
It's a fusion restaurant.
French is the base.
That's perfect.
The thing is,
Ji-won and I have
an engagement family dinner soon.
It'll be meaningful to have it there.
We were just talking about it.
If you're a friend from school,
is there a close friend discount
or an alumni discount?
That'd be so nice.
I'll call you back.
I look forward to it! Bye.
- What are you doing?
- Are you two close?
What is it? What did he say?
Was it her boyfriend?
What's wrong? Why? Is she busy?
I didn't get to speak with Ji-won.
I'll ask later.
What did you do?
From Ji-won's standpoint,
- she may not want an apology.
- You're right.
Either way! We should do something.
A decent person should make up
for their wrongs.
I, Ha Ye-ji, was fooled
by Jeong Su-min,
and it was the worst mistake of my life.
The date of the dinner
will be early December.
I'm counting on you.
I think she's getting married soon,
so gift her a lot of congratulatory money.
Getting married?
KANG JI-WON
Hey.
Eun-ho, I'm sorry.
It's fine. Well...
Congratulations on your wedding.
No, don't worry about what he said.
I'll take care of it.
I'll do it for you.
Eun-ho...
You were my first love.
Let me do it.
They're going to be your family.
I'll treat you to something special.
Your one and only grandfather
was admitted, and you came so late.
If I was more impatient,
I would've died waiting.
You live to see ten more years.
What?
I just came back from Japan.
Did it go well?
It's Yu-ra. We just met briefly.
There's no one like her.
She's a hundred times better
than that Kang Ji-won.
Grandfather, just leave her alone.
She has nothing to do with me.
I can't just leave her alone.
They're my feelings.
You foolish boy.
You're in love with someone who's taken.
You broke the promise between families.
You used the villa and yacht,
and lit fireworks.
I heard you even had the staff fly drones!
How is that just your feelings?
Do you hear about everything I do?
Of course.
You're not free.
Since your dad's no longer with us.
You...
are the one who will lead and take care of
over 600,000 employees at U&K
for the next 30 or 40 years.
You poor boy. Such a fool.
Just a fool in love.
Goodness.
What?
There were a lot
of things I missed out on.
What is it?
Grandfather...
must've cried a lot.
I'll do better. Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
It's so cold.
What brings you here?
We have a company warehouse near here.
I stopped by on my way...
Actually, that's a lie.
I came because I missed you.
Did something happen?
Do you remember asking me
what I wanted to be?
I never thought about it before.
My life was decided since birth.
So I studied and worked only for U&K.
I want to be solid land.
But you want to be something now.
I don't.
I could never be that.
Then let's start with something simple.
What you want to do right now.
When I first came back,
I just didn't know what to do.
"Where do I run to?
How will I make money?"
And I hated
the sight of Min-hwan and Su-min.
So I told myself
I wouldn't just take it anymore.
Then I made food spilled all over him.
Come on!
After that, I could see things
a little more clearly.
Getting them to marry is just the process.
In the end, I have to be happy.
I have to do what I love.
I have to meet...
friends I like.
Can I...
hold your hand?
Get Min-hwan to marry Su-min,
and you be happy, Ji-won.
Is it your wedding?
Just wear what I pick for you.
This is very expensive!
It's Authentique!
Who cares if it's expensive?
The color sucks,
and the shape looks weird.
Your undiscerning eyes...
Should I just claw them out?
Why argue so early?
Are you going early and wait?
Are you insane? I'm going 30 minute late.
She must wait
if she wants my precious boy.
It pisses me off that a good-for-nothing
brat's stealing you away.
Mom.
You're getting me a house, right?
Are you looking? What's the budget like?
What the hell?
Put this on! This is classy and nice!
I don't want to...
Not the red!
I'm in front of your house. Come out.
HAEYEONG VILLA
Damn it.
What the hell? Why are you here?
Isn't the family meeting today?
What? Well...
Don't be scared.
I know you're mine.
What on earth are you doing?
What? I'm just checking
how my man's doing.
I have about ten minutes.
I won't finish in ten minutes.
What?
You'll be late.
Go and introduce Ji-won to your parents.
Chef, I'll do it.
Do you not trust me?
No.
It's important to me.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Why does he look so sad?
Why is no one here yet?
Hello! I'm sorry I'm late.
The traffic...
- No one's here?
- No, no one yet.
What?
Where are you?
How could you be late?
My parents are both here!
But you're not here!
Today is important!
I'm at the door.
What took you so long?
Mom!
Hurry up.
She's not here yet?
She is. She went to the bathroom.
I thought I was late.
But I guess I'm on time.
Mother, Father. It's nice to meet you.
Wait. Aren't you...
You are!
I'm happy with now.
What's your problem?
It's obvious what kind of family
she'll marry into.
Oh, my. So you're Min-hwan's mother.
Thank you.
I heard your parents passed away early.
You must've lacked home discipline.
No, my father passed away when I was 23.
I received enough.
Of course, since my mom left home
when I was 14,
I didn't get her influence.
A good thing, though.
She was having an affair.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I was curious as to
who Min-hwan would bring.
And he brought quite the woman.
Mom, Ji-won's a great girl.
She's really nice.
She won't make you work at all! I'm sure.
What's with the eagle wings?
What about the clothes I bought?
You bought her clothes?
Well, no. Not these. No.
I'll wear those clothes
on a more special day.
But I brought the bag.
Mother, thank you for raising him so well.
To celebrate joining his family,
he bought me
everything from shoes to clothes.
He's so sweet.
He only ever bought me red long johns
with his first paycheck.
Seriously?
That's not right.
CAT CARE TRUST AGREEMENT
TRUSTOR: YU JI-HYUK
No matter what happens to you,
your cat will receive proper care here.
Thank you.
Are you going somewhere? Why the papers?
Who knows what will happen to me?
You don't even like cats.
I like him.
I have one more favor to ask.
I wonder if she's doing well.
Good boy.
I'll protect you.
I'll just say this
because I'm an honest person.
I love you, Mom.
I do not like you.
I never thought of accepting
a woman like you into our family.
You didn't learn much with no parents.
But it's okay as long
as you're willing to learn from now on.
You're willing to, right?
Yes, of course.
Okay.
I'm not that uptight.
Sexism is wrong.
You're both equally precious.
However, that's only in society.
Not at home.
Right.
The family life depends
on how the woman does.
Feed your man and keep your house clean.
Raise your child well.
Yes, Mother. I can do it!
Men lose energy
if they frequent the kitchen.
No matter how much they gripe and say no,
this is a known fact all around the world.
That's why I'm learning to cook
- so I can cook for him.
- Yes.
You must feed him breakfast.
Nothing ridiculous like bread or cereal.
Cook him soup or stew with rice.
Yes, I understand.
And as for kids, how about three or four?
Have as many as you can.
That sounds good.
I didn't have siblings growing up.
I was lonely.
I like that.
I'll call you when I have time.
Let's go see a doctor.
There are so many uteruses in bad shape
these days.
I'll take a look
and see what the doctor says.
As long as you took care of yourself,
there's no reason to say no.
Let's do a health checkup too.
I haven't been able to see my ancestors,
and it's bothered me.
Since we have a new family member,
let's revive ancestral rites.
Revive?
Red, right. White, left.
I'll teach you, so don't worry.
Just keep this in mind.
Treat your elders with care.
Be obedient to your husband.
Raise children properly.
And keeping your career after marriage,
I approve of it.
Why would I work, Mother?
Are you going to quit?
I don't want to,
but considering what you're mother said,
I'd be greedy.
No, no!
Do you know how expensive kids are?
How could you just play at home?
Play?
To treat you with care,
serve Min-hwan,
and raise my children properly,
I won't have enough time in a day.
Also, it's not red on the right,
white on the left.
It's red on the east, white on the west.
- What?
- You said it was left.
Same difference.
I did an ancestral rite for my father
every year on my own.
I have no objections either.
This is why home discipline is important.
That's not the case with customs.
Daughters aren't supposed to do that.
Your father probably thinks it's his fault
to have a daughter and understands.
This is why everyone wants a son.
There's a reason for that.
But I don't understand, lady.
"Lady"?
Are you a judge?
Why do you judge my dad like that?
Kang Ji-won, are you crazy?
How dare you?
Wait. Don't say anything.
"Lady"?
Hey, are you done?
This wedding's off.
That makes us strangers.
Lady, wake up.
Your son isn't that great.
Even if he was,
you should know someone else's child
is just as precious!
Listen carefully.
It's not you.
It's me that's calling this wedding off.
Got it?
Ji-won, are you crazy? Hey...
Wait here. Hey, Ji-won!
Kang Ji-won!
Hey!
What are you doing?
What do you think?
I'm breaking up with you.
What? Breaking up?
Are you kidding me?
I never want to see you again.
You little...
It's not easy for a woman
to throw a man who's bigger.
So when he's off guard,
do it in one move.
Min-hwan!
What the hell?
Subtitle translation by: Suyun Mounce
Kang Ji-won!
How dare you shout? You cheater!
What else do you have
besides being pretty?
How could you do that to Su-min?
My life is over!
I have a fiancé!
You said nothing was going on with her.
Will I be able to live like this
if they get married?
How could you do this?
Jeong Su-min, stop!
I won't let it go this time.
You fix what you did.
Ripped and resynced by YoungJedi
Resynced by TTEOKBOKKIsubs