Elder sister, where did my sister go when she was arrested
It's not going to jail, is it
Can you still come back
Coal core
Didn't your sister go to jail
She has gone to school
Is to get an education
It won't be long before you come back
Really
Really, I won't lie
Don't worry
Shirley, take the coal core to your place and sleep
I have something to discuss with Sister Hong Ying
I'll take them to sleep quickly
You two have a good chat
Go ahead
Coal core and sister go back to sleep in the house
Come inside and sleep with me
Tell me what's missing
What's the matter with you, Tian Zao
Reform prostitutes in Beijing
The street government issued documents
You don't know, you
I know that file
But that word knows me
I don't know the word
I looked at it for a long time and didn't understand it
How could I forget about it
I don't blame you for this
I should explain it to you
Sister, what's written on that document
You and the PLA chief said
It's not catching prostitutes, it's reforming
What does all this mean
The transformation of jujube prostitutes is new China
A major move to liberate women
What to say
Just now, the leader of the army and I
I told you everything
Save this group of suffering sisters
Let them get rid of the misery and turn over a new leaf
It is a good thing done by the party and the country
Elder sister
Regardless of whether it is a good thing or not
I know
I shouldn't have stopped a military vehicle
I shouldn't have caused you so much trouble
Not to bother me
Is to make trouble for yourself
You wanted to be a street activist
The leader has approved it
It will be announced soon
But at this juncture
You have made such a big disaster
Can you be a street activist
It's really two things to say
Don't price, sister
This can't be delayed
Elder sister
Director
I have seriously criticized Comrade Tian Zao
The mistake she made this time is really a bit serious
But since the PLA entered the city,
Comrade Tian Zao has done a lot of work
She is meritorious
Do you think you can think about it again
It hasn't been so long
Why don't you say something
What else can I say
You're from the government, too
You're a communist, too
Why don't you go talk to Sister Hong Ying and them
You tell them I know it's wrong
Give me a break this time
Let me be a street activist
Is that all right
You know it's wrong now
What did you do when you stopped the car last night
Fortunately, Sister Hong Ying and Director Lin gave you a guarantee
Otherwise
I must treat you as a spy and go counter-revolutionary
You're arrested
Don't scare me if it's not you
What spies and counter-revolutionaries
This hat won't fit on my head either
I'm telling you
Jujube
You said you were so old
And do such a stupid thing
What do you want me to say about you
You say I'm not good at anything
It's best to intercede for me
This matter
I really can't help you
Iron egg
What do you mean
You're my fiance
We had a deal
Wait for this street activist to approve it
We'll get married
You backed out at this time
You don't want to marry me, do you
You don't want to marry me. Say it
Jujube
You, don't be unreasonable
Can these two be the same thing
It's the same thing with me
Just say whether you will help or not
Jujube
Sit down first. You sit down
It's not that I don't want to help you
Is that I really can't help
Our Public Security Bureau is in charge of your district government
It's two systems
There is no direct affiliation
Even if I intercede for you
People don't listen to me either
Besides
Even if Sister Hong Ying can't speak well,
Then it doesn't matter who says it
Then what should I do
Now all the neighbors know
I'm going to be a street activist
I'm not thinking about it now
How ashamed I am
In such a big hurry with you
I'm afraid you won't be a street activist
Losing noodles, right
No
It doesn't matter to me whether you lose it or not
What is important is that
I am willing to be an activist in this street
I want to be with Sister Red Tassel
Do something practical for the residents in the neighborhood
Besides
You don't know
I can do something for everyone
I feel comfortable in my heart
I am happy in my heart
No matter how bitter or tired I am, I am not afraid
I will
I know you
May
But now the government is not happy
Then what can we do?
You will say these pieces of soup
Looking for you is redundant
Where are you going
I'm going to find Sister Hong Ying
Elder sister
I've done so much for the government
I have no credit and I have hard work
I'll make up for it if it doesn't work
Success or failure
Brother Lin is right
You are a little time bomb
If I don't deal with you this time
What kind of disaster will happen in the future
That Lin doesn't like me at all
He just took the opportunity to get revenge
He has no grievances with you
What did he get back at you for
He just doesn't like me
I don't like him anyway
What did he do to you
You don't like him anymore
He reused Qin Defu
Do you think I can take a fancy to him
Here you go again
That's enough
I won't tell you so much.
Jujube
The superior leadership has informed me
In the list approved by this review,
Mark your name
You want to be a street activist.
It's a complete failure
Elder sister
You can fight for me again
For your sake
I've been calling this morning
My mouth is almost worn out
I also got a bad criticism from our leader
I can't protect you anymore
It's really out of the question
You this
Elder sister
Let you worry about my affairs
I'm sorry for you
I have to go
Come back
Sit down
I haven't finished yet
Look at your quick temper
Jujube
Next
I want to tell you something very important
The reason why you are so impulsive and foolhardy
It is because you don't understand the party's policies
Unorganized and undisciplined
In the final analysis
It's because you have no culture
If you have the culture
You will study the documents carefully
So the reform of prostitutes
You will be clear
It's impossible to do it
Such absurd and outrageous things come
I also want to have culture
I have no money to go to school since I was a child
How did the culture come from
That's what I want to tell you.
The superior leadership has decided
Open orphan adoption homes in the whole city
Run literacy classes
For you
There is also Dayong Xiaofeng coal core
Children like this find a home
Let you stop wandering the streets
Let you have food and clothing
And organize you to study culture
What you said is true
When did I ever lie to you
New China under the leadership of the Communist Party
Is to reform prostitutes and eliminate opium
Let all orphans not wander the streets
Let all the people live a good life
Because we are the Communist Party
That's great
The Communist Party is really good
New China is really good
Sister, I want to join the Communist Party
Good
It is a good thing to want to join the party and work
But the premise is that
You must learn culture well for me
I must study hard
Elder sister
It doesn't look like a prison
Didn't I tell you
These lesbians
Is organized to transform labor
Who told you he was in jail
I understand everything you say
It's just that I don't believe it
You are really good
This row is a lesbian living area
All the bedding
Daily necessities such as toiletries
All provided by the state
It was the playground that we passed by just now
They usually do exercises
Exercise is done there
This is their study area
Let's talk about it now
The Basic Properties of Cotton
Its characteristic is good heat preservation
Then the elasticity may be almost
And where's our hemp
These lesbians
What are you studying here
Most of them have no culture
We teach them to read and write
In addition to doing some literacy studies,
The most important thing is to teach them some
Knowledge of job skills
Such as sewing, weaving, hand knitting and other skills
For them to join the work and go to the society in the future
Lay the foundation
How about Comrade Tian Zao
Hearing is false, seeing is believing
You saw it this time, didn't you
Sister, I am really happy for these sisters from the bottom of my heart
Without the Communist Party, there would be no new China
How can they be today
Sister Chun Xi
You have the true spirit of Lenin
This is all issued by the government
You know, Jujube
We are now in class every day to practice exercises and learn to weave
Life can be fulfilled
So are we
I'm telling you
My coal core is small and brave
We all got into that literacy class
Reading and reading culture every day
Do you know
The government cares what we eat and what we use
Whatever we wear
We don't have to go out on the streets anymore
Picking up garbage and begging for food
Sister, I have a name now
His name is Kong Jianguo
Right
Founding a nation
That's a good name
This is from the literacy class teacher
Jujube
Look at the coals
Non-statehood
Watching the founding of the People's Republic of China can enter the school to learn culture
I'm really happy in my heart
Elder sister
We can see you like this now
I am also happy from the bottom of my heart
Right? Coal core
Third brother, you should know that you are out of misery now
I'm sure I'm happy for you, too
What happened to the third brother now
Third brother sells fake medicines
But you can rest assured
He was deceived, not the principal offender
So the government dealt with it lightly
Sentenced to half a year's labor reform
Third brother is all for me
Elder sister
I really convinced the party
This is all for the good of the people
Let me put it this way
From now on
I will do whatever the party asks me to do
Let me go east
I will never go west
Let me jump into the well. I'm sure I won't go to the roof
Talk nonsense again
Who went up? You jumped into the well and went to the house
I was joking
Elder sister
I got into this literacy class
I have learned a lot of words
I can read newspapers now
Jujube
I really hope you can grow up quickly
Fast, especially fast
Elder sister
The location of street activists
You have to keep it for me
When I learn it well,
And follow you
That depends on your performance
Isn't it
According to various intelligence summaries,
It is basically certain
Three places where Zheng Qiang hid
We will arrest Zheng Qiang tonight
Is the information accurate
A large number of investigations and designations have been conducted
Basically accurate
I know this piece well. I'll take someone
I'll pack this one
Good
Then I'll take the rest of the place
In order not to disturb the people around us,
The operation time is set at 12 midnight
Yes yes
Eight horses
Man, the money is on the table
All right, take your time
Keep up
Quickly
Withdraw
Yes
Go
Busy all night
I didn't even see a Zheng Qiang man Mao
Comrades
What we're dealing with
Is rich in latent experience
An extremely cunning senior Kuomintang spy
We have to do well
Prepare for a long struggle with him
As long as he doesn't leave Beijing
We are sure to catch him
That's right
No matter how cunning the enemy is,
I can't escape the tight encirclement of the people
One day
We will put Zheng Qiang
And all the spies lurking in Beijing
Are uprooted
Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea and Defend Our Country
President Truman issued a statement
Strictly condemn the aggression of North Korea
Decided to assist South Korea
And action by the U.N.
At the same time, the US Seventh Fleet was dispatched to help defend
Enter the Taiwan Strait
We welcome and support this
Based on our obligations to the Republic of Korea
And the needs of common interests
At the request of President Li Chengwan
Decided to send the 52nd Army to reinforce
Its thirteenth division has set sail from Matsu
Return to Taiwan and return the fifty-second military system
The army should be within two days
Complete all operational preparations
And first concentrated in Songshan Airport in a group
Stand by for departure
That's great
Do you hear that
US Seventh Fleet
Has entered the Taiwan Strait
The international situation is excellent
The United Nations troops have reached the Yalu River
Volunteers of the Communist Party
Dare to confront the powerful United Nations army
This is the mantis arm as a car
They are eggs touching Stone
Find death
To find death
Brothers
World War III
It will explode soon
The national army's counter-offensive against the mainland
It will start soon
Shangfeng has orders
Ordered those of us lurking in Peiping
Iron Warrior
Arm quickly
Launch an action
In order to cooperate with the party and the state,
Take back our regime
It's time for you to be loyal to the party and the country
Prepare for action
Yes
To be registered
Don't forget it, sister
To register, to register
You guys line up
Don't squeeze, don't squeeze
Maintain order
Everyone has to line up
Uncle and aunt
You can't get it without waiting in line
Maintain order
Back row
Queue all
Everyone must maintain order
Back row
Don't cut in line
Come on, come on
Come on, one by one
Two pairs of cotton shoes
Slow down
Remy, right
A dustpan of corn
Come here and give it to me
All these letters will be sent to the post office then
Come on, come on
Cotton shoes
Thank you. Thank you
Register here
What is this? A quilt
Come and register here. Register here
Letter of condolence, right
All right
Find two people over there
Come to Aunt to register
Come on, come on, come on
Write it down. Write it down
It's all registered. Don't miss it
Remember to register
Come
A pair of cotton shoes
Small size
Paddy what
Let me have a look
Thousands of patriotic youths have left their homes
Leaving the classroom and leaving the factory workshop
Accepted the instructions and expectations of the motherland
Carry a light bag on your back
Say goodbye to relatives and friends at the station
Go, go bravely
Soldiers who defend their country
The great motherland is urging you
Suffering North Korea is looking forward to you
May you wipe out the enemy
May you write back often
Bring us the news ahead
A thousand words can't be said
Remember this sentence and wish you a successful return
Goodbye, dear comrades
This is
Did you win this?
There is no approval letter either
This has nothing to do with Americans
Boss, we don't like to hear this
You are not ambitious for others
Destroy your prestige
Let's not talk about anything else
Dare to follow the big old beauty of the Communist Party
Do it with live ammunition
I am convinced when I ask for modesty
Think about it
Lao Jiang
Eight million troops
Meet Americans
Is there only a nod and a bow left
Still clinging to other people's thighs
What about the Communist Party
The weapons and equipment are far worse than those of Americans, right
There are not even many planes
Dare to be brave and high-spirited
Crossing the Yalu River, right
Cattle
Let me tell you something
Give Chinese people a long face
This American shell
It's all on the edge of our Yalu River
Then Chairman Mao won't say it
This War to Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea is to defend the country
That's right
Dead lips and cold teeth
North Korea
Those are our brothers and sisters separated only by a strip of water
This Communist Party is really great
Suo Ye
I spent a few days in this prison
That's a great improvement in consciousness
What we're talking about is a reason
Let's not mention anything else
Just mention my ancestors
Thirteen generations of Qing Dynasty
Three hundred years of history
It makes people beat up
Compensation for ceded land
Humiliate one's power and country
What about the Communist Party
Now they are all out of the country
Dare to fight the United Nations led by the Americans
Sixteen countries
It is twice as many as the Eight-Power Allied Forces entering Beijing
What's the matter
It's on
Right
You can win if you fight or not
Let's put it aside first
Just rush this boldness of vision
I ask for three and only two words
Be twice convinced
Add another one
Throw yourself into the ground
Ye Suo has known you for so many years
That's the most reliable thing to say
But seriously
This Communist Party is for our common people
Be able to live well
Soldiers on the front line
Bloodshed and sacrifice
We can't do it as ordinary people.
We have to donate money if we have the money
Strong output
Yes
Right
Don't say anything
This jujube makes me accept the task of military shoes
I haven't finished it yet
I have to hurry to get busy
Get get
Then I will give it to the volunteers now
Sew a condolence bag
I'll go now
Busy busy
Our Pear Garden Guild
Is rushing to organize all the teams
Arrange a new program together
Propaganda to Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea
I have to go to a meeting
Busy all busy
Good busy
Get busy
We're all busy here
What are you busy with
I
Right
Sole
I can't come to this
Let me embroider this condolence bag
My eyes don't work either
Stab me again
I'm going to sing opera with the boy boss
Just like us
People who fight for banners don't want us
It's not that you said I can't bear this shoulder
You can't carry a basket with your hands
What can I do
My greatest contribution is not to add chaos
Come on, just a dude
Brother Suo, why are you here
Xi'er, I haven't seen you for several days
I miss you
Now our sisters
Working overtime every day
Weaving for volunteers
There is no other time
Understanding understanding
Multiple understanding
Then do it yourself
Don't be too tired either
Pay attention to the body
Eat something delicious
Don't worry
The food in our canteen is good
Besides
The Communist Party saved us from suffering
Let's learn culture
And now we're in a textile mill
Be a textile worker in new China
These are our second parents.
I have to serve my country even if I am exhausted
Contribute to the volunteers on the front line
Hang Chun Xi
Now I talk in one set
Have a level
Learn for nothing
Brother Suo, I won't chat with you
I have to get back
You should hurry back, too
Xi
I called you here to tell you
About our marriage
Let's talk about it later
Busy all busy
I'm the only one idle
Elder sister
Now the streets are full of recruits
Students in military cadre schools
I would like to sign up for the Army
I know about it
The district office also let us activists
It's been vigorously publicized
But dayong
Recruit students from military cadre schools this time
In fact, it is recruiting
Volunteers to Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea
This is to go to the battlefield to kill the enemy
I know that
But
I just want to defend my country
Go to the battlefield as a soldier
Good brother
I'm right. You have ambition
My hero should go to the battlefield
Kill the enemy and render meritorious service
I support you
All right
Sister, you've been busy all day
Why don't you go in and have a rest
None of you slept
I can't sleep
Jujube
Don't rush me
The task you gave me
I can finish it in one more day
Aunt is in no hurry
Sister Hongying said it at the meeting today
Said we should all do our work carefully
This is all for volunteers
Nathan's shoes
They all have to be strong
You can rest assured
I made shoes
How high a mountain are the soldiers guaranteed to climb
How far do you go
It won't even rot
OK, I believe you
Take a look
Can these things become
I said your uncle
This is the guy you eat
It's all donated
I said
An extra portion of iron
Just give it to our volunteers
Can build one more bullet
Don't worry
He keeps the guy who eats
Your uncle
You are really good
Jujube
That day, you will do the mobilization for our neighbors
That's very well said
Now we are in this area
The rich donate money and the possessions
That smashed the pot and sold iron
We have to support the soldiers in front of us
Boy is busy
I have to collect it again
See if there's anything else
My guess here
You must have come back
Fourth brother, I have been too busy at work recently
Come back very late
Fortunately, you take care of the coal core
The child is tired of practicing
I went to bed long ago
I'm the only one anyway
I have him with me
I don't feel lonely yet
By the way, I'll collect it.
Such a bag of white flour
You donated a piece. Come on
What do you eat when you donate white flour
I still have some noodles with sticks
Enough to eat for a while
Jujube
Our neighbors in this area
Donated flour and rice from house to house
Everybody said
I would rather eat my own steamed corn-bread
Let the frontline soldiers also
Eat hot steamed bread with white flour
Our neighborhood is really awake
Elder sister, that's not your leadership.
Then all our neighbors believe you
Believe in the Communist Party more
Sister Ying, look
This is our piece
The flour and rice of the old neighbor's own home
And the removed iron
Make bullets for all the soldiers on the front line
So that they can eat rice and white flour
This cooking pan
And kitchen knives were donated
What do ordinary people cook with
Boil some porridge with sticks and noodles in pottery pots
Add some steamed corn-bread at most
Don't need it
Stir-fry
You have gone too far, Comrade Tian Zao
Sister, I can't recognize your mistake
How could I have gone too far
Let me ask you something
What is the purpose of the Volunteers to Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea
Defeat the Americans
Defend one's country
To defend our country
In order to let the people of New China
Live a good life
You can pour it
Encourage the common people
Donated all the pots for cooking in flour and rice
I also let the people go back
The bitter days of eating chaff and swallowing vegetables
Your present behavior
It seriously violates the propaganda of our party
Donations and materials must be voluntary
The working principle of doing according to one's ability
Aren't you fooling around? You
I didn't force them to donate
They volunteered that
Then you didn't play a good role either
The masses
It is ok to donate money and materials
But the necessities of life
That can't be donated
To protect the people
Not only should you have a full stomach
And eat well
Have a strong body
In order to do more work for New China
Jujube
Look at your watery girl
Now black and thin
My face is green
Haven't eaten well these days, have you
Your enthusiasm for work
And the appeal among the masses
This is all worthy of recognition
But I emphasized many times at the meeting
Relevant disciplines
You are no longer
Illiterate people who can't read big characters
He is also a literate person
I have joined street activists for more than half a year
I also have work experience
Before doing something
Be sure to use your head
I can no longer rely on my own impulse
Nonsense
I see, sister
How is this jujube stubble
Why did you return it
Four brothers, aunts and uncles
I made another mistake
Jujube
What's wrong with this
I just want to encourage everyone
Support the frontline soldiers
But I didn't expect it
Neighborhood
Donate all these articles for daily use
How do you live
I have made a formalistic mistake
Sister Hongying criticized me
Sister Hongying said
The aim of the Communist Party is to serve the people
I want the people to live a good life
But now
The people put this guy who eats
All the flour and rice have been donated
Go back to eat chaff and swallow vegetables
This is something the Communist Party absolutely does not want to see
Sister Hongying said
The Communist Party serves the people
Can make the people of the whole country
Can live a good life
Make this country strong
This is the goal of the Communist Party of China
Jujube
What are you doing here
When Sister Hong Ying came to the city to report today,
Meet me
She told me
You've been working really hard lately
So
I just came to express my condolences to you
Baked sweet potato
It's still hot
Eat quickly
How sweet
You taste it, too
I ate it all before I came
These are all for you
You eat more
Jujube
I haven't seen you for days
You've lost weight
Lean and more energetic
Sister Hongying told me
You are active in your work now
Busy all day, day and night
You're a girl's house
Your body is not made of iron
In case you are really tired, something bad will happen
What can I do then
You feel distressed
Of course I feel bad
Jujube
I see you alone
No one takes care of the cold pot and stove all day
Do you think I can feel no pain in my heart
Or
Why don't we stop dragging our feet
Simply get married
After this,
I can take care of you every day
Isn't that what we said in the first place
The days have been set
Who knew the Yanks would make trouble
There are wars on the Korean battlefield now
People all over the country
They are all busy for the soldiers on the front line
You said we were going to work here
Isn't it inappropriate
It seems to be a little less interesting
Tell the truth
We are under a lot of pressure in the city bureau now
Those sleeper agents are coming out again
The Kuomintang's underground radio stations emerge one after another
And
Secret agent activities are becoming more and more rampant
We can't wait for twenty-four hours a day now
They are all catching spies
Even I came to see you today
It's all leave in advance
I have to go back to the station later
Then analyze the case
Iron egg
We made a deal
When the battle is over
We'll be married
Is that all right
Cheng
Okay, I have nothing else to do here
Why don't you hurry back to your work
Then I'm leaving
Go quickly and slow down
Take it
What does that mean
This is my salary this month
In the future
I give you my salary every month
Don't save me
Eat whatever you want
Buy whatever you want
Go away
Wait a minute
You gave me the money
What are you eating
I have more here
Don't save it
I saved it all for you
Third brother gets up early enough
Jujube
I'm waiting for you right here
I'll look for you if you don't look for me
Looking for me
What's the order
The police station gave me a task
You're my focus now
Now is an extraordinary time
You are honest.
Don't talk and move
Stay honestly
Don't do anything to trouble the government
Do you understand
Can't
Jujube
You can't look at me the same way
I was also deceived at the beginning
My original intention is to do something for the government
Ever since the government arrested me
I didn't read less in that labor camp
Policy towards the Party
Your third brother is clear to us
Come on, third brother
I don't have time to be here with you.
Go ahead. What can I do for you
Sister
Look at that
What about all the ordinary people in Beijing now
Are all contributing to this volunteer army
Lian Chunxi works in three shifts
It's like busy three
Just your third brother, I have no reason all day
Idle with five ridges and six animals
I was looking for you
I want to tell you
Look at your third brother and I
What can I do for the government
I see my third brother you
What can you do
Yeah, I'm not asking you
I'm still saying the same thing
You stay honestly
You don't give us any trouble
I'm Amitabha
What else are you doing
Be obedient
Despise people
Row
I don't believe it anymore
I ask for modesty or I won't do it
If you want to do something, you have to do something
I'm surprised you're sweating all over
Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea and Defend Our Country
Aunt Xiulan
Director Dapeng
What are your latest instructions for coming here today
Aunt, what instructions can I have
I just came to talk to Shirley about something