Then you have to eat breakfast on the table quickly
Make up for sleep after eating
Where's my dad
I went to the root of the city wall early in the morning
I went to teach those apprentices to play wrestling
Xiaomin
Have you seen our Juanzi
See you
She bought books with Huozi Dongzi and left
Why does this girl think of buying books?
You buy books. Isn't this with Weimin
Dong Zi also went
This Xiaomin in your family
Anywhere is fine
I just don't like to talk
I'm bored with this jujube sister
You are the master who keeps his mouth shut all day
How to give birth to a stuffy gourd
Maybe I love talking too much
God thinks I'm in a panic
Let me have a daughter who doesn't like to talk
I think this is really reliable
Gangzi is coming back with his daughter-in-law
What time does the train arrive
It will arrive in a long time
I let the two hadrons
Ask for leave and pick them up
It's been ten years since Gangzi left
That's right
In 1979, the educated youth returned to the city
But he just won't listen to me
Married a local rural daughter-in-law
I didn't wander back to our capital until now
Just come back
Then where will they live when they come back
Am I not worried about this
You see, I have only one bright, two dark and three rooms
The old man and the two hadrons squeezed into a room
Can't you let me and Juanzi
Sleep in a room with Gangzi and his wife
Sister Xiulan
Brother Tong
Sister Xiulan, don't worry
I can't. I'll spare a room there
Let them live in the young couple
Don't, Big Brother
That room of yours
It's reserved for coal cores
What if he comes back one day
Where does he live
You have touched a sore spot
Why are you carrying coal cores
Look at my smelly mouth
How did you forget this crop
Sister Xiulan
Let me give you an idea
Then say it quickly, Brother Suo
You just follow there
To Gangzi and his wife
Isn't it over to build one
To tell you the truth, Big Brother
It's not that I haven't made an idea
But isn't there another tree
I can't just build a house
Let's cut down that tree
It's not easy yet
If you build this tree in the house, it will be over
No, that tree can
That's not big enough
That's right
How about you two
Is it a lump in one's head
Use that cloister, too
Isn't it big like this
Besides
What happened to a tree
Isn't this really helpless
Don't say this idea is reliable
But you are by the window of my big brother
Build a house
Can't that block half the sun
No, no, no
Can Brother Tong agree
What kind of person is Brother Tong
It's not like you don't know
So warm-hearted
I just said I was going to make room for him
Can he still care about your half window
This will be angry
Wait for him to get better for a while
I'll talk to him for you
That's nice
Suo Dage Zao Jie
I thank my family for their son
Polite
What to thank? It's not easy to thank children
You have to have a place to live when you come back. No
The brick and mortar that built the house
Are you ready
Er Hadron has been practicing stalls recently
Sell enemas after work
Saved up a little, almost enough
Good
That
Dapeng left early
There is a shortage of hands when working at home
Let me know
Right right words
Come on
Why are you so stunned
Close the stall and leave
I'm leaving now
Push the cart. Hurry up
See you later. See you later
See you later, see you later
Go, go, go
This one for the morning shift
What's wrong with this
Guys, I'll go upside down first
Then I went back to dream of a beautiful girl
See you at twelve o'clock in the evening
Go away
Which is this? This is
Don't know
Don't people change their spiritual food
That's right
Let's have some more of this material
That's right, that's right
I can't compare with brother. I really can't compare with this
I said Dong Zi
I kind of convinced you
How does your brain move
It's still moving
Think for yourself
Hundreds of people don't sleep at night
Run to the door of the bookstore
Go in line to buy that famous book
Then can this book be worthless, right
Let me tell you two
I really regret it a little
I just turned it over a somersault
I knew I'd somersault them
Dong Zi is just one word cow
Let me tell you two
Follow me if you want to make money in the future
Make sure you are popular and spicy
There is wine to drink every day
Dong Zi, don't say you have wine to drink every day
I'm starving right now
Walking steamed buns and fried liver Dongge is enough
Go eat fried liver
Come on, don't cry
So is this Xiulan
It's very good
What are you doing with that bastard
Who the fuck
Coal nuclear is not a bastard
He's not an asshole
All you know is that money
Nonsense
What do you eat without money
What does our son Blue Flag eat
When it comes to this blue flag,
I managed to be in the factory
Tell the leader to let him take over the shift
He's good
Idle around in the factory all day, steal and cheat
You can't eat any bitterness
Still absent from work for three days and two ends
I'm in the factory
People point at my back
Poke me in the spine
Said I gave birth to a loafer
I have no place to put my face
Let the factory leader criticize him for two words
He's good
I almost quit
It's all your fault
He doesn't want to make progress and doesn't like to work
Is it my fault
You can't carry the blue flag on this shoulder
A loafer phase that can't be lifted by hand
It's all up to you
Don't you say that
When I go to work,
He is also an activist in the unit
Why doesn't he learn from me if he is good
That's right
It's all due to that smelly boy in Dong Zi
And Xiulan's family Juan
They all put our blue flag
The soul was hooked away
Leave a serious job alone
Idle every day
Chasing behind their ass
Follow them to set up cigarette stalls and do small business
You really don't say it
I think the blue flag boy is quite up to the road
He knows how to make money by doing business
It's been so long
At least the child didn't tell our old couple
Reach for the money
It's much better than the one who eats dad and drinks mom
What is strong?
Do you know that these people
All in charge of the street stalls
What's it called
Call a profiteer
How ugly it sounds
I don't think so
Isn't it
Make money by doing business with one's own hands
What's wrong with it
Line line line
I knew it
Everyone in the factory said that our son had gone to practice stalls
Joke at me
Shame
Why are you crying again
Come on, have some water. Have some water
Don't cry
You drink some hot porridge first
Really
Know that you have to queue up to buy books
Why don't you put on more clothes
On an ad hoc basis
That's what you young people are like
Think of one is one
Let's freeze all night
It's not frozen
Dong Zi gave me his clothes
Dong Zi, this child knows how to care about people
Wasn't Wai-min with you all the time
Talking to you
Mom, I'm sleepy. I'll go to bed first
Why didn't he give you his clothes
Huozi Sanliang steamed stuffed bun and two bowls of fried liver
You are really good enough to eat
Then what's wrong? Don't eat for nothing
Went to Ho Fung Hotel last night
You didn't eat less or drink less
And now you're eating a bunch
You're not afraid to hold on
I'm happy to hold on to it
Anyway, I don't earn less money today
Come on, you two
Can you stop arguing
This is the money you borrowed from your neighbors
Give it back quickly
Don't worry, I finally borrowed it
Two more days
Make what make
The old saying goes well
It is not difficult to borrow well and then borrow again
Besides
The money was borrowed in the name of Ren Xiaomin
Don't you give it back quickly
Xiaomin has no face
Is that Dong Zi is right
Rest assured
I'll go door to door and give it back to them in a minute
Come
This is the money we earned today
I divided it into three parts
One for each of the three of us
How embarrassed to hold this
Do you still have a time to be embarrassed
Dong Zi
You came up with the idea
You should take the big head
Come on, who are the three of us with who
Take it if you want it. Hurry up
Dong Zi asked you to take it, so you can take it
What are you being polite about
Row
Come on, that's it.
Let's go to twelve o'clock this evening
Then the subway station covers an area
All right
Yesterday, I went to the street office for a meeting
Director Hong Ying conveyed it to me
The situation and some problems in Beijing
Now, I will convey it to everyone
Beijing has a large number of educated youths returning to the city recently
There are so many more
Unemployed youth who have not been admitted to universities
But what about factories and enterprises
We can't arrange so many unemployed people at once
Then these people will have nothing to do all day
Some of them secretly start small businesses
Some just hang out in the society
In view of the serious social problems at present,
The leaders of the central and municipal governments decided
Great efforts should be made to rectify
What about the tasks of our neighborhood committees
Is to tell the educated youth of our segment
And these unemployed youths
It is necessary to strengthen management
This is very important
Especially for those released from two jobs
Focus on supervision
Although we don't have to ask for instructions early and report late
But we have to conduct household surveys frequently
Understand their ideological trends
Put all the signs of crime
To be strangled in the cradle
Director
I'm now from morning till night
Run from house to house every day
The heels don't touch the ground
That's a lot of good things to say
But those educated youths who returned to the city
There are also unemployed youth
And the two laborers
Then they have to eat, too
A young man of that age won't be assigned a job
Eat home every day
Can he be emotionless
Is
At the beginning
There are also some young people
Reading at home
Prepare to repeat the college entrance examination
But it's not so easy
These educated youths
This cultural foundation is inherently poor
No matter how you study, you can't get into college, can you
Be depressed at home
Why don't you go out and wander around
Don't you talk about him
Just the big boy in our family
You said it's been years since you came back
Run to that street office every day to find a job
Don't you think there are any jobs for them
Isn't that right
With a few of his friends
Go to the open space in front of Xidan Clothing Building
It's selling clothes
Don't say it yet
The money coming down this month
Which year did we earn it
Look at others
Really big sister
How much money do you earn? It's really good
It's awesome
I want to go
Okay, okay, okay, okay
Let me tell you something
This business is a practice stall for board masters
It's not always a good thing
Then you said so many educated youths
So many unemployed youths go to practice stalls
Our city of Beijing is not messed up
You, pay attention
Get your big boy under control
Tell him to put away the stall quickly
It's no use saying it
If you want to say it, go ahead and say it
I'll say it as soon as I say it
When will he be at home? I'll go
Who cares about others
Take care of your own girl
Is
You mean me
Director
I heard that
Your Xiaomin and that Weidong
And that Juanzi
And the one named Huozi
That's Soqian's son
Call it Solan Flag
Right
They set up cigarette stalls at the subway entrance
There is such a thing
You talk nonsense
I'm not talking nonsense at all
Someone saw it
That Weidong and that Juanzi
They sell cigarettes there every day
Their family Xiaomin is also there
She doesn't care about their family
I still care about others. I don't even care about my own children
Regardless of her children
Do you think so
Right? Is there one like this
It's out of control
Just do what
I can't manage my own family affairs
Really good
Three thousand six big trippers
Small trippers race cow hair
Although the tricks are different,
But each has its own ingenuity
Remember it all for me
Remember, remember
Remember
You guys keep practicing
Chief director
You are not busy in the neighborhood Committee
Why did you come here to inspect the work?
Don't be poor with me
Do you know
Your precious girl
Now I practice stalls with Dong Zi at the subway entrance all day
You're out of your mind
You sit down for a while
I won't sit
What am I supposed to do
What's the big deal
Xiaomin
I didn't even get into college for two years
You, the great director, carry forward the style again
Talking about so many unemployed youths and educated youths returning to the city
I haven't even arranged a job
I just don't want to go to the office
Find someone to trust a relationship
Arrange a job for Xiaomin
Then our daughter can't spend all day
Stay idle at home
Follow Dong Zi Juanzi Huozi and them
Set up a cigarette stand to earn some pocket money
What's the matter
Then you knew about it
I know
Then why didn't you tell me
There are so many things in your neighborhood Committee
As busy as something
Don't put you in trouble with this thing at home
Do you know
I'm in a neighborhood meeting today
I told them
Let them take care of their children
Don't sneak around doing business all day
When the board master practices stalls
This is not right
As a result, people
Say you don't care about us
Mind your own children
You said
I am the director of the neighborhood Committee
How do you say you want me to be
Keep your voice down
Old woman
When you were pregnant, you were too busy
I didn't keep it
We have a child in middle age
It's hard to have Xiaomin, a girl
This is a knot in one's heart
Besides
The child has grown so big
When has it ever been a jam for us
Who doesn't say you have a good girl in the neighborhood
What's going on now
Help Dong Zi sell a cigarette
You become a bad boy
Didn't say she was a bad child
I know Xiaomin is a good child
Let me tell you something
She learned from that Dongzi
Let that Dong Zi be slapped and broken
I'll find the red tassel
I'm looking for his mother
See if she cares
Don't you go
You leave me alone
Let me tell you something
That smelly son of yours
I didn't come back all night last night
Idle around all day and make trouble
Just now his brother told me
Fighting with others again outside
Yes
I can't blame him either
Is not a reading material
Fail to get into college
Well, then mix with society
You blame me for that
I said before that trustee
Let him work in the police
You disagree
You are awake and say you can't go through the back door
After that
Your street office
Got him a job in the factory
I called someone in a few days
It got us to go to the factory
Bow and kowtow and say good things
I called someone again two days later
Let the factory open
This boy has anti-bones on the back of his head when he hits him
This is a good soldier in the war years
Put it now
Is a scourge
I really can't do anything about this son
Mom
You are the director of the big street office
Who can't help it again
You come here
Stand here, stand here, stand right
I didn't come back last night, did I
I went to fight with others again
Lin Weimin
The whole thing is a traitor
You're the traitor
Return the traitor
Not bashful to say it.
Dad
Calm down, please
This is a bottle of Luzhou Old Cellar
A bottle of Yanghe Daqu
It's all your favorite wines
And that Marlboro
And that, that Hilton
Serious foreign trade goods
Honor your
Where did you get it
That
Why aren't you
I-I'm telling you
I made a small cultural fortune
Didn't do anything bad
Don't do this
I'm telling you
You go to that
Cigarette stalls at the subway entrance
The masses reacted badly
Many people come to me to complain
I'm telling you
These people just can't eat grapes and say grapes are sour
I'm jealous to see me earn some money
You talk nonsense
I'm not talking nonsense
You see me too
A big boy over one meter eight
I can't reach out every day
The housekeeper wants money, doesn't he
How shameful it is to spread out
Isn't that right, Dad
Children have a point in saying this
He lives hard by doing so
What do you know
What do I know
Of course I can know
At present, the state has no explicit prohibition
Unemployed youth set up stalls to do business with educated youth returning to the city
For this phenomenon,
The government is now studying
The policy will be introduced immediately
Guide and manage these people
These spirits
Didn't your street office convey it earlier
Isn't it settled yet
Mom
That
Then we'll talk when it's settled.
I haven't slept all night
I'll go back to sleep first
Go back to Dad
Take this away
Honor you and keep it
Red Tassel Sister
Jujube, come on, come on
Elder sister
My big brother is at home, too
Director Lin Da
Now the society is so chaotic
The leader of your police station
Is it in charge or no matter
How do you know we don't care
Who says we don't care
Say what I don't like to hear
Okay, you guys talk
How did you meet our old Lin
There is no good thing to say
Don't you remember that thing before liberation
I don't see a good word for him
I don't see anything nice about you yet
What's the matter
Your Dongzi is outrageous
Put up cigarette stalls at the subway entrance every day
Set it yourself
I also dragged our Xiaomin
I officially told you today
It depends on whether you care or not
He just fell asleep
Let's scream
What time is it
Gangzi, the boy should be here by now
It should be almost soon
Mom
Mom, my brother is here
Gangzi
Grandpa
Mom
This
Call someone
Grandparents
Grandpa
Mom
Gangzi
You Xiong Haizi, you still know to come back
Dong Zi
Wake up and don't sleep
Get up, get up, get up
Why are you sleeping
You hurry up
Get up quickly and ask you something
You said
What's the matter with Xiaomin
What? What's going on
Just this morning, this gang of hooligans took the guy
To beat you up
I'm telling you
I'm going to die with them
But he looked at Xiaomin, a little girl
Which station
I didn't say anything
The hooligans turned and ran away
Why
I've been thinking about it for a long time
This is illogical
I can't figure it out for a long time
You tell me something about it
You still claim to know Xiaomin yourself
You don't even know that
You live in vain
Think about it for yourself
Don't sleep. I'll ask you something serious
Come on, come on, you get up. Get up
If you have something to say, just say it
Well, let me ask you something
This Xiaomin is not a hooligan, is she
Where are you, a talented woman and hooligan
Then you tell me
Why
Why do these male hooligans see her
They all ran away
I kind of see it
If I don't make it clear to you
You won't let me sleep soundly, will you
Yeah, I'm here to get to the bottom of it
You go ahead
Get
Then I'll talk to you in vernacular
Let me tell you this
Not only Tu Liuzi
Our Hutong Strings in Shichahai
Local ruffians and hooligans
There is no one who is not afraid to see Xiaomin
You tell me why
Why
Because Xiaomin's mother, aunt jujube
Jujube aunt
Right
What do you think Aunt Jujube does
At the time of liberation,
Is the director of the neighborhood Committee
Our neighborhood
Who hasn't received her favor?
Let's not talk about favors
You think about it
Aunt Zaoyi has been doing so many years
For the neighbors in Shichahai,
That's really diligent and hard-working
Send warm of every household
Who has something to do with his family
What kind of dispute is there in the neighborhood
It was jujube aunt who came forward to help solve it
Right
You see, there are still our children
Not all of them grew up watching Jujube aunt
Especially those who are a little bit
That's the key supervision object of the street
That jujube aunt can't wait
Go to their house every day
Go and do ideological education for them
These kids
Meet Aunt Jujube
It's like a mouse seeing a cat
You can run three miles by listening
Let me tell you this
Don't talk about bullying Xiaomin
You don't need jujube aunt to come forward
Their own parents
You have to beat them half to death
You have to say this
It makes sense
Who is Aunt Jujube
Who dares to mess with Aunt Jujube
If this provokes Xiaomin, it will be tantamount to
Irritated Aunt Jujube
Why didn't I come up with such a simple truth
What you think about every day
They are all poetry, prose and novels
Those eyeballs are as high as the roof
When have you ever looked down
Am I like this
Don't squeeze the right people
Squeezing is what you do
Listen or not listen or not listen
Not in the back. There's more
Come on, come on, you talk, you talk
Let me tell you this
Don't look at our dad as a public security cadre
But our children in this area
No one is afraid of him
Nonsense
What do you mean, nonsense
Think about it yourself with your pig brain
Our children
Take a woman and have a fight
Do something about the miscellaneous glazed balls (not serious)
That can't get out of the big circle and can't break the law
It's not in our dad's charge
So no one is afraid of our dad
Of course
No one will be afraid of me
But the big and small things on this street
Can all be managed by neighborhood committees
Aunt Jujube, that's a positive difference
So these children are afraid of her
And then there is
Xiaomin's father, Uncle Tiedan
At the time of liberation,
It is the second division of the public security department of the city bureau
Plainclothes
Scout hero
How many spies have been arrested and how many cases have been solved
Of course
At that time
Said he was suspected of being a spy
Was cleared out of the public security team
Down and out to Shichahai Sports School
Being a wrestling coach
But people have real kung fu
The famous wrestling king in the capital area
The apprentice who learned to fall with him has gone to sea
That's in the city of 49
It is also a famous No.1 person
Dare to bully his daughter
That's pure shuffle when I get tired of living, isn't it
Make sense
Okay, I see
Okay, I'm okay
You, you go back to sleep
Why didn't I figure it out? I'm here
Why am I sleeping if you wake up with me
You say how annoying you are. You
Mom, what do you eat at night
Fried shredded pork with tomato, egg and green pepper
Eggplant with minced meat
Are you tired of eating this old three again
Do you like it
You go out to eat by yourself
Well, I went out to find a way to eat.
Wait
I still have something to ask you
What instructions do you have
Your aunt came to see me at noon today
You and I are almost in no hurry
You two sisters quarreled and bickered for three days and two ends
Isn't that normal to be anxious with you
We all fight about work
Today, aunt jujube, that's for you
It's for me
Don't pay me a price. I didn't greet the old lady
Okay, I'm going to recruit her
Can I still have a good life
You really don't have a good life
Let me ask you something
You put up a cigarette stand to embarrass me and your father
We turn a blind eye
Can't manage
But I heard Aunt Jujube say
You let Xiaomin accompany you to practice stalls
Someone else Xiaomin's child
A quiet child
You let people do this
Are you embarrassed? You
No, no, mom
Heaven and earth conscience
I really didn't pull Xiaomin
Go to the practice booth with me
That's Xiaomin. She has nothing to do
Go to the cigarette stall and find me Juanzi Huozi
Have a chat together
Really
But to be honest
I really want Xiaomin to
Doing business with me
But people don't want to do it either, do they
No
I'm telling you, I'm still
I really need to find the old lady to have a good talk
This can't make me take the blame for nothing
If you say so,
I'm still practical in my heart
In time for tomorrow
Have a good talk with Aunt Zao
Otherwise, she won't spare you
You can rest assured, Mom
With your son's three-inch tongue,
Two lines of clever teeth
You can definitely make Jujube Aunt's face round
Tell me to grow up.
Besides
Aunt Jujube hurts me the most when she is young, doesn't she
Sit and sit
I still have something to ask you
You said
I know you like Xiaomin
What about you two? We grew up together
It's a childhood sweetheart
How are you two getting along
Did you mention it to her directly
Oh, my God
I mentioned it to her
I said I liked her
I want her to be my girlfriend
But she never paid any attention to me
No way
Does she have someone she likes
I can't
She has no one in her heart but me
She, she ignored me.
It is because she has such a character
That, that
You've heard of the word Leng Yan Leng Yan
You use this word quite accurately
That child is giving people a kind of
An unattainable appearance
Right, right, right
How did you say that again
Cold face and hot heart
To put it bluntly, I am embarrassed
By the way, mom
Plus, have you ever heard that sentence
If you are not afraid of no good, you are afraid of no good
There is a big shit stick between Xiaomin and me
If it weren't for this shit stick
Maybe we'll be fine by now
Who's the shit stick? Who's the shit stick
Lin Weimin
Your brother
It is impossible
How many years are there between them
Real mom
I'm telling you
My brother is a valve core
Do you know
You say who he likes at his age is not good
He has to like Xiaomin
Then it's okay to always gather around Xiaomin
What poetry meeting does that always take Xiaomin to
I also encouraged Xiaomin to go to college
He also said that he would put Xiaomin
Get their magazine
I know your brother often looks for Xiaomin
I thought it was a brother
Help Xiaomin make progress
I really didn't think about it
But when you say so,
With their interests and hobbies
It's really a little like-minded
Come on, mom
You, you just said
We were childhood sweethearts
Now why are they two
Like-minded again
That's all I'll say
Mom
I'm telling you I'm your old son
You baby pimples
In the face of this kind of right and wrong,
You have to have a position
Then your brother is also my own son
What do you want me to do as a mother
Mom
You said who you two like
Why do everyone like Xiaomin
What an enemy
Mom
A big girl's family runs wildly outside all day
Make a public appearance
I also practice cigarette stalls
I'm shabby for her
Mom, don't talk about me
Do you believe that I am the only one who practices cigarette stalls
Dad, can you believe it? Is it possible
Then why did you go to see heaven and earth here
I am idle and bored during the day
Looking for Dong Zi Huozi Juanzi, them
The chat has gone to amuse the stuffy
I'm full and I'm going in
Look at that
It's not big or small, is it
I'm not saying anything
I hit the south wall
Still laughing
My prestige is getting lower and lower now
I figured it out
The man in the world who can cure you
That is, you are a precious girl
You are used to educating people with long speeches
Others can't refuse to listen to you
Our daughter won't eat you
You can't help it yet
Go? Go? Go, you
Find a cup to drink
I'm not done here. You sit down
Have to lead
You go on to say
Say
Too lazy to tell you
This is too much
Mom can't eat
Your grandfather hasn't cooked in years
Happy to see you come back
You have to cook yourself
Make you a delicious meal
Come on, don't say it
Eat quickly
Son eats
Sister-in-law eats
Aunt-in-law eats
Is it fragrant
The fragrance is too fragrant
Slow down, slow down
It's time for Gangzi to go back
Let me see
You clean up later
I
Slow down, slow down
It's not enough. Mom will do it for you again
Sister-in-law
You also move chopsticks and eat quickly
I'm I'm full
I'm not hungry
Shirley, I came to see the children
Jujube sister jujube aunt
I'm eating
Jujube aunt
What's wrong with Jujube Sister
This is Gangzi
It's on the opposite side of the street
I really can't recognize it
Much stronger
This is your daughter-in-law
Ah, aunt jujube
Jujube aunt
At first glance, it is a farmer's child
True simplicity
Sit down and eat
Sit down with Aunt Jujube
I'm finished
I just wanted to ask
How do children live? You guys
Brother Tong said
Make do with the coal core house for a few days first
Don't move here until the house is built
Yecheng
Are you ready for the two hadrons
All the materials are ready. Pull it over tomorrow
That is, it will start tomorrow
Right
That's great
Dong Zi
You said we had a good life
Why are you like a night owl
This family sleeps and we go out to the stall
I sleep when people go to work
This whole thing is upside down
Think of me as happy
I don't want to go to bed early and get up early like others
But isn't there no way
If you don't want to leave the stall late,
That becomes
Let's do it in the morning from tomorrow
Don't
You go out this morning
How far does that line have to go
At least more than others
Practice for three or four hours more
No, no, no, no
That's right
Everyone knows
It's near the subway entrance
Many customers, good business and fast sales
Instead of spending three or four hours behind it,
It is better to get up early and collect early
Go home and have a good sleep
Now that everyone understands this truth,
Then don't complain
Count it. I didn't say
Dong Zi
Where did we take the lead today
Wrong, Dong Zi
There is no figure in this person
There is a string of bricks in this area
It's getting more and more unruly
People don't come and get a broken brick
Give me land here
Gap kicked me
Take a break
What's the matter, Dong Zi
Didn't you tell us not to rob the land with us
Come so early again
Yeah, my spiritual food is sold out
I have to come back and practice my cigarette stand
I don't occupy a good position
What time do I have to sell it tomorrow
Right
Dong Zi, I've been here a long time ago
I put all the bricks
Don't give me nonsense here
I'm telling you
Don't you dare to deceive with bricks again
Believe it or not, I'll film you
Will you argue with me?
I said guys
Sell cigarettes during the day
Come here to set up a stall in the middle of the night
Do you think it's easy to earn some money
It's good to have money to earn
I'm telling you
We have to think this way
The money we earned from practicing cigarette stalls for one night
That one for my brother
A month's salary in the big editing room
What are you not satisfied with
You are right to say that
Although people on the street
Look down on us small business people
Say we are profiteers, Ban Ye
Our Hutong
No one is looking me in the eye
But I'm making money
My parents and grandparents every month
You can eat eight pieces of Beijing in Daoxiang Village
I see my grandma
The happy expression of eating trough cake
My heart is beautiful
No matter how bitter and tired I am, I am worth it
Really
Guys, aren't they
Right
What you said is reliable
It's a truth