My good brother
You went home
You little brothers, get out of here quickly
Don't price, sister
Such a big thing
I must be by your side
This is my own business
Sister, you really have to be careful
I'm all over the street now
They are all students from military cadre schools
I would like to sign up for the Army
Recruit students from military cadre schools this time
In fact, it is recruiting
Volunteers to Resist US Aggression and Aid Korea
This is to go to the battlefield to kill the enemy
I know that
But I just want to defend my country
Go to the battlefield as a soldier
Good brother
I'm right. You have ambition
A good man should go to the battlefield to kill the enemy and make meritorious deeds
I support you
All right
Brother Iron Egg, you have to take good care of my sister
I will. Take care
Sister, then I'm leaving
Sister Iron Egg Brother
You two have to keep your wedding candy for me
I thought we agreed to eat my sister's wedding candy
How come people are gone
People are gone
Jujube
Stop crying
I've been crying for days
What can I do if I cry
He is so alive and kicking a person
What a brother
I can't help it
I feel bad in my heart
Busy big brother
Remember everything I just told you
Remember, remember
What happened to the jujube
I told you to hurry up, hurry up
Let's go. Let's go back. Let's go
Suo Ye
You will pick up Chunxi in two days
What are you doing here
Aunt, you have my house
What has it broken into
Say something bad
It's going to rain here
I have a bigger head in this room than outside
Look at this broken furniture again
What the hell
The family is surrounded by walls
Do you understand that your family is surrounded by walls
How do you think I married Chunxi to enter the door?
I'm worried to death
No, no, no, this marriage can't be married
Suo Ye, I'm not talking about you
You are a typical eight-flag dude
Black sheep of the family
Don't bury me
Wrong, third brother
I remember the government gave you a subsidy
What about the money
That money is just enough to make it
That little money can either buy clothes
Or eat and drink in a restaurant
Buy some clothes for Chunxi
Buy something delicious
What do you say you have left each month
What do you want me to say about you
Save face and suffer
Is the critical moment gone
Serve it right
Row jujube
Let's not squeeze on Suo Ye
Our old neighbors
Can't look at him like this
Let's all reach out
I looked at the roof of Soye's house
Have to fill ash and change tiles
The ceiling in his house
And the window paper has to be re-pasted
And the wall needs painting
How do you have to fall to the ground in four white
Then if you get married,
Do you still have to prepare for the bed and be happy
You have to have satin noodles, too
Right
Red men, green women and mandarin ducks play in the water
The more auspicious the better
The bride's hijab must be prepared
Right
Let me stroke it
Washbasin kettle spittoon urinal
These articles for daily use
We all have to replace him with a new one
And the furniture next to Suo Ye's house
It's too broken
You have to buy some decent ones anyway
I said
This wedding banquet
We can set the table in the courtyard
But I did some calculations
I guess why I have to set up seven or eight tables
This, this, this
Wedding candy and cigarettes have to be prepared
It's not small. This expense
That's right
We have to scrape together the money for him
It's not easy for Chunxi to be a child
It's hard to get out of the misery
I met a person who loves her like Suo Ye again
A pair of bad karma mandarin ducks
I finally got married
This wedding
Our old neighbors can't be too poor
Yes
Then I have written down everything that should be prepared
Let's divide the work now
You just said that the roof
Just let iron eggs and small peaks
Let them plaster and change tiles
Then Dapeng can also help
Count him in
This way
This roof window and painted wall
I made a package with your uncle
Get it
Then coal core and I will help you two
Me, I'll be responsible for putting Ye Suo's house
All those old goods have been demolished
Find a cotton player to play well
OK, then I'll sew the new quilt
I'll embroider another hijab or something
I said wedding banquet
I'll take my guys with me
I'll set up a stove in the courtyard temporarily
I'm sure I'll let you
Eat well and eat full
Reliable
Then this is almost the same
We can change this furniture wherever we go
Let Tiedan Xiaofeng and Dapeng
Go to the street and collect it
If you can't buy a new one, go and buy an old one
Tidy up
Ye Biso's family
Those messy things are strong, aren't they
There's another one
Let's see how much money we can bring out
Let's just gather together
Get busy tomorrow
Can you move it
All right
I'll do it
Come
Slow down
Be careful
How nice
I haven't done this since I was a child
Clumsy
Sister, your hands are so clever
The bride is going to get married
Then you have to embroider a beautiful hijab
Jujube orchid seed
You two take this money
Go to the street and give it to Suo Ye and Chunxi
Buy the quilt cover
Remember, red men and green women
The more festive the better
Go quickly
Boss
Where's the money? You take it
You carry the coals
Go out and buy that water bottle washbasin
Such articles for daily use
It's so good
Coal core
Good
I said I said
That's all that's left
The money for furniture
I gave Dapeng and Iron Egg
You should weigh the banquet well
Just look at it. Okay, you
Do it well
Get it
Qi Huo
Brother Iron Egg
Where do you think we're going
Go and change the furniture
You are the director of the police station in our area
You should know better than me
This is the same as the director of the police station
What does it matter
All the furniture in this furniture shop is new furniture
We can exchange our money for one or two pieces
If you want to change the furniture of the whole room,
That's not enough
Why don't we go to the pawnshop
Pawnshop
Brother, do you really don't know or fake don't know
What's the matter
Which pawnshop have you heard of
Collecting worn furniture
People's pawnshops collect jewelry and jade articles
Wenwan calligraphy and painting
Even if the old furniture is collected,
That's also from pear, rosewood and mahogany
The mahogany furniture
It's much more expensive than the furniture in this furniture shop
I don't think you can think of this idea
Neither this nor that
So what do we do
We can't go to the waste collection place
Let's feel it
Don't you say it's really a trick
Now we ordinary people in Beijing
Living conditions are getting better and better
Say nothing else
Just the piece I'm in charge of
Many people are changing furniture
Brush the house
Who do you think the old furniture is sold to
Not all by that
Have the waste collectors been collected
Is it true or not
Really
Then what are you waiting for
Let's go quickly
Go
Director Dapeng, you are a coincidence today
What does it mean
I just collected a class of old furniture
Double bed nightstand
Wardrobe lying cabinet chest of drawers
There are four chairs outside the table
Eight pieces are complete
Although it's not a pear, red sandalwood
Such precious mahogany
But uh it's hard miscellaneous wood of one water
That's great
Where is it
What about the back warehouse
Go and take us to
Go
Boss, your set of furniture
The appearance is really good
That is
No knock, no touch, no shortage
Serious good things
Not bad, huh
That's not bad
I said shopkeeper's
This is such good furniture
How did it fall into your junk hand
That's my luck
On that day, there was a family at the east end of the street
To sell the small courtyard where they live
Go to Shanghai. Go to my son
I know the letter
I'll talk to them, male and female
I want to choose. What's there?
As a result, I went there to listen
I have a liking for this set of furniture
That male and female are eager to shoot
I didn't bargain much either
What about this set of furniture? It's cheaper for me
This furniture is really nice
Business boss
How much do we want
You want to buy it
Let me tell you something
If others want to accept this,
I really can't bear it
You are my father and mother
If you want to accept it, can I not give it
The price is easy to say
You look at it and give it
Don't charge
If you want to say so,
I dare not ask for this furniture
I'm just joking with you
I collected it for sale
What about this price? So
How much do I sell to others
How much is it for you, too
All right, can you make an offer
We'll gather together when the money is not enough
Then I'll get involved and inquire
Is this furniture for your own use
Not for my own use
It's for a friend
You also know this man
Suo Qian Suo Big Brother
Isn't he getting married
We are thinking of buying him a new furniture
Suo Ye is getting married
Good thing
Let me tell you this
Don't mention anything
It's as much money as you bring with you
If it is not enough, it should only be regarded as
I've joined Sawyer's men
Boss
It seems that you have a good relationship with Suo Ye
That's right
Let me tell you this
My father's generation
There is no shortage of good things in Suo Ye's family
The Qing Dynasty died
What about Suo Ye? His family will be defeated
But what
A skinny camel is bigger than a horse
After all, he is a descendant of an official
What about at home
There are also many antique calligraphy and painting
Although my father is a junk collector
But with money
He also collects some antique calligraphy and painting
What about this one and two
With Suo Ye's father
I became friends with Suo Ye
Suo Ye's family sometimes needs money urgently
So what's the matter
Just leak us some good things
My dad and Soye's dad
Soye and I are both fathers
Friendship between the children and the generation
That's a family friend
What about Suo Ye and Chun Xi
Our neighbors all know it
Since you bought the furniture for Suo Ye,
Then don't say anything
It's settled
Cheng
Please inside, please inside
Come on, come on, thank you. Thank you. Sit inside
You have everything to eat and drink. You can eat it on the table
Welcome welcome
Sit down
You all eat melon seeds and peanuts first
Please come inside. Please come inside in a minute
Sit inside, sit inside
Come on, come on
Thank you
Sit inside quickly
All right
Inside, inside
I declare that Comrade Suoqian
And Comrade Chunxi's wedding
It's officially starting now
Good
First
Comrade Suo Qian and Comrade Chun Xi below
Salute each other
Good
Finish the ceremony
Now I declare that
Comrade Suo Qian and Comrade Chun Xi
Formally married a revolutionary couple
Good
Okay. Next, the banquet begins
Come on, come on
Congratulations
May your relationship last forever
Thank you
Suo Ye has a good relationship for a hundred years
May you soon give birth to a son
May your relationship last forever
Grow old, thank you
Thank you all
Eternal unity
We can have today
First of all, I would like to thank Chairman Mao of the Communist Party
Also, I want to thank your uncle and aunt Li
Boss Xiulan
And those good neighbors of jujube
Without them
We really can't get married
My neighbors are really nice
You too
I'm so happy
Coal core and I finally have a home
What are you doing
Get up, get up
Aunt Li, Aunt Li
Your uncle
Brother Tong Zao Xiulan
Me and Coal Core
Since childhood, he has been an orphan without father and mother
From now on
You are my mom and dad
Brother and sister
You are all my Chunxi's family
Suo Qian and I returned the gift to our family
Thank you all
Get up, get up, don't do this
It's all a family
Comrades
Today is Comrade Lin Zheng
Wedding wedding day with Comrade Li Hongying
To express our joy
I propose that we sing a song
Bless them
How about it
Good
All stand up
Without the Communist Party, there would be no new China
Sing
There is no Communist Party
There will be no new China
Without the Communist Party, there would be no new China
The Communist Party worked hard for the nation
The Communist Party is bent on saving China
He showed the people the road to liberation
He led China to the bright future
He persisted in the war of resistance for more than eight years
He improve that lives of the people
He built a base area behind enemy lines
He practiced democracy for many advantages
Without the Communist Party, there would be no new China
There is no Communist Party
There will be no new China
Good good
Good
Red tassel
I wronged you
Where do you start
Dapeng's wedding is a wedding banquet held in a big restaurant
That's because Shirley's father
It's the chef in that restaurant
Their wedding banquet
It was run by the shopkeeper of the restaurant
Yes
But what about Dapeng
I also applied with the organization
According to his condition
He is married to ordinary people who can hold a big wedding banquet
But I always feel that our wedding
It's too shabby to do it
I feel bad about it in my heart
Comrade Lao Lin
How could you think that
We are cadres of the Party
Is a public servant of the people
Hard work and plain living are the fine style of our party
I don't feel bad
I think the big guys get together
Drink tea, eat sugar and sing
It's quite lively
The most important thing is
I can form a revolutionary couple with my beloved
I feel very happy
And very contented
According to the Beijing Municipal government
Decision of the 213th Executive Council
Set up street offices in various districts of the city
And residents' committees
Residents' committees are autonomous by the masses
Resident organization
Its mission is to
First, handle the relevant residents
Public welfare matters
Second, the people's government
Reflect the opinions and demands of residents
Third, mobilize residents to respond to the government's call
Assist the government in implementing policies and decrees
District government and public security bureau
District Court District Women's Federation and other units
Form a working group to publicize policies
Make a work plan
Divide the scope of neighborhood committees and residents' groups
Combined with household registration responsibility section
People's habits and living conditions
One hundred to six hundred households build a neighborhood Committee
Fifteen to forty households form a resident group
Review the original activists
After repeated brewing and consultation,
Establishment of a preparatory committee
The Preparatory Committee organizes residents' film meeting
Elect a leader of the residents' group
Select one or two deputy team leaders when necessary
Leaders of residents' groups
Form a residents' committee as a committee
And elected a director
One or two deputy directors
The director and deputy director studied and determined the division of labor of the Committee
And according to the needs, the deputy team leader will supplement the public security
Member of the Mediation Committee
After the division of labor is determined,
Hold a meeting of the whole committee and deputy team leaders
Announce the principle and list of division of labor
Finally, a general meeting of all residents was held
Declared by the Working Group
Formal establishment of residents' committees and division of labor among members
Jujube, now the government is organizing
Neighbors elect the director of the neighborhood Committee
And members' voting activities
You are the candidate for the first neighborhood committee director
Do you know this in your heart
Aunt, I still play drums in my heart
I have asked people to inquire about you everywhere
Our part
There are many people who want to be the director of this neighborhood Committee
Isn't it
Right
Elder sister
I've heard of several people who have read books
And people with culture
Jujube can't be taken lightly at this time
Neighbors value me and recommend me
I am a member of the neighborhood Committee now
Let me say something from the bottom of my heart
What kind of official are you
In fact, I don't care if the Lord is not the director
As long as it can give the neighbors
There are also ordinary people doing something practical
I will be satisfied
Really
Okay, so long as you can think of it that way
Passing through all residents in the Three Seas area
Democratic elections conducted
The first director of Sanhai Residents Committee is
Comrade Tian Zao applauded
Good
Welcome
Welcome Director
Director Tian Da
I'll salute you now
Third brother, don't laugh at me
I'm not driving ducks to the shelves
I'm in a panic
What are you panicking about
You've been doing this since liberation
Want me to say
There is no better director than you
That's right
It's deserved to be worthy of the name
Neighborhood Committee
To unify leadership
And promote the work of the streets
Street residents' committee root
According to the needs of the work, a propaganda team is set up; And
Don't boo blindly
Listen to our director Tian give us a report
Iron egg or I'd better not read it
Don't charge
Tomorrow is your first time in office
Give a report to all the members of the neighborhood Committee
If you stutter like you just did,
What a shame you have to be
You gotta practice tonight
Jujube sister, take it easy
Just keep reading
Jujube is not afraid
If you can't read it well, we will start over
We'll be with you all night
Sister, you can rest assured
If you can't read well,
We'll all stay up
I-I can still study for one night
Do you make me that stupid
Don't worry, you just
We're all here
Read it
First Street Residents Committee
To unify leadership
And promote all kinds of work on the streets
Neighborhood residents' committees according to the needs of their work
There are propaganda teams and public security and hygiene
Housing repair or construction special care
Special Committee on Relief, etc
Members of various committees
The director and deputy director are responsible for the division of labor
All work that needs to mobilize residents to carry out
By street committees
The committee called a street representative meeting to discuss the implementation
Special Committees
It is not allowed to directly convene the mass meeting to arrange
Meeting arrangement work
At the street residents' representative meeting
After the establishment of street residents' committees,
The original street organizations
According to the needs of work,
Reorganized into street residents' committees respectively
Various special committees to which it belongs
Or cancel it
Good
I'm so nervous
I'm sweating
Yes, jujube
You read it fluently
Isn't this a good read? This is right
You lie to us at ordinary times
You know all the words
Squeeze me, you
What's the coax of smelly iron eggs
Sister Zao, let's ignore him
Then read two
II
2. Clearly stipulate
The tasks of street residents' committees are
Promote the welfare of the masses
Mediate mass disputes
Assist the government in publicizing and implementing policies and decrees
Mobilize the masses to respond to the call of the Party and the government
Reflect the opinions and demands of the masses
All business work belonging to enterprises or institutions
And the work of mass organizations
All shall be handled by the relevant units themselves
It shall not be arranged to the street residents' committee
Red Tassel Sister
Sanhai Neighborhood Committee
The heads of the committees have been chosen
The work of the Committee has been fully rolled out
Xiaozaoa Sanhai Neighborhood Committee
It is a big neighborhood Committee with 600 households
You can start your work so quickly
It shows that your executive ability is very strong
Sister, don't praise me
You asked me to do it before
When street activists
At that time, I still felt relaxed at work
Now you want me to be the director of the neighborhood Committee
You don't even know how heavy my burden is
I'm under pressure
It shows that you have a sense of responsibility
Jujube, you have grown up
I have been with you for several years
Not only did I learn culture
I also learned a lot of things
But the more I learn, the more I feel
There is still a long way to go
Only when you know your own shortcomings can you make progress
Study while working
Learn experience from work
Enrich one's knowledge
This is everyone who works for the party
The process that is bound to go through
Don't be too stressed, either
Just remember that we Chinese Communist Party members
A sentence in the oath of joining the party
Serve the people wholeheartedly
You will always be on the right path
Elder sister, this sentence of yours
My Tian Zao will always be remembered in my heart
By the way, sister
Has my application for joining the Party been approved by the organization
Soon
Xiulan
Elder sister
Why did you come back so late
Neighborhood committees have a lot of work
Just finished reporting to Sister Hong Ying
No, why aren't you still asleep
Not only did I not sleep
The neighbors are still awake
They are waiting for you at my house
Is something wrong
You come with me
What are you doing in a hurry
Coming
They're all here
It's for me
What's the matter? This is
Give me a criticism meeting
Sit so straight and straight
You're really right
Big guys get together
Is to give you a meeting
Educate you well
Not the third brother
Then tell me what I was wrong
You made a big mistake
Sit here honestly
Go ahead
Jujube
You treat comrades as warm as spring
You treat your work as hot as summer
You treat individualism
Self-purification like autumn wind sweeping away fallen leaves
Treat the enemy
It was as cruel and ruthless as winter
Your heart is all around the neighborhood
On the people
Everyone takes you as a caring person
There's no one who doesn't praise you
Didn't you criticize me
Say the neat words that praise me
Be serious and listen
I just kicked off
But ah
You are too bad for yourself
Right
It's not just bad for yourself
It's even worse for the people who love her the most
Waiting for me here
Did Iron Egg tell you something again
I told you not to listen to him
I've been busy lately
Jujube doesn't blame other people's iron eggs
People really like you and love you
I've been waiting for you for so many years
Your marriage has dragged on and on
This has changed anyone's heart. Isn't it uncomfortable
Elder sister
You can quickly marry my brother Iron Egg
Save my iron egg brother from frowning all day
Jujube can tell you the truth
For your marriage to Iron Egg
All of us have broken our hearts
This doesn't like bed and quilt
We have quietly prepared everything for you
Really
Come here, sister
Sister Lai
You see
Your uncle and aunt
Third brother and third sister-in-law
Fourth Brother
Sister Xiulan
You said you were all so kind to me
I don't even know what to say
Don't say anything
You just tell us
When will you and Iron Egg get married
Say a date
Let us all be down-to-earth in our hearts
Soon
I made a deal with Iron Egg
When I join the Communist Party of China,
That's the day we got married
When will the Communist Party accept you
Yeah
Soon
It's over
I swear
I volunteer to join the Communist Party of China
Recognize the Party Program and Constitution
Observe Party discipline
Obey the Party's resolutions
Study Marxism-Leninism
Mao Zedong Thought
Strive to improve one's consciousness
Work actively
Proficient in business
Serve the people wholeheartedly
Perseverance
Fight for the cause of communism to the end
Oath-taker
Jujube