If I love you
It's never like a climbing trumpet creeper
Show off yourself by your tall branches
If I love you
Never learn from infatuated birds
Repeat monotonous songs for the shade
It's not just like a spring
Send cool comfort all the year round
It's not just like a dangerous peak
Increase your height
Set off your dignity
Even sunlight and even spring rain
No, these are not enough
I must be a kapok near you
Standing with you as the image of a tree
Roots clenched in the ground
Leaves touch each other in the clouds
This is the great love
Faithfulness is here
Love
Not only love your mighty body
Love the position you insist on more
The land under the first step
Thank you Xiaomin
Bring us such beautiful poems
All right
Everyone knows that
Shu Ting Liang Xiaobin
River index finger Munk
Their poems are in a rebellious spirit
It breaks the principle that we create with realism
The situation of unifying poetry circles
It also brings new vitality to poetry
It is also literature in the new period
Bring about a far-reaching change
In their poems
Thinking about Human Nature with Realistic Consciousness
Affirm human self-worth and dignity
At the same time, pay attention to the creative subject
The expression of inner feelings
All right, I'm here for everyone
Read a new poem of mine
Weimin, read it quickly
We are all waiting to hear your masterpiece
Good good
Yes, Weimin, hurry up
Don't dare, don't dare
Poetry "Winter Night"
Is there a sound when the residual snow melts
Who has heard the sound of the old locust tree breathing
Under the dim street lamp
A gecko with a broken tail jumped off the wall
Scared away two ants
Juanzi
Stick one with my brother
Who will post it with you
If you want to post it, find someone else to post it
Dong Zi
What for
Let's stick one
Stick on it
The Japanese ship is full
You have to chase somebody else Juanzi
You don't pee and look at yourself
Go and go
Who are you squeezing right
Squeeze you right
As a brother, have you ever seen a girl robbed by a brother
I gave it to him
Dong Zi Dong Zi, he said hey
Juanzi was given to you by him
I'll tell you where you get it
I really don't appreciate your affection
Don't come and come, Juanzi
If you dare to talk nonsense again,
Be careful I slap you with my big mouth
Smoke you with a big mouth
What's wrong? No way
I'm telling you
You have to be your sixth brother here. I'll take care of you
Do you know
What's the matter
I'll give you a girl
Come fat girl
Come on, come on, come on
Stick up with your brother Huo and walk
Good stick, good stick, good stick
Well-matched, well-matched, well-matched
It's also comfortable
Jump well. Come on, jump
Comfortable
The wind blows willow leaves fragrant and comfortable
Xiaomin
When I was reading poetry just now,
You're looking somewhere else
Why didn't you listen to me
Hear of it
Is it
Maybe I write too many poems
I forgot to read it to you
Are you hungry
Then I'll treat you to night snack
What do you want to eat
Casually
Xinfeng Hefeng Xiaobailou High Steps
There are too many people
And the drinkers and punchers are too noisy
The side street in the back
There is a new food stall of that kind
It's quite quiet
Why don't we go there and try it
OK, let's go
Go
It's not far away
Six sons
What to do
Gap-gap
I'm coming. It's killing people
Dong Zi, wait for me
Don't go if you dare
Come on
Fight
Don't run
How many stalls do you see here
This steamed stuffed bun is good
I've been very particular about eating
Elder Brother
Xiao Min Wei Min
You two
Why are you here
My brother and his daughter-in-law
I thought I was going back to the city
There is no place to live at home
My mother and my grandfather
Just thinking about being in the courtyard
Give them a small room
This is not a lack of money
I'm off work
Don't you set up a stall here
Make some bricks and tiles
Then your factory doesn't care
I earn money by my own craft
I didn't delay my work
Can they control it
Besides
Now the factory is in recession
I can't even give out the bonus
Is it okay if I don't do this
OK, then fry two for me
Get it
Eat here
How poor and dirty his sanitary conditions are
That's what I love to eat
Does it hurt
Nothing, nothing, just this little injury
I'm telling you
Just now, I beat him less
Come out
Dong Zi Tu Liuzi brought people back again
Why are you afraid of knocking with them
Why don't you scatter your girl
Go, go, go
Don't you go
Don't run, stop, don't go
How does Xiaomin taste
Delicious
That's my grandfather. That's the chef
He passed on all my skills to me
Since Grandma Li left,
I never ate it again
Your grandfather's craftsmanship
Brother Erqiang, you can help me get a plate of garlic juice
You're eating
You said you were a little girl and you were in every family
Why do you eat so much garlic
How delicious it is
Are you old Beijing
Gap
Dong Zi
Be careful and go quickly
Huozi, go quickly
Stop, stop, Dong Zi, don't run
Gap, gap, gap
Come on, come on, come on
Dong Zi
Stop and don't run
This Tuliuzi returned the carbine and killed it really quickly
I said Dong Zi
Why do you think he's in such a short time
Call so many people over
I really underestimated him
I remember
When I was at school,
He is also one of our parts
Rat ignorant man leader
I didn't expect to be mixed in the past two years
Dare to challenge me
Those who hand over their teeth break off and those who challenge shake it
Dongzi Plate Brick Service
I said Juanzi
You do it one by one
Why is it more ruffian than me
You two went from kindergarten
Primary and secondary schools
They are all in the same class and have never been separated
You two hang out every day
You said she was ruffian
Then she must have learned from you
What's this called
This is called black near Mexico
Don't talk nonsense about you there
Ren Xiaomin grew up with us since childhood
How can people be quiet
It's not at all ruffian
Dong Zi, then you have to say something you don't like to hear
You have to ask your brother Weimin about this
He is a great talent in our area
Graduated from the Chinese Department of the National People's Congress
Now it's that what
The editor of Spring Bud Monthly
Decent literary youth
You said he walked around Xiaomin every day
Then Xiaomin must have been edified by him
What's this called
This is called near Zhu Zhechi
You just stop talking nonsense there
As far as my brother is concerned, he also edifies others
You'd better be careful
Why am I careful
I'm telling you
Don't let them get too close
My brother and Xiaomin can't
How is it impossible to know
Dong Zi
I let you run
There's no end to it
Walk, walk
Go, go, go
Don't run
Come on
Is it enough to eat, Xiaomin
Shall I bring you another plate
Enough already
I did get a message.
Say this tomorrow
The bookstore will sell a batch of world famous works
Really
What are the specific masterpieces
The specifics are not clear
There seems to be some Tolstoy
Hugo's Mo Bosang's
What Chekhov Hemingway Pushkin
Quite a lot anyway
That's great
I've always wanted to see it
Tolstoy's Anna Karenina
Mo Bosang's "Junyou"
And Hemingway's the Old Man and the Sea
Selected Poems of Pushkin
I went to Beitu several times, and I didn't borrow it
I must buy it
The news
It is estimated that the 49 cities in Beijing have spread all over the world
You just want to
How many literary and artistic youths are holding back to buy it
I reckon the bookstore will open tomorrow
It's definitely a crazy rush
Let's go, then
Where to go
Go in line
Yeah, too
If you want to go there tomorrow,
It is estimated that this book will not be grabbed
Then walk, walk
Elder Brother
Come and settle accounts
It's not for any money
How much do you say
Isn't that enough
No, keep it
Yeah, yeah, take it
Enough already
What do you want to eat later, sister
Come to brother's stall
I'll make it for you
All right
Go away
Walk slowly
Go, brother
By the way, I'll call the old lady.
This night is not home
I'm afraid she's worried about me
Let my aunt tell my mother, too
OK, I'll make a phone call
Fight
I said Dong Zi
This Tuliuzi won't touch here, will he
The soil turtle is as poor as a grandson
Eat steamed bread and sesame paste dipped in white sugar
It's all like Chinese New Year
I have to pooled my money to buy it
It's beautiful for him to come here to eat
Gap
You are the light of both of us
If it weren't for the two of us
Cigarette stalls in the second half of the night
You can do it every three or five times
Come here with us. Peanuts and garlic sausages are draft beer
I said Juanzi
You have no conscience to say this
Who helped you in front of the Friendship Store
Pretending to be a Hong Kong businessman for foreign exchange certificates
I'm telling you this. Huozi is right
This boy didn't help us change foreign exchange certificates
Flush this
Let me toast you
Come on, come on
You really don't say a gap
You really have those skills
How dare you
I carry a tape every day
Look at the lyrics and sing Cantonese songs
This song makes me practice
I can't bend my tongue now
Wait a minute, wait a minute
So when you go to school,
Why didn't I see you work so hard
That's not to help you pretend to be Hong Kong businessmen
Do you want to change foreign exchange certificates
Do you remember
The last time the three of us went to the Friendship Store
Just let people get rid of it
Look at the Hong Kong businessman again
Not even with a block
I made up my mind from that moment on
Don't you just learn Cantonese
For me,
It's a piece of cake. This is
You just blow it. You just
Wait a minute
When you were in the alley,
What did you say about Zhu Zhechi
That's what I mean by saying yes
This Xiaomin is with Brother Weimin every day
It must be the route of literary youth
Don't look at you
Pull Xiaomin every day
Hanging around with you and Juanzi
You are not the same people at all
Get it
I remember
What did Xiaomin say to go with my brother today
What poetry club in Beihai
No, I have to find a pay phone
Call my mother and ask if my brother is back.
You eat first
I haven't finished my meal yet
Dong Zi
Where can you find a pay phone at night
Simpleton
You like Dong Zi
Dong Zi likes Xiaomin
But what about his brother
It is Xiaomin's idol again
If you want me to say it
You and Dong Zi are short enough
Eating won't stop your mouth
Aunt aunt aunt
Aunt aunt
It's called mourning
It's not a phone. Use it
It's urgent at home
It's very urgent. People are killed
Use the telephone
Five hairs
No, no, don't you usually only have two cents
Two cents to fight somewhere else
You get five cents, don't you
Wumao Hangxing
Wait a minute
Is it 50 cents
Thank you. Thank you
Xiaomin, do you want to go to our editorial department
What about going to work
I told our leader
Is it
Yeah
I'm in our editorial office
That's more or less a backbone
It carries weight to speak to our leaders
And then what
The leader listened to my recommendation and welcomed it
Really
Of course
But yeah
Come into our editorial office
He is principled
It doesn't mean you have to go to college
But at least you must have the same academic qualifications as this university
Don't worry about it
I've got it all figured out for you
What do you think? I have no chance to go to college
How can there be no chance
You read so many books, don't you
Have such a good literary foundation
And in this poem
I also have a lot of my own opinions
It is not difficult for you to go to college
It's not like I haven't passed the exam before
Too bad at math
You are a partial subject
You make up for it
I can make up for it for you
Forget it. As soon as I look at those formula numbers,
My head hurts
Xiaomin, I have to talk about you
You can't back down when you encounter difficulties
How about this
You sign up for the night school
Night diploma
It can be regarded as the equivalent of a university
Leadership is sure to pass
You say you
A quiet little girl, isn't she
Have ideals and ambitions
With a literary dream
You have to find a way to finish it, don't you
You can't keep following my brother
Those hutong strings are fooling around all day
I know you and my brother grew up
My classmates grew up in small pieces
He has nothing to do with pulling you to pour cigarettes and sell cigarettes
You can't grind your noodles, can you
In fact, from the bones,
You two are not the same people at all
Look at those people around him
What, Juanzi? Is that like a girl
A whole crazy girl
And don't mention the gap
I watched him get angry
You stop and don't like to hear it
OK, don't say it
Then you think about it. Okay
Let me know when you're ready
I'll sign you up
What's the matter
You drink slowly
Are you crazy
Run the bookstore in line to buy books at night
Isn't it sick
No
You said Brother Weimin and Xiaomin
I went to line up to buy books
My mom told me on the phone just now
That bookstore will have a batch of famous books tomorrow
These two people are like valve cores
Run to the bookstore to queue up to buy books at night
Do you think you are sick?
Dong Zi, it doesn't make sense for you to say this
You are only allowed to set up cigarette stalls in the middle of the night
No one is allowed to queue up for books
Can that be the same
No, I have to find them
Walk, walk
Walk, walk, walk, walk
Dong Zi
Walk faster
It's a mile in line, isn't it
Xiaomin came over at night
It's going to be tomorrow morning
You can't grab this
That's right
Here we are
Xiaomin, look at it
This is the power of knowledge
This is our generation of young people
A thirst for literature
With these people,
Our country is bound to be strong
Line up
Defender
Army building
Long time no see
This is Xiaomin
Hello, your good friend Jianjun
Sit and sit
Come on, is it appropriate for us to come out? Is it appropriate
What's wrong with it
Come on, come on, Xiaomin, Xiaomin
Army building
Hello, hello, hello
Sit and sit
Hello, hello
First meeting
Dude
Long time no see
Come on
Nietzsche's ghost has crossed the ocean
Wandering in Asia and ancient Chinese mainland
Nietzsche said that God is dead
Every day when I never danced
It's all a disappointment to life
If one knows what one should live for
He can put up with any kind of life
And
The higher we fly
In the eyes of those who can't fly
We're getting smaller, aren't we
But I still think Sartre's existentialism
It has more practical significance for us
Existence precedes essence
Sartre divided existence into free existence
And self-made existence
What is the existence of oneself
Is the transcendence of self
If in life
We can't act according to our own will
Make a free choice
Then you lose your personality and self
It doesn't really exist
This one you two are talking about
Philosophy of Nietzsche and Sartre
Not as interesting as Freud's
Oh, my god
Why are there so many people
Are you crazy
Cut the crap
Find me Xiaomin quickly
Where is Dong Zi Xiaomin
You have good eyes
Quick, quick, quick
I'm telling you, Jianjun
You haven't made any progress
You're still so shallow. I'm telling you
Tell me about Nietzsche
Make way
Why are you here if it's not you
The dew is so heavy this night
What should I do if I freeze myself again
Dong Zi, why are you here
I'll buy you a book
What books do you buy
This is a world famous book, not a picture book
You also buy books
You are allowed to be arty every day
It's okay to read one book in the east and one book in the west
Cheat the hearts of young literary women
Don't allow me to have something elegant, do you
Lin Weimin
No
It's about you
Why do you talk like a hooligan
Stop
You see, it's so late
Or you go home first
Let Juanzi go back with you
I'll line you up here
Can't you come back tomorrow morning
Xiaomin, that's what I just thought
You go back
I'll, I'll arrange for you
I'll arrange for you
Dui Xiaomin
Let's go home
At least you can still take a nap
Let these smelly masters line up
Dong Zi is broken
Dong Zi Run
What are you running for
Knocked with them
There it is, there it is, there it is
It's over. This boy is in trouble again
Lin Weimin, you start
It's none of your business
My brother is going to be beaten
My brother won't stretch out his hand
Am I still a human being
It's kind of interesting
Dong Zi
I'll see where you're going this time
Tu Liuzi, you and Dong Zi
They all grew up together in our alley
How much enmity can there be, isn't it
What kind of society is it now
You still shout and kill this
We have to talk about civilization
Why is there any reason
There is no problem that cannot be solved, is there
Eldest brother is reasonable
Look at my face. Your brother beat me up
What reason am I talking about? I
I'm telling you, big brother
Get out of my way
Move your hands. Don't hurt you later
I want to swallow this tone
Where else can I put my face?
Dong Zi, I'll spend you
How can I mix outside after my sixth son
Do you know
Cut the crap. You come.
All right, guys
Give him to me and spend it
Shangshang
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Wait a minute
Retirement
Retreat
Xiaomin
Your old man is here
It's not Xiaomin
Little ancestor
Look at this. This is between me and Dong Zi
Can your old man leave it alone
Got it
Understand all
Withdraw
Fuck off
Walk, walk
You ask me who this is
This is the princess in our area
Is the dream lover of our bald boys
It's a quiet girl film
Brother, are you so afraid of her
Don't even get revenge
Revenge. You still want revenge
You can take our part
Self-required ballast frame
The little aunt poked there
Regardless of the big frame and small frame
Just one word and
Really? It's so fantastic
That doesn't look like it
This is a hooligan in Beijing
You big brothers are so afraid of her
I'm really afraid.
If I dare to mess with her,
When I get home, my mother will have to chop me alive
Then my dad beat me up
If you can't play well, you have to kick me out of the house
Big Brother
What's the matter between your father and your mother
What does it matter to my father and mother
I'm telling you
Blow me out of the house. It's all light
Can't play well
Click to sever the father-son relationship
I don't even recognize my big son
Brother, this is too exaggerated
How can I listen
It's like listening to a story
Who has time to make up stories with you in the middle of the night
Whoever dares to mess with her is eating and twisting
Don't want to live, you know
This time, I'm a fold (failure)
Come on, this thing today
With her covering Dong Zi
Count Dong Zi, this boy dodged a bullet
Let's just forget it
Big Brother Big Brother
Big brothers have been busy for half a night
I'm hungry now
Be hungry
I don't think you are good at it, do you know
Hangxiaobailou Fried Liver Steamed Bun
Get it
His treat
Good
All the big guys are scattered, are they scattered
Go back to your home and find your mother
Chicken thief you
The lines are scattered and scattered
Okay, okay, let's go, let's go, let's go
Xiaomin, you're not going home
You're in such a mess
How can I sleep when I go back
I'm getting bored now
It's so late
So many people lined up to buy this famous book
Is this famous book that good
What do you know
Do you know
I want to buy this book
I can skip meals for three days
Can you do it
You are not afraid of starving to death
Do you know what spiritual food is
Is it so fantastic
You don't have eyes. You see for yourself
The end of the line is two miles away
Is there anything so evil
Don't sleep
Didn't sleep
You two hurry
Go back to your home and find your mother
Lend me as much money as you have at home
If it's not enough
Just find buddies and sisters to gather together
Anyway, how much money is there before dawn
How much money do you give me
Do you hear me
Dong Zi, are you taking the wrong medicine? You
Who are you? You borrow money from door to door
There is no rich money in the hands of ordinary people now
You can borrow it if you say so
Can someone lend it to you
What are you talking about? You hurry
Just say I borrowed it
Get it
Walk
Remember to push our scooter over
Xiaomin, why don't you ask me to borrow money
Don't ask
Dong Zi
You are so early in the morning
What do you need so much money for
Buy books
You can pull it down. You
You also buy books
The sun rises from the west
When did you read a book? You
Talk nonsense
Say something sarcastic
I don't care about you. It's interesting to borrow money
You ask me to borrow money
I don't have any money either
I just have enough money to buy books with Xiaomin
I don't have any spare cash
Brother Wei Min
I asked you to borrow the money
I'll pay it back
Not Xiaomin. I-I don't mean that
You don't have to pay us back. Look
To return
Cold and cold
Cold cold cold
How do you manage people to borrow money in the middle of the night
Everybody's asleep
How to borrow it
Knocking on doors from house to house
Knock on the door
Then you can't be beaten out yet
Look at you like that
These are all old neighborhoods that look up but don't look down
Who will hit you
This Dong Zi thinks of coming out as soon as he comes out
You have to be scolded if you don't get beaten
Don't you talk about those useless things
Let's hurry
Dong Zi is still waiting
I found out
How come Dong Zi has a word
You are like an imperial edict
Why listen to him so much
You're really right
I'd love to let Dong Zi let me die
You knock
I dare not
Don't sleep, Uncle Chang
Would you please wake up
Who is it
I'm not dead in the middle of the night
What's the funeral
Grandpa, don't worry
I'm Juanzi
Juanzi
These two midnight
Why don't you talk about it tomorrow
Urgent matter
No matter how urgent it is
Wait till I wake up tomorrow morning
Xiaomin asked me to borrow some money from you
About Xiaomin
Wait
Ti Xiaomin really works
Don't worry, take your time
Walk, walk
One by one, one by one
Don't worry, take your time
Get in line
Come on, come on, come on
Step back and come one by one
Don't worry, don't worry
Dong Zi Dong Zi
Come on, come on
Hurry up, hurry up
Don't worry, don't worry
We're not late, are we
Qian Qian, hurry up
This knocks on doors from house to house to borrow money from others
This is the first time
We all borrowed it. It's all here
Xiaomin really has a face
When it comes to borrowing
Don't knock
How much money does the family have to pay out
That's if you don't look at our Xiaomin
What are you talking about
When did this Xiaomin become your family's
So what's the matter
It's not ours or yours
I'm telling you
Xiaomin is my girlfriend
Of course it's our family
No, no, no
Aren't you two a family
My own brother
It's not Huozi. What can I do for you
What's wrong with you
Dong Zi, let me tell you something
Xiaomin never promised to be your girlfriend
Don't be wishful thinking
That is
Let me tell you something
Xiaomin didn't say it
But I have me in my heart, understand
Stop your bullshit
Go away
Quick and quick
Walk, walk
Is that all right
Line line line
Hello, I want Anna Karenina.
Don't squeeze "The Old Man and the Sea" and "Junyou"
Don't squeeze
Don't squeeze here
Mo Bosang's "handsome friends" are gone
Comrades, comrades, Hugo's Les Miserables
Is there Stendhal's Red and Black
Yes, yes
Give me "Selected Poems of Pushkin" again
Good
Don't squeeze
Give it to me give it to me
I'll pay the money
Come on, step aside, step aside
Come and make way
What about here? What about here
I'm coming, everybody
Don't move, don't move
But with this money
Give me two sets of each famous book
Good
What are you looking at
What's there to see
Haven't you seen a cultural youth who loves books like life
Cattle
Don't worry, don't worry
Don't worry
Come on, come on. Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me
The last box
Good
Why don't you hurry home and go to bed
I haven't slept all night
Then what are you going to do
You don't care what I do
Go, go, go
Come on, come on. Excuse me. Excuse me
Give way, please
Excuse me. Excuse me
Smelly boy plays mystery all day
I guess I didn't suppress any good things
Let's go
Let me hold it for you
Thank you, Brother Weimin
Not bad. It's fine today
It's good, it's good, it's good
Coming, guys
What does Dong Zi mean
Fell asleep
Last night, our brothers waited for you half the night
Didn't show up
Yeah, Dong Zi
Every time this first stand should be yours
Don't ask
I must have dreamed of a beautiful woman last night
I didn't get up.
I haven't got up today
Guys
Don't gloat
Today, Brother Dong, I am kind
Let you guys
You said this is normal
I'm always here
Business is the best
Every time I look at you
Do you charge it two or three hours later than me
I can't bear it in my heart
Fighting righteousness
This good experience will be more frequent in the future
No problem
Dong Zi
Why don't you practice smoking and books today
You said how vulgar it is to practice smoking
Spiritual food
This is called spiritual food
Guys, you practice first
I'm going in line behind me
Get it
All right, take your time
It's good to walk slowly
Take a look and have a look
Come and make way. Make way
Coming. Excuse me
Walk slowly walk slowly walk slowly
Get it, get it
This is it
Take a look and take a look at the gap
Unloading
Come on, come on
Come on, take a walk and have a look
Freshly released foreign classics
Red and Black
Take a walk and have a look
Freshly released foreign classics
The latest foreign classics
Boss, how much is this book
There are prices in the back
Have a copy
Wait a minute
Double at this price
Double
Right
You are too dark here
Excuse me
That's how the price is fixed
What if you want it? You want it
Don't you wander around
I want it. I want it
All right
Thank you
Come and take a walk and have a look
Foreign masterpiece Red and Black
Freshly released foreign classics
Red and Black
I'll have one. Thank you
Here's your change. Here's your change
Come on, Pride and Prejudice
Come and take a walk and have a look
Take a walk and have a look
Take your time, take your time
There are all queues
There are queues. Don't grab them
Queue up
Double at the price
All right
Take a walk and have a look
This one has its own
There is a price behind there is a price behind
Freshly released foreign classics
Red and Black
Come
Double the price
Five dollars five dollars
"Gone with the Wind", wait a minute, wait a minute
"Gone with the Wind" There is "Gone with the Wind" here
Okay, let's go, let's go
Okay okay okay okay
Thank you thank you
Five dollars
Five bucks, five bucks, five bucks
Five bucks okay okay okay
Come on, come on
Come and double it
Five bucks, five bucks
Here's your change
Do you want this
Red and Black
Okay, okay, okay
Here's your change. Here's your change
Red and Black, right
Okay okay okay okay
Come on, come on
Mom, I'm home
Xiaomin went to buy books
Then you have to eat breakfast on the table quickly
Make up for sleep after eating
Where's my dad
I went to the root of the city wall early in the morning
I went to teach those apprentices to play wrestling
Xiaomin
Have you seen our Juanzi