Where Luo Ye hid
It is the most famous in Beiping
Slums and grocery places
The most miscellaneous and chaotic place
Is that the Communist Party goes door to door
It takes ten days and a half months
When they're done
The task will be completed
Chief Luo has long since run away
I was fine when I went out in the morning
How did you come back and fall ill
I asked Jujube this morning
She said she went to Iron Egg's wrestling ground
This is what happened when she came back.
Look at her eyes
Have you ever cried?
Don't ask
I'm sure I'm at odds with iron eggs again
This iron egg has no mercy at all
That's outrageous. Let me tell you something
This guy
Jujube is so sick that don't come to see it
What is it?
Why are you going
I didn't ask the boy with iron eggs
Why should he bully our family
Don't look for him, Uncle
Jujube, you said you were like this
Why are you still protecting him
Please, please
Are you really not looking
Jujube
Is Xiaozao at home
Comrade Li
They're all here
Have a look at it
Be ill
What's going on here
My sister, she is ill and has a bad heat
Burn so badly
Have to be sent to the hospital quickly
Jujube
I'm not going to the hospital I'm not going
Jujube can't be willful
Burn so badly
If you don't go to the hospital, you will be in danger
Uncle go behind your back, ok
Come on, come on
Go ahead, go ahead, go ahead
Go, Jujube Sister
Jujube, I know your mood at this moment
Since you call me sister,
Then listen to my sister's words
The iron egg thing
Now it's just a guess
There is no evidence that he is a spy
So don't worry too much
Take good care of your illness
More important than anything else
Elder sister
Don't comfort me
Iron egg, he lied to me
It's true that he worked as an instructor for spies
I asked his parents
Said he hurried out that day
I don't know if I've done something bad
Then when he left home,
Did you say anything to his parents
His parents said he went out in a hurry that day
Tell them to do something
Tell them not to worry
And told them not to tell anyone
I didn't say anything else
Sister, you said he wouldn't really
Go and do something bad
Jujube, listen to me
Whether Iron Egg is a spy or not is his business
It has nothing to do with you
It won't have any effect on you
From the first day I met you
I knew you were a good and brave man
A good girl with revolutionary enthusiasm
And you're working on a hospital homicide
It has made great contributions to the party
I'm telling you this
I just wanted to tell you
Everyone has the right to choose his own path
Some people will go astray
But I hope you can follow your own heart
Go firmly on the right road
Don't think so much
Have a good rest and recuperate your illness
Fell asleep without knowing it
Elder sister
You stayed with me all night
The fever is gone. Great
Are you comfortable
Leadership
It's great that you're here
The fever has gone down
I went to work, too
Take good care of her
Then you can eat a fried dough stick before you go
Don't eat
Leave it for you to eat. My unit has it
Take care of yourself
Have a good rest
I'll come to see you after work
Jujube sister, do you want to eat fried dough sticks
Your favorite food
Come
I'm really hungry
Jujube sister
Such a big leader stayed with you all night
I've heard about it before
This cadre of the Communist Party
It is true to the people
I kind of saw it with my own eyes today
There is porridge here
The information you provided is very important
Chief, I was going to find out
The exact lurking place of Luo Wenhui
It depends
Liang Liqun doesn't know his foothold either
Top killers like Luo Wenhui
Has always been a loner
It is impossible for Liang to know
Of his hiding place
In this way
Your mission in prison has been completed
There is no need to crouch here any longer
You're talking about
From these two agents
I really can't ask anything
You're coming with me now
Report directly to the headquarters
Team leader
Don't I need to get out of jail
Your undercover mission is top secret
Is directly affected by the Central Committee of the Communist Party of China
Directly led by the Ministry of Social Affairs
Local public security system
I don't know who you really are
What about this prison
It's the military system again
So there is no need to go through any formalities
Just come with me
Good
Go
Team Leader Wu
Comrade Sun Tie
Our Central Ministry of Social Affairs
In order to solve the assassination of leaders,
A special task force was set up
This is the temporary headquarters
From today on
You are a full member of our command
If you want to be noble in front of people,
Must suffer after others
Just bear it
Brother Tong hurts, hurts
What boy is called Master
Master, give me a break
You didn't start until you were six years old
It's really a little late
If you don't work hard,
Then it will be wasted
Push hard
The last name is Tong
You can really kill yourself.
You torture such a small child
Are you still human? You
Start and open
What are you messing around with here
Am I human
I'm doing it for his own good
So that he can form a horn
Have a serious meal to eat
Don't get mixed up like you
A loafer who is idle and achieves nothing
Who do you call a loafer
It's about you
What's the matter
I can't even find a prostitute I like
My sister is not a prostitute
I'm sorry, good apprentice
Master is wrong
Master apologizes to you
If you ever call my sister a whore again
I will never be your apprentice again
Don't don't don't
Good apprentice
Listen to Master and practice well
When it becomes a corner and has money,
Redeem your sister from that dirty place
Good boy
Is a good boy
Come and push hard
You don't have to hold me
I feel almost there
Why did the girl come back so soon
Why don't you keep it for two more days
Aunt, I'm all right
How can I stay in a hospital
Elder sister
I have been an apprentice to Brother Tong now
I want to practice well
Form an angle in the future
Thank you, fourth brother
I should be the one who said thank you
Can receive such a good apprentice
Chief Gao
According to Comrade Sun Tie's report
Secret agents lurk in Beiping's famous
Slum grocery store
The most miscellaneous and chaotic place should be the overpass
There are many people in Tianqiao area
The situation is very complicated
If you want to find Luo Wenhui's specific hiding place,
It is necessary to mobilize the masses
Conduct large-scale household screening
If there is such a big noise,
Will surprise Luo Wenhui
He will probably escape from his hiding place
We'll look for him then
But it's more difficult
That's right
If this method doesn't work
That flyover is such a large area
If you want to find the specific hiding place of Luo Wenhui,
It's like looking for a needle in a haystack
The celebration is only five days away, comrades
We have to hurry and find a way
Luo Wenhui
Section chief
Do you think you can bring me a team
We disguised ourselves as kitchen knife grinders and goldfish sellers
All kinds of vendors who play cotton and walk the streets
We lurk into the flyover
Our search from street to street
Maybe we can find the trace of Luo Wenhui
This method is not good
Doesn't this turn into a blind cat to touch a dead mouse
That's better than being stunned here
Maybe my blind cat
I really met a dead mouse
The train of thought is right
But where is Xiao Sun
We don't have the time now
Xiao Sun, the section chief, reminded me
We searched from house to house for fear of startle
There is not so much time to search along the street
Can we change our thinking
Luo Wenhui, he wants to live, too
He also wants to eat and buy things
Then we have all the information about Luo Wenhui here
Can we take this information from
Find out some of his living habits and characteristics
Then send someone to guard
Lao Wu, this idea is good
Come and let's take Tam Man-hui's information
Analyze it carefully again
Focus on his living habits
Start with hobbies
Try to find a breakthrough
Good
Coal core, this child has a good life
You have jujube, Aunt Li and Uncle Gui
And Shirley raised him
Now the boy boss has accepted him as an apprentice again
Let him learn his skills and become a horn
I really don't know what to say
I said
And me
Coal core is your brother
After that, it will be my brother-in-law
I'm interested in your sisters
That's really giving everything.
Brother Suo, I know you are good to me
And I know you want to marry me
But your ancestors are in the flag
Although it's not Maharaja Baylor, is it
But he is also the gentleman of the official family
Popular and spicy
I grew up eating, drinking and having fun with cages and birds all day
Even that small courtyard is your ancestral property
I'm a whore
Not worthy
Here we go again
And I'm telling you
Don't mention the word young master to me
I'm ruined by these two words
That's right
I'm a cage bird
Teasing crickets and raising Guo Guo grew up
But besides playing, I can
What else would I do
That little fortune handed down from the ancestors
It's all ruined to me
You see, I'm down and out to be a gangster
I heard the boy boss tell the coal core
Learn your skills well
Grow up and be a horn
Earn money to redeem your sister
I gave myself a big slap in the mouth
What am I
I'm a fart
Don't say you're redeemed
Even coming in to see you today
They were all rewarded by the boss
Mention my ancestors again
I've lost people when I mention my ancestors again. I
I also told you
Your brother, I can't bear it now
You can't carry a basket with your hands
A complete waste
You said you didn't deserve me
I really don't think I deserve you
Brother Suo, don't say that
At least you are the world
The man who really loves me most
Xi
We're not demanding
Why is it so hard to be together
We are really a pair of bad karma mandarin ducks
This hard time for us
When will it come to an end
Coal core
You've spent two hours. Are you tired
Have a rest
Tired
My master said
I won't practice this big muscle again
It won't open
Do you have any pain
Pain
You still practice when you hurt
I have to practice for my sister's pain
A real man
Then you practice
Sister, you have been ill in hospital for so long
Why didn't Brother Iron Egg come to see you
He's dead
He he's dead
How did you die
Drowned in a cesspit
You lie
Don't you ask
Don't ask what you shouldn't ask, okay
I'll fetch water for you to sleep later
According to this data,
Luo Wenhui is from Sichuan
An important characteristic of Sichuanese
It is inseparable from eating spicy food in life
This feature is obvious and prominent
It is not common in Beiping
It is not difficult to find him by following this clue
Look at that
Luo Wenhui in the photo
Dressed neatly
Explain what
It shows that he loves cleanliness very much
But the flyover is a grocery store
All the people who live are ordinary people
And next to Longxugou
The sanitary conditions there are extremely poor
Even the daily water supply
Have to queue up for limited supply at regular intervals
Peiping is now in midsummer
He loves cleanliness so much
How to solve the problem of bathing
Yeah
I see
From now on
We should focus on investigating Sichuan restaurants
Bathhouse
Team leader
Restaurants in this area of Beiping
Most of them are mainly Shandong Shandong cuisine
I don't think I've heard of it
What big Sichuan cuisine restaurant is operated
But near the overpass
Zhushikou and Hufangqiao Street
There are several Tsinghua pools
That is the place where Peiping people often take a bath
There is no big Sichuan restaurant
Is there a small restaurant opened by Sichuanese
Or a stall set up by Sichuanese
There should be
Not only Sichuan restaurants but also food stalls
Also check the vicinity of the overpass
All the vegetable stalls selling peppers
There is a good possibility
Luo Wenhui bought pepper
Go back and cook for yourself
Then this range is too large
Xiao Sun sent out all the men
Rely on the local government to check
Yes
In addition to these
This Luo Wenhui is before the action
I will definitely step on the spot in advance
So we're going to be on that day
On the route of leaders' actions
Place people in advance to guard
Maybe we can find Luo Wenhui's whereabouts
Comrades, the task has been clearly defined
Let's split up
Good
The mountain bladder opened
Hold out your chest and put your stomach away
Hook toe
Push on
Don't be discouraged
Kick
Sige coal core from morning till night
They're all kicking in the lower back
I was so tired of him that I panicked
Let the children rest for a while
Eat all the bitterness and be a master
Where is this practice?
Push hard
Why did you stop kicking?
Master, I have to pee
No pee kicking
I can't hold it anymore
That won't kick either
Fourth brother, you have gone too far
Children are not allowed to pee
It's suffocated. Wait a minute
You don't understand
What we pay attention to in this line of work is to practice urinating in the morning
It's up to practice and sweat to send this thing out
That's how my master practiced me at the beginning
No
Jujube
This coal core is now a disciple of the boy's boss
How people want to practice is a matter for both teachers and disciples
Don't worry about it here
I have to be redundant, okay
You are really redundant
You don't worry about what you should worry about
What you shouldn't worry about, you worry about it
Let me ask you something
What the hell is this iron egg doing
I haven't shown my face for so long
It's outrageous
That's it, jujube
I didn't dare ask you
You said you were so sick
This iron egg doesn't show a face
What's more important to him than you
Elder sister
What are you two doing here
Let's see if you're feeling better, both of us
I'm much better
How did you guys
I didn't collect coal and garbage today
No
These days
The government organized the people to clean up the garbage mountain
There are too many of us
I didn't join in the fun
I can't pick up the garbage
You won't go to Shun Grain, will you
Then how can it be
In the past, ah, it was the grain of the Kuomintang
It's the Communist Party now
It's government food
Isn't it a crime to steal from us again
You boys are clever
Brothers must be short of chewing grain during this time
How many children do I have for you
Take a bite
Sister sister
No need
We're both grown up
It's not easy to find someone who stutters
Yeah, that's not this morning
Kongsan, Tianqiao Wrestling Ground
Ask us to be his trust
Just help heat up the venue and shout
And we agreed
There are many businesses like this
Don't worry
Can't starve us
Grow up.
Know that you have planed
Let my sister rest assured
By the way, sister
Do you have any news from Brother Iron Egg
Nothing, sister
Tomorrow, I will go to the wrestling ground with Xiaofeng
I'll ask for you again
I'm sure I'll find it
Sell peppers. Sell peppers
Fresh pepper
It's not spicy and it doesn't cost money
Peppers are sold
It's not fresh. No money
Boss, how do you sell this cucumber
Aunt, we have two cucumbers and one big son
Is it fresh
How fresh it is
Aunt, look at it
Top flower with thorns
Master, master
Don't you think selling vegetables is an iron egg
Bullshit
Can iron eggs sell vegetables
Yes, it is an iron egg
Master, look at it quickly
Get it
Aunt, would you like some of this pepper
It's spicy. Eat that thing on this hot day
Fresh
Don't don't don't
That's true
Where is this sung?
Yeah
Sell peppers. Sell peppers
Fresh pepper
It's not spicy, it doesn't cost money. Which one does this sing?
Peppers are sold
The day after tomorrow is the right day for us to act
The third one told your men
There must be no mistakes
Yes
Team leader
This
When Liang Liqun first entered Beiping,
Meet us
It's been five or six days
I didn't see anyone either
It can't be something's wrong, can it
It's right not to show up
They are under the direct leadership of Shangfeng
I can connect with us to convey the peak
The task assigned to us
Yes
The task is very clear
Our task is to create chaos
Cover the safe evacuation of killer one
But
Brother
This
Who the hell is killer number one
How do I know
All I know is killer number one
Approximate area of hands-on
We just have to stay in that area that day
As soon as the gun goes off
Let's act immediately to create chaos
Finish our task and it's over
Who is the number one killer
We don't even know
How to finish the task
You're stupid
I made it so clear to you
We'll do it as soon as the gun goes off
Whoever it is
It's over to do our thing
And the identity of this character
The fewer people who know, the better
Didn't that Liang say it
This killer is a sharpshooter
Extremely deep in martial arts
Shangfeng sent him on a mission
Never lost his hand
Since we can send him out this time,
There is also a person named Liang who is responsible for containment
I think the target of assassination will die
We just need to cover his safe escape
The party and the state will be rewarded
Brother was exposed when he started in the street
It's exposed. Okay
The more exposed the better
After this operation is completed,
Shangfeng will definitely send us to evacuate Beiping immediately
What's the matter
You still want to stay in this place
To tell you the truth
Now as long as I walk down the street,
I always feel like there are countless pairs of eyes staring at me
These people in Beiping
Now it has been incited by the Communist Party
Every other time is the household survey
In such a short time
How many times have we moved our quarters
This is a day when people are neither ghosts nor ghosts
I don't want to spend another day
That's right
The PLA has just entered the city
Just take this Han Qingkui in one pot
And that Xu Ming Lao Mu
They were all caught by the Communist Party
Fortunately, I am a cunning rabbit
Multiple residences have been placed in advance
Otherwise, now the two of us
Must be in this Communist prison
Going to jail
Brother or you are wise
Brother stay up for two more days
Our brothers will escape from this misery
Yes
Good
Look, this is called tooth sword
Two wings busy
Good
Quanfu Qitian
May your gold and jade fill the halls
When I took this kite,
We must copy our armpits
Good
When I beat this little wood,
How is it
I won't talk anymore
Come quickly
Good
Open
Take a swim in your place inside the overpass
Shouting big bowls of noodles here
Shouting over there is boiled bean juice porridge
The name of the five apprentices is Jumping Huluba
The name of the six apprentices is to jump the gourd
Seven apprentices named Feng Suihua
The name of the eight apprentices is Hua Suifeng
Look over there
Fuck off
Cheating
You cheat
This is not cheating
There are kicks in wrestling
How can you kick if you have a kick
How to kick it
Boot belly down. This is called kicking
How can you kick this
I just kick
Just kick it
I kicked short today
Kick short
Kick your head high. It's gone
You can kick, can't you
Stabbing my foot is me
We can do this
I'll put my leg here for you to kick today
Kick for nothing, right? Kick for nothing
Kick and kowtow to learn from teachers
What if the kick is broken and broken
It doesn't matter. I'm not strong
Get it
This one
Kick and kowtow immediately
Pick up your legs at the front door later
I'll pick it up there
Connect
Good
It's boring
Bao Jin
Connect
Come on, come on
Come and push hard
Good
It's not you. Come on. Come on
What's the matter
You told me to kick
I did let you kick
What's the name of your leg lift
Is this called leg lifting
What's this called
Basic skills of wrestling
Kick and draw plates and kneel
I call this a big plate leg
Don't follow this dish
Can you lie down without this plate
Thank you all
Good
This was for us just now
It's up to you this time
Come on, come on
Give it all
OK, thank you
Everyone gives it
Give, give, give
Come and come
Everyone gives it
Take a look and have a look
Peppers are sold
Fresh pepper
It's not spicy and it doesn't cost money
Take a look and have a look
Fresh pepper
Elder sister, do you want to see the pepper
Big brother, how do you sell this pepper
Sister, listen to your accent
Are you from Sichuan
I'm from Luzhou, Sichuan
Luzhou
Hello, Luzhou
Luzhou produces wine
The water there is good
We have wine workshops all over the place
Elder sister, what do you have in this altar
This one
This is the watercress chili pepper sauce from our hometown
What
Pepper sauce with watercress
Hot sauce with watercress
We also sell watercress hot sauce on this overpass
There are few people in this Beiping city and Sichuan
It's not easy to eat some hometown food
I've been looking for it for a long time, too
I found a small shop selling pickles
The boss's wife is also from Sichuan
Their home
Occasionally, I will make some watercress chili pepper sauce for sale
So I'm a regular customer of his
Then this watercress hot sauce must be delicious
Do you know where this shop is
Walk two blocks ahead
Turn around and have a small facade
The sign says Mingyuan Sauce Restaurant.
To weigh peppers
Good
Thank you, elder sister
Guest officer
What can I get you
I'm from the Public Security Bureau
Sir
We are all law-abiding citizens
Didn't do anything illegal
Don't be nervous, you two
I'm here to get some information
I hope you can cooperate actively
Cooperate with certain cooperation
What can I do for you
Have you seen the man in the photo
Haven't seen it
Take a closer look
I really haven't seen it
Look at it
I seem to have met this man before
Really
When have you seen it
I remember him four days ago
I came to the store to buy watercress chili sauce
Wife of shop-owner, take a good look again
Are you sure
It's this man
That man is not as spiritual as the man in your picture
The man was dirty and unshaven
But the man's eyes looked fierce
It's exactly the same as the eyes in this photo
It should be him
Do you know where he lives
I don't know exactly where I live
But it should not be far from here
Sometimes I can meet him in the street
He should be on the south side
Thank you both
This is my phone
If you two see him again,
Don't disturb him
Call me right away
All right
You can rest assured to walk slowly
We thought of Sichuan cuisine
I thought of pepper
I just didn't think of Douban hot sauce
Iron eggs really have you
This time, ah
It's really a blind cat that meets a dead mouse
God has eyes
It really made me meet the big sister in Sichuan
Sure
Now that we know that Luo Wenhui
Approximate lurking position
So our grass-roots organizations
You will find a clue to him
Lao Wu immediately cooperated with the local police station
Get in touch with the street government
Check the registration of all migrants in that area
And household information
I'm on my way
I'll go with you
Go
There's someone inside
Do it
Wait
This master is good at kung fu
The three of us may not be able to catch him
In this way, we will go back and report to Chief Gao first
Yes
Go
I said Da Yong Xiao Feng
You two brothers are also very clever
Don't pick up rags and beg for food every day
Simply go to the wrestling ground to help
Isn't it okay to kowtow to me and be an apprentice
Right
Come on, third brother
I really want to learn to fall
Then we have to learn from Brother Iron Egg
He is my future brother-in-law
Say something bad
He is much better at kung fu than you
Xiaofeng
Don't mention your iron egg brother
He is now down and out selling vegetables all over the street
Why did he fall?
You learn wrestling from him
You're not ashamed
You talk nonsense
My brother Tiedan is a famous wrestling king in Beiping City
How can you run to the street to sell vegetables
You really don't believe it
Yesterday, I was on the street
See, it's called a real one
He is carrying the burden and selling vegetables all over the street now
You don't believe me. Ask my master
Third brother, what he said is true
It's absolutely true
I saw him at the alley yesterday
Because one big son and two cucumbers
I'm still talking with an old lady
I should have said hello to him
But wasn't I afraid he wouldn't hang up
I ignored him
No, you're sure it's Iron Egg
My friendship with him
I can recognize him when he burns to ashes
You can never go wrong
Go
Brother
There was light just now
Where are the people
Hot sauce with watercress
It must be Luo Wenhui
Lao Wu asked the comrades to search carefully in the warehouse
Yes
Comrades check carefully
Did Tiedan see Luo Wenhui
No