=Love Me in Three Days=
=Episode 2=
(Five years ago)
Thank you.
Looking forward to working with you.
I've talked to the board
about the project.
Come on.
Let's wish Xinge Group will
get better and better.
Sir, are you not feeling well?
(In the past five years,)
(whenever I touch someone
for more than five seconds,)
(I'll turn into
that person's appearance.)
(I'll change back to myself
after three days.)
Mr. Shan, are you okay?
(But I didn't expect that
I changed back early)
(after kissing you today.)
You don't have to know why I'd change
like that.
You just have to kiss me
whenever I change into someone else
after we get married.
Get...
Get married?
Our wedding is fixed on 3rd next month.
After all, I'm busy
at other time.
Oh, right.
There's a secret agreement
that I need you to sign
because if
you expose my secret,
you need to bear the consequences.
I got it now.
It's not just your body.
Even your brain can't function well.
You don't believe me, do you?
I don't.
Mr. Shan,
I've prepared the things
that you asked me to prepare.
Yan.
Come and touch me.
No, but she's here.
Hurry up.
I got it now.
You have my blessing.
I'm leaving now.
Hold on.
You...
You two...
Don't come near!
See?
I didn't lie to you.
Who are you?
Why did you kiss me?
I'm so unlucky today.
I don't even know you
and you've kissed me twice.
Yan.
Take this as our wedding gift.
Here you go.
Are you crazy?
It's expensive.
You're getting married with me
to make me
a tool to recover yourself.
I don't accept it.
Also, I don't want to see you anymore.
Why wouldn't she accept it?
It happens too fast.
Let me tell you.
To normal people,
we need to date before we get married.
(I thought I'll be in love
wearing the high heels.)
(It just doesn't work that way.)
Chenxing,
why would I fail both
in my career and my relationship?
It's okay, Xia Luoluo.
Good luck will fall upon you.
Xinge Group?
(Job requirement)
I wonder who the boss is.
Such a wise man.
(Xinge Group)
Miss Xia Luoluo.
Let me introduce.
This is the CEO of Xinge Group,
Mr. Shan Yifan.
You're the CEO of Xinge Group?
I'm sincerely asking you
to work in Xinge Group.
Tell me what's the job about.
The job scope is simple.
Date me.
♪I'm honoured to have met you♪
♪During the rainy season♪
♪You have wide shoulders♪
♪Protecting me from the rain and wind♪
♪Keeping you company is an honour♪
♪In this long journey♪
♪Love is shining gently♪
♪In our eyes♪
♪It's my honour♪