=Love Me in Three Days=
=Episode 19=
Luoluo.
Can you give me another chance?
Don't you think it's too late now?
But, I really don't want to lose you.
I mean it.
Well.
Let's play a game.
You're not playing?
No, you...
Stop.
Are you playing or not?
I'll ask and you answer.
If your answer meets my requirement,
you can take a step ahead.
If it doesn't,
you need to take a step back.
Why not we...
Stop.
Go back.
Okay.
Are you playing or not?
Yes.
From now on,
can you not have any other girls
by your side besides me?
But there are 358 female employees
in Xinge Group.
I can't possibly get them...
Step back.
Do I have more strength than flaws?
Why not we change...
Stop.
Get back.
I got the answer now. Step back.
Step back.
The last question.
Am I the most beautiful woman
in the world?
Tell me.
If you insist on asking such a question
in a macroscopic scale,
I really...
Step back!
Can't you say something
to make me happy?
It's so annoying.
I'm not playing with you anymore.
Xia Luoluo.
The exclusive seat next to me
has always been yours.
No other girl has seated on it
besides you.
You asked me if you have more strength
or more flaws.
I don't care about
your strength or flaws,
I like you.
As long as it's you,
I like it.
I don't mind.
You asked me
if you're the most beautiful girl
in the world.
At least in my heart,
you're the most beautiful girl.
So,
do you like me?
What do you think?
I like you.
Of course I like you.
I like you very much.
Not like I'm a tool to you?
You're the girl I like the most
in my life.
Is it like love?
It's love.
You're my everything and my whole world,
okay?
But I really...
You know me.
I don't know how to express myself.
I don't know what to say.
You're my everything.
All right.
I got it now.
Come over.
♪I'm honoured to have met you♪
♪You have wide shoulders♪
Come over.
♪Protecting me from the rain and wind♪
♪Keeping you company is an honour♪
♪In this long journey♪
♪Love is shining gently♪
♪In our eyes♪
So, I have a boyfriend now,
right?
Wait.
What about Shan Chenxing?
You didn't say yes to him?
You only noticed that now?
Luoluo, can you give me a chance?
If you accept the flower,
it means you've accepted me.
Chenxing,
I know when I was in trouble,
you've helped me before.
But, I was only moved,
not like I like you.
Admiration is not love either.
So,
I'm so sorry.
I can't accept you.
I'm sorry.
Is it because of Yifan?
You told me that
I'm gentler
and more thoughtful than him.
Luoluo,
if you agree to be with me,
I'll treat you better.
But...
But, he's now in my heart.
I'm sorry.
Take this.
Even if we can't be together,
we can still be friends.
Thank you.
What a shame.
He was pursuing me with passion,
I couldn't return the favour.
Fine.
I'll invest in his Shadow World.
Take that as your return to him.
Why are you being so nice to me, Yifan?
Of course. Isn't he your idol,
Luoluo?
Are you serious?
Of course.
Fine, look for my brother then.
Okay, fine.
Are you angry?
What did Xia Luoluo do
that she gets to seduce Yifan?
She's good at that.
Not only did she seduce Mr. Shan Yifan,
she's seducing Mr. Shan Chenxing
as well.
I knew it.
It's my fault
that I didn't come back earlier.
Yes, Miss Xuewei.
What are you doing?
Sit back there.
I think
you're the perfect match for our CEO.
Xia Luoluo
is a pretentious mistress.
She's not a good person.
I need to think of a way
to let Yifan know
what kind of a person Xia Luoluo is.
Mr. Fang,
help me make a invitation card.
(Chenxing is about to start his movie.)
(Why is he holding a home party?)
(Celebrities are different.
They celebrate everything.)
1108.
1109.
I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
I'm all wet.
Why not you get changed
and put on the pajamas?
I'll get the customer service
to take the dirty dress from you.
Sure, I'll get changed now.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
(Xia Luoluo,)
(when I take a photo of you
meeting Shan Chenxing in private,)
(I'll see how you can still
get together with Yifan.)
How did you get in here?
What are you trying to do?
Xia Luoluo!
How dare you meet Shan Chenxing
in private behind Yifan's back?
♪I'm honoured to have met you♪
♪During the rainy season♪
♪You have wide shoulders♪
♪Protecting me from the rain and wind♪
♪Keeping you company is an honour♪
♪In this long journey♪
♪Love is shining gently♪
♪In our eyes♪
♪It's my honour♪