=Love Me in Three Days=
=Episode 5=
Babe, I'm counting on you.
You must record how he transforms.
Mr. Shan.
I'm coming in.
(I'm so lucky.)
What are you doing?
Why are you not wearing
your clothes properly?
Why should I do that at home?
Immoral.
What did you say?
Did you bring what I asked you to bring?
Yes.
What were you doing
in the past one hour?
What took you so long?
I rode an electric bike here
after working hour
to deliver the document to my boss
and it's pathetic enough.
How dare you say I was slow?
The document!
Here.
You must hold his hand for
more than five seconds.
No matter how he refuses,
you must not let go.
Don't worry.
I'm paid
so I'll get the job done.
Remember, five seconds.
No problem.
You're here.
I thought no one is using
the meeting room.
Mr. Shan wanted to meet us.
You have to join, too.
Let me use your laptop.
No.
Why?
My laptop is damaged.
This is an office laptop.
Xia Luoluo.
Photocopy this.
What?
Didn't you hear me?
Xia Luoluo, what's this?
Xia Luoluo.
My laptop has virus.
Go and photocopy the document.
Nice abs.
I
will check things out.
I'll get you a glass of water.
Tell me.
Why did you set up a camera in my house?
Nothing.
Are you helping Shan Chenxing
and being a spy for him?
No.
Did you forget what I said to you?
If you become a spy again,
you're done.
(No, I can't admit it.)
(I need an excuse.)
Can't find an excuse?
Who is looking for an excuse?
I...
I set up the camera at your house
to record your abs.
What?
After I leave in a hurry,
I can't forget about your abs, Mr. Shan.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Sure.
Let me satisfy you.
Didn't you want to see this?
Yes.
You're unbuttoning it too slowly.
Let me do it.
Are you not taking off yours?
It's not fair for me to
take off my clothes alone.
Or
you need my help?
No!
Mr. Shan.
I was wrong.
What did you do wrong?
I was wrong about everything.
Make it clear.
I...
I shouldn't be a spy.
You're helping Shan Chenxing
because he's your idol?
It's not as simple as you think.
Actually, he's important to me.
♪I'm honoured to have met you♪
♪During the rainy season♪
♪You have wide shoulders♪
♪Protecting me from the rain and wind♪
♪Keeping you company is an honour♪
♪In this long journey♪
♪Love is shining gently♪
♪In our eyes♪
♪It's my honour♪