Subtitles and Timing provided to you by
🎶 The Copper Sparrow 🪶Team @viki.com
"Go Ahead Fearlessly" - Liu Yuning
♫  Grudges and karma, right and wrong  ♫
♫  The past hides blood and tears  ♫
♫  It is hard to catch up after years of separation  ♫
♫  The truth cannot be fully revealed  ♫
♫  Fate is full of twists and turns  ♫
♫  Life and death, fortune and misfortune go hand in hand  ♫
♫  Obsession is hard to get rid of, keeping the truth
and getting rid of the lies, let the wind blow  ♫
♫  Tossed about by the wind and rain, I will never regret it,
I will accompany you for my whole life  ♫
♫  At least you share my joy and sorrow  ♫
♫  Unravelling fate, fearlessly, a dream returns  ♫
♫  The mountains and rivers are bright and beautiful,
holding hands, together we return  ♫
♫  In this life, my heart returns untainted of dust and ash  ♫
Just sit in and listen. Do not cause trouble.
Or you'll be charged with disrupting the court trial.
How terrifying!
But then again,
even if Ji Fangming is a minor official in the Ministry of Justice,
he is still appointed by the imperial court.
I certainly will not stand by and let you force a confession.
Ji Fangming, you may have many tricks up your sleeves,
but those are nothing but tricks.
What's fake is fake. Truth can't be forged.
You have been plotting for years
just to find out the truth about the case of the Jinxiu Workshop.
What a pity! You ended up targeting and killing
the wrong person for your revenge,
unaware that you were being used.
Clerk Yan, save your breath.
Your attempt to lure a confession from me is not so innovative.
Since you're so curious, I will tell you the truth.
Chen Shoujie and his wife, Madam Chen, were the instigators of that case.
I plotted everything that had happened these days
just to avenge the dozens of people who had died from injustice at the Jinxiu Workshop.
Why are you so certain that you know the absolute truth?
Madam Chen used to be an embroideress there.
Chen Shoujie took advantage of his position to cover for her
by forging her background and falsifying others' testimonies.
Back then, before Kong Xianrong delivered the summer clothing design
to Princess Runing's mansion,
he had checked them in person and sealed them after checking with the embroideresses.
Therefore, it must have been swapped by one of the embroideresses.
After that, everyone at the Jinxiu Workshop was put away for interrogation.
Only Madam Chen got away with it.
Once I found out about it, I went to sound Chen Shoujie out.
Shoujie, do you remember this?
Jinxiu Workshop?
No, you can't mention it! I don't want to die!
I apologize. We apologize. We don't know anything.
Every grievance has a source. Please don't come to us for retribution.
Wife, you must not say anything!
Just because of that, you concluded that Chen Shoujie was the murderer?
Do you know why those people would be terrified by the illusions?
Because they knew that the deceased had died unjustly
and might seek retaliation as vengeful spirits.
They felt guilty!
Spirits don't exist in this world.
Even if they do, they only exist in people's minds.
If you have a clear conscience, why would you be afraid of them?
Minister Shen, you're truly upright.
But not everyone is like you've described.
Some people may be able to act decent
even if they have done something shameful!
They may appear just like ordinary people.
So you killed Madam Chen.
That's right! She deserved to die! She was the ringleader!
She was the one who swapped the summer clothing design.
Jinxiu Workshop.
Karma has gotten me!
Do you have anything to say?
It's time to pay my debt.
I killed her to comfort the spirit of my best friend in heaven.
What's wrong with that?
Even the most sinister criminal shall be punished by the court and the law.
You are free to seek justice by appealing the case.
But you can't take the law into your own hands.
That's easy for you to say.
Seeking justice? Appealing the case?
So many years have passed. Everyone knows it was a wrongful conviction.
But who is willing to step forward and do justice?
Forget about others. Let's just talk about you.
Holding a high position, you've won the Empress Dowager's trust.
Yet you have let this case remain buried for years.
In that case, I might as well deal with the real culprits.
So you killed Madam Chen and spared Chen Shoujie,
who lost his senses due to the shock,
not for the sake of the old days, but to torture him alive. Right?
That's right.
Madam Chen was the instigator and deserved to die.
As for Chen Shoujie, I didn't kill him not because I didn't want to.
He shielded the murderer and cannot escape the blame.
An easy death wouldn't serve him right.
It suddenly occurred to me that I could torture him to death.
Let him experience the helplessness and despair we had experienced
when we lost our family and friends back then!
Brother Xianrong.
I have finally done you justice.
Those people should be
condemned to never enter the cycle of reincarnation!
But now, he has already gone mad!
Yet you all still believe that he is innocent.
You just won't accept the fact that the deceased were wrongfully accused.
So you are all guilty as well!
You all should pay the price for this.
What fire moths?
Fire moths, fire moths, fire moths!
I found the fabric of the Jinxiu Workshop at Chen Shoujie's mansion.
If they were the real culprits as you said,
why would they carefully preserve something
that constantly reminded them of their sin?
No way!
Perhaps, you're not the only one
feeling helpless and anguished after the incident.
I can't be wrong.
There's no way I'm wrong.
Perhaps you were blinded by revenge and didn't realize that
Mrs. Chen kept staring at the hidden compartment
on the roof beam where she had hidden the cloth until she died.
Perhaps she wanted to talk but she never got the chance.
It's all my fault. It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have concealed the truth for years.
I didn't want to die.
I have harmed so many people to protect my family.
I deserve to die.
No one can wrap fire in paper.
The truth is about to come to light.
Xianrong, I owe you an apology.
I was coerced to close the case in such a hurry because I was afraid of death.
I didn't expect… I didn't expect…
Coerced? By whom? Tell me now.
What's the point of confessing now?
So many people have suffered injustice and couldn't find peace.
As a public official, you covered up the truth because the real culprit intimated you.
Can you bring back the deceased even if you confess now?
Who coerced you?
Huo'e…
Chen Huo'e! Chen Huo'e! Chen Huo'e!
Chen Huo'e!
Chen Huo'e again?
No way, I didn't kill the wrong person.
Madam Chen was the culprit. She wouldn't have lied to me.
Who instructed you to lead Yan Xing to the Mingsheng Temple?
They used me for real.
People laugh at the moths flying to the flame.
But no one knows that mayflies live at dawn and die at dusk,
not entering the cycle of reincarnation, while moths survive the fire and await reincarnation.
Ji Fangming, wake up.
Kong Xianrong never stopped proclaiming his innocence.
All he wanted was justice and the truth.
But you were blinded by hatred and were incited to kill the innocent.
How are you any different from those who framed the Jinxiu Workshop?
There's solid evidence,
yet you are still spreading deceitful rumors to confuse the public.
Great Chief Shen,
don't you want to know who the other culprits are
as Chen Huo'e told me after she got resurrected?
The real culprit is...
the Princess of Valor.
The Princess of Valor has been jealous of Princess Runing for years.
- Thus, she used the Jinxiu Workshop to frame her.
- Shut your mouth!
Apart from her, Prince Xian was also involved.
He wouldn't settle for less than the Princess of Valor and craved power.
And the Grand Empress Dowager. They are all murderers.
You…
You're all murderers.
You're making a fuss by framing the royal family
and slandering the Grand Empress Dowager just to get a retrial.
Great Chief Shen, this is a serious matter.
A retrial may have implications.
Do not bring trouble upon yourself.
Just ignore this madman's ravings.
Wu Taiming, you despicable being!
I am not crazy.
I am more awake than ever.
I mean everything I say.
Great Chief Shen, I wonder if you dare to report what I said
to the Grand Empress Dowager without missing a single word.
You're really wishing for the death penalty.
If I can console
those lost souls and spirits by sacrificing myself,
then it is worth it.
In that case,
I shall do as you wish.
I will report what happened today to the Grand Empress Dowager.
Vice Minister Lai, what do you think?
You are the chief judge.
The Imperial Inspectorate is merely sitting in on the murder case of Madam Chen.
The final ruling is up to you, Great Chief.
One acts indifferently.
The other is as sly as a fox.
They make sure they stay out of the matter.
I, Ji Fangming, appreciate your effort on behalf of the wronged souls,
Great Chief Shen.
I truly admire you for your intelligence and courage, Clerk Yan.
I wonder if you're interested in joining the Imperial Inspectorate.
I'm in dire need of a capable assistant like you.
Master Wu, you won't be so petty as to hold on to a talent. Right?
Please don't make fun of me, My Lord.
Yan Xing may be working for the Ministry of Justice,
but she is also Great Chief Shen's wife.
You surely don't intend to take my person away in my presence. Right?
What an accusation.
It seems I have been rash and inconsiderate.
I simply wished to recruit some talents under my wing.
Please don't be paranoid.
Paranoid?
After all these years, you're still an expert in making counter charges.
Matters of the officialdom should not involve family.
Given your way of handling things,
I'm afraid that Clerk Yan wouldn't have a good time
if she had to spend all day with you to solve cases.
Besides, a fine bird chooses the tree upon which to perch.
You shouldn't hinder those who have a promising future. Right?
I'm quite content with this tree.
I am a lazy person who enjoys a leisurely life.
I don't intend to work somewhere else yet.
Minister Lai, thank you for your recognition.
In that case, I'll wait and see
how great the tree you've chosen can be.
People say that although a couple were birds from the same forest,
they'd fly in separate directions in adversity.
Master Wu, what do you think?
Well… I am dull-witted.
Love and affection are unfathomable to me.
"Love and affection." Well said.
Interesting!
It's a serious matter.
A retrial may have implications.
Do not bring trouble upon yourself.
The final ruling is up to you, Great Chief.
What are you thinking? Why are you absorbed?
I'm so tired. I need to rest now.
Is something wrong?
Yun Que seems particularly concerned about this interrogation.
She has been after the case of the Jinxiu Workshop all along.
Now, she can no longer hold back.
So you kept her in the mansion just to find out
whether she showed up out of a coincidence
or if someone was fanning the flames.
Jing Lin has looked into her.
She doesn't know much about the matter.
- However…
- However what?
However, her parents did have a lot of business dealings with
Jinxiu Workshop in the past.
But they were not implicated.
If they hid evidence to protect themselves,
then why did she steal the evidence to seek justice
after Chen Huo'e showed up?
Isn't it too much of a coincidence?
If that's the case, why don't you ask them directly?
It's not time yet.
And I'm afraid it won't be easy to keep them alive to testify.
We are in the light, the enemy in the dark.
Just leave it to me.
But the old case involves multiple parties.
Even Wu Taiming and Lai Luozhi were desperate to stay out of it.
It seems that the truth might be much darker than I expected.
What a surprise! The fearless Sixth Miss Yan can be afraid.
Are you really going to convey Ji Fangming's dangerous statements
to the Grand Empress Dowager?
I promised someone to get to the bottom of this old case in person.
Someone?
It can't be Princess Runing…
Fearlessness comes from ignorance.
Deep fear derives from knowledge.
Now I see the gap between us.
You knew this day would come,
yet you remained so calm and composed.
You don't sound like yourself.
Usually, you'd jump into action the moment
you heard about wrongful convictions.
And no one could stop you.
Of course.
Stand against injustice to serve justice.
That's our job as officials who get paid by the imperial court.
But I'm also aware of
the consequences of reopening the Jinxiu Workshop case.
With nothing but Ji Fangming's accusation, I'm afraid…
You have improved.
That wrongful conviction caused a sensation
and traumatized many commoners.
If we retry the case,
the shadows will fall upon all of us again.
No one will be able to avoid it.
That's right.
They wanted to use Ji Fangming to bring attention to the old case
and lead the people to doubt the royal family.
Ji Fangming must have realized
that he was being used but he had no choice.
How pitiful!
And tragic!
How confident are you about the retrial?
That's why I am worried. It's been so many years.
The Grand Empress Dowager may not allow a retrial if you bring it up suddenly.
Besides, what if she takes it out on you…
So, you've been worried since you left the Ministry of Justice
because of me?
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried you'll get me involved.
Anyway, I am known as Madam Shen at the moment.
And I have to think about all these people in our household.
Everyone holds a position.
The wronged people want the old case to be reviewed.
And the Grand Empress Dowager wants nothing but peace and happiness for the people.
But what about you?
Don't worry about me.
I have this under control.
I said I'm not worried about you.
Then I'll leave the one at home to you, Wife.
Since you know she is trouble, why do you still keep her around?
She may have key evidence on her.
Is that your explanation?
White Ghost is truly cold and callous.
You only cause people trouble.
Jing Lin, keep an eye on Yun Que.
If you find a chance, check and see if she's still hiding
something about the case.
Understood.
Abduct someone for me.
It's not a real abduction.
I just need you to make a trip to Jiangnan and bring the person safely here.
Jiangnan?
I remember that Yun Que
who wants to take your place as Madam Shen is from Jiangnan. Right?
Don't tell me you're jealous and want to…
Please, Talented Young Master Pan.
Master Pan. Pan Chi. Only you can help me with this.
Please.
It's not such a big deal.
- However, it's a bit of legwork.
- Rest assured.
Once you return, I will definitely treat you to a feast
and buy you top-quality alcohol.
Besides, I can tell that you're no ordinary merchant.
But I swear I won't expose you.
Are you threatening me?
Of course not. How would I dare?
After all, we are good friends who help each other out.
- Just friends?
- What did you say?
Nothing. Then I'll be waiting for the feast.
Right. Take this with you. It's on the way.
- What is this?
- A list of the people killed by Chen Huo'e.
You…
The crossed-out ones are the names
of the victims who were murdered near Xiang'an.
You'll pass by a few on the way,
so you can inquire about the deceased.
It's so hard to get a treat from you.
Right. Take this. I just obtained it.
Why are you giving me a fan?
Is there something fancy?
Be careful now. It has a mechanism.
The fan handle is hollow. You can put powder in it.
With a little sprinkle, you can disperse the powder without anyone noticing.
The fan handle is hollow.
Is this for poisoning?
That's not exactly the case.
How you use a hidden weapon is up to you.
You're giving me such a rare item?
Don't tell me…
Don't tell me you're forcing me to buy it?!
Just take it for now. You can pay me if you find it useful.
So you are indeed forcing me to buy it.
Is there poison in it?
It can't kill anyone. But it can easily take down a cow.
Have you heard?
- Another miracle at the Jinxiu Workshop ruins.
- Really?
Swarms of moths fluttered against the wall. Blood formed words.
Even the moths are crying out for justice for the deceased.
These moths are sinister. They're taking revenge on the real culprits.
The Jinxiu Workshop matter happened so many years ago.
Why is it happening so suddenly?
Haven't you heard? Someone else has died because of that case.
Everyone is deeply concerned.
It must have been a wrong conviction.
Too many people died tragically, unable to be vindicated.
That's why they lingered here.
Surely they won't just go after anyone. Right?
We are innocent.
It's said that only by reopening the case
and doing justice can these wronged spirits rest in peace.
Why aren't you eating?
The noodles are getting mushy.
You came back so late. I bet you've eaten outside.
Of course. I don't mind working hard but I can't starve.
I have done so much in the past few days.
I'm exhausted.
Dig in.
You know what?
I visited the Jinxiu Workshop at night
and as expected, I saw something like a ghost fire floating in midair.
There was something drifting, but I couldn't see it clearly.
That must be the ghostly shadow mentioned by the people.
On the way back, I saw each and every household next to the Jinxiu Workshop
having this hung above the entrance.
The Moth Jade.
You went there alone at night?
Didn't you find it creepy?
Those rumors are fabricated.
They're obviously made up
by Chen Huo'e who supposedly came back to life.
But I did see ghost fires quite often in the cemeteries during summer.
My master once told me that it happened because
something imperceptible arising from
the decomposing corpses was ignited in the dry air.
The ghostly shadows must have been created in a similar way.
It's just the shadow of a fast-moving black bird or beast.
I knew it. You know everything.
Did you plan this?
The Jinxiu Workshop should be guarded by the Imperial Guards.
But this afternoon, when the moths smashed themselves
onto the wall "miraculously," the guards did not disperse the crowd.
Jing Lin was there, but he just watched from a distance.
So what?
The Imperial Guards have a lot to investigate.
Ji Fangming has been arrested.
I don't need to bother.
Aren't you waiting?
For what?
For a trend...
that can help you reopen the Jinxiu Workshop case.
You went out for a bit and brought something back.
Be careful!
Don't play with it! Don't do that!
So nervous. Who gave it to you?
I haven't paid for this fan yet. Don't break it!
Really?
Why are you acting weird these days?
Am I?
Yes, you are.
If I forget to prepare the medicinal meal in time, find something to eat.
Don't starve.
And you're not allowed to just talk nonsense out of nowhere
and then assume a frightening pose.
And you're not allowed to suddenly…
Suddenly what?
Suddenly…
You're not allowed to waste food.
Fine.
I won't.
But you must not do something dangerous like visiting the Jinxiu Workshop at night again.
Luckily, I had someone on guard there tonight.
Otherwise, you could have been in grave danger.
Just this once. Don't do this again.
What's going on?
I feel so dizzy.
No way, Pan Chi.
This time, you really got me into big trouble.
Yan Xing.
Take down a cow.
What…
♫  The night is still long and the moonlight shines in the west window  ♫
You smell so good.
♫  With one touch, my heart flutters like the shadow of a candle, swaying and trembling  ♫
♫  The more one cares, the deeper it's concealed  ♫
♫  Leaves fall and turn yellow, with a thousand lines of yearning  ♫
Stop taking advantage of me.
♫  Two hearts collide between dawn and dusk  ♫
♫  Embraces come unexpectedly  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to hold you, staying by my side  ♫
♫  Passing through the obstruction of a storm  ♫
♫  I want to be your moonlight  ♫
♫  To accompany you to every dawn  ♫
♫  How I wish I could just forget the length of time  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, never forgetting each other  ♫
♫  There is always a place where the clouds and the sea meet  ♫
♫  I want to accompany you forever  ♫
♫  I will wait until my black hair turns grey  ♫
♫  In this life, I will only keep you in my heart  ♫
Not allowed.
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to hold you, staying by my side  ♫
♫  Passing through the obstruction of a storm  ♫
♫  I want to be your moonlight  ♫
♫  To accompany you to every dawn  ♫
♫  How I wish I could just forget the length of time  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to hold you, staying by my side  ♫
♫  Passing through the obstruction of a storm  ♫
♫  I want to be your moonlight  ♫
♫  To accompany you to every dawn  ♫
♫  How I wish I could just forget the length of time  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
It seems we have to...
pay for this fan.
♫  I want to accompany you forever  ♫
♫  I will wait until my black hair turns grey  ♫
♫  In this life, I will only keep you in my heart  ♫
Let her sleep.
Don't wake her up.
Understood.
Ji Fangming is outrageous.
His lack of proper conduct is already a grave disrespect.
He even dares to slander Prince Xian and the Princess of Valor
with the old case of the Jinxiu Workshop.
He deserves to die.
Grand Empress Dowager, Ji Fangming surely deserves to die.
But he was definitely instigated by someone.
They used his obsession to spread rumors.
Who did it?
The serial killer committed suicide upon her arrest five years ago.
Chen Huo'e.
What?
A person who has died
can still stir up trouble in Xiang'an City?
I remember you investigated
this case in person, Lai Luozhi.
What exactly happened?
Responding to Grand Empress Dowager.
The case of Chen Huo'e caused panic among the people.
Therefore, I executed her in public after I arrested her.
Half of the Xiang'an citizens were there
and they saw Chen Huo'e taking her own life.
Her corpse was thrown into a mass grave under the people's watch.
- It's just…
- Just what?
It's just that she had said crazy things about coming back to life.
So you're saying that she has truly come back to life?
Recently, rumors have it that Chen Huo'e has appeared.
And some followers are convinced
that she was Chen Huo'e who had killed herself five years ago.
But in my humble opinion,
someone has been using this to cause trouble and bewitch the people.
My ministers,
Chen Huo'e fabricated miracles to make the people suspect
that the people of the Jinxiu Workshop suffered injustice.
The Imperial Guards
have asked for permission to retry the cases of Chen Huo'e
and the Jinxiu Workshop.
Gentlemen, what are your opinions?
Your Majesty loves the people.
Now that Great Chief Shen intends to retry this case,
I don't see a problem here.
Vice Minister Lai, what do you think?
In my humble opinion,
the case must have been suddenly brought up for a reason.
But I dare not speculate
if the case would disturb the peace of Xiang'an City.
Grand Empress Dowager, I reviewed the previous files
and realized many unresolved mysteries.
Your Majesty has always been caring for the people.
I know it's a tricky issue but I dare not withhold the truth.
Grand Empress Dowager, in my humble opinion, Great Chief Shen is right.
If we can unravel the truth and bring peace to the people,
Your Majesty will surely be pleased.
That's also a way to show Mother Empress's determination to
free people from worries.
"Free people from worries." Well said.
Minister Shen, I will entrust this case solely to you.
You must get to the bottom of it.
I accept the command and will not fail to meet Your Majesty's expectations.
I'll arrest the culprit as soon as possible.
What do you think about Great Chief Shen's request for a thorough investigation of this case?
What happened back then caused panic among the people.
- I shall take my leave.
Your Highness never interferes too much with court affairs.
But you attracted unwanted attention this time.
Sir, I didn't think too much.
I just want to see what Shen Du would do.
Back then, when Princess Runing
was punished for the clothing design,
some people suspected that it was the work of the Princess of Valor.
Now that the case will be retried,
if it turns out to be related to the Princess of Valor,
then it would be great news for us.
We can use them to eliminate adversaries.
You misunderstand.
I only want to find out what happened back then.
Subtitles and Timing provided to you by
🎶 The Copper Sparrow 🪶Team @viki.com
"Only Want You" - Ding Yuxi, Deng Enxi
♫  One look confirmed our fate  ♫
♫  Upon meeting again, I know you're the one for me  ♫
♫  Gaze at the stars, dreaming about old times  ♫
♫  A pair of people have already taken root  ♫
♫  Lovers before the candlelight, do not ask their thoughts  ♫
♫  Affection is bound, lasting forever  ♫
♫  Using the evening breeze to express deep love  ♫
♫  I have someone I long for in this life  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  You are the only one for me  ♫
♫  Embracing each other, how serious we are about our love  ♫
♫  Every moment is treasured  ♫
♫  From dawn to dusk  ♫
♫  You and I, forever inseparable  ♫
♫  Without noticing, you broke into my heart  ♫
♫  Slowly immersing myself, I become undaunted by perils for love  ♫
♫  I charge into battle with unmatched resilience  ♫
♫  Because you are my responsibility  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  You are the only one for me  ♫