Subtitles and Timing provided to you by
🎶 The Copper Sparrow 🪶Team @viki.com
"Go Ahead Fearlessly" - Liu Yuning
♫  Grudges and karma, right and wrong  ♫
♫  The past hides blood and tears  ♫
♫  It is hard to catch up after years of separation  ♫
♫  The truth cannot be fully revealed  ♫
♫  Fate is full of twists and turns  ♫
♫  Life and death, fortune and misfortune go hand in hand  ♫
♫  Obsession is hard to get rid of, keeping the truth
and getting rid of the lies, let the wind blow  ♫
♫  Tossed about by the wind and rain, I will never regret it,
I will accompany you for my whole life  ♫
♫  At least you share my joy and sorrow  ♫
♫  Unravelling fate, fearlessly, a dream returns  ♫
♫  The mountains and rivers are bright and beautiful,
holding hands, together we return  ♫
♫  In this life, my heart returns untainted of dust and ash  ♫
At Chen Shoujie's mansion, only a piece of fabric from Jinxiu Workshop was found.
As to which year's pattern specifically, I need to confirm it.
Not your concern? Very good.
Jing Lin.
Yes, Great Chief!
I'll take this madwoman and incarcerate her in the eighteenth-level prison of the Imperial Guards.
Who said to bring her back to the Imperial Guards?
Take Yun Que back to Shen Mansion for care.
Miss Yun Que, please.
Miss, a maid from Shen Mansion seeks an audience.
Xiaohe?
Madam, please hurry back to the mansion to see.
As soon as the Great Chief left this morning, Yun Que changed her attitude.
If you don't intervene, things will be out of control.
You, move this porcelain vase over there.
Wipe the lantern in front.
Madam, look at her.
She's been troubling the entire mansion for quite some time.
She can even mistake the Great Chief.
The Great Chief took pity on her and kindly took her in.
But look at her, she really considers herself the lady of the mansion.
Better yet to complement the Great Chief's mansion.
You should go out and look around more.
So when you go out to make cushions, you'll have an idea.
Has the grass in the backyard been cleared?
Have you wiped the bookshelf, which was assigned by the Great Chief?
Hurry up and go.
I ordered them to arrange the front hall. Is it not considered formal business then?
Miss Yun Que, how can you say that?
That's too harsh.
You instruct the servants to do things. Naturally, they should be done well.
However, we take the silver from Shen Mansion and work for the Great Chief.
Firstly, for the matters entrusted by the Great Chief, we must arrange them first.
Am I right?
Let's talk about the arrangements tomorrow.
Butler Shen, sort out the account books of the mansion and bring them to me.
- I'll have a look.
- Sorry, Miss.
Only the lady of the mansion can check the account books of the Shen Mansion.
Madam, good morning!
Butler Shen, why do you…?
Madam, I forgot to greet you this morning.
I was wrong. Please punish me, Madam.
Punish you?
According to the rules of the Shen Mansion, servants of the mansion
must pay respects to Madam morning and evening.
Female family members must offer salutations and serve tea to Madam.
Since my first day entering the mansion, I've kept it firmly in mind.
The Shen Mansion does not keep those who lack manners.
Today, I was rude.
Madam, even if you cast me out,
it would be completely justified.
All right, that's enough.
Isn't it just that you want me to offer a respectful cup of tea to Madam Shen?
I'll offer it then.
Madam, please drink your tea.
Madam, now that you've had your tea
and almost all formalities have been established,
let's discuss what is reasonable.
It was the Great Chief who put me in charge of household affairs.
I naturally have to do my utmost.
Could it be that you want to go against the Great Chief's wishes?
Miss Yun Que, you just mentioned you wanted to see the account books. Right?
Right.
Since you want to see them, why not also take charge of the next season's accounts?
Well… Madam.
are you saying to entrust all accounts to my management?
I was not very adept at this.
If you are willing to share the concerns, nothing could be better.
- Madam.
- Butler Shen,
please bring over the account books and hand them to Miss Yun Que.
I have official duties these days.
All matters, big and small, in the inner courtyard, are to be decided by Miss Yun Que.
Miss Yun Que, thank you for your hard work.
Madam, please think it over.
He was momentarily dazzled.
He must have been bewitched by that outsider vixen.
Using trickery and deception,
she sweet-talked him into bringing her home.
Rest assured, in his heart, the first wife is only you.
Furthermore, all of us are on your side.
Butler Shen, it truly has nothing to do with Yun Que.
Madam, please don't treat me as a fool.
Had it not been for being angered by that vixen,
why would you need to move back to your parents' home to live?
Who said I'm moving back to my parents' home?
I have many investigations to attend to these days.
I'm afraid I will be at the Ministry of Justice until quite late.
So I will not be returning home for now.
Don't worry about me, I'm leaving.
What should we do now?
Speak up if you have something to say.
Great Chief, during the days you weren't at the mansion,
Miss Yun Que changed the porcelain plates and the embroidered cloth and so on.
Uncle Zhong argues with her every day.
Today, he even gave me an outright order.
If I don't bring you and Madam Shen back,
I'm not allowed to return to the mansion.
Since when did Butler Zhong...
get along so well with Sixth Miss Yan?
Great Chief, could you please give me a clear indication?
At first, I thought you were fond of Miss Yun Que.
But ever since you brought her back to the mansion, you have never returned.
So who should I support?
It seems your duties are quite leisurely.
You have even started to worry about my household affairs.
I'm at fault.
Get up.
How are the security arrangements for the coming days?
Great Chief, all has been arranged.
The security of the Lintai Secretariat is now completely taken over by our Imperial Guards.
The original guards have been transferred to assist the inspectors at the Hongwen School.
- Jiang Langxing is over there.
- That's just perfect.
Let us finish quickly and head home.
Jiang Langxing.
Candidates shall not talk to each other.
Marshal Xu asked us to pass a message to you; listen carefully.
The latest instructions from above stress the utmost importance.
This recruitment exam must be guarded rigorously so that not even a fly can get out.
Not even a single page can be brought in, do you understand?
You-You spoke too fast. I didn't hear it clearly.
Chuichui, could you speak a bit slower?
Didn't Marshal Xu instruct us to take a closer look
to see if there are any oversights in security?
We need to take a closer look?
Why not follow me inside to check the several doors?
We've also set up checkpoints in the inner courtyard.
Chuichui,
why don't you two go in first?
I'll wait here for my fifth brother until he comes.
Oh right! Your fifth brother also passed the preliminary exam.
- All right. I'm going inside then.
- Go on.
Jiang the Stickler, hurry up!
Being the matchmaker is not an easy job.
Excuse me. Could you help me find someone?
Pan Chi.
The person you're looking for is indeed on the final examination list.
But up till now, he has not yet registered for the exam.
Pan, have you really given up?
Who said I have given up?
Pan, it's really you! You've come to take the exam.
That day, after I sobered up from the drink, I thought about what you said to me.
It's rare for the Hongwen School to recruit everyone.
With all the talent I possess,
I must amaze those decrepit old masters.
Let them see what a peerless good article is.
Congratulations! I wish you success in one fell swoop.
To be listed on the honor roll.
Since you are also called Pan Chi,
sharing the name with the top detective among the people, you must be equally excellent.
Today, you look even more radiant.
Of course. I just spruced up casually.
Sure to be handsome and dashing. Unparalleled in Xiang'an.
Jokes aside. Your complexion doesn't look too good.
Have you been drinking again these past few days?
These few days, I've been busy investigating cases and reading case files.
But I'm completely clueless.
The case you mentioned
wouldn't be that one, would it? The case of the fluttering moth.
- You know it?
- Of course, I know.
The whole town knows it. It's told in an almost mystical way.
But in my opinion, you shouldn't just look at the files.
You need to ask around more.
I've asked the people around.
One of the parties is dead. Another is insane.
So what?
In our line of work, we fear not the corpse.
On the dead body, there could be many good things.
Besides, what the madman says isn't necessarily all nonsense.
This penmanship is the writing from before my father got injured.
When Sir Shen was young, his brush strokes were sharp like swords, vigorous and grand.
Later on, his strokes became reserved, smooth, and round.
I have practiced for a long time
to make the handwriting exactly alike.
Indeed, it is forged.
If it really was a fabrication done by Academician Yan who understands my father's calligraphy,
he would certainly not use the wrong brush strokes.
The forger is someone else.
Pan, thank you.
After your reminder, it seems I've thought of another method.
Me?
I didn't remind you.
Wife, you've made it difficult for me to find you.
You're not at the Ministry of Justice discussing matters.
Why have you come here to chat?
Great Chief, I came here on official business.
You take good care of your Imperial Guards and attend to your duties.
What I do and where I go every day, it's not your place to interfere.
Affairs at the Ministry of Justice are beyond my control.
But what if it's a matter concerning you?
The backyard is a mess.
As Madam Shen, you should go back and take charge.
Return to the mansion.
Do you delude yourself into being on an equal footing with Madam Shen
and share a husband with her?
Let me tell you! As long as I live, you can't join the Shen family.
This is not up to you.
I'll say it once more. Hand me the account books.
Great Chief. Madam.
My Lord, you've brought back Madam Shen.
The old saying goes well.
A couple quarrels at the head of the bed but makes up at the end of it.
Only then can they grow old together.
Butler Shen, I'm a bit hungry.
Could you go check out today's dishes in the kitchen?
All right, I'll go right away.
Miss Yun Que, don't argue with the old housekeeper.
You don't need to worry.
From the first day of my marriage,
I had an agreement with the Great Chief to divorce in the future.
The account books will be under your management sooner or later.
Divorce?
Such a good man as the Great Chief, yet you don't cherish him.
The Great Chief is a person of remarkable appearance. Graceful as a fine jade tree.
Anyone who fails to see that is truly blind.
Such a fine young lady.
What a pity her eyes don't work well.
What are you laughing at?
Could it be that you find the Great Chief very ugly?
No, no, no!
Miss Yun Que, you can be careless with food, but you mustn't speak recklessly.
I think we have nothing more to do here.
It's best to leave quickly.
Don't drag me!
Then you go on your own.
Come back to the mansion and stay.
After all, we…
I understand.
I am not the one in your heart.
If outsiders were to find out, it would only lead to more gossip.
Once the case is concluded, I will come back.
I won't cause you any trouble.
The Grand Empress Dowager has drawn today's final exam question.
We have been ordered to open it.
The question is: Appreciating the clear sky after the geese return,
and observing the grand view of Xiang'an
There are no restrictions on literary forms.
Poetry and essays are especially good.
Take him away.
Your Majesty, we've reviewed the papers for three days
and have decided on the final recruitment list for Hongwen School.
Please review it, Your Majesty.
The examination papers have been arranged according to their scored ranking.
The first one on top is the essay by Cheng Bojian, the top scorer this time.
Pan Chi is the last one?
Yes.
Wan'er, you read out this last one's to me.
Tall pines planted at the mountain's foot.
Short saplings grow at the peak.
With the saplings' diameter just an inch, they overshadow the hundred-foot pine branches.
I feel that the literary grace of this last one is also remarkable.
Pan Chi did not lose in literary grace.
But it is somewhat off-topic.
I don't quite understand these things.
Wan'er, interpret them for me.
This candidate uses the towering pine trees at the foot of Yangui Mountain
to symbolize the talented scholars from humble backgrounds
and uses the low-lying saplings on the mountaintop to symbolize the offspring of noble families.
Because their position at birth is already high,
the inch-wide saplings can overshadow the hundred-foot pines.
I think the scenery at Yangui Mountain...
is exquisitely depicted.
Continue reading.
Laughing heartily under the open sky.
Striding high across the divine land.
Though the noble prize themselves, I regard them as mere dust.
Though the lowly demean themselves, who says they aren't important?
Flapping my gown, I gaze at the mountains.
Washing my feet in the long river.
I not only want to take the exam
but also tear off your repulsive masks.
I see your mind is not on the chessboard at all.
Are you trying to ask me?
It's clearly seen
the selection at the Hongwen School involves unsavory practices.
Why was the original list still approved?
Indeed, I wanted to ask.
But I have figured it out just now.
Although Pan Chi is a brilliant writer,
his personality is too impulsive.
So he's not suitable for officialdom from the start.
This examination was just a trial.
The selection of talented scholars has been riddled with longstanding malpractices.
Many officials at court are involved in it.
It's already as solid as a rock. It's a stalemate on the board.
Even if I want to make a move in this chess game,
I have to wait for the right opportunity to make the move.
"Flapping my gown, I gaze at the mountains.
Washing my feet in the long river."
This piece of writing is grand and powerful.
Using scenery to satirize the present.
Implying that some use the pretext of not sticking to social hierarchy and fair selection
to actually oppress the humble and solidify the power of the nobility.
- It's so exhilarating.
- All right.
You've been praising this good friend of yours for quite a while.
Well, he really did write it very well.
Pan is not just sharing the same name as the top detective among the people.
He's very likely to be the detective himself.
Very likely.
Clerk Yan.
Marshal Xu asked me to tell you that you wanted him to help investigate
into Chen Shoujie's background and there are leads now.
Chen Shoujie indeed participated in the investigation of the Chen Huo'e case
and even got promoted because of it.
However, not long after his promotion, he went mad.
It turns out that before Madam Chen died, he had already gone mad.
The Huo'e case must be connected to him.
It's something we haven't discovered.
No, I have to make another trip to the Chen Mansion.
Shen Du.
Are you all right?
Be careful!
The style of the hidden weapon is different from that day,
but the moves it executed are remarkably similar.
You're injured!
It's nothing. Just a minor injury.
How come you're here alone?
I came to look for someone but didn't find them.
How can you be all right with all this blood loss?
Are you concerned about me?
I'm not concerned about you.
You got injured while saving me.
I should take responsibility for you.
This old man really is muddled.
The shop was clearly closed up properly.
Yet he insisted I go and check if anything was stolen.
You want to run?
I advise you not to make another mistake on top of another.
I'm a female official from the Ministry of Justice.
If you confess voluntarily, the crime of theft could be punished lightly.
But if you injure me, that would be a serious crime.
Nosy woman, go die!
Help!
It's you.
Who's there?
Wait a moment.
Just now, the patrolling ones were inspectors.
Why do we have to hide?
I don't want to deal with the officialdom.
You are averse to dealing with the officialdom
and skilled in martial arts.
I know your identity now.
You are...
a chivalrous hero who stands up for justice. Right?
Donning a mask at night. Becoming a righteous enforcer.
Acting valiantly and doing good deeds without leaving a name.
Sort of.
Wait a minute. You can't go. You killed someone.
Well? You want to arrest me and report to the authorities?
But I killed the person who tried to kill you.
Is this how you treat your lifesaver?
Regarding Great Cang's laws, if someone tries to kill people for no reason at night
and the victim resists the assailant and kills him,
he can thus be exempt from criminal responsibility.
But you can't just leave like this.
What are you doing?
I'm releasing water lanterns for you.
When I was a child, my mother
often brought me to release water lanterns.
My mother said water lanterns can drift along with the waves.
They can ward off disasters and sickness
and can also cleanse us of any ill fortunes from our being.
Although you did it to save me,
I will release a water lantern for you
to dispel some of the karma of killing.
No need. I don't believe in these things.
Belief makes it real, belief makes it work.
I didn't believe it as a child either.
So I did it very perfunctorily.
Later on, my mother's illness got worse and worse
and she left me.
I often think if at that time
I had taken it seriously to release each and every water lantern,
whether Heaven would then fulfill my wish
to let my mother always be with me.
Even if a thousand or ten thousand water lanterns were released,
those who are meant to go will still go.
In this life, this world, they had already made up their minds
to only accompany us for this part of our journey.
It can't be changed.
Nothing can be changed.
Ghost Mask…
Great Chief, the bandit hanged himself in the deep alley.
We're unable to identify him.
Hanged himself?
Since there's a need to silence someone, they wouldn't want us to find out their identity.
Go ahead.
Yes.
Great Chief, do we really not need to call a doctor to take a look?
-  No need for medicine?
- Talkative!
No need.
Who says there's no need?
Apply the medicine.
Is there something else later?
You seem to be in a hurry.
Surely you're not rushing to rest?
Of course not.
I was thinking,
if I finish applying the medicine for you and it's not too late,
I can go to the Ministry of Justice to sort out the case details.
The case is so pressing that there's no rest even at midnight?
Wasn't I just thinking about solving the case sooner?
Staying up all night is not a big deal.
But I am injured.
Can't you stay tonight to take care of me?
I…
Forget it.
I don't need your care.
Go ahead with your business.
I'll do it.
Who says I am leaving?
You got hurt because you saved me.
If I leave now, even the heavens would think I'm heartless.
What if a bolt of lightning strikes suddenly?
Wouldn't I be wronged?
♫  The night is still long and the moonlight shines in the west window  ♫
♫  Starlight is hidden in your eyes  ♫
♫  With one touch, my heart flutters like the shadow of a candle, swaying and trembling  ♫
♫  The more one cares, the deeper it's concealed  ♫
♫  Leaves fall and turn yellow, with a thousand lines of yearning  ♫
♫  Years pass like stanzas of poetry, romantic yet sad  ♫
♫  Two hearts collide between dawn and dusk  ♫
♫  Embraces come unexpectedly  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to hold you, staying by my side  ♫
♫  Passing through the obstruction of a storm  ♫
♫  I want to be your moonlight  ♫
I must have aggravated the wound.
♫  How I wish I could just forget the length of time  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, never forgetting each other  ♫
Don't get distracted.
Help me dress it properly.
All right.
♫  I want to hold you, staying by my side  ♫
Maybe I didn't bandage it well enough before.
It's fine now.
It's getting late. You should rest early.
♫  How I wish I could just forget the length of time  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, shadows become a pair  ♫
♫  I want to be with you, never forgetting each other  ♫
♫  There is always a place where the clouds and the sea meet  ♫
♫  I want to accompany you forever  ♫
♫  I will wait until my black hair turns grey  ♫
♫  In this life, I will only keep you in my heart  ♫
My Lord!
My Lord, spare my life. I have inquired about the matter regarding the inspectors.
It has been dealt with as a typical case of thieves fighting each other.
It has not been reported to the Ministry of Justice yet.
Trash, send someone more efficient to handle it.
If there's another mistake, you will be the next one to die.
I know my mistake. Thank you for not taking my life.
That Lu Chuichui from the Ministry of Justice,
no one is allowed to touch her.
Yes.
You may leave.
These ignorant fools,
a mere fire moth trick can turn heaven and earth upside down.
It won't take long before Great Cang…
Get up.
Go to the front hall and have something to eat.
When one is injured, they must eat more.
You've seen it.
I am currently seriously injured.
It's inconvenient for me to move.
Going to the front hall is too troublesome.
I just want to lie down.
All right. Then you should rest well.
I'll bring you breakfast in a bit.
Well.
- Where is my wife?
- Someone from the Yan Mansion came.
They have invited Madam Shen to a banquet.
She instructed that you are severely injured.
- There's no need for you to accompany her to the banquet.
- I…
We should serve you well during your meal.
You may leave.
Yes.
Great Chief, I…
What's the matter?
I have found out that Han Shiyuan is no simple character.
Sixth Miss, Young Master Han and I are set to get married next month.
I use tea in place of wine.
I toast to you and Young Master Han.
I wish you both a harmonious union for a hundred years.
I was hasty before and lacked proper courtesy.
Please forgive me for that.
You're too kind!
All right. Sit down and talk.
This year in our Yan Mansion, it's really one joyous occasion after another.
Mojie has been admitted to the Hongwen School.
Sixth Miss and Caiwei both have married decent men.
My sixth daughter, why have you been frequently coming back recently?
Is it because you're not on good terms with the Great Chief?
No, I'm quite well at the Shen Mansion.
A few days ago, that cook took a few days off to go home.
The food wasn't quite to my taste.
So I came back home to eat.
That's good then, as long as there's nothing wrong.
The rumors outside say that as soon as you return to your parental home,
the Great Chief would come to fetch you.
This situation is a bit frightening.
But the last time you came back, he did not come to fetch you.
I actually felt uneasy.
My Lord, Madam, the Great Chief has arrived.
Great Chief.
Great Chief, please take a seat.
Aren't you inconvenienced by mobility?
My father-in-law's banquet cannot be missed.
Yes, Great Chief.
Please come inside.
Subtitles and Timing provided to you by
🎶 The Copper Sparrow 🪶Team @viki.com
"Only Want You" - Ding Yuxi, Deng Enxi
♫  One look confirmed our fate  ♫
♫  Upon meeting again, I know you're the one for me  ♫
♫  Gaze at the stars, dreaming about old times  ♫
♫  A pair of people have already taken root  ♫
♫  Lovers before the candlelight, do not ask their thoughts  ♫
♫  Affection is bound, lasting forever  ♫
♫  Using the evening breeze to express deep love  ♫
♫  I have someone I long for in this life  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  You are the only one for me  ♫
♫  Embracing each other, how serious we are about our love  ♫
♫  Every moment is treasured  ♫
♫  From dawn to dusk  ♫
♫  You and I, forever inseparable  ♫
♫  Without noticing, you broke into my heart  ♫
♫  Slowly immersing myself, I become undaunted by perils for love  ♫
♫  I charge into battle with unmatched resilience  ♫
♫  Because you are my responsibility  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  Deeply in love, you are the one I have chosen  ♫
♫  Autumn moon and spring breeze, I only want you for my whole life  ♫
♫  The trace of your palm  ♫
​♫  Your gaze  ♫
♫  Our love is heating up  ♫
♫  You are the only one for me  ♫