[Episode 28]
[27 GUN 5233]
Yoon Huijae.
Mother.
Hyeonmu.
Here we are. Quickly.
There we go. Take it.
Wow, you got so many today.
Today's work paid off.
Hey, Unforgettable.
Today's your second day working here. It's admirable how diligent you are.
Excuse me?
"Unforgettable"? What do you mean?
It's the name of a new pork soup restaurant.
Isn't your mom the owner?
Yes.
Stop it, you lowlife.
Don't call him "Unforgettable."
Why not? Don't you like the nickname?
When you meet people, they should remain in your heart.
Beyond the vast ocean,
many relationships simply dissipate.
- What are you doing? Hurry.
- All right, wait.
Nakwon.
Namu!
Dojin!
Mom.
Dojin.
Mother.
I had a great dream.
What's the matter?
My son.
Mother.
What's going on?
Is something wrong?
Dojin.
Hyeonmu.
Did he come by?
[Intensive Care Unit]
Hyeonmu will be fine.
Mom.
You should go back in.
Hyeonmu.
Namu.
- Did you go to your shoot?
- Yes.
I returned just now.
Is your mom okay?
Yes. She is able to walk now.
She even has an appetite.
Glad to hear that.
And your brother?
Did he wake up?
No need to be concerned about him either.
It's you I'm concerned about.
He'll be okay.
Don't worry too much, okay?
Nakwon.
Whenever you're faced with something difficult,
don't keep it to yourself, and immediately let me know.
Okay?
You told me once.
You said to let you know if I'm hurting.
You told me not to suffer alone.
If you keep it in because of me,
then I have no reason...
to be with you.
I said that, right?
I asked you to use me.
Okay?
I'll do that...
after all this is settled.
I'll tell you everything.
[Deposition]
That scoundrel.
He's finally acting like a big brother.
Don't you dare...
mention my son with that filthy mouth.
If you had told on me instead of fleeing,
three lives would have been spared.
Including the parents of Gil Nakwon,
the girl Namu likes.
Lately, I visit a nun.
Sin, forgiveness, and salvation...
were not unreachable.
You should see me more frequently.
Our princess, you,
and Namu...
I also miss him a lot.
[Deposition]
[Personal Information]
So those he met face-to-face...
are Jeon Yoora, Baek Hyangran, Wi Deukkyu,
and yourself, Park Taeyoung.
Yes.
Jeon Yoora was so awesome.
She wrote to him frequently
and came to see him, too.
Someone has been assisting him.
He knew which way to go
and is moving as quickly as possible.
Get the list of hospital staff who worked that evening.
Focus on the employees who had direct contact with him.
Doctors, nurses, assistants, servers,
and everyone else involved.
- Yes, sir.
Also,
bring this individual in to be interrogated right away.
Will do.
[Jeon Yoora]
He was being moved from Euigang Prison to Prosecution.
When the accident occurred, this hospital...
was the only one that could provide immediate hospitalization.
Yeom Jihong probably planned the car accident,
while Jeon Yoora managed to find employment there a couple of months ago...
to assist Yoon Huijae.
Hyeonmu, are you all right?
Are you able to hear me?
It would be impossible not to when you're so loud, right?
Hyeonmu,
you aren't good at fighting.
Why do you always pretend to be strong?
Because my dad...
said I should.
How can you still refer to him as your dad?
Why do you call me your brother, then?
I was always mean to you.
Tell the old lady...
not to stay up.
I'll live alone.
Stop pretending to be strong.
I'm sure you'll come running to us again...
if you think something will occur.
Leave now. You're too noisy.
Hyeonmu,
I'm eternally grateful...
to you for saving Mother and me.
Sohjin,
fetch some water for Hyeonmu.
Okay.
Good job.
You were badly hurt.
I'm so glad you're up now.
You...
made it, too.
Why did you do that?
Why did you shield me? I didn't tell you to do that.
What about you?
Namu and I...
have no blood ties with you.
Why did you do that for us?
I can't understand it.
My true father was trying to murder me,
while a stranger was weeping for me.
She even shielded me to save me.
Why are you so nosy?
It's pathetic, isn't it?
Do you feel sorry...
for Namu and me?
I'm also human.
It's not like I'm a deity.
I couldn't have done that...
just because I felt sorry.
I could only come this far because of what I learned...
and saw in you guys.
I know you were aiming to get my attention.
You were grumbling...
to show that you were having difficulty. I realize that.
Liar.
You only cared for Namu.
Hyeonmu, I'm sorry.
If I've made you angry,
please forgive me.
Your mom will wait for you.
After your sentence is over.
You, Sohjin, Namu,
and I...
can share a home. How does that sound?
Don't go into hiding again.
Why?
Are you going to wait for me...
at the restaurant until the sun rises again?
Why not?
I can wait for my son.
If I come...
visit you this time,
don't send me away.
Understand?
As recent events catch the public's eye...
to the tragedy which occurred a dozen years ago,
people have started to do online searches on Ji Hyewon...
and are leaving commemorative comments and stories on online message boards.
With her birthday soon approaching,
it's anticipated that fans will
visit the charnel house where her remains are stored.
- Yoon Huijae's escape...
- Her birthday...
- is approaching.
- ...It's quite a popular topic.
- A lovely actress...
- Yes.
Will many fans visit again this year?
- She shouldn't be gossip fodder.
- That darn Yoon Huijae.
- The late Ji...
- Jaeyee.
...died at the hands of...
It's been some time. How are you?
Aren't you...
Yes. What do you want?
You met Kim Jiyeong's sister, didn't you?
I did a story on her.
I know. I read it.
I'd like to write about you and Chae Dojin.
Can you do an interview?
What, an interview? We don't do those.
I'd like to know more about your relationship and...
much more seems to lie under the surface.
I'm also curious about...
what truly occurred that evening.
If you write about us,
it could harm you.
What?
You know.
Park Heeyoung's murder.
Yoon Huijae's free, too.
Oh, but that's...
He's much more dangerous than you think.
You really could get badly injured.
Yoon Huijae brainwashed me.
I can't recall the exact details.
Park Heeyoung's hidden camera caught it all.
You were completely conscious and sane.
The judge won't accept that you were insane.
We'll have to wait and see.
There are some very competent attorneys.
What you subjected me to in the holding cell.
I'll sue you for that.
Yoon Huijae's hideout that you prepared for him.
Jeon Yoora.
Is she there, too?
[Yoon Huijae's Accomplice Arrested]
[Arrested Outside Han Jaeyee's House by Chae Dojin]
Huijae,
let's get a move on.
The worst is on the horizon.
Not at all. Every day is like a dream.
Jihong couldn't restrain himself and went too far.
You have me.
I will never...
cause you to be in trouble.
Let's go.
The source of the money you spent to help Yoon Huijae.
We're tracking it all.
A prison cell without him...
won't be interesting.
I should have offed Gil Nakwon at least.
What?
My dad stopped me.
I wonder why.
Yoon Huijae's plans.
Tell me everything.
He's like this...
because you go overboard whenever someone brings up Gil Nakwon.
He wants to end it himself.
To complete his autobiography on his own.
When did I start to go down the wrong path?
I always wondered.
As a result,
I remembered something that happened that I couldn't forget for 12 years.
[And Life Continues]
We're still...
right here.
So now,
I think it's time to finally have closure.
She will die because of you,
Yoon Namu.
Shut it.
I understand why Father is so...
infatuated with you.
You and him...
are crazy in similar ways.
But Gil Nakwon put an end to yours.
He was enraged
because he couldn't train you.
Hiding away or suppressing craziness...
doesn't cause it to vanish.
Yes.
I'm Yoon Huijae's son.
A psychopath's son whom he left his bloody hammer to.
If you want this position,
take it now.
It's yours.
You don't know what a great thing you have.
That craziness. That hammer.
You want that to become strong?
Do you actually believe that will give you strength?
You're wrong.
You're so weak and useless that...
Yoon Huijae clung onto you.
The strength that you envy?
Yoon Huijae was never strong from the very beginning.
What?
I crushed him already a dozen years ago.
A 16-year-old boy...
beat him.
As a result,
I remembered something I couldn't forget for a dozen years.
In the end,
you too...
were deceived by him.
[I Am Not Unlike You]
They already escaped.
"To my beloved son.
The stories we could not share, we shall keep in our hearts."
- Sleep well, Jaeyee.
- Goodbye.
Namu.
Nakwon.
What's the matter? Did something...
Namu.
Did you have a nightmare?
No.
I didn't.
Namu,
are you really all right?
Stay next to me.
Don't leave me.
If you vanish,
I'll be petrified.
I'm not going anywhere.
Do you still feel ill at ease?
How about now?
Sleep peacefully now.
Okay?
What if...
we hadn't been born to a monster?
Could we have lived...
a normal life?
This is Jeon Yoora.
I'd like to surrender myself.
[Ji Hyewon]
A long time ago,
I became another monster.
This is the moment...
when I must do battle with the monster that created me.
This is...
for my beloved Nakwon.