[Episode 22]
Senior Inspector Ko.
Dojin.
What are you doing here?
- I told you to take a break.
- It's about that report.
Did you get rid of it because of me?
I altered an official document.
I know I don't deserve to be a police officer.
I still don't regret it.
I didn't lie about any criminal records.
Because you were a psychopath's son, people blamed you.
I don't want to hear any of that.
But everything was exposed because of Park Heeyeong.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You know what?
If I never met you and your mother back then,
I would've probably quit this job a while ago.
Sir,
take me to the detention center.
No, Namu.
Don't leave.
During my police career,
I was let down by people.
Until I met you.
So don't say sorry.
Namu.
Come on, I've lived for long enough.
You're a monster.
Why are you my father?
Why?
Sit down, Yoon Huijae.
Sit down now.
[Emergency Transportation]
Hello, Jonghyeon.
Reporter Park Heeyeong was killed.
It was at her home last night.
What?
Come, I'll send you the address.
Come before the reporters arrive.
There are two sets of footprints.
They were merciless.
It's most likely it was due to a grudge.
I found a weapon.
If you can't bring yourself to do it,
I'll do it for you.
I'll make sure to clear everything useless...
that is a danger to my son.
A hammer?
Were they trying to start a fire? Why was this burned?
They did it on purpose...
to show me.
The police reported that the criminal started a fire.
The method of murder was inhuman,
while nothing valuable was taken...
Are you okay?
Dojin.
It's a copycat crime.
- What?
- It's a copycat of Yoon Huijae.
[Yoon Huijae, arrested in 2006]
[I Am Not Unlike You]
One of them went in with her, while the other followed right after.
What is this?
They covered their faces, so it's difficult to identify.
Is it them?
They have a similar build as Lee Seungwoo and Yoon Hyeonmu.
It looks like the two of them...
are working together.
What?
You don't fear anything, huh?
How could you trust me and open up to me?
I already know about you...
from your father.
What did...
my father tell you?
Let's sit down...
and talk.
I need something in exchange, don't you agree?
I asked a question, what did he say?
He called you a nuisance.
He said that you and your brother are completely different.
Yoon Namu...
What did he say to Namu?
What went on between them...
that night?
I should be asking you that question.
What's with Namu?
- What?
- People say psychopaths...
have an obsession with their own families.
You're basically a forgotten child.
Your father only has an obsession with your brother.
That's because he sees something in Namu. I'm right, huh?
What kind of person do you think Namu is?
Is his gentle face only a mask?
Could he possibly be even worse than Yoon Huijae?
So?
What?
I don't think they forced the door open.
They're either working together...
or possibly knew the password.
What is this? Did you call the police? Do you want to die?
No, of course not.
Why would I ruin such an exclusive?
Go inside for a second. It's probably the runner.
How can I trust you?
If it's really the police, they'll catch you for sure.
So stop being scared, and just go back inside...
so I can quickly finish the interview.
If you're up to something, I'll kill you.
Based on the footprints,
one was in the living room, but then went inside to hide.
In front of the door, the footprints are more concentrated,
and no signs of rummaging the room can be found.
Who is it?
Hello.
The other...
attacked the victim right in front of the door.
Then,
he dragged her...
up to the timeline.
I'm here to kill you.
What?
My father told me to.
He said that you were done with your work...
and that you even did what you shouldn't have done.
You must be the offender behind the community attacks.
Hyeonmu assaulted a woman, then ran away scared.
Then...
were you also responsible for the Han Jaeyee case?
It was you? Did Yoon Huijae put you up to this?
You're just like my father said, full of questions.
You're calling him your father?
Do you want to be exactly like him?
Then I can make it happen...
just like how I helped him.
I don't care about that.
I'm not interested in killing others with words.
It was like he was punishing the victim.
He batted her to death.
Why are you showing up now?
Did you want to hear what we were talking about?
You jerk.
If he beat her that much,
he must have gotten a lot of the suspect's blood on him.
He probably changed clothes here.
I'm sure he changed his shoes, too.
The blood markings are different.
They look like drops of blood that dripped off.
For blood to drip like this,
the clothing must not have absorbed any of the blood.
A raincoat.
Lee Seungwoo.
It's him.
He's Yoon Huijae's copycat.
[Yoon Huijae, arrested in 2006]
[Han Jaeyee, Gil Nakwon]
Park Heeyeong was killed?
I wouldn't be surprised if she was killed by someone she upset.
How many suspects do you have?
Is Yoon Hyeonmu on the list?
I can't tell you that.
This will just make us reporters throw around guesses.
Give me a hint. I hate people who say things like that.
You ask for too much.
It must feel strange.
Park Heeyeong made it really hard for you.
You, Jaeyee, and your family too, right?
Isn't this case linked to Yoon Huijae, too?
It happened after the show about you and your father aired.
I think it says a lot.
Park Heeyeong was too much, wasn't she?
- Do you think she had it coming?
- So what?
You're saying she deserved to die?
Aren't you...
a reporter?
I told you that...
everything that makes you...
weak and pathetic...
will be terminated by me.
The host of Investigation "Why,"
investigative reporter Park Heeyeong,
was found dead in her apartment this afternoon.
- Three years ago...
- Yes, Sir.
- She investigated...
- Right now I'm watching the news.
It's true...
that she bothered you and your brother a lot,
but I'm both scared and sorry hearing what happened to her.
- Recently, she revealed a secret...
- I know.
- about Yoon Huijae and his son.
- You're right.
See you tomorrow. You had a long day. Get some rest.
Hello, Sir.
It's been some time. You must be tired.
Investigations revealed she was struck with a blunt object...
[Namu]
Police collected her belongings...
and are investigating what happened.
A forensic team is collecting evidence at the scene.
Welcome.
Investigations revealed she was hit by a blunt instrument.
The violence of the attack despite the fact that nothing was stolen...
has led police to conclude that the motive was resentment,
and that is the direction they will follow.
People who knew Park will be gathered to give statements...
and security and dashboard camera footage from the area will be checked.
Namu.
I came out when you said you'd come.
Are you all right?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Did you miss me?
Doesn't my presence tend to heal people?
Yes.
If you...
just admit what happened right away then I...
Nothing bad happened.
Don't worry, okay?
Just a second. Sorry.
Wait.
Yeonji.
Dojin, we found him right away.
Yeom Jihong, age 26.
Arrested for fraud and embezzlement via stock price manipulation.
In April 2015, he was imprisoned in Euigang Prison
and was released in April of 2018.
That's only a month apart from Yoon Hyeonmu's release.
I called the prison to check.
For three years, he participated in the same religious activity as Yoon Huijae.
His father is pretty famous.
His father, Yeom Gijoon, is a famous modern artist.
Yeom Jihong studied business at a famous American university.
His older brother lives in Gangnam.
I'll message you his address.
Go there. We'll meet you there.
Okay. I'll go right now.
Don't wait outside anymore.
If something happens, call me.
Don't wander around by yourself.
Don't meet strangers by yourself either.
At least for now.
Sorry. I'm a bit too...
No.
You have to go now, don't you?
Later on...
tell me everything.
All of the things you just told me...
are things that I've wanted to say to you.
So...
let's both be careful, okay?
Go inside.
Don't you love your sister?
Why did you let her near my son?
Does Namu hate me?
Definitely not.
It's Namu. We're the most alike.
I guess you don't care.
What my son will...
do to your sister?
Mom.
Dad.
Who will the third person be?
Will the third person be your pretty sister?
Gil Nakwon.
Gil Moowon.
I also don't think you should stay close to your sister.
Stand up!
Sir.
If you touch my sister, I'll kill you. Understand?
Sir, please let him go.
Nakwon.
What should I get rid of first,
my son?
Out of all the things that make you weak and pathetic...
[I Am Not Unlike You]
What will it be?
What should I wipe out first?
Namu.
That hammer.
Are you trying to copy Yoon Huijae?
It's like kid's play.
- What?
- It isn't intimidating at all.
- It's cheesy.
- You punk.
It's you, right?
Please wait a little bit, Father.
You and I will meet soon.
It's nice to meet you,
Yeom Jihong.
[We thank Kim Seohyeong for her special appearance]
[Come and Hug Me]
What did you talk about with Father?
Guess who Father ordered me to get rid of first when I get released?
- Gil Nakwon.
- This is great.
All the things we couldn't do because we were sorry and grateful.
From now on, let's do all of them.
How much more of this can I do?
When or how they may be harmed remains unknown.
People think that they won't be hurt.
Who are you?
I told you that I would complete his autobiography.
Without Yoon Huijae, what are you?
Give the present when you meet.
Say, "What you've wished for over the past three years...
will come true soon."