12 years had passed.
[Year 2007]
Namu.
[Year 2015]
[I Am Not Unlike You]
[Yoon Huijae's son attacked by the victims' families]
[Year 2018]
[Nation's Top Actress Han Jaeyee]
12 years passed by,
An old villain who was locked up in the dark...
Yoon Namu.
Once again,
said he realized something.
Did you read that article?
[Episode 23]
It was about Namu meeting Nakwon at a hospital.
Yes.
Father, may I complete that book? The book.
Go see Jeon Yoora.
And hand her a present for me.
It's already the third spring.
Yet I still haven't heard back from you, Huijae.
Tell her that, "What you wished for over three years...
will soon become a reality."
[Serial Killer Yoon Huijae assaults reporter Park Heeyeong]
You better wake up...
Your time is up.
You're just an old thug who will rot and die in here...
That's it.
Yoon Namu.
Could he be a mutant?
He's your child,
yet he even tried to kill you.
He hates you so much.
Do you think that...
you're protecting your children?
No way.
You broke them apart.
Namu...
is not your child anymore.
He grew up by himself.
So don't be delusional.
Stop trying to deceive yourself...
thinking that you're his father.
Wake the heck up!
Namu.
Chae Dojin.
Yoon Namu.
That hammer.
Are you trying to imitate Yoon Huijae?
Seems like child's play.
- What?
- It's not threatening at all.
It's corny.
You bastard!
It's you, right?
Very nice to meet you,
Yeom Jihong.
Is this the best you can do?
You're not even close to him.
Father...
What's going on? It's too loud.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Evil...
does not wait to be proven.
will prove itself.
[GwangSoo Hair Shop]
Shit!
[Boiled pork slices]
I'm very sorry.
She smells like pork.
She smells like disinfectant.
- Why are you doing this?
- Why not?
Because I really like you.
Let's go on just one date.
I already told you, no.
You must be crazy!
My brother's a police officer.
He could kill you.
Geez.
What a cutie.
My goodness, whoa, whoa. What's your problem?
Why? Are you scared?
If this scares you, why're you doing it to her?
Excuse me?
I said, leave her alone or I'll kill you.
All right, okay.
What a nut job. Maybe I should call Namu.
I told you, he's not home right now.
Yeom Jihong got himself a fake ID.
It's a serious offense.
My son is not like that.
If you keep on bringing this up, we'll go to our attorney.
It doesn't seem like a big deal anyway.
When was the last time...
you saw your son?
What is your son
up to these days?
He's an adult. Should a parent know everything?
Bring an attendance request or a search warrant.
Stop making a hassle in my neighborhood.
His son must have caused a lot of trouble before
for him to be so knowledgeable about the law.
His residence is certain, and since he most likely won't bolt,
our warrant request will be denied.
Going forward, don't wait outside.
And call me if something happens.
[I was a fan of your mom, but you're pathetic]
[Your parents will weep in their graves because of you]
[Don't you feel bad for the victims' families?]
[The Police Will Be Different]
He does live nearby.
He knows where to avoid all the CCTV's.
I know you're anxious, but go home and rest.
Oh, sorry, sorry. I forgot, forgot.
Go get some sleep in the night duty room.
It's okay.
It's nothing.
It's Jaeyee the lovely.
Hello.
Nakwon.
[We are proud of our police]
How did you get here?
I didn't think there would be anyone else...
and you're here.
I came because I just wanted to see you.
- Is everything all right?
- Of course.
Is everything really okay?
I thought you might be sitting here all alone, missing me.
Forget about that 2D print and look at the 3D me.
Namu.
Do you know it's only been one day?
And already half the things we say are...
not, "I miss you,"
nor "Did you eat something?"
But it's "Are you okay?"
You see...
we really are okay so far.
What's the matter?
Are you hurt?
A little bit.
I really don't have to lie down.
Hush. Nope.
Lie down or I'm going to leave.
Lie down.
Did you really go to the hospital?
It's my shoulder, so they said it's okay.
Nothing's broken.
You always seem to hurt yourself.
Namu,
are you investigating Park Heeyeong's murder?
I watched her last broadcast.
How she talked about that night and us.
Perhaps...
it's a copycat...
of Yoon Huijae.
I see.
Nakwon.
I'm okay.
So don't continue to bear it yourself without telling me.
Don't do that.
You have to tell me.
Even the minor details.
Okay?
You tell me everything too, Nakwon.
Tell me if it's too much to bear...
If it becomes too much,
just tell me.
Tell me everything.
Just don't suddenly avoid me.
Okay?
If I thought this would be much to bear...
I wouldn't have started it.
Mom.
Dad.
The third one to go...
might be your pretty little sister.
Gil Nakwon.
Gil Moowon.
I don't think you should stay near your sister, either.
Sir.
Sir!
Touch my sister and I'll kill you. You hear me?
Sir, let him go.
Nakwon.
[Gangnam Police Station]
His mom left after the divorce and he doesn't get along with his dad.
He revealed that during his prison counseling sessions.
He once went abroad to study, he didn't return for a while.
[Criminal Record - Yeom Jihong]
Father.
His dad paid to have the smaller charges dropped
and he only got sentenced for stock price manipulation.
How many victims...
were there?
About 30. And the cruel part is,
most of the victims were his acquaintances
and one even committed suicide.
Hello. You have a visitor.
Is this Violent Crimes, Team 1?
He acquired his fake ID off the internet.
He's not a professional forger.
And he never used it to harm anyone.
He'll give a statement and wait for the sentencing.
What was the fake ID for?
To avoid other's scrutiny. Since I have a record.
My apologies.
Where were you last night?
And a month ago, on the night of Han Jaeyee's incident.
Please don't ask questions which are not pertinent to the fake ID.
You don't have any physical evidence or witnesses.
He does not need to provide an alibi.
I don't remember as far back as a month.
In prison, you attended the same religious meetings as Yoon Huijae?
Yes, I did.
Sister Anes told us a lot of things worth considering.
Such as?
That we should repent,
and receive salvation. Something like that.
So.
Did you receive salvation?
Yes. Most definitely.
You visited Yoon Huijae a few times after your release.
Yes.
He's on death row so I thought he'd be scary,
But he's a nice guy.
Isn't he your father?
I saw a photo of you two on the internet.
He showed a lot of remorse...
and saved his soul.
He's your father. Don't you miss him?
How come you don't see your own father?
You even live together.
Do you think he doesn't have the right to be a father?
Your father is temperamental and weak.
And fears you and cannot control you.
That's why you consider Yoon Huijae as your father.
You follow him unconditionally.
Correct?
You don't need to answer that.
What do you mean by that?
It sounds interesting,
but I don't understand what you mean.
Never mind.
I met someone yesterday and...
it wasn't fun at all.
He was too weak.
He was torturing someone who was half his size.
It was not copying, but only struggling.
It was quite painful to watch.
My question is...
Who are you?
Without Yoon Huijae,
who are you, really?
No need to answer him. Let's go.
Why did you come out so late?
Did you want to hear what she and I were talking about?
What kind of person is Yoon Namu that you've seen?
Is his innocent face merely a mask?
What if he's a devil worse than Yoon Huijae?
That man.
Was it his voice which you heard
that other day?
Yes.
- I'll organize and send you right away.
- Do it after your night duty.
- Who is he?
- What's the matter?
A guy just left. Why was he here?
It's a confidential investigation.
I've seen him before.
Pardon?
He came to your mother's restaurant. I saw him for sure.
Yes, Senior Inspector Ko is here.
What is it, Dojin?
Start closing the restaurant earlier for now.
You must stay with Senior Inspector Ko.
I'll explain why, when I see you.
I'll call Sohjin.
I understand.
Don't worry about me. See you later at home.
Okay.
- Was it Dojin?
- Yes.
I think something's wrong.
I'm sure it's nothing serious. Don't worry too much.
Bro, why did you come out so late?
Did you want to hear what she and I were talking about?
You punk.
Did you come after watching the show about Yoon Namu and Father?
She deserves to die.
Our father is a great man.
You also said that he's a good-for-nothing bastard.
Right?
Punk, who are you?
What did you talk about with Father?
Why?
Does it bother you that I stabbed your brother's pictures?
I told you that I'll complete his autobiography.
What?
Who do you think Father told me to eliminate first when I got released?
[Han Jaeyee]
First is Gil Nakwon.
She's the cause of everything.
She's the first candidate.
Chae Okhee always works late at her restaurant.
Sohjin leaves work last from the hair salon.
What are the crimes?
No one knows when or how they may be harmed.
People think that they won't be harmed.
These two don't have enough fear.
What?
I'll get going first.
You should run away. You won't call the police anyway.
The police announced that...
the culprit seems to be connected to last February's murder.
This will be considered during the investigation.
Those who are concerned,
What are you watching?
During the investigation...
I told you to wash up and eat.
Okay.
The crime will be investigated in detail.
[List of released felons in the last 6 months]
[Name]
[Yeom Jihong]
Sir.
Your requested info on "People Who Love Yoon Huijae".
Thank you.
They're no longer active, so the fan site isn't up, either.
We narrowed down
100 members who were active, and we're investigating them.
Inspector,
can you find out if Yeom Jihong was a member?
If not, anyone who used a fake identity?
Check on all of them.
- Yes, Sir.
- Also,
aside from Yeom Jihong,
see if anyone else had direct contact with Yoon Huijae.
Check the Euigang Prison.
See if anyone sent him something or visited him.
Yes, Prosecutor.
[Nakwon]
Gil Moowon,
I don't think you should stay near your sister, either.