Oh right.
You just rest at the hospital for now.
I'll keep an eye on things at the company.
As for Li Meixing,
though she's trying hard to hide it,
we still found out a few things.
I'll keep all this confidential from Bo Xingzhi.
Once you're back,
we'll fully carry out our plan.
Xinyu,
thank you.
I've reviewed
all the patient's medical records.
This patient's condition
is purely caused by shock.
After a few days of rest at home,
everything will be fine.
Just a little scare?
You're doubting my professional judgment?
No, doctor.
Um…
What about the girl brought in yesterday?
Ruan Su, from room 365.
How is she?
Without consent,
we can't disclose a patient's condition.
Doctor! Doctor!
The wound of the patient in room 326 reopened again.
The bleeding won't stop.
Please come check immediately.
Let's go.
Hello?
We found out that the leader of last night's assailants
seems to be an enemy of the Ruan family.
Two suspects are already in police custody.
Xingzhi, you're here.
I feel like my head is starting to spin again.
Can you help me call a doctor?
I don't feel well all over.
The doctor said you're fine.
How is that possible?
I clearly feel that
I'm not well.
Maybe they made a mistake.
Ziyin, why have you become like this?
This is obviously Ruan Su's fault.
Yesterday she was putting on an act all along.
She pretended to be weak in front of me.
Was that how she tricked you before?
Xingzhi, don't be fooled by her again.
I really am innocent.
You should believe me.
Enough.
Don't say anymore.
Go tell Ruan Su
that I came to see her.
Who are you?
Even our boss's name
isn't one you can casually say.
Miss,
please go tell your boss
that Mr. Bo and I are here to visit a patient.
That won't be necessary.
There's no need for you to go in.
Su doesn't want to see you.
I'm her husband.
I have the right to visit her.
And who are you
to make decisions for her?
Where does your confidence come from, Mr. Bo?
The reason you're not allowed in
is Su's decision.
I think,
someone else is now
more suited to stay by her side and care for her.
And that person is definitely not you.
And you?
Where does your confidence come from?
Driving?
I'll take you home.
Are you done yet?
I'm just worried about you.
I don't need your concern at all.
Mind your own business.
I think I do need to remind you
we've just
formally ended our marriage.
Please don't harass me again.
Let's have no more contact between us.
Four years of marriage,
Ruan Su, do you really not feel even a little bit of attachment to me?
Xingzhi, I heard you've officially divorced.
Mm.
That's great. Now that she's out of the picture,
you'll have time to keep me company.
How about we...
Ziyin,
I'm a bit busy right now.
I'll find you later, okay?
Xingzhi,
we haven't seen each other in so long.
How about this?
I'll wait here until you finish.
I think you've misunderstood me.
I've always seen you as a sister.
And the company really does have
a lot of matters waiting for me to handle.
I don't have the energy for anything else.
I'm sorry, Xingzhi.
I was too eager.
I'll leave now.
Ziyin, I found out.
Li Meixing is Ruan Su's stepmother.
Ruan Su was abused by her throughout her childhood.
Got it.
Welcome back to the Hengjiu Technology family, boss.
Su, happy divorce.
Thank you, everyone.
To celebrate your full return to the team,
we're planning a party.
What ideas do you have?
We'll follow your lead.
I appreciate everyone's kindness.
But divorce
really isn't something worth celebrating.
I think we should focus
on our company's women's safety app.
Let's prioritize our careers.
Then…
Let's wrap it up for now.
Wait.
To thank everyone for your hard work this year,
this year's year-end bonuses will be doubled.
Thank you, boss!
Can you be more careful?
Do you know who I am?
Apologies, Miss Cheng.
Please enjoy it.
You're Cheng Ziyin?
That's me.
Hello, Miss Cheng.
We finally meet.
I think that incident before
was a misunderstanding, right?
Sorry for hurting you last time.
My target
has always been Ruan Su.
Then now we share a common enemy.
What's your plan to deal with her?
Now's not the time.
I have more pressing matters.
This talent competition
is jointly hosted by the platform and Hengjiu Technology.
The winning singer
will become the product's spokesperson.
But I recently heard
Bo Group is in contact with Hengjiu Technology.
If I win this competition,
I can help them
connect,
and also gain some resources.
That's easy. I've got a way.
I didn't get the chance to greet Grandma just now.
Is she doing better?
She's recovering well.
That's good. Oh, right,
the list of singers for today's competition
was just released.
Cheng Ziyin is on it too.
Do you want me to intervene and make her withdraw?
No need.
Our original intent in holding this competition
was to select
the most suitable spokesperson for our new product.
Everyone should have an equal chance.
Cheng Ziyin is no exception.
Understood.