[1983]
Wang.
[Jiangshun Reclamation Depot]
I would like to confirm
something with you.
[Wang Jiangshun, owner, fence]
I care about nothing else
as long as I get paid.
Don't you have a clue
about why we come here?
I totally have no idea!
What's with the yelling?
Are you out of your mind?
I'll sort things out for you.
Wang,
listen.
Ma Xiaohu
told us something
that I wanted to verify with you.
He was trying to frame me.
You'd be a fool if you believed him.
I know he isn't trustworthy.
That's why I came.
Open up.
Just ask me out there.
OK.
He said you had a secret account book.
Take it with you
and come back with us for investigation.
I knew you were coming for it.
You know what?
I've hidden it up.
Wang,
put your gun down.
Illegal possession of firearms.
Resisting arrest
and assaulting a policeman.
I can give an order to gun you down.
You heard him.
Put your gun down.
You two.
Put down your guns first.
Wang,
easy.
We can talk things through.
We've known each other for years.
You can trust me.
I can't give you the book.
I'm not stupid
and I don't want to die either.
Put down your gun.
We can talk about anything but not this.
Don't come again
and everything will be okay.
Alright.
You're not considering your own benefit
but what about your son
who is working out of town?
Leave my son alone.
I'll kill you.
[Adapted from Zhao Junkai's novel,
Double Track Puzzle]
[Episode 20]
What's your plan?
We didn't see this coming.
The situation is not clear.
Sanmahu is not only your nemesis
but also a key suspect in this case.
Send Liu Liu and Nanyi to follow him.
Zhang and I
are leading a team to go there.
When the 766 Train
arrives at the station,
we'll lock down
this place for surveillance.
You can stick to your original plan
and act accordingly
when Sanmahu is spotted.
Mr. Xiong has contacted the local police
to block all exits.
When necessary,
the train's departure will be delayed
and I'll initiate
a full search of the train.
He'll be trapped there
the minute he sets foot
into the station.
[Train T766]
Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
Stop right there. Don't move.
Police on duty. Move aside.
Get up.
Take him away.
The guy is arrested
but why aren't we leaving?
It's already ten minutes late.
All units, attention.
Have you got sight of the target?
No sight of him.
Team one, two, three.
Follow me. We're boarding.
Others, wait on the platform.
Tell the conductor
the train can leave in three minutes.
Got it.
Where is your boss, Mr. Sanmahu?
Sending a brat to deliver the message
and hiding in the dark?
Shame on him.
What a coward.
Mr. Tu,
you're not being honest.
We had a deal.
You were supposed to come alone.
See?
You can't blame Mr. Sanmahu this time,
can you?
What are you here for?
To check things out for Mr. Sanmahu.
If you keep your promise,
he'll show up.
Get it?
Stay in and lock your door.
Don't come out.
Young man,
put down your knife.
Put it down.
Attention.
Mr. Tu is having a fight on Carriage 4.
Don't move.
Jump.
Are you delusional?
You. Jump.
Sanmahu
is at the turn coming ahead.
You won't get to see him
if you don't jump now.
Watch him
and tell Zhan Peng about this.
Mr. Zhan, Mr. Tu jumped off
to find Sanmahu.
Tell the conductor
to decelerate and stop ahead.
Contact Mr. Xiong right away
to request assistance
from the local police
to search the place
around the jump-off point.
We have to find Mr. Tu soon.
It's been 20 years.
Time for a closure.
Just cut to the chase.
Show your weapon.
I haven't used one for a long time.
Later,
please forgive me for cutting you,
shallow or deep.
Mr. Wang.
You were so freaking calm.
Come on.
Uncuff me.
Let's go to Mr. Jiang.
I have a secret for you.
Mr. Jiang is me.
Why?
Because
I am...
Wang Jiangshun's son.
I... I report Wang Jiangshun.
He's quite sly.
Last month when I went
to give him his share,
I saw that he had a secret account book
with info like amount, location,
and time in it.
I was responsible
for what happened.
Let things
end...
with me.
Don't hurt
any innocent people.
If you and Han Weidong
hadn't fired and caused the explosion,
I wouldn't have lost my family.
You should all die.
All die.
You have paid
for your debt.
Now, it's Zhan's turn.
♪The night covered up
how much I missed you♪
♪The wind tried to find where you were♪
♪The flowers withered
before bearing fruit♪
♪Yet you have never left♪
♪Looking back at the once-lit fire♪
♪Didn't expect it to die down so soon♪
♪But if I ask you this♪
Mr. Tu.
- Mr. Tu.
Call the ambulance.
Mr. Tu.
♪You wouldn't regret it.
We trust each other with our lives♪
Mr. Tu.
♪When the past finds you in your dream♪
♪And sings you an old song♪
[Hui]
♪When we cross
every river and mountain♪
♪To meet again♪
♪We'll reminisce about
every second of our past♪
Keep looking.
We must find him.
His home. His company.
Anywhere possible.
Han Xin.
Something's wrong with Wang Zhihui.
I found a bill of exchange
from an overseas account.
It matches the record of the account book
of my dad's company.
He secretly transferred
his money to his account.
I also found an account book...
I've already known.
Mr. Tu is badly hurt
by Wang Zhihui.
Now we're searching for him
across the city.
You should protect the evidence
and stay safe.
Keep me updated.
OK.
[Xiatong Railway Hospital]
[Emergency Room]
[In Operation]
Sorry,
the injury is too severe.
We have done our best
but he's in deep coma.
He's expected to enter
a vegetative state.
The chance of the patient waking up
is very dim.
[Han Xin:
He's at No.16 Huatengyuan Villa,]
[No.11 Binhe Road. Come quick.]
We found Wang Zhihui.
Go.
Zhang,
Nanyi, let's go.
Did you send the message?
What are you going to do?
Where is the notebook?
I don't know.
My father's death
has something to do with you, right?
I'll ask you again.
Where is the notebook from my safe?
If you don't want to tell me, fine.
It doesn't matter.
[Sanmahu]
[Tu Hongjiang]
We both lost our fathers.
How can you smile
so happily?
Han Xin.
Wang Zhihui, what are you going to do?
Anyone here?
Anyone?
Hello?
There is
no one.
Wang Zhihui, what's all this about?
It seems
that I underestimated you
or Han Weidong.
Now that you know who I am,
you must have known
what Han Weidong did before.
My father's dead
because of you,
right?
That's what he
deserved.
I was merciful enough
to allow him to commit suicide.
You are...
Mr. Jiang?
Surprising,
huh?
What do you want?
What do I want?
What if you're Mr. Jiang?
Worst case, we die together.
No?
Who on earth are you?
My father's name
is Wang Jiangshun.
Because of you,
he couldn't even keep his whole body.
You killed him!
I made a mistake.
I wouldn't deny it.
But my daughter,
she's innocent.
Innocent?
So am I.
But I'm not like you guys.
I don't push people into a dead corner.
Her safety is in your hands.
You know what to do.
I was supposed
to spend my whole life as a policeman
to uphold justice.
Yet, greed overtook me.
The bribery
forced me to silence him.
I never knew
Master would be dragged down by this.
All these years,
guilt keeps haunting me
but I don't dare to tell the truth.
Greed pushed me
all the way down the abyss.
What goes around,
comes around.
Wang Zhihui, you jerk.
You jerk.
I will kill you.
I will...
Clever girl.
It didn't take you long to find the key.
But it couldn't change anything.
Everything is going on as I planned.
No one
can get away with it.
Wang Zhihui,
you fool people around.
You despicable man.
Despicable!
Am I?
All these years,
thinking of what I've done
has been so exciting.
I enjoy it when I manipulate others.
I did it.
No.
Zhan Peng is still out there.
What does it have to do with Zhan Peng?
We both lost our fathers.
What makes his father a martyr?
Why could he live
under everyone's attention
while I could only drown in hatred?
Why?
Tell me.
Wang Zhihui,
what are you doing?
Hello, Han Xin.
Where are you?
I heard
you were after me?
Mr. Zhan,
Mr. Zhan, don't believe him.
Don't come over.
Wang Zhihui,
what do you want?
Listen carefully,
you won't get away with it.
I've never tried to.
I simply
want to talk to someone.
If you want her alive,
come by yourself.
Where?
Daoxiang Road.
Call me when you arrive.
What on earth are you going to do?
Hey,
I'm at Daoxiang Road.
What next?
Mr. Zhan,
you naughty boy.
It's already so late,
but many people are still following you.
Do you want her dead?
Mr. Zhan. Mr. Zhan.
Wang Zhihui has gone mad.
Don't come over.
He's already crazy.
He's crazy. Don't...
Han Xin. Han Xin.
Wang Zhihui,
before I arrive,
you must guarantee Han Xin's safety.
She's safe temporarily.
Mr. Xiong,
maybe you should retreat.
Wang Zhihui has surveillance.
He can see us there.
Han Xin is in great danger.
I'm at the yard.
What next?
Turn right.
And now?
Turn right again.
Eighty meters ahead of you
is a warehouse.
OK.
Wang Zhihui,
I know you can see me.
I'm here. Alone.
Come out now.
Wang Zhihui.
You're finally here.
Wang Zhihui,
you can't run away.
Han Xin,
are you alright?
Mr. Zhan,
Wang Zhihui has lost his mind.
He's Mr. Jiang.
Don't move.
Throw your gun over.
Hurry.
Have you collected Tu Hongjiang's body?
She's innocent.
Let her go first.
You all keep using the word "innocent".
You're innocent. She's innocent.
You are all innocent
but what about me?
Did anyone give me a way out?
[Young Wang Zhihui]
Dad.
All these years,
why can you get to live a steady life?
Why have you never expressed
the least feeling of hatred?
Why do you think
you can order me to let her go?
Why?
Because I'm a policeman
and so was my dad.
He was a martyr
who died for the country.
Why should I bear hatred?
Nonsense.
Zhan Peng,
listen carefully.
From Han Weidong dealing with drugs,
to Sanmahu's collapse,
and to Tu Hongjiang's miserable death,
I endured so much hardship
to make this happen step by step.
Wang Jiangshun is your father?
Yes.
He handled management fee
for different gangs.
They sold what they stole in my dad's place
[Jiangshun Reclamation Depot]
and left a part to him.
And finally, the money
was given to Han Weidong.
How can you be sure
what you know
is the truth?
I saw Han Weidong
come to fetch the money
and I know about the account book.
But one day,
you father learned from Sanmahu
about the account book.
He came with a gun for the book.
Your father
was the one who caused it.
He assaulted the police with a gun
before he was gunned down.
Zhang Yaohua took Han Weidong with him
and threatened my dad
to give them the book with a gun first.
Block all exits and entrances.
Snipers, get ready
on the commanding height.
Yes, sir.
Go.
Quickly.
My father protected himself
with a gun.
What's wrong with that?
Your father is to blame.
Zhang Yaohua.
Copy that.
Wang Zhihui,
you're surrounded.
Resist no more.
Surrender. This is your only way out.
Wang Zhihui,
you're surrounded.
Resist no more.
Surrender. This is your only way out.
They're here anyway.
That's good.
We can die together.
[People's Government of Hexi Province
Posthumously Awarded
Zhang Yaohua as "Martyr"]
What made you a martyr
while my dad died in shreds?
Morals? Laws? All nonsense.
You will all die.
Zhang Yaohua,
Han Weidong,
[Die]
Tu Hongjiang,
you'll pay for my dad's death
with your lives.
[Jiangshun Reclamation Depot]
Dad,
I'm coming.
Mr. Zhan.
Zhan Peng.
Call for an ambulance.
Quick.
Stay alert, you all.
Zhan Peng.
Hello.
Han Xin.
120.
We need backup.
[Two weeks later]
I'll give you the notebook.
Use it however you need.
I trust you.
Mr. Tu,
I understand your words now.
My father remained as my father.
And your master
remained as your master.
Thank you.
The 11·16 Special Case has been closed.
We successfully destroyed
the drug cartel in Xiatong
and gave a heavy blow
on the gang of thieves
along the railway line
connecting Kunyang and Xiatong.
Thank you for your hard work.
The Ministry of Public Security
has issued the Order of Commendation.
The special investigating team
has been awarded
Collective First-Class Merit.
Zhan Peng and Tu Hongjiang
have been awarded
Individual Third-Class Merit.
Salute.
Mr. Tai.
Come in.
Mr. Tai,
I have something important
to report to you.
These two notebooks
were found by Han Xin.
This
is the statement about the incident.
This is new evidence
for the explosion case
at Jiangshun Reclamation Depot
that happened many years ago.
Back then,
there were rumors
about your father.
Now the truth has been revealed.
The rumors that sabotaged
your father's reputation
will stand no ground.
It was someone else
who received the bribery.
Two notebooks.
One is legitimate and the other is not.
Just like his two disciples.
One upheld justice
and the other wandered into sideways.
Zhang Yaohua, while being a policeman,
[Pingzhang Railway Public Security Bureau]
had been impartial
and outstanding at work.
He had always been a great policeman.
[The End]
[After the People's Public Security's
strict investigation,]
[the People's Procuratorate had filed
a public prosecution in this case.]
[According to the ‌Criminal Law of the PRC]
[Criminal gangs led by Sanmahu,
Wang Zhihui, Han Weidong,]
[and Qi Lianshan
were sentenced as follows:]
[Criminal gang led by Sanmahu were involved
in killing, drug dealing, stealing,]
[and other serious crimes,]
[causing people's severe injuries
and deaths.]
[Sickly Dou and Specs
were sentenced to death]
[and deprived of political rights for life.]
[Lu Dingzhong and Hu Shangfei:
10 years in jail.]
[Bazijiao: 6 years in jail
for his support for investigation.]
[Principal offender Sanmahu
and accomplice Bai Taohua]
[died during the arrest
and were not prosecuted.]
[Criminal gang led by Wang Zhihui
were involved in killing,]
[drug trafficking and causing
grievous bodily harm with intent.]
[Sun Bojun and Crewcut
were sentenced to death]
[and deprived
of political rights for life.]
[Wang Zhihui died during the arrest
and were not prosecuted.]
[Criminal gang led by Han Weidong
were involved in killing,]
[drug trafficking and other crimes.]
[Hua Long and Sun Zhongze
were sentenced to death]
[and deprived of political rights for life.]
[Sheng Kuang and Li Daming were sentenced
to death with a two-year reprieve]
[for their great help
during the investigation.]
[Han Weidong and Mao died
during the arrest and weren't prosecuted.]
[Criminal gang led by Qi Lianshan
were involved in killing,]
[drug trafficking and other crimes.]
[Qi Lianshan, Yiman, and Dafei
were sentenced to death]
[and deprived
of political rights for life.]
[Langbu died during the arrest
and were not prosecuted.]
♪The brightest star in the evening sky♪
♪I still recall the dream
I chased so high♪
♪Time brushes past
like winds that stray♪
♪Yet never takes it all away♪
♪Those fearless moments from long ago♪
♪So many figures veiled their glow♪
♪If duty weighs upon my soul♪
♪Then turning back is not my goal♪
♪Who walks alone in the dark of night?♪
♪Who leaves behind all pain and fright?♪
♪Those vanished fast like fleeting day♪
♪I've learned to let go♪
♪Who smiles at dawn with quiet light?♪
♪Who makes the river pure and bright?♪
♪All we tried to guard♪
♪Is worth the pain we never barred♪
♪Who walks alone in the dark of night?♪
♪Who leaves behind all pain and fright?♪
♪Those vanished fast like fleeting day♪
♪I've learned to let go♪
♪Who smiles at dawn with quiet light?♪
♪Who makes the river pure and bright?♪
♪All we tried to guard♪
♪Is worth the pain we never barred♪