[1998]
I'm here.
Bao, thank you.
Alright.
That's Bao calling.
Hello?
Got it.
Don't worry, Bao.
Man, you're something else.
You got Bao to step in
and save this punk's ass.
Fine.
Kid,
today's your lucky day.
We are
letting it slide this time.
But
don't let me see you
in Kunyang again.
Next time,
nobody
can save you.
Let's go.
Stay out of my way!
We're all in this for the money.
My guy crossed you.
But he was paid to do this.
Just doing his job.
Here's the idea.
Let me apologize on his behalf.
This is for your medical expenses
and compensation.
Hao, please accept it.
You're a class act, man.
Respectable.
What should I call you?
My last name is Jiang.
Just call me Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Jiang.
See you.
Let's go.
Are you alright?
[Double Track Puzzle]
[Adapted from Zhao Junkai's novel,
Double Track Puzzle]
[Episode 19]
Based on Sheng's statement,
we've basically mapped out the structure
of the local drug trafficking ring
in Xiatong.
Initially, Han Weidong was the convener.
Under him was Sun Bojun,
who's still at large.
Further down were Hua Long and Mao,
and later, Sheng as their replacement.
Now, aside from Sun Bojun
who's on the run,
the Dragon Unleashed
drug trafficking ring
has basically been wiped out.
[Mr. Jiang]
Sheng
heard this name during the negotiations
between Han Weidong and Sanmahu.
Both sides were wary of this person.
His existence also explains
why there were so many doubts before.
Dragon Unleashed's gang
and Sanmahu's gang
have been fighting
yet negotiating all along.
That's because there was
always someone behind the scenes
controlling them.
I feel sorry
for what happened to Mr. Han.
I've been under him for many years.
He's always been good to me.
But he made mistakes.
And mistakes
come with consequences.
With Mr. Han gone,
there's a big gap left
in your operation.
Mr. Wang,
I heard you used to be
a straight-up businessman
and you were never
involved in anything this risky.
How about this?
Why not hand over
all their previous business to me?
That's thoughtful of you.
I've been scratching my head over this.
I need to find someone to take over.
You know Xiatong so well.
You'd be
the right fit.
Exactly.
Don't worry.
Rest assured, Mr. Wang.
You'll get every penny
of your cut.
When Mr. Jiang called me, he said
business decisions are mine to make.
If I don't want to do it,
I hand it over.
Once you take over,
you'll soon be the king
of Xiatong's underworld.
You can do whatever you want.
But there's one thing
you absolutely can't touch.
What is it? Please tell me.
Mr. Jiang says you can't
lay a finger on Tu Hongjiang.
So Mr. Jiang wants to
let him off the hook?
Of course not.
He just doesn't think
you're qualified to take him on yet.
I'm not qualified?
I don't like the sound of that.
I've been dealing with him for 20 years.
Let me tell you,
in Xiatong,
no one
can outplay him except me!
Don't be mad.
I'm just passing along the message.
If you disagree,
you can take it up with Mr. Jiang.
My apologies.
Sorry about that.
If Mr. Jiang says
leave him alone,
then I'll
leave him alone.
Come on.
To our pleasant partnership.
[Xin]
Xin,
by the time you read this,
I'll be gone.
There's a ledger
in the drawer of the shrine
at our old place.
It records all the financial aid
we've given to families of officers
in need over the years.
This is a legacy
that Mr. Tu and I
carry on from our master.
All the money comes
from everyone's donations.
It was meant to
support each other
in tough times.
I've kept doing this
over the years,
hoping to make up
for the mistakes I made.
♪Only a blurry picture remains♪
Sorry I've failed you.
♪Fading away bit by bit♪
What's so great about him?
I've been going up
against Tu Hongjiang for years.
I know Tu way better than he does!
Mr. Jiang
has connections everywhere
and has been running wild for years.
He's definitely not simple.
Not simple my foot!
Always putting on airs with me!
He might be
a big shot elsewhere.
But here in Xiatong,
no one messes with me!
Once I get close to him,
his spot
will eventually be mine!
- Pay us back!
When are you going to pay what you owe?
[Han Group]
Everyone!
- Pay us back!
Calm down, everyone!
Stay calm, everyone!
We will make this right.
Once Mr. Han's daughter gets here,
we'll have a solution.
Alright?
We don't need that!
We want our money now!
Give me back my money!
- Pay us back!
Ms. Han is here.
Ms. Han,
a man's dead, but his debts aren't!
This is our hard-earned money!
Exactly!
You've got to give us an answer.
How do we get our money back?
- Answer us!
- Pay us back!
Yeah!
Calm down.
Calm down!
[Han Group]
I'll repay every debt
my father owed!
If you don't believe me,
I'll write new IOUs.
You'll really write new IOUs?
When?
Yeah, when?
I'll do it today.
Alright.
Mr. Wang,
take them to the finance office.
Follow me.
One at a time.
One at a time. Take it easy.
Tu,
what's your take on Han Weidong's death?
Based on the scene investigation,
homicide's been ruled out.
I don't believe he'd jump
to escape his problems.
You're saying someone pushed him to it?
Weidong and I met back in the army.
He had no means,
and it was impossible for him
to get involved
with drug trafficking on his own.
Not long after he left the force,
he started his company.
He said
he made his money in transport.
I didn't think too much about it.
I was just happy for him.
But later, I thought about it.
There's no way he could have made
that much money
that fast
just from transport.
And during that time,
he was drinking a lot.
Right?
He seemed deeply preoccupied.
If I'd been there for him more,
maybe none of this would've happened.
I know you two had a special bond.
But Han Weidong was in the wrong.
This isn't on you.
We joined the army
and became cops together.
He never should've turned to drugs.
What a pity.
I know you wanted
to take the fall for him.
So, you insisted you were the one
who fired that shot.
And Han Weidong?
From what I've learned,
he was too shocked
to speak.
If not
for your gun records,
I think he
would have just
let you take the fall for him.
His family was struggling.
He needed the job more than I did.
No matter what his reasons were,
he shouldn't have turned
to drug trafficking.
And he kept at it for years.
No remorse.
He was driven by greed.
No excuse for that.
Have some water.
So, this is the situation.
All our accounts have been frozen.
There's no cash left
to pay the salaries.
Contact the bank for me.
I can take out a mortgage on the house.
We need to pay the employees
what they're owed.
Don't you know
the property and company assets
are already mortgaged?
Everything's mortgaged?
Then where did the money go?
It was all used
for the company's daily operations.
Fine.
I'll figure something else out.
I want to work at the company.
Is that okay?
Of course.
It's your family's company.
But
what about your current job?
I'll handle it.
Mr. Jiang,
you were right.
Sanmahu
is furious that you won't let him
touch Tu Hongjiang.
People from the company
have been called in
for questioning at the police station.
I just got back from being questioned.
Time's running out.
Since he's in such a hurry to die,
give him a push.
Keep an eye on him.
Update me anytime.
Understood.
- Mr. Wang.
Working late?
Were you looking for me?
Told you to go to the northern frontier
and clean up the mess.
Why haven't you left?
I was supposed to leave tonight.
But I heard something.
I'd like to talk to you about it.
Mr. Jiang.
I'm telling you the truth.
Do you think it's possible?
I see.
So you want to take over
Han Weidong's operations.
I don't have that kind of ambition.
I just want to
help you
manage part of the business.
Someone else has already volunteered.
You
don't need to worry about this.
Are you handing it all over to Sanmahu?
Mr. Han and I
built this territory
in Xiatong together.
We figured out
the northern frontier route bit by bit.
You're just gonna
let Sanmahu take it all?
That doesn't seem right.
With Han Weidong dead,
this matter is settled.
Drug trafficking is too dangerous.
Go to the northern frontier
and take over the Han family's mines.
Then you can go straight.
I know you're looking out for me.
But
I don't know the first thing
about mining.
Five years ago,
you didn't know anything either.
Now you run
all of Xiatong's operations.
So,
don't underestimate
your ability to start over.
Impossible.
If I get caught now,
I'm dead for sure.
There's no going straight for me.
As long as you're not caught,
there's still a chance.
I'm not giving
Xiatong's operations to Sanmahu.
I'm getting out for good.
If that's the case,
then I guess I have to give up.
But
if I get caught someday
and can't hold out, and end up
telling the cops about you...
Are you threatening me?
I just want a chance
to control my own fate.
I won't let you down.
Fine.
I'll give you
a fair shot against Sanmahu.
May the best man win.
You'll have to live
with the consequences.
Uncle.
I went through
Mabao's list again.
A few got caught.
A few ran.
Only three are left.
They say the heat's too intense now,
so they're afraid to take the goods.
What do we do?
It's good that they're afraid.
Anyone bold enough to ask for that much
is either trying to screw us over,
or
is a cop's informant.
Hello?
Mr. Sanmahu,
Elder Sun
from the Da'an League just sent word.
Says Qi Lianshan's nephew,
Qi Fengzi, wants to join us.
Asks if we'll take him in.
He says he'll vouch for him.
If Elder Sun vouches for him,
we can't say no.
Well,
put him under you.
Keep an eye on him for three months.
If he's got what it takes,
send him
to the northern frontier
to take back
Qi Lianshan's turf.
Understood.
♪I stand upon the tower wall♪
♪To see the mountains tall♪
♪Outside the gate, I hear the sound♪
♪Of chaos♪
♪All around♪
The Dragon Unleashed
drug trafficking ring
in Xiatong has been basically wiped out.
Only Sun Bojun remains at large.
He goes by Mr. Sun.
Sir,
has the merged case report
I submitted
on Sanmahu's criminal group
been approved yet?
Mr. Tai approved.
The official documents
will be issued to Xiatong today.
It's merged into the joint task force.
You and Zhang Cheng
will remain in charge.
Call me if you need
any coordination.
Got it.
Thanks.
Mr. Tu.
Any news?
East suburbs.
Around the Shisitiao area, Wuliying.
That's as specific
as it gets.
Alright.
Leave the rest to me.
Not a single one.
What's going on
with you today, old timer?
Haven't fished in a while, maybe.
Or maybe I'm just getting old.
What happened?
Nothing.
Mr. Tu.
Lately, I've been
really missing my hometown.
I want to go back for a visit.
I remember
you have no family left there, right?
Yes.
I left at fourteen,
and never planned to go back.
Lately, I don't know why,
but I keep dreaming about the place.
It's where I was born and raised.
To return to one's roots, I guess.
Feels like it's time to go back.
For the first time,
I've felt like I've lived a long life.
You're saying that
in front of an old man like me?
It feels long enough.
All my old friends are gone,
one by one.
Especially Mr. Qian.
He helped so many people,
and did so much good.
But he didn't meet a good end.
Mr. Tu.
Is this how it ends
for people like us?
What goes around, comes around.
Don't overthink it.
Let me know before you leave.
We'll get together.
These gatherings
are numbered now.
I understand.
Send me the materials later.
I'll let you know when I receive them.
Alright, that's it.
Han Xin.
I'm leaving.
I wanted to
say goodbye to Mr. Tu and the others,
but they're all out on missions.
Wait a moment.
All packed?
Yes.
I forgot something,
so I came back to get it.
Is it because of your father?
Not entirely.
There are issues he left behind
that I need to resolve.
But my role as a cop
doesn't allow it.
Resigning
is my best option.
Han Xin,
you are you.
And your father is your father.
Some things are clearly right or wrong
in the eyes of the law.
Some are judged by morality.
You don't have to carry this alone.
And you shouldn't
bear the weight of his mistakes.
Mr. Zhan.
I know your father was a hero
and a martyr.
You're stepping
into the responsibility
and mission he left behind.
So am I.
Though my father's gone,
the company remains.
So do the responsibilities he left.
I have to take them on.
No matter the outcome,
I'll face it.
Han Xin,
remember this.
Your colleagues here
will always be your comrades
and friends.
If you run into trouble,
come to us.
There's something
I need to ask of you.
Go ahead.
I know the evidence
at the scene suggests
my father killed himself.
But I firmly believe
he wouldn't do that.
I will find proof.
Please don't give up on this, alright?
We still haven't caught Sanmahu
and Sun Bojun.
As long as there's the slightest doubt,
we'll never close the case.
That's good.
Mr. Zhan!
♪How could I accept fading away?♪
Thank you for looking out for me.
♪Drifting with
the ocean's rise and fall♪
Thank you, too.
Take care.
♪After the sea has eroded all traces♪
♪Silence returns to claim it all♪
♪Counting the belated realizations now♪
Mr. Zhan.
Stay safe on your mission.
Protect yourself.
♪If only the roles could be rewritten♪
♪We'd lean less on illusions' glow♪
♪To find the grace to let you go♪
This place is hard to find.
Where are you?
Bridge. There's a bridge.
Alright.
Over here.
I've been looking for you forever.
Police! Freeze!
Mr. Tu.
Cuff him.
Let's go.
Be gentle.
Behave.
Xin.
I suppose I should call you Ms. Han now.
These are the financial statements
from all the subsidiaries.
Except for Dasheng Transport,
which is still under seizure,
the others are operating normally.
Take a look first.
Let me know if you have any questions.
Thanks.
Thanks to you,
the company is still running
and the employees can keep their jobs.
Don't mention it.
Mr. Han has always been good to me.
When I came back from the south,
my business had failed.
If Mr. Han hadn't given me a hand,
I'd be working
on an assembly line somewhere.
Even though he's gone,
I'll make sure
to keep the company in good shape.
By the way,
this was Mr. Han's office.
It was just unsealed when you arrived.
Haven't had time to tidy up.
Let me know if you
have any concerns about it.
Should we bring in
a feng shui consultant?
Or maybe move to a different office?
No need.
I used to be a cop.
I'm as tough as nails.
Besides,
being in a place where my father worked
will only make me more motivated.
Alright then.
Take your time getting settled.
If you need anything,
just reach out to your secretary, Li.
Dad,
what were you doing here
all these years?
Where do I
even start?
You said
the simplest way
is often the most effective.
Let's get started.
Mr. Jiang.
It's me.
I think Sanmahu's about to snap.
He's on the edge,
ready to go all out.
Then let him.
But you said the timing wasn't right.
Should we wait a bit longer?
Plans change.
But maybe it's for the best.
Stick with him for now.
I'll call him tonight
and tell him what to do.
Understood.
Do you need something?
I looked through the materials,
but I couldn't understand them.
Can I see the company's
recent financial statements?
So I can get a clearer picture
of the financial situation.
I'll have the accountant
bring them to you.
I already asked.
They're closing the books
at the end of the month,
so we'll have to wait until next month.
Do you have a backup copy?
Yes.
Just a moment.
Everything is here.
Let me know
if you have any questions.
Thank you.
From Majia Village?
Yeah.
Who's Sanmahu to you?
He's my uncle.
Also my idol.
Have you seen him lately?
No.
Think carefully.
Have you?
You can say I have if you want.
But I don't know where he is.
Officer,
is that okay?
Kid,
do you know who I am?
Mr. Tu.
Heard of me?
I know you guys from Majia Village
have guts and can't be messed with.
But let me tell you,
ten years ago,
I could've crushed you guys.
And I still can.
Think hard.
Say it when you've figured it out.
Mr. Tu.
Mr. Tu!
I'd like to
treat you and the other guys
in First Division tonight.
How about it?
No other intentions.
The bureau has decided to
merge the cases for investigation.
So Sanmahu is our shared target now.
You've been going against him
for over 20 years.
You're the veteran here.
I can handle drug dealers,
but when it comes to dealing
with an cunning fox like Sanmahu,
I'll need to learn from you.
Alright.
At seven tonight.
I'll pick the place.
You're paying.
Alright.
Mr. Sanmahu.
Have something to eat.
No sense of timing at all.
I'm starting to think
this Jiang guy
is a fraud!
Hello?
Mr. Jiang.
Finally, your called.
I heard what happened during the day.
Then do it.
Mr. Sanmahu,
let me remind you,
taking action against Tu Hongjiang
is a big deal.
He's a fixer for the law-abiding,
a grim reaper for the underworld.
If you're going to move,
make it clean.
No hesitation, no loose ends.
Either
take him out in one strike,
or
be prepared to burn together.
Understood.
Perfect, Mr. Jiang.
With your support,
I'm more confident
about all the scores
with him.
Actually,
I have a more thorough, reliable plan.
Today's incident was fate.
Then let's just follow it
and finish him tomorrow.
Let me remind you again.
Don't act rashly.
Stick to my plan.
If all goes well,
I'll meet you at the destination,
[October 4th, T766,
Xiatong to Shannan, Tu Hongjiang]
the very place where you
take down Tu Hongjiang.
Mr. Jiang,
thank you for your full support.
I will
never forget it.
Look forward to meeting you.
[Back for More]
Kid.
No, no.
Mr. Zhan.
Hey, don't.
By age,
I am almost as old as your uncle.
By seniority,
we're peers.
Your father was my master.
He taught me a lot.
How to conduct myself
and how to handle things.
I'll never forget that.
I know sometimes
you look down on my methods.
I won't hold it against you.
Times are different,
and so are the people
and situations we face.
But no matter when
or what era,
your father is your father.
My master is my master.
That won't change.
I'll remember that.
How was this money collected?
Why is Sanmahu on here too?
Dad?
This ledger is definitely fishy.
[Back for More]
Alright.
Everyone, head back now.
We've got work tomorrow.
Go on, get going.
Let me walk you home.
Don't bother.
In Xiatong,
I could find my way even blindfolded.
Go back.
I'll get going then.
You all go ahead.
I'll walk him home.
Bye.
Mr. Tu, I've got things to do.
I'll head out.
Alright.
Mr. Tu, take care.
Sneaking off early again?
What's your problem?
Watch where you're going.
The road's wide,
and you crash right here?
Mr. Sanmahu has a message for you.
Tomorrow, T766, hard seat.
If you've got any guts,
come alone.
Tell him
I'll be there on time.
Tomorrow's a big day.
Should I do something?
Be ready.
Don't worry about Tu Hongjiang.
Just keep your eyes on Sanmahu.
Whether he kills Tu Hongjiang or not
doesn't matter.
What matters is whether
you get the chance to take over
Xiatong's business.
Understood.
Thank you, Mr. Jiang.
You're right.
May the best man win.
It's him or me.
Tomorrow, only one of us two
will be coming to see you.
[Tu Hongjiang, Captain, First Division,
Xiatong Railway Police Department]
♪The brightest star in the evening sky♪
♪I still recall the dream
I chased so high♪
♪Time brushes past
like winds that stray♪
♪Yet never takes it all away♪
♪Those fearless moments from long ago♪
♪So many figures veiled their glow♪
♪If duty weighs upon my soul♪
♪Then turning back is not my goal♪
♪Who walks alone in the dark of night?♪
♪Who leaves behind all pain and fright?♪
♪Those vanished fast like fleeting day♪
♪I've learned to let go♪
♪Who smiles at dawn with quiet light?♪
♪Who makes the river pure and bright?♪
♪All we tried to guard♪
♪Is worth the pain we never barred♪
♪Who walks alone in the dark of night?♪
♪Who leaves behind all pain and fright?♪
♪Those vanished fast like fleeting day♪
♪I've learned to let go♪
♪Who smiles at dawn with quiet light?♪
♪Who makes the river pure and bright?♪
♪All we tried to guard♪
♪Is worth the pain we never barred♪