♪I used a lie♪
♪To keep you by my side♪
♪To make it real♪
♪I spent all my life♪
♪Who is your dream partner♪
♪I look forward to the dawn♪
♪I want you to stay♪
♪I've tried everything I can♪
♪I'm the liar♪
♪My love agitated in mind♪
♪But I dare not say anything to you♪
♪Let me taste alone♪
♪The time without you♪
♪I don't deserve it♪
♪I don't deserve to be forgiven♪
[The Princess and the Werewolf]
[Adapted from Orange's novel of the same name]
[Episode 30]
Never try to play tricks.
Tell me.
What's the deal with the secret room
in your chamber?
And why is that spring
almost dry?
How many things are you hiding from me?
It seems you got it.
Presumably you also know that
kings of Beast Clan won't live long.
What do you mean?
The spring in my room
is called the Holy Spring.
It is related to the fate
of the entire Beast Clan.
The mission of all the kings
is to protect the Holy Spring.
In fact,
the plague of the Beast Clan
a hundred years ago
has never ended.
If the common people can't drink
the spring water injected with internal force,
they may be at risk of being attacked
by the residual disease in their bodies
at any time.
We need to constantly inject
internal force into the Holy Spring.
Our lives
are also greatly depleted.
How come?
That's why the kings of Beast Clan
of all ages
couldn't show anyone their true colors.
As we become weaker and weaker,
our appearance
will also become uncontrollably animalized.
Haven't you always wanted to know my secret?
This is my secret.
The truth about my changing appearance.
I can't believe this.
So this is also the case with
our father and ancestors?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Because I am your elder brother.
This is a mission I should undertake,
not yours.
I sought the Holy Pearl
in order to completely change my destiny.
Yet I failed.
If you become the King,
I will pass on to you
all the cultivation methods
left by ancestors
to activate your internal force.
But do remember.
Jing Muhan.
You have to take back the Holy Pearl
to completely save the Beast Clan.
Never let Su Daqiang rule the clan.
This is the real secret of the Holy Pearl.
No.
I don't believe it.
Not even a word.
Jing Muhan.
Take the current situation seriously.
The hopes of the entire Beast Clan
is pinned on you.
Qi Pa.
Shall we begin?
He.
Can Qi Pa
be ruthless and kill Kui Mulang?
So many people detain them.
Even if she wants to play tricks,
there is no way for them to escape.
I think that
the so-called love
is just a lie.
I've known all along that
this woman only cares about herself,
not Kui Mulang at all.
Kui Mulang.
Now you also feel
the bone-chilling coolness.
It must feel good
to be cut into pieces by your beloved one,
huh?
Give her the sword.
Execution.
Don't be afraid.
I'm meant to die.
You just set me free earlier.
Qi Pa.
What are you doing?
Do it now.
It's okay.
Qi Pa.
Although I lost the Holy Pearl,
since my blood
made you sober from a mad state,
it will definitely help you
temporarily recover your force.
You'll be fine.
I love you.
Take him down.
Qi Pa!
Why are you so silly?
Because you are
my Mr. Right.
I am a little tired.
I am going to sleep.
Go ahead.
I am here.
You fool.
Kui Mulang.
Your Highness, you woke up.
Come on.
Great, you finally woke up.
You have slept all day and all night.
I was so scared.
You...
Your Highness, don't be afraid.
All the bad guys have been captured.
Su Daqiang and Xiniang
have been executed.
No one drugs us anymore.
Great.
What about Kui Mulang?
His Majesty...
Did anything happen to him?
[Kuixing Palace]
Kui Mulang, where are you?
♪You and the sun both shined♪
♪Into my lonely heart♪
♪Sweet or disappointed,
only I could understand♪
♪Tick tack, it slowly exposed me♪
♪As I played dumb♪
♪Tick tock, wet my struggle♪
♪I wish I could♪
♪Be with you till the end of the night♪
♪Watch over you in my name♪
♪If only I hold your hand♪
♪And look into your eyes♪
♪If only I could say it out♪
♪That I want to be with you forever♪
I was sending internal force
to the Holy Spring just now,
and I didn't hear you.
Sorry
to make you worry about me.
You have returned to
Li Xiong.
With the Holy Pearl,
nothing will happen to you again, right?
I have taken the Holy Pearl,
and now I am fully recovered.
Great.
With the power of the Holy Pearl,
you can completely restore the Holy Spring.
The people of the Beast Clan
are no longer in danger, are they?
The entire Beast Clan should thank you.
If it weren't for you sacrificing yourself
to merge your blood with mine,
I wouldn't have been able to take back
the Holy Pearl back then.
I remembered that
my blood worked on you
when you went berserk,
so I decided to take a risk.
I didn't expect it to succeed.
If I had known earlier,
I should have slashed my body
a few times
and merged my blood with yours.
Nonsense.
But the Holy Pearl...
How come?
No idea.
Maybe it's because of that kiss?
Great.
By the way,
where is Ma Yingxiong?
While in prison,
I didn't have a chance to speak to him.
Now things are all settled.
He should come to me.
Did he go for Chun'er?
Ma Yingxiong committed suicide
in order to keep the secret for us.
What?
I have arranged for an elaborate funeral.
His cenotaph is right in the back mountain.
If we miss him,
we can visit and pay our respects
at any time.
I shouldn't have brought him here.
I don't deserve to be his princess.
What about Chun'er?
Chun'er...
She was overwhelmed with grief
when she heard the bad news
and passed out.
Don't worry.
I have asked the imperial doctor
to stay by her side
to diagnose and treat her at any time.
Your Majesty, Your Highness.
Jing Muhan is kneeling outside the chamber,
hoping to have a private chat
with Your Majesty.
Will he try to do anything else to you?
It's okay.
I'm back to normal now.
He can't do anything to me.
Just wait here for me.
I will be right back.
Bai Ke.
Leave us alone.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What's done is done.
I have no excuse left.
I have only one request.
If you still regard me
as your younger brother,
I hope you can spare Haitang.
I can promise you
to spare her life,
but she has to pay
for what she has done.
I trust you.
My brother always keeps his promises.
Who allowed you to die?
Although you repeated the same mistakes
and your crime is unpardonable,
death is the easiest thing.
I want you to stay alive.
Copy the laws of the Beast Clan every day,
and earnestly learn
how to bear the responsibility of a prince.
Aren't you afraid
that I can't change my nature
and do something
that goes against the moral conscience again?
With your current strength,
I don't think you can make it.
What's more,
you are my younger brother after all.
I didn't know the ins and outs
of what happened in the past.
I used to think that father chose you
to be the King
because he favored you.
It seems that I'm wrong.
In fact, the person
father preferred is me.
He wanted you to bear
the hardships that all the kings
had to go through,
and gave me
a longer and better life.
Don't you blame him?
I'm the elder brother.
This is my responsibility.
I'm supposed to take care of
my younger brother.
And we are the royal family.
We have to take on the responsibility
of protecting the Beast Clan.
Brother.
It's my fault.
We are here today
to pray for the spirit of Ma Yingxiong.
I hope you can forget the pain soon,
and live well with his aspirations in mind.
Write down everything
you want to say to him.
He will hear it.
Yingxiong.
You really became a hero.
You will always be our hero
and my fool.
Alright.
Light the lanterns.
I grew up in the army
and lived a rough life.
I like to eat white steamed buns
with pickles.
I won't eat this steamed bun.
I'm going to dry it out.
I'll look at it
whenever I think about you.
You fool.
I would like to be your hero,
and I would also like to be your fool.
Where is Her Grace?
Where is she?
You Grace, I am here.
Don't be afraid of them.
Your Grace, revenge complete.
Hard work for you.
Ma Yingxiong.
I am from Daxia.
Of course I have to abide
by Daxia's rules.
- Just call him...
- Never mind.
Prince Consort.
Okay, Prince Consort.
General Ma.
Hope you are all well in heaven.
Don't worry, General Ma.
I will take good care of Chun'er for you.
I will accompany her out of the sadness.
General Ma.
Rest in peace.
Ma Yingxiong.
Thank you for everything
you did for us and Beast Clan.
May under your protection,
the people of Daxia and Beast Clan
can be happy and healthy.
Haitang.
Do you think I can atone for my sins?
As long as we sincerely repent,
I believe we can.
After tonight,
I will follow His Majesty's order
and go to jail to serve my sentence.
I'll go with you.
I promised my brother that
I would truly take responsibility
for protecting the Beast Clan.
Only when I am cleansed of my sins
am I qualified to do so.
[Yaohua Palace]
The story between you and His Majesty
is so sweet.
His Majesty even pretended
to be Mr. Li to date you.
So why doesn't His Majesty
wear his cape and hood anymore?
Why does the whole palace
have a three-day holiday?
Is there any happy event?
You have so many questions.
This is a secret of the royal family
and should be kept secret.
By the way,
what's your plan for today?
Ask Liu Jun out.
After all, it is difficult for a man
to chase a woman,
but it is very simple for a woman
to chase a man.
I've been trying hard.
It's different now.
After all, the world is stable and peaceful.
Why doesn't Liu Jun
agree to you?
Ask him out tonight.
Just tell him that...
I'm embarrassed to do so.
It's just short of the final step.
Liu Jun is very popular.
I will give it a try.
I believe in you.
Your Highness, Liu Jun asked to see.
Please come in.
Hongxiu.
I have something to tell you.
What?
It's up to you tonight.
Go for it. Don't let me down.
Well.
Hongxiu
also has something to tell you.
I will leave you alone.
I am going for Kui Mulang.
Hongxiu.
Do you have anything to tell me?
You go first.
Today I am on holiday.
I wonder if you have time.
Yes.
I do. Let's go together.
Okay.
See you later.
Hu Die.
The whole palace is on holiday.
Why don't you go out?
What's the point of going out alone?
Then go out with me.
Why should I go out with you?
Hu Die.
Yes or no?
Just let me know.
What do you mean?
Be my girlfriend.
Yes or no?
If you say no,
I won't bother you again.
You!
You always have an ambiguous attitude,
which makes me unable to eat or sleep.
Look.
Why are you laughing at me?
What do you mean?
What do you think?
I have no idea.
Your mind is the hardest to guess.
You!
Look at how Her Highness treats His Majesty.
Whether she likes him or not,
she never hides her feelings.
You!
It's obvious to all.
All the lovers are together.
What about me?
I...
I am still guessing your mind.
Then go for Her Highness.
Stop guessing my mind.
Now!
Go back where you came from.
I get annoyed when I see you.
Why are you angry again?
I...
Do I have to
make myself clear?
Of course you do.
Or I won't know.
Well...
That's a yes.
No.
Wait.
It's a yes.
Miss Hongxiu.
Mr. Liu Jun.
I'm sorry I'm late.
No.
I was early.
No worries.
I went to buy you candy.
I didn't expect
such a long queue on the streets today
because of the holiday.
So I was late.
Why did you buy me candy?
Mr. Liu Jun.
In fact, there is something
I wanted to tell you a long time ago.
I have long
been silently watching you.
But I'm just a maid.
There is very little I can do for you.
After much deliberation,
I felt that I could only buy you
all the sweetest and delicacies
of the Beast Clan.
I hope you will be happier
and smile more
after you eat them.
Hongxiu.
Mr. Liu Jun.
Actually, when we made wishes
under the sky lanterns last night,
I not only prayed for Chun'er
and General Ma,
but also secretly
made a wish for myself selfishly.
I hope that
the person I love can no longer escape
or restrain himself.
Mr. Liu Jun.
I like you.
Hongxiu.
I like you, too.
It started a long time ago.
You've always been there for me.
Your bravery puts me to shame.
After going through this,
I realized that
instead of being overcautious and indecisive,
it is better to cherish the person
in front of me.
You are wearing these gloves.
But...
Mr. Liu Jun.
As long as you like me the same,
there's nothing
the two of us can't overcome.
♪The day the sunlight touched your face♪
♪All the darkness faded away♪
♪I gave you my hand♪
♪And we ran to chase the sunset♪
♪We made a wish♪
♪That's just between you and me♪
♪Firefly on your fingertip♪
♪The flow in your eyes ♪
♪I just wanted the moment to last♪
[Yaohua Palace]
Watch your steps.
Here.
Qi Pa.
What are you going to show me?
You'll know it soon.
Let's go.
So mysterious.
Alright.
Open your eyes now.
How is it?
Does it look good?
The style of these clothes
is a bit special.
Let's put it on.
You...
I am afraid
I will lose my dignity in it.
A man dolls himself up for his lover.
Won't you wear it
for me?
This is a haute couture couple outfit
designed by me personally
and rushed out by the tailors.
What outfit?
It means that we are in love
and wear the same color
and style of clothes,
so that others know
we are a couple.
I will put it on
and show others that we are a couple.
Look.
The flower is me.
And the wolf is you.
It means...
We are bound together.
You are clever,
indeed!
You are so considerate.
But even if the flower is not on the clothes,
you are always in my heart.
What a
sweet talker.
So this is called a cute puppy in the eye
of the beholder.
What puppy? I am a wolf.
Okay.
You are a Cute wolf.
I am just a wolf.
Why do you think I am cute?
You can only be cute in front of me.
Thank you.
But I'm still not used to
seeing you like this at night.
It feels a little strange.
Strange?
Where?
Adorably strange.
You have to bear with it.
After all, I will always
be so handsome.
You were handsome before.
Luckily I had kissed that face before.
Otherwise it would be a big loss.
You really want to
take advantage of anything.
I only take advantage of you.
Who wouldn't want a good deal
of buying one and getting one free?
By the way,
you still owe me a word, right?
What?
Stop pretending.
Say it now.
All women love it.
I...
Listen carefully.
Qi Pa.
The only thing I want
in my life
is you.
I love you.
Are you satisfied?
Okay.
I saw the surprise you prepared.
I also have a surprise for you.
You do?
Let's go.
Let's go up the mountain
to watch the stars.
Hold on.
We should have something more important to do
before that.
Is there anything more important?
When we were in the cave before,
we had a wedding ceremony.
Shall we have
our wedding night now?
I've been waiting for this moment
for a long time.
I will never let you go today.
Ever since you came to me,
you have seduced me several times.
What?
Do you think I'll keep calm all the time?
I will show you tonight.
[One year later]
Kui Mulang left it behind.
Liu Jun left it behind.
Even the elders left it behind.
Why did they leave me with this mess?
Calm down.
Your Royal Highness.
I am coming again.
There are more?
It's all Qi Pa's fault.
She said that Daxia's people
would go on a honeymoon.
Kui Mulang went on a honeymoon.
Liu Jun went on a honeymoon.
Even Bai Ke went on a honeymoon.
Alright.
Easy.
When they come back,
let's go on a honeymoon.
Okay.
Not only a honeymoon,
but also a honey-year.
You two are so sweet.
Why don't you just
leave us alone?
Yes.
The princess cried very sadly,
staring blankly at
the tall and mighty man in front of her.
The book is not well written.
The princess
depends on men for everything,
and has no charm at all.
Dear.
You've improved.
It's all because of you.
The book is not good enough.
I will change it for you.
Auntie, uncle.
Xingping is coming.
Xingping, come here.
He came to see you from such a distance.
He must like you very much.
I
also like him very much.
Before, I was just pretending.
I knew it.
What are you two whispering?
It is a secret
between girls.
Your Grace, Prince Consort.
His and Her Majesty
have been holding two babies all day long,
refusing to let us help.
Her Majesty also asked
if she could stay with them a little longer.
That would be great.
We just want to ask Aunt Lyu
to take care of Xiao Zongzi
and Xiao Yuebin.
My Lady.
Let's go back and play
with the younger siblings.
Okay.
I knew you'd like to be alone.
Let's go.
Go.
Goodbye.
Xingping knows a lot.
I think she's right.
Prince Consort.
Aren't you supposed to
give me a honeymoon?
It's all up to you.
Let's go then.
My parents were overjoyed
when they heard that
I had found my Mr. Right.
They invited us
to exchange the latest Daxia culture
with the local people,
and then go back to Beast Clan
to have a look together.
Alright, just stop here.
What's wrong?
I have no problem with my suit.
But yours
is way too skimpy.
The people over there
are all dressed like this.
Alright.
Let's go.
Don't miss the ship.
Visa, tickets.
My dear.
Europa.
We are coming!
Enjoy your trip, Your Grace.
♪The wind blows the petals into rain♪
♪They turn into memories in the palm♪
♪It's you who makes me happy♪
♪It's also you who ruins it all♪
♪Sometimes it is your name♪
♪Stay in the starry sky♪
♪Sometimes it is thousands of miles apart♪
♪Sometimes lovesickness, sometimes hatred♪
♪But it's you all the time♪
♪I'm stuck in the day and night with you♪
♪Sometimes it's true love♪
♪Sometimes I got nothing in return♪
♪But it's your back all the time♪
♪Lovesickness turned into everything♪
♪And everything is you♪
♪I'm addicted to the fantasy of having you♪
♪Sometimes it's true love♪
♪Sometimes I got nothing in return♪
♪But it's your back all the time♪
♪Lovesickness turned into everything♪
♪And everything is you♪
♪Without me, can you get whatever you want?♪