Seoul Busters
Guys, this is the interrogation room.
It's used for interrogation.
I see.
We interrogate people here…
Minseo.
You left this out of the reimbursement.
Thank you, thank you.
Anyway,
how much longer will that tour take?
It's almost over.
A daycare center full of high schoolers?
I can't tell if I'm at school or at work.
Hey, stop scratching your head
and just wash your hair already.
It doesn't itch that badly yet.
Seriously, people shouldn't
wash their hair every day.
-We live in a water-stressed country.
-Listen.
I bet camels in the desert
wash up more often than you.
Hmph.
By the way,
does that boy know Detective Jang?
He's sticking so close to him.
He looks up to our rookie.
He looks up to Jang Tansik?
-Yes.
-Why?
The boy's father once got involved
in a road debris accident,
and Detective Jang tracked down the perp.
-Is everything clear?
-Yes.
What's this?
300 won for craft sticks?
Remember when we captured that wanted man
-outside the stationery store?
-Yes.
We accidentally damaged
some craft sticks in the process.
And the store owner demanded 300 won.
For the damages?
Yeah, can you believe it?
Please make sure I get reimbursed.
I paid for it out of my own pocket.
Junghwan.
This is 100 won short.
Anyway, please reimburse me.
I'll reimburse you 100 won.
You've already been paid 200 won.
-But still--
-Go away.
-Bye.
-See you.
You're so handsome.
-Bye.
-Take care.
-See you.
-Bye.
-Tansik, take this.
-What's this?
I told my dad I was coming here,
and he wanted me to give this to you.
He didn't have to.
What bold colors.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Beomjoon, don't eat
instant noodles too often.
You should eat well.
How did you know
I had instant noodles for lunch?
I have a really good sense of smell.
Oh, you're like Sherlock Holmes.
-You should get going.
-Okay, see you.
-Say hi to your father for me.
-Will do.
-Bye.
Why are you just standing there, sir?
You guys were blocking the way.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Ah.
-How did you know he had instant noodles?
-Instant noodles?
Ah.
I just smelled them.
If you ask me how I did that…
All I can say is that I smelled them,
so I said he smelled like them.
Then can you figure out
what I had for lunch?
Let me give it a try.
Please excuse me.
I'm not sure.
I don't smell anything.
That's incredible.
I haven't had lunch yet!
Ah.
You must have extremely well-developed
olfactory neurons.
The human nose is
one of the oldest sensory organs,
yet its exact method of detecting smells
remains to be fully understood.
In short,
it's an incredibly mysterious organ.
You must be…
…a natural-born…
…bloodhound.
Oh, I'm no match for a dog.
Dogs are amazing.
Don't say that.
I think you might be
even better than a dog.
You really have the nose of a dog.
Are you calling me a dog?
I'm flattered.
Would you like to try these on, sir?
-What are these?
-They're top-quality socks.
Wow. "Nice."
Guess this brand is popular
with young people these days.
Is that a person?
Excuse me.
Hello?
Seoul Busters
Episode 9
Keep up the good work.
Captain.
A resident found the body
on his way to church this morning
and called the police right away,
around 4:05 a.m.
I see.
What's up with Detective Jang?
He knew the victim.
You see, the other day--
-"Nice."
-What do you mean, nice?
The victim is the father of the boy
from the recent tour.
How do you know that?
His socks.
And the weapon?
They didn't find it at the scene,
so they're searching the area.
But they haven't found anything yet.
We're still looking.
-Check the CCTVs and dashcams first.
-Yes, sir.
The body is badly mangled.
Judging by the wounds,
he must've been struck
with a blunt weapon.
Not just once but multiple times.
It doesn't seem premeditated though.
I'm not so sure.
It might not have been a chance event.
That's hot!
Are you okay, sir?
Here, it's piping hot.
Okay, thanks.
Sure. Here.
CCTV facing another direction
A dead end
Red bricks
Hold on a second.
This is like looking for a needle in…
What was it?
-A haystack?
-Exactly.
Hey, have you found anything?
No, nothing yet.
Oh! I found it!
-Under your right foot.
-Where?
That's it, right? Captain!
We found it.
The victim is Mr. Yoon Haesik.
He sold items like socks from a truck.
The weapon, a brick,
was found at a nearby construction site,
with blood matching that of the victim.
I knew something was off.
I had a hunch.
Since the weapon was found on the street,
we can assume it was manslaughter.
Everything's falling into place.
It's the work of a mugger.
Considering the method and the scene,
it's 100% a mug--
It wasn't a mugger.
No, it wasn't.
A mugger wouldn't have been this cruel.
So the killer's too cruel to be a mugger?
Most wounds were inflicted
after the victim lost consciousness,
and they were focused on his face.
There were emotions involved.
Should I remind you
how cruel muggers can be?
In the mugging case in 2009
at the Mullae-dong Intersection,
the victim--
Nothing was stolen,
so it couldn't have been a mugger.
Nothing was stolen?
Nothing at all.
I don't know what exactly happened,
but how could someone
murder another person so brutally?
I'll…
catch the killer with my own hands.
Are you okay, Tansik?
Tansik!
What's up with him?
He knew the victim.
Why are you back?
I realized the meeting wasn't over yet.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's likely that the murder
was motivated by a grudge.
Let's find those
who held a grudge against the victim.
Mr. Yoon was a really nice person.
I doubt anyone held a grudge against him.
We'll see about that.
We'll catch the killer.
This is so unlike you.
Let's catch the bastard.
Do you recognize him?
He lived around here for a long time.
Don't get me started.
-Yoon, the socks seller, was notorious.
-Also known as Mad Dog.
Right, right?
"Mad Dog"?
Right, right.
Did he often clash with his neighbors?
And a lot of people
held grudges against him?
Right, right.
Including you two?
Nuh-uh.
Nuh-uh?
You mean no.
Right, right.
Right, right. Of course not.
I'm sorry, but may I use your restroom?
It's being repaired. Right?
You'll have to use the one
at the cell phone store nearby. Right?
I can't hold it much longer.
Where did you say the restroom was?
Just go out and turn at the toast shop.
You'll see the phone store there.
Sorry, I have to run.
She really needed to go.
Right, right?
-Here you go, sir.
-Thanks.
He was involved in many incidents.
Like what?
He was reported every other day.
I need a copy of this,
so grab me a pen and paper.
Sorry?
It'll take forever to copy this by hand.
Why not just take a picture?
Officer Jang, was it?
Are you one to give advice?
I obviously don't carry a camera around.
You could use your phone--
I don't have it on me.
Oh, that's my alarm.
I carry around my alarm clock.
Should I take a picture
and send it to you?
-I have my reasons for what I do.
-Of course.
Yunpyeong Precinct Report Log
Here you go, sir.
-Grab me a pen in a different color.
-Yes, sir.
NEULBIT FUNERAL HALL
Beomjoon.
Was there anyone
who was on bad terms with your father?
Not that I know of.
I figured.
But does anyone come to mind?
Did he ever argue with anyone?
People he argued with?
There's Mr. Jang next door,
and then there's the supermarket lady,
the chicken joint guy,
the produce vendor, and the wallpaper guy.
Oh, and Pastor Yoon too.
-Even a pastor?
-Yes.
They even grabbed each other
by the collar.
But they made up soon after.
In a word,
he was our neighborhood's…
public enemy.
Public enemy?
He clashed with every single person
in the neighborhood.
When my house was being renovated,
he threatened to sue me
over the dust and noise.
But you managed to put up with him.
Was there anyone
who was on especially bad terms with him?
The one who was
on the worst terms with him?
I think he was equally on bad terms…
with everyone.
He may have been a bit of a hothead,
but his socks were excellent.
I know. I only wore his socks.
Me too.
His socks were so nice and sturdy.
They were the best.
They came in various colors too.
What a shame.
This is bad.
I've run out of chocolate.
Victim Yoon Haesik
There are way too many people
who held a grudge against him.
He was more of a brawler
than a socks seller.
"Enigma chocolate"
Still, his socks were amazing.
We have way too many suspects.
Start by checking their alibis.
Huh? All of them?
Sorry?
Yes, what else can we do?
"What else can we do?"
You must be kidding me!
That's going to take forever!
I'll work twice as hard.
Don't be absurd!
You'll only cause twice as much trouble.
-This time, I'll--
-Be quiet! Argh!
-Hey, hey!
-I'm sorry.
-Come on.
-You should've been more careful.
Purchase
-Hey! What do we do?
-I'm sorry.
Hey, watch out.
You'll get shocked.
You're still here.
Oh, Captain.
I'm off.
Something's bothering me.
But don't worry about it.
Captain.
I don't think
I'm cut out to be a detective.
I'm doing my best though.
"Chief Jung Jingyu"
I worked my butt off
to transfer from the traffic division
to the Violent Crimes Team.
Yes?
I dreamed of becoming a police officer
working in the field
and busting criminals.
Is that right?
This time,
I'm determined to catch the culprit
with my own hands.
Oh.
But I keep making mistakes
and causing others trouble.
I'm not sure
if I should even remain in the force.
Do you have any advice for me, sir?
-I have to go.
-You…
-Sorry?
-What?
Oh.
I see.
What do you think we are?
We're…
the Violent Crimes Team.
I really think of us as a team.
Not everyone has to be a cleanup hitter.
That's not what makes a team strong.
You have a good nose.
-For cases?
-For instant noodles.
Instant noodles?
I'm sure there's a role for you
on our team.
Thank you, sir.
I ordered the classic flavor,
but I received the mint flavor.
No, I only eat the classic flavor.
You might not understand,
but this is an important matter to me.
I can't function without…
Sure. My username is Chocoholic.
Secondhand Marketplace
Swiss chocolate Enigma for sale
I'd like to buy all of them.
Sorry, I'm out of stock.
Songwon Police Station
has moved to a temporary location
Manchester United
is winning four to zero.
Good morning, detectives!
You're full of energy this morning.
I'm scared.
We're in for trouble. My goodness.
At least he's not feeling down anymore.
Yeah, I'm glad you're feeling better.
-Thank you, sir!
-Sit down.
Good morning, sir.
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning, sir!
Good morning, everyone.
Do we know
what Mr. Yoon was up to earlier that day?
We're struggling to track
his last location via CCTV footage.
By the way,
did you not sleep well last night?
I'm fine.
Did you try tracking his phone?
His phone is so old
that the GPS doesn't work.
His phone was turned off
before the incident,
so we can't really track it.
Check out this guy, Seo Mincheol.
He runs a hardware store.
He often clashed
with the victim over parking,
and he has multiple assault charges
on his record.
I have a feeling he's the culprit.
When did they clash?
About three months ago, I think.
So three months
after clashing over parking,
this guy suddenly murders the victim?
Sometimes,
people bottle things up,
and then they just snap.
Does that never happen to you?
Losing your temper
over something in the past?
No, that's never happened to me, ever.
Uh…
-Detective Moo.
-Yes?
Detectives Jung and Jang.
I told you ages ago
to renew your firearm permits,
and I just got a notification
that you still haven't.
Do I really have to stay
on top of every little thing?
It slipped my mind.
I'll take care of it right away.
All right.
He's acting weird today.
Is he dozing off?
Whoa! He's up, he's up.
Tansik, sit down.
Safe Songwon, Trustworthy Police
Oh my. Hey!
Who are you talking to? Me?
Just a second.
You haven't changed a bit.
You're as attractive as ever.
I knew I smelled testosterone in the air.
-How have you been?
-Who are you?
I only smell his sweat.
-Don't tell me…
-Do you know her?
She once got caught
cashing in forged gift vouchers.
What's she in for this time?
She smuggled knockoffs
and sold them on social media.
Knockoffs? I didn't realize
people still sold those.
Detective, they're hotter than ever.
Then again…
…you're clearly not into fashion.
Huh? What?
-Anyway, that's clever of you.
-What do you mean?
You're sticking with him
to make yourself look good.
You sly little fox.
You're being ridiculous.
-You sly fox.
-I look 1,000 times better than him!
My wife picked out these clothes for me.
-Huh? Whoa! Is that a Patel Flip?
-What?
I mean his watch.
It is, right?
I didn't expect to see one here.
Patel what? Is this expensive?
Totally. It costs more than 50.
50 won? Hey, is this a toy?
I mean 50 million won,
not 50 won.
-50 million won?
-Yeah!
It costs 50 million won.
Jeez.
-Wow…
-I can't believe this guy.
So this was a knockoff?
-No, it's…
-Have you no shame?
You're wearing a knockoff watch?
-Good grief.
-A knockoff?
-Go in.
-Bye!
Tansik.
How embarrassing.
You should know better than that. Tsk.
But this…
It's important to be humbled sometimes.
You're a detective,
for crying out loud. Tsk.
It was a gift.
Hey, your watch is blinding me.
I won't wear it again, sir.
I just grabbed a random watch.
So that's not the only knockoff you have?
I'm just curious.
Why did you buy a knockoff?
It was a gift.
Who had the nerve to give you
such an obvious knockoff as a gift?
I'm sure their whole life is fake!
My grandma gave it to me.
She has good taste.
You think so?
Yeah, that watch is really stylish
for a knockoff.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't worry.
-Detective Jung.
-Yeah?
Beomjoon says
Mr. Yoon wasn't a bad person.
Beomjoon is his son.
Even Lee Wanyong,
who sold out our country,
was a loving dad to his son.
When it comes to people,
there's always more than meets the eye.
Bestsellers!
Made-in-Korea Socks, Wholesale and Retail
Hi there.
Hello?
Ah.
Hey, who are you?
You're so cute.
Are you cold?
Is this yours?
This will keep you warm.
Nice and warm, right?
So warm.
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
Bang!
Who are you?
Why did you put my scarf on the dog?
Who the hell are you? A dog seller?
No, I'm not.
Mr. Yoon was kind of short-fused,
but he was incredibly hard-working.
I feel so sorry for him.
Do you know where he usually did business?
Socks sellers don't stay in one place
as produce vendors do.
They travel from place to place.
I see.
Look at you.
My scarf looks better on you than on me.
You can keep it.
I'm sorry.
Shit Well Daycare Center
Songwon Police Station
has moved to a temporary location
None of the neighbors
seem suspicious. Don't you think?
Captain.
We may have gotten the wrong idea.
Many people described Mr. Yoon
as a bad person,
but from his point of view,
the situation was different.
He had his reasons.
He had his reasons?
It all depends on perspective.
Look.
The lady from the supermarket
referred to Mr. Yoon as "Mad Dog."
But it turns out…
she built an illegal structure
in her backyard for storage
and clashed with Mr. Yoon over it.
The assault case is the same.
The victim had been scamming
elderly neighbors.
"Mr. Yoon persistently harassed
a civil servant."
In reality, he was simply asking them
to fix a pothole.
It had been neglected since last summer.
What's your point?
Mr. Yoon wasn't harassing people.
-His sense of justice--
-Detective Jang.
What we're looking for
is cause and effect,
not good versus evil.
-Sorry?
-Whether you personally think
Yoon Haesik was a good or bad person
has nothing to do with the case.
I suppose you're right, sir.
Has anyone found out more
about what Mr. Yoon was up to that day?
I'm finding out
where he usually did his business
and securing dashcam footage
from the buses in those areas.
All right.
Let's keep searching.
You did well.
You know how Captain can be.
Beomjoon
My dad sent me this picture
on the day of the incident.
Just in case it helps.
Detective Seo,
take a look at this.
Beomjoon sent me a picture of Mr. Yoon
taken on the day of the incident.
It's just a selfie.
All you see is his face.
Did he say anything else?
He just sent me this picture.
-Mr. Yoon!
-Hey, Officer Jang!
Did you eat?
Yes.
Seems like you had fermented soybean stew.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Did you get in trouble again?
No, that's not it.
I brought something for you. Here.
They're new designs.
Considering how well-built you are,
I thought they'd look great on you.
Thank you.
I hope you like them.
And you should eat well.
-I will.
-I'll get going.
Thank you.
Mr. Yoon…
Thank you, sir!
Captain, I think I found
where Mr. Yoon did business that day.
I started by investigating the areas
where he usually conducted business.
Pay attention to the trash bag behind him.
It's from Gangnam-gu.
Considering the color scheme of the sign,
this appears to be All Day Mart.
Once I brightened the image,
I noticed an apartment building
marked "Building 304."
In this vicinity, there are
a total of eight apartment complexes
with a Building 304.
Judging by the typeface, this appears
to be Cheongdam LH Apartment Complex 3.
You can see the sun setting
to the left of the building,
indicating it faces south.
The convenience store
is on the left side of the building.
I identified
three convenience stores in that area.
Street View confirmed
that the picture was taken…
in front of the second branch
of All Day Mart on Cheongdam Intersection.
How… did you do all that?
I analyzed a lot of CCTV footage
in the traffic division.
Mm. Great job, Detective Jang.
You did well.
Now that the location has been identified,
let's start from there.
Secure the CCTV footage.
Yes, sir.
-Hey.
-Well done. You nailed it.
No.
Here's the CCTV footage.
That really is Mr. Yoon.
There was a fight
right before the incident?
That can't be a coincidence.
Of course not.
That guy's the culprit.
There you go again.
Don't jump to conclusions.
We can't really see the guy's face.
-Can you go back three seconds?
-Sorry?
Go back three seconds.
His face is completely hidden.
It's difficult to see.
Difficult to see? There's nothing to see.
Ask the National Forensic Service
-to enhance the video quality.
-Yes, sir.
What can they possibly do
with this useless footage?
What about the banner?
I put one up in front of the store
where everyone can see it.
All right.
Witnesses Needed
Looking for witnesses who saw
an altercation with a sock seller
10 p.m. on December 21, 2023
I wasn't sure when I saw the news,
but then I realized it was the same date.
It was my friend's birthday that day.
Happy birthday!
Thanks, guys!
-This guy kept hitting on me.
-Come with me.
I'm with my friends!
I was about to take a taxi,
but he followed me out
and insisted on giving me a ride.
That's when a man selling things
from a truck stepped in.
In the end,
they got into a fight.
Did you call the police?
I thought it was just a minor scuffle.
You might have to come back
a few more times.
I'm prepared for that.
Detective.
Oh, do you remember something?
It's not related to the case.
It's about the tall detective
from earlier.
A tall detective? That would be me.
No? Then do you mean Detective Jang?
What about him?
He seems to be
the grandson of Ms. Hong Tanbong.
Hong Tanbong?
She's the founder of Tan Restaurant.
Are you talking about the Tan Restaurant?
Yes, the detective looks
just like her grandson.
I think you're mistaken.
I don't think
he has anything to do with Tan Restaurant.
By any chance,
does his name have "Tan" in it?
Actually, it does.
Ms. Hong only passes down
the character Tan to those she favors.
Rumor has it that whoever has it
in their name is her successor.
There's no way.
He can't be the only one
with Tan in his name, can he?
But it's not that common either.
-I'll get going.
-Bye.
Hong Tanbong?
Tan Restaurant… Tan Restaurant…
Tan…
Tan Restaurant?
Has Restaurant Mogul Hong Tanbong
Chosen A Successor?
Tan Restaurant
Sold for 300 billion won
300 billion won?
Does she have a successor?
Her grandson's
keen sense of smell and taste…
Sense of smell and taste
He does have a big nose.
Let me see.
You smell like
Ms. Lee Bokja's hangover soup.
Who had the nerve to give you
such an obvious knockoff as a gift?
My grandma gave it to me.
Ms. Hong only passes down
the character Tan to those she favors.
Rumor has it that whoever has it
in their name is her successor.
Grandmother.
A successor?
Tan Restaurant, founded in 1963
In 1963,
Tan Restaurant was founded by
Ms. Hong Tanbong with a passion for food.
"Founder Hong Tanbong"
Her warm dishes filled our hearts,
and Tan Restaurant
became deeply rooted in our lives.
"Reached 100 franchise locations"
Through continuous change and improvement,
they enriched our lives with food.
"The Tan Food, Tan Bar, Tanwoo,
Chinese Restaurant Tanrim"
Expanding beyond Korea to the world.
In 2023,
they opened their 1,001st location
in Marseille, France,
establishing themselves
as a global franchise.
The Tan Food,
a legend in the restaurant industry.
Tan, Tan.
Hello,
this is the Songwon Police…
Okay. Thank you.
The National Forensic Service
sent us the enhanced footage.
With the enhanced video quality…
we see the back of his head so clearly.
Maybe we should visit the club.
Tan, Tan.
Excellent. That's a great idea.
-What's with you?
-What are you saying?
Huh?
I just think it's a great idea.
Hold on, pause it.
I think I know who he is.
It's him… Nam Junghyun.
The hospital director's son
from the One Shot Chicken case?
Exactly.
How do you know it's him
when you can't even see his face?
Look at the number, not the face.
The plate number behind him.
With the enhanced video quality,
you can see it clearly.
4987.
It's Nam Junghyun's car.
This must be it.
-Let's go in.
-Okay.
Come on.
We just need to check something.
This is obstruction of justice. Got that?
As I said, you need to bring a warrant.
This is urgent.
Just let us check the CCTV.
No need to be so uptight…
with us, do you?
I'm sorry, but we have to follow protocol.
Protocol?
Get out of the way.
Now.
I'll count to three.
One.
Two.
Are you serious?
Fight!
Three for you, three for you.
What are you on about?
Gosh, I'm getting hot!
Four for you.
Just leave, okay?
Okay, fine!
Four for you,
and five for you.
Let's do this, huh?
What's the commotion?
Hmm?
Who are you?
Are we really going to push our way in?
What are we, bulldozers?
We'll need to get a warrant.
The warrant was rejected.
What? Why?
A risk of invasion of privacy,
insufficient relevance to the case,
or something like that.
Tell them we reject their rejection!
Hey! Where are you going
without a warrant?
Where are you going?
How are we supposed to do our job?
But seriously, is this really necessary?
Why won't they let us check
the CCTVs in the club?
I might be overstepping here, but…
Tan, Tan.
No way. Overstepping? Don't be ridiculous.
We're all equals. Go ahead.
I still think it's best
if we check the CCTVs in the club.
Who doesn't know that?
But there's no way to do that.
-How about we go undercover?
-That's easier said than done.
How exactly?
Minseo, hear our rookie out.
How are you planning to sneak in there?
I have a friend who might be able to help.
Let's get dressed up
and meet in front of the club later.
I'll find a way to get us in.
Ayo, Tansik!
-What the heck?
-What a dork.
Why is he dressed like that?
Tansik!
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Knock, knock.
It's me.
I totally went all out.
I bet you'll get bounced.
You look stunning.
So do you.
Really? Thanks.
Let's go in.
She's with me.
Welcome. Welcome.
-Thank you.
-You can't enter.
-I'm with them.
-Sure.
Please leave.
-I'll buy two bottles of liquor.
-Sure.
What if I take these off?
No.
-What about the beanie?
-No.
Are you here alone? Wanna join us?
Unless you want to get your joints broken
and crawl on all fours, get lost.
Okay! I prefer walking.
We love walking.
Detective Seo!
You got it?
-There it is.
-Go ahead.
What did they lose now?
Someone's coming.
What should we do?
-Take that out. Go hide.
-Where?
I don't know. Just hide.
Do we need to respond to every request?
Why are there so many entitled jerks?
It's always been like that.
Why would you hide right there?
Where did they put their bag?
Whatever. Just tell them
we couldn't find it.
How can you be so irresponsible?
Wait for me!
Have they left?
Hey!
Why would you hide there?
That was close.
Try it again.
What is it now?
Hurry up!
-Where do I hide?
-Quick. Hide!
Whatever!
I'm exhausted.
We can't survive on our salaries alone.
We need tips.
-Do we need just one?
-All of them.
You've got to be kidding me.
Jeez.
Stop whining.
You weren't like this before.
Hurry up.
I'm coming!
Wait for me!
That was really close.
Well done.
Seoul Busters
Translated by Minjin Kim