[♪ theme music playing]
Seoul Busters
We need to talk
to Mr. Jang's ex-secretary.
She quit six months ago.
What? The perp got busted?
Who busted who?
Episode 3
Wish-It-Well Daycare Center
[Minsik] I didn't mean to lie.
I just wanted to avoid trouble.
I'm looking for a job too.
I mean it, Detective.
Do you know what makes someone fake?
Sorry?
It's when they pretend to be
something they're not.
Don't leave anything out.
Write down everything you did
and didn't do at Lim Dongil's place,
including when you arrived and left.
[sighs] I didn't do much at all.
The more you leave out,
the more suspicion you'll raise.
So, imagine you're taking the SAT
and your life depends on it.
Think carefully and write everything down.
If you can't remember something,
do you see that over there?
[Joongryeok]
Sitting in that chair will help you.
It's a thinking chair. Got that?
-[door opens, closes]
-[sighs] That's just bullying.
[gasps, groans] Jeez, that hurts.
[thinking chair] Wait! Think for a second.
[sighs]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[thinking chair] Think and think.
Think and think. Think and think.
He doesn't seem like someone
who could kill a person.
[Joongryeok] Exactly.
That's what makes him
even more suspicious.
He borrowed an apartment
and a car from Lim Dongil.
Who would benefit the most
from Lim Dongil being gone?
It's him.
Why would he lie about what he did
if he was innocent?
How much did he borrow from Lim Dongil?
That's not important.
-Around a million won, sir.
-A million won?
That's not a small amount, is it?
A tenth of it was in gift vouchers.
Gift vouchers are just like money.
[Yubin] Detective Moo.
Shouldn't you have informed me first?
I was going to,
but I thought I should bust him first.
You should've notified me first.
If this happens again,
I'll take official disciplinary action.
[♪ tense music playing]
[Yubin] You got the wrong guy.
[sighs] Captain.
Have you contacted Mr. Jang's secretary?
Oh, I've been trying to reach her,
but no luck.
Regarding Jeon Minsik,
file a warrant request
only for his existing charges.
What do you think you're doing?
He's our prime suspect.
We need a thorough investigation.
If you want to investigate him,
bring the evidence.
Guys,
he just deliberately undermined me,
didn't he?
To be fair, he has a point.
You probably got the wrong guy.
[sighs]
Whatever.
Anyway, how am I supposed
to bring that woman in?
I can't even reach her.
[Joongryeok] A woman?
Who?
[Minseo] I heard you're not eating.
Minjae wasn't just one of my actors.
He was like a little brother to me.
Actually, he called me
the day before he killed himself.
What did he say?
He said he was struggling
after the incident.
[Taesik] He was childish, short-tempered,
and would do whatever he wanted.
But he was actually soft-hearted.
So?
[Taesik groans]
I should've met him that day.
He wanted to grab a drink,
but I couldn't
because I was on herbal medication.
I told him we should catch up
once I was done with them.
If it's any comfort,
I recently saw a movie called
Pieces of Friendship.
There's this line in it.
"Time may not heal all wounds,
but it does fade all memories."
I saw that movie at a special screening.
The final beach scene was incredible,
wasn't it?
[muttering] Yes, I guess.
Ugh, that bastard.
How could he leave like that? [sniffles]
If only I wasn't on these meds…
I heard the two of them go way back.
Mr. Jang seemed really shaken up.
I'm not sure.
Didn't you just see him?
He was crying and everything.
He seemed heartbroken.
It didn't seem that way to me.
Are you suggesting he was acting?
He's supposed to be refusing all food,
but his cuff was stained with soy sauce.
I told him we should catch up
once I was done with them.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
Unless he's moonlighting at a restaurant,
he must've had sushi for lunch.
[Yubin] Soy sauce can drip down
when you eat sushi with your hands.
"Soy sauce stain"
Also, his breath smelled minty.
[Yubin] I figure he must've snagged
a mint at the restaurant.
A mint?
He doesn't strike me
as the type to buy them.
But he's got a solid alibi.
A ton of people saw him
at the VIP screening.
I think you're jumping to conclusions.
I'd call it deduction.
[elevator chimes]
Look closely around you,
and you might uncover unexpected details.
What are you, Sherlock Holmes?
[Minseo clapping]
-[Yubin] Not this one.
-What's wrong?
It's going up.
[sighs]
Why don't you look
more closely around you?
You seem to be missing
what's right before your eyes.
[soft chuckle]
Songwon Police Station
has moved to a temporary location
Detective Jang, see me in my office.
[Tansik] Me, sir?
[Yubin]
How's it going with Mr. Jang's secretary?
Oh, she won't budge an inch.
[Junghwan] She's refusing to cooperate.
[Joongryeok] She'll show up.
She will? Why all of a sudden?
Why else? I asked her to.
Come on, as if she'd just listen to you.
Look, you can't just boss a woman around.
Forget it. You wouldn't get it.
[heels thudding]
[♪ sensual jazz music playing]
Speak of the devil.
I'm here to see Detective Moo Joongryeok.
That'd be me.
[♪ sensual jazz music continues]
Seoul Busters
[Yubin]
So you were Mr. Jang's secretary at JMT?
[secretary] I worked with him
since he started the company.
But eventually,
I got tired of him and quit.
Did Kang Minjae have
any enemies within the company?
Most of them were.
[secretary] The thing about him is…
[clicks tongue] …he can be a real pain.
[Yubin]
How did he get along with Mr. Jang?
Mr. Jang had to put up with him.
His whole company relied on Kang Minjae.
I heard they were like brothers.
[scoffs] "Brothers"?
[secretary] Well, they go way back.
They even lived together for a bit.
[♪ sensual jazz music playing]
[clears throat]
By the way, this is top secret…
but my friend at TMT told me…
that Kang Minjae was planning
to ditch his contract with JMT
and join them.
If that's true,
Mr. Jang must've been in deep water.
After that Octopus Game or Hagfish Game
or whatever it is blew up,
Kang Minjae became a big deal.
Mr. Jang scored some big bucks
from China riding on his success.
Being in deep water
would be an understatement.
For all I know,
he was probably on the verge of drowning.
[exhales deeply]
[clears throat]
Anyway, since I showed up and talked,
hold up your end of the deal
and have a meal with me, Detective Moo.
[♪ sensual Latin music playing]
I already ate.
But I want to eat now.
[exhales heavily]
You do?
Uh, Detectives Jung and Moo,
I need you to head over to TMT.
I'm busy today.
-Detective Seo, can you--
-I'm busy.
Detective Seo, I'm taking you somewhere.
-Where?
-Let's go see a movie.
Me?
A movie? Together?
With Detective Seo, not you.
Why… I mean, what movie?
300 Days of Confessions.
-300 Days of…
-Confessions?
You're fine with that, right?
I'll wait in the car.
-Has he lost his mind?
-Does he think I'm that easy?
[♪ comical music playing]
[sighs]
Hey, I bet our captain
will get in huge trouble soon.
What do you mean?
Has he completely lost it?
Going to the movies?
With his subordinate, while on duty?
I looked up the movie, and it's a rom-com.
It's totally a date.
This precinct has gone to the dogs.
Isn't it a good thing
if they get together?
Detective Seo can be a bit of a slob
and has a short fuse,
but she's a good person.
She's too good for him.
-She is a bit of a slob though.
-[groans]
[staff] Here's your popcorn.
Thank you.
Let's go in. It's Theater 4.
Let me see. It's that way.
[Minseo] Wait.
What the…
Are we really watching a movie together?
[sniffling effect]
[father in commercial] The Riverside Star
Forest Central Éclatni Palace!
An exceptional choice
for a prestigious person like you!
[son in commercial] Dad! I love our place!
-Detective Seo.
-Yes?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Yes, sort of.
You're denser than I thought.
I gave you plenty of hints.
[♪ soft music playing]
I usually don't have time
to go to the movies with a colleague.
[groans] Gosh.
Captain. [sighs]
I'm sorry, but--
You know what, Detective Seo?
In English, you "ask someone out,"
not "confess your feelings,"
because they don't hide their feelings.
I don't want to hide my feelings
from you either.
Actually…
[distressed groan]
[shaky, anxious breathing]
[exhales sharply]
I'm sorry, Captain, but--
-Detective Seo.
-Yes?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Please don't do this.
Detective Seo.
[♪ soft music continues]
-I have to go to the restroom.
-[♪ music fades]
Wait.
-What the…
-Gosh, why now?
[♪ comical music playing]
What's the deal with him?
[sighs]
What the heck?
[indistinct chatter in movie]
[gasps]
[grunts]
I'm sorry.
Is he making his poop
from scratch in there?
[scoffs]
Why did he even bring me here then?
He should've invited me
to the restroom instead.
Jeez.
[TMT manager] It's true
that we considered scouting Kang Minjae.
But he was the one
who approached us first.
He did? [echoing]
What the… How do I turn this off?
-Help me.
-Push that button.
It's off. Go on.
He wanted to leave JMT.
He thought he'd find
more opportunities abroad,
with streaming platforms and stuff.
So you were actually interested
in scouting him.
We were in talks. That's about it.
But it wasn't like
he could start working overseas right away
because of the language barrier.
[♪ comical music playing]
Right, Kang Minjae uses a burier.
Absolutely. He very much uses a burier.
I mean a language barrier.
Minjae couldn't speak English,
just like you two.
Still, he was a charming actor,
and I thought he was full of potential
before the incident.
Would he have been able
to ditch his existing contract?
[inhales sharply]
I'm not sure if I should tell you this.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
Wish-It-Well Daycare Center
Kang Minjae would've faced a hefty penalty
if he breached his contract with JMT.
To avoid this,
he was digging up dirt on Mr. Jang.
He hoped to find evidence
of embezzlement or dual contracts
so he could leave the company.
The so-called brothers
were digging up dirt on each other.
[clicks tongue] So two-faced.
[sighs]
No, that's wrong.
It's four-faced.
There are two two-faced people,
so four faces in total.
[♪ comical music playing]
-I can't believe him.
-[chuckles]
[laughing awkwardly]
Two two-faced people,
so four faces in total.
That's hilarious.
I mean, it's simple math.
[laughing]
-What is it now?
-You're so desperate.
[laughing continues]
I'm back, Captain.
[Junghwan] Four-faced.
[Yubin] Detective Jang, my office.
[laughing] He just sat down though.
[Minseo] What's with him?
That's enough.
[whispers] Hey, come here.
The captain is talking to Tansik again.
He seems to like working with him.
[Junghwan] How was the movie?
[Minseo clears throat] Whatever.
What do you mean?
Wasn't it awkward?
[Minseo] I said it was whatever.
I watched the movie alone.
What about the captain?
He was in the restroom the whole time.
Maybe I should recommend
some laxatives to him.
[whispers] I've never seen someone
so backed up. It's unbelievable.
He's backed up?
It took him two and a half hours.
It seems like a lot of us are backed up.
I found the taxi driver and the actor
as you requested.
-Nice job.
-Thank you.
-[Yubin] You're dismissed.
-Yes, sir.
[phone buzzing]
Hello, Dongbang speaking.
National Forensic Service
Diploma
Hanguk University
Oh!
Hmm.
DNA, Toxicology, Chemistry
Autopsy, Forensic Medicine,
Medical Examination
Researcher Jung Eunkyung
Are they the same person?
[Yubin] Jung Eunkyung,
Jung Eunkyung, Jung Eunkyung…
Is she the only one working here?
Are you the new captain?
Jung Eunkyung: Autopsy, Forensic Medicine,
Medical Examination, DNA, Toxicology,
Chemistry, Safety, Digital Analysis,
and Traffic Divisions
-Yes, I'm Dongbang Yubin.
-[soft chuckle]
-[Eunkyung] Have a seat.
-Okay.
[Eunkyung] Uh…
This was found inside Kang Minjae's body.
He must've swallowed it
right before he died.
It was stuck halfway down his throat.
It looks like it was a piece of paper.
A piece of paper?
[Eunkyung] It could be a person's name.
What could "29" and "02" mean?
Could it be a phone number?
[soft chuckle] Oh…
So that's what happened.
Sorry?
Thank you. This was very helpful.
Ah.
I'll come back for the evidence.
Actually, please send over the evidence
to the daycare center we're at.
All right.
[♪ dramatic music sting]
-[♪ comical music playing]
-[Eunkyung sighs]
And here I thought there was finally
someone normal on the Violent Crimes Team.
[♪ light music playing]
[van door closes]
Did you seriously come here
on your scooter?
The old clunker gave out.
[awkward chuckle]
So I'm picking you up on this baby.
I can't ride this!
[Minjae] I'll freeze to death!
[chuckles] I almost did.
Hop on. It's okay.
-This baby's faster than a car.
-[sighs]
Did you eat?
[Minjae] What do you think?
[Taesik]
Then I'll make you some instant noodles.
You know I make amazing noodles,
don't you?
Instant noodles again?
What about eggs?
[loudly] I've already bought some for you.
I know you never eat
instant noodles without eggs.
-[Taesik] Hold on tight.
-Let's go.
[Minjae] I said let's go… [screams]
When we make it big,
the first thing we'll do is buy a van.
Doesn't that sound amazing?
We'll buy a house…
-and a car too!
-And a car too!
[shouting]
-[Minjae] Won't that be amazing?
-[Taesik] It'll be amazing!
[engine starts]
[engine revving]
[startled shout]
[tires screeching]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Yubin's car door opens, closes]
Oh, Detective.
That was close. You scared me.
Sorry about that. Are you going somewhere?
I'm getting some fresh air.
[Taesik] What brings you here, anyway?
-[Yubin] I have some business with you.
-Business?
[Taesik sighs]
Can it wait?
It can't.
-I'm here to arrest you.
-I know.
[♪ tense music continues]
Pardon?
Jang Taesik, you're under arrest
for the murders
of Lim Dongil and Kang Minjae.
[sighs]
On what grounds?
I'll explain the details on the way.
You have the right to remain silent--
[♪ thrilling music playing]
Okay.
[annoyed groan]
[shouts] Out of the way!
[grunting]
[elder] What are you doing?
[♪ dramatic music sting]
["What?" effect]
[groans]
I'm sorry.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
[Taesik whimpers]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ dramatic music sting]
[♪ light suspenseful music playing]
[Taesik whines]
[panting]
[grunting]
[groans]
[panting]
[hiker 1] What a convenient entrance.
[hiker 2] It's a nice trail.
[hiker 3] My goodness.
[sighs] Damn it.
[♪ light suspenseful music continues]
You've got this.
[hiker 4] Go for it!
-[hiker 5] Keep going!
-[hiker 6] You can do it!
[hiker 7] There.
[Taesik panting]
[groans]
Whoa!
[grunts]
[panting]
My landing was weak.
[Yubin] There you are.
[Taesik] How did you come from that way?
Oh.
I ran up there, went over there,
and was going to go around there,
but then just came straight across.
Wait. Let's not climb any higher.
We'll have to get back down anyway.
-Okay.
-[pants]
Come to think of it,
I don't understand why I ran away.
Why are you suspecting me?
I thought you had no reason to kill,
but you did.
What?
You found out
Kang Minjae was bullying Lim Dongil…
and that's where it all began.
[secretary] After that Octopus Game
or Hagfish Game
or whatever it is blew up,
Kang Minjae became a big deal.
He wanted to leave JMT.
[TMT manager] It's true
that we considered scouting Kang Minjae.
But he was the one
who approached us first.
You started this.
[Minjae] Seriously?
[Yubin] If you were to kill Lim Dongil
and tell the press that it was suicide,
Kang Minjae would be accused of bullying
and hit rock bottom.
[Minjae on phone] Are you crazy?
You're telling me to eat this crap now?
[shouts] How the hell did this get out?
You probably figured that no agency
would want Kang Minjae then.
That was the only way for you to keep him.
[Yubin] As for the puffer fish poison,
the idea must've come from the series
-one of your actors was in.
-[prosecutor on TV] He said,
"I put a ton of puffer fish blood,
so she'll drop dead soon."
The defendant murdered his wife
with puffer fish poison.
And he disguised it as a suicide!
How does that make any sense?
I was the last person
who wanted Minjae to go down.
[Yubin] You would've been hit hard
at first, for sure.
But things would've blown over with time.
You're being delusional.
I've got a rock-solid alibi.
I attended the VIP screening
at the movie theater.
It's true you went there,
but you didn't watch the movie.
The final beach scene was incredible,
wasn't it?
[muttering] Yes, I guess.
[Yubin] I haven't watched that movie.
Nor have you.
VIP Screening
Pieces of Friendship
[♪ light suspenseful music playing]
Excuse me.
[Yubin] You left the theater
as soon as the movie began.
Start
[timer beeping]
[knocking on door]
[Yubin] You hurried somewhere
while your double watched the movie.
-Take me to this address, please.
-[driver] Okay.
15 minutes passed
-[doorbell rings]
-Who is it?
[Yubin] You barged into Dongil's place
by making up some excuses.
After all,
not many people can turn away their boss.
45 minutes passed
[♪ music fades]
[♪ ominous music playing]
And you poisoned Dongil as planned.
[grunts]
[grunting]
1 hour and 59 minutes passed
2 hours passed
[timer beeping]
[Yubin] You wanted to make it
look like a perfect suicide,
but you ran out of time.
[lighter clicking]
-I timed it myself.
-[door opens]
[pants]
Two and a half hours.
You must've barely made it back in time.
2 hours and 25 minutes passed
I've secured the dashcam footage
from the taxi you were in
as well as the driver's testimony.
I even got hold of the stand-in
who watched the movie instead of you.
Cut the bullshit.
That one was easy to solve, ah…
but not the Kang Minjae case.
Kang Minjae would've faced a hefty penalty
if he breached his contract with JMT.
[Junghwan] To avoid this,
he was digging up dirt on Mr. Jang.
[Yujin] Kang Minjae
would've snuck into your office
to find dirt on you
in order to nullify his contract.
This bastard's been pocketing bribes
left and right.
[air purifier beeping]
[whirring]
Jeez, that scared me.
[Minjae groans] What the hell?
[Yubin] That's when he stumbled upon
some evidence related to the murder.
And he found out
you were involved in Lim Dongil's death.
Yujeong Lake Apartments, Unit 302
8 Daerim-ro 29ga-gil, Songwon-gu, Seoul
Calm down. What are you talking about?
Why would I do that? Am I crazy?
Also, I haven't taken any bribes!
Forget it.
I'll come over right now, so hang tight.
If I did go to Kang Minjae's place,
how come I wasn't caught on CCTVs?
Do you know
how many cameras are around there?
Delivery.
[♪ resolute music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[Taesik] Delivery.
No one recognized you
because you were wearing a helmet,
especially since it was raining that day.
[♪ music fades]
What's with the getup?
I was feeling nostalgic.
So I hopped on my motorbike,
but it started raining.
[thunder rumbling]
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[sighs]
[Minjae] Have you lost your mind?
How could you
even think of killing Dongil?
What the hell are you talking about?
What's with you these days?
[scoffs] Shut up.
I can't believe
I considered you a brother.
Look, this is Dongil's home address.
I found it in your office
on the day of the incident.
Why would you hold on
to a roadie's home address?
Did you think
I wouldn't figure out your tricks?
Were you trying to get me canceled?
You're the one who told the press, right?
-[Taesik] Give me that.
-[scoffs]
Why should I? This is evidence.
[in angry voice] Give me that right now!
I should never have gotten involved
with scum like you.
Hey, watch what you say.
Do you have any idea
what I went through to make you a star?
I hustled until my feet were sore
and bent over backward,
sucking up to people
until my back gave out!
I bet my life on you, and what?
[breathing shakily]
Now that you've made it,
you want to ditch my company?
[shouts] Who do you think
got you to where you are now?
You're just a parasite.
[thunder rumbling]
Listen.
Apart from all the money you pocketed…
by mooching off of me,
is there anything
you achieved on your own?
It's time for you…
to pay for what you've done,
you dirty scumbag.
Scum like you
should be completely isolated
from society.
-[Taesik grunts]
-[thunderclap]
[♪ dire music playing]
[breathing heavily]
-[groans]
-[rain pattering]
[Taesik breathing heavily]
[Taesik] You brought this upon yourself.
It's all your fault.
[sobbing]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[breathing shakily]
[Taesik sobbing]
[sobbing]
This was found inside Kang Minjae's body.
Do you recognize the handwriting?
I did right away.
Luckily, Mr. Kang didn't digest all of it.
Once we process it,
we'll find your DNA all over it.
I was going to run away to China anyway.
It wouldn't make any difference…
if I killed you too.
-[♪ tense music playing]
-Goodness, that's a knife.
[chuckles] Too bad. I'm a detective.
We're the only people allowed to carry…
Where's my gun?
Where did it go?
Hold on. [soft chuckle]
[Yubin] People are looking.
Let's talk this out.
You little…
[♪ dramatic violin music playing]
Are you okay, Captain?
Detective Moo?
Take a little break.
[wolf-whistling effect]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
You should've talked this out
while you could.
Do you know
what kind of people I hate the most?
Get out of the way,
or I'll kill you, goddammit!
[Joongryeok] Don't mind us, everyone.
Have fun.
-Thanks.
-All right.
Fine, you can swear and take out a knife
when you're cornered.
That's all understandable.
But I can't forgive punks
who run away to high places. Why?
I even gave up on my pension
to skip running.
What are you babbling about?
-Three.
-Three?
Three.
Three?
Three. [blows air]
[both grunting]
[chuckles]
Bring it on.
[exclaiming]
[Taesik grunting]
[chuckles]
-[♪ music stops]
-[Taesik grunting]
Are you shooting a movie?
-No, it's real.
-It's real.
[whoops]
You're so good.
Are you shooting a TV show?
-[Joongryeok] It's real.
-[Taesik] It's real.
[both grunting]
-What are they doing?
-They're good.
[hikers] Are they shooting a movie?
-Is this real?
-It's real.
[hiker exclaims, chuckles]
[both grunting]
[♪ thrilling music playing]
Come here.
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
[♪ music pauses]
-[in English] Goodbye. [whoops]
-[thwacks]
[♪ thrilling music continues]
[Joongryeok whoops]
[hiker in Korean] Nice job!
[chuckles]
Wow.
How did you find me?
Just a hunch. A good one.
[♪ music stops]
[Junghwan] We'll hand him over.
Hey, let me ask you one last time.
Do you really not remember anything
about that day?
I'm sorry.
[sighs heavily]
Oh.
-What is it?
-When I was leaving Dongil's place,
I saw a man getting out of a taxi.
[♪ eerie music sting]
[Minsik] He seemed somewhat out of place.
Can you make a sketch?
[buzzing effect]
Even Hana could make a better sketch
with her feet.
[groans] I got excited for nothing.
Wait, this looks familiar.
[♪ resolute music playing]
It's Mr. Jang.
It's definitely him.
[line ringing]
Seonhwa, this is Detective Moo.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
What kind of detective loses his gun?
What are you, Handel and Grengel?
"Handel and Grengel"?
Dongbang Yubin's Encyclopedia
George Frideric Handel
Renowned German Baroque composer
It's Hansel and Gretel.
Hänsel und Gretel: A German fairy tale
collected by the Brothers Grimm
Let's go.
[Joongryeok whoops]
[siren blaring]
[tires screech]
[Tansik] Are you okay, sir?
I heard the perp swung a knife at you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. [chuckles]
I feel hurt. Is no one worried about me?
I'd be more worried about the perp.
Of course, you were on the national team.
The national team?
Were you on the national team?
Stop it. That was a long time ago.
It's no big deal.
[Junghwan] Oh, you didn't know, Captain?
Detective Moo
was on the national boxing team.
-The KO King of Athens.
-[boxing bell dinging effect]
Was he KO'd a lot?
Is that really what you think?
Moo Joongryeok the KO King,
who won a gold medal in Athens
by winning every match by knockout,
was you?
[in English] Yeah, yeah, that's me!
-[Joongryeok] Come on!
-[in Korean] Oh, my goodness.
I'm the only Moo Joongryeok in the world.
I'm sorry. I'm not that into boxing.
The whole nation
was rooting for him back then.
I only watch soccer.
-[whistle blowing effect]
-[Joongryeok] Enough about boxing.
Who watches boxing these days anyway?
Everyone watches soccer
and roots for Son Heungmin and Lee Kangin.
By the way, I want to ask a question.
-Don't.
-Why is Mr. Jang the culprit?
[sighs] I'm tired. Start the car.
-Let's go.
-[Minseo] Okay.
[♪ triumphant music playing]
-[vehicles honking]
-[grunts]
[Joongryeok] Hey, rookie!
You can't doze off!
-[Tansik] I'm sorry, sir!
-[Joongryeok groans] For crying out loud!
[♪ triumphant music continues]
-Wash up first.
-I did.
-When?
-This morning.
[♪ tranquil music playing]
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[thumping]
Kim Seonhwa, JMT Secretary
[panting]
[thumping]
Daddy's home.
[children] Daddy!
-He brought fried chicken!
-Fried chicken!
-Chicken!
[Junghwan's wife] Long day?
I'm fine.
The kids…
-[child 1] I'll open it!
-[child 2] Give it to me!
-Daddy will open the sauce!
-[child 3] No, I'll do it!
[Junghwan's wife] No!
[grunts]
Healthy Poops
[Junghwan] Dear Captain Dongbang Yubin.
This should work wonders
when you're backed up.
It was hard to come by.
Wishing you good health. Salute.
From Jung Junghwan, your loyal ally.
Oh.
I didn't know I was backed up.
Movie Star's Tragic Death Reinvestigated
[Commissioner chuckling]
Look at him.
Working in the field seems to suit him
better than I thought.
Mmm.
Then again…
he should be burning with passion
at his age.
[spits]
[♪ comical music playing]
That's hot!
[groans]
[Commissioner] I spilled it everywhere.
[sighs]
The late Lim Dongil
[♪ gentle music playing]
[Minseo] The whole country
is talking about this case.
But how come it's so quiet here?
How ironic.
How did you know
Dongil liked coffee-flavored milk?
I went through his credit card statements,
and he spent
less than 10,000 won on food a day.
He lived on lunch boxes and noodles
from the convenience store.
But he would enjoy
a small carton of coffee milk every day.
Did you know coffee milk contains
more caffeine than coffee?
Actually, coffee milk
has about 20% more caffeine
than an Americano…
What's wrong?
I was just thinking that you really seem
to love explaining things.
Oh.
-[chuckles]
-Mm.
But seriously, will there be
a team dinner any time soon?
Ever since you joined, we've been too busy
with the case to have a team dinner.
Let's do it.
I'll treat you guys to some nice food.
-Tell me what you want to eat.
-I want beef.
You want what?
I don't need anything else.
All I need is beef.
-So you like beef.
-Yes.
-What do you say?
-Sure.
-Yeah.
-[both chuckle]
Captain.
What do you think of our team?
[inhales deeply]
Well…
You guys aren't exactly invincible.
I agree we're quite far from invincible.
I admit it.
Still…
there's something charming about you all.
Charming?
[Yubin] Yes.
[Minseo] That's interesting.
But we're the Violent Crimes…
Seoul Busters
[♪ closing theme music playing]
Translated by Minjin Kim