Here is our next news.
Last night around 5 a.m.,
near the mouth of Yongcheon River,
the body of a supposedly
70-year-old woman was discovered
by a local resident,
and the police has started
an investigation.
Based on the ID she was carrying,
she has been identified as Ms. Choe
from Jagok-dong.
The reason of death
is yet to be confirmed.
BODY OF A WOMAN IN HER 70S
FOUND IN YONGCHEON RIVER
SINGER A AND ACTOR B ADMIT TO DATING!
The police stated Ms. Choe
has no residence near Yongcheon River
where her body was discovered,
and based on the fact
that there were no stolen articles...
It turns out that the second child
of that family
was born out of an extramarital affair.
My gosh. That explains it.
That kid didn't look like
his mother at all.
This is so shocking.
He didn't look like his father either.
I knew it. Something felt strange
when I saw them.
Goodness.
Who am I? Kim Yu-sin, who cut off
his horse's neck?
I keep coming back to this house
habitually.
At least Kim Yu-sin cut off
his horse's neck. What about me?
Should I cut off my ankles or something?
Is he not home?
Did he already leave?
He left. He really left.
How could he leave so cold-heartedly
and clean his home so neatly
like an uninhabited house?
If I had known, I should've asked
where he was going at least.
So, did you meet her?
No, I didn't. I guess
he went somewhere nice.
Where? Did that old lady go on a trip?
Old lady? Who are you talking about?
You know, last time when you went
to meet Hyeon-ju and Sang-eun,
that pretty lady who came by here.
Didn't you go to meet her?
Pretty lady? Did Lady Chanel come by?
That time? Why?
How would I know?
She seemed to be looking for you,
so I told her to come inside and wait.
But she said she had somewhere to go.
She came to see me?
It's me, Hui-seon.
Did she go somewhere?
Oh, my.
What do you want?
Who are you?
She paid for her room charge
and checked out a few days ago.
Where did she say she was going?
I asked her
but she just smiled.
She must've come by to tell me something.
Talk about bad timing.
She'd be okay, right?
But why do I feel so anxious?
DON'T ANSWER IT
Mix it for me.
Hello, sir.
How are you doing?
You're not doing well?
The investment?
I'm trying really hard
to pay you back first thing,
but I'm having a bit of trouble
gathering the money.
Where would I run away to?
Even if I do, I doubt
you won't be able to find me.
I know you still have various connections
all over this country.
Sorry?
It's strange you're asking me
about my health right now.
My kidney?
I go to the bathroom really often nowadays
My urine is all bubbly and it stinks too.
I have bad eyesight too.
I don't know if they're ghosts.
I keep seeing things.
My liver? You know that
I'm from the countryside.
As you may know, fatty liver is
quite common in that area.
I'll get your money prepared
within a few days
and bring some of your favorite
30-year-old whisky
and go see you.
Of course I'll go see you.
You don't have to go through
the trouble coming here.
Okay. Good day, sir.
My goodness, that scumbag.
How could he be interested in
my internal organs?
He didn't hang up.
Hello...
I was joking.
Is that funny?
Are you having fun?
No.
Does he want his money back?
How much was it? 200 million won?
It's 300 million won now,
including interest.
No matter how desperate I was,
I shouldn't have gone to that thug.
Get rid of this.
I lost my appetite.
Still, you should...
Hey.
-Stop eating.
-Come on.
Let's at least have one proper meal.
If you keep eating your meals properly
and end up having healthy organs,
do you think yours will be safe?
Don't forget the insurance policies.
That's the only way we can make money.
Get rid of this.
Come on, Hui-won...
Is he already here?
Go and open the door.
Hold on.
You go open it. You're the one
who borrowed money.
Before I die, I'll make sure to
tell him your address
and social security number,
so don't regret it later.
OFFICE
Ma'am. My goodness.
Tell me Lady Chanel's contact number.
Why are barging in here so suddenly
and asking that?
-I don't have it.
-She must've written down
her personal information here.
Give me her personal information.
Should I look for it?
No, that's okay.
That woman doesn't have
any personal information.
So whenever she didn't come here,
there was no way for us
to contact her either.
Then what about Jun-ha's number?
You should call him from here.
What do you think this place is?
A public payphone?
-You keep bothering me today.
-Hurry up!
Then I'll try calling him just once.
You see, he ditched us
and went on a trip, all excited.
Even if I call him, he won't...
The number you have dialed
is not in service.
What?
The number is no longer in service.
By the way, did you get the insurance?
The insurance.
Every elder who comes here
has signed up for it.
You're Mr. Lee Jun-ha, right?
We're the police.
-She passed away?
-Yes.
I heard you met her
while working at an exhibit hall.
That's a place
where things like fake supplements
are sold to elders, right?
Yes.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
It's nice to meet you all.
I own that building
And you saw my fat wallet earlier
If you don't act fast,
you'll let this opportunity slide
A hotshot like me is hard to come by
Give me a hug, just once
Isn't this song nice?
Your dog is so cute.
How dare you call her a dog?
She's my daughter!
-You rude punk.
-I'm sorry, sir.
Let's go, my dear daughter.
Where do you live, all alone?
With my tough
I really don't like this place.
I don't like it either.
A close friend of mine runs this place.
I agreed to work here
because he has helped me out so much,
but I'm not sure.
No matter how we spin it,
I can't stop thinking that
all we do is ripping elders off.
Of course you'd feel that way.
You're young. Do you have
nothing better to do or what?
I know, right?
I'm young, so I should find
something better to do.
What should I do, then?
You have good looks and a nice
voice. What are you worried about?
You're not old like those of us here,
who can't do anything because of our age.
I feel as if I woke up one morning
and became a 100-year-old man.
I have no idea what I should do.
I don't even know what I can do.
Is this for depression?
No, you can die with those pills.
I developed depression
when my son moved to the US
after my husband passed away.
I collected those pills
to take my own life,
but I heard I'd have to take
all of them to die,
and I wasn't sure if I'd be able
to take them all.
I'm not even sure if I can
take all those pills, let alone die.
That's why I just carry them with me.
To remind myself
how much of a coward I am.
Do you need it? Shall I
lend it to you for a few days?
-When...
-Oh, her time of death?
The autopsy is being performed
at the moment,
so we'll find out the exact
time and date when it's completed.
But we believe it was the evening
after she took you to the airport.
We found nothing on her after that.
She accompanied you to the airport, right?
Yes.
When I told her
that I was going on a trip,
she said she'd like to
accompany me to the airport
because I always dropped her off
and picked her up.
Then you parted ways
at the departure gate, right?
Yes.
I got you some emergency medicine.
Don't be sick.
She bought me emergency medicine
and told me not to get sick.
Then she waved her hand at me.
That was the last time I saw her.
Then why didn't you leave that day?
I couldn't leave
because my flight got canceled.
I was told to wait a few days
even for the connecting flights.
May I ask where you were planning to go?
Well, you don't have to tell me
if it's personal.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Please excuse me for a second.
I need to interview another witness.
We can order you some food
if you're hungry.
I'm all right.
You're Ms. Choe's son, right?
I'm sorry for your loss.
Oh, thank you.
Let's go over there. We'd like to
ask you a few questions.
DEPARTURE GATE
Bye.
-Oh, no!
-What are you doing?
You'll damage all of them.
Darn it. We have to sell them
elsewhere, you idiot.
These are almost expired.
What should we do with these?
What do you think? Throw them out.
Hey, wait! Pass me one.
What a waste. I should drink this.
Hey, that will strengthen your kidneys.
Throw them out.
Hey, hey.
Do I look suspicious?
-You have a suspicious face.
-Why you little...
Be gentle with them. We have to sell them.
Darn it! Why did the cops
have to barge in out of the blue?
She didn't even give us
her contact information.
We always wondered what more
we could do to care for her.
But how could she...
Gosh, I still can't believe this.
Well, I think we got enough information.
By the way,
-what did you sell?
-Pardon me?
Oh, nothing much.
We sold some dietary supplements
that are good for seniors.
They're all approved by KFDA.
We're not here on a crackdown,
so please relax.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
-Thanks for your cooperation.
-No problem.
By the way, was it an accidental death?
We'll have to investigate further,
but it seems so at the moment.
I see.
-We'll leave you alone now.
-All right. Bye.
I'll keep on living
as a law-abiding citizen.
Bye.
Hui-won, what was the cause of her death?
It was an accidental death.
That's what they think.
Hey,
how much is the insurance payout
for accidental death?
It's 100 million won.
Then...
We're saved now.
My goodness.
Is it your hobby to look for people?
This time, it might be something huge.
I mean, if what you say is true,
the lady found out her son
was in Korea, not the US.
She probably went to meet her son.
Then why would she have moved out
of her room?
Her son must have felt bad
about neglecting his mother.
He would've probably let her
move in with him.
Would you say that
even if your mother disappeared?
Ma'am!
I'm sure she's fine.
Who knows? She might have
actually moved in with her son.
She hadn't heard a word from him
for two and a half years, remember?
You can't know everything about everyone.
Next, accidents and incidents.
Two days ago, near the mouth
of Yongcheon River,
the body of a 79-year-old woman,
Ms. Choe, was discovered.
It has been discovered
that she had been staying
at a motel in Jagok-dong for some time.
The police suspect suicide
as an autopsy found no signs
of foul play.
Ms. Choe's acquaintances say
she had been distressed
about her son being out of reach
after moving to the US.
There is an investigation going on
while suicide
due to personal reasons being
the most likely cause of her death.
Are you okay?
-Hye-ja!
-Yeong-su!
-Yeong-su, get the bed ready.
Be careful. Lie in your bed.
What are you doing? Massage her legs.
Okay.
I did her hair.
She said she was going to meet her son.
Okay.
We went shopping together too.
Hye-ja.
She came to see me.
She came to talk to me.
I should've stopped her. But I...
I should have stopped her.
-Well...
-Gosh!
You don't like the sauce
over the food, right?
I'm sorry. These ones are okay.
-Eat these.
-That darn lady.
She is of no use ever.
Why did she have to kill herself?
It's not like she had
a long time left anyway.
There is no payout for suicide, right?
Are you kidding me?
Hey.
-Hey!
-Yes?
Why did you order so much food?
Why?
Are we having a party? Are we?
Well, you said
I could order anything I wanted
because we were going to get the payout.
Is this Dongan Chinese Restaurant?
It's Hyoja Exhibit Hall.
We'd like to cancel our orders.
We haven't taken off the plastic wrap yet.
It doesn't matter even if you haven't.
You can't return the food.
You're being unreasonable.
What's wrong? Let me talk to him.
Hello, Director.
You're not the director?
Hello, Manager.
What do you expect us to do
with those swollen noodles?
It's none of my business
if things are rough for you.
You can't return the food.
This conversation is over.
What is he thinking?
If you ever get a call like that
again, tell me.
I'll deal with it, okay?
Okay.
That jerk.
My gosh.
Gosh, why did Dad make you do this?
Move over.
Finish up and go home.
Gosh.
So what happened?
Well, it was pretty predictable.
It was about her son.
-Her son?
-Yes.
The man who was here earlier is her son.
He said the lady visited him
before she killed herself.
I know that. I gave her a ride.
You did?
Is there something wrong?
I think I should visit my son.
As I told you, your son is--
He is in Korea.
In Seoul.
He had been out of reach?
But it had been more than two years
since he left for the US.
How could she not suspect anything
in that situation?
Isn't that strange?
Well...
I wrote letters to her.
Pretending they're from her son?
Yes.
Why?
So she wouldn't feel sad?
So when she wanted to visit
her son in the US,
you had no choice
but to tell her the truth.
In the end, she found out
her son had been living in Korea
without saying anything to her
and went to see him.
Do you have to see him?
I just want to make sure
he is doing all right.
Also, my grandchildren must be big now.
You don't have to worry about me.
In any case, I'll get to see my son.
I'm happy.
Let me give you a ride then.
Is this where he lives?
Do you want me to follow you?
No.
Should I buy something?
Maybe some snacks for my grandchildren?
I think it'll be all right today.
Maybe next time.
Okay.
It might take a while.
Don't worry. I'll wait.
She came back after about 20 minutes.
I was relieved because she looked happy.
She looked happy?
It didn't take that long.
Is it because of me?
Not at all.
We're having lunch together this weekend.
-We'll talk more then.
-She said she was having lunch
with her son and his wife that weekend.
How did it go?
Well, he said he was sorry.
He went to the US
with the money we got from our house.
When his business failed there too,
he couldn't bring himself to call me.
My goodness. When they left,
their youngest child
couldn't even walk, and now he talks.
I said, "Who are you?"
And he said, "I'm Yu-bin."
How adorable.
I was so sure
my little boy was a genius.
When other babies who were born
in the same month as him
were barely creeping,
he stood up and started taking steps.
One day, when I was distracted
for a short moment,
he fell down and got hurt
near his eyebrow.
That wound is still visible.
Whenever I see that wound,
I feel so sorry.
It will barely be visible
if it's around his eyebrow.
Still, mothers never stop worrying
about their children.
Are you happy that you got to see
your son?
Yes, I do feel happy.
He's my child.
Did you say you're leaving Korea tomorrow?
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry to see you leave.
I'll go with you to the airport tomorrow.
Since you gave me a ride home
all the time.
That's fine, don't bother.
It's okay. I really want to.
What on earth happened then?
It's difficult for me to say.
I have a mother too...
and I guess all mothers feel the same.
I know it's hard,
but you should have a bite.
Is death always
like this?
What?
Death is...
such a futile thing.
Just up until yesterday
she talked with me
and I felt the warmth of her body.
It's like she never existed now.
As if everything was a dream.
Have a bite. It's not hot anymore.
If I die too...
No.
Don't say things like that.
You should never say things like that.
I know it's been tiring
after all this time.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You can go now.
I'm sorry you missed your trip.
It's fine.
They want to see Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee. Wait.
A new suspect has been found regarding
the suicide case of the 70-year-old woman
who was found in Yongcheon River.
The probability of homicide
is now being considered.
The police found out she signed
a life insurance policy before...
I heard that man lives
in our neighborhood.
The man who lived next to the house
with the blue door.
I saw detectives continuously
asking about him yesterday.
This case is now being considered...
Why did you turn it off?
I was watching it.
Yes, I saw him several times too.
He picked up elder people with his van.
My gosh. My mother-in-law
also went to that place.
Ask her if she signed some kind of
life insurance there.
Check who the insured is.
This is frightening. How could this
happen in this tiny neighborhood?
No wonder he pretended
to care for her so much.
There was a good reason behind it.
That means I could've ended up
exactly like her if he was nice to me.
How could someone be so evil?
You're all so mean!
During your time at this exhibit hall,
who here didn't receive any help
from Mr. Lee?
Lady from Yongjugol.
You complained all the time
that your TV or laundry machine
was broken.
You always asked Mr. Lee for help.
You over there. Say something.
When you filled up your pushcart
with all kinds of junk,
who was the one who pushed it for you?
How could you be like that?
You can forget your resent,
but never someone's kindness.
How could you be so mean?
My goodness. Dear, what a pity.
You haven't had a bite to eat.
Are you okay?
Look at her face.
Does she look okay to you?
Do you want water?
What are you thinking right now?
Hye-ja is about to starve to death
because of that Jun-ha guy.
Jun-ha?
What about Jun-ha?
Aren't you like this
because Jun-ha has been arrested?
What?
Hey, Hye-ja.
-Wait. You didn't know?
-Hye-ja, pull Yourself together first...
Hye-ja.
WOMAN MURDERED FOR INSURANCE PAYOUT
AN ELABORATE CRIME PLANNED
BY AN EXHIBIT HALL EMPLOYEE
-Wait, Hye-ja!
-Hye-ja!
I'm telling you, Jun-ha is really
not someone who would do that.
There's no use talking to us.
They're already investigating
up there, so it's pointless.
Who do you mean by "they"?
We'll go meet them then.
Goodness, ma'am.
You look tired. Detective Kang,
please bring her home.
Ma'am? Where did she go?
Hey. You might really faint
if you keep doing this.
You need energy if you want to keep going.
You'll have an upset stomach. Eat slowly.
Do you really have to do this?
Like you said, if he's innocent,
he'll be released.
He has no one.
Jun-ha has no one but me.
What use will it be if you go--
I have to protect Jun-ha!
There were many other elder women
at the exhibit hall.
Was there a particular reason
you were close with her?
-Like I told you...
-I looked into it,
and the deceased was well-known
for being rich.
After your flight was canceled,
where did you go?
To the beach.
-Which beach?
-Just...
-Any place that came along.
-After that?
I stayed there.
Then there will be records of you
using an accommodation nearby.
No.
I just sat near the beach.
-All night?
-Yes.
Did anyone see you?
Anyone who can prove your alibi?
Did you know you were the recipient
of the insurance payout?
No, I didn't know.
Excuse me!
Ma'am, we're closed.
I know you saw everything on the news,
so come with me to the police station.
Why?
"Why?"
He's being wrongly imprisoned right now.
And he's like your brother,
so you should help him.
He's not close like an actual brother.
And we've suffered so much damages
because of him.
The police is carrying out
some investigation
-and business isn't going well.
-A man has been unfairly arrested.
How could you be worried about business?
Let's say Jun-ha was really behind this.
Who could say no to that kind of money?
He could've gotten greedy suddenly,
and decided to--
How could you say that?
You jerk. You're a real scumbag.
Which police station is Jun-ha at?
Since it came out on the news, is it
the Central Police Station?
Did they mention it on the news?
Let's grab a taxi.
Hye-ja, this won't do you any good.
Right. And nothing will change
right now even if you go.
-You guys are the same as him.
-Hey.
You don't have to help me.
I'll go save him on my own.
Pull yourself together, please!
-Help me catch a taxi.
-Hye-ja.
You're not eating, right?
Then I'll put this away.
Mr. Lee.
Why aren't you trying to explain yourself?
You know that all the circumstances
are putting you at a disadvantage.
All you do is state the facts.
You don't even deny
the accusations against you.
It's not like you're trying
to take the Fifth.
What is it? Guilt?
Goodness, is this some quiz or what?
Just stay in bed.
No, I want to go. I'll go see him.
I'll go check in on him, okay?
I'll tell you how he's doing.
No, I have to go see him myself.
Gosh. Let me help you with that.
I'll go with you, then.
Please let me meet the detective
in charge of the case.
He's busy with the investigation
at the moment.
Then I'll just see Jun-ha.
Let me make sure he's okay. Please?
He's fine, so please leave.
Why won't you let me see him if he's fine?
-Pardon me?
-Why can't I see him if he's fine?
Is there a reason I can't see him?
Hye-ja.
Did you...
hit him?
Ma'am, how could you say such a thing?
Why can't you let me see him if he's fine?
I bet you interrogated
that innocent guy all night...
and hit him for not saying
what you want to hear!
No one investigates like that these days.
What you just said
could get us in big trouble.
I'm not sure why you're here,
but we can't answer your questions
as we're investigating the case now.
-Please leave.
-Officer,
I can explain everything to you.
-What happened was--
-What can you explain?
The fact that he's
the insurance beneficiary?
Can you tell us anything
that can be used as his alibi?
That's...
All of you, please leave.
RELEASE LEE JUN-HA AT ONCE
JUN-HA DID NOTHING WRONG,
SO PLEASE LET HIM GO
LEE JUN-HA DID NOTHING WRONG.
PLEASE LET HIM GO
RELEASE LEE JUN-HA AT ONCE
Gosh, those old folks.
You must've taken great care
of those seniors.
Yes.
A letter? What letter?
Are you sure that lady sent it?
Did you check the security footage
from the post office?
Before she died?
Dear warmhearted young man, Lee Jun-ha.
I'm sorry.
You must be in shock.
You're Yong-seok, right?
I wouldn't have recognized you
had I run into you on the street.
I'm sorry I haven't been in touch.
Has everything been well with you?
Yes.
Well...
Do you still keep in touch with Su-hong?
Pardon?
-Yes.
-Really?
Did he change his number?
The phone number I have doesn't work.
By any chance,
did something happen to him in the US?
I'm so worried about him.
I'd like to visit him in the US.
Well...
Ma'am.
Su-hong is...
in Korea.
SOLBIT APARTMENT 2-1304
SONGHYEON 3-DONG, SEOUL
Who is it?
What's your name?
I'm Yu-bin.
My gosh, you're Yu-bin?
You're a big boy now.
Yu-bin!
Who is it?
Mom.
What brings you here?
Oh, well...
Yu-bin, go inside.
Daddy will be right back.
How did you get my address?
Oh, right.
Your friend, Yong-seok, gave it to me.
I'm sorry I haven't been in touch.
I understand everything.
Just work hard and live a good life.
That's all I want.
I had a bit of a situation.
Yes, I'm sure.
It must've been so hard for you.
How's your health?
Good.
What about you, Mom?
Yes, I'm fine too.
What about your wife?
She's well.
My gosh.
Yu-bin, that baby,
is already a big boy.
He even talks like a big boy now.
He's four this year, right?
Yes.
The older one, Ji-yul,
looks just like her mother,
so I was a little disappointed,
but Yu-bin takes after you--
I should get back.
I have to bathe my youngest one.
Oh, okay.
Well...
Can I see your kids?
I miss Ji-yul, and I want to spend
some time with Yu-bin as well.
I think they're coming down with a cold.
If they're coming down with a cold,
they should stay home.
All right, then. You should get back.
Okay.
Stay healthy.
He was too sorry to call me.
If we ever meet in another life,
I'd like to be your mom, Jun-ha.
Thank you for everything.
Are you her grandson?
-No.
-Then...
I just know her.
She might have been unlucky with her son,
but she at least had Jun-ha.
Well, pour me one.
You'll get drunk.
Why can't I get drunk on a day like this?
-Pour me a glass.
-My goodness.
Goodbye.
I can go for you.
She was my friend.
I should go say goodbye.
CHOE HWA-YEONG
So that's her name.
"Choe Hwa-yeong."
Did you eat?
I'm okay.
-Are you tired?
-I'm fine.
Let's go home.
Go on. I'll catch up.
It's so futile, right?
Life seems so futile.
She lived for more than 70 years.
And look what's left.
During the 70-something years of her life,
she must have experienced
all kinds of things.
But all that's left now is a picture.
You see,
I mean so much to myself.
To others, I might be just an old person.
There isn't anything
to look forward to anymore.
It'd be pointless to even regret anything.
People would wonder why I even care.
But I still feel so sorry for myself.
I hope you
and your life
mean a lot to you.
Let's go.
Here we go.
LATE CHOE HWA-YEONG
JANUARY 4, 1949
NOVEMBER 20, 2018
Thank you.
"Thank you"?
How could you say, "Thank you"?
Your mother just passed away.
Look. I was just grateful...
For what?
For me mourning for three days
instead of you?
Is that what you're grateful for?
Or...
for me checking on your mother
from time to time
while she was staying at a shabby motel
and you were out of reach?
Or...
for me letting her live a few more years
even though she always carried a
bottle of pills that could kill her?
Thanking me...
is not something you should say
to me right now.
This grandma gave me this toy.
-What?
-This grandma gave me this.
When?
When we were taking a walk
at the daycare center.
You can enjoy your free time now.
Have fun.
Come on, let's play!
Yu-bin.
You're the grandma from yesterday.
You look just like your dad.
You look just like him when he was young.
Yu-bin. Who was that?
The grandma from yesterday.
Grandma from yesterday?
Yu-bin.
She's not the grandma from yesterday.
She's your real grandma.
Real grandma?
I knew you'd be here.
Buy me udon. I'm hungry.
Where were you planning to go?
Russia.
Russia? Why?
I'll take the Trans-Siberian train.
I wanted to take the train
to go see the aurora.
Don't you hate Hye-ja?
She left without a word
and said she'd come back
but didn't keep her promise.
Is she playing with our feelings or what?
Missing someone can be done on my own
so it's okay.
And I received a lot from Hye-ja.
And from you too.
You were the first ones
who embraced my life...
and cried for me.
The thing that made me suffer
the most wasn't my mom who left
or my dad who used to hit me.
It was myself.
I suffered my whole life, not being
able to embrace myself.
I was an error made from a mistake,
and I knew well that I was born
without any blessings.
So I really hated myself for it.
But...
even when I couldn't embrace myself,
she was the first one who
embraced me and cried.
Go.
Why aren't you going to see the aurora?
Will I be able to go?
You can just go.
Why are you sitting here like this?
You should go right now.
Go...
and see my share of the aurora too.
Okay?
You have to tell me all about it
when you get back.
Tell me how much you cried.
Promise me.
I'll think about you a lot
when I go there, ma'am.
You don't have to think about me.
Just think of Hye-ja.
The 25-year-old...
Hye-ja.
Here.
What is this?
I picked it up on the way here.
Throw it away then.
Or you can just keep it.
Hey.
DONGAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
Give me your hand.
Other hand.
They fit perfectly.
I was banned for life,
but I received a ton of candies.
Why is it red? It's so tacky.
Do you want to watch a movie tonight?
What's wrong with your face? Are you sick?
Hey, forget it.
Why would I watch a movie with you? Move.
I'll see you at seven o'clock.
You must've went through a lot.
Your face looks terrible.
You have a lot of money now.
You should get some herbal tonics
or something.
It feels unfortunate looking at you.
It makes me sad.
What do you mean, money?
Goodness.
Come on. There's no secret between us.
Lady Chanel.
You're really good at acting.
What else did she have besides money?
And you're the one who
she adored the most.
Right?
How much did you get?
I didn't get anything.
When her son went to the US,
she sold her house to support him.
She used to stay at a motel.
You know that too.
How would I know, you scumbag?
Seriously? Are you really
going to be like this?
I thought we were like brothers.
Gosh.
And you talked Lady Chanel into
making you the beneficiary
of the insurance payout?
Gosh, you're a real crook.
Speaking of which,
stop selling life insurance policies
to seniors.
It's wrong, Hui-won. You're trying
to make money off people's lives.
Look at this little punk.
Fine, you jerk.
I make money off people's lives.
Got a problem with that?
Yes? What are you going to do about it?
Will you report me to the police?
Go ahead, you punk.
You know what?
I don't think you can get on that plane.
Hye-ja.
Hey, just cry if you're sad.
No, I feel relieved.
Even I think I'm a pretty cool lady.
I didn't cry at all.
I was trying so hard to hold back my tears
that my eyeballs almost burst.
Girl, we told you that you don't
need to act tough in front of us.
I'm telling you the truth.
All right, then.
Then shall we go on a trip together?
I'd love that!
Where do you girls want to go?
You know you must respect
your elders, right?
You girls have to respect
my opinion no matter what.
-Then we can't go away.
-Says who?
You just belittled seniors. Come here.
Hey, calm down.
Were you really going to turn me in?
This is out of line. Stop, please.
All those seniors will die
because of a punk like you.
Have you seen Mr. Lee?
-Lee Jun...
-You've seen him?
Mr. Lee has been kidnapped?
We're the only ones who can save Mr. Lee
and the seniors
who are going on the picnic.
We need a perfect plan
to make sure no one gets hurt.
Jun-ha.
That's not Mr. Lee.
Hye-ja.
Jun-ha.
Jun-ha!