"Wooju Bakery"
What do you call that thing we were just
on?
This?
I'm not sure what it's called either.
It's actually pretty amazing.
Oh, you mean a swing?
A swing!
Swings are so much fun.
Oh!
Your Highness, I'm sorry!
Get up.
I'm the reason Hachi got arrested.
What do you mean he got caught because of
you?
The police got him
when I wasn't paying attention.
Let's go check on him first.
Thankfully…
- Huh?
- He got away…
- He's here.
- Huh?
Why didn't you say so sooner? You scared
me to death!
Your Highness…
Please don't send him to jail!
Hachi! Hands up!
Hands down.
Hey! Are you a dog? Are you?
Why are you eating dog food?
Because… I can't resist the smell of it.
Ugh…
I'm speechless… Hey!
If word gets out that I'm feeding my
bakery staff dog food,
that I'm some kind of sweatshop owner,
what am I supposed to do?
- Huh?
- Aren't you already a sweatshop owner?
Seriously… How am I a sweatshop owner?
You haven't paid our wages, have you?
Oh, really? I knew you'd say that.
Look, read the contract!
You signed it yourself!
It's not that I'm not paying you.
You guys caused trouble, and now you're
working off your debt!
Hmph.
Tsk!
Um… Senior?
Yeah?
That Wooju Bakery over there.
What now? Are you going to talk about
aliens again?
No, no.
Is their bread… any good?
Why?
Did someone say it wasn't good?
No, no, that's not it.
Among the staff there,
is there anyone who carries around some
kind of weird gun?
A gun?
What kind of gun?
No, I just…
I think I might have been hit by some
weird gun.
Maybe I was, maybe I wasn't… was I?
Did you finish handling that complaint
from yesterday?
Yes…
I have to go, I've got things to do.
Good work.
It's suspicious no matter how I look at
it.
Ugh… But how am I supposed to prove it?
That jerk… Wooju Bakery…
Mina… Dragon Palace Restaurant… Jirol…
Wait, wasn't Jirol already suspicious
before the bakery even opened?
He looks so dim-witted.
Could he be hiding the fact that he's an
evil alien?
Is he putting on an act?
I'm back!
Come here for a second.
You were only delivering nearby, why did
it take you so long?
- Ouch…
- Why are you so late?
I thought something happened to you!
No, how could I possibly get into trouble?
I'm the best delivery guy in this
neighborhood.
Cut the crap.
All you do is dance and mess around with
those kids all day.
That's not it.
I'm doing it for the future customers of
Dragon Palace.
I'm helping to attract customers, right?
Enough. I'll give you one more chance. If
you drag your feet again,
I'm firing you, you hear me?
Yes…
Can you come out for a second? I have
something to tell you.
Officer… I didn't do anything wrong.
No, boss, it's not like that… I…
I came here because I know everything!
What exactly do you know? Seriously.
Aliens!
You're one, aren't you?
No, I…
You really…
What aliens?
What are you even talking about?
I'm not one.
I'm a person who even have an ID card, you
know.
Then why did you kidnap the YouTuber Mina
last time?
That was…
Rather than a kidnapping, it was more
like…
If you tell me the truth,
I might go easy on you.
I'm really not an alien, okay?
Actually, the alien…
is a guy named Chairman Lee.
Chairman Lee?
He's truly despicable!
Despicable?
Yeah! Exactly.
He's the kind of guy who came here to
destroy the Earth, seriously.
But…
You can't tell anyone I told you, okay?
Tell me more clearly, I can go easy on
you…
Wooju Bakery, no bias, no hype, just an
honest review.
If you go to Wooju Bakery,
You really have to choose your bread
carefully…
Damn it.
I don't want to just stand by and watch
the shop turn into a mess.
The boss hasn't even woken up yet, and
we've already cleaned the whole shop.
That's not what I'm talking about! I mean…
A bakery is supposed to smell like fresh,
delicious bread.
And there should be customers quietly
coming in to buy bread.
Right now, it's just noisy and chaotic,
isn't it?
But the customers love it…
Quiet!
The boss is talking.
Get rid of all those questionable breads
and start over.
But…
The bread you make…
What about it?
It's really bad.
This is the place, right?
Please wait a moment…
Try them all.
- They look so delicious.
- Those ones too.
Boss, look over here.
Only the bread you made hasn't sold.
So annoying.
This bakery, even the bread is weird.
The drinks are weird, the staff is weird,
everything is weird.
The customers are the weirdest ones!
Scream!
Air!
Shut your mouth.
Why are you up so early?
Hey! Stop making noise and go back to
sleep.
The boss's bread isn't popular, so I'll
make some.
I told you to go back to sleep.
I said go back to sleep, are you deaf?
Hmm~
The bread smells really good.
Why are you making that face?
Or… did I do something wrong?
No.
Are you mad because I didn't help?
I said it's not like that.
I said it's not like that, can't you
understand?
Alright, stop it.
It's not because of you.
Then what is it?
The smell of the bread baking right now…
do you like it?
Yeah.
When I was little,
I always loved the smell when my dad made
bread.
I really want to smell that again.
But now, I can't sense anything…
Wow~ the bread smells so good.
Hyung.
Why are you here so early?
I thought I'd bring some of your bread to
share at the station.
After all, you just opened recently.
Yeah.
Our bread doesn't need promotion.
Because it sells too well.
Except for the bread Wooju makes.
I specifically want to buy the bread Wooju
makes.
The ones that just went into the oven need
a while.
At least 10 minutes.
Hmm? This one… I can just buy this one.
Not that one… that one…
That's from yesterday.
It doesn't matter, I'll take this one.
Uh…
Yuck!
This is terrible. You call this bread?
No.
Isn't it a bit harsh to say it's terrible
right to his face?
A baker should know whether their bread is
good or not.
Hey~
Wooju, your sense of taste will come back.
Didn't the doctor say it was only
temporary?
Opening this bakery… it's really pushing
it.
Boss.
Hmm?
Boss, don't worry.
You've got me.
What did you say?
I'll teach you.
How to bake bread!
The best bread in the world.
The best bread in the entire world?
What are you talking about, you fraud?
Why would I want to learn
how to make your weird bread?
Hey?
Get out.
Hey.
Did you go to culinary school too?
What makes you say that?
Your technique… it's not bad.
Do you want to give it a try?
How do I do it?
Take it slow.
How's that? Doesn't it feel smoother?
I've never seen anyone bake bread like
that before.
Never?
I doubt that.
I don't remember clearly…
But I think my dad used to bake bread just
like this.
Think of your father.
Imagine he's watching you right now.
Yeah.
Now, it's time for a taste test.
Want to try it?
Sigh.
Raon…
Yeah?
Do you think I can really…
Do you think I'll ever be able to taste
again?
Yeah.
That's good.
Well?
Can you taste anything?
Stop it.
Why not?
Chairman Lee, about Mr. Kim from the
salvage shop…
I can't shake this uneasy feeling.
Are you sure it's okay to just let him go?
That guy is a highly skilled engineer.
They don't have a ship or any
communication gear anyway.
If they want to go home, they'll have to
do exactly as we say.
Chairman Lee.
How have you been?
Those people who crash-landed recently…
They seem to be high-ranking officials.
This…
The news from off-world is blowing up.
What? Tell me exactly who they are.
They keep demanding the location of the
ship.
But they won't reveal their identities or
where they're from.
Find out where they are right now.
And bring them to me immediately.
Understood.
If we keep this up, won't it cause trouble
later?
It doesn't matter.
We just need to catch them before that
happens.
Understood.