Eun Dong told me to wait,
but Eun Dong never returned.
My Love Eun Dong
Episode 2
How was Eun Dong's life for past ten years?
The space in my heart for her was alway empty, but
Eun Dong's face was slowly fading from my memory.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Oh... That...
Kiddo? Kiddo?
Are you okay? Are you coming to your senses?
This is Eun Dong.
♫    How can I meet you again like this?   ♫
Have... You... Been well?
♫ The warm memories are coming back out now ♫
That...
♫   Back in the days we loved  ♫
Have you eaten?
♫   Back to the days we shared  ♫
Like a dream and like a movie, we met like that again.
Like when I met Eun Dong ten years ago.
Just like that, we met again.
Oppa... I've grown taller, right?
Yeah.
I got prettier, right?
Yeah. Totally.
You are embarrassed aren't you?
- Why would I be embarrassed?
-Yeah, you are.
I always wondered how Eun Dong had changed.
I never thought I'd feel embarrassed looking at her face.
But, the whole time looking at her face,
my heart raced like crazy.
That little kiddo became a woman and reappeared in my life.
Then...
Then, you become an actor?
Right, it just happened. That was your dream.
No, I don't watch dramas or movies that much.
Tell me the dramas or movies you are in, so I can search.
Oppa.
You know what star in the sky shines the longest?
The latest star.
Are you comforting me?
What about me?
- Hey you little kiddo, you acted mature back then and you are still acting mature?
- Yeah.
I don't know about in front of others, but you don't have to act mature with me,
because I am not mature yet.
Oh, the smell! Take it easy on your aftershave!
This little punk...
You've finally gone off the deep end?
Mother, I am so very happy!
- Found her!
- Found what?
- Eun Dong!
- What?
- Really?
- Stop over there.
Eun Dong!
Hey! Hey!
How did he find her? So fine...
Wow! She is killing me.
Oppa! You're here!
Wow, that kiddo. How did she grow up so fine?
- Oppa, faster!
- Faster!
Hold on tight.
♫   Would I ever get a dazzling girlfriend like that?   ♫
- Hold on tight!
- Yup!
Don't let me go again, okay?
Okay...
After meeting Eun Dong again, I stopped calling the TV program.
In fact, that program was too old.
I even thought like that.
Hello, my name is Ji Eun Dong.
I am in my fourth year at the City University, studying literature.
From today, to you grandmas and grandpas,
I will teach Korean.
During the class, if you don't fall asleep and study hard,
I'll buy pizza.
Wow!
The Korean class for the seniors
was cancelled due to the reconstruction.
But..
That young teacher came to see the city counselor,
so the class was revived.
That young lady is pretty impressive and smart.
Right...
The young lady has solid principle,
volunteering and all...
You, Hyun Soo too, should get some acting work.
I feel bad for you being compared to Lee Seok Tae.
Supervisor Oh, do you know which star shines the most in the sky?
The newest star.
Yes, I am all done.
Oppa, I will submit the report to school and come back. We'll have dinner together, okay?
Ohh... Okay, okay.
Are you okay?
What are you? Were you nearby?
Why are you riding a bike? It's dangerous!
Oppa, where were you?
I am always near you. Heed that!
You are bleeding! Aish!
You stay put!
You still have a scar from that motorcycle accident.
No Oppa. That was gone long ago.
Then what is this?
I frequently fall and get hurt,
so my nick name is QuaDang. (falling sound)
- What?
- Funny, isn't it?
Is it funny to you?
You need to be careful.
If you know you fall and get hurt frequently, then you shouldn't be riding a bike! You should use public transportation.
From now on, use the subway or the bus.
You are sweating a lot.
You must have run fast because of me.
Don't ride your bike from tomorrow. It's an order.
I fell in a bus because of the quick stop.
I'll be careful Orabeoni.
I'll take you.
You are currently serving the public, not unemployed.
You are making me nervous.
Were you nervous during the ten years without me?
Of course.
Those ten years felt like a hundred years.
I too, missed you a lot.
I'll take you home.
You are still on duty.
I just finished.
Hello?
Yeah.
No I can't come, I have to go to Mi Sun.
Hello? Hyun Soo?
Did you just hang up? Hello?
Can't you tell me before I ask
how you've been?
After Grandmother passed, I was adopted.
I am sorry, I should have found you already.
No, my parents are nice folks.
I am thankful to them.
Yes.
I didn't think you'd leave that way.
I was in the hospital on the day of your grandmother's passing.
The day you disappeared.
So it was...
But why were you in the hospital?
I fought thirteen against one and got hurt a little.
Of course you were in the thirteen?
I should have been discharged sooner.
I waited, Oppa.
We met like this again, so all is well.
Wow the City University is impressive.
Why are you limping?
Did you sprain your ankle?
No, I am fine.
This won't do, I'll give you a piggyback.
No, I'll return shortly.
No, I'll take you to the door.
No, I am fine.
I can go alone.
You, with an injured ankle,
and this many steps?
No way! Get on.
If I needed to find you, what would I find you with?
I'll recognize you just from your back.
How could you find me just looking at my back?
I'll recognize you easily because you have the warmest back in this world.
It is a bit embarrassing, but it is warm, too.
You are a bit heavy,
but it's not hard at all.
I like it, but I'm a bit sorry.
I am curious, but can't ask.
If asked, I can answer everything.
You don't have a boyfriend, right?
Humanity Building
I'll wait in the car.
Okay.
Eun Dong did not answer, but I knew what it meant.
The fact that Eun Dong cannot lie
was a resentful moment for me.
Aish... What bum—
Ah, seriously!
Imposition of Fine and Objective car being towed
- Ahh.. What bum— Seriously!
I am going to your house, so come see me.
Ah, this isn't it.
It's me...
What are you doing? Have you eaten?
Aish... We are not elementary kids.
Is it you Eun Dong?
It's me, Oppa.
It is Hyun Soo...
No...
This is Oppa. Oppa.
Must read Korean modern poetry 222 lines.
What are you to me? And what am I to you?
Was I just Oppa to you?
Hyun Soo, make some copies please.
Hyun Soo, mine is more urgent.
Wait, this is urgent. Do it fast.
This too.
Hyun Soo...
- Give it to me.
- Thank you.
-  Hyun Soo!
- Yes?
Please eat! Please eat!
You have to eat that and don't bother our oppa again, okay?
You must! We'll be watching you.
Oppa!
Wow, you're so cool! Hyun Soo, Oppa!
You're so cool! So handsome!
Hyun Soo Oppa! Hyun Soo Oppa!
You're so handsome. I love you!
Oppa, please come here!
I love you! You're so handsome!
- Do both of your adoptive parents know about  me?
- Yeah.
What did you tell them about me?
Eun Dong.
- Oppa.
- What kind of entity I was, and am to you now,
is up to you. So I won't care, but...
You aren't just like a sister to me.
Let's continue this brother-sister relationship.
Am I just a brother to you?
You aren't a sister to me.
I'm just a brother to you?
I never had a sister like you.
I'm already tired of having my own sister.
- Then, do you not have a girlfriend?
- I don't!
Brother-sister... Yeah, right.
Eat slowly, you'll get indigestion.
- Hurry up and eat.
- I am.
It's delicious.
Of course it is. You bought that from a chicken restaurant.
A girl, like you, eating messily like this...
Stay still.
- Oppa, I'll be going now.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Eun Dong.
- I'm telling you to be careful.
- Okay.
- I'll be going.
- I acted like it didn't bother me,
- but the awkwardness that was flowing between me and Eun Dong
- Go.
was so heavy that it couldn't be erased.
I needed some kind of breakthrough.
But not knowing what kind of breakthrough was needed,
was the problem.
Aigoo, hello.
- I work with Hyun Soo Hyung.
- I see.
Excuse me. I'm Lee Seok Tae.
How unlucky.
Hyun Soo, who was that lady, earlier?
- Why?
- She's not your biological sister, right?
- She called you oppa.
- No, she isn't.
She's not your girlfriend either, right?
Please introduce me to her.
- What?
- She's totally my type.
But... Why did you think that she wasn't my girlfriend?
You guys didn't have that special atmosphere given out
when two people are dating.
I don't want to date entertainers any more.
They said you need to date a lot when you're still a public servant.
You can't date when you start your career.
Seok Tae, can we talk?
- Hey you bastard!
- What? Oh gosh, that scared me.
Hey, she's my girlfriend.
It's been ten years.
She's not someone you can look at so easily, so don't even think about it!
And I'm an early 79, you punk! (born in early 1979)
If you ever speak informally to me again, I'll kill you!
Oh, who is this?
Isn't this Korea's best actor, Park Hyun Soo?
I'm outside the hospital. Let's have a drink.
Indeed, because you are in administrative and not in the defense,
- you are more smooth with the civilians.
- Hurry up.
What's wrong? Why are you slumping down like that?
You look like someone who just experienced a broken heart.
I will be your consulting partner today.
- Just tell me the category. Dating, work, or—
- Hey!
How do you steal a woman who already has a boyfriend?
A  new  category!
Why are you getting troubled over something like that?
What's so hard about that?
Create a similar point between you two.
- What are you saying?
- What I mean is,
you make it so that the girl feels sorry to her boyfriend,
so that both of you have the same feelings, a similar point.
What on earth are you talking about?
You really don't understand anything!
What I'm saying is that
you feel sorry towards that man because you have feelings for his girl, right?
Why would I feel sorry towards that punk?
I was the first one to hug Eun Dong. I was the first one to like her. I was the first for everything!
- The person who should be sorry is that punk!
- Eun Dong?
You like Eun Dong, Oppa?
- How did you come to like her?
- Forget it, just drink your beer.
Oppa!
This girl. Your manners are so...
I have someone I'm going to marry.
Park Hyun Ah.
If you marry before me, I'll kill you!
I'm going to marry first!
I may lose my opportunity waiting for you to get married.
- Don't know.
- What you mean, don't know?
But, that girl, Eun Dong's, boyfriend...
What if he's someone who is more successful than you are?
As my curiosity grew over who Eun Dong's boyfriend was,
so did my feelings of wanting to rip them apart.
Just thinking about how Eun Dong was with another man was very painful for me.
You need to date me.
Why?
Because we're fated.
Fate.
He really opened the lid. That's what you're saying, right?
Yeah.
He definitely sees you as a woman! He's jealous!
The answer is so clear. Start your scheme!
Can I do that?
But you... What is it exactly that you want from him?
Marriage.
Hey, how can you fearlessly say you want to marry a public servant who is so much older than you?
I can raise money and feed him myself.
What's it to him?
Oh my, oh my.
You worked really hard!
Teacher, you worked hard!
Go home safely!
Are you Teacher Eun Dong's boyfriend?
What?
You look really good with Teacher Eun Dong.
Watch a movie with me today.
I have plans already.
Cancel them. Right now.
Oppa.
I'm going to do things my way, so you do things your own way.
I won't disturb anything.
Hey, no matter how much I think about it,
you having a boyfriend is such a given. I'll play fairly.
I just have to win in the championships. Am I right?
What exactly your feelings for me are...
You don't even know.
That's the thing I can confidently say I know for sure.
I'll take care of my feelings, so you just take care of yourself.
Whether I'm like an older brother or a man to you.
I'll see you in front of the movie theater at seven. You 'd better come looking pretty,
since it's our first date.
Good job, good job. Park Hyun Soo, you're a man.
Hey little kid!
♫  I must be regretting it, I must be waiting for you  ♫
Oh... This?
I wanted to wear them when I turned twenty, but my feet grew too much.
Shall we go?
Okay.
Your hairpin is pretty. Your hairpin is pretty.
♫   As if we'd met yesterday  ♫
♫   Not really needing to ask you how you've been  ♫
♫   Maybe I was needlessly concerned  ♫
♫   Being nervous, maybe I made it awkward between us  ♫
♫   Telling me that you look awful  ♫
Since I heard you had a boyfriend,
♫  Because you couldn't sleep last night after my phone call   ♫
holding your hand like this is so difficult.
♫   Because you couldn't sleep last night after my phone call  ♫
But...
♫  You are shyly smiling   ♫
I don't want to think about things like that.
♫  How could you still be the same?   ♫
I can't give you up.
♫   How could you still be the same?  ♫
I wouldn't have expected anything else if your heart felt the same way mine did.
♫  You say you didn't even know it was love back then   ♫
I bet it doesn't yet.
♫   And that you always felt bad when you heard news about me  ♫
I'll wait.
♫   Hearing that, tears start to flow  ♫
I'll match you,
and I'll control my heart.
♫  Hearing that, tears start to flow   ♫
♫  Should I say I love you, again?  ♫
You can... Increase it.
You can increase the amount (of love) more.
♫  If you didn't know it was love before  ♫
♫  Whenever you hear about me  ♫
♫  When I hear the words stating how you always felt sorry towards me  ♫
♫  My tears start to fall down without me knowing ♫
♫  Should I tell her I love her again?  ♫
♫  Will you accept me comfortably like you are now?  ♫
♫  Even if I'm born again, loving you again  ♫
♫  Is my life's purpose  ♫
♫  Should I tell her I love her again?  ♫
Oppa! Oppa over here!
Oppa, come out for a second please!
-  Oppa, please come out!
- I can't come out because of this punk!
Wow...
Oppa, come out anyway! Hurry!
Hey.
Go out there. They're waiting for you.
Yes sir. Thank you.
Oppa!
Oppa! Is that guy bothering you?
He's so annoying!
Spring.
Summer.
Fall.
He's so handsome.
- Handsome?
- Have we learned it?
I don't know.
Oh, he is handsome. Very handsome.
This is a story about a guy who can't forget his first love.
Lee Seok Tae was supposed to be the main character, but as he entered military, we're down-playing him now.
So Jo Yoon Jung is the main character, and you're the female lead's boyfriend.
It is a small part, but these days the supporting act can outshine the lead act.
The female lead is Mi Sun, so we put you in the package. You must do well this time.
You have to audition for this part.
Practice like crazy!
If you don't get this part, you'll have no chance.
The filming will start in two months, so the timing is perfect with your discharge.
Right? Timing is everything.
You learn that while you live. Timing!
Read.
What kind of smile
Hyun Soo, let's eat!
Hurry up kids.
Thanks for the meal!
Mom, Hyun Ah said that she had someone to marry.
Wow, look at how loose lipped you are!
Really?
Oh, it might be true.
Do you marry by yourself?
You have to look into that family's current standing. You marry just because you're dating?
What kind of person is he?
I met him at the hospital.
Oh, he's a doctor?
That's a relief then.
What do his parents do?
I don't really know. I haven't asked.
Oh look at this girl. Why wouldn't you ask that? That's the most important part.
If you want to know how that person really is, you need to know about his parents.
I mean, you need to just look at that person. Why the need to look at the parents?
What really annoyed me about our history was the fact that they put a death sentence for three generations.
What do the parents have to do with this? There are kids without parents who grew up splendidly.
Why are you going so overboard?
It may be for men, but for women, you have to look at the household.
The kids raised without parents are melancholy and tend to hold grudges, so they are not suitable for family.
What department does he work in?
Is he a fellow or—
He's not a doctor.
He's a patient.
Huh?
What?
You should have let me tell them later on. Why did you go and tell them now? Huh?
Who knows what you'll do if we leave you alone?
Someone needs to know to prevent you from doing anything.
You said he was a patient. What kind of patient is he?
Hemorrhoid?
Cancer.
What?
He's a patient under my care. He has stage three brain cancer.
- Hyun Ah.
- Oppa.
I'm serious.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that and...
I just...
You did well.
It's better to have them know sooner than later.
That person doesn't have time.
I was thoughtless.
I shouldn't have let our parents know.
But, that girl Eun Dong, does she not have parents?
No.
What do we do? Even you are in a difficult situation.
We really back-stabbed our parents.
Why don't you listen to your father and do whatever you want?
This ungrateful child!
Oppa. Do you remember this song?
What is this?
You don't remember?
I don't know.
Hey, what is it? Tell me.
You really are too much. This song was a big part of our lives and you don't know it?
- Big part?
- Forget it.
Tell me. What is it?
We. That day. First.
First?
How could you forget this song?
I've heard it over a hundred times.
Hey, I really was out of my mind that day.
I was seduced by a fox with ninety tails and my soul was buried in the ground.
Do you think I would remember this song?
That's right. It was this song.
It's great.
♫ When you said you are still alone ♫
♫ My heart ached without realizing ♫
♫ Will you tell me that you love me again? ♫
♫ It's been a long time but I have been waiting ♫
♫ Waiting for you is the easiest thing for me to do ♫
♫ I didn't even know time was passing by
Will you tell me that you love me again? ♫
♫ I lack many things as always but will you accept me? ♫
♫ Loving you is my everything ♫
♫ It couldn't be helped ♫
I heard you are going for an audition.
Yeah, the script looked great!
Indeed, the script is great.
I am disappointed. I really wanted to do it myself.
But it is a bit unrealistic.
The male lead is meeting the female lead in fifteen years, but how could he not recognize her?
It could happen, if it is fifteen years.
I recognized her at first glance.
If meeting a fateful person, you'd recognize in the first glance after twenty years as well, not only fifteen years.
But, is it something that you should be concerned with?
If anybody should be concerned, then it should be the male lead.
Yeah, this punk...
That is why your anti-fans are increasing rapidly.
Is your pride bruised?
I am sorry.
Hey, it's your pride that should be bruised.
That is why you can't escape modeling.
Either supporting act or extras, you must understand the exact emotion
to execute. This punk...
How could you  not  know something so basic!
Is he really an actor?
I have an audition next week.
I heard.
From who?
From your manager.
Hey, why do you keep meeting a guy without me knowing?
Should I go follow you to the audition?
You have class, though.
Anyhow, you will go after your work.
Okay, fine. Come.
If you're there, I'll do a lot better.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
You... Are you still meeting that punk?
- Oppa...
- I already told you
that I'd play fairly, that I'd win in the end.
I'm canceling those words. From today on— No—
From yesterday—  No, from the day before—you can't do this.
You... This is the ring that bastard gave you, right?
- Now that bastard—
- That ring!
My mom gave it to me!
Ah! Oppa!
Oppa, it's dangerous!
♫ ♫
Oppa! Come back!
Why would you jump in to find it, you dummy? You didn't even know how deep it was!
Wait here. I'll go buy a towel, okay?
You have to come back, okay?
Of course, I'll come back.
I'll be back, so don't move and stay here, okay?
♫  Because I love too much  ♫
♫ Just looking at her makes me yearn for her ♫
♫ Should I say I want to be with you? Laugh with you? ♫
♫ All the words that I have kept inside are about to explode ♫
♫   Putting you in my heart, you've remained in my heart  ♫
Eun Dong,
she told me to wait.
♫ Me, who smiles when I see her
me, who can breathe thanks to her ♫
♫ My heart is like that, just yearning for her ♫
Eun Dong, she told me to wait.
However, Eun Dong...
She never came back.
Hey you in the front! Move...
I heard your reason for making an autobiography is to find someone.
What is her name, exactly?
♫ ♫
Hyun Soo Oppa.
Oppa...
Hurry!
We're departing now. Both are in a critical condition.
The man's name is Choi Choi Ho. The girl's name is yet unknown.
- I found her name!
- The girl's name!
Ji Eun Dong.
Is she, by any chance, your first love?
She's my fiancee.
What?
We heard you were dating Young Sun Group's oldest daughter Jo Seo Ryeong.
How do you think Jo Seo Ryeong will feel when she finds  out about this?
Jo Seo Ryeong and I are just very good friends.
A relationship between us seems to be something reporters want,
but we're not in any kind of relationship.
Mister Eun Ho!
You must be tired.
Let's go.
Where?
There.
Oh. Okay.
- You brought my clothes right?
- Yes! In the bag in the back.
Let's go to IlSan.
You have to come back.
Of course, I'd come back.
I'll be right back, so just wait here, okay?
Eun Dong disappeared, just like that.
Eun Dong told me to wait.
Let's go now.
You go by yourself.
How are you going to get home?
I'll take a taxi.
The director keeps texting to bring you.
I'll talk to him. You go first.
Okay... Ah.
I agreed to meet with the ghostwriter you told me about.
You told me to get the writer without anyone knowing.
So why would you reveal it all at the press conference?
Honestly...
Come back safely then.
♫ What do I have to do to see you again? ♫
Eun Dong, be careful!
♫ I see the yearning painted on my lips ♫
Eun Dong be careful!
♫ The things I've kept close to me in my hand,
the things I haven't said ♫
♫ When I cried for a long time because I wanted to forget ♫
♫ Those warm memories are coming back out now ♫
Eun Dong, be careful!
♫ Back in the days, we loved ♫
♫ When we loved each other ♫
♫ Back to the days, we shared ♫
♫ We just need to go back to the days when we were dreaming ♫
Eun Dong...
Where are you?
♫ The changing appearances after the quickly passing time ♫
♫  An awkward meeting, how it all began  ♫
♫ Love once again...♫
By any chance, are you Writer Seo Jung Eun?
Yes.
♫ I didn't know it then, those days when I was too young to understand love ♫
♫  At that time  ♫
Who iss Ji Eun Ho now?
You're the most popular guy in Korea.
Ji Eun Ho's unforgettable love of ten years.
Please find her. I'm curious as to who she is.
The fact that I'm ghostwriting is a secret, okay?
Zip!
Why do I have to get so frustrated over a simple ghostwriter?
Can you please give this letter to Eun Dong if you see her?
I hope the two of you don't meet.
Forever.
♫ Back to the days, we shared ♫