My Love Eun Dong
Last Episode
Jae Ho! Ra Il!
Ra Il.
Ra Il! Ra Il!
Ra Il!
Someone please!
It's exhaustion. Your child experienced a considerable amount of mental shock.
Let's make sure he gets a lot of rest.
What happened?
Don't worry too much. They said it's exhaustion.
Can I be a good dad to Ra Il?
The feelings he has for that man... Do you think Ra Il can redirect them to me instead?
But if I keep trying to achieve that goal,
is there a chance that Ra Il could get hurt?
He's your son, Oppa.
For raising Ra Il like that,
thank you.
Now you do all of it, okay?
Let's go get something to eat.
No, Oppa. I'll stay here.
I know you haven't eaten yet. Let's go.
Ra Il.
Ra Il!
Yes, welcome!
- We will go in the private room.
- No, no, no!
Someone else has reserved that room so sit over here.
Sit over here.
Please give us two beef short rib soups.
Two gal-bo ! (Two whores!)
(similar to gal-bi = short rib)
I guess you all walk around without reading the newspaper?
When They Reunited She Was Already Married
Has Actor Ji Eun Ho Become the Nation's Adulterer?
How can you even face your child?
Have them hurry up and eat so they can leave soon!
Dad, are you awake?
Are you not sick any more?
You, why are you here?
Why did you come here?
It's hard for you isn't it, Oppa?
Yeah.
The problem is Ra Il and Jung Eun.
Right now, everyone is talking about the rumors coming out of those misleading articles written about you and Jung Eun.
Ra Il and Jung Eun are the ones being harmed the most.
People don't believe that Ra Il is your son.
That's why
I will make a public statement confirming that Ra Il is your son.
No, don't do that. We're  not prepared for that yet.
Do you know what kinds of names people are calling Jung Eun?
You're a celebrity so you're used to these things, but
it's going to be really hard for Ra Il and Jung Eun to cope with all of this.
I will meet the reporters and show them the DNA results.
Let's reveal that Ra Il is your son, Oppa.
You never know. It might get better.
Doing that won't resolve this situation.
It might even make things harder for Ra Il.
I suppose.
Ra Il's  face, hands, hair and body...
All of these may come from me, but
his heart doesn't belong to me.
I don't have the right to cause him any pain.
Especially considering I'm only his father in name.
Oppa.
Was it wrong for me to show up in Eun Dong's life again?
All I wanted was to be good to her.
My intention was to give her more happiness.
But instead, for both of these people,
I'm having thoughts about whether I'm giving them more pain.
No, Oppa. It's not like that.
But I really don't see a solution to this problem.
Also, Ra Il knows
that you are his dad, Oppa.
It seems like he found out somehow.
What?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Ahjussi...
Are you really my dad?
How did you find out?
But why didn't you come until now?
I'm sorry.
For me, that is
my biggest regret and apology to you.
Ahjussi, please don't take my dad away from me.
I heard what the nurses were saying.
They said my dad tried to kill himself because of you.
I hate you, Ahjussi.
Because of you
my mom gets hated by people,
and I also get hated by my grandmother.
I'm sorry, Ra Il.
I was the happiest when you weren't here.
Same for my dad. Same for my dad.
Please
take good care of Ra Il.
I will let go of Eun Dong.
I will let Seo Jung Eun return to her rightful place.
I ask that you also
let the two of them go.
I will leave as well,
so that Eun Dong and Ra Il don't experience any more pain.
I don't see any other way we can resolve this entire situation.
Now we just need to leave it all up to fate.
Thank you for raising Ra Il well.
I will never forget that.
Here. Hyung asked me to give this to you, President.
He left it up to you, however you want to take care of it.
How did everything turn out like this?
Eun Ho Hyung said he was going to meet with Chief Jo today. He said he plans to make President Hwang testify as a witness.
-  Then there's a chance you may not have to go to prison.
- But instead, what would we have to do in return?
Knowing what type of person Jo Se Ryeong is, there's no way she would bestow such kindness without any conditions.
He said he's willing to turn this company over to her.
Well, I suppose with Eun Ho leaving, this company would no longer have any meaning for me.
But you know, I don't hate Eun Ho Hyung even one bit.
Why would you hate him? He's such a pitiful guy.
You've been through a lot.
Speaking of, it's you who's been going above and beyond.
It's okay if I spend a little time inside. Don't overdo yourself.
It's been a while. Should the three of us have a drink together?
Should we?
Here.
You guys have worked really hard.
What are you going to do?
Me?
Just...
Wondering whether I should go find a quiet spot to crawl into and live.
I can't be out and about too much since people know my face.
What are your plans, President?
I'll go back down to Chun Cheon.
What do you think about me running a motorcycle wholesale business?
Motorcycle.
Times were good back then, when I was racing around town fearlessly. Those were the days.
That little kid who finally put an end to my speed demon days,
who would have known she would become the center of my life?
Park Hyun Soo was really the coolest back in those days.
Hyun Bal.
You...
- Go into Chief Jo's company.
- I don't want to.
Even if I fall into the water and start drowning, I don't dog paddle.
- Go there, you bastard.
- I said I don't want to.
Ay, this punk.
Your  pretentiousness is still a big problem.
You have to admit that I have some loyalty, right?
Loyalty, my ass.
Hurry up and pour it.
Fill it up.
- Dong Gyu.
- Yes, Hyung.
You—
Make sure to call me when you get married, okay?
Yes.
All this time,
you've really gone through a lot.
And hey, after you get married, quit acting like such a smart ass.
I put up with your crap because I'm cool like that.
Dad, I'll see you later.
Okay.
Ra Il, go outside for a little bit while Dad and I talk.
Since you're awake now, I'm going to go.
Mother-in-law
told me to stay only until you woke up.
Mother-in-law will take care of your discharge from the hospital.
Let's talk when you get discharged.
Don't ever
do something like this again.
act like a coward again.
I'm leaving.
I hope business goes well.
Are you going alone?
Yeah. I have to.
Take care. And I ask that you please take care of my employees.
I just want to ask you one thing.
If, let's say...
If Ji Eun Dong had never existed in this world,
would you have given your heart to me?
Why would Ji Eun Dong not exist in this world?
If I was born into this world,
it's only fate that Eun Dong would automatically follow.
If she never existed, then I probably wouldn't be here either.
- Aren't you nervous about leaving that woman behind?
- No.
I'm not worried
because we will definitely meet again.
That's how it is for us.
Take care of yourself.
He's arrived! He's here!
Ji Eun Ho! Ji Eun Ho!
Just a moment. Just a word! Just one statement! Can you open your window?
Please give us some statements.
All of you are working so hard. Let's go inside my house and talk.
Pardon?
This situation is entirely my fault.
That woman and that child are victims.
And the claim that she is your first love...
Then what about that book?
All of that, I guess that was just me wasting time being foolish and kidding myself.
It's true, this was all of my own doing.
Is the child your son or Choi Jae Ho's son?
He is that man's son.
Please treat it as if I was just acting crazy on my own, and  let's just put an end to this incident.
The child and the woman didn't do anything wrong.
Hello, Ms. Writer.
You came.
We had all of your pictures taken down, but there will probably be some people who will still recognize you.
Please hang in there just a little longer. Soon everything will be forgotten.
Alright.
Eun Ho liquidated all of his assets,
but he insisted on buying a house for you to live in.
There are a lot of empty houses that have been put up for sale close to where you live right now.
What is Oppa doing right now?
The company is causing him an extraordinary amount of problems.
Remember last time I told you about President Hwang, that guy who left behind his entire mess for Eun Ho to deal with.
I swear, if we ever catch him...
Hello?
Oppa.
Yeah.
It's really nice here.
Really? That's such a relief.
You must be crazy busy because of everything going on with the company. Make sure to eat properly.
Of course.
I will contact you as soon as I move in. I'll be able to see you then, right?
I feel so awful that you're having such a hard time. Is there anything I can do for you?
No, there isn't. Don't worry, I took care of everything.
That's a relief.
Eun Dong.
Yeah?
You can't get sick, alright?
Why are you saying that? You sound like someone who's planning to leave all of a sudden.
Oppa.
Hmm?
I will call you as soon as I'm done packing everything up.
Oppa, call me as soon as you're done dealing with all of the company  business. Got it?
Y-Yeah.
Do you think I'll ever be able to buy this house back?
I bought this house for me and Eun Dong to live in together.
Who bought the vacation house?
Someone who runs a clothing business in Nam Dae Moon.
I gave him your message not to alter the house too much.
Told him there was a chance you might return and buy back the house.
Okay. You did well.
Did the article come out?
Yes.
Do you think that it will be enough for people to leave Eun Dong and Ra Il alone?
Yes. I think so.
Oh Hyung. Here.
This is for a language practice course. While you're over there, please take the opportunity to study English.
If you don't, you might encounter problems with your visa status.
You didn't tell Eun Dong that I was leaving, did you?
No. You told me not to.
If she finds out, I'm afraid she might insist on leaving with me.
Then, you can leave together.
What about Ra Il?
My father said that... He said I am not a father yet.
That's why I am doing this. So I can become a real father.
Do you have any idea, man? This was a huge decision for me. It wasn't easy.
I know, Hyung.
The last thing on my list, there's a place I want to visit.
Hyung. It really has been a long time, hasn't it?
That's right.
- Eun Dong! Have a good time.
Yes, I will!
Hey kid.
If you meet that Oppa,
tell him not to worry too much.
Tell him everything will work out fine.
Yes.
My Love Eun Dong
Eun Dong, by the time you read this letter,
I will probably no longer be in Korea.
When I look at you and when I look at Ra Il,
it will be hard for me to leave Korea,
and even harder for me to leave alone,
so I'm just moving forward with this decision.
My love Eun Dong,
for giving birth to my son, raising him for ten years,
and for coming back into my life, I'm so extremely grateful.
But right now,
we have no choice but to be separated like this.
For me, who waited for ten years,
this short time will probably be nothing.
We will surely meet again,
because that is our fate.
Even if you and I were on Mars and Venus, separated on different planets,
we would be fated to meet again.
That's why I am not scared of any such things.
I will become a good dad for Ra Il.
I really want to do that.
You don't even ask if I want any?
Do you want to try some?
Oppa, did you sleep well?
Hurry and wash up.
For giving me the blessing of loving just one woman my entire life.
I'm deeply moved by you.
That one thing alone makes me feel like I've had a successful life.
Eun Dong, this time,
you must come and find me, okay?
But you know what, Eun Dong?
Even now, I miss you so much.
I love you.
Oppa, I was grateful.
I won't ever forget.
I still have the sneakers Eun Dong gave me.
In the topmost space of the shoe rack,
all beat up and tattered,
still dirty from wear.
♫  Your  ♫
The reason is because I truly love you.
♫  Eyes glittering like stars  ♫
It's because you're you.
♫  Your voice softly blowing in like a breeze  ♫
Just because you're you.
Who are you? Eun Dong?
-Eun Dong!
-If Eun Dong sees that drama,
♫  It remains  ♫
I'd be handsome as always.
♫  with me   ♫
More than that time 10 years ago,
♫  like it was yesterday  ♫
though I've gotten older, I'd be the same as ever.
♫  Like it was yesterday  ♫
I'm sure
♫  It seems like I won't be able to  ♫
that it will be the same feeling from 10 years ago.
♫  see you again  ♫
Eun Dong.
♫  It seems like I won't be able to see you again  ♫
There's a chance she may love you even more.
♫  You passing me by, pretending not to notice,
causes me such pain  ♫
Just a little more. A bit more.
♫  Always  ♫
Try to wait.
♫  and everywhere  ♫
Eun Dong...
♫  the image of you I loved
is a shining ray of sunlight  to me  ♫
♫  The image of you I loved is a shining ray of sunlight  to me  ♫
♫  Now it seems like you won't come back again  ♫
Why did she live like that?
♫  you won't come back again  ♫
And  so far away...
♫  You who's forgotten me  ♫
I felt happy while I was writing your book.
♫  it seems I can't catch you  ♫
It feels just as if...
♫  Just as if it was the first time we met,
without a word, the moment passes  ♫
♫  Just as if it was the first time we met, without a word, the moment passes  ♫
What do you think of me?
Are you scared right now?
Are you scared again? You must be thinking a lot of thoughts that you don't want anyone to discover.
Is that so?
Yes, that's right.
I like that person so much, I feel like I'm going  crazy.
I really feel like I'm going crazy.
Just thinking about that person makes me feel like my heart is going to burst.
- It keeps getting harder for me to get through the day.
- Your husband...
Do you love him?
- Yes.
- When that person is next to me,
he comes directly into my heart.
Without so much as a knock, he walks right in.
That feeling... I really like it.
♫  This unbelievable moment right now, my heart is aching  ♫
I like that man.
My heart jumps whenever I see you.
The fact that you have a husband,
okay. Fine, I'll accept it.
What am I supposed to do when I can't forget about you?
You were originally my woman from the start.
Let's just keep trying until the very end,
until one of us dies.
You have to come back.
Didn't I tell you she would come back if you waited?
And then what?  When she lives with another man?
When she has another man's son?
When she doesn't even remember me...
Please find Eun Dong for me.
I'm asking this of you.
♫  have passed  ♫
♫  When you shed painful tears in front of me  ♫
I love you.
I was unable to say these words to you
before we became separated.
Holding onto these words for ten years
in my heart,
has been incredibly hard on me.
I almost died, you know!
Eun Dong
I love you.
Even now, I miss you so much.
Your goof-off slacker, Park Hyun Soo.
Take care of yourself.
Please let me  see Ra Il every once in a while.
I'll explain things to him slowly, over time.
Alright.
I'll do that. Let's do that.
Jung Eun.
I'm sorry.  I loved you.
I thought that if I loved you then you would have to love me as well,
but I became resentful because that didn't happen.
All of my wrongdoings where I had acted out of anger, I thought  I was done paying the price for all of that.
But I think there's still a lot left to make up for.
I was foolish and mistaken.
It's all in the past now.
It will all be forgotten.
Please forgive me.
Okay.
You
helped raise Ra Il so flawlessly and spotlessly.
No, actually, you created half of Ra Il.
I'll make sure there is a place left for you as Ra Il's father.
I'll contact you as soon as the papers start getting processed.
Okay.
Choi Jae Ho!
"Ji Eun Ho and Seo Jung Eun, Their Love is Genuine"
'Exclusive Interview With Choi Jae Ho, Former Baseball Player Who Attempted Suicide'
Ten years ago, I fell in love with a certain woman.
That woman was carrying another man's child,
and she loved that man like crazy.
It was impossible for me to tolerate,
because that woman didn't love me.
So out of anger, I forced that woman into my car and started speeding down the street like a maniac.
That's how we got into the accident.
That's how I became disabled and how that woman lost her memory.
- And she lived as my wife for ten years.
- Hyun Soo Oppa...
Oppa
That woman gave birth to that man's child.
And with that, we became a family.
But ten years later, that man appeared
to search for the woman he loved.
That woman is in fact Ji Eun Dong and that man is Ji Eun Ho.
The two of them had genuinely loved each other.
This is the truth.
1 year later
Not bad!
- Throw it, let's see what you've got!
- Yah!
- Oh!
- Very good!
-   Arigato! (thank you  in Japanese)
Okay great. This time then, I'm going to throw it up high.
- Yah! I got it!
- You got it?
- Yah! Uh yoo!
- See, you can do it now that I've taught you.
- Open it! Open it all the way!
- I opened it!
So, you were just listening patiently and holding it all in?
Violence is bad, so I didn't hit him,
but just to make sure he doesn't say anything like that  again, I gave him a piece of my mind.
You did well!  I've got to say, my son is pretty cool.
Come on, whose son am I?
Ra Il, you know that you have another dad besides me, right?
Yup.
People don't all live the same way.
Each person has a different way that they love and different situations they face.
I know. I guess it would be nice having two dads.
I'm going to be cool from now on and just acknowledge it.
Ra Il, if you happen to meet with your other dad again, then call him Dad, okay?
You'll do that, right?
If I ever see him, I'll do that. Dad, if you tell me to do it, I will.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Starting today, I'm going to sleep at your house.
Mom is all over the place lately because she's trying to write.
Really?
I'm Park Jung Eun! What is wrong with you?
Where would I have another synopsis?
I don't know, whatever then! Just forget it!
Ms. Writer.
There's a synopsis I've been working on for a while.
- What?
- Would you like to take a look?
- Mi Na!
- You've arrived!
- Grandpa!
- Aigoo ya.
- Hello.
- Aigoo, look at our baby.
- Father, please take a seat. You too Mom, sit down.
- Let's go and sit.
Wow, you've prepared a lot of food!  Oh, it's seaweed soup.  Did you make it?
- Nope.
- Oh, Ajumma made it.
Nope. Ra Il's mom did.
Oh yeah?
You know how it's Oppa's birthday on Saturday. Ra Il's mom,
she also left this note.
Father and Mother,
Thank you for giving birth to Hyun Soo Oppa.
I felt sorry and anxious about meeting with you, so I am just leaving behind this food I made for you.
Please be healthy.
Hey, then you should have told her to stay.  Why would you let her just leave like that? Sometimes, you are just really...
Oh! How can it be this delicious?
This is the first time I've tasted such delicious seaweed soup!
Wow, she really knows how to cook.
The seaweed soup tastes good.
- Eat a lot.
- Yes.
Mom, you completely forgot it was Oppa's birthday, didn't you?
No way! Why would I forget?
- It looks like you forgot...
- No, I didn't!
Do you have any actors or role models you admire?
I consider Kim Yoon Suk to be my role model.
Ah you're a Kim Yoon Suk fan? I'm a Kim Yoon Suk fan too! I'm happy to meet you.
They're here?
Kim Han Chul, Hong Chi Hwan, Kim Emma. What a snore-fest.
Start off by changing your names.
What in the world is  ki-man chuh-lee ?  (=  dealing with deception ; wordplay of Kim Han Chul) One controversy with betrayal and your popularity as an actor will be over. Complete shutdown.
And what are you going to shut down? Are you  Madame Aema ? (= a.k.a. Mrs. Emma, an erotic movie from 80s)
You know those actor names that hook you as soon as you hear them, like Ji Eun Ho. Ji Eun Ho.
Eun Ho!
- Eun Ho, that knucklehead, when is he coming?
- Ta-da! I'm picking him up tomorrow.
Hello. Welcome.
- Did you see Ji Eun Ho?
- Yeah!
He's  daebak (amazingly)   good-looking, isn't he? Omo, what do I do?
Did you see him? Ji Eun Ho, Ji Eun Ho!
Mr. Ji Eun Ho...
Are you on your way back to Korea?
When you go back to Korea, you're going to continue acting, right?
What are you doing? It's okay, he likes it!
Ah, I'm tired, tired! I feel horrible! How could I have been sitting in economy...
So embarassing. Hey!
Who's the actor and who's the manager?
Isn't it true that you had retired? Ahjussi, don't forget you're not an actor any more.
Aigoo, a jerk like you... I could just...
It was my mistake, asking you to come meet me.
It's not like I got injured because I wanted to!
Who said anything?
You've been going on and on, complaining this entire time!
It's because I'm utterly exhausted.
Hey, for ten hours I was sitting, trapped like this, as if I was stuck in a beehive!
I didn't sleep one wink!
Hyung, grab that pen over there for me?
Just constantly ordering me around for everything...
Oh, that feels so good!
Ayoo, ayoo, ugh. How does...
Who in the world drops a frozen piece of meat on his foot and gets injured like that?
I have never seen anyone like you,  ever!
A dummy who's never seen that happen is more ridiculous than the dummy who got injured.
- Ayoo, you can stop now already.
- What did you say, you punk?
Dummy?
Seriously?
This little asshole. I haven't seen you in a while and now what, you're coming up, are you?  Coming up, eh?
It must have been killing you, trying to hold in all that snarkiness while you were over there.
Yeah, now that I'm back, my mouth is starting to open up.
Hyung, admit it, you love being back in Korea, don't you?
Ayoo, ayoo, ayoo.
What am I doing with a guy like you...
Eun Ho. Eun Ho!!
Ayoo, this bastard! Ayoo!
Let me see... You didn't get beaten by kangaroos in Australia, did you?
- You look the same as before.
-  Your jokes are no fun, man.
Hey, bring a glass of iced coffee.
Ayoo.
Okay, okay. Now that you're sitting right here, it finally feels this office has found its groove.
Did you meet up?
No.
You have to get back to work.
I don't know. I just came in because of my visa.
I made  an appointment for us to go see Writer Park Jung Eun.
Hey, I retired! Going back to work, doesn't that seem a bit weird?
I really don't have much desire.
And also, of all the writers out there, why Park Jung Eun?
Why does that woman focus on me so much? Am I the only actor who exists in Korea?
Ay, this is tiring.
Who asked you to appear in anything?
The plan is to produce.
My Love Eun Dong. Let's make a drama.
- What?
- Let's produce it.
Hyung, it smells good, doesn't it?
- Why is the entryway so narrow?
- Bathroom, bedroom...
Hyung. Window.
Ayoo, this is it?
What is this?
Hey, how do you expect me to live in a place the size of a booger?
It's nothing but bright, to me.
Hey, did I or did I not ask you to manage my money well?
What have you guys done with the account I gave you? How... What did you spend the money on?
Did I give you that money to spend it on a house this small?
Hyung, you left us a booger-sized amount behind.
That  booger wasn't  this  booger!
Hyung, really! You know exactly where President spent that money.
- Oh is that so?
- Okay, I understand.
- I'll ask them to transfer you to a bigger space.
- Hey!
Just because you start talking to me in baby talk,  oooh jjoo jjo , you think I'll suddenly stop feeling bad?
This is a problem with your guys' level of sincerity. Sincerity!
Hyung. Really, this was the best I could do!
The size is not what's important. It's your guys' basic  attitude !
The problem is the  attitude !
The start has got to be good for the ending to be good, you punk!
Oooh,  attitude...
Pretty Writer
Editing friend's name.
Eun Dong.
Eun Dong
Since Dong Gyu's foot is injured, looks like I'll be the one giving you rides  for a while.
- Where are we going right now?
- What do you mean, where? We're going to meet a writer.
Writer? Who? Park Jung Eun?
Park Jung Eun once told me about this superstition of hers.  If she's at a production site where the project isn't doing well,
she just needs to rent out a pension and go there to write for about a week.  And then  bam,   it blows up as a hit!
She's in Chuncheon. Let's go meet her.
I think there are a lot of things she wants to hear from you since you're the original author.
Wow, the first person I go to visit after I return to Korea is Writer Park Jung Eun.
Hey, it's been a long time since I've gone to Chuncheon,
and it's funny that I'm going with you, of all people.
You don't think it's the same for me?
Anyway, wow, it really has been a long time since the last time I went to Chuncheon.
The weather is great.
I had no idea you were coming.
This time, I found you Oppa, okay?
You found me well.
How'd you do it?
I planned it with President, to meet you like this, Oppa.
Not bad. It was dramatic.
Your company agreed to produce this drama.
- I heard.
- Also...
Writer Park Jung Eun agreed to give me credit as co-writer.
Really?  That's great.
Our Eun Dong has finally accomplished her dreams.
But
the main character is a woman.
It's a story about how this female character loved one man for twenty years.
The man doesn't know. He only knows about how he loved her.
That woman
loved that man much more, and before he did.
You see, at a young age of thirteen, she knew he was her first love.
Now I know.
So we can't cast you, Oppa.
- Why?
- I heard that you refuse if the main character is a woman.
- Who said that?
- The writer.
Since the topic's come up, let's talk about it.
Despite what you say, there's no doubt the male main character loved the female main character more. How could the woman love him more?
Absolutely not true! The woman loved him so much more.
You want to debate it, who loved who more?
- Okay, sounds good. I'm confident.
- Then from now on,
let's talk about who likes and loves who more.
Any time. I'm going to win that debate.
Okay, promise?
Stamp!
- Promise.
- Okay, promise.
- I'll make a promise too.
- What's that?
What is it? Hey what is it?
Oppa, have you eaten?
Make me home-cooked rice. I want to eat home cooking.
Okay, let's go.
- Not just today either.
- I know.
I'll make it for you, always.
I love you, Eun Dong.