GETAWAY AND GO WITH JANGDOBARI
DO-YEON AND OK-SEOP
RETURNS TO PARIS FROM GIVERNY
THEIR DAY IN PARIS BEGINS
AT A RESTAURANT WITH GREAT VIBES
GETTING DOWN TO BUSINESS,
ENJOYING PARIS
This looks delicious.
The skin is delicious.
JEAN & MARTHE
ENJOY THEIR MEAL TO THE FULLEST
A MUST-DO FOR PARISIANS (?)
What a charming little place.
That's so cool.
FINISHING OFF A MOVIE~!
…OR MAYBE NEXT TIME, HAHA
What will it look like at 1 a.m.?
At 1 a.m.?
-Wow.
-Hurry. Look!
THE EIFFEL TOWER DAZZLES IN WHITE…!
It'll be beautiful even from afar.
DO-YEON AND OK-SEOP SAVORED THE ROMANCE
DEEP INTO THE NIGHT
Even though it's our last day,
we'll make it worthwhile.
We'll have even more fun than yesterday.
Is this where Amélie worked as a waitress
in the movie?
We can see the whole city from here.
STANDING TALL AT MONTMARTRE,
THE HIGHEST POINT IN PARIS
Everyone here is unique in their own way.
That's why it's a joy to watch the people.
REVEALING THEIR FINAL DAY IN PARIS!
TOO FULL OF ADVENTURE TO FEEL SAD
GETAWAY AND GO WITH JANGDOBARI
WOW…
-The bridge and that building…
-Stunning, right?
-It's like the National Assembly building.
-You're right.
That's the Orsay Museum.
Is that the Orsay Museum? No way.
It feels as though time is frozen
in that place.
-How grand is that?
-I know.
It's Notre Dame Cathedral.
Where?
Is that the cathedral?
The pointy building?
That must be it.
NOTRE DAME CATHEDRAL IS KNOWN
FOR ITS POINTY SPIRES
Are you talking about those pointy tops?
Quasimodo's up there, ringing the bell.
AN ICONIC EXAMPLE
OF FRENCH GOTHIC ARCHITECTURE
It's huge.
It's still being reconstructed.
RECONSTRUCTION IS STILL UNDERWAY
AFTER THE FIRE
I bet it'll look cooler at night.
Look at the people standing over there.
We're currently being taken
to the Panthéon,
where famous French figures are buried.
Marie Curie and her husband, Victor Hugo,
Émile Zola, Jean-Jacques Rousseau,
Alexandre Dumas, André Malraux and others
are buried there.
-They're buried there?
-Yes.
Yes, within the Panthéon.
I thought it'd be like a park.
Same here. Like a memorial park.
HISTORICAL FIGURES REST
IN A GRAND BUILDING, NOT IN A PARK
It says "Panthéon" on top.
- EPISODE 8 -
THE THIRD NIGHT WITH MY FRIEND
If I was born in Paris,
I doubt I would've done comedy.
Why not?
I don't know.
What would you have done instead?
I don't think I would've been obsessed
with success.
It just crossed my mind, but who knows?
THEY ARRIVE AT THE RESTAURANT
AFTER A TAXI RIDE THROUGH PARIS!
-This must be it. Let's go.
-Sure.
Follow me.
Nice.
THEY ARRIVE AT A VIETNAMESE RESTAURANT
It has the vibe of a good restaurant.
Even those look super cute.
DECORATIVE ITEMS THAT ADD
AN AUTHENTIC VIETNAMESE TOUCH
I think the owner filled the space
with what they liked.
It's like a gift shop in Mangwon-dong.
I can't wait.
Who knew we'd have pho in France?
Who knew?
We also had pho in Istanbul.
I know, and it was incredible.
It was the best.
People might think it's strange
to have pho in France,
but when France colonized Vietnam,
many Vietnamese people came here
and introduced their food.
I prefer beef pho.
I heard it was really popular.
We'll have the beef pho, then.
Sweet.
-Let's have this since it's something new.
-Sure.
Sure. Banh mi chao.
Banh mi chao and…
Pork works.
-She's so sweet.
-I know.
I can't wait. I bet it'll be good.
I'd love to just drink the broth.
That's ours.
-Let's share.
-Sure.
-Elders first.
-Bao is supposed to be bread.
BANH BAO KEP: STEAMED BUN WITH PORK,
PICKLES, CARROTS, PEANUTS, AND SHALLOTS
I'll enjoy.
Take a big bite.
MMM~
Have some while it's hot.
Is it warm?
It's very warm.
The meat is super moist as well.
The sauce is incredible,
and it has peanuts in it.
There's something fried inside too.
It's so good.
It tastes like jokbal.
You're right.
It's a sweeter take on jokbal.
HIGHLY SATISFIED WITH THEIR FIRST DISH
That's so good. Let's order some drinks.
BANH MI CHAO IS SERVED
-Saigon?
-Yes, Saigon Beer.
This also looks good.
BANH MI CHAO: A WARMER TAKE ON BANH MI,
SERVED IN A HOT IRON PAN
I've never seen this
at a pho place before.
Me neither. I'm glad we ordered this.
-Shall we try some?
-Sure.
Let's try this first.
-It looks like minced meat.
-You're right.
-Various meat--
-There are three cuts of meat.
One looks like pork belly.
Let's try the minced meat first.
Sure. It's the most unusual.
-Have some with the onions.
-Right.
Cheers.
Is it good?
-I don't think it's meat.
-Isn't it?
-Hold on.
-Is it liver?
It's liver.
That's really unusual.
PÂTÉ: A SMOOTH PASTE
MADE FROM GROUND BEEF AND LIVER
The liver just melted in my mouth
before I even chewed.
THEIR PHO IS SERVED
Let's try the other meat.
We'll try that over there.
THE SAIGON BEER IS ALSO SERVED
Is it hot?
HAVING A BITE
AFTER COOLING IT DOWN WITH A BLOW
Isn't it good?
It's so soft.
It's good.
It must be eaten with bread.
It's a baguette.
With the bread, it's kind of like banh mi.
You're right.
With more vegetables, I mean.
THIS TIME, THEY PUT MEAT ON THE BREAD
-Is it good?
-That reminds me of bulgogi.
Careful.
Right?
It's a familiar taste.
-The texture's like bulgogi too.
-Exactly.
CHEERS!
-Is it good?
-It's icy cold.
It's not like the Saigon Beer I remember.
It's not.
BEEF PHO: HANOI-STYLE PHO
WITH HOUSE NOODLES AND RICH AROMATIC BROTH
-Should I add the spicy chili?
-I'd love that.
ADDING SOME VIETNAMESE CHILI
Should I squeeze the juice in?
Maybe just a little.
ADDING SOME LIME JUICE
-Let's try the broth.
-Sounds good.
That's a rich broth.
I'm glad we added the chili.
It's nice and spicy.
It's good.
It's rich but not heavy.
It's similar to the pho we've had,
but a bit different.
In what way?
I like how the broth is richer.
I'd crave this broth
while getting over a cold.
I bet I'll sweat the cold off right away.
Try the noodles too.
None of the food here
is particularly greasy.
You often find yourself wanting kimchi
with meals when traveling abroad,
but this feels like beef radish soup.
We even had some bulgogi.
(MEAT + NOODLES TOGETHER)
-The meat is also nice.
-Right.
What are you most thrilled about today?
Visiting the burial site.
What part of it
are you looking forward to?
At the burial site?
I wonder how it'll feel to see
the building up close for the first time.
The Panthéon, was it?
When I first heard about a burial site
for historical figures,
I thought it'd be an ordinary building
with a graveyard like a park.
-Cremation wasn't allowed in the past.
-No.
It's fascinating how the burial site
has a look similar to a charnel house.
It looks like a temple.
There are several options,
including a grave,
-a woodland burial,
-That's right.
and cremation.
What would you choose?
I've always wanted my ashes
to be scattered in the sea
instead of being buried in one place.
I still want that,
but I'm also considering
my loved ones' wishes for me.
If my remains or ashes are set
in one place,
-they could--
-They could visit you.
I'm not sure if it's better
to give them a place to mourn
or to let them think
my soul is free to wander.
Is it legal to scatter ashes in the sea?
In the sea? They do that in movies.
I should check what's legal.
That's why I considered
a woodland burial instead.
Under a tree.
You try to think about death
as often as possible.
-Right.
-What prompted you to do that?
Every morning,
you wake up to news of unexpected events
and accidents that happened overnight,
any of which could easily happen to you.
I read somewhere
that there's no specific reason
why freak accidents happen.
They just happen.
Finding a reason only deepens the pain.
But we're wired
to ask why things happen to us,
or to believe we didn't do anything wrong
to deserve it.
However, now that I realize
there's no reason for things happening…
It's like you've accepted it
before it even happened.
I'm training myself to get there.
This is so good.
I feel as if we had Korean food.
I know.
When abroad,
Asian food serves as a good alternative
to Korean food.
It's the best.
In Istanbul, we had Asian food
at the perfect time.
I learned to treasure pho.
CHUGGING
(THE PRECIOUS BROTH)
-Let's go.
-Sure.
Thanks for the meal.
THEY FILLED UP ON PHO IN PARIS
I feel great now that I'm full.
This is also a vlog with closed captions.
-Right now--
-Friends aren't usually on camera.
-Only parts of their bodies are shown.
-Like this?
I'll place a smiley sticker
over your face in the video.
Right now,
we're following the line that runs
from Notre Dame Cathedral
along the Seine.
For lunch, we had pho.
The pho we had in France was memorable,
but mostly…
They're like the rats from Ratatouille.
-They're so cute.
-So cute. What are you looking at?
Is that bug in the painting or on it?
No way. It got stuck on the painting
and became part of it.
-There's a drawing of a man below.
-There's a man.
This is so cool.
Can you believe these rats?
-They're adorable.
-I know.
-Look.
-Are those toothbrushes?
They're so cute.
Eiffel Tower toothbrushes.
Are you kidding me?
Isn't this a scene from About Time?
-No way.
-Wow.
BRIDE AND GROOM IN AN ADORABLE CART
Gosh.
-It was like a movie scene.
-That was sweet.
THEY ENCOUNTERED A MOVIE-LIKE MOMENT
-No way.
-I have a new dream.
-Doing that?
-Yes.
I want that for my wedding.
I must say,
it feels like living in a dream.
What kind of world do they live in?
What would you like?
How about mango?
That seems to be most popular.
We'll get mango, the most popular flavor.
This is a generous serving.
It's like a small hill.
A BITE
Is it good?
It's so good.
It's so good it makes my eyes widen.
-Boing.
Look!
Modigliani is one of my favorite artists!
You talked about him earlier.
Yes, and this is his painting.
They must make music boxes here.
How fascinating is that?
I feel like they'll start moving
when the lights go out.
Here are the rats we adore.
This is so pretty.
You're right. That's cute.
CUTENESS EVERYWHERE!
There's a heart. Come closer.
-Someone left their mark here.
-Yeah.
There's a bird.
Over here, someone's being asked
-for directions.
-What is this place?
It's fascinating.
There are fun details hidden everywhere.
You're right.
See this over here.
It's a portrait of a woman.
It's so pretty here.
Stand over there.
(SHE DOESN'T FIND IT HARD
BECAUSE SHE'S USED TO SKITS)
Anyone can tell it's not my house.
It's a boat.
-How peaceful is this?
-I know.
HOW PEACEFUL…
What's your take on the gentleman
with the dog?
How sweet is that?
It's a beagle.
He's my kind of guy.
My ideal man is someone
who walks his dog in a suit.
This is adorable.
The locks came all the way here.
THE PADLOCKS FROM MONTMARTRE
ARE HERE AS WELL
We're seeing a lot of hearts today.
I know. This is so cute.
This was hung by Dudu and Bubu.
Dudu and Bubu.
I hope they're still happy.
I hope you're all well
and at peace.
We'll head back
to the Vietnamese restaurant now.
See you later at the cemetery.
PARIS VLOG, THE END!
VIETNAMESE RESTAURANT, A 20-MINUTE DRIVE,
PÈRE-LACHAISE CEMETERY
So, we enjoyed the pho.
I don't know if it's right
to go here next,
but the well-fed living are on their way
to a cemetery.
It's where your favorite writer,
Balzac, is buried.
How does it feel being a fan of his work?
I've never gone to a memorial park
when traveling abroad,
but this time I wanted to.
Kim Cho-hee,
the director of Lucky Chan-sil,
visited Japan
and tended Yasujiro Ozu's grave,
pulling weeds and wiping his tombstone…
-Really?
-…out of admiration.
I came across a video
where she shared the experience.
Just hearing that cleansed my heart.
I may not be able to pull weeds
or wipe anything clean, but--
You need tools to pull out weeds.
-She used her bare hands.
-That's admirable.
Her love and admiration for him were clear
just from how she cleaned his tombstone.
I suggested coming here,
as I wanted to visit Balzac's grave
during my time in Paris.
I like the idea of doing something
"while we're at it"
or "since we're already doing it."
Because anything we do in the moment
will be okay, even if it doesn't go well.
He gave me so much already.
Is paying tribute to him
your way of giving back?
I'm doing it to feed my own soul.
That's how we all are.
It's my first time
visiting the grave
of someone I never personally knew.
You came all the way to Paris to do that.
If there's any trash on the ground,
I'll pick it up.
I'll be as kind as Amélie.
Nice.
THEY'RE ALMOST AT THEIR DESTINATION
Wow, it's so big.
Is this it?
THEY ARRIVE AT THE PÈRE-LACHAISE CEMETERY
PÈRE-LACHAISE CEMETERY
It's this way.
-No way.
-It's vast.
Tell me about it.
Wow.
The cemetery must be spacious.
But of course.
Let's keep it down.
We'll remain quiet to honor the deceased.
THE LARGEST CEMETERY IN PARIS
THAT ALSO BREATHES HISTORY AND CULTURE
HERE LIE THE REMAINS OF MANY ARTISTS
INCLUDING BALZAC, OSCAR WILDE,
CHOPIN, MOLIÈRE, LA FONTAINE,
DELACROIX, AND MODIGLIANI
AROUND 70,000 TOMBS
ABOUT A MILLION PEOPLE ARE BURIED HERE
WHERE PARISIANS ARE LAID TO REST
WITH GREAT NAMES IN HISTORY
MOLIÈRE (1622~1673)
THE GREATEST FRENCH ACTOR AND PLAYWRIGHT
WHO PERFECTED FRENCH CLASSIC PLAYS
VIVANT DENON (1747~1825)
DIPLOMAT, WRITER, AND ARTIST
WHO TOOK PART IN NAPOLEON'S EXPEDITION
AND SERVED AS THE FIRST DIRECTOR
OF THE LOUVRE MUSEUM
ARMAN (1928~2005)
CONTEMPORARY ARTIST
KNOWN FOR HIS DESTRUCTION
AND REASSEMBLY OF EVERYDAY OBJECTS
There's a map. Let's check it out.
Let's take a photo of it.
So that's how they're marked.
They've been sorted alphabetically.
Hey. There's Balzac.
Number 97.
-Number 97.
-Where is number 97?
Number 91, number 96,
number 97.
I'll take a photo of this.
This is where we are.
-We'll walk straight up.
-It's quite far away.
-We'll walk to the far end.
-Let's visit another person we know.
How about Chopin?
-Number 20?
-Yes.
It's right here.
-In the center.
-I see.
Then…
We'll walk this way, visit Chopin's grave,
and go around this way
to where Balzac rests.
Why don't we go that way?
BALZAC
CHOPIN
I'm going to clear away spider webs
as I go along.
-I'll help.
-Sure.
-I love Balzac's work just as much.
-Right.
The face is covered.
I wonder why.
STATUE WITH FACE COVERED
AND APPEARS TO BE CRYING
Look at what's on our left.
-She looks sad.
-I know.
A MOURNING STATUE
-I feel the pain.
-Me too.
I don't see any numbers on the tombs.
They're just here.
What if those numbers were only
for the map?
WHY DO THE WORST FEELINGS
ALWAYS TURN OUT TRUE?
A MAZE-LIKE CEMETERY WITH NO NUMBERING
THEY WALK…
AND WALK…
DESPITE WALKING SO FAR,
THEY CAN'T SEE CHOPIN'S TOMB
I heard this place was huge,
and it really is.
-Chopin's tomb was in the center.
-Yes.
So we're not even halfway
into the cemetery yet.
This place is massive.
THE SUN IS BLAZING
AND TIME KEEPS PASSING
WHERE DOES CHOPIN REST?
Wait, here's Chopin.
AT LAST, THEY FIND CHOPIN'S TOMB
-He's had so many visitors.
-I know.
He's still loved even after his death.
FRÉDÉRIC CHOPIN (1810~1849)
POLISH COMPOSER AND PIANIST
OF THE ROMANTIC ERA
KNOWN AS A POET OF THE PIANO
FOR WORKS SUCH AS NOCTURNE IN E-FLAT MAJOR
WALTZ IN A-FLAT MAJOR,
AND REVOLUTIONARY ETUDE
Look. Someone placed a candle here.
-Where?
-Here.
FANS HONOR AND REMEMBER CHOPIN
IN THEIR OWN WAYS
She's his wife,
so who's that woman up there?
Maybe she's the wife.
What does she have in her hands?
-It looks like an instrument.
-Really?
CHOPIN'S PROFILE
NOT HIS WIFE
STATUE OF EUTERPE
THE GREEK MUSE OF MUSIC
MOURNS CHOPIN'S UNTIMELY DEATH
WHILE HOLDING A BROKEN LYRE
It's a dog.
I thought a dog was buried there,
but apparently the one buried
was just a dog lover.
If it's possible, I'd like to ask
for a statue of my dog Gyeo-ul.
What about you?
If I could choose
how to decorate my grave,
-I'd choose photos.
-Photos?
I could decide ahead of time
which photos to decorate
-my grave with.
-How about this?
The photo that looks different
depending on the angle.
A hologram?
It'll look like I'm moving in the photo.
-That's not a bad idea.
-You could keep bowing.
THRILLED ABOUT DECORATING THEIR GRAVES(?)
I love it.
This person appears to be
looking at their smartphone.
When has a phone like that been released?
-It's someone's face!
-It's a face!
FERNAND ARBELOT (1880~1941)
THE STATUE OF THIS FRENCH ACTOR
AND MUSICIAN
EXPRESSES HIS DESIRE TO FOREVER GAZE
AT HIS WIFE'S FACE
Is he looking up at his wife?
-No way.
-Now that's bizarre.
DESPITE WHAT YOU MIGHT THINK,
THE STATUE EXPRESSES LOVE
That's not it. Sorry. I was mistaken.
It's Balzac's tomb.
HONORÉ DE BALZAC (1799~1850)
A FOUNDER OF 19TH-CENTURY LITERARY REALISM
I feel strange for some reason.
HIS BEST WORKS INCLUDE THE HUMAN COMEDY,
FATHER GORIOT, THE LILY OF THE VALLEY
I feel funny.
What does it say down here?
Those are the names
of the people buried here.
It's not just Balzac.
-Really?
-Yes, like his wife.
HE RESTS WITH HIS WIFE, HAŃSKA
It's good to know he won't be lonely.
What's fascinating is that the
black-and-white photo of him I saw online
made me think of him as just
a great writer from the past,
but standing at his tomb
reminds me he was once alive.
OK-SEOP LOOKS AROUND THE TOMB
I'd love to get rid of the spider webs,
but I can't seem to.
-I'm embarrassed.
-Do you think that would dishonor him?
-Then honor him with all your heart.
-Sure.
SHE SEEMS DISAPPOINTED
SHE COULDN'T CLEAN HIS TOMB
-Shall we get going?
-Sure.
CONCLUDING THEIR BRIEF
BUT ANTICIPATED VISIT TO BALZAC'S TOMB
We've never been able
to see him in person,
and it feels kind of strange.
Even though we never saw him in real life,
visiting his tomb made it feel
-as if we had.
-Does it seem real?
-We feel like he existed.
-Yes, exactly.
Now he feels like a person
who really existed.
Thinking about classical writers
from the past,
I know we can read their work
because they once lived.
Yet because it was so long ago,
-they feel like mythical figures.
-Exactly.
They really did exist, as it turns out.
Now that we've visited Balzac's tomb,
we'll go to his workroom.
THEY'RE NOW HEADED TO BALZAC'S HOUSE
Taking this feeling with me to his study
will make the visit feel different
from going there
without visiting his tomb first.
Right?
Didn't he live there for seven years?
That's right,
when he was hiding from creditors.
TO THE HOME BALZAC LIVED IN FOR 7 YEARS
WHILE AVOIDING HIS CREDITORS
Visiting Balzac's grave was your dream.
How did it feel to be there?
I wanted to tidy it up a little,
but I couldn't bring myself to do it.
You honored him from the heart.
I imagined myself
clearing away the spider webs.
Good.
Why couldn't I do it?
I was amused by our conversation earlier.
We were able to truly grasp
that he had once been alive
when we stood at his grave.
His death proves he once lived,
and that's an amusing way
to think about it.
I bet Balzac's studio is a lot different
from Monet's house.
-I'm excited to see how it differs.
-Same here.
As you know,
Paris has been home to many artists.
Of all of them, why did you choose
to visit Balzac's grave?
The reason is simply
my annoyingly pure love and admiration
for his work.
The Lily of the Valley, right?
Yes.
Two people forbidden to be together
end up falling in love.
Holding back her feelings for him
leads to her death.
That's right.
The longing and love
are depicted so movingly
that they reached me,
even here alive in the 2020s.
I know, it's fascinating.
Balzac, too,
longed for and waited for
the woman he loved.
I think it was his pure love
that drew me in.
SHE FELT DRAWN TO HIS PURE LOVE
Are you mostly at your studio?
Yes, I sometimes work from home,
but I'm more motivated at the studio.
Getting some fresh air
during my commute and all that
is how I stay energized.
About a month or two ago,
we splurged a little
and bought a desk each.
-The same one.
-Yes, the same one.
Of all the items I've bought,
that was the most expensive.
Same for me.
It was way out of my price range.
That's why I want to see Balzac's desk.
I'm curious too.
I bet his setup's pretty minimal.
-I agree.
-I doubt it's extravagant.
Only a poor craftsman blames his tools.
I wonder
if he kept a lot on his desk
or if it was mostly empty.
I wonder how it was.
HOW DID HE KEEP HIS DESK?
We're here.
BALZAC'S HOUSE
"Maison de Balzac."
-Are you nervous?
-Well…
It's like going
to a friend's birthday party.
-Really?
-Yes.
"He's such a gifted writer
and wins awards at writing competitions."
That makes me think strange things like,
"I wonder what his room is like?"
-How is that strange?
-Finally, I'm getting to see it.
This must mean, Balzac's house.
MAISON = HOUSE
DIFFERENT VERSIONS OF BALZAC
GREET THEM AT THE ENTRANCE
DRAWING OF BALZAC
BY BENJAMIN ROUBAUD, THE 19TH-CENTURY
LITHOGRAPHER AND CARICATURIST
Where's the rest of his hair?
A CUTE LITTLE SCULPTURE OF BALZAC
SHOWING HIS RECEDING HAIRLINE
Look, this is adorable.
That's really well made.
Look how cool this is.
I heard he didn't look as funny
as people make him seem.
-Check this out.
-Oh, no.
-No way.
-This is so cool.
Isn't that lovely?
QUIRKY AND UNIQUE SCULPTURES
His desk is tiny.
BALZAC'S DESK WAS MORE MODEST
THAN THEY HAD EXPECTED
Ours…
-is about four times bigger.
-Let's return them.
His desk is so small.
I sort of knew it would be.
That's where he wrote all those books.
SEEING HIS DESK ONLY DEEPENED
THEIR ADMIRATION FOR HIM
How many years did he spend writing
at this desk?
THE MANUSCRIPT WRITTEN AND REVISED
BY BALZAC
He used this for 25 years.
Just the chair.
He used the desk for 10 years,
and the chair for 25.
How could he use the same chair
for 25 years?
That's amazing.
THE CHAIR THAT HELD BALZAC
THROUGH 25 YEARS OF JOYS AND SORROWS
Let's try reading this
with the translator app.
THIS BALZAC FAN IS CURIOUS
ABOUT MANY THINGS
I wrote for 19 hours yesterday and
will have to write 20 or 22 hours today.
I'm neck deep in writing manuscripts
I have 16 to 20 pages to complete,
revisions and all.
Le Constitutionnel printed all my work,
and I still need to write more.
That's why I can't leave this desk.
He had to write for 20 hours.
Yes, 20 to 22 hours.
-He wrote 16 to 20 pages…
-He was amazing.
AN INSANE WORKLOAD
Let's look over here.
Is she the woman he longed and waited for?
EWELINA HAŃSKA
A POLISH NOBLEWOMAN AND BALZAC'S MUSE
THEY FINALLY MARRIED,
BUT BALZAC DIED 5 MONTHS LATER
She married Balzac
only after her previous husband died,
but Balzac died shortly afterward.
If you compare their story
to The Lily of the Valley,
she would be the equivalent
of Lady Mortsauf.
NOW THAT THEY KNOW
ABOUT BALZAC'S LOVE LIFE
THEY UNDERSTAND THE BOOK MORE DEEPLY
THERE'S A LOT TO SEE IN HIS STUDY
"I'm a huge fan,
and The Human Comedy
is disgustingly good."
I think that's a compliment.
I think so.
Isn't that what we saw earlier?
BALZAC'S FAN ENJOYS HER TIME
Did he limp?
Perhaps he used a cane
since he was quite a large man.
-Let's read this as well.
-Sure.
EXPLORING THE STUDY,
CAREFULLY READING THE DESCRIPTIONS
Wow.
NEXT IS A ROOM
DISPLAYING LITHOGRAPHS OF CHARACTERS
What am I seeing?
Wouldn't they be the characters
that Balzac created?
-From his stories?
-Yes.
-He introduces countless characters.
-Exactly.
He reused a lot of them in various books.
THE HUMAN COMEDY
IS THERE ANY CHARACTER I RECOGNIZE…?
It feels unique
to have them shown this way.
What a spread, right?
I guess they drew inspiration
from Balzac's style for this one.
Why don't we read this?
This is a list of characters
from The Human Comedy.
He introduces about 2,500 characters.
Fascinating, right?
"Who became monsters…"
They must be called monsters
because they're distorted in some way.
Wasn't there a comment saying
The Human Comedy is disgustingly good?
-That's the best compliment ever.
-Completely.
The Human Comedy.
OK-SEOP CAME TO VISIT BALZAC
DO-YEON ALSO CAME TOGETHER, THEN LEFT.
THEY END THE BALZAC TOUR
BY WRITING IN THE VISITOR'S LOG WITH LOVE
GETTING SOME COFFEE
AFTER AN INTERESTING TOUR
There's no A/C here.
I actually prefer that.
HOT GREEN TEA, ICED CAFE LATTE
Are you fine with hot green tea?
Fight fire with fire.
Have some ice cubes if it gets too hot.
THEY HAPPILY PICK UP THEIR DRINKS
That looks refreshing.
Sure. Help yourself.
What do you think of us enjoying
coffee and tea in front of Balzac's house?
I never even dreamed of this.
HOW ADORABLE, HEHE
Before coming here, you said
this was what you were most excited for.
You were most curious about Balzac's desk.
What did you think when you saw it?
-It was modest as expected.
-Yeah.
-He sat with his back toward the window.
-I know.
I sit facing the window, so I often end up
gazing outside and spacing out.
You said you didn't want your desk visible
as soon as someone walks in,
so you placed it deeper in the room.
Meanwhile, Balzac's was right by the door,
turned away from the window.
This was also memorable.
He once spent a day working 17 hours…
But he had to work 20 to 22 hours
the next day.
Today and the next day.
He had to write for 20 hours straight,
-and that…
-Amazing, right?
Visiting his grave made us realize
he truly lived,
and we felt it even more at his home.
I still can't believe
he actually wrote at that desk.
Were you amazed to see it?
It's hard to believe
he was a real, living person.
-Even though you saw his study?
-Exactly.
It's mind-blowing.
After visiting Monet's House,
we talked about the importance
of an inspiring space.
-Yet in that small study,
-He wrote a lot.
Balzac created many of his masterpieces.
Compared to Monet's house, his is small.
Also,
Monet's house was surrounded by nature
and felt open and spacious.
Meanwhile, Balzac worked
in a small, square-shaped room.
Who would've imagined?
-Now…
-Now?
What do you want to do?
Didn't you say you wanted to go
to Pont Neuf?
That dream of yours
will come true.
Keep saying it out loud.
That way, it'll come true.
Since we're going to Pont Neuf,
we'll teleport there,
and reappear with a poof.
-Do we stand?
-Let's head to Pont Neuf.
On the count of three, we'll teleport.
-Do we jump?
-Yes.
One, two, three.
-Poof.
This is Pont Neuf. Goodness me.
It's pretty.
PONT NEUF BRIDGE
-Sweet.
-Don't you think
they all have different expressions?
You're right. That's so cool.
We're at Pont Neuf,
the place we'd only heard about.
Being here at Pont Neuf
makes me want to watch
The Lovers on the Bridge.
It would be a joy to watch.
I don't know why I never watched it.
-I bet you'll like it.
-Right.
I ask because you're a filmmaker.
As you know,
this bridge has been in many movies.
Let's capture this view
of the bridge right here.
What scene would you set against it?
Any ideas?
The Lovers on the Bridge was so iconic
that it's hard to imagine
another scene here.
It's like how that hill scene
in Léon: The Professional,
where she walks up carrying a plant,
made it impossible
for anyone else to do it better.
No other scene here
could ever top that iconic moment
from The Lovers on the Bridge.
I'm saying I'm drawing a blank.
Here's what I was meaning to ask.
Since the scenery is beautiful as it is,
would you choose to pair it
with a sad scene
or one that contrasts its beauty?
Or would you
save this scenery for a scene so beautiful
that the view would make it even better?
When I write a story,
I like to film in places
I've seen firsthand.
What's an example of that?
I did that for Your Country.
Anyway, at this bridge?
Nothing's coming to me yet.
That's your assignment.
Got it.
The deadline is whenever
you figure out an answer.
Get back to me on that when you can.
I'll try to answer over dinner.
PEOPLE CROSSING THE PONT NEUF
UNDER THE AFTERNOON SUN
Isn't there a nearby restaurant
from a movie you enjoyed?
Yes, from Me Before You.
I watched that movie when I was
going through a hard time in my life,
and I watched it again
just to have an excuse to cry.
The movie only lasts two hours,
but I still had feelings
I needed to get out of my system,
so I bought the book afterward.
Was the book better?
I enjoyed the book more
because I could imagine the scenes better,
even though I had watched the movie.
When I was watching the movie,
I really wanted to visit the place
since it looked nice.
Which part of the movie
has the restaurant scene?
The two main characters
are deeply in love,
but the ending is quite sad.
There's a scene that brings
the whole movie together,
where Louisa reads the letter
the man left for her.
-She reads it at this cafe.
-At this cafe?
If you watched the movie
hoping the main characters
would stay together in the end,
you're heartbroken by this scene.
But because Louisa had
to move on with her life…
She reads it with the strength
of a champion, you see.
She doesn't cry or fall apart
while reading his letter.
She reads it calmly.
In that moment,
I felt like Louisa would be okay
and able to move on.
Is that why you wanted to go to this cafe?
No, just since we're here.
Tell me this isn't lucky.
I'd love to try what they serve.
I bet it's delicious.
FILMING LOCATION OF ME BEFORE YOU
RESTAURANT PAUL
Here she comes.
Beer and…
Jade Blonde, one.
She's so sweet.
She made my day.
Ravioli and tartare.
Beef tartare.
She's stunning.
THEY ORDER IN GOOD SPIRITS,
THANKS TO HER SMILE
This is why we should smile more.
She made my day.
ARMED WITH A SMILE
CHUCKLING…
(HURT)
I'm a lady in one of Renoir's paintings.
(SOMETHING… LIKE THIS?)
You're freaking me out. Look away.
You kind of look like Pinocchio.
Since it's a painting.
-This time, I was filming a scene.
-Sure thing.
You should watch Me Before You sometime.
You'd recognize this restaurant
and be happy to see it.
-Does she sit outside?
-Yes.
She sits right about here
and reads the letter.
-I remember seeing it from this angle.
-Really?
SHE REMEMBERS VIVIDLY
I'd only seen this cafe in a movie,
and now I'm here.
We watched Four Nights of a Dreamer
-in May.
-Exactly.
And now we're at the Pont Neuf.
The Pont Neuf,
much like the Eiffel Tower,
is a beautiful place to visit,
romantic in every sense.
However, the film opens
with the female lead attempting suicide.
It was eerie to me somehow, and I wondered
what inspired the director to do that.
It's fascinating to be here.
When I watch movies in the future,
I'll imagine myself
going there someday.
You're right.
-Something tasty is on its way.
-Really?
-Is it ours?
-Yes.
FIRST, BEER TO QUENCH THEIR THIRST
What's that? This is a Monaco.
Enjoy.
MONACO
JADE BLONDE
QUENCHING THEIR THIRST
CHUGGING DOWN
Oh my.
This isn't sweet at all.
-It's so good.
-This is also good.
It only smells sweet.
-This is my kind of beer.
-Really?
PERFECT TO DO-YEON'S LIKING!
It's lightly carbonated and smooth.
THEY TRY EACH OTHER'S DRINKS
-It's mildly sweet.
-Really?
This is the life.
It still feels surreal.
Here's what I thought
about Four Nights of a Dreamer.
Falling for the person who saved you
is a typical love story.
But that movie was different.
The guy falls in love
with the woman he saved.
He gets lost in a fantasy
and pines for her.
-That--
-They came up with a clever title.
-It only lasted four nights.
-Right.
Did we stay here for four nights,
or was it three?
-We stay for three.
-Is it three?
We're one night short
of becoming a dreamer.
For us, it's Three Nights of a Korean.
That sounded like Korean Dining Table
or Documentary 3 Days.
What was the theme of our trip again?
Eating, drinking, and friendship.
We ate enough and are now drinking.
So what's the status of our friendship?
EATING, DRINKING, AND FRIENDSHIP?
What I can say for sure
is that I ate well and drank well.
But I'm not sure
where our friendship stands.
What do you mean?
I can confidently say
that we ate delicious food
and enjoyed good drinks on the trip.
But friendship?
-It's hard to discuss an abstract concept.
-Yes, exactly.
-Maybe this question will clarify things.
-What is it?
If you're open
to traveling together again,
then our friendship was good.
But if this trip…
-While we're at it…
-Maybe we've hung out enough.
We even traveled to Paris together,
so maybe it's time to…
Maybe this will be our last.
So, how was it for you?
I'd love to travel with you again.
Why are you saying something nice
in such a lackluster tone?
Because sounding too enthusiastic
-feels corny.
-Is it corny?
You're right. I had a great time.
-It was fun.
It was also a treat to visit
so many places in such a short time.
Think about it.
Just visiting Monet's house in France
would make the trip unforgettable.
Is that what you enjoyed the most?
For me, yes.
We not only went to Monet's house,
but we also visited Balzac's study.
-Even his tomb.
-The Lovers on the Bridge…
Both of them lived in France.
What a wild trip this was.
Truly unbelievable.
Sometimes,
what feels like a dream
ends up becoming real.
Amazing, right? Just live long enough.
We're super lucky.
Just live long enough.
This has to be a dream.
It is.
No, it's not!
AAAAAAAHHHHHH!
FLUSTERED
IF THIS IS A DREAM,
I NEVER WANT TO WAKE UP…
Don't tell me this is a set.
We're not in Sangam-dong, are we?
Who the hell are you?
Are you an actor from Surprise Mystery TV?
THE FOOD SNAPS HER BACK TO REALITY
EMBARRASSED
-Everything looks good.
-See?
You can't go wrong with the food here.
BEEF TARTARE
A CLASSIC FRENCH DISH
OF SEASONED RAW MINCED BEEF
RAVIOLI
A CLASSIC ITALIAN DISH
OF PASTA POCKETS WITH FILLINGS
I'll enjoy. What will you try first?
I'd like to start with the brighter dish
that's not so red.
-The ravioli, then.
-Sure.
Given that Marthe
attempted suicide on the Pont Neuf,
she might have eaten here once as well.
That's possible.
What if she had eaten the food here and…
A BITE
And?
She might've changed her mind
if the food was that good.
There's a reason I'm saying that.
I sometimes watch food review channels.
This is delicious.
I can't recall what the food was,
but I do remember this.
It was described as
"a taste worth living for."
This is how I'd define our trip.
-How?
-"A trip worth living for."
-Really?
-You said before that living long enough
has its perks.
You're right. Just live and you'll see.
Isn't it delicious?
It's like… Is this mushroom?
The smell of the cheese
and mushrooms is amazing.
Anything made with flour here
turns out soft and thin.
Let's try that too.
Yes, let's.
Isn't it like tuna?
The flavors are simple,
but it's nicely tangy.
It's a main dish,
but I'm eating it like a salad.
CAN'T STOP MOVING THEIR FORKS
It's so good.
I'm glad we ordered this.
FLAVORS THAT LEAVE YOU SPEECHLESS
It's so good.
You know how you always feel sad
-at the end of a trip.
-Right.
How do you cope with that?
When I know I'll be going back tomorrow,
I try to find something that excites me
in my everyday life.
Whether it's a gig I'm excited for,
meeting a good friend,
or spending time with my family,
I keep thinking about those things.
I try to force myself
to be excited to go home.
-That's a good idea.
-If there's nothing to look forward to,
I remind myself to plan my next trip soon.
I had such a great time, and working hard
is what lets me go on another trip.
That's what I always tell myself.
What about you?
I feel it through my whole body.
"Damn." Just like that.
YOU'RE SO RIGHT
It's like your entire body is aching.
RETURNING TO EVERYDAY LIFE
IS HARD FOR EVERYONE
If we get to come back,
I wonder what will lead us here.
I'm curious.
Isn't that up to us to decide?
If you had a diary,
what would you put in it?
We mentioned this before, but Balzac wrote
that he had to work 15 hours today
and 20 tomorrow.
Oddly enough, that comforted me.
Even Balzac, as great as he was,
had to meet tight deadlines and recorded
how tough his work was.
I could relate to
what he was going through.
That left me with good feelings
I want to hold on to,
and I'd like to write about that.
-I had a great time.
-It was a lot of fun.
IT WAS EVEN BETTER BECAUSE
THEY SHARED THIS DREAMY 3-DAY TRIP
Now it's time
for the final part of the trip.
-This is how we end the show.
-I know what it is.
We'll write in the travel diary.
It's like this.
Imagine the camera is off,
and write what's in your heart.
In a way, you're the main character
of this diary session
we're about to start.
TRAVEL BUDDY OK-SEOP TAKES THE SPOTLIGHT
IN THIS SEGMENT
I can't resist reading what others wrote.
That can't be helped.
FILLING ONE MORE PAGE IN A DIARY
BRIMMING WITH MEMORIES
THREE NIGHTS IN PARIS WITH TWO DREAMERS
WHO FOLLOWED THEIR HEARTS
THEY FILL THE TRAVEL DIARY
WITH SHARED MEMORIES
LIKE CLOSE FRIENDS,
THEY FINISH AT THE SAME TIME
Done?
I'm too embarrassed
to read it out loud though.
-Then--
-Can't we just read what the other wrote?
Why don't we read what each other wrote?
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
THEY'LL READ EACH OTHER'S WORDS
Who should go first?
-You.
-Me?
"What I received
from the people I met in Paris."
"Balzac worked 17 hours today
and planned another 20 tomorrow."
"Despite the stress, he met his workload
and produced countless works."
"Monet worked in bliss, painting
the garden he created for his art."
"I'd love a garden of my own.
Monet was fortunate to have good friends."
"What would it take
to have a life like Monet's?"
"When filming at Pont Neuf was banned,
Director Leos Carax even built a replica
to complete The Lovers on the Bridge."
"The witty nature of Do-yeon shines
in Getaway and Go with Jangdobari."
"Eating, drinking, and friendship.
Two exclamation marks."
"Let's do this again."
That was clean and simple.
My turn.
"I still can't believe I'm in Paris,
a city I once only dreamed of visiting."
"It's bittersweet knowing
I'll be reluctant to leave,
but that only makes me want
to come back even more."
"In life, I'll see new things,
visit new places, and have experiences
that will motivate me."
"If what I say could come true,
I should make sure to think positively
and imagine good things."
"Instead of being negative,
I'll say I'll go there someday."
"I'm in Paris now.
So my next stop is Greece."
"I will go there someday."
"Greece, here I come."
"I also hope my friend had fun
on her first trip as part of a show."
"Here I am, writing near the table
where Louisa sat in that Paris restaurant
from Me Before You."
I had a blast.
All right.
This is what I do
with a close friend
to greet or say goodbye.
After toasting
to eating, drinking, and friendship,
we'll stand up.
Come over here.
WHAT NOW…
This is what we'll do.
Bounce, tap, bounce, and tap.
1. TAPPING THEIR FEET TOGETHER
Next, lock legs.
Then, hop around in a circle like this.
Got it.
-That's all.
-Sure.
Okay, let's try that.
THE FINAL GOODBYE
DANCING WITH A FRIEND
Okay, I had a great time.
-To eating, drinking, and friendship.
-Friendship.
CHUGGING
Goodness, Marthe.
Don't make me do that.
Bounce, tap, bounce, and tap.
What a blast this was.
That was embarrassing.
THE DREAMLIKE BUDDYMOON ENDS
ON A HIGH NOTE
YI OK-SEOP
JANG DO-YEON, YI OK-SEOP
I wonder what he'll be wearing.
As for me, I'm in my finest clothes.
I've gone on a blind date with him,
dated him,
and even married him.
He's a friend
with the most charming pink gums.
Don't be nervous.
You've got this, Do-yeon.
Do-yeon!
Se-chan!
SEASON 3'S FIRST TRAVEL BUDDY
Looks like I'm going on a date
with Jangdobari.
HE'S STILL AS ATTENTIVE AS EVER
Doesn't this look like my tongue?
Are you asking for a kiss?
Kissing in the middle of the day?
Please close your eyes.
Jangdobari and I are going to smooch.
SHOWING OFF THE CHARM AND DIGNITY
OF THE ORIGINAL STUD
You looked sexy just now.
-Really? Did I seem charming?
-Yes.
FOR SE-CHAN, WHO'S MAKING AN EFFORT
JANGDOBARI REVEALS A NEW SIDE!
THAT'S SO COOL
AND…
-Hey, Se-chan.
-Hey, there.
Hi, Do-yeon.
FRIENDS CELEBRATING THEIR REUNION?
We were on
Comedy Big League together, remember?
LAUGHING SO HARD
THEIR GUMS COULD NEVER DRY
DO-YEON AND SE-CHAN'S
A TRIP DOWN MEMORY LANE IN SEOUL~!
All we lived for was comedy.
Subtitle translation by: Hyelim Park