GETAWAY AND GO WITH JANGDOBARI
Hello. Bound for a breezy break
with bundles of stories in my bag.
I'm Jang Do-yeon
of Getaway and Go with Jangdobari.
Hello, everyone.
I'm greeting you today
from the city of romance and art.
This is Paris.
THE CITY OF ROMANCE
THAT BREATHES CULTURE AND ART
TODAY'S DESTINATION
PARIS, FRANCE
I'm still in disbelief.
I wonder how it is for you.
I often use the phrase "watching
from the front row of your screen."
The Eiffel Tower I was used to seeing
on a screen at home
is now just a few steps away from me.
I'm incredibly excited
since this is my first trip to France,
and to Paris too.
However, part of my excitement
and nerves come from
who my travel buddy is.
Could you take a wild guess
who that might be?
To give you a hint,
since we're in France,
I'll introduce her as my mon amie.
Mon amie. That's "my friend" in French.
We've traveled a lot together,
but Paris is a first for us.
She really loves films,
and also makes them.
She's…
I don't know what to do.
They're adorable.
That's so cute.
YEAH-
PLAYING WITH SOAP BUBBLES
HELPS HER TRAVEL BUDDY RELAX
There are so many people around here.
AWKWARD
TRAVEL BUDDY SPOTTED
I've known her for a few years,
and even though it hasn't been that long,
the time we've spent together has shown me
that she doesn't like
set-ups like this.
Look.
What is she mumbling about?
This is hilarious. Check her out.
She's scratching her leg.
YI OK-SEOP
MOVIE DIRECTOR
DIRECTOR OF MOVIE MAGGIE
WHIMSICAL AND WITTY IMAGINATION
A DIRECTOR DELIVERING
STYLISH VISUALS AND MUSIC
SHE GUEST HOSTED
SALON DRIP 2'S 100TH EPISODE
You two are much closer than I thought.
JEALOUS
-We've known each other…
-But you met over 100 times.
…for about two years.
But we probably got together
over 100 times.
The more time I spent with her,
the more addicted I became.
THE TWO GREW CLOSE, AS THOUGH
THEY WERE ADDICTED TO ONE ANOTHER
THEIR FRIENDSHIP WAS BUILT
BY TRAVELING TOGETHER OFTEN
THEY COLLABORATED AS DIRECTOR AND ACTOR
IN YOUR COUNTRY
How about traveling
with Director Yi Ok-seop?
It'd be nice to see
how you two travel together
and what you talk about.
You want me to travel with someone
I'm already close to, right?
AT LAST, THE TWO ARE TRAVELING TOGETHER
She hates it.
Have a seat.
SLIDING AWAY
It's hilarious to see
how much you hate it.
My stomach hurts from laughing.
Everyone,
here's something you must consider.
I might not have a long career,
but I've done many variety shows,
so I'm used to adding flair and flavor
to the opening of a show.
But Director Yi will find it awkward.
Despite that,
she did her best
sitting here with this picnic basket.
GIGGLING
On that note,
could you please introduce yourself?
To the camera.
Who are you?
Hello, I'm…
HOLDING A BAGUETTE MIC
TO EASE THE AWKWARDNESS
I'm film director Yi Ok-seop.
Thank you for having me on the show.
BOWING
Thank you for agreeing
to travel with me to this faraway country.
First, I think you should tell us
about your outfit of the day.
Those who just tuned in
might think you haven't gotten changed
for the show yet.
Actually, I'm wearing my favorite clothes
from head to toe,
-and I even have my favorite backpack.
-Really?
I made sure to dress properly
for the viewers.
Don't you carry something fun around?
-Can you show us?
-Which one?
There's an item you always carry around.
My Jang Do-yeon goods?
She makes sure to carry around
Jang Do-yeon goods.
-There's also this.
-What is it?
This is what I got at the cafe.
A FAN GIVEN OUT TO CELEBRATE
THE 100TH EPISODE OF SALON DRIP 2
You're eating bread.
-What?
-You're eating bread.
That's me eating bread?
LAUGHING
Shoot.
-Can we expect hilarious jokes today?
-No.
But you just served us one.
-And…
-She stuck it on the basket.
I also have this.
That's also something you carry around.
These are items
she actually carries around.
I couldn't bring the mirror.
Not the mirror though.
That's a relief.
I doubt you're curious about my outfit,
but there's a story behind it.
First of all,
I bought these pants so long ago
I don't even remember when.
Then I heard Bermuda shorts
were back in style.
I'm wearing the pants low on my hips
so the length looks right.
Since my flight was a red-eye,
they gave me a free pair of pajamas,
which just added to my luggage.
The producer told me
to wear the pajamas underneath,
so I did, and voila…
-See?
-It looks trendy.
Don't I look stylish like TARZZAN?
This is how TARZZAN of ALLDAY PROJECT
styles his clothes.
Anyway, that's what I chose to wear,
and here I am.
Do you know
what the theme of this trip is?
I don't.
The theme of this trip is…
You know the movie Eat Pray…
-Love?
-That's the one.
It's a play on that movie's title.
Eat, drink, and friendship.
That's the theme.
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
Honestly,
all I know about Paris
is what I picked up from TV.
I only know bits and pieces
about the city.
Still, if I were given the chance
to go anywhere,
I'd definitely
go to Monet's house
or see his work here in the city,
not anywhere else.
The emotions I'll feel will hit me
on a different level.
As long as I get that chance,
I'll be fine with everything else.
I believe what you wish for will come true
if you say it out loud.
Remember going to the Ueno Royal Museum?
Of course. We saw Monet's work there.
She told me
-she'd love to visit Monet's house.
-Exactly.
I'm amazed it came true so soon.
What's something you want to do in Paris?
I haven't read a lot of his work,
but Balzac is one of my favorite authors.
As you know, he left behind many works.
He's someone I aspire to be like,
and I would like to visit his grave.
So maybe
we'll enjoy Monet's paintings and…
Are you happy overall
with our sightseeing plan
-for Paris?
-Absolutely.
-There's no way it can be a flop,
-Absolutely none.
so don't worry too much.
Besides, even when things don't work out,
they become memories.
That's true.
Anyway, we always set a rule for the trip.
-Decide on one first.
-Me?
What matters to me
is not falling out
over something silly that happens
when working with a friend.
I'm afraid you might see something
you shouldn't.
If either of us thinks
the other has crossed the line,
-let's give some kind of hint.
-I'll text you.
-You'll text me? Got it.
-Yes.
I'm not really worried about anything.
We've traveled together a lot
and know each other's likes and dislikes.
Still, this trip could reveal something
we didn't know about each other.
That's true.
We can change the rules anytime,
but for now,
let's hint at it if either of us
-is close to annoying the other.
-Sure.
-Should we head to our first destination?
We're first going
to the place we mentioned earlier.
-Monet's house?
-That's right.
We'll learn how he lived his life,
-but only after we see his work.
-Sure.
Is there any gallery
that Paris brings to mind?
The Louvre?
Sorry?
CHUCKLING
-Orangerie Museum?
-That's the one.
We're off to the Orangerie Museum.
-Can you do this with me when I say that?
-Sure.
We're off to the Orangerie Museum.
-Can you say it with me?
-Got it.
-We're off to the Orangerie Museum.
-We're off.
-Oh, no.
-Are you regretting this?
Of course not.
Press and wave it around.
FAN
GIGGLING
Let's help him get a cool shot.
Put bubbles in the background.
ADDING BUBBLES TO CREATE A COOL BACKDROP
Let's help him get a cool shot too.
THANK YOU!
-And to these guys.
-Thank you!
That must feel nice.
He looks so good right now.
Wow!
EPISODE 6
CHAMP DE MARS
10-MINUTE DRIVE
ORANGERIE MUSEUM
Hold on a second.
Was the Monet exhibit we saw in Japan
from the Orangerie Museum?
There are so many paintings
in the Water Lilies series.
There's a lot of them?
-During our trip in Paris…
-Yes?
…even though we spoke formally on camera
a few minutes ago,
we'll speak casually
since being good friends
-gives off a certain vibe.
-Sure.
GIGGLING
Instead of me calling you Director Yi
and you calling me Ms. Jang,
let's pick names to call each other
while we're in Paris.
We'll choose one for each other.
Sounds good to me.
Good. What will my name be?
We're in Paris, right?
Hold on.
I get to veto it if it isn't pretty.
-She's saying that because in Japan--
-In Japan,
she called me Sashimi.
Sashimi.
I didn't back down
and kept saying
how we both liked raw fish.
SHE CALLED DIRECTOR YI "SASHIMI"
BECAUSE SHE LIKED RAW FISH SO MUCH
Since then, we stopped
choosing nicknames for each other
on trips.
We're at it again,
-let's go with a good one.
-Anything you'd like to be.
Back in the day, after watching Amélie,
I got my hair cut like the lead actress.
No way. Do you have a photo of it?
It was a disaster.
No, I erased them all.
I'm suddenly reminded of that movie.
Amélie? Well…
The name's a little too long
-to use easily in urgent situations.
-Is it?
How about the one we talked about
on the flight here?
Jang?
-I don't mind that.
-Right.
Jang is my last name,
and Monet and Camille's son was Jean.
-Go with the son's name.
-Jean?
I don't mind that.
I quite like it.
-Call me "Jean," then.
-Sure.
What should be your nickname?
WELL……
Another movie we both like
-is Four Nights of a Dreamer.
-Of a Dreamer?
Call me by the name of the girl
the protagonist likes.
Of course!
I called you that so many times.
Didn't it start with an M or a B?
-I'll look it up.
-Call me by that name.
Got it.
I hear you.
SHE FOUND THE NAME RIGHT AWAY
-Is it Basath?
-No.
"Montmartre" is your clue.
-Remove "mont" from it.
-Martre?
-Marthe.
-Yes, it's Marthe.
-Marthe, got it.
-I like how it sounds gender-neutral.
You left me "marred,"
-so Marthe it is.
-Marthe.
Beginning at our first location,
Marthe and Jean will talk casually
and enjoy the trip like two friends.
This is awesome.
I'm in awe.
Who knew I'd get to visit
the Orangerie Museum?
Merci.
-This must be it.
-In the back?
This is so cool.
THE HOME OF MONET'S WATER LILIES
ORANGERIE MUSEUM
Are you excited?
Of course I am.
What are you most excited to see?
SHE'S BEGUN TO TALK LIKE A SOLDIER
-Should we use honorifics again?
-I'm good.
Do you two normally speak with honorifics?
Well…
We recently dropped them,
so I'm annoyed
that she won't speak casually.
CHUCKLING
Look. There's no line.
THE LINE IS SHORT
BECAUSE IT'S NEAR CLOSING TIME
We'll head inside and enjoy.
OFF TO ENJOY THE MONET PAINTINGS
THAT SHE WANTED TO SEE
It's so pleasant.
ORANGERIE MUSEUM
THE ORANGE GREENHOUSE
REPURPOSED AS A GALLERY IN 1927
FEATURES A HIGH CEILING
THAT BRINGS IN NATURAL LIGHT
MONET'S WATER LILIES
DISPLAYED UNDER NATURAL LIGHT
MONET'S WATER LILIES SERIES IS DISPLAYED
ON THE OVAL WALL
MONET'S WATER LILIES SERIES
THIS 8-PAINTING SERIES IS
THE EPITOME OF IMPRESSIONISM
FEATURING SHIFTS IN LIGHT, SEASONS,
AND EVERYDAY MOMENTS.
MONET DONATED THEM TO HIS COUNTRY,
YEARNING FOR PEACE
DURING AN AGE OF WAR AND DISEASE
They must be sitting here
so they can enjoy the paintings.
It doesn't fit in the frame.
Is it not classy to view them up close?
They're all looking from afar.
Who cares?
I'd like to look at them up close.
This must've taken him forever.
Which of these four paintings
do you want to look at the longest?
Which do you want to look at longer?
That one.
Why?
Let's go over there.
I just love this one.
WATER LILIES: GREEN REFLECTIONS
It feels damp.
I'd love to know what things were like
when he drew this.
Which is your favorite?
That one's so pretty.
Let's head over there.
His mind could've been waging a war
on itself at the time.
We have no way to know,
but you could be right.
This is pretty.
Let's look at some other paintings.
There's more.
No way.
ANOTHER OVAL SPACE
He must've felt like he would've died
if he hadn't painted this.
These are even gloomier.
If he were in pain at the time,
what would he think of people
enjoying his work now?
I wonder what it would be like
for a painter
to lose their sight.
Her dress color matches the painting.
It's like she wore that on purpose.
Looking at trees after only seeing water?
-I feel better.
-I know.
I feel lighter in my heart.
There weren't any earlier.
-Exactly.
-There were no trees.
It's so pretty.
-Just seeing it was worth it.
-Of course.
A PRECIOUS EXPERIENCE
FULFILLED DO-YEON'S WISH,
SEEING THE MONET AT THE GALLERY
ORANGERIE MUSEUM, PARIS
A 1-HOUR-20-MINUTE DRIVE
THEY HEAD TO GIVERNY,
HOME OF MONET'S HOUSE
How was it for you, Marthe?
I intentionally didn't look online
to find out what paintings
were in the museum.
I wanted to imagine
what I'd be seeing today.
Anyway, I'll be checking out
the paintings again online
when I go to the hotel later.
After a day at a gallery,
we always talk about
which piece we'd like to take home
or which one we'd want to look at longer.
What we feel while looking
at the paintings is one thing,
but I also wonder what the artist
would have thought
while painting them.
I thought about bringing that up later.
The paintings were displayed
in a circle around us,
and it felt like we were surrounded.
The paintings were done
by someone significant.
No pun intended,
but he painted the Water Lilies series
to really develop his artistry
over many years.
This might not make sense,
but I felt so small in comparison.
That's how it was.
Have I ever done anything in my life
that I can say I truly gave my all to?
Would I ever be able to invest myself
in something the way he did?
I thought about it, and it turns out
there wasn't anything I did
that I can say I poured myself into.
I got a different impression
from the paintings than I expected.
That's how it was.
The atmosphere shifted.
In Paris, it was like walking along
a street full of luxury brands.
AWAY FROM THE CITY,
HEADING DOWN A COUNTRY ROAD
There. It says Giverny.
How fascinating.
GAZING
The houses share the same color palette,
but no two are exactly alike.
They were built in harmony
with one another.
A MELLOW GAZE…
ACROSS THE ROMANCE-FILLED SEINE
It's so quiet.
ARRIVING IN THE TRANQUIL VILLAGE
OF GIVERNY
-Wait.
-No way.
-No way. It's like a secret garden.
-I know.
It's beautiful.
THE CHARMING PLACE
THEY'RE STAYING FOR THE DAY
It's like someone named Ms. Charlotte
would answer the door.
With her rabbits tailing along.
It'd be a waste to just stay indoors here.
SURROUNDED BY A SPACIOUS GARDEN
OF ABOUT 9,900 SQUARE METERS
I can't believe this is someone's home.
GASPING!
No way. Even the lights are pretty.
It's like a studio.
It's endless.
What is this place?
Are we allowed back here?
A COZY AND WARM COURTYARD
How cute.
Wow.
This is so cool.
A REMODELED 13TH-CENTURY HOUSE
It's so pretty.
This is amazing.
A VINTAGE-STYLE ROOM
This looks fake.
It's too surreal.
The night has settled in.
It's so romantic.
A SURREAL DAY COMES TO AN END…
Good morning!
(COME HERE!)
Go.
APPEARING IN A "TWIN LOOK"
THAT THEY PERSONALLY PREPARED
Hi, Mr. Sky.
What? Hello, Ms. Tree!
Good morning, everyone.
EMBARRASSED BY HER FRIEND
DOING HER DAY JOB
Your turn.
SHAKING HEAD
Go ahead. I'll help.
Look! Hi there, my dear friend bug.
HEADING TO BREAKFAST, BURSTING WITH ENERGY
It's like a fairy tale.
TRYING ONE OF FRANCE'S
SIGNATURE BLACK TEAS
Thanks.
GASPING!
I didn't get any on me.
SHE TRIPPED AND SPILLED THE TEA
-I didn't burn myself.
-Everything's good then.
You watered the wood.
When will our sister-in-law be back?
USING IT AS MATERIAL FOR A SKIT
TO LESSEN OK-SEOP'S EMBARRASSMENT
Marthe.
Will we ever be able to go
to parties like princesses do?
Darn.
Marthe, I want to dance the waltz.
FLEEING
Marthe, that fool,
finds things like this embarrassing.
If you do, you'll spend
your whole life cleaning floors.
Marthe. What?
The music changed.
I can't dance to this.
I can't.
I can't dance to music like this.
Marthe, come on. Join me.
Marthe, what do I do?
MARTHE TURNS THE OTHER CHEEK
Come back over here. The sketch is over.
- END OF SKIT -
I'll have the egg first.
Recently, my favorite way
to eat boiled eggs
is with perilla oil, salt, and pepper.
This looks like olive oil though.
SALT+PEPPER+OLIVE OIL
TRYING HER FAVORITE COMBO
That looks good.
YUMMY!
That's so good.
No way. The egg's so good.
I've been dying for a croissant.
No way.
It's the same shape as your purse.
Exactly. My mini purse
is shaped like a croissant.
Of course.
Here.
-Have it with some jam.
-Sure.
I just tried a bit on its own.
How is it?
It's so moist.
-Really?
-Yes.
You can really taste the butter
in every layer.
It won't need more butter then.
It doesn't.
You can taste plenty of butter.
You must like tangerine jam
more than strawberry jam.
I like having tangerine jam this way.
I haven't had tangerine jam before.
-Gosh.
-Isn't it delicious?
It's just as good without strawberry jam.
-I like the subtle flavors.
-It's so good.
Isn't it delicious even on its own?
A BEE WAS DRAWN TO THE SWEET SCENT
Hey, it's a bee.
-It must be that good.
-The food must be tasty.
It must've been drawn to the honey.
Are you claiming it?
Gosh, what a magical moment.
THE BEE LANDS ON THE BREAD TO TASTE IT
It must be to its liking.
Doesn't it look like a character?
Right? It's not threatening at all.
From a traveler's perspective,
even bees are adorable.
Watch out.
THE BEE SUDDENLY BUZZES AROUND DO-YEON
Stay still.
It must think we're flowers.
SHE'S SLIGHTLY AFRAID OF IT
You know how people who freak out
always get stung first.
I'd rather not jinx it.
NOM
I actually prefer this.
-Let's order everything.
-I prefer this.
THE BEE COMES FLYING BACK TO THEM
It's a real bee.
SCARED
-Be careful.
-I'm kind of afraid. Where is it?
It's gone. No, it's not. Hold still.
THE BEE KEEPS FLYING AROUND HER HEAD
It's okay.
You're fine thanks to
all that hair on your head.
It could still sting me.
It won't sting you
through your thick hair.
The stinger's too short.
I'm terrified.
I'm not kidding. This is scary.
What can I do?
Stop messing with me
and chase the bee away!
What does my hair
have to do with anything?
It might sting you.
What if it stings you when I swat it away?
Tell me to move, then.
I can't see where it is.
-It's still buzzing around me.
-Stay still.
You need to stay still.
If I get stung by a bee,
I'll be the happiest person
on earth today.
GOSH…!
SHE EMBODIES MS. POSITIVE AGAIN
Isn't that right, Mr. Louis?
It's my first time meeting him.
As of today,
I'll be taking over this house.
Get on my good side,
and you'll get strawberry jam for free.
You were giving off the vibe
of the classical novels you love.
Really? Thanks for saying so.
What would you like to eat today?
Dishes eaten by the locals,
not what tourists eat when they visit.
When we're on trips
and eat at a good restaurant,
we ask the owner
to recommend other places.
You're right. We used to do that a lot.
When we saw someone on the street
who just looked like a foodie,
we'd follow them
and order whatever they were eating,
which was fun.
Then, today…
After our walk,
we'll head to Monet's house
and then leave Giverny, unfortunately.
We only spent such a short time here
that it might feel like a dream.
-Still, we'll remember it for ages.
-I know.
-I enjoyed that.
-Thank you for breakfast.
We're now off to Monet's house.
What a beautiful morning.
-I expected no less.
-It smells incredible.
-People should spend time in the sun.
-Right.
The roofs are all so pretty.
I like that the weather is cool.
And there's a shade.
PRIME WEATHER FOR TRAVELING
GIGGLING
And…
Look how pretty that is.
You're right. Come over here.
Over there.
The only thing there is a bench.
It must be a tanning spot.
That flower's beautiful. Do you see it?
No wonder the people here
created such incredible art.
It's fascinating to see scenery
that feels familiar to the paintings.
You're right.
I didn't expect a view like this
behind the inn.
I would've regretted not taking this walk.
-We came by car yesterday.
-Exactly.
THE RELAXING VILLAGE THEY MISSED YESTERDAY
Hey, is that morning glory?
Yes, it is.
It's so pretty.
It's shaped like a heart.
Isn't it nice to see heart-shaped things?
There are hearts everywhere here.
It's the city of romance for sure.
CITY OF ROMANCE, GIVERNY
Check out that old lady.
What a beautiful scene.
Isn't this like a scene from a movie?
This is stunning to watch.
No way. She must be cutting them
to put in a vase.
-That's so beautiful.
-Gosh.
It's surreal.
What a sight.
That's a Rose of Sharon,
Korea's national flower.
Isn't that the result
of KPop Demon Hunters going global?
Let's go.
Zhang Hao actually gave this to me
as a gift.
What is it?
It's a phone.
It's a used phone.
Take a selfie with this.
It comes out really pretty.
It's been trending lately.
After we wrapped up filming,
I told him to take it back
just to be sure,
but he said it was a gift.
-Does he speak in a dialect?
-Gosh, no.
I messed up my impression of him just now.
Well, how adorable of him.
He's handsome, but he's even sweeter
on the inside.
Anyway, let's take a few photos
with that phone today.
-How about a photo?
-What?
-Where?
-Over there. Come here.
Don't look directly at me.
What should I do?
WIDE- APART
A HUMAN TRIPOD
-Should I drink some tea?
-No.
AWKWARD
Turn a little away from me.
Like this?
No, don't turn your head.
-My whole body, then?
-Yes, but look this way.
Like this? Got it.
Wait. Hold on.
With your legs…
-I'll take a shot of you, so show me.
-Sure.
Look at my poses
and tell me which one I look best in.
DIRECTOR YI IS IN HER ELEMENT
One, two, three.
Three.
I got it. Take a look.
You'd get embarrassed if I took too long.
-Seriously?
-Isn't it great?
It looks amazing.
I should copy you.
Yes, like that.
-My legs are too short.
-It doesn't matter.
One, two, three.
I'll keep taking them. Just do your thing.
BURST MODE
We're good.
BOWING
Hello.
WHAT!!
This must be where he lives.
Wow.
What?
SHOWING THEM HIS GALLERY ON THE SPOT
-This is awesome.
-Are those all of his works?
Is this his studio?
A GALLERY EXUDING FRENCH AESTHETICS
-No way.
-This is so cool.
GASP
Oh, I get it. It's like a container.
I see.
How is this a container?
It's not. It's a bell.
AN INCOMPREHENSIBLE CONTAINER(?)
-A container?
-It's my work.
What did he mean by that?
Did he mean something else?
-It's so cool.
-There's a lizard.
WHAT IS THIS CONFUSING-LOOKING BOX[?]
I see. Soap.
BRONZE SOAP SCULPTURES
SCULPTURES MADE FROM SELECTED ART PIECES
OF DECADES-OLD MARSEILLE SOAP
FROM MARSEILLE OR OTHER REGIONS
THAT WERE CAST IN COPPER OR BRONZE
This is soap?
FASCINATED
He must've sculpted all of these.
Did a rat nibble on this soap?
CHUCKLING
This one's huge. It's big.
Check this out.
He says we can sit on it.
-Should I sit?
-Yes.
You know what? I'll take a memorable shot.
SOUVENIR PHOTO TAKEN
AT THE RECOMMENDED SPOT
Did you get it?
THEY TAKE IT RIGHT AWAY
You look great.
Wow.
THEY CONTINUE THEIR TRIP
AFTER THE UNEXPECTED DETOUR
How fascinating was that?
Recently, I read somewhere that
in order for people
to have good luck and opportunities,
they need to be kind and smile often.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let's do both today.
-Yes, let's make it a day.
-Sure.
Are you good?
LAUGHING
That's an example of kindness
done the wrong way.
-Oh my.
-Cool, right?
-That hat…
-It's so pretty.
We used to call that
the Shim Yang-hong hat.
A lot of them are wearing pink hats.
I already saw two today.
See? There's another pink hat.
-Hold on.
-What if we need one to enter?
-Could it be like an entrance ticket?
-Painters used to wear those.
There's another person in a red hat.
Let's buy one
if we come across a stall or shop.
Yes, let's.
QUEUE
They're waiting in line.
This looks like the line.
-We should get in line.
-Yes, it's the line.
VISITORS FILL MONET'S HOUSE AND GARDEN
Is it this big?
How rich was he?
It's Claude Monet Road.
-No way.
-It's huge, isn't it?
In we go. Finally.
I'm so nervous.
-Is that him?
-Yes.
-Wasn't he stylish?
-You said so earlier.
CLAUDE MONET
FATHER OF IMPRESSIONISM
What you said you would do
is finally coming true.
I know. It feels unreal.
I'm only going to say nice things.
Are you kidding me?
Nice.
It's the same shade of green.
-The same shade?
-This shade.
GREEN WELCOMES THEM AT THE ENTRANCE
It feels weird.
-My feet itch.
-Really? Then, scratch them.
I can't. It'd be embarrassing.
THEY WALK DEEPER INTO THE GARDEN
-Isn't it so pretty?
-It is.
How is this someone's house?
Even the stems are pretty.
MONET'S PALETTE, MADE BY NATURE
THE FLOWER GARDEN PROVIDES
A CONTRAST OF COLORS
How can this be someone's house?
Someone actually lived here in Giverny!
-How was that?
-It was funny.
-I see chicken.
-Are those chickens?
SHUTTING DOWN HER AWFUL JOKE
They're as white as swans.
That's an actual chicken.
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
This is stunning.
-Are those apples?
-They are.
EVEN THE APPLE TREE WAS PLANTED
TO RECREATE MONET'S GARDEN
It's like we've stepped
into his paintings.
No way. Was this his studio?
This is where he lived.
It's so pretty.
-Come this way.
-Why are there so many rooms?
MONET'S RESIDENCE
FOR 43 YEARS SINCE 1883
FEATURING HIS WATER LILIES POND,
A JAPANESE-STYLE BRIDGE, STUDIO,
KITCHEN, BEDROOM, ALL IN HIS AESTHETIC
It's beautiful.
Now I see why a lot of things
are this shade of green.
The house across the road
caught the green fever too.
You're right. It caught the green virus.
Nice. We're heading in now.
ENTERING MONET'S HOUSE
Look, there you are. Jean.
There's Jean. That's me.
JEAN DO-YEON
Jean.
Look. That one's a famous piece of his.
I can't believe I'm seeing it.
THE 1ST FLOOR DISPLAYS REPLICAS
OF MONET'S BEST WORKS
Haystacks is also
a famous painting of his.
-I had no idea.
-That middle one is Haystacks,
and he drew a whole series of them too.
WITH OVER 25 PAINTINGS,
THE HAYSTACKS SERIES
CAPTURES THE CHANGING LIGHT
AND PASSAGE OF TIME
-That must be his wife.
-Yes!
That's her when she passed away.
That's right.
He painted her like that,
probably because he wanted
to remember her even like that.
CAMILLE MONET ON HER DEATHBED
TO THE 2ND FLOOR
Doesn't it feel like we're in Japan?
He was heavily influenced
by ukiyo-e prints.
Do you know what's funny?
Pottery was shipped from Japan to Europe,
and the paper used for wrapping
had illustrations like that.
-Is that what he copied?
-That's right.
Monet and Vincent van Gogh were known
to be heavily influenced by them.
JUST THE KNOWLEDGE YOU'D EXPECT
FROM THE HONORARY(?) SON
Is that why they're displayed
with the pottery?
Hey, it's the bedroom.
They must've been so happy.
-It's stunning.
-Wow.
Did he sleep here after he lost his wife,
or did he share this room with her?
-The bed's not that big.
-It's small.
They could've cuddled,
being in love and all.
LOOKING OUT THE WINDOW IN MONET'S ROOM
The flowers look amazing from above.
I know.
YOU HAVE A FULL VIEW OF THE FLOWER GARDEN
Imagine him standing here
and seeing the gardener from afar.
He would've brought out his canvas
and painted that scene.
MY GARDEN IS MY MOST BEAUTIFUL MASTERPIECE
- CLAUDE MONET -
LOOKING AROUND THE REST OF THE ROOMS
This must've been a sewing room.
Even the wallpaper is charming, gosh.
The rooms are different colors,
almost like each has its own theme.
It'd be amazing to eat here.
Right? What a joy that would've been.
Look how pretty this is.
This must be where they cooked.
Head out there. I'll take your photo.
You look great.
Here's the Water Lily Pond. This way.
THE POND THAT INSPIRED
THE WATER LILIES SERIES
SOUND OF FLOWING WATER
I can hear water flowing.
We'll simply follow the sound of water.
LETTING THE SOUND OF WATER GUIDE THEM
Why don't we paint like Monet did
back in the day?
It's a pond!
Do you reckon he said that too?
No, he wouldn't have.
I'll play the role
of one of Monet's broke friends.
Monet, my friend.
Is this how you spend your days?
I don't have this at home.
Could I maybe paint something here too?
-This is stunning.
-No way!
Are those bamboo?
A BAMBOO GROVE EVEN MONET'S FRIEND
WOULD'VE BEEN AMAZED BY
-It's the same color as in his paintings.
-Oh my lord.
-Aren't the colors the same?
-Yeah.
If we stay still,
we'll hear the water flowing.
It's so pretty.
THE WATER LILY POND
WHERE A RAY OF SUNLIGHT RESTS
This is the best.
It's stunning.
Monet could've sat there
-since this is his home.
-Exactly.
THEY GO FURTHER IN,
FOLLOWING THE SOUND OF THE WATER
WOW!
(ARE YOU SERIOUS?)
It's exactly the same!
STOMPING
Are you kidding me?
THE WATER LILY POND,
WHICH BREATHES MONET'S INSPIRATION
THIS WAS THE PLACE OF ART
WHERE HE STUDIED THE ESSENCE OF LIGHT
A PLACE HE LOVED
UNTIL HIS EYES SUCCUMBED TO CATARACTS
No way.
-Look at that lotus.
-It's so elegant.
I kept seeing that flower on the map.
You're right.
I wondered why, and now I know.
MONET HAD MORE THAN 250 PIECES
IN HIS WATER LILIES SERIES
He must've been so happy.
-While he painted?
-Yes.
Absolutely.
His house is right over there.
-He could see it from here.
-This is like a painting.
They prepared a spot for you to stand in.
-Let's check it out from another angle.
-I love it.
The volume of birds chirping
and water flowing is just about right.
GLANCING
No way.
GLANCING AGAIN
I almost cried
at the way that person gazed at the pond.
Do you know how it was?
Like this.
Without even blinking.
I can see why.
It's stunning.
This was worth it.
SCENERY THAT'LL NEVER GET OLD
Do you want a photo here?
You've been dying to come.
Can you turn to me a bit?
Done.
No way.
All the beautiful colors are
in this garden.
There's even a butterfly.
How can it be this perfect?
Is that Monet's boat?
-No way!
-I've always wanted a boat like that.
-I want that boat. I'm so jealous.
-It's so pretty.
Enjoy, Do-yeon.
Enjoy from a higher position.
Are you talking
to that squashed version of Do-yeon?
Let's go grab some lunch now.
Are we off to the restaurant
where Cézanne and Monet used to eat?
Yes, we're off to that salon.
I loved it here.
THEY'RE NOW OFF TO GRAB LUNCH
ATTENTIVELY
They could've sold the hats here.
-Let's look at the hats.
-Let's take a look.
THEY'RE LURED INTO THE HAT STORE
-Here they are.
-Where?
These are it.
None of them are pink.
-They must've already sold out.
-Exactly.
Do you want to try on a different color?
Try this one.
I think it'll look good on you.
RECOMMENDING A BROWN BERET FOR DO-YEON
STRUGGLING
I don't know how to put this on.
Like this?
(LET ME HELP)
That's right.
She's stretching it out a bit first.
You stretch it slightly.
Since she stretched it out,
I'll have to buy it.
WON'T I HAVE TO BUY IT NOW?
Is this how you wear it?
Maybe that shouldn't have been pressed.
Is this what "French chic" is?
-Lift up the front a bit.
-Right.
-Don't I look like TWO TWO? In a good way.
-It's pretty.
-I'll also try a different color.
-Really?
Sure, try one on.
Is black better?
Black or blue?
Here. Try this navy one on.
-Like this?
-You look good.
It looks different from yours.
Don't I belong at a theme park?
I look like a frozen corpse.
I feel like I could make you spin.
-How do I make it look like yours?
-Wear it crooked.
Crooked? Oh, like this.
Hey, that looks good.
AWKWARD
I look good as well.
-You look just as good.
-You look like a chef.
-Two of them?
-How much is it?
GIVERNY SOUVENIRS BOUGHT
Have a nice day.
Wearing this hat alone
makes me feel like a painter.
Is what we saw earlier this way?
Hold on. Isn't that…
Earlier…
Is this the place we mentioned earlier?
-Wait. I think it is.
-Right?
Wow. Bonjour.
Here's an empty table.
THEY SIT AT A TABLE
WITH SUNLIGHT POURING IN
Haystacks is here too.
That's one of your favorite pieces.
This is fascinating.
A PLACE LOVED BY IMPRESSIONIST ARTISTS,
INCLUDING MONET, CÉZANNE, AND RENOIR
Look, desserts.
What should we order?
What's good here?
Since the sun is blazing outside,
let's get the sun platter.
What would you recommend?
THE WAITRESS RECOMMENDS A BEER
Here's what we can have. Then…
Two, please.
-Two? Okay.
-Yes.
I'm super thirsty right now.
GULPING
-That's so pretty.
-Look how pretty that is.
FRENCH CRAFT BEER
THAT'LL QUENCH THEIR THIRST
My God.
It's like an ad.
CHUGGING
KAH-!
That's exactly how I like my beer.
The foam…
There's a lot of it, but it's soft.
-Also, it's very bitter.
-Exactly.
It's bitter.
It's slightly more bitter than Hoegaarden.
It must be IPA.
JUST HOW SHE LIKES IT
-I can't wait to eat.
-Same here.
I'm feeling drowsy.
Were Monet and Cézanne best friends?
Monet and Paul Cézanne?
Cézanne had great respect
for Monet's work,
and it was Renoir who helped Monet
through his toughest times.
Anyway, what I found interesting
was that Eugène Boudin
was his first mentor.
-Monet's mentor?
-Yes.
Monet started out as a caricature artist.
I'd love to see his work.
-Caricature…
-Like those artists at Lotte World?
Yes, that's right.
Monet drew caricatures,
but when Eugène Boudin saw his work,
he told Monet
to paint landscapes outdoors,
-instead of drawing indoors.
-So that's how.
That's when Monet started painting
landscapes outdoors.
Outdoors, he learned
how light transformed what he saw,
and that inspired him to hone
and perfect his artistry and style.
Anyway, at one point,
people once said he had become a traitor
to the style.
-Monet--
-When he became an impressionist?
He changed his style, you see.
At the height of his career, he took
on a challenge and changed his style.
Renoir traveled with him during that time,
and the paintings he created
were just as beautiful.
LA GRENOUILLÈRE
Why was Renoir so good to him?
Renoir was a very loving man.
In Renoir's paintings,
the people are like this.
DRUNK ON LOVE…
They look like this.
You'll know what I mean.
FEATURING WARM COLORS
AND THE PLAY OF LIGHT
THE ARTIST WHO DEPICTS HAPPINESS, RENOIR
The people in Renoir's paintings
are like this.
CTRL+C, CTRL+V
They all look like this.
AS THEY TALK, FOOD IS SERVED
Here's your steak.
This looks so good.
A GENEROUS AND HEARTY MEAL
AT A TRADITIONAL FRENCH BISTRO
All of this looks so good.
Look, it's cooked medium.
It looks so good.
Are you kidding me? Is that gochugaru?
THEY TRY THE STEAK FIRST
It's so good.
MMM
This garlic butter is amazing.
Right. I forgot this was garlic butter.
The steak's incredible.
-Why don't we try this too?
-Sure.
I want to try the eggplant.
The cheese looks amazing.
SUN PLATTER FULL OF BRIGHT VEGGIES
Try it like a lettuce wrap.
It's not salty.
This is so good.
It's light and fresh, not heavy at all.
The cheese is so tasty.
-This is incredible.
-Have a prawn. You love them.
It's really soft.
This is huge.
YUMMY!
Do you like that best?
It's worth peeling them
even if you hate peeling prawns.
CRUNCH
How is it?
SHE EATS EVERYTHING, EVEN THE PRAWN HEAD
You know,
whether it's jokbal, chicken feet,
or mackerel,
you always eat it so clean.
…LAUGHING
You have good eating etiquette.
You must've been taught well.
YOUNG DO-YEON WAS WELL-TAUGHT
IN TABLE MANNERS
My hands are clean.
It's fine.
-Wow, really? No way.
-Eat up.
There haven't been many times
when someone else peeled prawns for me.
When I was young
and didn't know any better,
I loved eating crabs.
Blue crabs.
We'd have blue crab stew,
and my dad would peel the crabs for me.
Do you know what I said while eating?
"I guess Dad doesn't like blue crabs."
That's how kids are.
It's the same as saying,
"My mom only eats fish heads."
But you know, the head is the best part.
GIGGLE
-Isn't it good?
-It is.
That's a satisfying chew.
After this, we're heading back to Paris.
-Cheers.
-That was delicious.
WHAT WILL AWAIT THEM IN PARIS?
Guys, we're here.
We went from being girls from Giverny
to being Paris girls.
This must be a place loved by locals.
That looks so good.
Isn't it delicious?
It's nice and chewy.
THE TEXTURE IS DIVINE
I can imagine it snapping and cracking.
That's really good.
FINDING HER… LIKE A CREME BRULEE…
A SWEET, HEART-FLUTTERING MOMENT
BROUGHT TO YOU IN PARIS
A ROMANCE MOVIE
IS THIS THE LIFE OF A PARIS GIRL…?
Did he say he's an actor?
What a charming theater.
Even Blow Up is playing.
PACKED WITH MOVIES
RECOMMENDED BY CINEPHILES
There's Aftersun.
We're going in.
-This is so pretty.
-I know.
EXCITED
BEING A PARIS GIRL IS A CHALLENGE
We're about to see the Eiffel Tower
in a special way.
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO TRANSFORM
INTO TRUE PARIS GIRLS?
PARTYING PARIS WITH PARIS GIRLS
It looks like fireworks, like something
out of A Midsummer Night's Dream.
Subtitle translation by: Hyelim Park