GETAWAY AND GO WITH JANGDOBARI
WHERE ARE WE…?
Hello. Bound for a breezy break…
Hello. Bound for a breezy break
with bundles of stories in my bag.
I'm Jang Do-yeon.
You wouldn't guess it at first glance,
but it's currently a little over 5 a.m.
And not that you'd be wondering,
but I left home at 3:20 a.m.
Then I put on my face
and headed back home.
Why, you ask?
That's because today's travel buddy
happens to be my neighbor.
Do-yeon.
WHO ON EARTH COULD IT BE?
I'm finally headed to this person's house.
I only need a single word
to give you a clue about them.
Queen.
She's the sexy queen
this era has been waiting for.
That's odd.
I'm only just getting to her place,
but I already feel drained.
KNOCK KNOCK KNOCK
Yes?
EVEN HER VOICE MAKES DO-YEON LAUGH
Do-yeon?
GABEE
DO-YEON'S NEIGHBOR
Oh, you're glowing!
THE BREAKOUT STAR
OF THE VARIETY ENTERTAINMENT SCENE
AND GLOBAL DANCER
What should we do with you?
-I came because I missed you.
-Oh my.
When you were on Radio Star,
you mentioned how you'd texted me.
A lot of people enjoyed that story.
You asked if we could go
to the sauna and pool together.
I'm crazy for saunas.
GABEE'S WISH IS TO GO
TO A SAUNA WITH DO-YEON
GULP
You're not trying to bring me down,
are you?
Is it okay if I wear a mask?
GABEE MADE DO-YEON SHY
I won't come on too strong.
WILL THE HOT AND COLD PAIR
MAKE IT TO A SAUNA OKAY?
FIRST REUNION AFTER SALON DRIP 2
-Please come in.
-May I?
RUNNING BAREFOOT
Then excuse me.
You're actually here in my home.
I can't believe it.
Your place is so colorful.
COLORFUL HOME TAKES AFTER GABEE
This is… You have so much stuff.
Hold up.
Do you have a show somewhere?
AREN'T WE GOING ON A TRIP?
My shoes for today. They're brand new.
Where do you even buy shoes like these?
I buy them abroad.
I feel so underdressed beside you.
I'm devoid of all color.
-I have no color.
-I can't wait. This'll be fun.
You've traveled with other people, right?
I have. You're my fourth guest.
-I am?
-Yes.
Are the trips always a single night?
Isn't the blood going to your head?
Wow, you look great.
IT'S TOO EARLY FOR THIS ENERGY
-And one last check.
-You always do this?
-It suits you.
-It does, right?
THE AURA OF A QUEEN
PUMP IT!
(RUN AWAY)
Have some water, Do-yeon.
Great, thanks.
Would you like some water?
SUDDEN CHANGE OF MOOD
Have you eaten? Fancy a banana?
Wait, so you walk around the house
in heels like that?
Banana, anyone?
A banana for you, Do-yeon?
I'm good.
It's a perfectly ripe banana.
Then may I take one?
-Of course you may.
-Okay, then.
It's weird. I could have sworn
I was so full earlier.
GOT A BANANA FOR LATER
I have to ask.
Are you heading somewhere after our trip?
I thought it was just a one-night trip.
What do you mean?
I only packed for one night.
With this thing,
you'd think this was Jung Saem Mool's bag.
Jung Saem Mool's bag?
A lot of makeup artists actually use this.
Yeah, they take it on trips.
-Shall I do your makeup?
-Mine?
Sure.
Is it just me,
or have they gotten even whiter?
Have they really? That's not good.
I think it just feels that way
because I haven't seen you in a while.
It feels like we're in Beverly Hills
or something.
I could have sworn we were in Ichon-dong.
Deary me.
STARING
I'm so excited. I can't wait.
Thanks for being so excited.
-Thank you.
-I'm not your luggage manager, am I?
No, you're not. You're my friend.
You're not my manager.
Thank you.
I'm no color. I have no color.
Why do we look so different?
I look like an elementary school kid
who's had a growth spurt.
PRETTY DIFFERENT LOOKS
I'm so hyped!
Let's go.
-Driving manager?
-She's really doing that?
Driving manager!
(BACKING OFF)
It's so much fun flustering Do-yeon.
What should we do?
I don't think I can stop myself.
-The driving manager is actually here.
-Driving manager!
(RUN AWAY)
Where are you, driving manager?
Oh, there he is!
It's like magic.
SHARING A RIDE WITH THE QUEEN
TO THE AIRPORT
You running away is priceless.
Wow, the lights are great.
I feel exhausted.
-I really enjoyed watching Salon Drip.
-You did?
I really do like you,
and I think that came across.
You were adorable.
I was gushing over you.
THAT'S HOW MUCH I LIKE YOU
Wait, so am I your first female guest?
Yes, you are.
Not only are you the first woman,
but you're also very different
in temperament.
FIRST EXTRA-EXTROVERTED GUEST
On the show, you mentioned
wanting to go to the sauna together.
Since you agreed to travel with me,
we'll be going on a trip
that's tailored just to you.
In Taiwan, there's a hot springs town.
TODAY'S DESTINATION
TAIWAN
TAIWAN, HOME TO GABEE'S FAVORITE THING:
HOT SPRINGS
WHAT ADVENTURES LIE AHEAD OF THEM?
EPISODE 9:
BETWEEN HOT AND COLD
We'll come back with prunes for fingers.
-I'm so hyped.
-You should be.
My go-to sauna ritual is to warm myself up
for about five minutes inside.
Seven or eight minutes works too.
Then I jump straight into cold water.
You like that?
It's my favorite thing in the world.
They say it gives you
a heavenly dopamine rush.
When I was really stressed,
that's how I relieved all my stress.
Are there also health benefits?
I think I heard
there were?
Fact-check manager?
A COLD PLUNGE AFTER THE SAUNA
STIMULATES CIRCULATION
AND BOOSTS METABOLISM,
BENEFITING OVERALL HEALTH
And from this trip on,
we've got a new rule.
We have a daily conversation cap.
NEW RULE MADE IN THE FIRST 30 MINUTES
All right, let's hear it, then.
How high is the cap?
Let's see if it's enough for me.
I have this thing where I break out
in hives if I keep my mouth shut.
That's why we're going to the hot springs.
So you can take a plunge
if you have a reaction.
Let's say
you're at a sauna, and there's a fire.
Where would we cover?
-Let's cover our faces.
-Yes, we should.
They wouldn't know it's me
just by seeing my body.
In my case, I'm so obviously me,
even if I cover my face.
That's true.
My body's very outspoken.
But only you can rock your body.
My body practically screams
that I'm Gabee.
I'm Gabee. Hey!
I'm Gabee. Oh my God!
Can we take a picture?
One sec. I forgot I wanted to.
Do you always take pictures
on your way to the airport?
Not really, but I'm with you,
so this is special.
Thank you.
YOU GET ME?
-I'll send it to you.
-I'm gonna eat the banana now.
Yes, please do.
It should be nice and ripe.
It's even clearer in this picture.
That you're a beauty.
Hey, don't say that.
You get that a lot, don't you?
That you look
so much more beautiful in person.
A little bit.
You have a different aura.
You're so tall, like a supermodel.
I wonder what the camera crew is doing,
for everyone who sees me
to say I look better in person?
We should blame the cameras.
What are they even doing?
My apologies.
Leejung was on Salon Drip too, right?
-She was.
-She told me she had fun talking to you.
She said you often go over
to each other's houses.
All the time.
Leejung and I are really close.
I heard that she lives close.
Yes, she does.
We live close, so we meet up pretty often.
So you squeeze in time to meet
despite your busy schedules?
Yes.
I think it's really important.
-Hanging out with friends.
-Yes.
Meeting people in the same line of work
lets you share your professional concerns.
I think that's really valuable.
Nowadays,
I've been thinking a lot about the phrase,
"Right time, right place."
That's right.
There's a time for everything,
and a lot of things
are beyond our control.
Wait, what? Are you possessed?
Those kinds of thoughts.
We talk about stuff like that.
"Right time, right place"?
Yeah, there are people you meet like that.
ARRIVED AT INCHEON AIRPORT!
-Off we go.
-Let's go.
Looking at you,
I don't feel like I'm in Seoul.
Wait, we're in Incheon.
What city do I remind you of?
Ichon-dong.
NON-STOP LAUGHTER WITH THE ICHON GALS
A TWO-AND-A-HALF-HOUR FLIGHT TO TAIWAN
(WEATHER'S GRIM)
TAOYUAN AIRPORT
Jang Do-yeon.
MADE IT THROUGH FIRST,
WAITING FOR DO-YEON AT THE GATE
JANG DO-YEON
(WHEN'S SHE COMING?)
THRILLED AT THE THOUGHT
OF MESSING WITH DO-YEON
(FOUND HER)
JANG DO-YEON
Hello.
(LOOKING AWAY)
Wait, I'm here!
Do-yeon, I'm here!
What took you so long?
How was your trip over here, Do-yeon?
Was it okay? Yes?
I'll be your tour guide for the day.
It's good to meet you.
It's raining a lot today. Very humid.
-Are you okay?
-Are you possessed again?
How many times does that happen in a day?
You're hilarious.
It's raining outside. Will you be okay?
-It's pouring.
-It is.
I think, in terms of weather,
we're screwed.
-Today's weather…
-The weather's grim.
But our trip won't be.
The weather's awful,
but my energy's still up.
What are you gonna do about it?
Do you think I'll be stuck
inside my hotel the whole time?
-Do you need to change your shoes?
-I already did. And I have a raincoat.
They're so glamorous.
GLAMOROUS BUT COMFY SHOES ON
Let's go. Rainy Taiwan.
(CHECKING HERSELF OUT)
-Do you feel energized from your nap?
-Yes.
Totally refreshed.
You slept like Sleeping Beauty. Like this.
-Sleeping well is such a blessing.
-I do sleep really well.
-You didn't wake up?
-I didn't wake up at all.
-I woke up once when I smelled food.
-Just after we took off?
-But I forced myself to sleep again.
-That was a good choice.
In case you might be hungry,
I brought some snacks.
-A little bit of snacks.
-Oh my God.
Thank you!
Taiwanese pudding.
I think it's famous.
-Bubble tea.
-Oh, bubble tea?
Thank you.
It's delicious.
-It's yummy!
-It is? That's good.
It's so good.
People drink a lot of this in Taiwan.
-I see why people love bubble tea.
-Right?
Even though it's a little wet,
it's very atmospheric.
Saunas on rainy days are really charming.
Getting into water when it's raining?
Of course.
So you're gonna rain?
Then I'll just jump in the water.
SUDDENLY TAKING ON THE WEATHER
I'm just going to dive right in.
Queen Gabee, do you always feel like
someone's picking a fight with you?
What, you think I'll lose?
I'm gonna go out.
GETTING MORE AND MORE EXHAUSTED WITH TIME
You're a warrior.
I love that. "Warrior."
You're Warrior Gabee.
So, we're headed to Wulai.
I looked it up, and it means hot springs.
WULAI, AN INDIGENOUS VILLAGE
FAMOUS FOR ITS NATURAL HOT SPRINGS
THE MILDLY ALKALINE HOT SPRING
IS NICKNAMED "THE BEAUTY BATH"
-Wait, so the water's carbonated?
-Yes.
-That's cool.
-It's meant to be good for your skin.
Sounds awesome.
What makes it even more special
is that it's home to Indigenous people.
A HOT SPRING SPOT
OCCUPIED BY INDIGENOUS PEOPLE
Then, when traveling,
what's most important to you?
It's only a one-night trip,
but shouldn't we try
to make the most of it and have fun?
Number one is who I'm going with.
That's important to me too.
For me,
that makes up about 80% of the trip.
What do you look for
in a travel buddy, then?
How much I like them.
What would I have to do
to make you like me?
My feelings for you are already at 100%.
The second thing
is the weather.
(WHAT DO WE DO?)
The weather tends
to determine my mood on a trip.
-But some people like rain.
-Right.
I think today's weather is decent.
It's not the kind of weather
that forces you to stay in.
Right, of course.
Third for me is the food.
You didn't seem picky,
but your list is pretty long.
That's pretty much everything.
What should we avoid?
I'm good with anything except coriander.
I honestly eat anything.
You'll be surprised.
I like tteokbokki…
Hey!
Isn't Smile Tteokbokki so delicious?
-Smile Tteokbokki?
-In Ichon-dong.
I've seen it but never tried it.
-Why haven't you tried it? You're nuts!
-Smile Tteokbokki?
That's a massive deal.
The Yongsan Station will come for you.
Seriously?
How can you live in Ichon-dong
and not have tried Smile Tteokbokki?
How does it taste?
It's not a super red gochujang sauce.
It uses chili flakes,
so it tastes brighter.
GULP
But the downside is,
you end up eating too much.
I should try it. I've never been.
I'm craving tteokbokki now.
-Still, we should eat Taiwanese food.
-It's nice sharing our favorite spots.
This isn't in our neighborhood,
but I found this brilliant place.
They give you yukhoe,
which you wrap in brisket.
And you top it off
with a shot of soju and beer.
Oh my God. It's so good.
If you take the yukhoe
and wrap it in the thinly cut brisket…
It's hot and cold.
So you like stuff that's hot and cold.
You like extremes. Hot, then cold.
Hot, then cold.
-It sounds delicious.
-And drinks.
-Do you like lamb skewers?
-I love them.
-Know the great place in Hannam-dong?
-I don't know.
I should write this down.
They have a sweet corn jeon.
I thought someone zapped you.
-Sweet corn noodles.
-Their sweet corn noodles are great.
I love them. It's slightly spicy.
Hot noodles.
And when I want to eat close to home,
I go to…
I've never… Wait, that place?
I've had a lot of grilled fish there.
-Grilled fish.
-Yes, it's good.
-Have you been to the Ichon Market?
-I have.
In the alley, there's a mandu place.
-I know that one.
-It's a small shack, but delicious.
-They have great shrimp dumplings.
-Yes, they do.
And mushroom dumplings.
DROOLING…
Shall we go back to Seoul?
We should have just met near home.
We got on a flight all the way to Taiwan.
A food tour with you would be so much fun.
Can't we shoot an episode
around our neighborhood?
-Our neighborhood?
-Can't you come sometime?
Not a bad shout.
-There's a lot of good food in the area.
-Sounds good to me.
I love our area.
I feel so at peace.
-Right?
-That's why I love our area too.
This is nice.
This is so nice. I think it's true
that what's most important
is who you travel with.
-Thank you.
-You need to get along.
-That's good.
-Honestly.
Shall we decide on some rules
for your trip?
-Rules for today?
-Yes.
Is there anything you want to do,
or anything you'd like me to do?
Not really.
Like giving you some time to yourself.
Yes, please.
Like "Please don't come to my room."
Yes, please…
(DON'T COME TO MY ROOM)
That should not happen.
PROTECTING HER SPACE
I'll lock my door shut,
then swallow my key card.
No, I'm just kidding.
There's nothing like that.
Then is there anything
that you'd like to try with Gabee?
Things to try?
Gabee and I
have never had drinks together,
so we could have some over good food.
I wanted to say that,
but I didn't want to come on too strong.
That's totally fine.
-Drinking alone with you.
-Sure.
Without any cameras.
I only move when there are cameras.
I went a step too far.
I'm just kidding.
A pleasant drink.
Yeah, we're on vacation.
We're abroad, so we should drink
some Taiwanese beer.
Taiwanese beer.
I can't wait.
A drink with a good meal is the best.
Recently,
I've been into whiskey and tequila.
So Jaejae told me,
"You're following in my footsteps."
-She's a whiskey drinker.
-Yes.
"You're following in my footsteps."
-How many years older is she?
-She's three years older than me.
Her Chinese zodiac is a horse.
Mine's a chicken. What's yours?
Me? Mine's a cow.
Cow? I get on well with cows.
-Don't lie.
-I swear!
Earlier, you asked me my star sign.
"When's your birthday?"
"It's March. It's passed."
"Then are you an Aries?"
"No, a Pisces."
"I get on well with Pisces."
FLIRTING WITH STAR SIGNS
NO CHANCE OF INCOMPATIBILITY
Then you asked, "What are Pisces like?"
And you said,
"I don't know. I'd have to look it up."
I'm still grateful.
It's nice of you to say that.
But honestly,
I get on really well with cows.
Chickens and cows get along.
Because Seung-heon's is a cow,
and I've read that they get on well.
-Are you a chicken?
-Yes.
Chicken.
I like chicken
because my zodiac animal is a chicken.
-It's the chicken song.
-There's an actual song?
I made it.
I like beef
because my Chinese zodiac is a cow.
Moo.
DRIVING DEEPER INTO THE MOUNTAINS
It looks like the home
of a mountain spirit.
With a celestial maiden taking a bath.
-There's so much green.
-There is.
I love the fog.
I strangely do.
AFTER A ONE-AND-A-HALF-HOUR DRIVE,
WE'VE ARRIVED AT WULAI
This is the Wulai Village,
and if we go this way,
we can get foot baths for free.
Really?
-For free?
-Free.
The hot springs here are naturally made.
I heard the locals here
like to use them too.
-It's so quaint.
-Right? Such a cute neighborhood.
Look at the painting.
It's huge.
It's so cute.
It's written here. "Wulai."
All right!
I'm sorry.
-All right, Wulai.
JOINS IN TO KEEP GABEE'S SPIRITS UP
This is such a pretty neighborhood.
I love it.
It's not too crowded and not too loud.
It's pretty cute.
I think a lot of locals come here.
Would you look at that?
The path is so lovely.
I think this painting
is of the Indigenous people.
The Indigenous people
look incredibly charismatic.
-I want to ride this.
-What is it?
Let's ride it.
I think it'll be a thrilling ride.
It's so picturesque.
The trees are so lush.
Is this a massive boulder or a mountain?
It feels like we're in Gangwon-do
in the summer.
-I get you.
-You feel me?
The green here is somewhat greener.
Exactly.
He's doing martial arts.
Wow, you're right.
-Like Qi exercises.
-It looks like it, yes.
-How fascinating.
-I like it here.
You don't get to see this very often.
He's swimming.
I think we wash there before we go in.
You're right.
We're just going to dip our feet.
Yes, just our feet.
I'll just wash my feet.
It's nice and cool.
-Shall we go?
-Yes.
Where should we take a seat?
-Wow, it's warm.
-It is?
It's so warm. It's really warm.
It's the perfect temperature.
-It's not too hot.
-Yes, it's the ideal temperature.
I think the hot water is coming out
from underneath here somewhere.
The water here's cold, though. Touch it.
You're right.
This place is so nice.
We're in the middle of hot and cold.
So we enjoy the hot water,
and when we feel a little too warm…
-You go to the cold water?
-Right away.
Wow, Do-yeon!
Do-yeon, there are fish!
-Where?
-There.
-Hey, you're right. I wanna see.
-They live here.
-It's too cold.
-It's nice and cool.
It's very deep.
Then, when you're feeling cold,
you go back in.
So warm.
Wow.
Wow. Bravo.
It's harder than you'd think
to dive in like this, you know.
It was such an elegant dive.
This is fascinating.
It's like a whole different world.
If I go in here, it's…
Please be careful.
Lucky you have long legs.
Na-rae would just fall in.
Her head would be in the water already.
Lucky I'm me.
Na-rae would have gone for a dive.
Maybe someone's under there
playing a pipe.
Wait. Are you okay in there?
GIGGLING OVER AN IMAGINARY PIPE
We can check the water depth with this.
What is this place?
I think I like it.
I really like this place.
Taiwan and I get along.
Taiwan and I mesh really well.
-Such a peculiar place.
-I want to try catching one.
I think I can.
-Please be careful.
-Okay.
Oh my!
-They're really smart.
-Did they swim away?
Please don't go. I can't go any further.
They're so smart.
Come on.
THUMBS UP
-They're not easy to catch.
-Koreans?
-Yes, Korean!
-We're Korean!
That's great!
-Thank you.
You're a great diver!
I like Korean music.
-Korean music?
-K-pop?
-G-Dragon!
-Rose?
Did he say "Multiflora Rose"? Hold up.
Do-yeon heard him as multiflora rose.
I heard G-Dragon.
Not multiflora rose.
-I was thinking about his age.
-Come on, now.
There's a song by Jang Sa-ik
called "Multiflora Rose."
-Oh, G-Dragon?
-G-Dragon.
I'm so embarrassed.
Taiwanese Dragon!
-T-dragon.
-He's an awesome guy.
This place is so much fun.
Bravo!
Okay!
You enjoy the hot springs,
then catch a few fish.
-Then go for a dive.
-A dive.
Wow, he's good.
It's like watching a coming-of-age movie.
It's so peaceful here.
This place is great.
I love it here.
It's nice being in nature.
I didn't spot any fish.
Please sit.
I can't wrap my head around it.
How is it so warm here?
Exactly. It's so nice and warm.
And it's drizzling.
Right.
The view's great.
This is nice.
It's such a nice place.
The perfect inspiration to write a poem.
What sort of poem?
She was a Pisces
I was a Scorpio
Her zodiac animal was a cow
Mine was a chicken
No matter how we look at it
We were made to be
Don't bother resisting
My charm is like Lucifer's
How drained do you feel right now?
-How exhausted are you?
-Exhausted?
I'm actually recovering.
-This place is doing that, right?
-It's great.
-That's the power of foot baths.
-This is so nice.
This place is lovely.
This is a gift from nature!
GIVING THANKS TO NATURE
GIVING THANKS TO GOD
GIVING THANKS TO EVERYONE
GIVING THANKS TO THE RAIN
GIVING THANKS TO THE WARM WATER
But, above all…
THE GREATEST THANKS TO NETFLIX
Tudum.
I love the atmosphere.
You can go diving
and snack on a watermelon over there.
Because being in the water
makes you hungry.
And when you get cold,
you come here to warm up.
And repeat.
I'm not entirely sure,
but this feels like a love tub.
-A couple's tub.
-Yes, exactly.
-Or a family tub.
They look great together.
They look so peaceful.
Maybe it's because they live with nature,
but they look so peaceful.
This is so nice.
I think it's even better
because you're with me.
-Honestly.
-Thank you.
Truly.
I'm having such a great time
because you're here with me.
That's so sweet of you.
Hey. Let's check out the love tub later.
Hey!
Hey! Let's use the love tub.
The love tub…
It feels a little too soon.
REJECTED
Let's leave on a high note.
-I'm hungry, Do-yeon.
-Wait, you are?
I said that because I thought
you'd want to stay longer.
Give the piper his pipe back.
Yes, I will.
-He's still underwater.
-Is he?
Take your pipe, sir.
-He's got it.
-Good.
-Let's go.
-We're free to go now.
Let's go to eat.
They're making their own coffee.
Could we try a sip?
Okay.
-Really? Thank you!
-Thank you!
Taiwanese oolong tea?
Thank you!
It's slightly tangy.
It's not the oolong tea we know.
This is lovely.
It's delicious.
It feels like my body temperature
has gone up a couple of degrees.
Isn't this lovely?
It is. Today's been perfect.
I love this.
FEELING WARM FROM THEIR KINDNESS
I really love this place.
It has such a great vibe.
We've had a great time.
Let's go.
RECHARGED AFTER A PLEASANT REST
SURROUNDED BY NATURE
-Now, we're going to eat.
-Great!
-Did I tell you about the boar sausages?
-Yes.
Boar sausages.
I think it's there, Do-yeon.
Wow, what's this?
It looks exciting.
The entire place is fascinating
and feels new.
It's so pretty.
It looks just like a hot spring town.
And the more I listen to this,
it feels like white noise.
-Right?
-It's easy on the ears.
It feels like a very mystical place
where anything could happen.
You're absolutely right.
-It's a little unrealistic.
-It is.
It feels entirely different
on the other side of the valley.
How pretty.
There's a lot to see.
Maybe it's there?
-There are a lot of people.
-You're right.
WULAI OLD STREET
A TRADITIONAL STREET
PRESERVING WULAI'S PAST AND CULTURE
WHERE YOU CAN EXPERIENCE VARIOUS FOODS,
CRAFTS, AND INDIGENOUS CULTURE
They sell a lot of sausages.
-There are a lot of people.
-This place looks popular.
This looks delicious.
I think they're queuing. Are you okay?
Queen Gabee is moved.
I can't contain myself.
They look so tasty.
She's talking to the camera
more than she's talking to me.
OH MY GOD
She's not talking to me,
but she's talking to the cameras.
I'm pretty rich,
so I'm going to splurge
as if I'm Paris Hilton.
Clearly, you exchanged money
at the airport.
Hush.
Wow, she's buying a whole load.
Oh, like that?
You douse it in sauce,
then eat it with garlic.
With a slice of garlic?
Thank you.
I can't wait. They look delicious.
The smell is totally up my alley.
This is crazy.
You know what this smells like?
This smells exactly like
the sausages we'd eat
at the end of the day
back in elementary school.
-It smells great.
-The ones that sizzle.
There's no way these taste bad.
See? I told you they would snap.
Wow.
It's so good.
It's seasoned on the inside.
Let's try it like the locals do.
These sausages are so good.
They do have a little…
-Some spices?
-Yes, they have spices.
-But it's so good.
-Not overpowering at all.
-They're not an issue at all.
-It's so good.
This time, I'll try it with garlic.
It's not too spicy.
This is so good.
The slight kick of the garlic
blends really well with the sausage.
It's not spicy at all. It's perfect.
-It elevates the taste.
-Right?
The aftertaste is lovely and crisp.
This is so good.
This place is so good.
Please come and try this.
It's your loss if you don't.
This place is so good.
HER MOVES SAY IT ALL
TIME FOR A QUIZ
WHAT'S GABEE TRYING TO TELL US?
You're saying, "Try them. They shred."
-So delicious.
-Really tasty.
They're perfectly seasoned and very chewy.
They're so addictive.
It's very hard to walk away after one.
I guess this is a market.
You saw I'm loaded, right?
-Tell me whatever you want.
-Do-yeon!
What's this?
-What is this?
-What might it be?
-Shall we try it?
-Yes, shall we?
What is this?
-Mochi!
-Mochi?
XIAOMI MASHU
AN INDIGENOUS TAIWANESE RICE SKEWER
Thank you.
Tteok.
Tteok?
I guess a lot of Koreans come here.
I love trying small bites of everything.
Me too.
The grill isn't too hot.
Sweetened condensed milk.
-And peanuts.
-Peanuts?
(THUMBS UP)
It's very hot.
-It looks so good.
-Thank you!
Are you bad with hot food?
-Shall I try it?
-I think you'll burn yourself.
Shall we wait, or should I try it now?
-Shall we buy drinks first?
-Sure.
This place sells Indigenous drinks.
What do you recommend?
HERO SOMIJU, AN INDIGENOUS DRINK
MADE FROM FERMENTED SORGHUM
DELICATELY SWEET,
WITH A PLUM-LIKE TARTNESS
-Shall we try it? Indigenous drinks.
-It looks good.
Cheers.
Smells like plum.
-It does.
-Like plum wine.
-It tastes like plum.
-It's good. So good.
It has a fermented taste.
It's like plum wine, but more tart.
-It tastes very fresh.
-It is.
MABULAU
A SWEET DRINK WITH A TINGLING FINISH
It smells like rice.
It's so sweet.
-This tastes great.
-This one…
It's like makgeolli, but sweeter.
-Yeah, it's very sweet.
-I like both.
CAUGHT BETWEEN THE TWO
BECAUSE THEY'RE BOTH GOOD
This is tricky.
I think this will pair better with food.
Sounds good. It's a little crisper.
-I think it will be good on ice.
-Let's go with this.
ONE BOTTLE OF THE PLUM-FLAVORED DRINK
Would you like to try this now?
I think my throat is feeling
the alcohol now.
You could totally live here.
What's this?
She dances according to the menu.
Let's go!
It's really soft.
-Let me try it.
-Go on.
It's super soft.
So soft, right? Isn't it good?
Let's go!
Let's go, Jang Do-yeon!
-It's so good.
-Right?
It's not chewy, yet it's so good.
Perfect as an appetizer.
So good. The peanut powder is delicious.
IN LOVE
NOW THEY'VE HAD A FEW BITES OF STREET FOOD
All right, then. Let's go for dinner.
It's so fun trying new foods.
I have a feeling that the food here
will be to our taste.
I do too.
I think their local food
will be so delicious.
-I'm so excited we'll be drinking.
-So am I!
I want to take the plum wine,
pour it over ice,
and then add a dash of Sprite.
-Doesn't that sound good?
-It sure does.
HEADED TO DINNER TALKING ABOUT FOOD
RECOMMENDED BY LOCALS
A TRUE TASTE OF TAIWAN
AT A ROADSIDE EATERY
INEVITABLE YUMMY NOISES
(STILL MAKING THEM)
DO-YEON'S SUDDEN REACTION OUTBURST
Sis!
Thank you!
BUT THIS QUEEN WON'T GO DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT!
Oh my God!
SO GOOD, REALLY GOOD, CRAZY GOOD
VOTE FOR YOUR REACTION QUEEN!
JUST WHEN WE THOUGHT THE DAY WAS OVER…
Do-yeon?
AN ONSLAUGHT OF QUESTIONS
Do you enjoy love talk?
When were you last asked out?
We've covered love,
so now let's talk breakups.
GULP
FINALLY SNAPPED AND WENT ALL OUT
Babe, can you get dressed?
Spending time with Gabee
can never be dull.
UNTIL DO-YEON EVENTUALLY BROKE DOWN
Shin Gabee, please leave.
WILL THEIR DAY
EVER COME TO AN END?
Never have I ever had a crush recently.
Three, two, one.
-I have.
-Have you?
I STILL HAVE A QUESTION LEFT
AND I PROMISE IT WON'T TAKE LONG…