CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
The police confirmed the identity
of a woman in her 40s
who was found dead at an employment
agency in Busan this evening.
The victim was Jang Kyung-ja,
CEO of Navis Well-being,
who was wanted for fraud
and conspiracy for murder.
Jang was found to be in the country,
The police have found evidence
that Jang was murdered,
and have specified a suspect
based on evidence found at the site
and a testimony from an informant.
Lee Ro-eum, you're under arrest
for the murder of Jang Kyung-ja.
Did you kill her?
Answer me.
Jang Kyung-ja.
Did you really kill her?
24 HOURS EARLIER
We received a tip
that the suspect showed up at
Sangjin University Hospital an hour ago,
so we made an emergency arrest.
She had no belongings with her,
and her clothes were sent to forensics.
I don't believe this.
What about the autopsy report?
We'll get it by tomorrow morning.
This is the postmortem report.
We should leak to the press
that the suspect is Lee Ro-eum.
Why would we do that when we
don't even have an arrest warrant?
It'd be impossible
not to get a warrant with this.
Mr. Kim.
We need to use the press
to earn some time at least
so that we can have an excuse.
Keep all details under wraps.
This is no time for tricks.
What's our priority right now?
Did we find any criminal proceeds
or catch the CEO of Navis?
We should least announce to the press
that we caught Jang Kyung-ja's killer.
First, we get the proof
and witness statements,
then we'll file for a warrant.
Whatever situation we're in
and whoever the suspect is,
it changes nothing.
Lee Ro-eum has agreed
to be questioned at night.
She'll be in interrogation room 1
in 30 minutes.
I'll be questioning her myself.
The special investigation team
investigates murders too?
Since it was the CEO
of Navis Well-being who was murdered.
You really don't need a lawyer?
That's you, isn't it?
And that's a gun in your hand.
The time you went to meet the victim
with an illegal weapon
matches the estimated time of her death.
And at the scene,
your fingerprints were found.
Did you go to see the victim with a gun?
Was Jang Kyung-ja shot?
Where did you get the gun?
Where is it now?
What was her cause of death?
Why did you go to see her?
If she wasn't shot dead,
was it something I could've done?
Arson?
If it wasn't a gun or arson,
how could I have overpowered her
in a struggle?
When she was 10cm taller than me?
Were you in a struggle with the victim?
You took my clothes.
Did you get anything from them?
It's being processed.
Do you admit to seeing her?
Was I really the only one
caught on camera?
Yes.
You want to put me away,
don't you?
What did you talk about with the victim?
Why did you take a gun?
Seeing how you're not answering,
it is something self-incriminating?
You agreed to being questioned at night.
I thought you were ready to cooperate.
I can only help you
before the arrest warrant is issued.
You should know how this works
since you've been through it once.
Tomorrow,
I'd like you to start by admitting
that you met the victim.
Put her in lockup.
Got it.
I don't need it anymore.
She didn't ask for a lawyer.
I know.
She's not cooperating.
At this rate, she'll be arrested.
From what I understand,
there's only circumstantial evidence.
That may be true,
but if it meets the arrest requirements,
she will be, you know that.
The biggest problem is that she doesn't
have a permanent address, and…
Because she's a criminal.
As you've seen.
I'm not so unprofessional
to use things that I saw in private.
Don't get me wrong.
But having her arrested
is not the only way.
Unless you have a reason
to make any kind of arrest.
Are you really going to keep this up?
Taking her side?
Why did you quit?
Quit what?
Do I have to explain
and make you understand
how powerless and incompetent I felt
and how hard I've been working on this
despite that?
You have no right to criticize me.
And what? Make any kind of arrest?
There must be grounds to make an arrest.
This person Jay you mentioned?
All we found were his pay slips.
The only person
that I'm most likely to find evidence on
and bring charges against
is Lee Ro-eum, not Lee Jay.
Is there proof she's not the killer?
Then bring it to me.
I will.
I'll get you the proof.
Yes?
I heard from Da-jeong
that Ro-eum was taken in.
Yes.
If you mean to be her lawyer,
I was thinking
maybe you should pass this time.
What is this about?
An article is coming out tomorrow.
My former employer found out
that Han Jae-seok is your father.
I tried to stop it,
but I have no pull. I'm sorry.
I understand.
-Thank you for telling me.
-Sure.
You regret it, don't you?
What?
Bringing me in to the firm.
That was ages ago.
It's not like
I didn't know you.
How long has it been already?
I had just returned to school,
and this freshman
was single-handedly taking up a fight
in a sexual harassment case
of a female student. Wow.
I knew we were in law school,
but I wondered
how you could fight
as if it were your own problem.
Crying at that. You were one crazy dude.
You know,
I was born in a well-to-do family,
but I didn't have a sense of vocation.
I just asked my parents to send me to
the US so that I could go to law school.
All I did there was have a good time,
and the first thing I saw when I got back
was pretty cool.
The power you had
was like a special limited edition.
Something you couldn't get
with money or connections.
So,
since I was going to start my own firm
once I passed the bar,
I believed you could
be the conscience of the firm.
That's why
I hired you myself, so why would I
regret it? I care about you.
But you weren't happy here,
so it bothered me
that I might be the cause.
You're the one who helped me
stick through it this far.
Thank you.
That's true.
An article is coming out tomorrow
about my father.
Along with my name.
Once it comes out,
the Ye Chung-sik case
will come under scrutiny.
It'll seem like I betrayed my client
to cover for my father.
The firm will come under fire too.
I told you in advance this time,
so I hope you forgive me.
RESIGNATION LETTER
What's the truth?
Did you turn Ye Chung-sik in
knowing about your father?
Is that the truth?
I'm also a lawyer who seeks the truth.
I have a duty to defend
the truth too. It's not just you.
I can't turn away from my conscience
just to avoid rumors and fake news…
Gyu.
I have too much money for that.
You'll regret it.
I know. I don't care if I do.
Hey.
I'm rich, you know.
Moo-young, if someone
tries to bring you down,
fight back until the end,
like you always do.
It's taken me this long to tell you that.
So, it's settled then.
We're good enough friends
for me to do this for you, right?
We are.
Here, take this back.
It's giving me heartburn.
It's the list of Navis' earnings
including the gift certificates.
Since you want to
divert everything overseas,
that's how I'll proceed.
What about the search
into domestic accounts?
There'll be some loss,
but it's within the estimated range.
The trail will go dead with CEO Jang.
They won't be able to track anything
further than that.
I prepared two tickets.
The departure date is next week.
You think you can meet the deadline?
When Han Jae-seok turned himself in,
a sketch of my face was circulated.
-I don't have much room to--
-I know.
I'm asking…
if you can handle the kids
before you get caught.
If we want to get Ro-eum out,
you have to go in instead of her.
You should hurry.
And what if it gets traced back to us
while hurrying?
When Ro-eum gets out,
I don't want her to have
any options.
And so,
we rule as follows against the defendant.
Defendant Lee Ro-eum
is sentenced to 15 years in prison.
You're early.
-Well…
-Would you like some coffee?
It's okay. I'll get it myself.
In-young.
Can you forward all calls to me?
And for the time being,
set up online appointments only.
Okay, I'll do that.
Gyu.
Hello?
This morning, the police arrested Han
who turned himself in
for the Geumseong murders.
The police are suspected of
trying to close the case
through an internal investigation.
Questions are being raised
regarding his son, a lawyer,
therefore whether the total truth will
come out about the Geumseong murders
will be watched with keen interest.
Hello?
Da-jeong, it's me.
Are you at the comic book store?
Why do you ask?
I wanted to ask you something.
Which hospital is Ringo in?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to hurt you,
but it seems like Ro-eum can't focus
because of you guys.
Da-jeong.
I think Jay
really is going to take Ro-eum this time.
That's why he had her arrested.
Once he gets rid of us,
everything will go his way.
What are we going to do?
We don't have time.
And I'm out of options to save Ro-eum.
I have a way.
I'm going to save her
and keep you all safe too.
I will.
Yes, Mr. Han.
Are you at the repair shop?
Yes, I'm about to go see Ringo
at the hospital.
I was just picking up some stuff.
I need you to come to the comic store.
As soon as you can.
What? Why?
Be careful.
Okay.
Got it.
Hello?
Doctor, this is Han Moo-young.
Yes, hello.
I'm sorry for suddenly calling you.
It's all right.
I saw the article.
It couldn't be more wrong. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I wanted to ask you for a favor.
Can you find a new hospital for me?
Ringo's safety is on the line.
Do you know a place
where we could get some help?
I know a place. My cousin runs a hospice.
-Su-ho!
-Help!
Move!
Get in!
-What the hell?
-What?
I'm so dizzy.
What about Lee Ro-eum's clothes?
It was black, so it wasn't
noticed at first, but blood was found.
It's being analyzed for DNA.
These are the forensic results.
Let's listen to a recording.
I have a bomb
that will blow up the Closing.
I was thinking about
cutting a deal with you.
Navis Well-being's network was hacked,
and at the presentation, Ma Kang-su's
stock manipulation was exposed.
This is the conversation you had
with the victim that day.
Since you have an exceptional memory,
I'm sure you remember.
The exposure of stock manipulation…
Were you behind it?
Did you do it alone or did you have help?
Let's say I did. But because of it,
Navis Well-being's fraud was exposed,
and you became the head
of the special investigation team.
Is that so?
You made me the team leader?
Putting aside the fact
that it's a violation of the law,
this recording tells me a few things.
You and Jang Kyung-ja
were not on good terms.
It could be your motive.
And you
have the ability
to hack into Navis's network.
Like the way you got your hands
on an illegal gun,
it suggests that you are capable
of committing a crime.
Also,
you asked about
the Chairman in the recording.
Who is this Chairman?
Why are you asking
like you never heard of him?
Because I haven't.
So tell me.
I heard you received a tip
on who the real owner
of Navis Well-being is.
That the Chairman is Lee Jay.
We questioned 36 people involved,
out of which three were arrested.
They all claim that the main culprit
is Jang Kyung-ja, and evidence shows
that she is the final beneficiary
of Navis Well-being as well.
And so, this investigation
depended on capturing Jang Kyung-ja.
Until someone killed her.
If that's your claim, then all right.
Why are you looking for this Chairman?
The Chairman was the head of Red Eye,
the scholarship foundation I was part of,
and he's the one who made me like this.
Though I'm sure
it's your first time hearing of this.
Then you must've gone
to see the victim that day
to ask about the Chairman.
This is your phone we found at the scene.
You looked up drugs with it, didn't you?
The kind you gave to the victim.
You have both a motive
and the capabilities,
and you met with the victim, with a gun
at the time of her presumed death.
She was strangled to death,
unable to fight back
because of the drugs you looked up.
Even if she was considerably bigger
than you, you could've killed her.
What happened that day?
Can you still lock up people these days
based on circumstantial evidence?
You think this is all we have?
Lawyer.
I want my lawyer.
And who is that?
Han Moo-young.
Haven't you heard?
His father is
part of the Geumseong murders.
Where did you hear that?
The news broke this morning.
That Han Moo-young is
the son of one of the killers
in the Geumseong murders.
Despite knowing that,
you still wanted him as your lawyer?
People are saying
that he leaked the recording
with Ye Chung-sik to cover for his father.
Of course,
I know that's not true.
However,
I'm doing everything I can
so word doesn't get out of your arrest.
We're trying to protect you.
I'm telling you
that reporters' eyes are on this case.
There were three in total,
and they had knives.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Su-ho got a nasty shock though.
I'll be requesting police protection, but…
He may have gotten away from them today,
but will this be enough
to keep him safe? What do you think?
It probably won't be.
Then what?
For starters, watch over Ringo.
Doctor Mo will be here too.
Okay, I'll be in touch.
Stay safe.
No, you can't.
This is not what we wanted.
You'll be in trouble for this too.
I need your help.
I know that this is
a difficult decision for you both.
We're fine with it.
It's not like we weren't prepared
for this and we're used to it too.
But you're different.
If you get caught,
there's no coming back from it.
You won't be able to be a lawyer anymore.
It's just a job.
I don't care.
To the Chairman, this is just a game.
And I'm going to change the rules.
EMPATHY DILEMMA
HOW THE LAWYER FACED THE TRUTH
Wow, look at the views.
People these days don't read the news.
LAWYER HAN MOO-YOUNG
Yes, Mr. Han.
Mr. Woo, do you still have the pass
to the Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office?
Yes. Hold on.
I meant to return it.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Yes, of course.
It's me.
I borrowed a phone.
I need a lawyer.
Good thinking.
I don't think I can do this on my own.
Can you come?
Okay, I'll be right there.
-Attorney Han?
What are you here for?
Why did you release the recording?
Did you know
your father was one of the killers?
Please comment.
A judge will review
the warrant at 8 p.m. tomorrow.
It's harsher on suspects
who don't have permanent addresses,
but you're denying the allegations
and suspected of owning a gun,
so you'll probably be taken into custody.
I'm really being taken into custody?
Yes.
It's most likely.
I told Da-jeong that I would end this.
But I lose again?
Ro-eum.
I heard about the article.
I'm sorry
about how things ended.
I don't think I can keep my promise
to be your lawyer.
It might be better this way.
You'll need
someone objective and practical,
not someone like me
who's tangled up in this case.
Are things so bad for me
that you're giving up?
It's not the worst.
I'm going to get you out of here.
So tell him what you know.
Did you kill her?
Answer me.
Jang Kyung-ja.
Did you kill her?
I want you to bring in
my accomplices.
What?
I had help.
Are you admitting to your crime?
The accomplices. We're asking you
to question Na Su-ho and Jeong Da-jeong.
My client won't be saying another word
until you do.
What do you think you're doing?
Is this a joke to you?
No. What about you?
Bring in the accomplices.
Have them confront each other.
That won't be possible.
Who knows what they'll be planning?
Yes, Mr. Han.
Da-jeong.
Did you get there okay?
Yes.
Mr. Go and I brought everything we needed.
You'll be summoned first thing tomorrow.
Come as soon as you get the call.
I will.
Lee Ro-eum has to be arrested
to write a huge story
on her and Han Moo-young.
The warrant will go through, right?
When does the news embargo lift?
Soon, I guess.
But don't you think it's odd?
If Han Moo-young's father killed
her parents, why doesn't she fire him?
Why does she still have him as her lawyer?
This is supposed to be a news embargo,
so watch what you're saying.
Why is everyone
talking about classified details?
And did none of you read my piece?
It has everything you need to know.
Han Moo-young didn't know about it
during the Ye Chung-sik case
or the damages…
Who reads articles by freelancers?
It wasn't even exclusive.
Weren't you fired?
Why haven't you returned your pass yet?
I'm here to do that now.
You came to return your pass
with all your gear?
A journalist should always be prepared.
Where am I being questioned today?
Interrogation rooms are inside.
What's the room number?
Last time I was here, it was so freezing
that my face almost got paralyzed.
I'm not kidding.
You'll be in 712 on the 7th floor.
Thanks.
What do you have in your bag?
Just my laptop.
The prosecutor gave us
specific instructions…
We'll hold on to your laptop
until you get back.
All right.
Thank you.
Name.
Jeong Da-jeong.
Occupation?
I run an auto repair shop.
And address?
It's the same as my comic store.
I see you have a record.
Yes, I do.
How do you know Lee Ro-eum?
We grew up together
at the same foundation.
Red Eye, you mean?
Yes.
And what did you learn to do there?
Hacking.
Did they also teach you how to shoot?
Do I have to answer that?
Were you part of exposing
Navis Well-being's stock manipulation?
Yes.
You helped Lee Ro-eum?
We did it together.
Did you kill Jang Kyung-ja
together too?
Did Ro-eum say she killed her?
If she named you as an accomplice,
it's good as admitting to it.
If that's what she said, it must be true.
Then do you admit it?
If she is the real killer.
Do you have proof that Ro-eum killed her?
Did you help Ro-eum kill her or not?
If you don't have any proof,
why should I confess to anything?
Lee Ro-eum says she'll confess if they do,
and they say they'll confess
if Lee Ro-eum does…
They're running us around in circles.
And they're not demanding to leave.
Still no word on the warrant?
Sir.
I just confirmed
that Na Su-ho's probation officer
is the same as Lee Ro-eum's.
Call him in.
Yes, sir.
I thought you'd question me
in the kind of room
you see in dramas with a two-way mirror.
You're in charge of Lee Ro-eum
and Na Su-ho, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
And you must know she's been arrested.
I do.
Na Su-ho is being questioned as a witness.
He could be complicit in a murder.
As their probation officer,
were you aware of their conspiracy
to commit murder?
I'm so insulted.
Do I look like someone
who wouldn't have reported it
if I had known anything about it?
So, you had no problems with them?
With either Lee Ro-eum or Na Su-ho?
What was so urgent
that you put out a BOLO on her?
It was all done by the book.
Lee Ro-eum and her accomplices
hacked into Navis Well-being…
If you're investigating Navis Well-being,
shouldn't you be investigating
their fraud?
And not the people who exposed it?
On what authority?
What authority did they have
to dig into Navis Well-being?
Are they prosecutors? Or the police?
Who gave them the authority?
Whose side are you on?
Not on the side of a murderer,
that's for sure.
Ha…
Shouldn't they be presumed innocent
until found guilty?
If you didn't know about it,
that makes you incompetent.
But if you did know and ignored it,
that makes you an accomplice.
Considering your job,
just having overlooked it
could be a problem.
If you tell me
what you know right here and now,
I'll make sure you don't get penalized.
This is your last chance.
I don't find that acceptable.
As long as I'm my mother's son,
I also need to be accountable
for the crimes those people committed.
What are you talking about?
My mother was one of the people at Red Eye
who turned Lee Ro-eum and the others
into criminals.
Her name is Professor Shin Seo-ra.
You probably know her if you had a TV
in your home in the 90s. That's my mother.
It's hard to explain
who Lee Ro-eum and Na Su-ho are
without getting into Red Eye.
Including the crimes they've committed
and the ones you're suspecting them of.
So,
Professor Shin is an important witness.
She won't come of her own accord.
But if you tell her
her son is being questioned
for helping the Red Eye Kids,
she'll come running.
Professor Shin, right?
Is it true you were a consultant
for Red Eye Foundation?
Are you being questioned
in regards to Red Eye?
Is it true you kept
the kids locked up and brainwashed them?
Please comment.
How deeply
is Yo-han involved?
Is it serious?
How could you make me
come to the prosecutors' office?
Is this your way of acting out?
Did it inconvenience you that much?
Some people spent ten years
behind bars because of you.
You came here because of me.
Because your own child is precious.
Now when people talk about Red Eye,
your name will always come up as well.
You're the one who called them?
The reporters?
Once the warrant is issued,
you'll be taken to a detention center.
Counselor.
Anything more to say?
No, your honor.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Do you feel that you've been wronged,
or do you have anything to say?
Please wait until a decision is made.
Even after a warrant is issued,
you may file an objection.
Put the cuffs on her.
Excuse me. I need to use the rest room…
The transport vehicle is here?
Yes.
Did you hear that?
The warrant has been issued,
and you'll be taken to a detention center.
Come on out.
You're walking me to the car yourself?
I had hoped
you would cooperate a little more.
All day, I asked people if they helped you
and why they did,
but I got nothing.
That's their way of helping me.
Aren't you curious
about why people help others?
To pay back a debt?
Because their interests align?
Because they don't
want to be a bad person?
Or…
is it really because of empathy?
What about you?
Why did you help me?
I'm Ryu Jae-hyeok.
I'm with the criminal division at SCDPO.
I hoped that with my help,
the outcome would change.
Instead of the outcome changing me.
That day,
I went to kill Jang Kyung-ja.
I'm only doing this…
to protect the people I care about.
I never wanted you to die. I just…
I just…
wanted you to help me. Was that so hard?
It was the same with me.
Actually,
I don't know.
Maybe I didn't want to.
I was glad to hear
that you wanted to leave,
but it was insulting too.
While you were in prison, I was
trapped in that night as well.
How was it for you?
I've never regretted it.
I killed my husband that day
because I wanted to
and because I wanted
to truly own everything I had,
so I kept it.
Was it worth it?
Was that bastard worth it?
I made
him worthy.
I gave him everything.
Do you know why I hated you so much?
Because you're like Jay.
You understand him naturally,
and you easily found a way
into his impenetrable mind,
but not me.
I had to work hard at it,
and it came with a price.
If threats were what it took to have him,
then that's what I had to do.
You crazy bitch, that was your reason?
What about my parents?
What about the kids?
While you were protecting the bastard
who only you found worthy,
do you know how many people died?
You may not have killed them yourself,
but didn't you feel guilty at all?
My parents were innocent,
but they were killed.
At least,
you should've given them time
to live with regret.
It was regretful.
Do you want an apology?
No.
If I want to meet the Chairman again,
I have to kill you.
Those are the rules now.
It's the only way.
So, if you want to live,
think well and hard.
Think of a way for me to get to him
without killing you.
We won't be leaving this place
until we do.
Is it true?
You have no reason
to lie to me anymore.
Did Jay really tell you to kill me?
You?
I'm sending someone over.
I'm sending her with my phone
and my business card
with my signature on it,
so when she arrives,
open my safe for her.
Give her everything
that's in there.
Yes.
Everything, no strings attached.
Make sure she gets it,
especially if I die.
That was the general manager
at Haemyeong Hotel.
Use this to open the safe.
Take everything inside.
With it, you can prove one thing.
That I answered to Ji Seung-don.
The fact that Jay was the one
using that name
is something you'll have to prove.
Whether you investigate
or hack information with it,
do what you have to do.
I'm not doing this for you.
And I'm not doing this
because I don't trust Jay.
I just need to hear it
from him for myself.
I deserve that much at least.
I'm curious…
You had no reason to let me live, and yet…
Let's not see each other ever again,
Ro-eum.
Is this true?
Why didn't you tell me when I asked?
If I had, would you have believed me?
Besides, I still have some work to do
before I hand over that evidence.
You'll get it soon.
In the way you want it.
Also, considering my bad experience
with them in the past,
I couldn't fully trust the prosecutors.
Even ten years ago, you people arrested me
based on circumstantial evidence
and suspicions alone.
I never expected to feel this way,
but I had hoped a little
that you would know the truth
without me having to pull a con.
So this is
somewhat
on you people too.
What?
Once the warrant is issued,
you'll be taken to a detention center.
It's locked from the other side.
Lee Ro-eum is taking the emergency stairs
from the fifth floor.
Stop her from getting out.
Seal off the stairs and all exits!
3 HOURS BEFORE THE ARREST
So, you took it?
Kyung-ja's cell phone.
What are you going to do with it?
What did you do…
to her?
What do you think?
What do you think will happen now?
Ro-eum.
I meant it
when I said I'd get you back.
Jang Kyung-ja is dead.
I might get arrested.
Why would you?
He'll make it that way.
He's done it before.
No. We have Mr. Han now…
I don't have an alibi,
and I have a record,
so it's likely I'll be arrested.
In the meantime,
there's something you need to do.
This is everything Jang Kyung-ja
gathered on Ji Seung-don.
Find proof that Jay is connected…
No, it doesn't even have to be that.
Just find as much as you can
so that we can make a deal
with the Chairman.
This is the only option
we have left.
I'm asking you for one last favor.
Help me…
so that I can end this, Da-jeong.
How far along are you
with what Ro-eum asked you to do?
It'll be ready by tonight.
Is Ro-eum really going to be arrested?
The warrant will be issued?
We're going to get Ro-eum out.
And by that, you mean…
I'm going to break her out
from the prosecutors' office.
So tell him what you know.
Tell him
that your accomplices are
Da-jeong and Su-ho
so that they'll be summoned
tomorrow morning.
They'll come and prepare your escape.
The way from holding to the basement
parking lot is the best route.
Once the warrant is issued,
you'll get taken out that way.
Once you escape,
those two will be detained on the spot.
They'll be protected.
So that they're safe.
I'll prepare what you asked.
So go and end this.
I thought you'd stop me from going alone.
This is something
you need to end yourself.
Only you can do it.
Thanks.
For your support.
Tell them I'm the one who made you
do it.
Okay.
Mr. Woo, do you still have the pass
to the Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office?
INFORMATION ON FLOORS, ACCESS
LAWYER HAN
A WARRANT FOR LEE RO-EUM'S ARREST
HAS BEEN ISSUED
I need to use the restroom…
Hello?
What do you mean, you can't find her?
Check the CCTV footage.
Find out where Jeong Da-jeong
and Na Su-ho were in this building today.
Police!
Ringo will stay where he is
but in a different room.
Da-jeong and Su-ho, go to the hospice.
Take Yoo-il and Yoo-neung
instead of Ringo.
Get admitted under Ringo's name.
Once you do, I'll call the police.
By the way,
you might be getting some calls
about the research you did.
I got so mad and called the reporters…
I'm sorry about that.
Because of my foul temper…
Don't worry about it.
If you feel any guilt
about the professor
over what you did today,
give me a call.
I'll provide counseling.
Wow, it's late. Don't you have to go?
Yes, I should be going.
I hope that everyone is safe.
It's true.
I have important documents
which will be released if I die.
I'm not lying.
Everything that has
Ji Seung-dong's name on it.
Navis' earnings were
laundered under his name.
They'll soon realize
that the name is a front,
and once they investigate who's behind it,
the net will close down
on you.
Come with me.
I'm giving you a chance.
Are you threatening me?
I'm not doing this to attack you.
I wanted to protect you and me.
It was the same with the notebook.
I just held on to it.
I may have hidden it from you,
but I didn't show it to anyone.
It was the only way to protect us.
Kyung-ae.
Do you even believe what you're saying?
Why won't you believe me? Why?
If you don't trust me, who will?
Then,
what about you?
Do you trust me?
I do.
So you can trust me too.
Drink this.
If you trust me,
prove it.
Did you really
send Ro-eum to kill me?
You couldn't even bother
to kill me yourself?
Do I mean so little to you?
You had to send Ro-eum? How could you?
Do you think anyone else
will love you as much as I do?
Can you really…
live without me?
Will you really…
be fine without me?
You bastard.
Jeong Da-jeong.
You're under arrest
for helping Lee Ro-eum escape.
-Cuff her.
-Yes, sir.
Na Su-ho.
You're under arrest
for helping Lee Ro-eum escape.
There's no answer from the Messenger.
I'LL GO BACK TO MY PLACE.
Can you also install a GPS
on Ro-eum's phone?
Not an app, a device.
And what's next?
I'm going where she goes.
I'm not going to make her
fight on her down.
You said
you'd be there once I ended all of this.
If it's me the Chairman wants so badly,
there is a weapon I could use.
Meet Lee Jay.
And see the proof that it's him.
Are you insane?
You pulled something this rash
over that tiny possibility?
Once Ro-eum sends the signal,
get to her on time.
Unlike Ro-eum,
I don't care if you live or die.
You think I'm like you?
Me?
I'm sure that's what you hoped.
You'll never get away from me.
Doesn't it excite you?
You like choices.