BASED ON A NOVEL BY DOK MAI SOD
You also want to see your brother happy.
So why don't we work together?
Help him eliminate the competition.
It's the scent of Thai flowers.
It's not a scent any man would wear.
If she gets married first,
it would mean that Sa-ngad
and Sa-Ang will never be married.
Is this all your plan, Sawaeng?
Is that her new suitor?
Anong is trying to prove
that she can look after herself.
Jamlong and Sawaeng might use this chance
to have their guys befriend Anong.
Wichai doesn't have a wife.
Haven't I told you?
He's a widower.
Wichai is probably traumatized
by what happened.
Since then, he's never been
interested in any woman.
He found love,
but fate took her away from him.
That's what I call unfortunate.
Don't forget that I invited Kacha
to come have dinner at our house.
Kacha wants us to be his dealer
and find furniture for the embassy.
A dealer?
Did you tell him you'd do it?
That's why I invited him.
I want my brothers to help
talk to him about the contract.
Hello.
Is it Choy? How is Samarn doing?
Is it Choy?
I wouldn't have to get up
if you came down sooner.
What is it?
Do it now. The guy fessed up.
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
SUKNIWAS RESIDENCE, 5:00 PM
It's your first time in court.
Are you scared?
The court doesn't base
their ruling on appearances.
What you wear
doesn't affect
the weight of your testimony.
Don't be embarrassed.
No! Stop!
Stop it!
So you finally show your face?
You scammed me
and tricked me into marrying you.
- Damn you!
- Stop, ma'am.
- Please, ma'am.
- You're a monster!
Please calm down.
You can go to hell!
- Gosh!
- Anan!
Well, what do we have here?
Are you the mistress
that helped him scam money from me?
- No!
- Stop it, ma'am!
Why have a trial at all
if you're going to resort to violence?
Take her away to calm down.
You need to keep
your client under control.
- Come on.
- Where are you taking me?
Let me go.
I didn't think baking would be this hard.
These aren't edible.
Don't serve them. You can throw them away.
Let me prepare something else
for our guest.
Please help set the table
and take care of the flower arrangement.
Everything has to be perfect today.
We must show Kacha that
we're accustomed to Western culture.
We must convince him
that we can work with the embassy.
He said he has an appointment
with Mr. Pong, so I let him in.
Another appointment?
Yes, ma'am.
I heard that Pong asked you
to meet with him today.
Are you sure
you got the date right this time?
He said all his brothers are busy,
so he asked me to come.
What's that?
Well, I saw someone
about to throw the scones away,
so I asked to have one.
I didn't want your staff
to have to prepare food for me,
so I told them I could eat the leftovers.
Goodness.
Listen, Wichai.
Stop.
Did you swallow it?
Spit it out. I said spit it out.
Don't chew it. Wichai.
Wichai, don't chew it.
Stop chewing.
Well, I…
This is quite good,
considering it's your first time baking.
Your guest is here.
Should I let him in, ma'am?
From the looks of you,
you probably tried
to bake for him yourself.
If I were him, I'd be very happy.
Please follow me to the living room.
This way, sir.
Actually, I have
urgent business to attend to.
- I have to go.
- Wait, sir.
Sir, wait a moment. Sir.
Your guest said
he had urgent business to attend to.
What did you say?
Mr. Kacha was here.
He apologized
that he couldn't stay for dinner.
He asked me to give you this.
But Mr. Wichai is still here.
Everyone is asking about you downstairs.
It's just Pong and his friend.
They can keep each other company.
But Wichai came all the way here.
You should come down for his sake.
How can I face him?
What happened earlier was so embarrassing.
Why must I embarrass myself
every time I see him?
I know.
You're so used to being this perfect girl.
Why don't you try to relax
and be yourself like when you're with me?
You know, you look kind of cute
when you're pouting like this.
There has to be a guy
who likes this side of you.
This guy has good taste.
I'd rather not drink today.
I have a mouth ulcer.
Then you should drink Utaitip syrup.
It will make you feel better.
It can help cure mouth ulcers
and it's also refreshing.
All right then.
I'M SORRY, THE AMBASSADOR
REQUESTED MY ASSISTANCE
Anong didn't suspect at all that it was
Jamlong and Sawaeng who sent Kacha.
So how can we know whether
she's already given him her heart?
That's easy.
If Anong really likes this man,
she will never criticize
his taste in anything.
What's gotten into you today?
You're unusually clever.
We have to convince Anong
and make her believe
that this guy has bad taste.
We've been waiting for you to join us.
Cheers.
It's a shame
the person who brought us
this wine couldn't join us.
Right.
You're right.
He brought us top-notch wine.
Then let's invite him
to join us next time.
Sure.
But can we not drink
rotten wine next time?
I was wondering
how you could drink that.
It tastes horrible.
Or are you biased
because you know who brought it?
What's that?
- It's nothing.
- What is it?
- It's really nothing.
- Prasit.
- It's nothing.
- Stop, Anong.
- Anong.
- Come on, Anong.
- It's nothing.
- Leave Prasit alone.
You're upsetting him. Stop.
Just take it. Gosh.
Utaitip syrup.
What's the meaning of this?
Well…
Is this another one of your tests?
I just said you were clever.
You blew it.
That was my idea.
Don't blame Wichai.
Do you also think
that I can't think for myself?
It's not like that.
I just wanted to know
how you really feel about that guy.
Why must you all try to find fault
with every guy I date?
Prasit.
If you also question me,
I'll have no one left
that's sincere to me.
No, we're all just looking out for you.
Please don't be mad, Anong.
I'll let you flick my ear if you want.
Flick my ear really hard. Go on.
Prasit.
We're siblings. We don't hurt each other.
Maybe just a little.
But you said you wouldn't hurt me.
Liar.
So do you forgive me?
Are you working on this case?
You're so good
at solving others' problems,
yet you're unbothered
by the problems in your own house.
DOZENS OF WOMEN GOT SCAMMED
BY THE SAME MAN
Are you talking about Chut again?
You're becoming
more and more like your father.
He protected his subordinate
and left his family to starve to death.
Take a look at this.
All these women are in debt
because of love.
When your dad got discharged
from government service,
it was me who had to borrow
people's money to care for our family.
Now you're turning a blind eye
to what's going on.
But I don't see
that Chut is in any kind of trouble.
Marriage and love
are two different things.
If you let Chut marry the girl he loves,
he's going to spend all his money on her.
Do you want to see
his life get ruined like that?
Didn't you see what happened to Choy?
She married that man
though his family despises her.
In the end, they both got cut off
by their families.
She will be left to pay off
his debt once he's gone.
She's throwing her life away
all because of love!
Did you fight with Mom again?
Hey.
Who's with Samarn if you're out here?
Samarn's sister quit her job
and comes to nurse him every day.
She's been a big help to me.
Chantorn is Samarn's stepsister.
But their family won't let her
use the family name
because she was born out of wedlock.
Samarn's the only one
who stays in contact with her.
Everyone thinks that Chantorn
will become a mistress like her mom.
It's so hard being a woman.
It all depends on the man we marry
how our lives will turn out.
Here you go.
Hey.
It's you.
This is Wichai.
Choy's eldest brother.
I heard that Choy's brother is a judge.
So it's you.
I also didn't expect to see you here.
I suspected that
you might be nursing someone.
I saw potassium permanganate stains
on your dress the other day.
But I didn't think
that someone would be Samarn.
Why did you get fired from your job?
The jewelry shop owner thought
I double-crossed her
and gave the jewelry to the thief to sell.
You mean Sompob, the guy who was
at the court the other day?
I know him by the name of Anan.
Anan is our customer.
- Hello.
- He knows a lot of diplomats.
I'd like to speak to the owner.
He often comes by to look for jewelry
for the ambassador's wife.
He's also a salesperson like me.
The difference is that I work at the store
while he takes the jewelry
and sells it to important people.
ANAN KLAIKARN
At first, he would take Madam
to meet the clients with him.
But lately, he would take
the jewelry to sell on his own.
There were many occasions where
he asked me to prepare jewelry for him.
We had no idea
that he used those pieces
of jewelry to deceive women.
He even gave the jewelry
to those women as dowry.
When he returned the jewelry to us,
those women thought he stole
the jewelry from them to sell for profit.
Our shop then bought
the stolen jewelry from him.
I only found out that day
that Anan stole our jewelry
to use for his own gain.
The shop owner accused me
of working together with him.
We all got duped by him
because he sometimes brought us
money for the jewelry he sold.
He probably got the money
from scamming women.
Then he would buy more jewelry
to trick his next victim.
When he found out
that I would testify in court,
he wrote me a letter
begging me not to testify against him.
Can I see that letter?
Here.
DEAR CHANTORN,
PLEASE DON'T TESTIFY IN COURT
FOR THE SAKE OF OUR RELATIONSHIP
The police informed us that a famous hotel
is suing an embassy staff
who's been staying with them for months
without paying for the room
as well as the food and alcohol bill.
The police suspect that he may be
the same person as the thief in our case.
I feel like I've seen this before.
DEAR CHANTORN
Do you still have his business card?
- Can I see it?
- Sure.
Here you go.
ANAN KLAIKARN
I didn't dare throw it away.
I thought I could use it
to prove my innocence.
BANGKOK, TEL. 32254
The grilled egg vendor asked me
to sell this to Madam for him.
He meant to give it to his lover
as an engagement gift.
But I suspect that
that guy was sent here by someone
to talk business with Anong as a cover.
This guy has good taste.
The police informed us that a famous hotel
is suing an embassy staff
who's been staying with them
without paying for the room
as well as the food and alcohol bill.
Anan is our customer.
He knows a lot of diplomats.
He often comes by to look for jewelry
for the ambassador's wife.
You scammed me
and tricked me into marrying you.
You have the nerve to trick other women
when you already have a wife.
Please follow me to the living room.
Actually, I have
urgent business to attend to.
I have to go.
Can I help you, sir?
Sir.
DEAR CHANTORN
I'M SORRY
This is why he ran away that day.
Where is Anong?
Is it this place?
I think so.
This is the address on the business card.
You just hung up with him.
It's possible that he's hiding here.
I'd like to ask him as well
why did he have to lie to me.
Is anyone home?
Kacha.
I have another way.
Goodness, Wichai!
Are you sure about this?
Wichai!
Wichai, stop!
Let's not do this!
Wait for me here.
WIBOON WATTANA
ANAN KLAIKARN
Is it him?
I think so, but we're too late.
But there's enough evidence
to give to the police.
He has many names and identities.
There must be other victims.
I was such a fool.
How could I fall for his lies?
Everyone has a weakness.
Scammers know how to use
those weaknesses to their advantage.
So what's my weakness?
Your weakness is you want acceptance.
You're trying
to prove yourself to your brothers.
You want to help them
run the store, right?
How can this man
know so much about my personal life?
If I know about it, it's not strange
that others know as well.
SOMYOD PANPETCHAKUL
MANOP THEPDEE
KACHA CHINNAWORN
SINTHAI BANK
If you're here to see Kacha,
you're too late.
Jamlong.
What are you doing here?
Well, I…
Are you here because Kacha Chinnaworn
is a comprador for your bank?
Don't tell me he scammed you
out of money too.
Does this mean
you and Kacha knew each other?
He was the middleman.
He took me to the bank to deposit money
and took all of it for himself.
I have nothing left.
I can assure you.
He didn't open an account with us.
I got scammed by him too.
Don't tell me
that you tried to set me up with him.
Do you realize you almost got
a con artist to be your brother-in-law?
How would I know that
he wanted to scam us for money?
This guy doesn't just want money.
He wants Anong's inheritance.
You might've been outsmarted by him,
but you've really hurt
your sister's feelings.
I didn't expect this from you, Jamlong.
You tried to set me up with a guy
for your own benefit.
I saw that he has connections.
He brought a lot of money to our bank.
He got that money from scamming women.
If you can't read people,
you should worry about yourself
before you try to set me up with someone.
Please, Anong.
Don't tell Pong about this.
That nosy bastard.
He's probably going to tell Pong
so you can end up with his brother.
And you're still just a selfish person
who only cares about yourself.
Wichai is an outsider,
but he protected me more than you did.
If we weren't siblings,
you would be a stranger to me.
It's Wichai
who cares for me like a brother.
Wichai!
Wichai, stop!
You might've been outsmarted by him,
but you've really hurt
your sister's feelings.
I heard about what happened.
Wichai is such an observant guy.
He helped protect you
from a bad guy yet again.
He just happened
to be working on this case.
Let's see here.
What's this?
They are samples from the store.
I want to give one to Wichai.
I accidentally tore his shirt.
But I'm not sure which size would fit him.
This might be too big.
If something unexpected happens,
it's called a coincidence.
But when coincidence keeps happening,
it's called destiny.
What did you say?
It's destiny.
What happened between you and Wichai
isn't just a coincidence.
It's me again.
Is this the friend you invited?
No.
Stop.
Did you swallow it?
Spit it out. I said spit it out.
Don't chew it. Wichai.
I do run into him a lot.
See?
It's not a coincidence.
It's destiny.
It's not.
He's Chut's big brother.
How can it be destiny?
It's a small world. That's all.
But…
if there's another coincidence,
you have to believe it's destiny.
Deal?
It can't be.
It can't be destiny.
Just wait and see
whether it's destiny or not.
The police issued
an arrest warrant for him.
We've discovered that
this guy is named Manop.
He used to be a market vendor
and a chauffeur for a foreigner.
He used the foreigner's car
to trick people that he was rich.
He also sent me this picture.
He lived a lavish lifestyle
to trick women
into falling in love with him.
He scammed money from those women
before running away.
He went from a prince
to a woman's nightmare.
Our society judges people
based on appearances.
It's all thanks to you
that we were able to expose this man.
He's managed to get away with it until now
because most women were
too embarrassed to press charges
since people might say they deserved it.
If you see him again,
what will you do?
I'll probably make him apologize to you.
All done.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, Wichai.
Why are you thanking me?
You helped fix my shirt for me.
Thank you for showing sympathy
for a victim like me.
You can thank me
after I help you get your job back.
I don't want to work there anymore.
Where does Wichai usually go
to have lunch?
He usually eats near here.
And what time
does he usually get off work?
It depends on what time
he gets back from the court.
Does he usually go straight home?
Or does he make a stop
at the Barristers Club first?
You should come back later if you didn't
make an appointment with him.
Mr. Wichai is a busy man.
Please, sir.
The exit is that way.
Prasit.
Wichai.
You should've told me you were coming.
I have to leave for a meeting soon.
What are you doing?
I came to thank you
for catching the thief.
I see.
Don't worry about it.
We're all acquaintances here.
Anong is like a friend of my brother's.
That sounds so distant.
Can't she be more than that?
You got a nice family name.
Right.
You mean she can be my sister-in-law?
No.
Anong can be more than that.
Do you still have a mouth ulcer?
That's my brother-in-law's
Chinese herbal medicine.
I pick it up for him every three days.
This is from Easae Pharmacy.
What a coincidence. Do you go there often?
Well, occasionally.
There's a shaved ice store
near the pharmacy.
I really like to go there with Anong.
Have you ever been there?
Maybe we'll run into each other.
I hope I'll get to see you there.
If we keep running into each other,
it will no longer be a coincidence.
Aren't you tired
of having shaved ice every day?
No, I'm not.
I can't have enough of it.
Goodness. I see you complain
about the food at home every three days.
Have you waited long?
Another coincidence.
Hello, Wichai.
Hey, there.
I just picked up my niece from school.
I remember Prasit said
that he likes to come here.
This is Nid.
She's my niece.
- Hello.
If you don't mind, please join us.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Are you in this neighborhood often?
I have to come pick up medicine
for my brother-in-law
every other day.
But today is special because… Thank you.
Nid has to work on a craft project.
So I brought her to buy some supplies.
Isn't that right?
The teacher told us to craft something
and we could win a prize.
I want to craft a magic object.
A magic object?
How about a magic casket?
Or maybe you could make a magic flute.
What do you think, Uncle?
That's up to you.
You can make anything you want to make.
I want to be as pretty as Ms. Anong.
Well then…
Why don't you ask Ms. Anong?
Ask her
what she does
that makes her so pretty.
Ask her
whether she drinks dewdrops for breakfast.
And at night,
does she spread her wings
and fly to meet other angels?
Ask her what she does
that makes her so pretty.
Please excuse me.
Where's the bathroom?
- It's over there.
- Thank you.
What should I do?
I suddenly can't look him in the eye.
I shouldn't have fantasized about him.
Come on.
Let's wash your hands and face.
Yes? What is it?
I know now what I want to make.
I want to make something
that makes my dad smile.
In that case,
you need to make your dad believe
that he'll get better soon.
Okay?
Can I make a smile maker
for my craft project?
Then let's go back home
and work on it today.
Okay? All right?
You're all clean.
Let's go.
Is that the shirt you tore?
Look at this.
I don't think so.
Maybe you can give him a new suit
to replace this one.
Will Wichai accept it?
Just leave it to me.
My goodness, Anong!
Anong, what should we do?
This is bad. What should we do, Anong?
- I--
- It's okay.
I can have it washed.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive my clumsiness.
It's all right. This suit is old anyway.
- Let's go.
- Wichai, wait.
Please allow me.
Let me take care of it for you.
- I'll return it to you later.
- But…
Please.
Thank you very much then.
You're welcome.
Goodness. It's all dirty.
It's all right.
We're proud to present
Lady Dajchanee.
It's a love story
that captivates the world.
This is the most magnificent play
like you've never seen before.
Tickets are available now.
LADY DAJCHANEE
A LOVE STORY THAT CAPTIVATES THE WORLD
RUANG'S SHOP
My gosh.
Look, guys. There's a typing contest.
I want that prize.
Do you want the prize for second place?
You're good, Uncle. Can you win it for me?
My store also sells piggybanks like this.
But buying it won't be
as fun as winning it, right?
How about this? If you want the piggybank,
I'll try to win it for you.
I won't do it.
Are you sure it's a good idea?
I'm not good at typing.
You should do it.
If Wichai ends up getting first place,
we won't get the piggybank.
I'll do my best.
This is a touch-typing contest.
Participants must put on blindfolds.
The winner is the one
who types the fastest
with the fewest typos.
Please put on your blindfold.
Try to relax.
Relax your fingers.
You got this.
Focus, Anong.
But don't come in the first place.
Is everyone ready?
If you're ready, you may begin.
"There is no greater happiness than peace.
If you think happiness is money,
you will seek wealth.
You will seek a partner
if you think happiness lies in a person.
If you think happiness means pleasure,
you will seek vices."
What does vices mean?
It means gambling.
"Like a bird jumping
from one branch to another
without knowing that true happiness
lies within oneself."
You've made two typos.
That means
your total score is eight points.
If the person who finishes second
made no typos,
they will win the contest.
But if they made more typos than you,
you'll win a typewriter from our store.
Don't win!
You finished second,
which gives you nine points.
You didn't make any mistakes.
That means
your total score is nine points.
That's the highest score right now.
We did it!
Hold on. Why are you guys so happy?
Why are you so happy?
You came in second.
- Do you like it?
- That wasn't fun at all.
You told me to compete, but not to win.
Don't make me do
something like this again. I feel stupid.
Can I have a consolation prize?
Here's a prize for you too, Uncle.
I can't tell anymore
who is kissing who.
You have lipstick on your face.
Right.
Be careful. That's a white shirt.
Let me help you.
Forgive me.
I didn't mean to get it on you.
If you meant it,
Wichai might've melted on the spot.
This way, Doctor.
Samarn can't keep anything down.
He keeps throwing up food.
The doctor said
we should prepare ourselves.
The doctor said…
he won't last through this month.
Here you go.
Here's a magic ring, Dad.
What powers does it have?
It will make you feel better.
Help your dad put it on, dear.
Uncle Wichai helped cast a spell on it.
It will make you better.
LADY DAJCHANEE
It wasn't even a big deal.
Then how come…
Wait. It's okay. Let me do it.
You should get to work or you'll be late.
You're leaving so early.
I'll prepare breakfast for you.
Wait, Soon.
Please don't bother.
I can look after myself.
All right.
This magic ring can turn tears into smiles
and vice versa.
No one can have the best
of everything all their lives.
The more we find out
about someone's secrets,
the closer we become to them.
I don't want to pretend.
I want to date you for real.
You must let her see your flaws,
so you know how much she can take.
You can't even look after yourself.
You're no different
from that cripple Prasit.
You shouldn't have been born a man
since you can't protect anyone.
This could be the reason why
people look down on our family!
Where did you drop Prasit off?
He's not home yet.
Subtitle translation by:
Pannapat Tammasrisawat