BASED ON A NOVEL BY DOK MAI SOD
Don't go see Lady Mayom just yet.
I think Chut ran away to Korat.
Urai just told me that
Chantorn ran away from home.
Let's live happily together.
Does Chantorn love you?
She does. She'd been waiting for me.
But once Anong and I broke up,
you became the problem.
Are you saying that
I'm the one standing between you two?
Don't betray me by asking
another girl to marry Chut.
They love each other. I can't stop them.
If she's so great,
why don't you marry her yourself?
You can call me selfish.
I don't want anyone
to be happy if I'm not.
If you can't be happy for others
when they find happiness,
maybe the problem is you.
Are you preaching to me right now?
Wichai!
We're told to prepare for the worst.
Wichai may never fully recover from this.
If you want someone you love to be yours,
that's lust.
Or maybe it's infatuation.
If you want someone you love to be yours…
I get it now.
I know now
what you tried to run away from.
So you understand now
what it feels like
to not have anyone love you.
The person who gives love
is the one who must bear its weight.
I'll never forget that.
My life was like a living hell
because I had to live with that feeling.
I'm sorry I disappointed you.
Please forgive me.
Master. Are you okay?
You damn ghost.
Get lost!
Where are you?
It's you, right?
Damn you.
Just leave Wichai alone!
-Hello, ma'am.
-Hello.
This is Wichai's coworker
from the radio station.
I brought you a gift basket.
Take it, Lamoon.
-Thank you so much.
-Sure.
Mom.
This is Wichai's assistant judge.
Hello, ma'am.
Don't forget the basket.
Take it, Lamoon.
-Thank you.
-Please make yourself at home.
Hey, come here.
When Wichai was conscious,
he asked me to write down information
about the subpoenas he has issued
and all the cases he's responsible for.
I wrote it all down here.
Thank you.
Actually,
I already asked other judges
to take over all of Wichai's cases.
I'll let him know once he wakes up.
All right.
Tell him not to worry.
Please excuse me.
Madam.
Ms. Chuen.
I'll take my leave now.
-Thank you for coming.
-Sure.
-Goodbye, ma'am.
-Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Madam.
Doctor.
Wichai has been unconscious all day.
I think we should limit
the number of visitors.
With this many visitors,
Wichai might not get to rest
and his condition may become more severe.
I agree with you.
But I can't stop people from coming.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I just wanted to bring Wichai
letters from our listeners.
They might help cheer him up.
Here you go.
A lot of people sent him
their well wishes.
I'll be off now. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Chut isn't home.
You can leave
if you're only here out of courtesy.
We just want to--
Prasit, let me take that.
Please give this to Wichai.
Once Wichai feels better,
we'll come to visit him again.
Doctor.
Let's go see how Wichai is doing.
I'm sorry you had to come
all the way here.
Wichai wanted to know
if you've made your decision yet.
From the looks of it,
your mom seems to really dislike Chantorn.
It's one of the reasons
I'm reluctant to let her marry Chut.
I'm afraid she'll have problems
with her mother-in-law
once she's moved in here.
Wichai is really worried about this.
He wants to help Chut while he still can
so Chut can marry the girl he loves.
We're not asking for much.
We just want Chantorn
to have a house in her name.
This is so that she will at least
have somewhere to go
if she gets kicked out of here.
You mean you're okay
with letting Chantorn marry Chut
if they have their own house to live in
once they're married.
We're still disappointed
Chantorn isn't marrying Wichai.
Chut doesn't seem
like the right man for her.
Wichai is really sick.
He wouldn't want to marry anyone
when he's in this state.
Maybe Chantorn
just isn't meant to be with him.
Chantorn made her own decision.
I'll let Wichai know
that you agree to let Chantorn marry Chut
under the condition stated.
Where is Chut anyway?
He doesn't dare face anyone
after what happened.
C. WARATHABUT
Congratulations.
You two are now legally married.
I wish you
a long and happy marriage.
I'm sorry
that we can't have a wedding
since Wichai has fallen ill.
But I promise that
I'll love and be faithful to you
no matter what happens.
This ring represents my promise
that I'll work hard
and fully commit myself to you.
I don't care what anyone else says.
They can't change my mind.
This is all I want.
I want to start a new life with you.
Congratulations.
You're now a married man.
Wichai got sick because of that girl.
Why are they in such a hurry
to have a wedding now?
That woman caused
Wichai and Chut to fight.
It'd be absurd
if Chut still wants to marry her.
Wichai just wants to keep his promise
to Chantorn's family.
What about Chut's promise to marry Sa-Ang?
He didn't seem to care
about his promise to her.
Wichai has never asked you
for much, ma'am.
Just do this for him
if it's not too difficult.
You know this will break Wichai's heart.
Do you want his condition to get worse?
And where is Chut?
Does he know it's his fault
that Wichai got sick?
Chinese people believe that
peach blossoms can bring luck
and drive away misfortunes
from our lives.
Don't bother your uncle.
How annoying. Just get out of here.
Mom.
Let's go, honey.
I'm telling you.
I'll never accept her
as my daughter-in-law.
I'll never welcome
a fickle woman like that into my family.
You think some women are like flowers
that are out of your reach,
so you go for the ones
that are closer to the ground.
And I'm just a weed
on the side of the road
that's not even worthy of your attention.
If you aren't going to fight for him,
we should let him be with Chantorn.
We're part of the reason he's heartbroken.
If I had known,
I wouldn't have encouraged Chantorn
to leave him for Chut.
I wonder if I can do something to fix it.
It's too late.
You can't do anything now.
I'll get the door for you.
-Come on out.
-Thank you.
-Go on inside.
-All right.
-Have a nice day.
-Okay.
-See you.
Look after my girl for me.
Don't be too harsh on her.
She means a lot to me.
Sure.
I heard that Chut just bought a new car.
He probably wants to rub it in our faces.
Ever since Chut quit his job,
he suddenly has a lot of money to spend.
People suspect
that he married a rich girl.
He seems to be lucky
both in the game and in love.
He doesn't care who has to suffer
as long as he's happy.
Thank you.
Hey!
His condition is stable.
He's occasionally conscious,
but the doctor still
won't let him out of bed
since he might faint again.
He sleeps all day
after he takes his medicine.
It might be good if he gets
to go outside once in a while
instead of staying in bed all the time.
I promise
to help you find happiness.
If I can't do it,
I'll never show my face here again.
Please wake up so you can be happy.
We're thinking about moving him downstairs
so he's closer to the garden.
I wish he would wake up and talk to us.
It's unlike him
to be quiet like this.
A girl brought you flowers.
Won't you wake up
to see who they are from?
Will you bring Wichai
Chinese herbal soup tomorrow?
Can you ask the kitchen staff
to prepare it?
Sure. I'll let them know.
Thank you.
I know now.
I know where Chut got his money from.
An old palace was on sale recently.
They put it on an auction
and invited our bank to bid on it.
It turned out there were only two bidders,
our bank and a mogul
who owns a movie theater.
But on the day before the auction,
that man
just gave us one million baht
and asked us to drop out of the auction.
ONE MILLION BAHT
Chut was the one who brought us the check,
but the check was made out
in the theater owner's name.
This means that
Chut must be investing
in a business with him.
The mogul you mentioned
is probably Prach.
He and Chut are close friends.
My guy looked into it and told me that
they plan to turn the palace into a club
with annual membership fees.
I heard they plan
to make the club really luxurious
with a billiard room and a cigar lounge.
This means that
Chut is probably a partner in the club.
Hang on.
The club isn't even open yet.
Why is Chut already getting rich?
That mogul was willing
to give us one million baht.
They must have a lot of money
to spend on their project.
But I heard that
Wichai had to pay for the house
that Chut and Chantorn will live in.
I don't think
Chut has that much money to spend.
In that case, I'll wait and see
whether they're really good for the money.
Okay.
I haven't approved your resignation yet.
How can you just disappear?
Something happened that caused me
to suddenly change my life plans.
It seems congratulations are in order.
Is that a wedding ring?
Actually,
Chut doesn't want me to tell anyone yet.
Is Chut the reason why
you can't come back to work?
Is he still mad at me?
It's not like that.
Chut's fine with me working here.
Then come back to work.
I'll give you a promotion.
Unless Chut wants you
to be a stay-at-home wife.
If I no longer have to move
to the countryside with Chut,
I think I'll still be able to work here.
But still,
I'll have to talk to Chut
about this first.
I hope to hear good news from you.
You're a competent woman.
It'd be a shame
to lose someone like you.
DECO PLAZA APPLICATION FORM
Goodbye.
Ms. Anong.
There's something different
about her information
in the job application form.
Come on in.
Mom went to the temple to pray for Wichai.
I tricked Boi to go run errands for me
so I could sneak you in.
Otherwise, he wouldn't let
anyone come in here.
Is he doing better?
He's awake occasionally,
but he's asleep most of the time.
The doctor said
Wichai has peripheral neuropathy
which affects his motor functions.
So we don't know
whether he'll be able to walk
once he wakes up.
What's this?
It's the blueprint
for Chut and Chantorn's house.
Her family wants them to get married
in three months.
So Wichai asked Luang Sak
to help with the wedding arrangements.
Wedding arrangements?
Do you mean
there will be a wedding ceremony?
Wichai promised Samarn
that he would look after Chantorn.
So he wants everything to be done
according to tradition.
There's something different about her
information in the job application form.
So she ran off to get married.
But it's strange that
she didn't tell anyone about it.
Did you know about this, ma'am?
I thought that
they would just go register their marriage
at the district office.
Wichai insists on holding
a wedding ceremony for them.
He doesn't want them to wait
until he gets better to have a wedding.
How can someone be this generous?
I'm thirsty.
Can I have some water?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I'll get you water.
Hurry. I'm really thirsty.
All right.
Are you in a lot of pain?
Is that why you don't wake up?
I'm sorry for being so selfish.
I was angry
and I took my anger out on you.
I encouraged those two
to run away together
because I wanted you
to be heartbroken like me.
I know now that I went too far.
But I'm going to make it up to you.
I know that I'm not good enough for you.
Since I'm a bad person,
I'm going to be as bad as possible.
I'll get the woman you love back for you.
You won't have to see her
with anyone else.
There will be no wedding.
And you can live with Chantorn
in the house
that you're building for Chut.
Thank you.
Can I have more?
Do you want more?
Brother…
What did you say?
You said you'd think of me
as your brother.
Can you hear me, Wichai?
What day is it today?
It's Tuesday. Why do you ask?
Do you remember me?
Thank you for being here.
I've been wanting to come visit you.
Why?
Can you promise me
that you'll live a long life
so that I can keep loving you?
You don't have to love me back.
Just stay with me and don't go anywhere.
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Please say something.
Tell me whether you understand.
Don't you want to hear me
call you big brother?
What are you doing here?
We're not doing anything.
"We"?
No, that's not what I mean.
Please don't go in there.
Wait.
Who let you come up here?
You sneaky bunch.
We're just visiting Wichai.
We'll leave soon.
Prasit.
Your zipper is down.
Wichai doesn't want to see anyone.
Can't you see you're bothering him?
Don't make me kick you out. Get out!
I let them in. Stop yelling at them.
Why can't you let Wichai sleep in peace?
There's no need to yell. We're leaving.
Don't come here again
or I'll hurt you.
Hey.
Who are you yelling at?
Madam.
Hey.
What's with you people?
What do you want with Wichai?
I just wanted to visit him.
What business did you have with him?
She came to see how Wichai was doing
so she could consult a doctor she knew.
All right then.
I thought you were using Wichai
to get back together with Chut.
You can leave now
since you got what you came for.
I forgot to congratulate you.
Congratulations on
your new daughter-in-law.
I wish Wichai could see
how much his mom
loves and cares about him.
He's craved for your love all his life.
You've only started to care for him
when Chut has let you down.
Don't forget to make it up to Wichai
for all the horrible things
you've done to him.
Let's go, Prasit.
Madam.
How dare she say that to you?
Uncle Wichai is awake.
Mommy, Uncle Wichai is awake.
I almost slipped.
Wichai.
Have some food, Wichai.
Eat up, Wichai.
You're getting too thin.
It's my salary for this month.
They still paid me
though I couldn't go to work.
Stop worrying about me.
Don't worry about work or anyone else.
You've already given us so much.
We'll be fine even if
we don't have this money.
I don't plan on dying anytime soon.
I promised Samarn I'd look after Nid.
I can't leave her.
Don't think you have to live
because of your obligations.
You've helped pay our family's debt
since you were in school.
You've provided for all of us.
You're my son.
I can manage and look after you just fine.
Even if you don't work,
our family will be fine.
Others won't let us starve.
You're loved by so many people.
People brought you so many gifts
that we could set up a store.
People brought us so much food
that I almost didn't have to cook at all.
Everyone helped look after me
in your place.
You can put them there.
You can't buy
this kind of generosity with money.
You have nothing to worry about.
Just stay with me like this.
You've given me life.
So I'm going to make the most of it.
You must rest if you're tired.
Don't overwork yourself.
Your body won't be able to take it.
I know that now.
I've been living too recklessly.
You've also been too selfless.
Your body is telling you
to take care of yourself for once.
Do you want to look outside?
Come on.
Get up so you can get a good look.
Are you stunned by its beauty?
I'm more stunned by the man you've become.
Why is there still music
this time of night?
Anong came to stay with her aunts.
If it bothers you,
I'll call and tell her to stop playing.
Tell her to come play every day.
I've been asleep for so long,
I don't know what day it is anymore.
Is it almost your wedding day?
It's two more months
until the wedding.
But if you're too weak to attend,
Chantorn and I think we'll postpone it.
We've agreed that
we want to wait until you're better.
Without you,
there wouldn't even be a wedding.
From now on,
I guess it's finally my turn
to take care of everyone.
I'm not just talking about my family.
I'll take care of Mom
and take on the responsibilities
in this house.
You can rest now.
It's like I've been given a new life.
Am I really not dreaming?
Now that I'm awake,
why does the world seem different?
You're the one
who has woken me up to reality.
I've just realized
that I can't live without you.
You have to get better, Wichai.
Stay with me
so I can show you my gratitude.
I'm going to make you proud of me.
You'll see that
everything you've done isn't in vain.
I'm glad to hear that.
I hope you'll get to experience
more moments like this.
Hey, there.
What are you guys doing?
Gosh.
That looks good. Keep at it.
Right. I was wondering
where those paper flowers came from.
Anong and I made these charms for you.
We wrote messages on them
and Nid read them out loud to you.
So how is Anong doing?
I haven't seen her in months.
Wait.
You don't know that she's been here?
Every time she came to visit you,
you were always asleep.
I didn't know that.
I'm still worried about
whether she has gotten over Chut yet.
Anong doesn't care about him.
She's too busy worrying about you.
Visiting time is over.
-See you later.
-Thank you for coming.
People can feel dead on the inside
while they're alive.
If I continue to waste my life away,
I might be the one
to experience death before you.
If we give something enough time,
we'll start to appreciate its value.
When I go to visit you,
it makes me realize
how important you are to me
and how much I don't want to lose you.
I used to wonder
why movie characters
like ramble to themselves
about problems in their love life.
But now that I'm the one rambling,
I also keep talking
about my own heartache.
Thank goodness
you can't complain about it.
The reason I'm so miserable
is probably because
I pressure myself to be happy.
Even if you wake up,
I'm still not sure
if I can ever be happy again.
Prasit said that the first thing
you'll forget about someone
is their voice.
And the last thing
you'll forget about that person
is their smell.
But…
I still remember the smell
of your massage oil from that day.
A lie that we tell ourselves repeatedly
will eventually come true.
I convince myself every morning
that you'll finally wake up
and talk to me.
But it's been so many days
and you still haven't woken up.
Try to stand up first.
There you go. That's it.
How are you feeling?
Slowly put your weight on your feet.
You're doing really well.
Ms. Anong is waiting for you upstairs.
Chantorn.
I'm sorry I asked you to come
all the way here.
It's okay.
Here you go.
This is this week's sales report.
Give me some time
to read through the report.
Then you can take it back to the store.
Please take your time.
I don't mind waiting.
Anong.
Let's go.
Since you're not doing anything right now,
can you take the compresses to Wichai?
No way. She can't have them.
Prasit.
I asked Aunties to make these.
She can't have them.
Prasit.
Take these to Wichai for me.
They will help him feel better.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey. What are you doing here?
I came to see Ms. Anong
at the house next door,
so she asked me to come
and see how you're doing.
What about Anong?
She's busy at the moment.
So how have you been doing?
Are you feeling better?
Well…
The doctor allowed me to come outside now.
But I still have trouble walking.
I have to learn how to walk again.
Well then.
I'll help put the compresses on your feet.
Wait. It's okay.
You don't have to do that.
I can call Boi to help me.
I really don't mind.
Let me be the one
to take care of you for once.
Thank you.
This is nothing
compared to what you've done for me.
You've helped me with my marriage.
You're even building a house
for me and Chut.
Before Samarn died,
he asked me to help look after you.
I just want to keep my promise to him.
You've been too kind to me.
I'm doing it for my own peace of mind.
I don't want to have any regrets.
I don't know what I can ever do
to repay you for the kindness
you've shown me.
Well…
You can repay me
by giving Chut all your love.
That's all I want from you.
Why did you want her to go see Wichai?
Seeing her would only hurt him.
Wichai might be happy
to have Chantorn look after him.
He would feel awkward.
She went from being his lover
to being his sister-in-law.
His physical wounds are treated.
All that's left
are the wounds in his heart.
And Chantorn is the only one
who can heal them.
She'll only make him feel worse.
You should be the one
to help mend his broken heart.
If my presence could help,
he would've all been better by now.
Chantorn is the one
who's stuck in Wichai's heart.
She just came to visit me.
Are you sure she didn't come
to try to rush the wedding?
She already told everyone about it.
Don't be so prejudiced against her
and try to get to know her first.
She's a girl born out of wedlock
who tries to find herself a nice man.
She's asking us for a house
when she herself comes from nothing.
It's clear that she wants money.
Mom.
If you give her a chance,
you'll know she's not like that.
The only possession your dad left behind
was wasted on a low-class woman
that your brother picked as his wife.
A good woman wouldn't make
such shameless demands.
You mark my words.
Ms. Anong.
Here's the name card
you asked me to print out.
CHANTORN WARATHABUT,
HEAD OF SALES DEPARTMENT
Mom didn't even go ask
for Chantorn's hand for Chut.
I don't know why they think
they'll still be getting married.
Mom will never accept Chantorn
as her daughter-in-law.
If she approves,
it will be like she condones
how Chut stole a girl from Wichai.
Mom is punishing Chut for what he did.
It's funny how everyone is suddenly
doing nice things for Wichai.
They all want to do whatever they can
for him one last time.
Everyone tries to do something
for him in their own way.
I want to return these.
These shoes hurt my feet.
When did you buy them?
Do you have the receipt?
You sold us a low-quality product.
Won't you take any responsibility?
It was that woman who sold me these shoes.
She tricked me
into buying a defective product.
Hey, you.
Can I have a word?
Are they already married?
This is why that woman told everyone
Chut is her man.
What about the house?
Did Chut give it to her?
This is the house deed.
It's in your name.
I lost Chut to that woman,
but I won't let them have the money
that's supposed to be your inheritance.
Just walk away from him.
Let go.
Someone tried to break us up.
Was it Anong?
So that's why she came to the wedding.
Anong must've told Chantorn
something about me.
The wedding is ruined.
If this is your doing,
then you're very cruel.
You can't stand to see them happy.
You don't know how to love anyone.
The only one you love is yourself.
You've hurt people for your own pleasure.
You should be happy they broke up.
Is it that hard to be selfish
for once in your life?
Subtitle translation by:
Pannapat Tammasrisawat