It was him, right?
The bastard who
told you to kidnap Soo Ji.
Get them.
Stop right there.
Mal Koo.
Mal Koo, are you there?
CEO.
If you want to come any further,
then kill me right now.
But If you keep me alive,
your parents, siblings, and children...
will be going to hell before me.
Today will be the last day
we back out, CEO.
CEO.
You lost her?
Then what about Jang Sun Doo?
It seemed like she was with him.
They already took him away.
Took him away?
We'll look around and call you back.
Jang Sun Doo is...
the punk who brought
us Seo Soo Ji.
That punk was alive?
You said you killed him!
I told you that he saw me.
There's no need to be scared.
He's in a vegetative state
and can't lift a finger.
Then why did they take him away?
He can't lift a finger, so why?
Yes, Prosecutor.
Be quiet.
Otherwise, you'll be
in a vegetative state.
Try tracking that
crazy b****'s phone again.
Her cell phone is...
turned off?
Yes. The first flight tomorrow.
The destination?
I don't care. Whichever
is the earliest flight.
What are you doing?
I really think I chose
the wrong person.
What did you say?
If I locked you up for being crazy
and chose your wife as my partner,
at least I wouldn't have this mess.
What?
Listen to my words carefully
from now on and obey them.
When the sun comes up,
go to work as usual.
Have a meeting and eat lunch, too.
And make sure to attend any events.
Are you crazy?
My wife could show up anytime.
Are you scared?
Just endure it and
go about your business.
That way, your wife will
approach you easily.
You'll use me as bait?
You should earn your keep...
if you're Korea Tech's CEO.
By the way,
where is she?
Jang Min Seo.
I mean, your daughter's corpse.
I cremated her and...
threw her ashes in the ocean.
You did?
What a heartless dad.
A heartless dad.
Just relax.
We'll be seeing each other
for a long time.
Huh, I see.
Jang Sun Doo is Jang Il Koo's son.
Who's this?
He was the leader of Ilkoo Gang.
He took care of Jang Il Koo
after he retired.
So these guys disappeared too, right?
Yes.
That crazy b**** must be
with these people.
I've already talked
to your chief, so
look for them with a
few trusty guys.
- Call me if you find them.
- Yes.
But Prosecutor...
Why did you release that
crazy b**** a few days ago...
when she was in front of your eyes?
Remember this from now on.
I'll be the brains here, so
you just do as I say.
Got it?
- You turned off your phone, right?
- Yeah.
Where are we anyway?
Someone's house. He owes CEO one.
We can relax for a few days.
Let's go. CEO needs rest, too.
Geez, darn it.
There's no way...
When I went to Bertram,
it was packed with people.
I don't know.
The whole building was empty
when I went there today.
That's even weirder.
All those people
disappearing suddenly.
I agree.
If we want to reveal
Yang Mi Hee's true identity,
we need to confirm
what exactly Bertram does.
Then Jang Chul Min
needs to tell us.
Will we be able to find him?
He must be hiding because
he knows you're alive.
I called the company,
and he's at work.
And he didn't cancel
any of his schedules.
As usual?
Ms. Ma, by any chance...
Yes, it's too dangerous.
Let's think of a different way.
This is a trap Yang Mi Hee
set up for you.
Jang Chul Min is the bait.
I think so too.
But we have no choice.
Since time isn't on our side.
That woman is here.
Where are you?
The Cultural Development Agency.
Thanks to Korea Tech's full support,
we're opening earlier than expected.
- Yes.
- Thank you so much, CEO Jang.
I'm glad I could help.
Then let me show you
the second floor.
Jang Chul Min!
Let go of me!
What are you doing? Take her away.
Let me go!
CEO Jang, are you okay?
We got her.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Hey.
What's going on?
You bastards!
I said, what's going on?
Can you hear me?
You bastards!
I said, can you hear me?
You'll see me again soon.
Excuse me. Excuse me!
No, no, no. I don't know
anything. It wasn't me!
This is the girl you kidnapped, right?
The one who ordered you...
is this man, right?
No, Honey.
It wasn't me, Honey!
Liar.
- It was you.
- Eun Ji.
Why? Why did you
do that to my Soo Ji?
- Bring Soo Ji back. Bring her back!
- Eun Ji!
Bring my Soo Ji back.
Bring her back!
Bring her back, you bastard!
I said, bring her back!
Honey.
I didn't want to do it.
You know that...
I'm not capable of such things.
I did it because that
woman ordered me to.
Yes! That Yang Mi Hee
ordered me to do it!
Please believe me, Honey!
Get up.
Honey.
I said, get up.
Where is Min Seo?
Honey.
I asked where Min Seo is.
I have somewhere to be.
Call this number
if anything happens.
I'll go with  you.
No.
You stay here with Eun Ji.
They're on the hunt for you.
You can't go by yourself.
Go with Mal Koo oppa.
I'll be fine alone.
Let's do that.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
He deserves to die a hundred times.
I swore that I'll kill him myself...
when I find Soo Ji's killer.
I've sworn many times.
Your sister doesn't want
you to kill for revenge.
There's an order for revenge, too.
First of all,
find the ones who hired Sun Doo...
and reveal everything they've done.
Whether you'll kill him or
not comes afterward.
The detective who
had the evidence died.
That detective...
was trailing Ms. Ma, right?
I've seen a lot of detectives like him.
They're like hunting dogs that
never let go once they bite.
They all have one thing in common.
If it's important evidence,
they always make a copy.
So even if something
happens to them,
the culprit  could still be jailed.
Is this the place?
Is Min Seo here?
Honey, please believe me.
I had no idea that'd happen to Min Seo.
Min Seo.
Jang Min Seo!
Where's Min Seo?
Min Seo.
Jang Min Seo?
Daddy's here!
Min Seo.
Min Seo!
Min Seo?
No, Min Seo...
Your wife is probably
at the police station.
No, Min Seo...
The police will contact you,
so go home for now.
I'll take care of her.
Take care of her?
You said Min Seo was okay!
You said Min Seo would be okay!
That's why we
kidnapped another girl.
So why?
Is this what they
call "self-deception?"
What?
You already knew it.
You knew I was lying about your
daughter being safe.
No.
No?
Are you a fool?
How can you succeed in
framing a mom for a murder
if her daughter is still alive?
Yes.
Her mom went to jail for killing her.
What child would not do anything?
She'd run out and
say that she's still alive
and that her mom is innocent!
No!
I thought I could send her abroad.
I thought it'd be okay if
she was at a place...
where the news won't reach her.
It's your charm that
you think the way you want.
But you know that it's...
complete nonsense.
Don't you?
No. No, this is wrong.
I'll go and tell the police...
that I'm completely innocent!
I warned you...
that there's no turning back
once you start.
No.
I can stop right now.
If you stop pedaling,
the bike will fall over.
The ones on the bike will get hurt.
Because that can't happen,
I kept pedaling instead of you!
No, no...
No.
Min Seo.
Yes.
Min Seo liked these flowers.
Aren't they pretty?
Why do you like these anyway?
You'll meddle in
what kind of flowers I like?
But still.
There are roses...
and lilies, too.
Yes, tulips are pretty, too.
I like their name's meaning.
Their name's meaning?
Min Seo, you know
about such things?
Listen.
They're called mini-mums.
Yes. Mini chrysanthemums.
They're chrysanthemums?
Mini chrysanthemums.
Are you saying that...
you know their name meaning without
knowing they're chrysanthemums?
Anyway, I do know the meaning.
Okay, let's hear it.
You don't know the flower's name,
but you know the flower
name's meaning. Let's hear it.
The meaning is?
It's "Let's be friendly."
- Let's be friendly?
- Yeah.
The word "mini-mum"
comes from "playing house."
Let's be friendly as if we're
playing "mums."
That's why they're mini-mums.
Min Seo!
Jang Min Seo?
Okay.
Should we try what we
practiced again?
Mom. Mommy!
- Did I do well?
- Yes, you did a great job.
By the way, when is Daddy coming?
Daddy?
No.
Min Seo!
Min Seo! No!
Min Seo.
The foolish mom of yours...
hands hurt.
You're buried like this right now.
Min Seo.