Where can you find the belongings
of a traffic accident patient?
If the police didn't take them,
then their guardian has them.
Then Han Tae Kyu and
Choi Woo Joon...
The accident in Rainbow Town.
That hit-and-run accident?
The officer's belongings
were claimed by his guardian,
and Choi Woo Joon's were...
Just one second.
Hey.
Geez.
Did Prosecutor Yang Mi Hee send you?
To capture me?
Why?
Because I'm Seo Soo Ji's sister,
who Prosecutor Yang Mi Hee killed?
So...
what will you do after taking me?
Huh?
Kill me then bury me?
Tell me, you thug punks!
Eun Ji.
Are  you okay?
Eun Ji, were you...
looking for this?
It was in Woo Joon's pant pocket.
I came here to take Woo Joon's
clothes after the hit-and-run.
But kept this because of an inkling.
Did you look at it?
No.
But Woo Joon's accident...
wasn't a hit-and-run, right?
You stay out of it.
Thanks anyway.
Eun Ji.
You'll come back, right?
Yes.
I'll come back for sure.
Hey, hey, hey!  Hold on.
We received a report.
Can you show me your IDs?
Aigoo. You're not
behaving yourselves.
Excuse me! Come over here!
Seriously, these people...
Where are you going?
What did you just say?
Bertram?
You sent them money nine years ago.
I'm sure you're still doing that now.
The evidence must be there.
I need that.
What will you do with it?
Will you fight with Bertram?
I must reveal Yang Mi Hee's
true identity.
You want to dig up
Bertram because of that?
Honey.
Yang Mi Hee is just one of
Bertram's members.
There are judges, prosecutors and
a ton of well-known politicians, too.
You can't deal with them alone.
I don't care if the King of
Hades is one of them.
I can't forgive that...
Yang Mi Hee woman.
There aren't any, Honey.
There isn't any...
evidence at all.
What?
Do you have any guilty conscience left?
Don't you know why I'm doing this?
Okay, fine.
We've come this far, so
I want to help you.
Yang Mi Hee deceived me,
and I lost Min Seo.
And I haven't controlled our
company since then.
But...
After the day you called me,
some people from there came.
Afterward, all records regarding
Bertram completely disappeared.
Are you serious...
- Hello?
- Let me talk to Auntie.
Hello?
I found the evidence.
Where are you?
You couldn't even capture that girl?
What the heck are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Keep searching! Hurry!
May I ask who that was?
You.
I warned you not to use your brain.
Where's Jang Chul Min?
I couldn't track him down.
Shouldn't he be on the Wanted List?
Wanted List?
CEO Jang Chul Min
is an important figure.
If he got kidnapped
in broad daylight...
Stop spewing nonsense,
and go to CEO Jang's place.
If he's not there,
try his vacation home.
Okay, will do.
What brings you all the way here?
No, Honey. We'll all end up dying.
I'm serious, Honey!
At this rate, we'll all die!
Honey! Honey, you must believe me!
Honey!
We'll all die!
Let me go!
Hey!
You better stay quiet.
Hey.
Do you know why it
was your sister?
Why your sister was chosen
among the other kids?
Shut your mouth.
Because you are...
poor folks who have nothing.
Huh?
We thought it won't be an issue...
even if you vanished.
I told you to shut up.
It's too bad.
This wouldn't have happened to me...
if we got rid of you, too.
Yes.
Keep blabbing on while you can.
You won't be able to after
your mouth gets filled with dirt.
Could you really do that?
Hey, Jang Chul Min!
Eun Ji's gone?
I think Jang Chul Min took her.
This way.
How about here?
Okay then.
They probably didn't get far.
Keep looking and call me back.
What should we do?
They have the evidence.
It was definitely
Han Tae Kyu's doing.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm positive.
Where's Seo Eun Ji right now?
I tied her up and
put her in the trunk.
You managed to earn your way.
Ms. Ma.
Why don't we take that
to the police?
Didn't you see the detectives
that came earlier?
Then what about sending it to a
newspaper or a TV station?
Then what about Eun Ji?
Put Eun Ji on the phone.
Don't come here.
Put it on the internet, Auntie!
Come to Bertram by midnight
with Han Tae Kyu's things.
You know where, right?
Evil b****!
Look.
If she does as you say,
then everyone here will die.
So let's all observe quietly
from now on.
I'm scared, too.
I'll take you there.
But this doesn't concern you...
This doesn't concern me?
Yes, it does.
Eun Ji and Woo Joon...
are both precious to me.
And so are you, Ms. Ma.
Get in!
Auntie.
Are you okay?
Why did you come?
Why?
That's enough judging.
Release Eun Ji first.
What are you doing? Uncuff her.
All good?
Then give it.
Not until I...
confirm that she
left the building safely.
Hurry.
- Auntie.
- Now.
Wait, wait.
But what happens if
after she leaves...
and I still don't get the goods?
I'll give it to you.
Eun Ji.
Get out now.
That's your idea.
Eun Ji!
Auntie.
Eun Ji.
Eun Ji!
Snap out of it.
Eun Ji, snap out of it.
She's not dead yet. Don't worry.
But she'll need treatment
soon, of course.
You...
This is it.
It's over now!
Call the ambulance.
Don't be so hasty.
CEO Jang.
You too.
I said, call the ambulance.
After we finish our chat.
Hurry.
Don't take too long.
Eun Ji.
You probably have an
idea about Bertram.
How should I explain what Bertram is?
You can't see it,
but it certainly exists.
It exists, but you can't understand it.
It's like a god, I guess.
A god who's very cruel and sensitive.
Stop talking and
call the ambulance.
There are two kinds of
people in this world.
The ones who chose god
and gained happiness,
and the ones who
didn't and gained pain.
Alright.
You have one more chance
to make a decision.
If you choose god,
you'll be cleared of the false charges,
and you'll have Korea Tech again.
What are you talking about?
And of course...
that Seo Eun Ji...
will be safe, too.
You think I'll believe
such nonsense?
Is it too difficult to choose?
Then I'll make it easy for you.
Is it easier to choose now?
If I choose you people...
then what about Min Seo?
Whichever you chose,
she won't be coming back.
Then you should make
a realistic decision.
You're crazy.
You're crazy!
Then your answer is...
a no, right?
When Bertram ordered me to
hear your answer,
honestly, I didn't want to.
Do you know why?
When I look at you, I'm
reminded of your daughter.
Just like right now!
I told you that...
I'll kill the people
who killed my daughter.
What is this?
Call for backup. Hurry.
Will do.
Detective Cheon.
Kill that...
b**** right now.
Are you able to move?
If you go in the opposite direction you
came in, there's an elevator.
Why did you do that?
Chief Han was...
killed by Yang Mi Hee.
I didn't have the courage at first, but
when you came to
see her the other day...
it's embarrassing to admit,
but it encouraged me.
Go.
I'll take care of the rest.
The evidence
Chief Han left behind...
I sent it to Chief Han's email.
Please check it.
A mysterious organization
called Bertram that was
exposed through a murder
in central Daejeon
is being brought to light
more and more.
The police investigated on
their fund management records
and acquired a list of politicians
closely related to Bertram,
including Assemblyman Baek Doo Heon.
And East Daejeon police dept.
which is in charge of this case,
reopened the investigation for Ms. Jang's
murder from nine years ago.
According to the police,
Chief Prosecutor Yang of
Daejeon Prosecutors' Office,
who died a month ago
and CEO Jang of a Daejeon
based company
framed his wife Ms. Choi for the crime
to take the company from her.
Hey, Ms. Ma!
Why were you gone for so long?
You know Eun Ji's at home, right?
Let's go.
My goodness. Goodness.
Unni!
Ms. Ma,
we have a library meeting later.
Make sure to stop by.
- Ms. Oh.
- Yes?
She's not Ms. Ma, but...
She's Ms. Ma to us,
no matter what others say.
That's true.
Ms. Ma, mosey along.
- Make sure to come!
- See you later, Unni.
But this is kind of...
Seriously.
Here it is.
Auntie.
Can you call me Mom from now on?
Really?
Mom.
♫  Where will I go alone?
On an empty street  ♫
♫  Like that day, good night.
The scattered pieces of my heart  ♫
♫  I can't forget, beyond the memories
which I can remember  ♫
♫  I'm hiding the truth again today  ♫
♫  The light that's fading away  ♫
♫  I wish to wake up if it's a dream  ♫
♫  If it's not too late now...  ♫