Ahjumma,
have you heard of "art rock?"
Well, geez, Chief Jo.
So...
I found the hospital so uncomfortable,
so I came back home to relax.
But I can't relax
because of that noise!
This is not a noise, but...
it's an art.
It might be art or whatever to you,
but it sounds like
noise to your neighbor.
"A priest sees people at their best."
"A lawyer sees at their worst."
What?
A Buddha sees only Buddhas,
and a pig sees only pigs.
Excuse me.
Are you saying that our Ms. Oh is
a pig or something?
Seriously. How dare you
say things like that?
- Let go!
- I mean, really...
No way.
It's a legendary art-rock band's music.
But you say it's noise? What the hell?
Is this a comedy skit from the 80's?
How dare you roll your
f***ing tongue like that?
Anyway.
If it's too loud, please
cover your ears.
Hey, hey, hey!
Isn't it easier for you to
wear headphones?
Why should I? Why?
You must listen to music with "air."
The stuff you listen to
using headphones...
that's noisy. A true noise.
Hey, hey! Come on!
Oh, come on! Seriously.
Where did that piece of
work come from anyway?
He's apparently  from Berkeley.
Berkle... what?
It's a famous music college.
Aigoo, so annoying.
I'm annoyed, yet what are
you eating by yourself?
I have yours too.
Huh?
Nice.
Ms. Ma.
I was going to call you.
Let's go to the Yellow Sea next week.
What is it this time?
It's not like that this time.
It's for Do Ja Hyun's case, and
the chief wants to give you an award.
Not everyone gets those!
I strongly told him that
we must give you one, Ms. Ma.
I'm sorry, Chief.
I'll be gone for a while
for important research.
You're playing hard to get again.
And Officer Bae.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
What did she thank you for?
That's a secret between
Ms. Ma and me.
I asked Mal Koo to take Woo Joon in.
Woo Joon was happy, too.
I put the house up for sale.
It'll take some time for it to sell.
You can stay here till then.
Do what makes you comfortable.
Auntie, the thing is...
I went to Daejeon.
Hello?
Who is it?
- Eun Ji.
- It was Jang Chul Min, wasn't it?
Give it to me.
Do you not believe me
or are you in denial?
I said, give it to me.
Today, that woman...
That woman...
Those people...
killed Ma Ji Won
thinking she's your aunt.
Who was that?
I think it was a wrong number.
Send 2 billion won this week
if you want to get by.
I sent you that much last month.
So?
You don't want to?
This week will be difficult.
I'll send it by next month.
This week, Chul Min.
This week.
Don't forget...
how you got away from that woman.
And who gave you all the success...
you've been having
at your company.
Three or four fingerprints were
found on the toothbrush.
It is that crazy b****.
How about the DNA?
I asked them to rush it, but...
she wouldn't have brushed
someone else's teeth with it.
Let's report this after the DNA results.
Aren't the fingerprints enough?
Why don't we report this and end it?
Let's really drive it in. Drive it in.
Also...
I sent a request for cooperation.
Go to the prosecutor's archives and
make a copy of Jang Min Seo's case.
Including the crime scene
photos and everything else.
But why do you want those?
Just do as I say!
Who was it?
Remember that...
killing a few people...
means nothing to those people.
Seo Eun Ji.
- It's nothing, Auntie.
- Give that to me right now.
Huh?
I have a favor to ask you.
If you trust me even a little...
please stay as "Ma Ji Won" for now.
At least...
until you move out.
Don't leave me alone here. Okay?
I'm scared and tired, that's why.
Eun Ji...
what happened in Daejeon?
Tell me.
What happened?
Not now.
You'll find out...
later why I'm doing this.
We should see Woo Joon living
well at Mal Koo's place, too.
So please stay with me until  then.
And don't call your
husband or someone else.
Please?
I beg of you, Auntie.
Can't you...
peek at the answer sheet?
Only our teacher knows the answer.
I'll think this over then.
Go read a book to Grandpa.
"When the lumberjack
arrived at the heavens,"
"his children and wife
ran over to him."
"- Dad.
- Honey, how did you come up here?"
"The lumberjack hugged
his wife and children,"
"and cried tears of joy."
Grandpa, are you okay?
Could you let me rest a bit?
Does it hurt a lot?
Yes.
I'm about to die soon.
But what happens to
a person after they die?
They probably go to heaven.
Then...
who lives in heaven?
I'm not sure.
Like you said, probably the
ones who went there first.
Hello?
What?
You can't find Woo Joon?
- Did you find him?
- No.
I looked everywhere, but...
- Did you call the police?
- I did.
I didn't see him around the store.
Did you try calling him?
He's not answering.
Did something happen at
home by any chance?
Well, the thing is...
I shouldn't have said those things.
Did he mention he's going somewhere?
I'm not sure.
I didn't hear anything like that.
Unni, are you okay?
I came because Eun Ji called me.
What's going on all of a sudden?
Let's do this.
Mal Koo,  go to the orphanage.
He may have gone there.
Also, Eun Ji...
Don't worry, Auntie.
He's probably okay.
Yes. Right.
I'll go to the mausoleum
where his mom is.
I'll look around the
neighborhood again.
I'll also notify the headquarters.
He might've gone to the new city.
Then I'll look around  the school.
Auntie, you go home.
He might go there, too.
Probably not.
Right.
I'll visit Woo Joon's friend.
Woo Joon's friend?
What should we do?
Woo Joon didn't come here.
Do you know where Woo Joon
likes to go by any chance?
You guys are close.
But Ahjumma...
I'm not close with Woo Joon.
But you used to study together.
He came over that day
because he really wanted to.
Woo Joon did?
I was going to tell you.
The reason why...
he came was probably to see you.
He guessed you'd come to
play the detective game.
I went because Woo Joon was coming.
Ms. Hong mentioned that to me.
By any chance...
I told Ms. Hong myself.
Woo Joon had asked me that favor.
By the way,
he said that someday, he'll die
where his mom died at.
But that was a lie, right?
Right, Mom?
Woo Joon!
Excuse me!
Hello? Is anyone in there?
Woo Joon!
What are you doing? Huh?
That little punk...
Oppa, wait.
I was looking all over for you!
Woo Joon!
I missed Mom.
But I was...
I was too scared to die.
Yes.
I miss Min Seo, too.
But I was too scared to die.
Min Seo...
is my daughter who died.
Truthfully, I'm...
looking for my daughter's killer.
That's the reason...
why I came here and
why I'm trying to leave.
Please don't go.
Also I'm...
a liar.
I'm not a writer, and...
the reason why I was
close with your mom...
and friendly with the library ladies...
I wasn't being sincere.
But my concerns for you...
were never lies. Not once.
Really?
If I ask you to live with me...
would you say yes?
Auntie.
He finally fell asleep.
For now, I think...
I need to stay with Woo Joon.
Me too.
I...
also need someone next to me.
You can go now.
I can go by myself.
Do you want to?
What?
By the way, where should
I go to after school?
You should come home, of course.
Our home.
See you later.
I'm going to the library. Want to come?
The library?
Ms. Hong wanted to see me.
Why don't you go ahead?
I'll join you after some errands.
Did you find out who
Jang Chul Min's accomplice is?
Almost.
Who is it?
I'll tell you later.
I don't have definitive evidence yet.
Why are you here then?
I'm here to see your aunt.
Why?
To ask her if I missed anything
from nine years ago.
And most of all...
I want to apologize to her.
About what?
To say that you're sorry for locking up
an innocent person for nine years?
Tell her that after catching the
culprit and making them pay.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
That was thoughtless of me.
There's no time.
If Auntie finds out that
Ma Ji Won was killed instead,
she'll try to find out who did it.
And if Jang Chul Min
discovers that Auntie's alive...
she won't be safe.
I'm delaying the case
announcement for now.
By any chance, if you...
Don't worry about me.
But next time, bring the evidence
that Jang Chul Min
kidnapped and killed the kid,
who the accomplice is,
and the supporting evidence.
Without that, don't bother
coming here or contacting me.
You're putting Auntie's life in danger
by just showing up here.
Got it?
How about what I'd requested?
Must you really see that?
Yes.
Eun Ji.
It's more violent and
devastating than you think.
Why must you see it anyway?
It's my sister's final moment.
Not because I want to see it...
but I have to see it.
I won't forget it...
Soo Ji.
Unni!
Hi!
Soo Ji.
I'll...
never cry.
♫  Somewhere deep
inside my memory  ♫
♫  Your footsteps  ♫