♫Hu Manli, Manli♫
♫Who's obsessed with money♫
♫Hey Manli, Manli♫
♫I just wanna tell you♫
♫Long lashes big bright eyes♫
♫Always rockin' shades♫
♫Tiny steps click-clack beat♫
♫Graceful fierce elite♫
♫Your loyal sidekick here♫
♫Ready to cheer♫
♫Copy your swagger every day♫
♫Ah-ha Ah-ha♫
♫I see you rush♫
♫Through crowds on streets each dawn♫
♫Bump into you texting alone♫
♫Midnight café empties out♫
♫Fatigue fights the void♫
♫Victory's sweet shout♫
♫Hey Honey♫
♫Let's pause♫
♫Breathe deep feel the air♫
♫Sense the vibes we share♫
♫Wallet's magic sparks the night♫
♫Whirlwind takes flight♫
♫Love's a comet streaking high♫
♫Vanishing in sky♫
♫Hey Honey♫
♫Love you first♫
♫Tomorrow's world reborn♫
♫Slip into new threads♫
♫Leave blissful steps ahead♫
♫I'll wait♫
♫Where we first met♫
♫Who craves that cash♫
♫Hey Manli, Manli♫
♫I'm so dazzled♫
♫Hu Manli, Manli♫
♫I'm all about that Manli♫
[A Better Life]
[Episode 6]
[Happiness]
Ms. Qiu, are you up?
I'm here to congratulate you.
Congrats
and congrats.
What is it?
On your third marriage.
Hope you have a big family.
Qiu Lisu of Building 38.
Come out for gifts.
Ms. Qiu.
Get up.
What is it at this ungodly hour?
Someone's at the door for you.
Who?
See for yourself.
Have a long third marriage,
a happy life,
and kids.
Congrats.
Qiu Lisu.
On your third marriage.
Have kids soon.
Ms. Qiu.
Come on.
Your gifts.
Hu Manli.
Ms. Qiu.
What are you doing?
Congratulating.
Come on, your gifts.
What the hell do you want?
Call security.
Didn't I tell you?
I'm here to congratulate.
It's a third marriage.
But we can't skip the routines.
Look.
Eight sets of bedding.
All designer brand.
Your good sleep is ensured.
Sleep until the dawn.
You won't have nightmares because of
the things you've done.
Bright colors.
Vintage.
It's costly.
But you're worth it.
Unload.
OK.
I don't need them.
Take them away.
You bought my unwanted bags,
took the man I ditched.
You're nice.
I should repay you.
Right?
Ms. Qiu marries the third time.
Get some of her lucky vibe.
Grab the candy.
Come on.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Hu Manli.
Are you done?
Not even close.
I made a red envelope
with the rest 5,000.
Go on, take it.
Third, third is a good one.
Have more kids.
Come.
Embarrassed?
Ask your husband to take them.
Prof. Ding, come out for gifts.
Come on.
- Third marriage…
- I take them!
I take…
You win this time.
Lisu.
Live happily after.
Go back.
Nothing to watch.
You're so late.
She's disturbing us.
Leave.
Get rid of her.
We're here to congratulate.
Take gifts.
We'll leave soon.
Go back.
Go.
No worries.
We'll leave soon.
Go home.
Qiu Lisu.
You should see her face.
I should've taken a pic.
You're really something.
That's insulting.
A spittoon?
That'll disgust her for sure.
She deserves it.
She pissed me off first.
She ruined my yard sale.
There's consequences.
You don't let anyone off the hook.
You're going to learn a lesson.
It's in my genes.
My mom had cancer when I was 10.
She was dying.
She held my hand and said,
"Life is about
putting on a show.
Keep up appearances.
Or you'll get laughed at."
I remember it until now.
What now?
You sent your gifts
and avenged yourself.
What's next?
I have money.
Mom, I like your car.
Really?
Congrats, Ms. Hu.
Thanks.
Hold it.
OK.
We have a car!
How about a photo?
Yes. One sec.
How do I look?
Perfect.
Come on.
Dingding.
Here.
Look at the camera.
Excellent.
Ready, cheese.
Nice car.
Original paint.
Get a cab for us.
No cheese.
Sure.
Come on.
Car!
It's generally fine.
The ornaments are tacky.
As long as the car is fine.
You can
throw it away.
What are you doing?
Don't touch anything in the car.
You don't sell?
Not to you.
I won't buy.
Away from my car.
Funny.
Why did you put it here then?
Madam.
I tried but
this is the best
we can offer.
It can't be higher.
You're kidding.
This is too low.
Here's the thing.
This is an old car.
Big mileage.
That's a fair price.
Everyone knows the prices
in flea market.
I needn't lie.
How about this?
You should go back
and take your time.
Come to if when you decide.
OK I'll sell.
Such hassle to drive around.
I'll draft a contract.
They look professional.
Ms. Duan.
Mr. Kang.
Wu Ya.
You're here.
Xiaozhou.
This is Xiaozhou.
Ms. Duan.
Kang.
This is Xiaozhou I mentioned.
He studied at my department.
Talented young man.
He's working in insurance.
Xue.
Hello.
You are one of us now.
Welcome.
Hi.
How should
we play today?
Wu Ya says
Xue was at the tennis club.
A good player.
Kang, test it out.
How about a round?
Come on.
OK.
Here.
Get changed.
Go.
Hey.
Here.
Remember what I
told you.
Rest assured.
Kang's warming up.
Let's go.
Go!
You first.
OK.
Nice.
Bravo.
Xiaozhou
is being obvious.
Did you tell him anything?
No.
That's how he plays.
Mr. Kang is a tricky opponent.
You're doing bad.
Tennis club they say?
You
have to run.
Run.
OK, running.
That's it.
At court,
go in full swing.
Don't think I'm old for you.
I'll tell you.
How about this?
I give you two points.
And I'll still win.
Again.
Xiaozhou plays nice.
No.
He lacks stamina.
Shall we take a break?
He might faint.
Really?
He's doing just fine.
It's OK.
He's no child.
He'll stop if he feels uncomfortable.
Take a break.
A break.
Mr. Kang.
Are you OK?
Sure, it's fine.
Break time.
Mr. Kang.
You OK?
Yes.
Good, good.
Kang.
Have water.
You sweat too much
after exercise.
Drink this to refill your energy.
Young men.
They're better than me.
Mr. Kang, are your legs OK?
Sorry.
Young talent.
Formidable.
Take it easy next time.
I know.
Mr. Kang.
You're such a good player
for your age.
Oh you have water.
Mr. Kang.
Let's take a break.
Take a break.
OK.
Yes, you should.
Take a break.
Good for your health.
You guys go on.
Mr. Kang.
Duan.
They left.
Take your belongings.
Bye.
So.
We'll play?
Did I
do wrong?
I don't know what was with you.
Didn't I tell you?
Let him win.
Weren't you doing fine at first?
Why did you suddenly...?
Why?
I, I tried.
But he was pushing me.
Nagging all along.
I was pissed.
So Kang stopped.
Everyone's fetching water for him.
You?
Drink on your own?
I gave it to him after.
Xue Xiaozhou.
You have to talk back?
I wanted you to butter him up.
Now?
You upset him,
a lot.
No way.
He's a superior.
Could he be that petty?
He called me formidable.
Right?
Are you stupid?
He was being polite.
You couldn't see?
Would he fall out with you
in public?
I...
We used to eat together
after playing.
If he were pleased just now,
he would invite us.
But he probably wouldn't.
So be it.
And you said,
"He's a good player
for his age."
That's how you talk?
That hurts.
You embarrassed me.
I wanted to run away.
But I was complimenting him.
Don't mention seniors' age.
You don't know that?
I'm off.
Ya.
Calm down.
I was wrong.
I was inexperienced.
I apologize.
OK, I'll apologize to Mr. Kang.
Don't.
If you do that,
it'll only make him look petty.
How could you do that?
And if you said something wrong,
good heavens...
So.
What do you want?
I'll listen to you.
Play with Kang next week.
Lose, completely.
And don't make him see it.
Make it natural.
OK?
This is so fake.
Xiaozhou.
Relationship needs
maintenance.
You sell insurance.
If you don't butter people up,
why do they place orders?
Don't want such dishonest practice.
This is socializing.
Dishonest? Come on.
I know you care about me.
I want to try in my own way.
Give me time, OK?
Ya.
There there.
Hungry?
I'll order takeaway.
No.
[Mr. Zheng, it's been long.]
[Got any free time?]
[See you tomorrow.]
What?
Someone paid the bills for me?
Yes.
Days ago,
Doc Wu Ya transferred 20,000.
Got it.
Ai Zhonghua.
Ai Linjiang.
Linjiang, it's been long.
A small gift.
Do take it.
Manli.
Thanks.
Sit.
Your mom passed away so suddenly.
I called your dad.
He's in health care center, right?
Yes.
My parents have supported each other.
Now Mom's gone.
My dad must feel bad.
He does.
The center is nice.
He should get some rest there.
That's good.
I don't think
you should live long.
You must live happily.
Ke Ming was lucky
to have a good husband
and a talented son like you.
No regrets.
I would kill for such luck
like hers.
Thank you,
Manli,
for your kindness.
I don't drink.
Didn't you know?
It's not liquor.
Medicine.
Can't get it anywhere else.
From one of my connections.
Mr. Ai.
There's a small change
about my work.
Thought you should know.
Changed your job?
Where to?
Secret.
When I settle down,
I'll tell you ASAP.
OK.
Keep in touch.
I sure will.
We've known each other so long.
I would come to you if anything's up.
When I first met you,
you were just 20.
Back then...
Hey, you, stop.
Where are you going?
I made an appointment.
You can't go in there.
I called.
Sir, please leave.
You can't go in.
Who are you?
I made an appointment.
Sorry.
Be right back.
It's OK.
Leave.
Five minutes.
No.
My boss isn't available.
We'll call the police.
Please leave.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm um...
Mr. Ai.
He wanted to go up.
He slipped in when we were away.
From some insurance firm.
He just won't go.
Mr. Ai, hello.
I am
a broker from TSI.
Get off me.
It's OK.
We TSI
have various
products.
Come to me
if there's need.
We are different
from others.
We...
Hold it there.
Yes.
TSI?
You know it?
Never heard of it.
That's the problem.
Tough Shields...
I've worked in this business
for nearly 20 years.
Never heard of it.
What Shields?
You mean...
Are you working with
an artist lately?
Spy!
I'm not!
Not a spy.
I know her.
She's Hu Manli.
We were colleagues.
Smart.
I left my info
at front desk,
everything.
Mr. Ai.
Does everyone
remember others'
personal info?
No...
Something's off.
I'm not...
You done?
Security.
- TSI…
- Security!
Google it!
It's real.
I'm a...
Hu Manli, how could you?
Move.
Despicable.
I'm not a bad guy.
I can walk on my own.
I've checked.
TSI exists.
He's really
a broker.
My bad.
It's just you run an art company.
So many articles.
Can't be too careful.
Can't just let anyone go in.
Especially some
lousy broker.
Who did you call lousy?
Hey, you.
Can't do business.
And you called Ling for help.
Do you think everyone's idle
like you?
Sorry.
If you can't do it, leave.
Can I go?
Yes.
Hello?
What is it, Mr. Ma?
Manli.
I want to ask.
Was Yuan Lang your colleague?
Yes.
At Blue Ocean.
He tries to sell products to Wei,
saying he's superior than you.
A director.
Said he could do better than you.
Did Wei buy anything?
No.
Wei never trusts the insurance business.
And now you're banned.
He doesn't
believes anyone easily.
So Wei,
didn't buy any insurance before.
No.
I see.
Thanks, Ma.
TSI.
[Hospital]
Xiaozhou.
Off work?
What are you doing here?
Picking you up.
Ya.
About yesterday.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Trust me.
I'll secure a deal
in my own way.
Give me time.
Xiaozhou.
You said things like this before.
I think you need to change.
I will.
What's wrong?
Bad mood?
I'm fine.
Let's go home.
Let me.
You look tired.
I'm OK.
He spoke up for me in front of Jin?
No way.
Why should I lie?
Ms. Hu.
Why do you bring him up?
A friend told me
he's selling insurance for TSI now.
I'm curious.
Insurance?
No wonder.
What?
He took exams as a CPA.
Why?
He said
the insurance
needs healthy development.
And
he needs to prepare for the new age.
Well, he sure thinks
like the management.
He's a good kid.
But certificates
aren't everything in our business.
Good kid?
He was ruthless to me.
Mr. Chen.
Take a look at the proposal.
I'll look through.
Call it a day.
OK.
Um, Manli.
I'm not defending him.
But he wasn't
the mastermind.
He was used.
I know.
You do?
He was abandoned then.
Expected of you.
Know everything crystal clear.
Such a shame for Xiaozhou.
Hey, Xu.
I heard because of him,
you won't have a raise.
You still speaking up for him?
I've been doing this for 30 years
and seen sorts of people.
Xiaozhou's different.
Every time there was a claim,
if he had ever consulted me a bit,
he would mention me in the report.
He takes everything
he deserves,
and won't take anything he doesn't.
He's too honest,
ended up
hurting you.
He was
kicked out too.
Alright, I see your point.
Thanks.
No need, keep in touch.
Yes.
Can't do business.
You called Ling for help.
Do you think everyone's idle
like you?
If you can't do it, leave.
Here.
This is that lady's notebook.
You tried to secure deals
with this?
Lucky she didn't know.
Or she'd be mad.
I'm desperate.
Out of choices.
OK, drop it.
It got me all screwed up.
I'll mail it to her.
Thought she blocked me.
Who is it?
That lady. Look.
[Let's meet. Something important.]
So are you going?
I...
She messed with me today, hard.
If I'll go since she asked,
who do you think I am?
I won't go.
Hey, listen.
You should meet her.
You work in the same business.
You'll meet sooner or later.
You don't want an enemy.
What if she bullies you
when you guys meet again?
Return this to her in person.
Be nice.
End this nicely.
OK.
Do as you say.
Don't think.
So awkward to see her.
I'll text her back.
What do you want?
You're here, sit.
Order whatever you like.
Straight to the point.
You joined TSI?
Good for you.
Not everyone gets in.
None of your business.
I care about you.
You called me a spy.
Why dwell on yesterday?
What?
The old woman ditched you?
Here you are.
Where did you get this?
Bet you peeked.
Sorry.
For what?
I visited Linjiang
because I'd seen your book.
I did wrong.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
I was
wondering how
I bumped into you there.
Since you hate me,
why return it to
and be honest with me?
Hating you doesn't mean
I'll play dirty to you.
It's different.
Though I hate you too,
I respect you for
that speech.
Leaving.
Hold on.
Want to cooperate?
On what?
I have clients.
You work in the business.
We should make deals together.
No.
Why?
I made you banned.
You smeared my name.
We have grudges against each other.
We won't last.
Totally wrong.
Sit.
We have a common enemy.
Qiu Lisu.
She ruined my family
and abandoned you.
Right?
We both hate her.
That makes us friends.
We work together,
having each other's back,
to slap her hard.
How nice.
No, thanks.
Why?
We're different.
How?
Don't you sell insurance
like me?
I want to be decent.
So I'm indecent?
I should go.
Young man.
It's not easy to sell insurance.
You need my help.
Or you're getting nowhere.
Don't look down on me.
I can do whatever you can.
All clients on this book,
I introduce them to you.
See if you can secure a deal.
I'll never sell insurance if you do.
Bet?
What if I do?
Oh yeah?
OK.
I'll leave you alone.
You said it.
And,
if you fail,
you work with me.
OK?
Scared?
You agreed?
Yeah?
I'm surprised.
Thought you hated her.
She said
I couldn't even make
one deal.
Too insulting.
I must prove myself.
She should know
I can sell insurance decently.
I believe in you.
Eat up.
Work hard
from tomorrow on.
Stay strong.
What?
Working with Xiaozhou?
You crazy?
He set you up.
I know the whole story.
He was used.
[Bai Yongfeng]
♪Will be you mine forever♪
♪I'm forever yours♪
♪You're my wife now♪
♪You're my one true lover♪
♪My dear wife♪
♪We'll live happily after♪
He returned my book
to me
and apologized.
I thought
he might a nice person.
Of all nice people,
you chose him?
♪Dear kids♪
Hello.
Ms. Liu Duo, right?
♪Dear kids♪
♪Little Papageno♪
♪Little Papagena♪
♪Another little Papageno♪
♪Another little Papagena♪
More importantly,
he's at TSI.
He gets double of my old commission.
Highest in the market.
Won't that double
my income?
That makes sense.
But he turned you down.
Trust me.
I'm convincing him.
Wait for good news.
♪We'll have numerous kids♪
♪Which will leave us in ecstasy♪
♪Bless their parents♪
Hello.
Are you Ms. Zhang?
Yes.
I'm a broker from TSI.
What?
Someone's stealing your clients?
I'll teach them a lesson.
Just ignore him.
Shut him out.
Who is it?
Hello, sir.
I'm from TSI.
My name
is Xue Xiaozhou.
Mr. Hu, if you have doubts,
I can explain for you.
Um...
Here's the thing.
Yes.
I'm thinking...
Oh, I forgot something big.
My rice was delivered.
At the delivery center.
I'll go get it.
OK, I'll wait.
And.
I will
lock the door.
I'll wait outside.
It takes long.
Too heavy.
It's OK.
Um...
I should help you.
OK?
I'll fetch it for you.
It's OK.
You know the way?
Walk past two blocks.
Turn left.
Left.
No problem.
OK.
Read our file.
Sure.
♫If I close both eyes tonight♫
♫Back to that wishing summer night♫
♫Wind brushes your shaking frame♫
♫That world feels close just the same♫
♫If I dare to face the dawn♫
♫Do you know this face you'd drawn♫
♫Gray spirals looped in endless chase♫
♫Tracing tears not words they trace♫
♫How many times must this repeat♫
♫Sighs pull my gaze to retreat♫
♫Sleepless nights, risks untold♫
♫None of it for my own soul♫
♫Winds blew, rains poured♫
♫Umbrellas broke, we soared♫
♫Sky fell, ground shook♫
♫Through dusk till dawn I stood♫
♫Cars passed, dreams drowned♫
♫Every stop's chain unbound♫
♫Moon watched, stars blazed♫
♫Lamps died, connections phased♫
♫Held hands, laughed then cried♫
♫Hearts froze, parts died inside♫
♫Tried hard, spoke true♫
♫Now I'm someone I never knew♫
♫Love came, hate stayed♫
♫I arrived, you frayed♫
♫Voice cracked, tears burned♫
♫Life lost, lessons earned♫
♫Grew up, let go♫
♫Why cling to old sorrow♫
♫How many loops replay♫
♫Sighs steal my gaze away♫
♫Lost nights, bold bets♫
♫Nothing for my regrets♫
♫Winds raged, storms crashed♫
♫Dawns broke, I held fast♫
♫Cars fled, dreams fled♫
♫Every route left dead♫
♫Love left, hate stayed♫
♫Voice gone, tears paid♫
♫Grew strong, moved on♫
♫Why dwell when it's gone♫