♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪Who's obsessed with money♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I just wanna tell you♪
♪Long lashes big bright eyes♪
♪Always rockin' shades♪
♪Tiny steps click-clack beat♪
♪Graceful fierce elite♪
♪Your loyal sidekick here♪
♪Ready to cheer♪
♪Copy your swagger every day♪
♪Ah-ha Ah-ha♪
♪I see you rush♪
♪Through crowds on streets each dawn♪
♪Bump into you texting alone♪
♪Midnight café empties out♪
♪Fatigue fights the void♪
♪Victory's sweet shout♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Let's pause♪
♪Breathe deep feel the air♪
♪Sense the vibes we share♪
♪Wallet's magic sparks the night♪
♪Whirlwind takes flight♪
♪Love's a comet streaking high♪
♪Vanishing in sky♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Love you first♪
♪Tomorrow's world reborn♪
♪Slip into new threads♪
♪Leave blissful steps ahead♪
♪I'll wait♪
♪Where we first met♪
♪Who craves that money♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm so dazzled♪
♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm all about that Manli♪
A Better Life
Episode 12
Come on, let's drink.
[Grilled skewers]
[Giant clams]
Drink up.
Dude,
you have such an amazing dad!
Why didn't you mention it?
I didn't know either.
Wait.
Will he really give you that much money?
Not chicken wings?
Listen up, everyone.
He wouldn't dare refuse now.
He's afraid his precious son finds out.
Three million!
I wouldn't see that much money
in eight lifetimes!
Man, truth be told,
I think three million is too little.
What?
How so?
Whatever historical issues aside,
you're his real son, right?
Yes.
Then you and that official heir of his
should have equal status.
By all accounts
your rich dad's money should be split
fifty-fifty.
No, no.
Dude,
three mil is plenty of money!
It's more than you can spend
for a lifetime!
Look how small-minded you are!
Man, listen to me.
He's trying to hush things up now
not just because
he fears his son will find out.
He's definitely scared
you'll demand more.
Think about it, makes sense right?
I'm just too kind-hearted!
Exactly!
Dear father,
looks like three million won't be enough.
You'll need to compensate me more.
You make a pretty good point!
Here.
Cheers.
Drink.
Wow.
Humidifier?
No wonder it didn't feel so dry today.
Hey.
The logistics department went all out.
Logistics?
What are you thinking?
It's not in their budget.
Huh?
Then where's this humidifier from
The lady who
came to our ward three months ago,
the one who later
passed from lung infection,
remember her?
She has a son.
He's tall and handsome.
Heard he's some business owner.
Mr. Ai. Do you know him?
To show gratitude
for our care of his mother,
he donated a humidifier to every office
in the Rehabilitation Department
Who's he really doing this for?
I don't believe
he has no ulterior motive.
Hey,
Wu Ya.
Is he the one
who sent you flowers before?
What?
You're applying for hospital dormitory?
Why?
Keeping some distance between two people
is good for relationship development.
Helps maintain novelty, too.
Tell me the truth.
Are you saving money to get married?
It must be.
Living alone,
he can rent a smaller place, right?
Ms. Duan, please stop asking.
I want to move in as soon as possible.
Please put in a good word fro me.
Alright, I understand.
It's ready.
Eight seconds, right?
Here's one for you.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Xiaozhou.
I'm moving into the hospital dormitory.
Since our lease
is about to expire anyway,
I was thinking
we could switch to a smaller place.
No, you...you don't have to.
It's not like I'm being considerate.
It's just my department...
What about it?
You know how my
overtime keeps increasing.
My daily commute takes 1-2 hours,
and traffic jams make it unpredictable.
Several times,
I was late for morning rounds.
The director didn't look happy.
Should we maybe
move closer to the hospital?
The director suggested it to me.
Said there's an available bed
and asked me to consider it.
I can't play dumb, can I?
I see...
It's way over eight seconds.
Eat it.
Overcooked? Let me make you a fresh one.
Here.
Eight.
Why do I feel like
I'm being abandoned?
Exactly.
I'm climbing the social ladder
and dumping you.
Don't you dare be so dramatic.
You can't joke about such things.
Don't scare me.
Just kidding.
Here, it's ready.
Have something light.
Dad.
During my trip to France,
I met some young contemporary artists.
They're quite interested in
entering the Chinese market.
So,
my initial plan is
maybe after this June,
I'll get their representative works
and see if we can organize an exhibition.
Good.
You handle it.
Dad.
Any instructions?
What should I do first?
No special instructions.
The company affairs are yours now.
You make the decisions.
Thanks, Dad.
I'll get back to work.
Everything alright?
Yes.
Dad.
Why is one of Qin's paintings missing?
You put it away?
I,
I thought
I could put up another painting
for a change of mood.
Oh.
In that case,
I can take it back for you.
The preservation conditions here
might not meet the requirements.
It's perfectly safe here.
I'll have someone hang it
in the bedroom this afternoon.
I'm right here.
Why ask someone else?
I'll do it.
I need to take a nap.
Off you go.
Sure, Dad.
Okay.
Who are you?
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Mr. Ai.
Stop right there. Who are you?
Dad, you know him?
Sorry, this is a private club.
Hey, Mr. Ai, are we in the wrong place?
Get out!
Hey, look!
What?
Do we two look alike?
No.
Yes.
Man,
it's unbelievable!
You're just like twins.
What are you doing?
Dad.
You know him?
The three days aren't up yet.
Why are here?
Three million is too little.
Then how much do you want?
How much can he get?
I want the same.
What did you say?
Dad, who is he?
Okay, you can leave for now.
Hey, Dad.
Your son's talking to you.
I said leave.
Go.
Alright?
Dad.
Dad, who is he really?
Tell him.
Having another brother is a good thing.
If you keep talking.
I'll make sure you get nothing.
You hear me?
Leave.
No, wait.
I said get out!
No.
Well.
You won't talk? Then I will.
Your dad is my dad too.
Ma Xiao...
After college, he was assigned to
the cultural center
in my mom's hometown.
He dated my mom.
- Ma Xiaowei. -She then had me!
Don't listen...
Later your mom
- Don't listen. - went painting.
Don't listen to him.
When our dad saw
your grandpa had power and influence,
- he wanted the big city! - Ma Xiaowei!
- Ma Xiaowei! - Then later,
he abandoned my mom!
Ma Xiaowei!
Ridiculous right?
Get out now!
Out!
Is what he said true?
Let me explain okay?
-Let me explain. -Dad, Dad.
Okay?
Since my brother is here today,
let's lay all cards on the table.
Why does he get to live large,
while my mom just gets
a few thousands yearly?
You kept in touch with them.
You maintained contact.
You gave them money.
How could you do this to my mom?
Hey, man.
There's an order to everything.
Shut up!
My mom was his first love.
It's unforgettable.
Shut up!
I... I...
I never betrayed your mother.
Let me explain.
Okay?
Dad.
You kept the communication.
Is it because you can't forget that woman?
No, I never...
No.
Ai Zhonghua.
How could you do this to my mom?
How could you do this to me?
Linjiang.
It's not what you think.
- All these years were just an act?
- No.
So you had another family outside?
It's not what you think.
I can't stand this anymore.
Linjiang.
Dad! Dad! Dad!
- Don't go. I'm here. - Linjiang.
- I'll take care of you. - Linjiang!
Give me a bigger share of the money.
- You're... - Let go!
Mr. Ai!
I didn't do anything.
Help! We need help here!
Mr. Ai!
Let me ask you.
If the old man dies now,
can I still get half the estate?
Yes.
I already checked for you.
As long as there's no will,
it's 50-50 split.
Really?
Are you sure?
Suspected heart attack.
Nearest green channel center
is about 1km away.
Call 120! Quick!
Man, call 120!
Heart relief pills!
Here.
Baodan.
Xue Xiaozhou.
Look what you've done.
Mr. Ai is admitted to the ICU
because of Ma Xiaowei.
They're resuscitating him now. Happy?
Let's go.
Hu Manli.
What's going on?
If anything happens to
Mr. Ai today,
I'm telling you...
I... I didn't...
What exactly happened?
Chen.
Ms. Hu
You finally came.
How's Mr. Ai?
Heart attack.
Still unconscious after CPR.
Currently under observation in ICU.
[ICU]
Insurance salespeople?
Why are you here?
So eager to do business?
Can we see Mr. Ai?
No.
Don't you know ICU
doesn't allow outsiders?
He won't even let me in.
Call the police!
We did.
When police came
and heard he's Mr. Ai's son,
they said it's family dispute
and told us to work it out.
Where's Linjiang?
His phone's turned off.
Nobody knows his whereabouts now.
This critical moment shows
which son is actually reliable.
Exactly.
All you bystanders step back.
Go away.
Get out!
How annoying.
Ms. Hu,
there's another situation now.
I'm afraid this Ma Xiaowei
won't be satisfied with 3 million.
What does he want?
He's now guarding outside ICU
blocking everyone from seeing Mr. Ai.
If anything happens to Mr. Ai,
without leaving a will...
So that's his scheme.
Now.
List all possible places
where his son might be.
We must find Ai Linjiang now
to take charge of this crisis.
Understood.
I've sent you several addresses
of places Mr. Linjiang frequents.
Let's search separately
If we find him?
Tell him to come here immediately!
He won't come.
He has to.
Mr. Ai deceived him for so long.
He'll never forgive him.
Mr. Ai is lying in bed now.
What are you saying?
Hu Manli.
The day you assigned me
Mr. Ai's case was
my dad's death anniversary.
I'm sorry.
What I said that day
was indeed too harsh.
But you insisted I deceived you.
That made me angry too.
Three years ago, he had a car accident
and was critically injured.
Before dying,
he asked to see me.
Said he needed to talk to me.
I didn't go.
Why didn't you go?
Why should I?
What could he possibly say anyway?
Nothing but that same "I'm sorry".
Can his sorry
undo all the harm he caused?
And no matter what he says,
I'll never forgive him.
Whether forgiveness comes is uncertain.
The key is your dad is gone.
You'll never hear him again.
That's why you've regretted it till now.
Deep down,
you actually want to forgive him.
Hating someone is easy.
But forgiving takes courage.
Hu Manli, you don't understand anything.
You don't know how much
I used to idolize my dad.
How good he was to me.
I just feel like
all my memories before
were just an illusion.
I'll never forgive him.
Never.
The reason you're in such pain
is precisely because your dad loved you.
When there's a knot in your heart,
undo it.
Your dad's "I'm sorry",
you need to find it yourself.
Understand?
My ride's here.
I'm leaving.
Call me later.
Ten years ago
when he was with that woman,
he stopped being my father!
He doesn't deserve to be my dad!
I'm not his son!
I won't forgive him!
I'll never forgive him!
Dad, is this your new office?
It'll all be yours someday.
Son,
remember:
All dad's hard work
is for your future.
I'll take responsibility for my mistakes.
Hello, need a driver?
No, no, thanks.
Mr. Ai!
Your father had a heart attack.
He's in the hospital now.
What kind of trick is this?
A sympathy play?
Save it.
No, I-I-I'm not lying!
You can call Chen
to confirm it yourself.
I'll arrange
the best doctors for his treatment.
I'll fulfill all my obligations,
but that's all between us.
- Hello? - No, Mr. Ai,
Are you the owner of car 0081?
Here, come here.
It's okay, I'll take him.
I'll cancel the order.
Thanks, thank you.
Xue Xiaozhou!
What your father needs now
isn't a doctor!
I'm sorry.
You... your father...
I know exactly what he wants.
But many things require reciprocity.
He never gave it to me.
How could I give it to him?
You simply don't understand!
You're completely trapped in
your own imagination!
If you don't go to the hospital tonight
and don't sign those papers,
your father might...
You'll
never get to hear his explanation.
I know this feeling.
My father called for me before he died.
I...
I didn't go.
To this day, I still live with that pain.
Your father...
Do you
want to hear my story?
Okay... I understand.
Xiaozhou found Mr. Linjiang.
He refuses to come back.
Doctor.
Who's Ai Zhonghua's family?
Me! I'm his son!
Sign the critical condition notice.
Critical condition notice...
My dad's condition is critical?
No.
We still need to treat the patient.
This is an unexpected incident notice,
meaning we should prepare ourselves.
Doctor, I'm the patient's subordinate.
I'd like to know
Mr. Ai's current condition.
The patient is currently stable
with standard treatment.
If all goes well,
he should wake up tomorrow.
The prognosis is quite optimistic.
That's good.
Dude.
You can't sign this document
Why? Why?
Only when the old man
is gone
can we get half the inheritance.
How can you say that?
He's my biological father!
Exactly.
Did he ever treat you as his son?
If he wakes up,
forget half the inheritance.
You might
lose even the original three million.
Xiaowei,
three... three million?
Ma Xiaowei.
Sign it now.
The doctor said
Mr. Ai will wake up tomorrow.
Three million!
Don't.
You can't sign it.
Are you sure?
I won't sign.
You crappy notice says you're
not responsible for anything.
What if you kill my dad?
Exactly.
It's just a formality.
Then guarantee
you can cure him.
How can I guarantee that?
See? He can't guarantee.
Right, I think your hospital
just wants my dad's money.
We're going home!
Let's go home.
Ma Xiaowei!
Are you trying to kill Mr. Ai?
What are you saying?
He's your boss's real son!
You dare drive us away?
Hear that? Xiaowei says no treatment.
Right.
Find someone!
Get Mr. Ai discharged!
Doctor.
Can you treat him first?
Family will sign when they arrive.
Well...
It's a matter of life and death.
Doctor, let me tell you.
You can't treat recklessly.
If anything goes wrong,
you'll be held responsible.
Right.
Ma Xiaowei, you bastard!
What are you doing?
Hit me?
Stop it!
What are you all doing?
Stop arguing! Quiet! This is a hospital!
Don't fight!
Stop fighting!
What's all the noise?
What are you doing?
No fighting!
Doctor, I'll sign.
I'm Ai Zhonghua's son.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
I'm signing it.
Go back.
What are you doing?
How dare you come here?
My dad became like this because of you!
And now you come to sign this thing.
I think you're
deliberately trying to kill him!
Right.
I did this to him?
Ma Xiaowei,
we'll settle our score later!
Right now I'm here to sign this!
No way!
Sign it, I dare you.
Listen up everyone
Nobody harms my father.
I'll stand guard here today.
If I say no treatment, then no treatment.
Exactly.
Stop it!
This is a hospital!
We won't tolerate your nonsense!
Family disputes, is it?
Take it outside!
Let me tell you.
Now is the critical recovery period.
Miss this window,
you face the consequences!
Move aside!
This is ridiculous!
What?
What now?
Bring it on.
Mr. Ai, calm down!
Wanna fight?
Calm down, Mr. Ai.
Ma Xiaowei.
You'd better pray that Mr. Ai
can wake up.
What do you mean by that?
He's my biological father
Of course I want him healthy.
And safe and sound.
No, you don't.
You want something bad to happen,
so you can get half the fortune.
You... you...
Don't talk nonsense.
That's your assumption.
I never meant that!
Your clever scheme isn't wrong.
But if things really
come to that point.
You'll need to prove your relation
with Mr. Ai.
Right? What will you need?
A DNA test.
To run a DNA test,
you need Mr. Ai Linjiang's approval.
If he disagrees,
you can't get tested.
Listen, don't try to scare me.
You're his man.
You side with him.
I graduated from law school.
If you don't believe me,
we can make a bet
to see if I'm telling the truth.
You'd better pray Mr. Ai stays safe.
And in good health
When he's awake,
he might still spare you some change
for your mother's sake.
Otherwise, you won't get a single cent.
Xiaowei.
Alright.
Sign if you want to.
Do whatever you please.
But let me make this clear.
If anything happens to my father,
I won't let you off the hook. Let's go!
Just you wait!
Call the doctor! We'll sign.
Okay.
It's already dawn.
How did you finally convince
Ai Linjiang?
I'll never know
what my father wanted to tell me
before he died.
Even just an "I'm sorry"
or calling me "son" once.
I might
not have suffered this much.
Mr. Ai.
Don't you
want to hear your father
tell you the truth himself?
Your story is moving,
but it doesn't move me.
The truth is already clear.
My father,
for all these years,
has kept ties with his first love,
even with shady dealings
I didn't know about.
What if he maintained contact
out of responsibility?
Don't speak for him.
I'm not speaking for him.
When I first heard Mr. Ai's story,
I thought it was fake too.
I thought he made it up.
It thought it was to
make excuses for himself.
I was furious too.
But I'm just an outsider.
I know nothing.
Only you know
whether he played
the perfect husband and father
for 30 years,
or
he genuinely cared for you both.
Only you know the truth, Mr. Ai.
Let me ask you.
What if it's really as I suspect?
Then go hear his confession.
Even the most wicked villain
deserves the right to repent.
Seriously, Mr. Ai, don't end up like me.
In the days to come,
you'll keep thinking over and over
about the days you spent together.
Were they real
or just fake?
Take my advice.
Go to the hospital.
Listen to Mr. Ai.
Let him explain.
Don't regret it for life.
Not bad.
You've improved.
Mainly thanks to what you said.
Really?
I've said so many reasonable things.
Which one?
The one about
apologies needing to be reclaimed.
Have you reclaimed yours?
Me?
Still working on it.
Not that fast.
I'm back.
Yes.
Baodan.
What are you doing?
Looking for something.
Looking for what?
Ya, you asked me before.
After my mom had the accident
if I regretted
dropping out to care for her.
Why bring this up suddenly?
Everyone thinks I did it
because I'm a good son.
But actually no.
I didn't do it for my mom,
or not entirely for her.
Mostly I did it for myself.
For yourself?
After my dad passed away,
I felt so much pain.
To put it simply,
I was utterly devastated.
I felt like
I had nothing left.
I had to exhaust myself
by taking care of my mom
just to forget the pain.
I was using this to numb myself.
Otherwise,
I might have...
Xiaozhou,
even though you keep saying
You won't forgive your father,
you actually love him dearly.
Don't you?
My dad asked someone
to buy me is game console from Japan.
After he bought it,
we both became
totally addicted to this racing game.
We played it every single day,
day and night.
Later because of this,
my mom kept scolding my dad.
But dad always protected me.
They went back and forth.
Anyway...
It was pretty happy times.
But soon after, they separated.
What?
Test if it still works.
It's been so long.
Probably won't work.
Just give it a try.
Here, hold this.
Take it.
Steady.
Careful.
It still works.
What?
I'll play with you.
No...never mind.
Consider it remembering your dad.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Your parents split up 13 years ago.
But this game's last login was
three years ago.
On your birthday.
Xiaozhou.
I guess
after your parents separated,
every year on your birthday,
your dad would launch this game.
He was using this method
to quietly think of you.
I'm waiving inheritance rights
to that apartment.
The agreement.
Xiaozhou.
Thank you for understanding
Once I receive
the down payment, I'll transfer
the 500K immediately.
No need.
Wait till the company turns profit.
I'm not selling for the money.
My dad...
Anyway, the sale proceeds
must go to company operations.
This is clearly stated in the agreement.
After the transaction,
I'll show you transfer proof.
Get the contract notarized by lawyer.
Then arrange sale immediately.
This needs urgent handling
before he changes his mind.
Alright.
by the way
is everything arranged with Li Fendou?
It's all scheduled.
But what if Professor Ding
doesn't cooperate?
He will.
He's a scholar.
What scholars want is respect.
As long as we show enough respect,
he'll give us
whatever we want.
Thank you.
Just a small 42nd birthday party.
Some noodles at home would suffice.
Why must we go out?
This is the first birthday
we celebrate together.
You have to follow my arrangements.
No objections allowed.
Isn't this Li Fendou's place?
Why are we here?
Ms. Qiu!
Mr. Li!
I didn't know you are today.
Just finished a lunch meeting.
And this is?
Let me introduce you.
This is my partner, Ding Zhiyuan.
Hello.
Professor Ding!
Hello!
I've long heard of your reputation.
I contacted you the other day.
Ms. Qiu said you're busy.
But look!
I caught you red-handed today!
As they say, planned meetings
aren't as good as chance encounters.
Let's have a proper drink today, okay?
Allow me!
That won't do.
Today is Professor Ding's birthday.
Don't you dare steal my guest.
Birthday, huh?
Perfect.
Wang, come here!
Coming!
Clear out the best private room for me.
And order the finest cake.
It must arrive within half an hour.
Yes, Mr. Li.
Mr. Li, really, there's no need.
Professor Ding...
I understand.
Birthdays should be for couples' time.
But I must show my respect.
Don't worry,
I'll leave after arranging everything.
Won't be in the way.
How could we accept this?
Exactly. You're the host treating us.
Guests shouldn't make the host leave.
That'll be inappropriate.
Mr. Li, how about...
You...
Join us?
Ms. Qiu.
I shouldn't be a third wheel.
Don't be silly.
We'll have plenty of couple time.
Right, Zhiyuan?
Right.
Yes.
See?
Let's eat together.
That'd be wonderful!
If Professor Ding doesn't mind,
let's celebrate together!
Tea first, alright?
Alright!
Here.
Let's go.
♪If I close both eyes tonight♪
♪Back to that wishing summer night♪
♪Wind brushes your shaking frame♪
♪That world feels close just the same♪
♪If I dare to face the dawn♪
♪Do you know this face you'd drawn♪
♪Gray spirals looped in endless chase♪
♪Tracing tears not words they trace♪
♪How many times must this repeat♪
♪Sighs pull my gaze to retreat♪
♪Sleepless nights, risks untold♪
♪None of it for my own soul♪
♪Winds blew, rains poured♪
♪Umbrellas broke, we soared♪
♪Sky fell, ground shook♪
♪Through dusk till dawn I stood♪
♪Cars passed, dreams drowned♪
♪Every stop's chain unbound♪
♪Moon watched, stars blazed♪
♪Lamps died, connections phased♪
♪Held hands, laughed then cried♪
♪Hearts froze, parts died inside♪
♪Tried hard, spoke true♪
♪Now I'm someone I never knew♪
♪Love came, hate stayed♪
♪I arrived, you frayed♪
♪Voice cracked, tears burned♪
♪Life lost, lessons earned♪
♪Grew up, let go♪
♪Why cling to old sorrow♪
♪How many loops replay♪
♪Sighs steal my gaze away♪
♪Lost nights, bold bets♪
♪Nothing for my regrets♪
♪Winds raged, storms crashed♪
♪Dawns broke, I held fast♪
♪Cars fled, dreams fled♪
♪Every route left dead♪
♪Love left, hate stayed♪
♪Voice gone, tears paid♪
♪Grew strong, moved on♪
♪Why dwell when it's gone♪