♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪Who's obsessed with money♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I just wanna tell you♪
♪Long lashes big bright eyes♪
♪Always rockin' shades♪
♪Tiny steps click-clack beat♪
♪Graceful fierce elite♪
♪Your loyal sidekick here♪
♪Ready to cheer♪
♪Copy your swagger every day♪
♪Ah-ha Ah-ha♪
♪I see you rush♪
♪Through crowds on streets each dawn♪
♪Bump into you texting alone♪
♪Midnight café empties out♪
♪Fatigue fights the void♪
♪Victory's sweet shout♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Let's pause♪
♪Breathe deep feel the air♪
♪Sense the vibes we share♪
♪Wallet's magic sparks the night♪
♪Whirlwind takes flight♪
♪Love's a comet streaking high♪
♪Vanishing in sky♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Love you first♪
♪Tomorrow's world reborn♪
♪Slip into new threads♪
♪Leave blissful steps ahead♪
♪I'll wait♪
♪Where we first met♪
♪Who craves that cash♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm so dazzled♪
♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm all about that Manli♪
[A Better Life]
[Episode 27]
Ms. Hu.
Mr. Jin didn't want me to tell you.
But for the 10% damages,
he threated to resign.
Thank you for telling me.
Mr. Jin.
Have tea.
Thank you for looking
after me these years.
And for criticizing me just now.
I feel enlightened.
This time I'll save myself.
But don't worry. I won't perish.
After this,
I'll thank you again.
This bell here,
can you reach it?
Try it.
OK?
I'll be here with Dingding.
Call us anytime.
Xiaozhou.
What happened to Mom,
is it serious?
It's a little tricky.
Can you help her?
Calm down.
Wait until she's back.
Hey.
What happened?
[Seizure Notice]
Don't.
Unnecessary.
Why are you here?
I
came to check on you.
I'm fine.
You're in this state.
Don't play tough.
I have family.
I have to support
them.
Don't you forget.
You still have me.
Mom.
I want to talk to you.
Dingding.
Were you scared?
What's the big deal?
You think little of me.
Um.
Dad will pick me up.
Can I stay
there a little longer?
Why?
Nothing.
It's just you don't
have time for me now.
And I'm unable to take care of Grandpa.
I'm useless.
I should stay out for a while
in case I take up your time.
I told him everything.
It all happened.
No need to keep a secret.
Don't say that.
No matter how, I'll love you.
Mom.
Actually, I want to save money for you.
Look.
I could enjoy
my life at his place.
How nice.
They feel guilty.
I do whatever
I want.
If I spend their money,
won't it be saving money for us?
Mom.
Once I'm gone,
you'll save money, and time.
Win big.
Right?
Dad's downstairs.
I'll be off.
Stay if you don't want to go.
I'll be worried.
It's not a battlefield.
I want to go.
It's nice.
I'll be enjoying myself.
Mom, focus on your goals.
Xiaozhou.
You too.
I'll be back on weekends.
You're really going?
I see you off.
Have meals regularly.
You need nutrition now.
Cut down on snacks.
A milk before bed.
Yes.
I'll make good use of their grocery.
Let me.
It's soon monthly tests.
Work hard.
Spend less time with your phone.
OK, go back.
Right.
Brought your calcium supplements?
Yes.
Probiotic?
I guess I did.
That's a no.
I'll get them for you.
No.
I can have Dad
buy them.
Mom.
Don't treat me like a kiddo.
I've grown a lot these days.
For you,
I'll be good.
OK?
Watch me.
You always say my shoelaces
are loose.
Here.
Test them. They're tight.
Bye, Mom.
Mom.
You're the best.
I love you forever.
Drive safely.
What happened to Mom?
Nothing.
It's all good.
I'm sleepy.
I'll take a nap.
Don't talk to me.
I want to negotiate
with the firm.
I'll sell the house to pay.
No, I told you.
Wait for a while.
I'll have Lisu's money.
It's not about money.
Is it
time?
It'll take more time
to sell a house.
OK.
I can be your guarantor.
I don't want to run again.
What do you mean?
Back at the entrance of the firm,
you called me
blissfully ignorant.
I succeeded
simply because I joined in
at the right timing.
It was not much about my capability.
I was angry. It didn't mean a thing.
You were right.
During the decades,
I was indeed lucky.
I ran in an elevator
and thought I made it by myself,
omnipotent.
I crossed the line
and thought I was wronged.
In that case,
anyone in insurance
during the period
can hit it big.
Impossible.
You made it
for the right timing,
and for you are better than others.
Thanks.
But this time.
I really think I'm wrong.
Selling the house
isn't just for payment.
I want to get up
on my own,
washing away the past,
and start all over again.
Don't worry about me.
I had nothing
but I became Insurance Star.
I can now
start from scratch too.
Daer cried on the way.
He wouldn't tell a thing.
Then,
I called Manli and
learnt the whole thing.
Manli could do anything
for personal gains,
stooping so low.
Now it's on the up and up,
she suffered even more.
You can't be sure.
Probably there's a misunderstanding.
I know her.
She looks snobbish,
but she won't break the law.
I think there's
a story behind.
Of course, it doesn't
matter now.
I just think it's a special time
for the kid.
So I want him to stay
for a while.
How long is that?
Zhiyuan.
I also need to be looked after.
I don't want to neglect him.
You won't.
He goes to school during day,
and has dinner at night.
He does his homework
and goes to sleep.
Lisu.
Look.
We'll going to have a baby.
Though you're not Daer's mom,
the baby
in your belly
is still Daer's sibling.
Daer could stay here
to get to know them a little earlier.
The room downstairs faces north.
It's a bit cold.
Will he mind?
No...
Thanks.
I'll go to prepare.
Daer.
Li Fendou.
You know him?
No.
But this professor influencer.
Ding Zhiyuan, I know him.
Li Fendou is something.
He has a humble background
but he's sharp.
Running a stall,
he made money and bought houses.
Then he purchased buildings
in the right time.
Now he's worth a lot.
You mean...
I'm informed
he's consulting
inheritance.
This is our chance.
Follow up on his case.
I see.
I'll read the autobiography.
And, Qing.
I'm familiar already with
the family office's work.
Now you assigned a new task.
I want to request
a team of my own.
OK.
Tell the human resources to
recruit.
I have my candidate.
[Nursing Home Example]
Hello?
Is that Tianyang Nursing Home?
Check here.
Sign at the bottom if everything's OK.
Madam.
Anything wrong?
Can we raise the price?
Well.
I bought this house
for 12,000,000.
If I sell it at 9,000,000,
I'll suffer a huge loss.
You know the market.
This is the best we can do.
I know a guy sold a first-floor house.
The same layout.
9,500,000.
But you want a one-time payment.
We'll have to lower the price.
Is that right?
How about this?
Eight is a lucky number.
Let's make it 9,080,000.
Madam, if you're still considering,
we should call it a day.
No...
But you'll also
keep the furniture.
These pieces are
costly.
I know you have a kid.
New ones will give out chemicals.
It's bad for the kid.
Right.
These pieces of furniture.
All designer brands.
I've been maintaining them.
The chair.
A whole piece of marble.
Not pieced together.
Look, steady.
A bit dear.
Fine, a little expensive.
Should we raise a bit?
OK.
Another 50,000.
We are really in need.
80,000 is really a bargain.
Right?
He's right.
60,000.
Not a penny more.
- But…
- OK!
That's...
Deal.
Thank you.
OK.
Please sign.
I'll make a supplementary
agreement on furniture.
OK.
Sign where?
Here.
OK.
This way.
Thank you.
OK.
Bye.
See you, sir.
Thanks.
Bye.
What's next?
I'll pay
Blue Ocean
and pay up mortgage.
I'll use the rest
to accommodate Dad.
What about you?
Me?
Let's see.
[Employment Contract]
What?
For me?
It's not right.
I was banned.
I can't sell.
You won't sell.
You'll join the family office.
I said
the last thing I need
is sympathy.
It's not sympathy.
I need you to work with me.
Work with you?
Funny.
Always working together.
Running in circles.
Come on.
Let's ally.
No.
Why not?
I don't have the energy.
Look at my dad.
I need to look after him
and his recovery.
Go find a helper.
Leave it to the professional.
I asked around.
They charge nearly 10,000 a month.
I can't afford it.
Manli.
I'm sincerely offering
you a job.
Full welfare
and a base pay.
Extra bonuses come with
any new projects.
You get to decide the ratio.
You'll earn a lot.
Forget it.
I don't want others to look after Dad.
Then,
I have an idea.
At Tianyang, we design zones
catering to various needs.
Just now it's self-care zone.
So it focuses on good environment.
This is nursing zone
where people with reduced mobility
and elders who need care live.
So it addresses
recovery functions.
This way.
Here.
This bed is imported.
It syncs moments of your back and knee,
reducing deviation of body.
And it restricts angles to
reduce pressure on your chest
and stomach.
Mr. Xue.
You said the client had
a cerebral hemorrhage.
Right?
Yes.
You've come to the right place.
We have professional recovery equipment
and doctors.
They'll guide your recovery.
An elder used to live here.
After a year of recovery,
he moved to the self-care zone.
If you're interested,
we can talk to him.
OK.
No, thanks.
Thanks...
Excuse me.
A moment.
You don't like it here?
I like it.
It doesn't like me.
With my dad's conditions,
it'll be 20,000 a month.
I calculated.
After you pay Blue Ocean
and mortgage,
you then buy an annuity product.
Your dad can live here,
and you get to work at TSI.
There's no place like home.
But you don't have
a home.
I'll rent.
I'll pass on a nursing home.
But what about your dad?
He needs care
and recovery.
He needs help.
You'll help him?
Yes.
You won't work?
Having a helper costs money too.
My pay might not cover the bills.
I'll do it.
Have some senses!
Listen.
You got fired
and banned from insurance.
Why did you work so hard
to get back into the business?
For money. Why else?
Because you love your job.
Your passion.
You can have the best of both worlds.
Why will you give up?
He's my dad.
He needs my care.
I can't bear to push him
into a nursing home.
My dad
didn't do anything big.
But he gave me his all.
I can't treat him this way.
Manli.
Dong?
Ms. Zhou.
[Homage to...]
Honey.
They're here to see you.
Manli.
The one who
sells insurance?
Yes.
This is...
I'm Xue Xiaozhou.
Her colleague.
I also do this job.
We met before.
I can't recall.
It's OK.
After her last year's checkup,
I asked Sun Jie about it.
She said Zhou's in the early stage.
Yes.
She got oblivious.
So I told Sun Jie
I should move in
and take care of her.
Turned out I
hurt her instead.
Hurt her?
How so?
You need to be careful
and professional
to look after patients with AD.
I thought
as long as I
watch over,
keep an eye on her,
nothing will happen.
But her memory failed so bad
that one time
she didn't recognize her granddaughter.
The girl cried nonstop.
She finally recalled days after.
Then,
the doc advised us to get treatment
at institutions.
I need to thank you.
You guys got her
a EverTogether plan.
It comes with
access to living in a nursing home.
So I brought her here.
I'm OK...
You're Dong.
You're Manli.
You're...
Xue Xiaozhou.
Xiaozhou.
Oh.
I remember.
Sun Jie should've told me.
If I hadn't bumped into
you here,
she might've forgotten me.
She knows your situation.
She didn't want Sun Jie to worry you.
But don't worry.
This neighborhood is excellent.
We're warmly received
and moved in smoothly.
Every morning,
helpers guide the patients
to recover their touch senses.
There's classes in the afternoon.
The helper and I both watch her closely.
She's on diet and medicine regularly.
Now she's much better.
You don't know.
Nursing homes these days are amazing.
I've sold
many health care products,
but I lost touch
with the latest health care values.
This isn't your fault.
Chinese always want their children
for help.
These values
are essentially good.
But time has changed.
Our life routines
changed.
The elders' needs changed.
That's why there's nursing homes
to solve your problem.
Manli.
Ms. Zhou.
Here.
You've been knitting since you moved in.
They're for her?
Yes.
Put them on
when it's cold.
You remember.
You give a pair to me every year.
Pretty. I love them.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Isn't it nice here?
Your dad should take a look
to see if he likes it here.
It's indeed nice.
I'll talk to Dad.
When he moves in, where do you live?
Me?
Anywhere's OK.
When you go to TSI,
I'll apply for a dorm for you.
You can do that?
Yes.
Dad.
I've
met some troubles.
Guess you've known.
Next,
I want
you to live in a nurse home.
If you agree,
shake it.
Dad.
Nursing homes nowadays are nice.
I just got back.
They're different from
those from before.
In there,
you'll recover better
guided by professionals.
OK?
It's not I want to leave you alone.
You...
I see...
You're on my side no matter what.
Right?
I know.
Don't worry.
Dad.
If you feel bad there,
I'll get you home right away.
Mr. Hu.
I'll also help.
Mr. Zhao?
We have a vacant room
in this apartment, right?
Storage, you say.
Can I use it too?
I'll pay extra 200.
No problem.
I'll handle the stuff inside.
It's locked.
OK.
I'll come to you for keys.
OK?
Sure...
OK...
Thanks...
Thanks.
OK.
♪Wave once more then release♪
♪One last wave to false peace♪
♪Why force love river's lease♪
♪Each step chills what we know♪
♪Is the end just hollow woe♪
♪Rush to dodge life's hollow grind♪
♪Vowed I'd never lag behind♪
♪My joy soared for eyes to find♪
♪Yet dust clings where I stood♪
♪Time's stream bears what's misread♪
♪What if we can't catch its tide♪
♪Glance back where shadows hide♪
♪Fearless though sorrows glide♪
♪No soul is born to love by design♪
♪Strange doubts haunt paths we trace♪
♪Follow fate's faint embrace♪
♪No dream's born to save our race♪
♪Scars mark where light once glowed♪
♪Pain's whispers cascade♪
[Insurance Star]
Didn't I tell you to wait?
You've got all here?
I mailed some to Ning's
and sold some in flea market.
I told you.
Don't mind me.
Just text me the address.
I'm your leader now.
I want to know how it feels
to care for a subordinate.
Do sound like a leader, Director Xue?
Let me.
I'm a man.
I have more strength.
Can I boss my leader around?
A man at your age is still growing.
Don't hurt yourself.
Manli.
Still growing?
Can I be taller?
In your dreams.
Where's the dorm?
You'll know.
Mysterious.
Get in.
Careful.
It's OK.
Here.
Come on.
Look.
Nice?
Someone lives here.
It's a dorm.
They just moved out I guess.
It's smelly.
Open the windows.
Guess they didn't have good hygiene.
Two rooms.
Dingding lives here.
I'll take this.
Dingding lives here too?
Of course.
I wanted to rent a one-room apartment.
A bunk bed.
It'll be hard, I know.
I brought him to visit my dad.
I could see
he wanted to live with me.
I told him.
I'd get him after this.
I need a bunk bed here.
What about this bed here?
What did you say?
I said...
What?
Isn't it
smelly?
I'll open the windows.
Why is Baodan here?
Hold on.
You rented this house.
Yes.
Why lie?
I was afraid you'd turn me down.
Of course I would.
It doesn't matter.
You said
in old days,
you could be my mom.
But it's present days now.
What's the difference?
No need to panic if you're innocent.
You make it sound easy.
So do you have
a thing for me now?
Yes.
I fancy you, OK?
A lot.
I might eat you
up someday.
Oh, you speak
what's on your mind.
Only listen to nice words.
Don't worry.
You're the last man
I want in this world.
Hey, I'm helping you.
Don't be so harsh.
OK, I'm sorry.
You know me.
I don't like pity.
It's not pity.
Never.
There's two rooms.
It'll be a waste on my own.
I wanted a roommate.
But then,
I was like,
"Why don't I
come to you?"
Win-win.
Look.
One-room house would
cost 4,000.
We can split the bills here.
2,500 each.
Cheap.
Dingding can live here too.
When you get busy,
I can look after him,
and tutor him.
Win-...
triple-win.
One two three, yes.
We've lived together before.
Go get Dingding.
We're together again.
How nice.
Boss, you should know
the poor fears being looked down upon.
I never look down upon you.
In that case,
it'll be rude to decline.
Right?
OK.
Send me the rental agreement.
I won't take your advantage.
Don't decline.
OK, I won't.
I take the smaller one.
You have the main.
No.
I have the smaller one.
The bunk bed.
You can't put it in here.
Where will Dingding sleep?
I want the smaller one.
Good for sleep.
You rented here.
I take the main room?
Let's keep it that way, OK?
You're the boss.
You have to listen.
OK.
I'll pay more of the rent, OK?
OK, whatever you say.
Thank you.
It's
settled then.
Happy living together, again.
♪If I close both eyes tonight♪
♪Back to that wishing summer night♪
♪Wind brushes your shaking frame♪
♪That world feels close just the same♪
♪If I dare to face the dawn♪
♪Do you know this face you'd drawn♪
♪Gray spirals looped in endless chase♪
♪Tracing tears not words they trace♪
♪How many times must this repeat♪
♪Sighs pull my gaze to retreat♪
♪Sleepless nights, risks untold♪
♪None of it for my own soul♪
♪Winds blew, rains poured♪
♪Umbrellas broke, we soared♪
♪Sky fell, ground shook♪
♪Through dusk till dawn I stood♪
♪Cars passed, dreams drowned♪
♪Every stop's chain unbound♪
♪Moon watched, stars blazed♪
♪Lamps died, connections phased♪
♪Held hands, laughed then cried♪
♪Hearts froze, parts died inside♪
♪Tried hard, spoke true♪
♪Now I'm someone I never knew♪
♪Love came, hate stayed♪
♪I arrived, you frayed♪
♪Voice cracked, tears burned♪
♪Life lost, lessons earned♪
♪Grew up, let go♪
♪Why cling to old sorrow♪
♪How many loops replay♪
♪Sighs steal my gaze away♪
♪Lost nights, bold bets♪
♪Nothing for my regrets♪
♪Winds raged, storms crashed♪
♪Dawns broke, I held fast♪
♪Cars fled, dreams fled♪
♪Every route left dead♪
♪Love left, hate stayed♪
♪Voice gone, tears paid♪
♪Grew strong, moved on♪
♪Why dwell when it's gone♪