♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪Who's obsessed with money♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I just wanna tell you♪
♪Long lashes big bright eyes♪
♪Always rockin' shades♪
♪Tiny steps click-clack beat♪
♪Graceful fierce elite♪
♪Your loyal sidekick here♪
♪Ready to cheer♪
♪Copy your swagger every day♪
♪Ah-ha Ah-ha♪
♪I see you rush♪
♪Through crowds on streets each dawn♪
♪Bump into you texting alone♪
♪Midnight café empties out♪
♪Fatigue fights the void♪
♪Victory's sweet shout♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Let's pause♪
♪Breathe deep feel the air♪
♪Sense the vibes we share♪
♪Wallet's magic sparks the night♪
♪Whirlwind takes flight♪
♪Love's a comet streaking high♪
♪Vanishing in sky♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Love you first♪
♪Tomorrow's world reborn♪
♪Slip into new threads♪
♪Leave blissful steps ahead♪
♪I'll wait♪
♪Where we first met♪
♪Who craves that cash♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm so dazzled♪
♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm all about that Manli♪
[A Better Life]
[Episode 19]
Another gift?
Sit.
Haven't seen you for a while.
You're glowing.
Really?
Not making fun of me?
No.
I tell
only truth.
On any health care products?
No.
You look so good.
Tell me
so I get some for my dad too.
No... I'm not.
I just feel happy.
Linjiang
has a new girlfriend.
Really?
He sounds like he's
going to marry her.
If he really does,
when
I go
meet his mom,
I can bring her good news.
This is nice.
Don't talk about death.
I still expect orders from you.
I knew.
You must want my help.
Say it.
Since we're friends,
I'll go
straight to the point.
Our company is doing a campaign,
decreasing premiums
on a few plans.
If you have anyone you know who
wants a plan,
recommend me.
You see?
You talked about expecting
my orders.
Now you've got
discounts,
benefits.
You won't consider me?
Tell me what else you want.
Mr. Huang.
Mr. Ding.
What should I do about you?
This is something for you.
Not much.
Please take it.
No, what is this?
Do take it.
Ms. Qiu, look.
[Fund-raising]
You sure
Prof. Ding's relatives
post this?
Mr. Ding's disciple Xue reposted.
Though the photos are blurry,
I can make out them.
It's them.
So I underestimated Manli.
You think she did this?
Prof. Ding thinks highly of himself.
How would he post to raise funds?
Listen to this.
"He wanted to turn to his relatives,
but he's a scholar
living a hard life.
Hopeless
and penniless,
he asks you for help."
He'd rather die
than say something like that.
Should we intervene?
It's about Mr. Ding's image.
It's all a mess.
Don't.
We don't want mistakes.
Let him fight Manli.
No matter the result,
it won't be bad for us.
When everything settles,
we'll show up.
[Fund-raising]
Mr. Ding.
You've been so good to us.
Now something happened to your family.
So we pooled some
funds.
It's not much, but...
Hey.
What are you guys doing?
Nothing happened.
Don't buy this stuff.
It's smearing my name.
We saw
Ms. Hu reposted it.
You don't have to keep it from us.
Enough.
Take your money away.
I don't need your pity.
We're not pitying you.
Simply want to help.
Stop.
Dad.
What the hell did you do?
Now my girlfriend
and her parents
all know you run out of money
to pay for your medical bills.
And that you can't throw a wedding.
So,
did
did she
say anything?
Nothing.
She wanted a breakup.
Now all her family know
she married a poor guy
who begs for hospital fees.
Nonsense.
Don't worry.
I will raise the money
to throw a wedding.
Listen...
Go raise it then.
What to do?
He finally has a girlfriend.
If they
break up,
our bride-dowry
will be gone.
Get Zhiyuan.
Call him.
His wife did this.
He'll take care.
Yes.
I...
Hello?
Zhiyuan.
Come over, emergency.
Hurry up.
Emergency.
Apart from
the smart mode,
it has a RR layout.
A strong engine.
Young men like
this RR layout.
Will you try?
It makes the driver
feel in control
of speed and driving.
Come over.
You should come back later.
Get me anytime.
Why are we here?
Take a look.
This is
the bonus car for your best broker.
You couldn't buy a good model like this
with such a low price before.
Will you look after your mental state?
You think those accident and medical plans
from that market vendor
can make us the first?
Buckle up.
Listen.
Ai Zhonghua will separate,
through insurance,
his family assets from the firm's.
His price is 10 million.
A call for bids soon.
If we make this happen,
we'll be top one.
This car will be mine.
Do you trust us?
Don't touch me.
So,
who else will bid?
Brokers, lawyers,
and private bankers.
Why do you think
we'll win?
Intuition.
Really?
I'm lucky lately.
And we make a good team now.
Our career is taking off.
You can't
shake off your good luck.
This time,
we'll strive forward.
[Ding]
You won't take it?
Bad luck.
I don't want that.
I must
have this cutie.
Whoever stops me
dies.
Ruthless women
are horrible.
So what to do next?
Next,
take a picture of me.
Come on.
Hand forward.
Yes.
Your chin...
Smile.
Nice.
OK?
Zhiyuan.
What did you do exactly?
You.
When they come back,
tell them to remove
that stuff from online.
Give our 200,000 back.
Fugui.
Zhiyuan.
You can't be fooled.
He's seeking justice for you.
You're too generous
to leave this house
empty-handed.
She's here.
Why are you here?
See?
The young guy I told you about.
They're always together.
Can't bear to watch.
Let me introduce.
Xue Xiaozhou, my colleague.
You'll regret if you keep
spouting nonsense.
Prof. Ding.
Please ask them to leave with
their belonging.
Remove that thing from online.
OK.
It'll be depended on what you do.
Uncle...
Let's go.
We can't.
No.
You mom said
she has to give us the money.
Would you stop
messing around now?
What about the money?
Let's go now.
I won't.
I don't leave.
Fugui.
I beg you.
Let's leave.
You're useless.
A woman bullies you like this.
You're making our entire family ashamed.
You won't go?
Fine.
I'll make you.
We can't go.
Leave.
Zhiyuan.
We should stay.
For money.
If you don't go,
forget 200,000,
I won't take even 20,000.
You.
Will
you leave?
Go.
Hurry.
Let's go.
Go.
Go...
Are we leaving?
Really?
Let's go.
Shameless.
Hold up.
Who did you call shameless?
Not you.
Apologize.
Don't push it.
I should say that to you.
This young man requested
the fund-raising online.
If you upset him,
he won't take it down.
Apologize.
Sorry.
I can't
hear you.
Sorry, young man.
I was wrong.
Who do they think they are?
Calm down.
Don't take it to heart.
Don't get
mad
at them.
What a scene.
[Cash Advance]
[Ding...]
I want to share with you today
The Turbulent Career.
Between 19th and 20th centuries,
many Western explorers
like missionaries and travelers,
visited Southwestern China,
bearing various purposes.
The sought and found.
In the perspective of human science,
they observed and recorded
local customs and people.
I hope you
make time to read this.
Cut.
Put the sea cucumber box.
Mr. Ding.
We have a teleprompter.
Just read along.
Put that box
nearer Mr. Ding.
Closer.
OK.
All departments.
Three, two, one,
action.
Mr. Ding.
Tiger sea cucumber,
for the worn-out
middle-aged.
Women thrive,
men...
rise.
Cut.
Mr. Ding.
One more time.
Emotions.
More emotions.
Stand by.
Three, two, one,
action.
Tiger sea cucumber,
for the worn-out
middle-aged.
Women thrive,
men rise.
Bravo.
Where are we headed?
Restaurant.
Fugui.
I've transferred the money to you.
Did you receive?
Yes.
I called
my in-laws to tell them the good news.
Look at Zhiyuan.
He gets money with a few calls.
They want to cancel the wedding?
They'll regret.
That's right.
By the way.
I see your job is easy.
Any vacancy there?
I think
our son can talk too.
Why won't you help him?
Get him a job like yours.
Yes.
Look after him.
Remember.
We're family.
So fancy.
The lights.
Colorful.
Like we were in a movie.
Zhiyuan.
The painting
looks real.
The furnishings
are
fancy.
This
private room is nice.
Fugui.
Sit here.
No, I can't.
Seniors should
sit in the middle.
Listen to him.
Sit.
You sit there.
OK.
I'll take my seat here.
Come on.
Uncle Fugui.
Let's drink this.
This is good liquor.
Don't...
Just had a surgery.
No.
Right.
Then we'll have juice.
Juice is fine.
Uncle and Aunt.
I've always wanted to meet you.
I just couldn't make it.
I'm here to apologize.
Zhiyuan.
She's...
Introduce her.
Qiu Lisu.
My uncle and aunt.
Finally meet you.
Uncle and Aunt.
Just call me Lisu.
Sorry I've been on
business trips.
Couldn't see you in time.
It's OK.
Work is more important.
Finally meet you.
Come over.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Ding.
I was wrong.
What?
She's...
His family needed money.
Were the procedures necessary?
You were away.
I couldn't use your account.
I used the firm's account,
they were necessary.
The firm would be under investigation.
Enough.
You failed.
No excuse.
Get your compensation
and leave tomorrow.
Please give me another chance.
- Please…
- Stop!
Uncle and Aunt.
I was wrong.
It was all my fault.
Help me.
Mr. Ding, please.
Uncle, I...
Lisu.
She's young
and makes a mistake for once.
Why won't you forgive her?
She'll learn a lesson
after this.
Listen to Fugui.
Did you hear?
Thank them now.
And Mr. Ding.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Ding.
I'll leave you alone.
You go on.
I'll check up on the kitchen.
Serve our dishes.
OK.
Come on.
Dig in.
You're busy.
What would you like to drink?
Juice, OK?
OK...
I'll help you.
Can I drink wine?
Lisu, it's so kind of you.
I got so many.
How sweet of you.
You're welcome.
Come to me when you visit Shanghai.
OK?
OK.
Let me.
You're so nice.
What's the date?
Take it.
For what?
Wedding.
It's your second marriage.
We still have to
meet each other's family.
Let me know.
Take care.
Careful.
Bye...
Bye.
Take care.
Call me.
Zhiyuan.
You've been
living at school?
Yes.
Can I see?
This is
where I sleep.
It's not fancy.
But,
I have my books,
food, and clothes.
Enough.
You should
go.
I'll do some reading.
Zhiyuan.
About Uncle and Aunt.
It's really a misunderstanding.
I'll go read.
Tell me if you're still
upset.
I'm afraid you can't take it.
Tell me.
I'm here.
You set me up to write the preface
for Fendou.
You get close to me
just to use me.
Right?
People told me
what you were.
I didn't believe.
Now...
I don't know what I should do.
Never mind.
Enough talking.
Go.
What did they call me?
A vain
gold digger
who sells herself?
None of my business.
Don't worry.
I won't smear your name.
If I had cared
about my name,
I should've
married my first love from school
and got children.
I'd been devoured by life.
You wouldn't spare a glance when I
walked past you.
But no.
I wasn't willing.
I had this possibility
in my life.
I was not content.
When I met a successful man
who'd
help me grow immensely,
why couldn't I fight for him?
Sorry.
I'm not that man.
You're wrong.
Yes.
I realized in the beginning.
But I
still chose to stay,
because
I love you.
You see everything
crystal clear.
You know how
the world
goes in a deep way.
Being with you,
talking to you,
it always makes me
feel enlightened.
Runnian left three years ago.
I had admirers
better than you.
But in the end,
we got together,
because
I really like you.
You don't have to.
I'm merely a teacher.
I'm mean and arrogant.
I'm not that good.
Zhiyuan.
I know I failed
you.
But I really hope
you can understand.
Zhig is in big trouble.
I can shut down and leave.
But once I do,
the rumors will be true.
I'll show them
I, Qiu Lisu,
on a higher
better platform,
can still achieve something.
I want them all to know
I have talent.
I don't solely rely on men.
You feel me?
I know
your firm's in trouble.
I didn't say I wouldn't help.
But I have principles.
I know.
That's one of the reasons I love you so.
I'm also glad
our child
has a father like you.
Our child?
Zhiyuan.
I'm pregnant.
You're going to be a dad.
Let's go home.
OK?
Tiger sea cucumber.
Women thrive.
Men...
rise.
Look at his face.
As if he had a gun against his head.
Look at you.
Making fun of him.
You're totally over him.
Well.
When we first broke up,
I hated the couple.
Then, I realized,
without that woman,
for some other reason,
we might've ended up in this state too.
What do you mean?
We'd been married for a decade.
You have to respect me for that.
But I haven't gained any good out of it.
Zhiyuan is a fool.
You're right.
But maybe I was wrong too.
Self-reflecting now?
This is not you.
Really.
You know.
I speak harshly
but act mildly.
I'll suffer losses
for sure.
So you want be
a lady from now on?
I won't.
I can't change.
I just decide I'll be nice
only to those who appreciate me.
It's not that I'm not enough.
Zhiyuan doesn't deserve me.
It's getting late.
I'll see a client.
Manli.
Wait.
It's about my family.
I want an education annuity
plan for Jun.
Education annuity for Jun?
Didn't you buy one two years ago?
I want more.
Ning.
Would you listen to yourself?
What do you mean?
I know you want to help,
I appreciate it.
But you know me.
I don't like pity.
No, don't take it the wrong way.
This is for myself.
You buy the same thing twice?
You think you're too rich?
What?
Something's up?
I have my medical reports.
How are they?
They don't
look good.
How so?
I can't tell you shortly.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
Get treated then.
You can even do that abroad.
Didn't you buy that high-end package?
Including that
some center's service.
One of my clients was in late stage
of lung cancer,
and he went to that center.
They used a drug in clinical trial.
His cancer cells decreased in months.
It worked.
2 million's medical fees.
All covered by his insurance plan.
Will yours be worse than lung cancer?
I don't buy it.
My disease
is incurable.
You haven't even get treated.
You...
I won't let you die.
What is it?
You're scaring me.
ALS.
How's my mom?
Somehow,
she had a lung infection,
causing multi-organ failure.
What's happening?
It hasn't been a day since
her infection, I'm afraid...
No, do something.
Calm down.
She's out.
Ms. Duan.
How's my mom?
How's she?
Xiaozhou.
My condolences.
[Wu Ya]
Don't worry.
I have clients in pharmacy.
I'll ask around.
Manli.
Stop wasting your time.
You can't cure me.
Don't give up.
Technology is developing.
Everything is possible.
Think positive.
I do.
I want to arrange
everything
while I can still talk and walk.
No regrets then.
Manli.
You'll help me, right?
Can't believe you said that.
Anytime you need me,
just call.
I'll show up.
My parents died early,
I don't have close relatives.
I just miss Jun.
Though
he forgets about me.
No.
Teenage boys are all rebellious.
Don't take it to heart.
He'll grow up.
About insurance...
What's your plan?
Doc said I have two years.
Jun won't be an adult even then.
No matter it's money or house,
they'll go to my ex.
So
I want to sell my house.
Apart from my loan,
there's about 1.5 million left.
I'll be honest with you.
I didn't want you to know
so I
went to other brokers.
They said they couldn't
make it happen.
No.
You're the policy holder.
If you die before Jun turns 18,
the policy holder will be changed
to Jun's guardian,
that is, your ex.
If he becomes the policy holder,
he'll decide what to
do with the plan.
Exactly.
That's what they all told me.
Manli.
Is there another way?
Don't worry.
Give me some time.
[Wu Ya]
Hello?
Ya.
Manli.
I've got all the paperwork.
I'll go back to work.
I'll leave him to you.
OK, I got this.
Talk to him.
OK.
Let's go home.
Xiaozhou.
My condolences.
It's hard for your mom
to hold on till this day.
Talk to me if you feel bad.
You'll feel better.
Cry if you want.
You can't keep your emotions within.
I'm useless.
How can you say that?
It was not your fault she was in a coma.
You're a good boy.
You gave up studies for her,
supported her.
You've done very well.
Don't blame yourself.
She could recover
if I had made money.
She could've had a surgery sooner
so she wouldn't die.
You're not thinking clearly.
Go to sleep.
Lucky that Ya left me.
Or
I'd drag her down like I did
to my mom.
I'm useless.
Don't say that.
I asked you to save my career.
You pitied me.
Without me,
you could do better.
Yes I said I pitied on you.
But that was to gain more commission.
I thought carefully
before coming to you.
I'm experienced
but lacking in knowledge.
You're a law graduate
and worked in a claim department.
You can do what I can't.
Don't try to comfort me.
I'm not that nice, OK?
I just have this order I can't secure.
I need your help.
I didn't want to
bring it up now.
You made me.
Even you can't?
How am I supposed to?
Manli.
Any progress on my plan?
And I remember.
You've got me a critical illness plan.
If I die,
there'll be a large compensation.
Thought it's for Jun,
he's still a minor.
Will
the money fall into the hands of my ex?
Ning.
You're being pessimistic, talking about
death all the time.
Two years is what the doc estimated.
About my insurance plan,
you have to help.
Rest assured.
I've figured it out, you know?
Really?
Yeah.
I'll have Xiaozhou talk to you.
OK.
♪If I close both eyes tonight♪
♪Back to that wishing summer night♪
♪Wind brushes your shaking frame♪
♪That world feels close just the same♪
♪If I dare to face the dawn♪
♪Do you know this face you'd drawn♪
♪Gray spirals looped in endless chase♪
♪Tracing tears not words they trace♪
♪How many times must this repeat♪
♪Sighs pull my gaze to retreat♪
♪Sleepless nights, risks untold♪
♪None of it for my own soul♪
♪Winds blew, rains poured♪
♪Umbrellas broke, we soared♪
♪Sky fell, ground shook♪
♪Through dusk till dawn I stood♪
♪Cars passed, dreams drowned♪
♪Every stop's chain unbound♪
♪Moon watched, stars blazed♪
♪Lamps died, connections phased♪
♪Held hands, laughed then cried♪
♪Hearts froze, parts died inside♪
♪Tried hard, spoke true♪
♪Now I'm someone I never knew♪
♪Love came, hate stayed♪
♪I arrived, you frayed♪
♪Voice cracked, tears burned♪
♪Life lost, lessons earned♪
♪Grew up, let go♪
♪Why cling to old sorrow♪
♪How many loops replay♪
♪Sighs steal my gaze away♪
♪Lost nights, bold bets♪
♪Nothing for my regrets♪
♪Winds raged, storms crashed♪
♪Dawns broke, I held fast♪
♪Cars fled, dreams fled♪
♪Every route left dead♪
♪Love left, hate stayed♪
♪Voice gone, tears paid♪
♪Grew strong, moved on♪
♪Why dwell when it's gone♪