♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪Who's obsessed with money♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I just wanna tell you♪
♪Long lashes big bright eyes♪
♪Always rockin' shades♪
♪Tiny steps click-clack beat♪
♪Graceful fierce elite♪
♪Your loyal sidekick here♪
♪Ready to cheer♪
♪Copy your swagger every day♪
♪Ah-ha Ah-ha♪
♪I see you rush♪
♪Through crowds on streets each dawn♪
♪Bump into you texting alone♪
♪Midnight café empties out♪
♪Fatigue fights the void♪
♪Victory's sweet shout♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Let's pause♪
♪Breathe deep feel the air♪
♪Sense the vibes we share♪
♪Wallet's magic sparks the night♪
♪Whirlwind takes flight♪
♪Love's a comet streaking high♪
♪Vanishing in sky♪
♪Hey Honey♪
♪Love you first♪
♪Tomorrow's world reborn♪
♪Slip into new threads♪
♪Leave blissful steps ahead♪
♪I'll wait♪
♪Where we first met♪
♪Who craves that money♪
♪Hey Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm so dazzled♪
♪Hu Manli, Manli♪
♪I'm all about that Manli♪
A Better Life
Episode 32
You and Mom worked
yourselves to the bone to make money.
Before long,
we moved into a bigger house,
had a car,
a helper, and a nanny,
but
Mom was gone.
Keke,
why do you think
your mom worked so hard?
She did it just for you.
I don't need it!
I don't need my mom to get stomach cancer
from drinking and socializing!
I don't need her to be sick
and put off going to the doctor.
I don't need her that when the cancer was found,
it was already late-stage and spread.
I want to go back to when I was little,
when the whole family squeezed
into one bed at night.
Mom would be doing needlework,
you were keeping the accounts,
and I was lying on the bed doing homework.
That was what home felt like for me.
I know we can never go back to that,
and that’s why
I wanted to open this little shop.
I just want to fill
that missing piece in my heart, in my own way.
Yuki, don't be sad.
I'd like to say a few words for your father.
As a child,
there are a lot of things you just can’t understand,
you know?
The things your dad worries about
might not make sense to you right now.,
but no matter what,
his intentions were good.
He did it all because he loves you,
okay?
Dad,
if you do care about me,
then you must respect how I want to live my life.
I really want to respect the life you want,
but do you even know what kind of life
that is?
That’s a fairy tale!
Does that exist in real life?
Well, Disney does,
but only if you pay for a ticket.
What life is this?
Dealing
with landlords like that every day?
Is that life for you?
I’ve worked hard my whole life,
and now my daughter wants
to run a grocery shop?
After everything, we’ve come full circle.
What’s the point of all my struggle then?
There's no point!
This is your own problem.
I live to make my life
more meaningful!
Keke,
can your small shop
even earn money?
Is it meaningful when you're not
making money and the landlord
bothers you daily?
Li Yuke,
you don't know what it means to be poor!
Stop being so dramatic with me!
Don't worry.
I won't spend any more of your money.
Even if I have to deliver food,
deliver packages,
or do e-hailing,
I’ll still live the life I want!
I can't communicate with you!
Mr. Li!
Mr. Li.
Fine.
Let’s say you manage to do e-hailing
and deliver food.
At the end of the day,
you’re covered in sweat, exhausted n your bed.
Where’s your freedom?
What about your poems and dreams?
At that point, the struggles
that you faced
will be pointless!
Mr. Li.
Hey, Mr. Li!
Mr. Li!
Calm down.
Sit down. Your father was just anxious.
He does love you. He'll think it through.
I'm sorry.
I still screwed this one up.
So can you sleep at night?
I can't.
The thought of not getting the job done
will keeps me awake at night.
It's so hard.
Then I'll support you.
Dummy,
At my age, I can still work
as a maternity nanny.
What can you do?
Well, food delivery.
Food delivery?
E-hailing,
packge delivery,
and food delivery
are called the Ironman Triathlon.
With someone like you
who won’t sleep at night
and can’t get up in the morning,
I wonder who’ll supporting who.
Then you take care of me.
That’s called mooching off an elder.
I don’t care. I’m sticking with you.
Looks like no matter how hard I try,
I can’t get rid of you.
Mr. Li,
about the trust...
The more Keke acts up,
the more I have to think about her future!
This kid...
I understand.
Then I'll meet up
with a couple lawyers of other firms.
Mr. Li,
Coco is your daughter after all.
Please don’t take it too hard on her.
Today’s incident reminds me
of something from over ten years ago.
I went to the west for a real estate deal,
but the deal fell through,
and they kidnapped me.
They threw me in a pigsty
and fed me pig food for days,
threatening to kill me
if I didn’t sign the deal.
It’s a society of law.
You should've called the cops.
What for?
Back then, people were ruthless.
It was Keke’s mother
who single-handedly barged in
and saved me with just her words.
Your wife was a true heroine.
This story could be made into a movie.
Today, I saw her shadow
in Hu Manli.
In the end,
I’m still thinking about my late wife.
If only she were alive,
she could help me with some ideas.
Lu Manli.
I thought about it.
I don’t want to give up
on the Li Fendou deal.
But I offended them today.
You did it for his own good.
Once he cools down,
he’ll understand.
As long as the deal isn’t finalized,
there’s still hope for us.
Next,
I’ll keep researching
the Li family’s background
and see if I can find another breakthrough.
As for you, find opportunities
to have them attend
our company’s
VIP events.
What kind of events?
I’ve sent them to your phone.
It’s just some financial seminars,
and family values workshops.
You just need to find the right moment
to invite them to these events.
First, it’ll help us maintain
our relationship with them.
Second, it’ll give them
a chance to improve
their father-daughter bond.
I really didn’t expect this.
At first, I encouraged you to become a leader
because you seemed lacking in confidence.
But now,
you’ve progressed so quickly,
you’re even
assigning tasks to me
like a real professional.
When you praise a superior
or flatter them,
make sure you think carefully.
You were even mocking me at first.
Watch your wording.
Sorry,
slip of the tongue.
It is too hot?
My retirement pay
went up.
Your retirement pay went up?
How much did the government raise it this year?
It raised
for 120 bucks.
That's a lot!
Hu Degong,
looks like you’ll be supporting me!
I'll support you.
Let Dad support you.
You'll support me?
I'm telling you,
don't think about anything else right now.
Focus on your physiotherapy,
okay?
Don't cut slack.
Okay.
Who is it?
Wait for me.
Take the receipt.
Who paid for my dad’s expenses
for another year again?
His name
is Ding Zhiyuan.
You're here.
Are you busy?
I'm going to Huangshan
for a closed-door symposium.
Any thing?
The nursing home told me
you paid
for my dad's nursing home fees for a year.
It's nothing.
It's just a token of appreciation
for the kids' grandpa.
It's inappropriate.
It's not.
I've already paid it.
Just leave it.
Let me put it this way.
If we were divorced
and you were still single,
maybe I could accept it.
But right now, it’s inappropriate.
As for the refund,
it’s a bit tricky now
since they've already processed the payment.
I’ll try to talk to them again.
Manli,
I want to do this.
Please, just leave it.
I appreciate the gesture,
and thank you on behalf of my dad too.
No.
I don’t need your thanks,
or anyone’s.
I’m doing this
because he’s the kids' grandfather,
your father.
I’m doing this
because
I regret it.
I'll leave you to it.
I'm leaving.
Manli.
Don't go, I...
I've got something to tell you.
Manli,
I'm sorry.
I know my mistake.
I really do.
But I also know
that nothing
I say now will help.
I’ve already
caused you and the kids
irreparable harm.
But I’m begging you,
give me a chance to make it up to you.
I used to mock the way
you handled problems with money.
I even called you materialistic.
But now,
I’m not even worthy of calling myself that.
I waited until your most difficult time
and tried to use a bit of money
to ease my guilt.
I’m like someone taking advantage
of your pain,
but it’s the only thing I can do.
Manli,
I'm begging you,
please accept my repentance.
Are you just repenting now?
What else can I hope for
besides repentance?
I’m not in a position to ask
for your forgiveness,
let alone a second chance.
I heard everything you said.
But what do you want me to do?
Isn’t this how it started with her too?
Mutual feelings,
convincing yourself it didn’t count,
that emotional attraction
isn’t cheating?
Ding,
I want to know,
what do women mean to you?
What do you take us for?
Clothes?
Wear them when you like,
take off when you don’t?
You need to remember,
you’re a husband,
and a father of two.
You have responsibilities on your shoulders.
I accept your apology,
but I can’t accept anything else.
I have my boundaries.
If you have feelings, keep them
to yourself.
If the nursing home money can’t be refunded,
I’ll write you an IOU and pay you back
as soon as possible.
Manli.
Within the constraints of endless joy,
I felt the freedom to embrace.
of embrace.
You kept pouring new wine
into my clay jar,
each with a different color,
a different fragrance.
You're back so late. Where did you go?
I had dinner with Zhong Ning.
I just saw Zhong Ning's social media post.
She went out to eat with her son.
Are you hiding something from me?
Where exactly did you go?
What do you think
he meant by that?
If he regrets it
and wants to remarry you,
what will you do?
Are you crazy?
No, don't avoid the question.
Answer me.
It's impossible.
What do you mean?
How could he remarry you?
Or you won't accept it?
A kid like you won't know.
What do you mean I won't?
I'm trying to help you understand
so you don't make a mistake.
I just have mixed feelings.
I’ve done a lot
for this man in the past.
I guess I was a good woman.
But tell me,
which man would love a woman just because
she’s good to him?
Not a single man
has ever been crazy about me,
and not one
has given me passionate love.
I feel like I’ve failed
as a woman.
Wait, do you really think Ding Zhiyuan
can give you some kind of grand,
passionate love now?
No,
this has nothing to do with him.
It’s just that today,
for once, my identity as a woman
was acknowledged.
Feeling out of place too, right?
Thinking that words like romance, love
don’t seem to fit me.
I used to think the same.
I told myself
those things can’t make money
or get results,
so what’s the point?
But today I realized
it’s not that I don't want them,
it’s that I can’t.
So I convinced myself that I don't want
to have them.
But what woman
doesn't want a romantic love?
Then,
let say,
if someone said they could give you
a romantic relationship right now,
would you be tempted?
So what if I do?
If you do,
start a new romance
with this new person.
Start again?
Ii'm old now.
I just want to live my life in peace.
He went to the nursing home
to pay the bill for Hu Manli's father?
Yes.
I went there myself and checked.
Hu Manli’s father is indeed
in that nursing home.
I asked a friend,
and it’s true.
Wait for me here.
Okay.
Who is it?
Zhiyuan.
Why are you here?
Didn’t I tell you
I’m leaving early tomorrow,
so I won’t be home tonight.
I was at home and thought of something
I wanted to discuss with you.
Can’t it wait
till I get back?
I went to a postpartum care center today.
After I give birth, I’d like to stay there.
If you want to go,
you can just book it.
I’m a high-risk pregnancy because of my age,
so I'd stay for two months.
But the place
is a bit expensive.
Understandable.
Your health comes first.
Lately
I’ve been a bit tight on cash,
and I was thinking...
How much short?
200 thousand.
Can you help me?
Your 200 thousand...
I put all my money
into investments.
Really?
What kind of investments?
Show me the account.
Wait,
what do you mean by that?
You don’t trust me?
Fine, fine.
If you want to go to the postpartum center,
we’ll go.
I’ll figure something out
about the money.
Did you really invest the money,
or did you give it to others?
Can you stop being so passive-aggressive
and suspicious all the time?
Okay, fine.
I’ll tell you the truth.
A friend of mine
needed the money urgently,
so I lent it all to him.
Who?
You don't know him.
Well, I'll know them once you say the name.
Does it have to be this way?
Fine.
I’ll call him right now
and let you see for yourself, okay?
But think it through,
if I make this call,
the trust between us
will be gone
Okay.
I believe you.
You should
stop overthinking everything.
Focus on your pregnancy.
Why is Mr. Jin
looking for me?
Ms. Hu,
you'll find out when you meet Mr. Jin.
Here, have some tea.
Thanks, Mr. Jin.
ast time on the forum,
you really pissed off Professor Zeng,
but I didn’t interrupt you.
Do you know why?
Why?
Professor Zeng’s research is very theoretical
and high-level,
but in practice,
it really needs
people like you, the sales reps,
to implement it.
o honestly, his kind of research
doesn’t hold much value.
Thank you for your recognition.
Drink the tea.
Sure.
Take a look at this.
The company just set up a new
eldercare services department
to handle market promotions
and outreach activities.
Annuities,
priority admission to nursing homes?
These kinds of insurance products
have been around for years.
My dad is already living
in the Tianyang Nursing Home.
Why create
a whole new department just to promote this?
Shanghai has already entered
a stage of deep aging.
Seniors over 60 now make up
nearly 40% of the population.
So we plan to go all in
on the silver economy
and shift traditional ideas about eldercare.
Interested?
Me?
Thank you for thinking of me,
Mr. Jin,
but
this is a bit sudden.
No rush to decide.
Take your time.
But let me be upfront.
This is an internal position.
If you accept it,
I hope that
you'll fully commit
and give up
selling insurance for good.
Give up selling insurance?
I don’t think I can do that just yet.
To be honest,
I’ve got elderly parents and kids to support.
My responsibilities are heavy.
The income from selling insurance
is still really important to me.
Understood.
Once you're on board, I can talk to HR
and help you apply
for a better salary package.
I’m sorry, Mr. Jin.
How should I put it...
A lot has changed
in my personal life
recently,
It has just started settling down.
Emotionally,
I’d really love to work with you,
but now,
I just don’t have the energy or strength
to start something new.
I get it.
I really get it.
If you ever run
into any difficulties in life,
you’re welcome to come to me.
Thanks, Mr. Jin.
Where are you?
I've got a new idea
for Li Fendou's case.
Manli!
Chunlu.
Thank you about last time.
Manli,
have you forgiven me now?
Let's have coffee sometime
when we're free.
Sure!
That’s why I think
he doesn’t even know
what he really wants.
Sure,
but Li Fendou isn’t like an ordinary parent.
I’m worried you two might fall out completely.
And how is that any different now?
I just spoke with Secretary Yan,
he said Li Fendou’s free
and is willing to give us half an hour.
Let’s go.
Okay.
We reviewed all the assets under your name
and our suggestion
is to set up a holding company,
directly distributes benefits
to the beneficiaries.
The specific structure is shown
in the diagram.
Hold on,
how is this proposal
any different from the last one?
It’s the same.
Am I just wasting my time entertaining you?
Mr. Li,
would you say what you really want
is for your daughter
to give you
an heir?
Yeah.
Wrong.
What?
Did I pay you to teach me right from wrong?
Can you do this?
If you can't do it, get out!
Please calm down.
I think what you truly want is
for your daughter, Yuki,
to live a peaceful and safe life,
right?
Of course!
So all this talk about professional managers
or sons-in-law taking over
are all nonsense!
You’ve seen how things are with Keke.
She’s fine standing up to me,
but if I’m gone,
those wolves outside
will tear her apart!
Mr. Li, look.
It's been half a year since you first started
considering family succession.
You've seen all kinds
of family office companies
in the market,
yet none of them have satisfied you.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because they’re not capable,
of course!
If you can’t do it,
I’ll get foreign companies.
The money’s in my hands!
I can find someone better!
Do you think Yuki is really that unreliable?
Without your protection,
she’ll end up in a miserable situation?
I think
you’re just feeling guilty.
You missed out on most of your daughter’s
growing-up years,
and now you want to make up for it
in an unreasonable way.
But I can assure you,
no family office in the market
can fulfill your demands.
If you can't do it, then get out!
Stop wasting my time here!
There's no point in more talks!
Stop spewing nonsense!
Please calm down.
I’m embarrassed to admit it,
but I only started learning about family trusts recently.
All the terms
about equity structures and clauses
are giving me a headache.
I feel just like you.
Why make things so complicated?
Isn’t it all just to sell a product?
Exactly!
Listen to her!
Keep going.
Mr. Li, please sit down.
Let’s talk.
A few days ago, a client came to me
with three million and asked
about insurance.
She wanted safety
and high returns.
After going in circles,
I realized her real demand
was to protect her money from
her gambling-addicted son-in-law.
Right now,
you’re just like her.
How am I like her?
Why do a family trust with just three million?
My scale is nothing like that!
You all want to give
your kids 100% security.
Sure,
your funds are ten times hers,
and you’ve got enough legal terms
for a family trust to fill several books.
But still, it won’t meet your needs.
Why?
Because no plan can match
a parent’s love for their child.
We realized it too late,
and in the end,
that client bought something else.
Xiaozhou was a bit rude earlier,
but he’s just anxious.
I hope you can understand.
Sorry, Mr. Li.
I was too impulsive
just now,
but I just wanted to clarify things with you.
Family trusts
are often called the hand that reaches out
from the grave.
You don’t need
to regret the past neglect
toward your daughter.
A good trust can ensure that,
even a hundred years from now,
and Yuki will always feel
her father’s love
and protection
in another way,
Mr. Li,
if you have time,
please listen.
Sit down.
Go ahead.
Alright, then. Mr. Li, let me continue.
This is the structure of the holding company,
so the trustor would be you,
Mr. Li Fendou.
Congratulation, Xiaozhou.
We did it.
We succeeded.
Xiaozhou.
Hu Manli,
thank you.
I...
I'm speechless.
If you don't know what to say,
then keep it for later.
There are many people here.
Let go.
No need to thank me.
Your persistence paid off.
I told you
that rich people like it when you're
straightforward.
Let's
find a place  to celebrate. My treat.
I want your handmade food.
You think I'm not tired enough?
Fine then.
My superior has already spoken,
I've got no choice.
Let’s go. I’ll show you something special.
Hou much?
That'll be 560 bucks.
Okay.
It's through.
Thank you. Come again.
Let's go.
Well well, business is good.
Mr. Li, what brings you here today?
Secretary Yen couldn't get you to come,
so I had to come here myself.
What is it?
I gave the big family trust deal
to your dear friend, Hu Manli.
I'm kind enough to you, right?
Now, you should show me some kindness.
So, how do you want it?
Come home for dinner tonight.
The car is waiting for you downstairs.
It's not ready yet? I'm hungry.
Almost.
It smells great.
Hu's mandarin fish is a success.
It's not burnt?
Anything else?
I'll take it.
Bowl and chopsticks.
Okay.
It's ready to eat.
I'm full.
I can't eat any more.
I told you, if you can’t eat it,
don’t force yourself,
but you insisted on finishing.
Did you make this yourself?
You’ve had a meal I cooked before!
Well, I never tried Hu's mandarin fish.
This fish is tasty, right?
Yes.
It looks simple,
but every step,
from the ingredients to the heat
is crucial.
I experimented a lot
before I perfected it.
I figured out
when it will be crispy outside, tender inside,
and when to pour the sauce
for the best flavor.
Ding used to love it the most.
Okay,
forget about him.
I'll make some barley tea to help
with digestion, okay?
No, don't move!
Just sit down.
Let me
get something.
A present for you.
For me?
What is it?
Take a guess.
A bag?
Jewelry?
This is light.
Could it be a cheque or money?
You'r so materialistic.
Open it and take a look.
How domineering, boss.
Open it up.
What is this?
You want me
to work more overtime?
No! You don't have to do anything.
This annuity insurance is something
I made for you.
For me?
♪If I close both eyes tonight♪
♪Back to that wishing summer night♪
♪Wind brushes your shaking frame♪
♪That world feels close just the same♪
♪If I dare to face the dawn♪
♪Do you know this face you'd drawn♪
♪Gray spirals looped in endless chase♪
♪Tracing tears not words they trace♪
♪How many times must this repeat♪
♪Sighs pull my gaze to retreat♪
♪Sleepless nights, risks untold♪
♪None of it for my own soul♪
♪Winds blew, rains poured♪
♪Umbrellas broke, we soared♪
♪Sky fell, ground shook♪
♪Through dusk till dawn I stood♪
♪Cars passed, dreams drowned♪
♪Every stop's chain unbound♪
♪Moon watched, stars blazed♪
♪Lamps died, connections phased♪
♪Held hands, laughed then cried♪
♪Hearts froze, parts died inside♪
♪Tried hard, spoke true♪
♪Now I'm someone I never knew♪
♪Love came, hate stayed♪
♪I arrived, you frayed♪
♪Voice cracked, tears burned♪
♪Life lost, lessons earned♪
♪Grew up, let go♪
♪Why cling to old sorrow♪
♪How many loops replay♪
♪Sighs steal my gaze away♪
♪Lost nights, bold bets♪
♪Nothing for my regrets♪
♪Winds raged, storms crashed♪
♪Dawns broke, I held fast♪
♪Cars fled, dreams fled♪
♪Every route left dead♪
♪Love left, hate stayed♪
♪Voice gone, tears paid♪
♪Grew strong, moved on♪
♪Why dwell when it's gone♪