Sharks following the boat brings disaster.
According to the rules,
we must throw a body to ward off evil.
Since there is no dead body,
we have to choose one
from you piglets.
You are going to throw a living person
into the sea to feed the sharks, right?
Stop.
What year of the Republic is this?
You're still doing human sacrifices?
What do you know?
This is the will of Heaven.
If we don't throw one down to sacrifice to the Dragon King,
the whole ship will die.
Besides,
these piglets
have all signed a bill of sale.
If not them, should we throw you?
I...
We can't read.
So you screw us over like this?
Why? Shut up.
Rules are rules.
It's clearly written in the contract.
Do you expect the whole ship
to die with you?
Wait a minute.
You are treating human lives like dirt.
We are all Chinese.
How can you be so ignorant
to harm your own compatriots?
Get out of the way.
No.
If we don't throw them,
will you die for them?
Don't get in the way if you don't want to die.
Who says it has to be
a living sacrifice?
To stand up for others,
you need to have a solution.
A reckless fool like you,
who else should we throw?
Cut the crap.
Where did you come from
to cause trouble?
I have a way to avoid casualties
and drive away the sharks.
Will this
really work?
We won't know until we try.
They retreated! They retreated!
The sharks really retreated.
Great.
They retreated! They really retreated!
Excellent!
The Dragon King has accepted the sacrifice.
Great.
Finally, some luck.
Little girl,
you've got some skills.
You are much better than
that useless pretty boy.
Break it up.
Disperse.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I might have fed the sharks.
You're welcome.
Since I travel by sea often,
I naturally know more
about these things.
It looks to me
like it's your first time traveling.
I embarrassed myself, Miss.
This will calm your nerves.
Eating some sweets will make you feel better.
I'm off.
This is your first time delivering a living package,
and it's a child.
Be very careful.
My mom used to say when she was alive,
if you run into something unhappy,
just eat a piece of candy.
A sweet taste brings a good mood.
Have it.
Are you scared?
No, no.
This letter is...
This is from an older brother of mine.
He sent me this letter.
He is very talented in writing.
When I'm bored on the boat,
I would take it out to read.
It passes the time.
It's a pity that these past few years,
I haven't had the chance
to visit him in Quanzhou.
Wangshu.
You are Lin Wangshu?
Wangshu, it's me, Chen Jiadong.
I didn't expect that after 12 years,
you'd give me another piece of candy.
Jiadong.
You're Jiadong.
Yes.
I haven't seen you in so long.
Come, sit down.
Why are you standing?
Jiadong.
Why are you
on the ship to Malaya?
You never mentioned it
in your letters.
Mingshu wrote me a letter saying
he has news about my parents.
I set off as soon as I received the letter.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
My brother...
he...
went missing.
What?
How could he go missing?
Half a month ago,
he went to the northern suburbs to collect remittances,
and he never
came back.
How did this happen?
Was there anything unusual before he disappeared?
Well...
Yes.
A few days before he disappeared,
I saw him keeping on
repeatedly
reading an old newspaper.
An old newspaper?
It was a 12-year-old
newspaper.
I think it was about
news of a Japanese tea factory.
Right.
There also seemed to be a wanted poster.
Where is that newspaper now?
Why can they write it,
but I can't?
No, my friend.
Didn't I tell you?
These coolie coins of yours
are not currently
circulating currency.
You have to wait for the date
when the courier collects the remittances to use them.
If you're in a hurry,
you can exchange them for cash
and come back.
Dragon silver, eagle dollars, or Straits dollars,
they're all fine.
But I can't wait!
I don't care.
I must send the remittance today.
I can't explain it to you.
Who is making trouble
in my Wansheng Remittance Bureau?
Wangshu is back.
Dad.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I was just explaining to him.
How was it?
Did everything go well?
It went smoothly, Dad.
Look
who I brought back.
Are you going to
send my letter or not?
I...
Brother.
My dad just
explained it very clearly.
This is Zhuzai currency,
not silver dollars.
It can't be mailed separately.
You have to wait for the specific day
for the courier to collect it
to mail it.
If you dare to make trouble again,
I won't be polite.
Foreigners bully us,
and your post office bullies us too.
Why won't you let me send my letter?
I really have urgent business.
Why can't you
understand plain words?
Wangshu, let me handle this.
Brother, please get up first.
Please sit.
Brother.
What do you want to write?
I can help you.
I...
My name is Li Laishun.
The night before yesterday,
I dreamed of my mother
standing by my bed.
She just looked at me without speaking,
and she didn't look too good.
Mainly because that day
was the day before the anniversary of my mother's death.
I've been feeling uneasy.
Dear Xiaocui and Ximei,
The day before yesterday,
late at night on June 20th,
I dreamed of my mother.
She stood there silently,
with no joy on her face,
which woke me up in fright.
I couldn't sleep for the rest of the night,
and felt uneasy all day.
The night I had the dream
was the eve of my mother's death anniversary.
I am sending six silver dollars today.
Four dollars are for household expenses,
and two dollars are for the memorial ceremony for my mother.
I beg you, sister,
to stand before mother's grave and tell her
that everything is fine with me in Malaya.
Please don't worry.
Your brother, Laishun.
Brother Jiadong's writing is indeed excellent.
Brother,
I've finished writing this Qiaopi for you.
But the money...
I only have these Zhuzai coins right now.
Wangshu,
you tell me what to do.
He wrote the Qiaopi.
He didn't take your money.
As for the letter,
you now have your own Qiaopi.
You just need to wait for the courier
to come and collect it,
and give him the exchanged silver dollars.
That's it.
Thank you.
Thanks.
It was my fault just now.
Thank you, miss,
sir,
and Boss Lin.
I was just too anxious.
All right.
We are all Chinese.
I understand how you feel.
Thank you.
Okay.
Fine.
Wangshu.
Who is this?
Dad,
he is Chen Jiadong.
The little boy my brother
sent back to Quanzhou 12 years ago.
Chen Jiadong.