What did you say?
Luo Wang, you bastard.
Jiadong can't die.
I won't let you hurt him.
You only have Chen Jiadong in your heart.
Don't you know
that I really like you too?
I want you to marry me.
Luo Wang.
You know that everything
Jiadong has done
is to fight the Japanese
and protect our compatriots.
And you?
You're harming him to help the Japanese.
The Japanese.
You just mentioned the Japanese to me,
didn't you?
The Japanese.
Do you understand the Japanese?
Do you know how cruel they are?
Have you seen
their methods of killing?
Do you know where
their offensive has reached?
You know nothing.
For the sake of Chen Jiadong,
do you want to let yourself
and your whole family
die with him?
Speak.
I don't care.
I just want you to let Jiadong go.
I know you look down on me.
Has it been easy for me to survive until today?
I barely managed to survive.
I'll make you
the police chief's wife.
I'll protect you.
Isn't that good?
I'll protect your brother,
your father,
and your whole family,
to keep them alive.
Isn't that good?
What about Jiadong?
Luo Wang,
I know you must have a way.
I beg you.
Don't you know
I can let Chen Jiadong go,
but I will die too?
But if Jiadong dies,
I won't live either.
Fine.
You only have Chen Jiadong in your heart.
Then go die with him.
Luo Wang!
Okay.
I promise you.
As long as you let Jiadong go,
I'll marry you right away.
Okay?
Luowang.
I'll go with you wherever you want to go.
We,
we can leave Malaya together.
We can start a new life.
Okay?
I'm begging you.
Luowang, I'm begging you.
Luowang, just one look.
Let me,
let me see with my own eyes
Jiadong leave the city.
Okay?
Okay.
Then tonight.
Tonight,
I'll wait for you at Gurney Drive.
Okay.
Thank you, Luowang.
Director.
If we release Chen Jiadong,
how do we explain it to President Yamada?
Don't tell Yamada.
Wangshu.
How did it go?
It's done.
He promised to bring Jiadong
to Guanzaijiao Alley tonight,
and release him in front of me.
As for Yamada,
we'll leave it to you, Shopkeeper Zhao.
Don't worry.
Watch how I completely fool
that Japanese devil.
Yes, sir.
Rest assured, General.
This time, I will definitely capture Chen Jiadong
and his accomplices all at once.
Very good.
Yamada,
afterwards I will report to the headquarters
and ask for a reward for you.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, General.
President,
Manager Zhao from Zhicheng Post Office
wants to see you.
Mr. Zhao.
Yes, sir.
Let him in.
Yes.
Have a seat.
Mr. Zhao,
what a rare guest.
What can I do for you?
Mr. Yamada.
I know Luo Wang,
and shutting down the Chinese Chamber of Commerce
was your idea.
Now the Chinese merchants are divided.
It's really
too difficult for us.
So,
I want to join you.
Well,
as the Chinese saying goes,
'a good tree is a good shelter'.
I've prepared a token of my loyalty for you.
A very useful piece of information.
This
really surprises me.
I wonder what special news
Mr. Zhao has brought.
It's about Chen Jiadong.
I know
that boy Chen Jiadong
is always against you.
You are going to execute him soon.
But I accidentally
heard that Luo Wang,
he...
why is he going to
release Chen Jiadong?
Impossible.
Chen Jiadong is locked up in prison.
Tomorrow at noon,
he will be publicly executed.
Right.
That's why I felt
it was
so strange when I heard the news.
Why would Luo Wang
release Chen Jiadong?
Mr. Yamada,
you might not know.
Luo Wang
has long had his eyes on
Lin Wangshu
from Wansheng Remittance.
He's always wanted to be with her.
But Lin Wangshu,
she likes Chen Jiadong.
You mean
Lin Wangshu asked Luo Wang to release him?
Mr. Yamada, you're so smart.
Impossible.
I still don't believe
Luo Wang would dare to do that.
Mr. Zhao.
I also doubt
the real purpose of
you bringing me this information.
Mr. Yamada,
I came to Malaya
to make money.
You have seen
what kind of person I am.
But Mr. Qin,
for the sake of Wansheng Remittance
and Chen Jiadong,
he almost put us in danger
time and time again.
Me and a few other business owners
have disliked him for a long time.
President Yamada.
I came to you
in the hope
that you will support me
in becoming the new president of the Chinese Chamber of Commerce.
Rest assured.
If I become the president,
I guarantee all Chinese merchants
will fully pledge their loyalty
to the Empire of Japan.
Understood.
So that's how it is.
Mr. Zhao,
your proposal is very good.
If I can verify
that what you say is true,
I will consider it.
Thank you, President Yamada.
Everything I said is true.
Okay.
Somebody.
President.
Contact Luo Wang at the police station for me.
Hurry.
Yes.