♪They say time will reveal a person's heart♪
♪In all lives, may the sea calm the tides♪
♪Blue silk drifting to one's hometown,
carrying greed, hatred, and ignorance♪
♪Going to the corners of the heavens
to seek a long-awaited reunion♪
♪To live or die together, that is but an act♪
♪Letting down our memories♪
♪Why should we rip out our heart
for a heartless person?♪
♪Treating each other with courtesy is
but a scene in my dream♪
♪We'll wake up eventually♪
♪As the autumn wind blows, the maple leaves fall,
pulling myself away♪
=Don't Forget My Love=
=Episode 4=
Send her to her residence in secret
when she wakes up tomorrow.
Yes, Your Highness.
It's better to avoid
a femme fatale like her.
Your Highness, I shall take my leave.
Your Highness,
your wound is...
I'm fine.
Your Highness!
The jade pendant His Majesty
has rewarded you is missing!
Why are you panicking?
I...
I gave it to someone else.
You gave it away?
You...
Who did you
give it to?
I gave it
to my future consort,
the crown princess.
What is this?
Tell me.
How did he escape from you?
Tell me. Why did you fail?
Please pardon me for my ineptitude.
You failed due to your ineptitude, huh?
Who is it?
Chi, it's me.
This is rare.
It's the first time you couldn't
tell that I was coming.
Young Lady, what do you need?
Chi,
did you sleep well last night?
I fell into a dreamless slumber.
But last night, you were...
Forget it.
I'm glad he didn't find out.
Chi, you can rest.
I'll return to my room now.
(Two Days Later)
You guys can get married to him
all you want.
I won't get married to him.
Young Lady, this is bad.
The matron of rites
are on their way here!
Stop them! Hurry!
My future depends on you guys now.
You guys are my only ticket out of this.
Father.
Today's weather is pretty good, huh?
Huh?
It's windy and sandy today.
Oops.
I think some sand got into my eyes.
(Old Man, once everything settles down,)
(I'll buy anything you like for you.)
Your Highness, I thought His Majesty
already issued an imperial edict?
For some reason, I just wish to see her.
I cannot afford to wait any longer.
Who's there?
You!
Hold this for me.
Thanks.
It's you?
What are you doing here?
Miss, you're...
Isn't it obvious? Of course I'm...
Why should I explain myself to you?
By the way, why were you hurt
when we were in the bamboo forest?
I...
And,
you actually left without saying goodbye
even though I rescued you.
Actually, I...
Forget it.
It has nothing to do with me.
So, can you hold this for me?
Thanks.
Let's go.
You're escaping from your marriage?
That's right.
You're escaping from it even though
it was His Majesty's order?
Goodness.
What's the matter?
I'm at the peak of my youth now.
Besides, I haven't even seen
the crown prince before.
What if he's a stinky old man?
I heard
that the crown prince
is dashing and handsome.
Girls have to queue up all the way to
our neighboring nation just to see him.
That's right.
I've heard about him as well.
You guys should marry him
if you like him that much.
Miss, do you have
any place in mind then?
I don't.
Miss, you're the next crown princess
after all.
I'm afraid it's inappropriate for you
to wander alone.
If you wander outside for too long,
people might criticize you.
Why don't we...
Criticize me?
That's a great idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
Are you sure Young Lady
went to take a walk?
Yes. Young Lady said she was
going to catch a song performance.
That was close.
My lord.
Young Lady is...
Keep a close eye on her.
Don't let her cause any trouble outside.
Yes, my lord.
♪My longing knows no bounds, in memories I wallow♪
♪Us and our wishful thinking♪
♪When memories turn into poetry♪
♪Which poem will be yours?♪
♪Year after year, an instant change♪
♪The few nights that contain our memories♪
♪Looking as the stars vanish,
you grew distant from me♪
♪Why can't I forget about you?♪
♪Words after words, tears flowing down♪
♪As the trees and plants wither♪
♪Where are you during New Year's Eve?♪
♪Can you please look back?♪
♪Just once♪