♪They say time
will reveal a person's heart♪
♪In all lives,
may the sea calm the tides♪
♪Blue silk drifting to one's hometown,
carrying greed, hatred, and ignorance♪
♪Going to the corners of the heavens
to seek a long-awaited reunion♪
♪To live or die together,
that is but an act♪
♪Letting down our memories♪
♪Why should we rip out our heart
for a heartless person?♪
♪Treating each other with courtesy
is but a scene in my dream♪
♪We'll wake up eventually♪
♪As the autumn wind blows,
the maple leaves fall, pulling myself away♪
=Don't Forget My Love=
=Episode 20=
Where's Xulin?
He hasn't returned since last night.
Send someone to inquire about
his whereabouts.
Yes, Your Highness.
The crown prince has arrived.
Noble Consort Liu, I'd heard that
you and Xulin were childhood friends.
Now that I look at it,
your relationship with him
is different indeed.
Your Highness, please mind your words.
Do not try to malign me.
Malign you?
What did I say?
Besides,
I heard that Xulin was your hometown
friend before he entered the palace.
It's a fact that you two
were childhood friends.
As for your relationship with him,
I didn't explicitly state that
it was love between men and women.
Noble Consort Liu, seems like
you've gotten the wrong idea.
His Majesty has arrived.
Father.
(How did he know about that?
Don't tell me Xulin is already...)
Chuan, why do you say so?
Your Majesty, I don't know
how I've offended the crown prince.
He's actually slandering me.
Your Highness, you must
uphold justice for me.
I'm slandering you,
huh?
Father, I found out that Xulin
bribed a servant who was good
at holding his breath underwater
when Noble Consort Liu was pregnant.
He hid underwater
and installed a hidden panel.
After that, he spread fish food
all over the water,
causing the carps
to form a huge "Fu" word,
which means prosperity.
That's why it was said that the carps
presented abundance and prosperity
when Noble Consort Liu
was pregnant with the child.
Noble Consort Liu,
will you be able
to clear your name now?
At worst, you deceived the emperor.
At best,
you created a fake heavenly phenomenon.
Are you trying to shake
the nation's foundation
and destroy order?
My love,
is that true?
Your Majesty, I have no idea.
However, I can guarantee
that Xulin
had no such intention!
What's your relationship with Xulin?
Why are you covering up for him?
Your Majesty,
I can swear a vow.
Xulin was only concerned about me
because he was afraid that
I had it rough in the palace,
since we were childhood friends.
Hmph.
Bring Xulin here.
Xulin isn't castrated.
Someone!
Execute this beast immediately!
Strip Lady Liu of all her titles
and banish her into the Cold Palace!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Please believe in me!
Take her away!
- Your Majesty!
- Take her away!
Your Majesty!
You are not to leave the Cold Palace
without my order!
Chuan,
is this the show you wanted to show me?
Father,
I've prepared a show for you.
Please join me.
Chuan,
you've changed.
I'm just trying to protect the person
I want to protect.
I'm getting rid of all the dangers
around her.
I hope you will never
regret your decisions.
I will never regret it.
The dart was coated with
Shihe Snake Poison,
a potent poison from
the Western Regions.
Luckily, Xie Yu
brought back the antidote
after he visited the Western Regions.
This is the only antidote I found
after searching through
the Pavilion of Artifacts.
Crown Prince,
please take this immediately.
It can neutralize the poison.
Thank you, Imperial Physician Jiang.
The crown princess
has returned to the palace.
Yan Chi is poisoned.
He was struck with Shihe Snake Poison.
I heard that Xie Yu, the envoy of Dayu,
brought back the antidote
after he visited the Western Regions.
You're the crown prince.
You can surely find the antidote here.
Why must I save him?
Who is he?
What has that got to do with me?
Now, he's my only kin in the world.
Moreover,
he was poisoned
because of me...
Yun Qianyu,
do you care about him that much?
So, to you,
his life is everything, huh?
What do you mean by that?
You don't wish to save him?
No, I don't.
You...
You're the crown prince.
You just need to lift a finger
to get the antidote for him.
If you're willing to save him,
I'll stay in the Eastern Palace forever.
I'll become a sensible
and subservient crown princess.
I will obey your every word.
I'll do anything
you say.
Yun Qianyu,
you're still as gullible as always.
I married you
in order to shut the people up.
Now, I've achieved my goal.
What makes you think that you have
the right to negotiate a deal with me?
Jun Lingchuan,
you're a scoundrel!
You failed your duty
as the crown princess.
Not just that, but you also
mingle with other men.
Now that he's injured,
you want me to save him?
Do you truly think that my benevolence
knows no bound?
That's not it!
You said this before.
You...
Yun Qianyu.
Did you truly think that I fell for you?
Don't tell me you think that
your sugar-coated words
can conquer the heart
of the crown prince of Dayu
and manipulate him however you want?
Yun Qianyu,
your naivety is through the roof.
Has it never occurred to you
that you were the pawn here?
Stop it!
What's wrong?
Did you fall for me?
I...
It's best if you didn't fall for me.
You can only blame yourself
for being too gullible.
You never change no matter
how much I deceive you.
Now,
I have other things to fret about.
I no longer wish to entertain you.
Leave.
Your Highness,
your wound is...
Imperial Physician Jiang already
examined me. I'm fine.
Put this in Yan Chi's medicine
in secret.
Go now.
Your Highness,
he's your rival. Why are you saving him?
Mujin!
Yes, Your Highness.
♪My longing knows no bounds,
in memories I wallow♪
♪Us and our wishful thinking♪
♪When memories turn into poetry♪
♪Which poem will be yours?♪
♪Year after year, an instant change♪
♪The few nights
that contain our memories♪
♪Looking as the stars vanish,
you grew distant from me♪
♪Why can't I forget about you?♪
♪Words after words, tears flowing down♪
♪As the trees and plants wither♪
♪Where are you during New Year's Eve?♪
♪Can you please look back?♪
♪Just once♪