According to Seven cats' popular novel, Her Highness doesn't care about moral ethics. Adapted?
Your Majesty.
Princess Qin’s medicine is for you.
I hope you can help the royal family as soon as possible.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I’m so grateful.
Prince Qin,
You are getting more and more impolite.
Father, Princess Consort is weak.
She can’t afford such expensive medicine.
I know you feel wronged.
How about this? I promise you one thing.
Myo-shim lives in the countryside.
so she has never seen much of the world.
and admired Yan Academy.
I’m the daughter of the Marquis of Wanhu.
and Princess Qin.
That means
Other than that mysterious question mark,
The Ming Emperor.
Empress.
I can contact the Marquis of Wanhu and Prince Qin.
The only thing I need to do
is Cheng Lixue from Yan Academy.
Go to Yan Academy then.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I will study hard.
I won't let Your Majesty down.
We've been here for so long.
It's time for you to meet Concubine Yu. You may leave.
Don't eat anything in the Imperial Study anymore.
Why?
If you don't want to die, do as I say.
He is protecting me.
Zhou, you are here.
Greetings, Mother.
Get up.
Thank you, Your Highness. Thank you, Mother.
Brother and sister-in-law.
Why are you standing here?
Sister-in-law, come here.
Mother.
I'm hungry. We want to eat cakes.
Changping, you...
Here comes His Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Get up.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
What?
I came at a bad time.
Your Majesty, you must be joking.
Father came to see mother
for something important.
We won't disturb you then.
Let's go.
Leave.
Go!
What brings you here today, Your Majesty?
Have you seen that child?
Don't you think
she looks like someone?
Your Majesty.
They are all dead.
Your Highness.
This is the medicinal bath therapy I read in the book.
Ask Mo Li to come here later.
with special massage techniques
can effectively suppress your poison.
Tonight,
we must find out the secret of the lonely boat.
Come out.
Already?
I'm not ready yet.
His Highness's heart...
It hurts.
Help me.
What are you doing?
Didn't you ask me to come here?
Your Highness.
[Have you heard of a word called "Effect from the East"?]
What does she want?
I don't believe I can't handle you.
Make the fan bigger.
You'd better give me an explanation.
Give me another chance.
Your Highness, why didn't you tell me what's on your mind?
How would I care about a mere beauty scheme?
Your Highness.
Get out.
I told you not to show up here.
How dare you come here?
This land is dirty.
Since you agreed to let me enter Yan Academy,
why can't I come to school?
Because I hate you.
Then don't look at me.
How dare you talk back?
Yan Academy
has always been learned.
If I ask Young Master Jin for advice,
will Young Master Jin agree?
This girl is so interesting.
Love it.
Changping.
Why isn't Yan Academy allowed to go to school?
Who are you?
Do you know my father is General Kim?
Do you know my father is the general?
I'm General Jin's only son, Kim Se-quan.
Who are you?
She's my sister-in-law.
So you are the shameless
who stole my sister's kiss.
I think you're ugly.
Jin Shi Quan, your words are too mean.
You should be happy
you should be happy.
Jiang Hutong.
Don't think you can rest assured
after entering Yan Academy.
Sir,
You seem to like bullying women.
So this is the general's manor.
What's going on?
My sister is new here.
She doesn't know the rules.
Please be magnanimous.
and forgive her.
For the sake of Jiang Xian,
for the sake of Jiang Xian.
If you wanted to come,
why would he show up now?
How could he admit
for no reason?
Miss Jiang, what do you mean?
Don’t you understand?
She said you were pretending.
She said you have ulterior motives.
Let's not argue with them.
If we want to enter Yan Academy,
you have to pass the basic exam.
This is hard.
You’ve never been to school.
Why don’t you go back and beg Prince Qin
to talk to the hill leader
to exempt you from the exam.
This is...
How do you know
how do you know I can't pass?
If you can,
I'll lie on the ground and learn to bark
to cheer you up.
Sorry.
Many people want to be my dog.
I'm afraid Mr. Jin can't make it.
But
if the bet is 100,000 taels of silver
I can think about it
You're really poor.
I have plenty of money.
But if you fail,
you'll be Jiang Xian's maid for three years.
Mr. Jin, it’s not appropriate.
Princess Qin is my maid.
Isn’t that embarrassing?
I admit defeat.
If Prince Qin dares to make trouble,
our General’s Mansion won’t be easy to deal with.
Sure.
As long as you can give me money,
you’re dead this time.
Princess Qin.
Flowers match beauties.
Stop fighting!
Stop!
Your face...
What happened to my face?
Didn’t you say Prince Qin was disfigured?
The World's Best City?
I'll keep that in mind.
It's an honor.
Director team.
Vice director, Li Haihao.
The production team.
Photography team.
Art team.
The recording team.
Lighting Team.
Costume team.
Props team.
Late production.
Jinma of Shenzhou.
Sunshou Jinma
Beijing Jingzhou Jinma Film and Cultural Communication Co., Ltd.
Special effects production.
Beijing Guangguang visual Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
All copyright.
Seven Cat Chinese network.
Monkey Film Media (Dongyang) Co., Ltd.
Joint production company.
Beijing Central TV Hengye Media Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Seven Cat Culture Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen Sang Mei Film Co., Ltd.
Dongyang Qimeng Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Jing Dejin Vivie and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen, SS Pictures and TV Production Co., Ltd.
The publicity company