According to the popular novel, "The Queen is not virtuous." Adapted
This experience is really good.
Look at his face and flexibility.
Lady Ruan, why are there men in your room?
Even if you grew up in the manor,
you're still the legitimate daughter of the marquis manor.
You colluded with a man before getting married.
and did such a dramatic thing.
and disgraced the marquis manor.
You're already framing me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Lady Ruan has degraded herself.
I can't let you go astray.
Kill that man!
What are you doing?
Whoever offends me will die.
Even fighting is so cool.
A man among men.
How dare you set me up?
This isn't right.
Special characters detected.
[will give you ten minutes of unbeatable hang time.]
I didn't expect that I would become a martial arts master one day.
Interesting.
Why is your handsome face getting darker?
Should I say something?
I didn't mean to bite you last night.
Hug you.
Touch yours.
How dare you seduce me?
I'll make it up to you.
How about you say a number?
Oh, my. I'm so happy.
You think I'm a model?
Pretend to be crazy.
Sir,
Can we pay the bill first?
Don't move.
The poison is the most poisonous poison in the world.
Those who are poisoned
will suffer the pain of bone corroding.
I lost my mind.
You're just leaving?
The system should be on a mission.
Speak in human language.
I think we need to do some specific movements
to translate into human language.
What's the movement?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Your damn system should have been destroyed long ago.
Hey, girl.
The world is so beautiful
but you're so grumpy.
This is not good.
Here.
Why is it different from the environment I read in advance?
Did you get the instance zones wrong?
I've customized a sweet instance zones.
I want to quit the game.
Sorry, sister.
You can't get out.
What does that mean?
I think I heard a special character.
You mean I
a member of this world?
Your Highness.
I failed my duty last night.
I failed to stop you.
If anything happens to you,
if anything happens to you?
Go and receive your punishment later.
Yes, Your Highness.
What's the progress
How is it going?
Last night, the eldest daughter of the Marquis
went into the Crown Prince's villa.
She hasn't come out yet.
That evil woman.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, do you need me to spread the news?
Go and check
Young Lady Yu Zhu in the manor of the Thousand Houses.
Your Highness, did the poison attack again?
His poison is getting worse.
Only the Ghost Doctor can cure him.
But...
But we searched for a long time
but we couldn't find the Ghost Doctor.
Keep looking.
Prince Qin, Marquis of Wanhu, Empress and Emperor Chengming. Cheng Lixue.
What’s my relationship with this mysterious man?
Please reveal everyone's secret
before the rose petals fall.
Otherwise, you will stay here forever.
Your unbeatable hang time is over.
Here are three basic skills for you.
You can choose one from three.
Rejuvenating Magic.
No need.
Entering Skill
I'm pretty. I'm pretty.
acupuncture skill.
This is it.
I hope you can be yourself in this world.
Time is running out.
What do you mean?
How dare you!
How dare you commit such a crime in the mansion?
Then report it to the government.
You must be Lady Ruan.
Why are you so rude?
Come and greet Madam.
Where am I from?
Of course I'm the second daughter of the Marquis of Wanhu.
Lady Ruan of the Thousand Houses?
live in such a place?
How can a mother dislike her daughter so much?
There's something fishy about her.
The fortune teller said
that you're the Monstrous Lonely Star.
You can't live with your parents before 20.
Otherwise, how could I
put you in the manor?
Let me have a look.
What do you mean?
Are you here to take me home today?
Her Ladyship arranged you to marry Prince Qin.
Just stay in Zhuangzi and wait for your wedding.
Prince Qin.
Nice to meet you, Prince Qin.
You don’t know what kind of person he is.
It’s best if you can figure it out.
In this world,
she has to rely on the strong to survive.
Prince Qin is powerful.
If you marry him, you’ll be a respectable Princess Qin.
Honey.
My lady.
You're not the eldest daughter of the Marquis.
Who do you think you are?
I'm also the legitimate daughter of the Thousand Houses.
Your Highness, please take me in.
I hate people who are frozen in the Li Dynasty.
A pheasant is a pheasant.
I can't fly up to the branches and become a phoenix.
Your Highness, I'm your man now.
You don't want to be your enemy, do you?
Fine. You look pretty.
Come on.
No.
Your Highness, no!
You're not complete.
Tell me who the adulterer is.
Actor watch.
Director team.
The journal, Hong Yanfei.
The production team.
Photography team.
Art team.
The recording team.
Lighting Team.
Costume team.
Props team.
Late production.
Shenzhou Jinma.
Beijing Jingzhou Jinma Film and Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Beijing Guangzhou visual Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
All copyright.
Seven Cat Chinese network.
Product company.
Fire Monkey Film Media (Dongyang) Co., Ltd.
Joint production company.
Beijing Central TV Hengye Media Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Seven Cat Culture Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen Sang Mei Film Co., Ltd.
Dongyang Qimeng Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Gyeongdejin Vivie and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Haining University Smart Pictures and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen, Double City Pictures and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Publicity Company.
Beijing Junyi Movie Production Co., Ltd.