It's a mouse!
Ugh, what is it?
Stop! Stop!
Enough!
[This series is a work of fiction.]
[Characters, behaviors, violence, places,
organizations, and events are fictional]
[and created for entertainment only.
Viewer discretion is advised.]
[MOUSE]
I'm not like anyone else.
That's why I'm hated and punished, right?
Hey, Karan!
Every single wound inflicted.
This person didn't hesitate for a second.
Each stab was precise,
a single strike was enough to kill.
All of this...
is the work of a single killer.
If what you're saying turns out to be true,
do you even realize what would happen?
If you want to stay alive to reveal the truth,
you don't need to find anything else.
Why did it have to be grandma?
I'm the killer.
What are you looking for?
The truth.
I feel like something's off.
I've never seen this evidence report before.
This one is missing elements
from the previous investigation.
[Case File: The Gold Leaf Killer,
by Police Captain Angkan Prechachaicha]
Inspector,
can I see the CCTV footage from the day
the Gold Leaf Killer evidence was delivered?
Inspector,
can I have the case file
and CCTV footage to investigate further?
Do you have an approval letter?
No, sir.
Alright, I need to use the bathroom.
Watch my stuff.
[Evidence]
What is it, Captain?
I searched the old evidence documents
of the Gold Leaf Killer
at the Evidence Collection Department.
And I found some evidence
that suddenly appeared.
But some evidence that was there
has gone missing.
What are they?
The new addition is the CCTV files
from the hospital and the prison,
which confirm that Dr. Kan was actually there.
But the missing evidence is Dr. Kan's contact
information with his friend, Komsan.
So you're saying someone switched the evidence?
When the case is closed,
all evidence will be sent
to the Evidence Collection Department
in case the investigation continues.
The report states it was delivered
on August 20, two years ago,
but CCTV evidence confirms
the documents were actually delivered
on August 23 of the same year,
three days later.
If so, there would have been enough time
to remove the old evidence
and replace it with the new one.
Who would have the power to do this?
I don't really know.
Grandma,
I really miss that thing
you used to say...
I'm getting older every day.
You should have someone
walk with you in the rain
when I'm no longer here.
I'm worried, worried all the time.
But I trust Wit.
He can take care of you.
Now,
it has come true, Grandma.
Wit and I...
Grandma!
Nurse, please help!
Grandma's seizing again.
Grandma!
Please step outside.
Stay calm, Grandma.
- No pulse detected.
- Grandma!
Move.
- Starting CPR!
- Start compressions!
Hey, you!
Your body's weak from lack of rest.
You need to take good care of yourself.
You need to eat more nutritious food.
Wit,
where are you?
W-What's the matter?
Well,
I'm pregnant.
Wit?
Do you think our child will turn out like us?
If you're not going to fix anything,
just jump.
What should I do first?
I've brought you food, Captain.
Hey, Captain.
Did you steal evidence again?
What do you think?
I guess so.
PM's son, look at this.
- Do you see this clip?
- Yes, sir.
Two seconds are missing from this clip.
This one too.
Hey, this part's missing almost a minute, sir.
Calculate it. If we fill in the missing time,
how long would it be
between walking and running?
Yes, sir. Wait a moment, please.
On average, humans walk
1.25 to 1.38 meters per second,
and run 7.5 to 8.8 meters per second.
The distance in the CCTV
is about 12 to 15 meters.
Okay.
This part is the time
when Wit followed Patthapol
and killed him before coming back alone.
Suddenly, the body was gone.
It means someone took Patthapol's body.
So what Wit said
about killing Patthapol was true?
We have to find Patthapol's body.
That's the only way we can find the truth.
That means whoever could edit
the footage from this CCTV
must have had access to data
in the Evidence Collection Department.
Either someone in our unit
or someone
in the Evidence Collection Department.
I don't think it's one of us.
Angkan signed as the investigator
on the evidence submission date.
It was already three days late
when submitted. Why?
Exactly.
- PM's son.
- Yes, sir.
Just the two of us know this.
So before we can actually get the evidence,
we need to quietly watch our unit members.
Yes, Captain.
Yes, Captain?
Can I ask you something?
The day before...
Dr. Kan was shot.
Were you with him?
Let's name our baby.
Isn't it too soon?
Just choose one, please?
I checked the CCTV, but it doesn't show...
it doesn't show you being with Dr. Kan.
Someone made it seem
Dr. Kan wasn't at the hospital,
to frame him as the killer.
At least you're starting to suspect
he wasn't the killer.
Thank you.
That's fine.
I'll find the truth.
If anything else happens,
I'll call you again.
Sure.
What's up, Picha?
What?
Okay, I'll be there.
Are you going to do the laundry?
As if.
- Let's go.
- Hey, where to?
- Hello.
- I told you not to reach out yet.
I think we should exchange some information.
You're going to be a mom already?
Congratulations.
Does Wit know yet?
I called him,
but hadn't even finished talking
before the call got cut off.
I can't get hold of him either.
- Hey, PM's son.
- Yes, sir?
Did you see Wit before you left the unit?
I haven't been able to reach him
since this morning.
Weird.
Come on,
He's probably following his case.
Don't worry. If I find him,
I'll tell him to call you back.
[Samor-riang Community]
Hello.
Where are you?
Okay, I'm on my way.
You're still alive.
Why are you hiding?
I'm being targeted.
That's why I told you to be careful.
Why are you being targeted?
The day you came to see me,
I felt like I was being watched.
So I quickly gathered
the information I had and hid.
I planned to hide elsewhere,
then contact Kan to hand over the info.
He probably knew something, too.
We agreed to meet here.
While meeting Kan,
they tracked me down.
I should've been dead.
If it weren't for Kan helping at the end.
Kan took me to a safe house, treated me,
and told me to hide.
We discussed the details
and exchanged information.
Everything we discussed
was directly related to him.
He found data related to
the Department of Medical Sciences.
We're about to get that information.
But in the end, I didn't find him,
and I didn't see the information.
Dr. Kankavin has passed away.
Kan passed away,
so I had to hide
and pretend I was dead.
Do you know who's after you?
I don't know.
He's got a hat and a mask on.
Anything suspicious?
Things like his voice, scent,
bracelet, and necklace.
Things that could identify him.
It's the letters "OZ",
tattooed on his wrist.
OZ...
- It's like this?
- That's right.
Have you seen them before?
You talked about the data. What is it?
The government's behind a law
to abort kids with the psychopath gene.
My police friend investigating this case
found a link to the Gold Leaf Killer.
He found proof that the Gold Leaf Killer case
was twisted to frame Dr. Kan.
I also doubt Dr. Kan's injuries.
They weren't fatal. But then, he suddenly died.
You know who's behind this, right?
It's just my assumption,
I think I know.
We've made progress in this case,
so we should move forward.
I think the safe house I'm at
will be secure for a while.
If you get more info,
you can come find me there.
I've planned all my escape routes
in case they catch up.
Where is it?
I'll share my location with you.
If it were me,
would you forgive me?
Would you really forgive
me?
Hey.
Say it.
Say it now.
Tell me.
How angry are you? How much hatred do you feel?
And you've never forgiven what happened,
not even for a second?
Say it!
Where have you been?
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
Wit...
Are you alright?
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Hey! Wit!
Will he survive?
He probably hasn't had enough rest
and hasn't eaten anything either.
I've already given him saline,
vitamins, and supplements.
After resting here for the night,
he can go home tomorrow.
Thanks.
No worries. You can call me anytime
if you need anything.
Did you hear that? He can go home tomorrow.
You should go home and rest, too.
I'll look after him here.
- It's okay.
- Go.
I'll send him back home tomorrow.
Go, go.
- Okay, I'll leave him to you.
- Okay.
Did Wit know yet?
I called him,
but hadn't even finished talking
before the call got cut off.
I can't get hold of him either.
Picha.
Wit.
Are you okay?
You don't need to worry about work right now.
Just take care of yourself first.
You're not alone anymore.
Thank you so much, Captain.
I always make you worry.
Something's been off with him lately.
Keep a close eye on him.
Call me if anything happens.
Sure.
You too.
You're a mother.
You're going to be a mother,
so you need to take good care of yourself.
Thank you.
What's up, Captain?
Are you at the studio?
Yes, I'm preparing some work.
Can you step out for a minute?
Sure.
Okay, I'll pick you up.
Sir,
I'm going out for a bit.
Cover things for me, please.
Hey, you.
Hey.
Picha.
Wit, you woke up?
Didn't you go to work today?
I just got back.
- Can you cut the pork? I'll get rice.
- Okay.
You've been asleep for a while.
You must be really hungry.
A little bit.
Wit,
grandma has woken up.
Really? That's great.
- And how's grandma doing?
- She just opened her eyes.
She can't talk or respond yet.
We'll go visit grandma later, okay?
Okay.
This is a clip from the CCTV that was cut out.
On the day we went live together,
the hospital timesheet shows that
Dr. Kan is on rounds.
But the CCTV didn't capture him at all,
even though Wit was keeping an eye
on him the whole time.
But the cameras on the opposite side
captured Dr. Kan's car driving out.
And Wit was following him.
And then?
I'm taking you to check out
another incident site.
I'm pregnant.
Do you think our child will turn out like us?
It was my fault...
for overlooking the possibilities at this spot.
No, Shen!
But the person behind this
intended for Dr. Kan to be the murderer.
What was the purpose of doing this?
Psychopath.
Because he's Orachun's son.
All the evidence points to him,
so people easily believe he's the killer.
But I've never believed that he's the one.
The important part is
who had access to the data
and edited or deleted those clips.
It definitely can't be an ordinary person
or organization.
What if it turns out
that someone on your team is involved?
What would you do?
You trust Dr. Kan.
I trust my team, too.
I'm going to find the truth.
If you're not going to fix anything,
just jump.
Grandma!
Grandma, you know Wit...
Wit.
Grandma.
Okay, Mom. I'll be right back.
What's up?
Oh, nothing. The PM's son told me
he dropped some case details for me.
- What case?
- Well, the prisoner's case.
Ugh, where did he put it?
Oh, it's here. I found it.
Did he go through my desk?
Grandma!
- Grandma! What's wrong with her?
- Please wait outside.
Grandma!
- What's happening, Wit?
- It's...
Doctor.
- The patient has passed away.
- What?
She just woke up.
How could she have passed away?
- What is it, Doctor?
- Clinically, it's called terminal lucidity.
The patient recovered,
showing an unexpected return
to consciousness before death.
No, that's not it. She was murdered.
- Wait, Wit. Who killed whom?
- Excuse me.
- Doctor!
Captain, you have to believe me.
I saw someone run out of the room.
So I followed through the car park,
but I couldn't catch him.
Then I came back here to see grandma--
Enough, Wit!
Calm down and stay focused.
Why are you here?
- I came to visit Grandma.
- At this time?
- Hey.
- Picha.
- Grandma! What's happening? Grandma!
- Please wait outside.
Doctor? Let go of me! Grandma!
- Miss, calm down.
- Grandma! What's happening to you?
In the hallway.
Hey!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Who's that?
Hello.
I'm Dumrong.
- Uncle Dumrong.
- Hey!
The... the parking lot. The parking lot.
You'd better calm down, Wit.
Picha is feeling sad at the moment.
You should stay with her.
I'll handle this myself.
Okay, sir.
Copy all the clips for me.
- But...
- I'll need them to investigate.
Wit.
What happened?
I don't know, Picha.
I really have no idea.
Why?
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
Did she really pass away?
It's okay.
[Maga One City Police Station]
Captain, you have to believe me.
I saw someone run out of the room.
So I followed through the car park,
but I couldn't catch him.
Then I came back here to see Grandma--
Enough, Wit!
Why are you here?
- I came to visit grandma.
- At this time?
[Special Investigation Unit]
Picha.
Are you alright?
If you're not, I can help.
I'll take over the shop,
alright? Let me know, okay?
I'll get going.
I'm sorry, Picha.
I could've helped you more.
[Maga One City Police Station]
Can you remember his face?
I'm sorry...
Everything happened so fast,
I didn't have time to react.
So I can't even remember his face.
I'm sorry, I didn't believe you at first.
I understand,
even I'm not sure these days...
whether what's happening in front of me...
is real or just in my imagination.
Wit,
you should take a break for now.
Your body isn't strong enough at the moment.
- No, I can't, Chief.
- I think it's a good idea.
You look really weak right now.
And Picha's mental state
isn't that good either.
You'd better take care of her.
- Let us take care of grandma's case.
- You think so too?
I really want to catch whoever killed grandma.
No need, I'll handle it myself.
- Hey, PM's son.
- Yes, sir.
Find a way to unlock it.
What is it, Captain?
Something doesn't feel right.
- Captain.
- What?
I can't access it.
What the hell? Seriously?
Even the PM's son can't access it?
It's a two-step verification code.
It's not a normal code.
Alright, sir.
Just give me some time.
That's right! The PM's son never disappoints.
Yes, baby.
Yes, miss you too.
Wait for me. I have to work first.
Yes, miss you, baby.
Yes, kisses.
When are you getting married?
Soon. You'll be the first
to be invited if I get married.
Don't give her too much hope.
You're a cop, anything can happen.
I'm not like you, Captain.
I'm sorry.
Wit,
I'm sorry to you and Picha about your grandma.
At the same time, I'm happy for you, too,
that you're about to have a kid.
I also have some good news.
About...
What's it about?
I'm getting married.
Congratulations.
Here, here, here.
Let me show you a picture.
What do you think?
What kind of answer do you want?
Mr. Wit, just say "Perfect couple"
and "Your girlfriend is so pretty." That's all.
- Perfect couple.
- That's right.
- Your girlfriend is so pretty.
- Thank you.
After getting married,
I'm planning to quit.
What?
Why's that? Didn't you say
you wanted to be a cop like the captain?
Previously, yes.
But when the whole psychopath thing came up,
it really threw the captain off for a while.
You're the same.
It's like you died and came back to life.
It makes me think that this career
could end any day,
and who knows what might happen.
So,
what are you going to do
after leaving the job?
Good question.
I was traveling with my girlfriend
and found a house for sale near the mountain.
I bought it, how's it?
I'm planning to open a homestay
that's completely off the grid.
It'll be powered by solar panels.
I'll have a chicken farm,
grow my own vegetables,
and cook for the guests.
Live life to the fullest, in tune with nature.
How's that? Sounds good?
- It's good.
- Yes.
You really think things through.
I haven't thought about this.
But living a peaceful life does sound nice.
So when we have children,
let's quit this job and enjoy life.
I'm serious.
After the wedding, I'll have a baby right away.
Our kids can be friends, you see.
If it's a girl and a boy,
we'll have them get married
and start a family, just like in the movies.
Sounds good?
Then your family can open a homestay
and a shop near me.
What is it?
You should take Picha to relax a bit. Here.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I'll send you the location.
I've been thinking
about so many things I wanna do.
Man, I'm so glad to have you as my friend.
Me too.
Here's to our future success.
During the show,
I was analyzing
how all the victims were murdered,
each punished for the sins they had committed.
In chronological order,
Chuto was the first victim.
He was tortured in many ways.
It was said that Chuto once murdered a family.
What was done to Chuto
was an eye for an eye.
Just like Sangchai.
It was the same pattern.
If the person who killed Chuto...
is the same one who killed Sangchai.
Then Dr. Kan...
isn't the killer.
I'm sorry.
How can I help you?
Is Auntie Kunlamas here?
Kunlamas...
Oh, she moved out years ago.
Where did she move to?
Hmm, which one?
This one is cute.
Hey, this one is so cute.
Hmm, children's gloves?
Should I buy them?
What are you thinking about?
A present for my friend. He's having a baby.
- Your friend's having a baby?
- Yes.
Are you sure it's a friend?
Of course, a friend.
Hey, help me choose one?
Or...
shall we choose for our baby too?
You're crazy, we're not married yet.
Soon.
- We should get married first. Propose to me.
- You want to marry me?
Who doesn't?
Or what about these?
These baby mittens are cute.
But... how do we have a baby?
Oh, no, no.
- You sure you don't know?
- Yes, I don't know.
- It's okay.
- I mean...
- I'll teach you.
- Hey!
Really?
No, keep looking. Just kidding.
- So these and this.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Okay, go.
Auntie Kunlamas.
Why didn't you call before coming?
Sorry for dropping by suddenly.
I'm here to see Uncle Dumrong.
Is he here?
He died.
He died?
What happened?
A car accident.
Why can't I remember anything?
He died while you were in a coma.
I didn't think you'd remember him,
so I didn't tell you.
I moved here after splitting up
with him a long time ago.
He died while I was in a coma?
Impossible... I saw him just a few days ago.
Uncle Dumrong.
I'm sure. I remember his face.
Were you there when he died?
You saw his body, right?
I split up with him a long time ago.
I knew because someone told me.
I didn't see him.
Boy, it's after hours.
I told them about the raw material stock.
I said it needs to be reported by Friday
so they can ship the orders out sequentially.
What kind of way is that to work?
Alright, I'll be there.
Baby, I need to go back to the office.
Got something to handle.
I'm sorry.
No worries, baby. You'd better go.
Aw, don't cry.
We'll see each other again soon.
- Okay. I'll call you when I get home.
- Okay.
Alright, my pretty girl.
Okay, bye.
Captain, I'm in.
I'm thinking of finding a small plot of land
for the three of us. For you and our baby.
If we can be together here,
it would be great.
Do you really think
you can live...
a peaceful life?
Psychopaths are dangerous,
they must be eliminated from society.
I'm not getting involved with this anymore.
I don't know what happened.
I'm lost. Everything's confusing.
How did the killer know that you assigned
Lt. Chin to investigate?
I don't get it.
An insider.