[This series is a work of fiction.]
[Characters, behaviors, violence, places,
organizations, and events are fictional]
[and created for entertainment only.
Viewer discretion is advised.]
[MOUSE]
Congratulations on the new show.
Kill him.
Go on.
Kill him!
Wit, get inside. Please.
I'll raise Korn the best I can,
just like I raised Kan.
Kan.
Police.
What's going on?
What's up?
The DNA results from Sangchai's case
just came in, sir.
I asked how the hell you let them in!
The DNA test from the knife
used to kill Sangchai belongs to Boonsong, sir.
Then it's over.
Boonsong's dead.
Captain, where are we going?
Who is she?
Her name's Nilla.
She went missing.
So we're taking this case?
I'm not worried about that anymore, Grandma.
Wit takes really good care of me now.
I lost our bet, Grandma.
About Wit.
So you need to wake up soon.
I'm heading to work.
We'd like to ask a few more questions
about Nilla.
Nilla was a student at a private university.
I heard she had an older boyfriend.
He was planning to take her abroad with him.
Did you ever see this boyfriend?
Wait a minute.
Here.
Nilla's phone.
Wait, this is Nilla's phone?
- Yes.
- Why didn't she take it with her?
She said her boyfriend
was buying her a new one,
so she left this for me.
We'll need to take this phone as evidence,
if that's alright.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Uncle.
Excuse me.
I'm here to see Ms. Naruemon.
The head nurse isn't in today.
She's at an out-of-town seminar.
What about Ms. Somrudee?
No one's here. We're just filling in.
- So the whole department is gone?
- Yes.
Hello customers!
For a limited time only,
our mystery boxes start at just 599 baht.
You can win amazing prizes,
from small gold charms up to 10-baht gold bars.
And that's not all.
We're also giving away brand new motorcycles.
Police.
One moment, everyone.
Yaya will be right back. Just a second.
We need to ask you some questions
about Miss Parinda.
You were friends with her, right?
I knew her, but we weren't close.
Did she have problems or...
get into any arguments with anyone recently?
I don't know if she argued with anyone,
but if I had to guess,
I'd say it was loan sharks.
I used to see debt collectors shouting for her
out in front of the warehouse.
They were really loud.
But honestly, officer,
you're wasting your time here.
No one here was close to her.
Is there anything else?
- No.
- Okay. Thank you.
Kaneungha saw a lawyer
about filing an adultery lawsuit.
Parinda... was financially supporting
a male university student.
She saw a lawyer... about her debts
and a mystery box scam.
And Nilla, who had a sugar daddy,
was about to move abroad.
She saw a lawyer about getting married.
No matter what, Lawyer Patthapol
seems really suspicious to me.
Because he's connected to both cases.
He might even be involved in
Nilla's disappearance as well.
But...
Yes, Captain?
What's the motive?
I don't know if it's a coincidence,
but all of these cases
seem to revolve around affairs.
If he's a psychopath,
he'll definitely strike again.
So for now, we need to keep an eye
on Patthapol.
I'll handle that.
Hello? You want me to leave now?
Sure, see you later.
You bastard! Get out of my way! Move!
I need to search your vehicle.
Do you have a warrant?
Darn it.
You bastard!
Sorry about that.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're just like me.
Alright, let's move it. On time, everyone.
Hurry up. The guest speaker is about to arrive.
Let's be on time.
Please head into the lecture hall.
Let's pick up the pace, please.
- Hello.
Let me help you with that.
It's an honor for our university to have you
speak to our students, Mr. Patthapol.
- The pleasure is all mine. Thank you.
- Right this way.
Hey, you three. Get up here.
Alright everyone, settle down, please.
Thank you all for being here today.
Before we begin,
I have a question for all of you.
Let's see if anyone in this room can answer.
The questions is this.
What are the legal limits of...
a police officer's authority...
when dealing with a suspect?
Who knows the answer?
If the cop is as handsome as you,
I'd volunteer as a suspect.
Thank you.
Okay, one more question.
And this one is serious.
Let's say...
you're accused of a crime you didn't commit.
What are your legal rights in that situation?
Does anyone know?
What did you do?
That lawyer, Patthapol, called me.
He said you searched his car.
And look at this.
He sent a messenger to drop off
his lecture notes for me.
Does he think I'm a student or something?
I thought he was about to flee, sir,
so I went to intercept him.
You two need to stop obsessing
over this psychopath nonsense.
From now on, you're working separately.
We can't do that, sir.
And why not?
These two cases are connected.
There could be other victims.
I don't know what kind of lead you have,
but whatever it is,
don't let the press get wind of it.
Catch the killer first.
Then you can go on whatever talk show you want!
Yes, sir.
Are you going to read that?
Kill him.
You want to kill him, don't you? Then do it.
Wit, where are you going?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Take your medicine first.
I have to go check on something.
Can you take your medicine first?
You don't look well.
- Wit.
- Picha,
I'll be back.
Wait for me at home, okay?
You're burning up, Wit.
Take something for the fever.
Let me get it for you.
The police officers from yesterday
are waiting out front.
Did they go upstairs?
Not yet.
I'm going upstairs to work on a case file.
I won't be answering my phone.
If anyone calls, take a message.
Understood.
[Police Major Commits Suicide
After Wife Leaves Him]
Are you here for Chanya?
- Yes.
- She's in this room. You can go in.
Thank you.
Chanya, you have a visitor.
Hello.
Can I help you?
I was hoping you could do me a favor.
I found information suggesting this family
is connected to a suicide case.
But when I searched the police database,
I couldn't find any details.
Is this related to a case you're investigating?
Yes, with Captain Ramil.
Did Captain Ramil send you?
No, I came on my own.
Okay. I'll search the old news archives
for you.
Thank you very much.
- Wit.
- Yes?
Who taught you to do that sign language?
Sign language? No one.
Why?
The other day at the studio,
what did that sign you made mean?
I'm not sure, actually.
In that moment, I just felt the urge to do it.
My hand moved on its own.
I don't know what it meant.
Hey.
Is something wrong?
No. It's just...
you remind me of someone.
If I find anything,
I'll contact you right away.
Thank you.
Is Mr. Patthapol in?
- Yes.
- I have urgent business with him.
It would be better if you came back later.
He said he's not seeing any visitors today.
I need to see him today.
I'm sorry, he insisted.
No calls and no visitors.
I can make an appointment for you.
Can you schedule an appointment for him?
Sir, please!
You can be charged with trespassing!
Sir, please stop!
Sir, you'll be charged with trespassing!
You can't go in!
Wit.
I found it.
Miss, have you seen this woman around here?
Thank you.
I've missed you so much.
Of course I missed you, Note.
You never call me.
I've just been really busy.
I've been working to pay for tuition, Note.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to be a bother.
You're not bothering me at all. It's fine.
- I just didn't want to impose.
- How do you want me to transfer the money?
If it's a bank transfer,
could you do it in the back?
Sure thing.
Miss, have you seen this woman around here?
No, I haven't.
Hey.
Is something wrong?
No.
No. It's just...
you remind me of someone.
Excuse me. Let me through.
Help! Help me!
Mr. Patthapol, what are you doing here?
I had a meeting with a client nearby,
but I'm finished now.
What about you?
I just got off work.
Want to grab dinner?
My treat.
I actually forgot something at the university.
I have to go get it.
Alright, I'll come with you.
Okay.
I found her. I'm following her now.
Sending you the location.
Please wait here, Mr. Patthapol.
I'll be right back.
Hurry up.
Okay, wait here.
You can't. Someone might see us.
You can't, Mr. Patthapol.
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
What do you want from me?
Get out of my life.
You're the reason I'm this way!
Stop haunting me.
Get out of my life!
Get out!
How can I get out of your life?
I'm inside you, aren't I?
What the hell are you talking about?
Get out!
What the hell is so funny?
Go ahead, punch me.
What the hell?
I didn't know you could punch yourself.
Wit!
Wit.
Calm down.
[Ruamkatanyu Foundation]
Wit.
- Hello?
- Where the hell did Wit go last night?
Is he home?
Yes, he's home. He's resting now.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
He suddenly had a seizure and passed out.
Keep an eye on him.
If it gets any worse, take him to the hospital.
Call me if anything happens.
Okay.
Wit.
- Captain.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine. Really, there's nothing wrong.
You didn't show up last night,
so I called Picha.
She told me you were sick.
If you're not feeling well, just tell me.
You don't have to rush back to work.
No, I'm completely fine now, Captain.
Thank you for your concern.
Yes.
Chanya sent this over.
Why were you in contact with Chanya?
And why didn't I know about it?
Today's top story.
A police major was abandoned by his wife,
leaving him for another man.
He reportedly tried to reconcile,
but she refused.
Locals say that not long after,
the wife gave him custody of their son,
and then committed suicide
by hanging with her new partner.
The heartbroken father
then hanged himself as well.
A true tragedy for the child left behind.
We can only hope
for a positive outcome for him.
Patthapol's mother and her new husband
hanged themselves.
Then his father did the same.
What are you getting at?
It's suspicious, Captain.
His father may have had a motive for suicide,
but his mother and her new husband didn't.
Which makes me wonder if their deaths
were staged to look like suicides.
The nurse, Kaneungha, also died by hanging.
And when Parinda's body was found,
there were ligature marks on her neck.
In every single one of these hanging cases,
Patthapol was connected to the victim.
Are you suggesting Patthapol
murdered his own parents
and his mother's new husband?
I'm just saying the cases from 20 years ago
and the ones now are all connected.
There's a high probability
that the killer is the same person.
If that lawyer is the killer...
Psychopaths won't stay quiet for long.
He'll strike again.
This is Khing. She's an acting coach, Captain.
- Hello.
- I've already briefed her.
Is there anything you want to add, Captain?
Are you sure you can do this
without making him suspicious?
She studied acting in the US.
There's no way Patthapol will suspect anything.
I've never done anything like this before,
but I promise you,
I won't mess up your plan.
Don't worry.
When you're with Patthapol, we'll be nearby.
If anything happens, we can get to you
in under two minutes.
You'll be wearing a hidden camera.
If something goes wrong,
we're ready to move in.
Okay.
Then let's get everything ready.
We can't screw this up.
Right.
Here's your coffee.
And for you.
Thanks.
Go. Go on.
Get out.
Okay.
To be honest, my husband is incredibly boring.
I'm this pretty
and spent a fortune to get this body,
and he never pays any attention to me.
If I file for divorce,
what grounds could I use?
Has he ever...
been physically violent with you?
He slapped me once and called me a slut.
You'll need evidence for that.
It's a complex matter.
Do you have some time?
Yes.
[Wed & Sun]
Alright, I'll see you later today.
- Okay.
- Let's get dinner. My treat.
Do you think I'll win the case?
Absolutely.
You haven't touched your drink.
That's because I'm driving.
I'm putting my trust in you.
And that includes for tonight, too.
We're here.
Watch your step.
- How's it going?
- Right here.
Have another drink.
Where's he going? Is he getting a knife?
Hold on. If we're wrong, we'll blow our cover.
Shit!
- Get the key for Room 405.
- You can't go in there.
- Shinohm.
- Police! Get the key. Now!
Watch the video.
This woman is about to be killed!
A killer is attacking a woman.
She could die. Give us the key, now!
Hurry!
Go!
Check on the victim.
- Copy that.
- I'll go check the bathroom.
- Khing!
- He's not in the bathroom!
- How is she?
- She's still breathing.
- Call an ambulance.
- On it.
Yes.
Hello, we have an emergency.
If you're so tough, follow me, you idiot.
Come and get me, if you dare!
Come on. Bring it on!
You're just like me.
Kill him.
You want to kill him, right?
Then do it. Kill him.
Captain.
Hello, Lieutenant.
The captain has been injured.
The doctor says his condition is improving.
He'll probably be moved out of the ICU soon.
And don't worry,
I'll take care of all the hospital bills.
Thank you, officer.
Thank you for taking care of everything.
What have I done?
What happened?
That patient is being reckless.
The doctor didn't discharge him,
but he insists on leaving.
If something happens,
he shouldn't come crawling back here.
Why did you do that, Captain?
It's fine.
Are you in pain?
It's not too bad.
But it was worth it. At least now we have proof
that Patthapol is the culprit.
- Captain.
- Yeah?
That's my coffee.
Thanks.
And what about Shinohm?
He's not doing so good.
He feels incredibly guilty
for getting Khing involved in this.
- Captain.
- Yeah?
Do you think we went too far?
I've reviewed the X-rays.
You can go home soon.
Just make sure you come back
for your follow-up appointment.
Thank you, Doctor.
Not you.
You're the stubborn one.
You never listen to the doctors or the nurses.
With a concussion like that,
how can you even think about going home?
You're staying here.
And listen to the nurses.
How is he, Doctor?
What can I say?
He's stubborn, so he has to stay.
- Stubborn?
- Extremely. Please look after your friend.
Come on, Wit, I'll take you home.
Thanks.
And how's Khing?
She's safe.
So, you're being stubborn, Captain?
It's a good thing
the doctor is making you stay.
I'll call Tawee to keep you company.
Hey! Why are you taking that off?
I'm not.
It's itchy.
Maybe it's an allergic reaction.
Wit, where were you all night?
And...
what happened to you?
The captain and I ran into some trouble,
so we ended up at the hospital.
Sorry I didn't call.
Things got a little chaotic.
And the captain still has to stay here.
Are you hurt?
It's nothing.
The doctor said I can take this off
when I shower, so it's not a big deal.
And what about Mil?
He has to stay in the hospital
for a couple more days.
But the doctor said it's nothing serious.
I was planning to visit grandma
and Mil after work,
but...
I'll just stay here and look after you today.
It's okay.
You should go.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Okay, I'll head to work then.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Okay.
I'm not sure, sir.
When was the last time you saw him?
The last time was yesterday evening.
Why is this thing so hard to get off?
Sir, you can't take that off!
I have to use the bathroom,
and this is in the way.
Either you take it off,
- or I'll do it myself.
- Okay, I'll help you to the bathroom.
It's okay, I'll take him.
Okay, then.
Come on, I'll help you.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm going home.
You can't go home.
The doctor ordered you to stay.
What did you two get into
to both end up injured like this?
Didn't Wit tell you?
If he had, would I be asking you?
Nurse!
Mil.
Keep your voice down,
you're bothering the other patients.
Nurse!
Mil, you're being loud.
It's embarrassing.
Sorry about that.
Captain, I've tracked down Patthapol.
What?
I'm not scared of you,
loser.
She deserved to die!
Deserved to die? You monster!
Just answer me this.
Did you perform my brain surgery?
I was in prison.
How could I have performed your surgery?
If not you,
no one else in this country could've done it.
No father would let his son die.
What did you say?
You're lying!
I don't know what you're talking about,
but I'm not your mother.
Doctor said grandma's getting better.
When the part of your brain
with the killer gene activates,
you start craving an outlet
for your murderous instincts.
You're here?