Please look that way.
Your story is served as today's menu in…
The Blank Menu for You.
Here.
FWIGHLING
My nostrils are
rather dark.
There's a lot of microdust these days,
so our nostrils tend to get very dark.
Right.
And my chin looks like it's broken,
but I quite like it.
Even at first glance,
you didn't compliment me on my drawing.
It's unique.
Right, this era does value uniqueness.
It's good in its own way.
Good in its own way,
but not objectively good?
It's unique.
Yes.
Let me take it back.
I'll just trash it.
Wait.
I'm only joking.
-Please hold onto it.
-I will.
You made such an effort,
so we shouldn't tear this up.
Right.
I'll treasure it. Right here, like this.
Shall we read today's order?
Their handwriting
is very poised, don't you think?
It reminds me of expressive calligraphy.
Right.
Like, swish.
-Swish.
-Rhythmical breathing.
-Just like this?
-A sense of breathing.
Right, well, I'll read it for us.
"I may be wrong today
even if I was right yesterday,
but I constantly strive
to improve my weaknesses."
"I remind myself that having flaws
means I have more room to grow,
but I sometimes worry
that it might be too late."
"When I spend my time
locked in a silent struggle,
it's easy to forget to take care
of my heart and even my meals."
"I would like to request a dish
that's good just the way it is,
even if it wouldn't be considered
perfect or complete."
"Thank you."
This is tricky.
They seem to be going through
a fierce internal struggle.
What kind of struggle?
-Like a battle?
-It could be.
We may not be hurling punches.
-But everyone has internal battles.
-Right.
We all endure those battles
during our lifetime.
Right.
So what are your thoughts
for today's menu?
-For today's guest?
-I think…
They said,
"A dish that's good just the way it is,
even if it wouldn't be considered
perfect or complete."
No matter how hard I think,
Korean curry, or kare, is the only answer.
Why? In what way?
When moms
go away on a trip somewhere,
they say,
"Honey. I've cooked you some curry."
The assumption is you'll be eating
curry for at least three days.
Right.
And when you eat
your first spoonful of curry,
sure, it's curry,
but slightly milder.
-Fresh curry?
-Yes, curry that's freshly made.
The next day,
you eat it again.
And today, it's perfect.
It's thicker.
On the third day, you eat it again.
"Hold up."
"This isn't the curry I had yesterday."
But it's ultimately
still curry.
-Curry is so overwhelming.
-Right.
Even if it's not perfect,
and even if it's not complete,
it's still curry.
CURRY TAKES MANY FORMS OVER TIME,
BUT IT ALWAYS SAYS, "IT'S ME… CURRY."
This guest of ours
may find themselves a little frail,
so we'll use bone broth.
A curry made from bone broth.
Then would it be heartier and thicker?
-Right?
-Very thick.
-Yes.
-Sounds great.
-With love and encouragement.
-Absolutely.
What do we say to cheer someone on?
Chin up!
We normally say
-Fi…
-Oh, hwaiting!
-That's it.
-Right.
Fight!
Fwight!
Life requires
fighting!
-Shall we start?
-Sounds great.
-We need some apples.
-Okay.
-Please grind them gently.
-Grind them gently?
-Sure.
-Then…
Fighling!
Emphasize the "f."
Fighling! Two, three. Fighling!
-"Ling…"
-Two, three. Fighling!
-But you…
Two, three.
Fight… Okay.
Fighling.
-But the…
-Yup!
Can't we say "fighting"?
-Instead of the "ling."
-"Ling"?
It starts with a fierce "f."
Right.
-It's "fight."
-Sure.
But the "ling" makes it…
-We lose momentum with the "ling"?
-Yes, we do.
-Then let's try with "ting."
-Sure.
Two, three. Fighting!
Why aren't you saying it with me?
I am.
-Oh, okay.
-Deep down.
Sure.
I'm shouting it inside.
Then I'll say it inside too.
-Here we go.
I thought only vegetables went into curry,
but we're also using fruits.
I've never seen this done before.
You can make a curry
in so many different ways.
In more ways than we know, right?
Exactly. There must be many ingredients
I still haven't tried putting in a curry.
-There's a lot you can try.
-Exactly.
We'll be using this as our protein today.
This takes the longest to cook.
So we want to parboil this.
-Sure. I'll be doing this.
-Great.
BEEF TENDONS
PARBOIL THE BEEF TENDONS
TO REMOVE ANY IMPURITIES AND EXCESS FAT
ADD CHEONGJU TO A PRESSURE COOKER
AND COOK THE TENDONS
We're going to add a lot of onions.
I love onions in curry.
Yes, they're great. Let's use a mandolin.
So we won't be dicing them
into large cubes?
We won't. We could,
but this will save us time.
Okay.
I'll slice these up for you,
so please sauté them.
-Sauté them?
-Yes.
What sauce will we sauté them in?
Today,
we'll be using lard.
Lard?
Lard oil?
It's my first time seeing this.
If we sauté the onions in this…
it's better than using
regular cooking oil.
How should I explain?
-It's pig--
-Pork fat?
Exactly, yes.
I've actually seen that some households
stock up on a lot of lard oil
and use it often in their cooking.
It's a condiment of sorts.
-So we'll be using lard.
-I see.
LARD
It's melting.
We melt down the oil.
Okay. I want to do a good job.
For starters…
-You need perseverance for this.
-Perseverance?
It takes a decent amount of time.
-If you keep stirring this up…
-Yes?
You'll need to stir it even longer.
If you keep moving it around,
the heat
won't distribute evenly.
-It won't cook all the way through?
-Absolutely.
-So just let it sit.
-Okay.
And give it a toss every once in a while.
-Is that okay?
-Sure, got it.
It has a slight buttery scent.
Onions
have a much more inviting scent
when cooked than when they're raw.
An inviting scent.
Yes, they do.
It's almost like they're trying to say,
"You can approach us now."
They're more welcoming.
They're usually not, but all of a sudden,
they become so inviting.
-"Welcome."
-"Welcome!"
"Is this your first taste of sweetness?"
As if to ask,
But our method of approach
is also important.
Method of approach?
Yes, take these onions, for example.
If we cook them slowly on low heat,
they'll start opening up to us
and giving off that inviting aroma.
-Yes.
-If we keep sautéing them…
The onions
will slowly develop a gentle sweetness
and release their aroma.
But say
we spiked up the heat and shoved them in.
If we toss them too vigorously,
we might not coax out
their natural sweetness.
So we need to be meticulous
in choosing our method of approach.
Right, just like you do with people.
CARROTS
As for the celery…
CELERY
GARLIC
Will we sauté these too?
We will, yes.
Once the onions have cooked down more,
we'll add these in.
Understood.
And we need the meat.
BEEF RIB MEAT
It looks delicious.
The marbling is stunning.
It should be delicious, yes.
BAMBOO SALT
They look delicious.
We'll lightly sear the meat,
then simmer everything together.
LARD
Earlier, it was the onions,
but now it's the meat.
The meat will take on an inviting
and approachable flavor too.
Right.
But in this case,
we want to be approaching
the meat with high heat
to bring out its wild charm.
Should we be a little rough with it?
Exactly. As with people,
when working with ingredients,
you need to find the right approach
to bring out their unique charm.
They'll show you everything.
Even if we completely cook the meat now,
this particular cut won't go tender.
-So we're searing the surface.
-Right.
Just a mouthwatering sear.
Now, the onions
are starting to stick to the pan.
Right. Hold up.
I think we're ready.
-Shall we add them?
-Let's add the veggies.
Do I keep stirring it as I've been doing?
Spot on, yes.
Let's take this seared beef.
-We want to add it in.
-Okay.
It's hot.
So it has pork fat and beef fat.
Yes.
Sounds indulgent.
-Now, next in line.
-Right.
In go the bananas.
This looks so good.
Those with different natures
find ways to coexist.
Even here in this pot.
Right, yes.
They all have their unique charm.
-But come together.
-Together.
-To form a small world.
-A small world.
Their own universe.
So this is a globe.
-A globe.
-Sure.
If you're alone in the kitchen
for too long…
-You become a storyteller.
-Right.
Then, in this world,
I will be these bananas.
-Bananas?
-I'll be these guys.
What will you be, Samchoon,
in this world?
I'll just be the least-used ingredient.
I'll be the garlic.
-The least-used?
-Yes.
But you pack a punch.
Wait, that's not good.
Doesn't garlic have a strong presence?
In that case,
I'll be the apples.
They're in there,
but some will never realize it.
Apples.
I'll just be doing
my duty as a member of society.
-You'll be doing your duty.
-But it's fine if I'm not recognized.
-Banana.
-Yes?
-A banana and an apple.
-Yes.
I love it.
If it's somewhat cooked down,
let's add in the broth.
Okay.
-I'll pour this in.
-Let me get this.
Is that fat on top?
BONE BROTH
No, a layer has formed on the broth.
The broth is rich.
It should be packed full of flavor.
It looks like cream.
-Next.
-Yes?
-Please scrape the bottom as you stir.
-Gently.
Scrape the bits stuck to the pan.
-Dissolve everything into the broth.
-Sure.
You've got it.
And some meat.
We'll add this in
and cook it together.
The juices from the meat.
Moving on.
After it's cooked for a while
and the meat is tender,
we'll add the curry and season it.
Understood.
BUTTER RICE
We need to cook some rice.
We're going to add
some butter to the rice.
-We are?
-Yes.
And, at the very end,
when the rice is steaming,
we'll add one last slab of butter.
The fragrant butter will…
So this butter rice will come together
with this curry sauce?
Exactly.
SAUTÉ ONIONS IN BUTTER, THEN ADD RICE
BONE BROTH
I've never seen rice
cooked in bone broth before.
Some bamboo salt.
Bamboo salt.
And now, we'll cook it
on low heat.
-We won't stir it too much.
-Right.
Or else it would become a risotto.
Rice that is too sticky
would take the fun
out of mixing it with the curry.
The rice will be done shortly.
Is there anything else for us to do
while it's cooking?
Now, we…
-We need to work on this, right?
-Yes, we do.
I think we should blend it up.
Could you just take out the meat?
Sure.
Just the meat.
The meat looks good as is.
-Now, these guys.
-Those guys.
They'll become
a smooth soup.
Right.
-To become a curry.
-Yes.
Let's use this.
Wow. This looks delicious.
It doesn't have any bits,
but we'll have chunks of meat.
And now,
the tendons are nice and jiggly.
Would you look at that?
Let's do big chunks.
Great.
I think we should cook the meat more.
I see.
-But let's add them in for now.
-Okay.
-Next step.
-Yes?
Shall we try seasoning this?
What's that?
It's mango chutney.
Chutney?
This mango is what will elevate the dish.
It looks like jelly.
MANGO CHUTNEY
A SWEET, JAM-LIKE CONDIMENT
Now, let's add in the curry powder.
-Please stir that up.
-Sure.
Stir it up.
Let's also add some curry chunks,
one by one.
This looks so good.
They'll melt easily,
but still keep an eye on it.
-Shall I have a go?
-Sure.
Like this.
I see.
The color should be getting richer.
-Richer?
-Yes.
We want it to look
a little more like curry.
Right.
So we'll add more of this.
Will it make this thicker?
Yes, it should.
And the color a little richer.
Right, I think a true curry
gives you that instant feeling of
"Wow, this is super rich."
-The roux we added earlier has melted.
-Right.
Once the rib meat gets even more tender…
-Yes?
-We're done.
-Once the rib meat is tender.
-Yes.
THE BLANK MENU FOR YOU
Hello.
-Hello.
-Oh!
Hello, welcome.
Welcome.
The moment he walked through the door,
I thought, "Wow, how deep."
"His eyes are just so deep."
"How are they so deep?"
Man, this…
"Is this the way in? How deep can I go?"
OUR FIFTEENTH GUEST
YOO SEUNG-HO
-This way, please.
-Sure.
-Just there, yes.
-Should I sit?
Right.
I'm Yoo Seung-ho.
-I'm an actor.
-Yes.
Hello.
Welcome.
Thank you.
WISHING YOU A COZY NIGHT'S REST
This is cute.
-Welcome.
-Yes, hello.
I'm a little…
Yes?
It feels as though we grew up together.
I, myself, grew up in Songpa.
Right.
Do you have any relation to Songpa?
Not at all.
Right.
I'm a long-time resident of Gyeonggi-do.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
-Hello.
-A meeting between Songpa and Gyeonggi.
-Your order was…
-Right.
-Is this the order I wrote?
-Yes, it is.
You asked for a dish
that's good just the way it is.
Yes.
-That was your order, yes?
-It was.
It's nice when a guest
requests a specific dish.
Right.
But it's also nice to get
the occasional order that makes me think.
Right.
I really quite enjoy the orders
that make me reflect.
Your order also gave me
a moment to reflect.
-Your order.
-Yes?
It seemed riddled
with some of your concerns.
-I felt compelled to share their weight.
-Right, thank you.
I didn't have any worries about the food,
so I thought I'd order something that
resonates with my thoughts and concerns,
although I suspect that made it
a more challenging order.
Right.
The dish we're going to serve
in response to your order is curry.
-I like it.
-I'll hurry to… Sorry?
-Very well.
-Sounds good.
You're okay with curry, right?
Of course, I like it.
-Samchoon and I…
-Yes?
We poured our heart and soul
into making it an inviting dish.
-Thank you.
-It's an inviting curry.
-Here's your inviting curry.
-Inviting.
Yes.
-To me, curry is…
-Yes?
It's dish that fulfills
the last sentence of your order.
It's dish that's good
just the way it is,
even if it isn't perfect or complete.
-The curry I cooked today…
-Yes?
I would sell starting tomorrow.
Okay.
Why would you cook it the day before?
I think that's what makes a curry
truly delicious.
Right.
But even though I'd sell it tomorrow,
it's still fine to eat today.
-Because it's curry.
-Right, it's curry.
So,
even if it's not perfect, it's good as is.
I can't wait to dig in.
So… thank you.
-Please enjoy.
-Sure.
You're drizzling it at the perfect height.
-Am I?
-Yes.
-It's the perfect height.
-Great.
Aren't there usually chunks
of potato or carrot in curry?
I thought that was standard.
Right.
It looks very different.
Yes, even in Mom's curry,
she would always add potatoes.
-My mom.
-Oh, right.
Right, Mom's curry.
I haven't met your mother… Never mind.
-Curry also…
-It's delicious.
Well, thank you.
We used a bone broth base.
You seemed a little
worn out.
Like you had a lot of concerns
about the future.
I sensed some worries
about how to prepare for the future.
-Of course, I may be wrong.
-Sure.
So
instead of "hwaiting…"
You know, "Fighting!"
Fighting!
We wanted to cheer you on
as you face the fight of life,
so it's a pick-me-up.
But honestly,
it's seriously good.
The onions were a little sharp when raw.
-Right.
-But we heated them up.
-So they've taken on an inviting aroma.
-I see.
"Welcome."
-"Welcome."
-"I'm an onion."
"I'm an onion."
They started exuding
a more approachable aroma.
I see.
And to that, we added garlic and celery.
-And carrots.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Yes, they're all in there.
And mangoes.
Mangoes?
Yes, and bananas.
And apples.
These are ingredients
you wouldn't notice unless we told you.
Wow.
Because…
the curry has taken them all
under its wing.
Right.
Even if they're less than perfect,
under curry's wing,
they're able to find their place.
If the scent of butter
is a little too overwhelming…
-We have plain rice.
-It's not.
Not at all.
They pair beautifully. It's so tasty.
It's seriously good.
The meat is so tender.
We've used two kinds of meat.
Beef seuji,
which are the tendons.
And we also added some ribs.
-Ribs?
-Yes, rib meat.
Right.
So those two meats
are also dressed in curry.
-It's truly delicious.
-Thank you.
I'm glad.
Is it okay without any side dishes?
Totally. Could I please have
some more rice?
Of course.
Did you rush through that?
-Are you okay?
-I'm good.
It's really good.
Please eat up.
When moms leave on a last-minute trip,
you end up eating curry alone at home.
Curry in a bowl.
You would roughly
serve yourself some curry in a bowl.
-Right.
-And mix it up.
A rough mix.
The curry you indulge in
when you're home alone.
Right, I get you.
Right.
You know that sense of knowing someone
you've never actually met?
Sure.
I've never felt that more than today.
I almost blurted out, "Come on in!"
Did you almost say "You're all grown up"?
Yes, almost.
I feel as though, in some way,
we grew up together.
I haven't felt that with a lot of people.
I understand.
Thank you.
I'm feeling a little…
It's making me quite sentimental.
After reading your order,
preparing something
for you today felt easy.
-I felt…
-You did?
-I did.
-What about my order was…
"Even if it wouldn't
be considered complete."
Often, when I'm cooking,
I obsess over the idea of completion.
I worry about
whether my customer will be satisfied.
But
the way you worded your order.
I felt like you were being
considerate of me.
At the end, you wrote, "Even if it
wouldn't be considered complete."
"Something that's good the way it is."
That phrase, in and of itself,
let me prepare the food
with a much lighter heart.
If I'm honest,
that's actually not my handwriting.
It isn't?
Did your manager write it?
No, my usual handwriting looks different.
I must have written that order
over twenty times.
It felt like an introduction,
like you could probably tell what kind
of person I am just from my handwriting.
So I wanted to make an effort.
I wanted my writing to be neat,
but I think I just messed it up.
So I did write it myself,
but it's not my true handwriting.
I tried to imagine who you'd be.
Sure.
-Your handwriting is powerful.
-I agree.
Like calligraphy,
handwriting with a sense of breathing.
I wrote with a heavy hand.
I think that comes across.
Right.
I felt a sense of rhythm.
-That's a good thing, right?
-Yes.
-Great.
-It is.
It's been about seven years
since I've lived on my own now.
It's been a good while
since I've had a meal
that's been made with so much care.
At first, I ordered a lot of takeout,
which created so much plastic waste
that I felt a little pathetic.
My inability to cook
was causing so much waste.
So I started cooking here and there,
learning from YouTube videos.
But whatever I cook,
it always tastes the same.
Whether I cook kimchi-jjigae,
doenjang-jjigae, or sundubu-jjigae,
it always tastes the same.
At a certain point, I started wondering
whether my food tasted good.
I'm a little curious
how kimchi-jjigae and sundubu-jjigae
can taste the same.
Mine do.
It sounds good, though.
-Doesn't it sound good?
-It does.
Even if sundubu-jjigae
tastes like kimchi-jjigae…
that's still your cooking.
-Something only you can cook.
-Exactly.
Ask anyone,
"Can you make kimchi-jjigae
taste like sundubu-jjigae?"
"I can."
"You can't, can you?" That sort of thing.
But would that still be considered
sundubu-jjigae?
That would be…
You can call it
Seung-ho's special sundubu-jjigae.
Let's do that, yes.
You don't have to live
by the world's definitions.
Right.
"Could you do this?"
-Are you speaking from experience?
-I guess I am.
If you…
Other people will see you
and think, "Hey, that's a skill."
I have a question.
There's something I always fail to do.
You know the order
of putting oil in a pan, sautéing kimchi,
adding the next ingredient, and so on?
Yes.
I get impatient
and do things out of order.
So I…
-You start with water?
-I just boil water.
Shove all the ingredients in,
then let it boil.
I see.
If that's the case, for your own good,
if you get impatient…
I want to eat quickly
and move on to doing other things.
I think you need rest.
He does.
You should rest.
You're right. He does, doesn't he?
The ingredients also need rest.
You can shove everything in
and cook it all at once.
-Right.
-You can.
It's perfectly fine.
But there are things
that should be cooked separately.
For example, if you cook
high-sodium ingredients with low ones,
it affects the final result.
-It makes the dish saltier.
-Right.
Because of the heat.
So, even if it feels a little frustrating,
you should set those ingredients aside.
Think about what to add in later.
If you consider such things,
you should get a better final result.
At the appropriate time,
you need to let things rest.
Let things rest.
You need to take some rest,
and the quality of rest is also important.
You need rest
that allows your heart to heal.
When you learn a skill…
Back in the day,
when I was learning how to fillet fish,
they would train us intensively
for a full week,
then tell us to rest for about three days.
The idea was that our bodies
would automatically absorb the skills
while we were resting.
Your body says,
"Thank you for letting me rest,"
and somehow, you seem to learn faster.
So if things feel monotonous
or if you feel uninspired,
you could consider ways
to give your heart some rest.
I think that might be helpful.
In your order,
you mentioned having flaws and weaknesses.
-I did.
-What might those flaws be?
I think, inevitably,
they're mostly related to my work.
Acting.
It's only been a couple of years
since I've found joy in acting.
I would say five years at most,
despite having worked for 28 years.
And what's hit me
are my shortcomings and flaws,
the ones I didn't even notice
when I had no real drive for acting.
I started noticing so many of them.
After hitting the age of 30,
I can sense a real difference
in the way I absorb things.
Back in the day,
I was very sharp.
Or, at the very least,
I could mimic things.
But at some point,
it hit me how much slower I am.
For a while,
I wondered whether it was all too late.
If I'd realized too late just how much
I still needed to learn and grow.
Earlier today,
this very morning,
while I was cooking the curry,
I wondered if it was too late
and if I had enough time
to complete the dish.
"Will it taste good?"
At the start of all journeys,
you're bound to have so many thoughts,
but just have certainty…
because you're revisiting
what you've already experienced.
Right.
-"I've made curry before."
-Right.
"Others may not know it,
but I've walked this walk before."
"So I can walk it again."
If you just have that in mind
as you approach your goal,
you'll arrive fine.
And maybe,
you're cooking a curry of your own.
Yes.
Maybe that will ease some anxiety.
It's still curry.
Am I talking nonsense?
Not at all.
-Then, let's say…
-Yes?
You've made a thousand curries,
and you know it's something you can do.
What if you make a mistake
on something that is a total no-brainer?
-A novice mistake.
-Right.
Do you find you can forgive yourself?
I can't forgive myself, no.
-Right.
-It's hard.
Especially if others are watching
when I make such a mistake.
First things first, I'm embarrassed.
Right.
But mistakes open the door
to discovering and gaining new tools.
You never know
when these tools might come in handy.
-Right.
-Let's say I'm chopping onions.
If you have the experience
of cutting your hand,
you might seek out another tool.
Maybe a mandolin.
That's why we used a mandolin today.
Right.
These tools
will eventually prove their value.
Sure.
You're right.
Shall we cheer him up a little?
Sure, let's do that.
-Our own "fighting."
-Yes.
One, two, three.
I didn't say anything out loud,
but deep down inside…
I yelled "fighting" for you.
Right.
Did I receive it from you?
-You did.
-I did?
Did you not receive it?
No, I think I did. I received something…
Receive it this time.
Sure.
-Listen carefully.
-Okay.
One, two, three.
I almost broke my molars.
I heard a cracking.
Me too. I thought
that was the sound of my teeth.
I guess it was your teeth cracking.
Was today's meal good just the way it was?
Yes. It was perfect.
It's been a while
since I've had food
that felt like a proper meal.
It was so delicious.
You read my order and took it seriously.
You didn't just skim it
and serve a meal that sort of fit.
From beginning to end,
it's clear you put
so much thought into the food.
The curry you served me today
was so meaningful.
I'm truly grateful.
The thing with curry is,
because of its simplicity,
it's not normally considered a fancy dish.
But you've gracefully called this curry
a "proper meal."
Thank you for calling it that.
If you're finished,
I'll clear your plates.
Yes, thank you.
It's really good.
So good.
Could I ask for a to-go box?
Of course.
I have a manager and staff
who have worked with me for years.
-We'll pack some up for you.
-Perfect.
I would be so honored.
There's enough curry to feed ten people.
We'll just pack that up for you.
-That should be fine.
-You can do that?
Thank you.
-It's nothing.
-I'll also…
I'll eat it again tomorrow.
As you eat, you could compare
the taste to today's curry,
and I think
you'll enjoy tasting the difference.
Understood. I'll do that.
-This is our menu.
-Right.
We don't receive payment for our food,
but we ask guests to name their dish.
Of course.
Yes.
Curry.
Is it kare or curry? Kare?
I think either works.
I want to come up with something…
that includes "curry."
-Are you done?
-Yes.
Right.
"Imperfectly Beautiful Curry."
It's imperfect but seems perfect.
It seems incomplete
but somehow feels complete.
You gifted me with
an incompletely complete curry,
and, to me, it was simply perfect
and complete.
It was incredible,
so I thought I'd name it that.
"Imperfectly Beautiful Curry."
You've used the character "mi,"
which means "beauty."
I thought you would name it,
"Imperfectly Insane Curry."
-Right.
-Well…
-Thank you.
Thank you.
The food was delicious.
Here's the takeout you requested.
Thank you so much.
We'll enjoy this.
Thank you.
-Please take care.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
INCOMPLETELY BEAUTIFUL CURRY
"Just for today, I would like to try
the epitome of fine dining,
so I won't go home and crave
something like cockle bibimbap."
Our own clam sot-bap.
We'll redefine "fine dining."
The silent outcry of umami.
Introverted MSG.
Oh, hello.
Can you see it?
This is fascinating.
Deep sea, shallow sea.
It feels like I just got out of the water.
It's such a pleasure.
You should tell the clams.
It's a pleasure to meet you!