Look at the camera.
One, two…
Right now, you are too much
like a robot.
-If you could smile a bit…
-This is my brightest smile.
All right. Here's an idea.
Say "cheese" after I count to three.
-Got that?
-Chee… Okay.
Give me a nice and long "cheese."
One, two, three!
Cheese.
Cheese!
Your story is served as today's menu in…
The Blank Menu for You.
My lips are…
What do you think?
Well, they are…
They are uneven.
-Uneven Steven?
-Yes.
Still, saying "cheese" helped.
Kinda.
I look like I'm smirking at someone.
Looking down at someone?
Exactly. That's why even my lips
are looking down.
No way!
What a coincidence.
Today's order slip also mentions cheese.
-I'll read it out for you.
-Okay.
"Hello, Chef."
"Even with appetizers,
five small plates can make a full meal."
"I'd love to enjoy a variety of dishes
that bring out the best in each other."
"I care a lot about the order and pairing
of what I eat
like sweet and salty or tofu and kimchi."
"I'd like you to tie the dishes together
with cheese, one of my favorite foods."
"And I'd appreciate it
if you could avoid
using sugar and carbohydrates."
There it is.
That's a unique request.
It's not about having a regular meal.
The guest is asking you to prepare cheese.
You see, not everyone wants
the usual rice-and-soup combo these days.
Some prefer meals
with a different structure.
Unconventional meals
that reflect their tastes.
-Right.
-The guest has made various requests.
And the way they requested them
feels a bit Western.
Western?
How so?
Imagine walking into a McDonald's
in the US.
Their menu is layered with choices.
Customization.
People often ask to leave things out.
"Cook it this way."
They are designing a personalized set
through carefully chosen details.
-They know exactly what they want.
-Yes, precisely.
The order starts with a suggestion.
"Five small plates can make a full meal."
Meaning, "Cook five dishes."
-It also says, "Use cheese."
-Right.
Do you get it?
-It's very clear.
-Yes, very straightforward.
It makes you want to say that.
-The order slip gave me an idea.
-Okay.
-I thought of a kingdom.
-My!
What is this?
-It's French.
-Right?
How do you say it?
-What?
Let's just call it "Ordevre."
-It's French for "appetizer."
-Oh, appetizer.
HORS D'OEUVRE: FIRST DISH
IN WESTERN-STYLE COURSE MEAL
Today's guest must be from Cheese Kingdom.
Cute!
Maybe a princess or prince
with a tiny appetite?
A light-eating princess or prince
from Cheese Kingdom?
Yes.
This is the map of Cheese Kingdom.
There are five kinds.
Instead of going for overly niche cheeses,
I figured it'd be better to stick
with five well-known ones.
Using cream cheese,
I'm going to make gyeran-jjim.
And with mascarpone,
maybe a cheese mash? A cheese salad?
-A cheese mash?
-Yes.
I'm going to use Haloumi as well.
-I've never heard it before.
-Along with ajillo.
-Garlic oil.
-All right.
Haloumi with ajillo.
Mozzarella will be paired up with natto.
You don't like natto?
It's not that.
I'm not sure if those two could get along.
They are both fermented foods.
-So they are similar, after all.
-Yes.
With mozzarella,
I'm going to make natto noodles.
Lastly, Grana Padano in a salad.
Salad!
-Shall we start making them?
-Sure!
We have so many things to make!
-Yes, so we need to hurry.
-We do.
Do you have to put it there?
Let's hurry!
We are going to make gyeran-jjim
using cream cheese.
CREAM CHEESE
Take the gelatin and…
-Soak it in ice water.
-Okay.
Give it a firm squeeze.
-And…
-Plop.
MIX KATSUOBUSHI BROTH, SOY SAUCE, MIRIM,
AND CHEONGJU, AND ADD GELATIN
I think gyeran-jjim and cream cheese
would go really well together.
Like a proper cheesecake?
-Exactly!
-I think they are a great pair.
Now I'm going to add the mixture
to the cream cheese
and whisk to dissolve it.
POUR THE MIXTURE
INTO LIGHTLY MICROWAVED CREAM CHEESE
MASH UNTIL SMOOTH
Poke and swirl.
Keep going until it's smooth.
Should it turn completely creamy?
-It should come together as one mass.
-One mass.
-Slowly.
-Got it.
-One mass.
-It looks just like cheesecake batter.
-Right.
Imagine a cheesecake batter with no flour,
not baked but steamed.
That's the vibe.
Is it one mass now?
-Almost there.
-Okay.
-We will be straining it later.
-Oh, we will?
When we see how much solid is left behind,
we'll know if you stirred it well enough.
JELLY TOPPING SAUCE
SIMMER KATSUOBUSHI BROTH
WITH MIRIM AND SOY SAUCE
GELATIN
Drop that in.
It will thicken as it cools over time.
Is it starting to set?
I'm not sure yet.
But this feels kind of strange.
-The way the bits are floating…
-Yes.
I know it feels strange.
At one point,
it goes all soft and curdy.
Soft and curdy.
Has it become one mass now?
Yes, this is more than good enough.
Okay.
-Let's see.
-All right.
-Is it ready?
-Yes.
You don't see it?
Actually, I thought it would thicken more.
Right.
But it just went
from water to cooking oil.
It will get thicker than this.
-That was the signal.
-Okay.
It's telling us, "You can pour me."
-See that?
-I get it.
Soft and curdy.
-It looks like it's in…
-Pre-jelly stage?
CHILL THE JELLY SAUCE
IN THE REFRIGERATOR UNTIL SET
Now…
-Let's cool it in here.
-All right.
Next up. Do you know cheese fondue?
-Yes, you dip it.
-Right.
Let's try and make the sauce.
HEAVY CREAM
MILK
-Now…
-Yes?
I'll reduce it first,
then add butter and let it melt.
Sounds delicious.
It's best to keep the heat low.
Add everything in and take it slow.
Got it.
-Now this.
-Yes.
GRANA PADANO
This is Grapano?
Grana Padano.
-Put it in.
-Grada Padano?
Grana Padano.
Gra… Grana Padano.
That's right.
Now melt it slowly, bit by bit.
Okay.
-Reminds you of fondue, doesn't it?
-It does!
It's got the same thickness.
A bit more.
-This is pure cheese.
-Cheese.
A sauce made with just cheese.
Take your time.
This is butterhead lettuce.
BUTTER-SOFT LETTUCE,
SWEET WITHOUT BITTERNESS
The leaves are tender,
and it's got good taste.
Do you dip tomatoes in fondue too?
-Yes.
-That's got to be good.
It's better to trim off the tougher parts.
-Okay.
-Right up to here.
-That looks almost ready.
-Really?
How about softening it up a bit more?
Okay.
-It's become a sauce now.
-I see.
Now…
Do you like cheese?
I do. I love it so much.
-Here's your fondue.
-Thank you.
Try chilling the sauce
and dipping fresh salad into it.
It goes very well with ripe tomatoes too.
Eat it cold.
It goes so well with the cold lettuce.
You can serve the sauce warm like fondue
and dip blanched potatoes
or fresh vegetables into it.
Since we are serving the sauce
in a bowl today,
let's cool it down and serve it cold.
All right.
Cheese number three is mascarpone.
It looks like this.
This cheese blends well with tofu.
They have surprisingly similar textures.
-The recipe is quite simple for this one.
-Okay.
Dump it all in, give it a whiz,
and it's done.
-Dump, whiz!
-Yes.
Tofu!
-So silky.
-It really is.
This tofu has been lightly drained.
-That is 30 grams of mascarpone.
-All right.
Add 20 grams of tahini.
DRAINED TOFU, MASCARPONE, TAHINI,
SOY SAUCE, SALT, HEAVY CREAM
The guest asked for no sugar,
but just a little was added
because it was really necessary.
It wasn't added
to make it intentionally sweet.
That's right.
-Good enough.
-For the sake of the balance.
-We must not lie to the guest.
-Of course not.
Mascarpone is usually quite mild
and subtle on its own.
I see.
But when you mix in something like tofu,
it takes on a unique character.
Cheese isn't there to stand out.
It's there to support.
This dish is
more of a dessert-like appetizer,
so it goes nicely
with Shine Muscat grapes.
The firmer the grape,
the better it tastes.
-Dried persimmons.
-Okay.
They have a strong flavor,
so we want them in small slices.
The rich sweetness of concentrated fruit
works really well with cheese.
It looks amazing.
We are going to mix these together.
There.
It's best to start by making garlic oil.
If you rush to extract the flavor,
it won't taste right.
We need to cook it slowly.
Thoroughly.
Chili pepper.
-This one's a grilling cheese.
-Yes.
HALOUMI
-Gr-chee?
-What was that?
-Brie cheese?
-No, like Gucci.
It's luxurious.
Grilled cheese is fancy like Gucci.
-Luxurious?
-Yes.
Could you cook them
until they are golden brown?
No problem.
Oh no!
-You can just toss them around.
-Like this?
Hum a little tune too.
But they need to be flipped.
-Yes, I like that color.
-Right?
A guest might see this
and ask if this is burnt cheese.
-Then tell them this.
-Right?
"It's been browned to look just right."
I flipped this piece too late.
-I'm sorry.
-What's wrong?
I think I burned this one.
That is totally fine.
-What?
-It will taste even better.
Oops.
I'll heat up the garlic oil later
and pour it over the top.
Moving on to…
MOZZARELLA
Natto.
You smell that, don't you?
-Yes, the funky smell.
-Funky.
Natto tastes much better
when it's stir-fried.
WHITE WINE
-Let me.
-Sure.
-Mash the natto?
-Yes.
We are letting the acidity cook off
and turning it into a sauce.
That's it.
-Can I give it a try?
-Yes.
When I'm alone in the kitchen,
I end up doing all kinds of weird things.
It gets boring.
That grunt just now was one of them.
But that was straight out of an anime.
-I see what you mean.
-You know?
You could say
it's my way of coping with loneliness.
-It's about standing alone.
-I guess it's a battle of your own.
Of course.
I can't let the kitchen overwhelm me.
-I cannot give in.
-Right.
YUZU KOSHŌ
Plenty of pepper.
And then…
-We just have to stir it well now.
-It's starting to stick.
Take it off the heat for a while.
Can I? Okay.
-Do this.
-Right.
There's that grunt again.
Look how it stretches.
I bet you've never seen
anything like this.
Cheese and soybean.
Natto.
-Cheese and soybean…
-And noodles later.
-We will mix all of them.
-Noodles too.
Just a touch of noodles.
Just a touch.
Shall we sign it off here?
Cool.
Such a charming little alleyway.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
This must be the place.
"The Blank Menu for You."
I'm here!
Welcome.
Hello, everyone.
-Hello!
-Hi.
How charming.
-Thank you.
-A place of charm.
Let me show you to your seat.
Welcome.
-Hi there.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
OUR EIGHTEENTH GUEST
JUNE KANG
I feel like I have been given
such a precious seat.
This is a beautiful restaurant.
I can't believe a place like this exists.
I almost feel bad sitting here
all by myself.
Oh, do you?
-We are really fine.
-It's too…
Please make yourself comfortable.
Thank you so much.
-My goodness!
-Water and a warm towelette for you.
Why, thank you.
LIKE A ROSE, A MAGNOLIA, A LOTUS
YOU ARE FRAGRANT ALL SEASONS
AND STRONG TOO
This looks like me. Oh my!
It's gorgeous.
-Yes.
-This is awesome too.
-I'm very excited now.
-Oh, are you?
Well, big expectations
can lead to very big disappointments.
-Don't say that.
-If you could enjoy it as is…
Sure, I appreciate that.
-Let me check your order for you.
-Please.
First of all,
"Even with appetizers,
five small plates can make a full meal."
-That was your first remark.
-Yes.
You also wanted all the dishes
tied together with cheese.
"I'd appreciate it
if you could avoid
using sugar and carbohydrates."
Yes.
-That was your request.
-Spot on.
Your order slip brought to my mind
the princess from Cheese Kingdom.
Oh my.
The princess of Cheese Kingdom
with a tiny appetite.
I felt that someone just like that
would walk in today.
Oh my goodness.
To the light-eating princess
from Cheese Kingdom.
Is that too childish?
It's divided into five types of cheese.
-Yes, it's a fictional land.
-Cheese Kingdom.
This is amazing.
-So…
-Thank you.
-Wait just a moment, please.
-All right.
I really enjoy cooking too,
but it's my first time
just watching and waiting
like this.
I feel like he'll put a lot of care
into his food.
He strikes me as someone
who is incredibly meticulous.
Not at all, to be honest.
It is fascinating to see the process
of such beautiful dishes coming together.
Good.
This must be the Cheese Heaven.
Today is Cheese Day.
-A happy Cheese Day.
-Cheese Day!
So charming.
-Here is the menu you ordered.
-Thank you so much.
This is art.
All of the dishes were created
within the category of appetizers,
and I used five different types
of cheese throughout.
First, we have gyeran-jjim
made with cheese.
The next one features cream cheese.
Right beside it is Grana Padano.
The one that looks
like a potato salad on top
is cheese that's been chilled and set.
I see.
Take small pieces of the cheese
and enjoy them with some veggies on top.
The mascarpone
is mixed with Shine Muscat grapes
and dried persimmons.
-Impressive.
-It may come off as a bit intense.
The sweetness of the fruit
will balance it out.
I would love that.
You said no carbohydrates,
but I thought a little noodle at the end
wouldn't hurt.
So there's just a bit underneath,
and it's topped with mozzarella
and natto.
-Gosh.
-It's an unusual combination.
But I tried it before, and it worked well.
That over there is Haloumi.
It's a grilled cheese.
I've soaked it in garlic oil
for you to enjoy now and then.
Just something I made
from the inspiration you gave me.
You have made it come to life.
Princess of Cheese Kingdom.
Please enjoy, Your Highness.
Do enjoy.
Thank you very much.
-You know what, Chef?
-Yes?
I'm going to tie my hair first.
I want to focus on the meal.
Ready for battle.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I mean, just a little.
-Okay.
-Not too much.
-I'll start with gyeran-jjim.
-Okay.
Look at this pottery.
This is exceptionally cute.
The way the lid opens…
Oh dear!
It looks so good,
I'm not sure if I'm supposed to eat it.
You can eat it.
There's a light sprinkle
of lime zest on top.
Underneath is steamed egg
made with cream cheese.
And the one on top of it
is made with katsuobushi broth.
-It's jelly.
-Jelly?
Katsuobushi has such an appealing aroma.
The combination of cream cheese and egg
in a chilled steamed dish,
paired with the katsuobushi seasoning,
the jelly's texture,
and the cool temperature…
It's all so charming.
-I see.
-Yes.
It's a cool appetizer,
just right for summer.
Wow, this is…
It's incredibly fresh,
and the flavor
is quite elegant.
It feels like I'm dreaming.
I find myself
wishing this moment would never end.
It's a one-time-only dish,
made just for today.
-Is it?
-Yes.
-A dish just for me.
-That's right.
It's absolutely delicious.
Now, I'm going to move on
to the next dish.
Okay.
Just like you would dip into ssamjang,
you can place a vegetable
or a slice of tomato on the cheese.
-Just a bite first.
-Sure.
If you're a cheese lover,
just one bite will say it all.
I have to say,
that just launched me into the sky.
This flavor is just…
So,
I started off
with this amazing, elegant gyeran-jjim
and then moved on to the next dish.
I think that kind of flow really matters.
There is such a thing
as the right order of flavors.
Of course.
The fact that you planned that sequence
is just so charming.
For this dish,
you have paired the fresh texture
of the vegetables
with this Grana Padano
to create a wonderful combination.
The cheese on its own is so delicious,
you could honestly just eat it by itself.
I see.
So this pairing?
It goes without saying
that it's absolutely perfect.
This is right up my alley.
-I see.
-So…
I can't stop
eating this.
I see you've given the cheese
a firmer texture for this dish.
-You can, of course, serve it warm.
-Okay.
But even when served cold like this,
it has its own unique charm.
If you serve the cheese warm,
would it melt a bit?
Yes, just slightly.
-Would it spread?
-Yes.
-The warm cheese will have its own…
-Charm.
-It will taste great.
-Obviously.
-I'll move on to the next one.
-Of course.
You might not be too familiar
with this one.
I used mascarpone here.
As the mascarpone blends with the tofu,
I feel like it brings out
the tofu's flavor even more.
-It's a fruit salad.
-Okay.
The sweetness that comes through
as you chew
is the highlight of this dish.
I know you are not fond of sugar,
but I did add just a little.
Okay.
But I used xylitol
instead of regular sugar.
-Thank you.
-Only 20 grams.
-I appreciate that.
-I didn't use the whole pack.
I understand.
Yes, the combination…
It's unfamiliar, but not entirely.
Honestly,
I never would've thought
of this combination.
I was like, "Mascarpone?"
"The tiramisu cheese?"
I get it.
But here, you've paired it with sweetness.
-Yes.
-And it works beautifully.
Yes, I tried to explore
some new combinations.
You are a true genius.
Not at all!
You've come up with these combinations.
That is totally genius.
Well, I did come up with
a lot of new combinations.
I mean,
I feel incredibly happy right now.
-Her words just make you happy.
-I'm so happy.
-Don't they?
-Yes.
That kind of refined compliment…
I haven't received many like that.
Inside, I was more than thrilled,
but I couldn't show it properly.
I just kept twitching a smile instead.
I couldn't even make eye contact.
Not that I ever could.
What a charming meal.
I'm on a pleasant journey right now.
Let me move on to this dish now.
-Are these noodles?
-Yes, they are.
It's a wide udon-style noodle,
paired with cheese and natto.
There's spicy chili tucked inside.
-Inside?
-Yes, and scallions are sprinkled on top.
-So these are natto and cheese on top?
-Yes.
-What kind of cheese?
-Mozzarella.
-Yes.
The thing about cheese is
that it can get a bit too heavy,
but the chili inside really cuts through
all that richness
and brings balance to the whole dish.
-This is also an excellent combination.
-Thank you.
Just excellent.
I'm so…
Oh my God. This is too good.
And I have to say this about the noodles.
The noodles are very charming.
-Yes, they are udon noodles.
-Udon noodles.
You might want to try stir-frying them.
-Lightly?
-They are going to feel quite different.
Cheese pasta.
I mean it.
Chef, this is really…
Hold on, this calls for…
-An applause.
-Thank you.
-It's incredible.
-I've never been applauded before.
Really? It's incredible.
-It's so delicious, chef.
-Thank you.
I feared it might have been a mistake
to serve noodles.
No, you shouldn't.
I actually love noodles.
That's my problem.
I just love carbs way too much.
I see.
I only asked you to avoid using carbs
because I wanted to hold myself back.
Allow me to move on to the next one.
To me, this feels like a piece of art.
You can enjoy it piece by piece.
Garlic and grilled cheese.
The texture.
Haloumi.
This is also art.
Samchoon here grilled it
to a beautiful color.
-Getting the right color is important.
-Samchoon!
Did you grill this yourself?
Yes, I gave it a try.
-It's amazing.
-Really?
-Yes, really.
-That's a relief.
I mean, this is a gorgeous color.
It looks so appetizing.
That's kind of you.
A quick sear wouldn't have done the trick.
This pretty color comes
from grilling it with real care.
That's the perfect color.
Look how mouthwatering this is.
-It's beautifully grilled.
-This is just so…
It's so tasty.
I feel like I'm on a trip.
I see.
Chef,
this is my first time
experiencing such a variety of cheeses
in a single meal.
Oh, is it?
Being able to pair
such a variety of ingredients
in your own ways to create new flavors,
that's pure creativity.
You flatter me.
It takes a truly creative mind
to pull something like this off.
The truth is, whenever I cook for someone,
I'm always curious to find out
whether they enjoy the food or not.
-Always.
-Yes.
But guests don't usually give
real feedback.
Now that's a shame.
Honest feedback can really make
a cook's day, you know.
But giving feedback is not that easy.
I think it's something
you have to get used to.
If you haven't had much practice,
it's hard to do.
-You're right.
-Right?
I've been making meals for people,
but I don't think I've ever received
a lot of detailed feedback.
Not many at all.
So more often than not,
I had no idea
what kind of impression my food made.
But then you shared all this with me.
-Yes.
-How touching.
Being invited
to such a special occasion today,
I felt I had to express myself in a way
that was truly mine.
-Yes.
-And…
This food moves me to say something.
-Okay.
-You can feel the care.
So much thought went into preparing this.
-That's true.
-It really shows.
I'm grateful.
-My goodness.
-I'm really…
I'm so moved right now.
Funny thing is…
Samchoon said
that after reading your order,
he assumed you might be
a guest from overseas.
The level of detail was…
Your requests were specific and clear.
Did you catch that?
Yes, it sounded like
how you would place an order abroad.
I see. Okay.
-Did you live abroad before marriage?
-Yes.
So I was born in Canada.
Okay.
I was living in Canada until I was 23
and met my husband
during a visit to Korea.
-I read it in the papers.
-Did you?
"A Love Story for the Ages."
-At the time?
-Yes, well…
-That's right, I…
-Yes?
I followed the story closely.
Oh, did you?
I've been a fan
since your husband played Daebal.
-Oh, yes!
-No, before that.
-You were a fan?
-Yes.
Were you?
He was the best in The Terrorist.
I remember The Terrorist.
It was a year into our marriage
when he filmed that movie.
-That's when he did Sandglass as well.
-Of course. Sandglass.
-I guess I'm a bit of a relic myself.
-I guess so.
-You seem to know everything.
-Why do I remember Daebal?
This is exhilarating.
Yes, it really is.
-We share the same memories.
-Yes.
-I find that fascinating.
-I see.
I've felt that
since I started working here.
I think of that as
the scent of an era.
-Right.
-And that's…
The scent of a certain time really exists.
The first time I came to Korea was
in 1977, when I was just seven.
It was my very first visit,
and I never thought that one day,
I would spend 30 years of my life here.
Yes.
And being here today
got me thinking about cooking.
Korean food, to be honest, has been
a bit of a painful subject for me.
Because before that,
I had never actually cooked Korean food.
Okay.
But then I met my husband and…
-He's quite old-fashioned.
-Old-fashioned.
So I guess he assumed
I'd know how to cook Korean food,
at least to some extent.
But I didn't
because I got married
right after finishing university.
So I had to learn Korean cooking
from scratch,
all while trying to match
my husband's picky taste.
And he's not the type to eat
and compliment the food
or even say it's good,
regardless of my effort.
"This isn't how doenjang-jjigae
is supposed to taste."
"This doenjang-jjigae is not quite right."
I must have heard that hundreds of times.
So, to keep up with my husband's taste,
I had to put in quite a lot of effort
when it came to cooking.
Consideration stems from empathy.
And to empathize,
you have to understand
the effort that goes into cooking.
Today's guest…
has clearly done a lot of cooking.
That is why she can naturally
understand the work
that goes into each dish.
You can't be considerate without empathy.
They go hand in hand.
There are five cheese appetizers here.
Yes.
Would this be enough for you as a meal?
It's more than enough for me.
It's well-balanced
in both nutrition and portion.
It's just right.
For me,
this is the perfect kind of meal.
-Thank you.
-It is.
Today must've been therapeutic for you.
Yes, well…
As always,
compliments
are good for us.
I was really touched today.
You made me think
I should take the time
to savor my food like you did.
-My goodness.
-You are so inspirational.
-You are far too kind.
-I was really moved.
Please.
You invited me to such a precious place
and, even without knowing who I was,
prepared every dish
with such care and thoughtfulness.
It made me feel
deeply cared for and loved.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
This is all so heartwarming.
Thank you.
-I appreciate that.
-I'm touched.
Back when I used to run a restaurant,
I would say,
"Thank you for eating wholeheartedly."
-I'd say that to my customers.
-That's sweet.
-It always gave them a chuckle.
-Yes.
Eating takes a lot of energy, after all.
So, thank you for eating wholeheartedly.
-Thank you.
-Not at all.
Thank you for preparing
such a precious meal for me.
Where is my…
-Oh, your bag?
-Where is my bag?
Would you like your bag back?
-Thanks.
-No problem.
Our payment system
isn't working at the moment,
so we won't be charging for the food.
Instead,
in place of a bill,
we'd like to ask you
to give this dish a name.
I can't do that.
-Yes, you can.
-I have to pay.
-We insist.
-Yes.
-Gosh.
-Please sit.
-But it's such a precious meal.
-Please take a seat.
I can't just leave without paying for it.
That's fine.
-But this isn't a payment.
-It's okay.
-This isn't how we pay.
-It is for us.
-This is how we take payments.
-But still…
This place is full of surprises.
Is it?
I feel bad.
For the record, you're the first guest
who's reached for their wallet.
-Really?
-You are the first.
I mean,
what kind of restaurant
are you running here?
-Just a moment, please.
-Sure.
So you write down
all the dishes you've made.
That's right. That is our menu.
And the meal you had today?
It was a one-day-only offering for you.
Oh my.
We call it a menu,
but really, it's a collection of dishes
that can never be ordered again.
I see.
So precious.
Oh my goodness.
Dear me.
Gosh, this is…
Wow!
Everyone came up with such great names.
There are so many amazing dishes too.
Am I supposed to write the name down?
-Yes, your own name for today's menu.
-All right.
Are you done?
Okay.
Yes.
"A Cheese-Fueled Journey of Love."
Is that the impression you got?
-Yes.
-I guess you've been on a journey.
-All right.
It was a meal that really filled my heart.
My time here gave me so much peace.
All I can say is thank you.
We were touched by your energy
just as much.
-Yes, we were.
-Thank you.
-Can I take this with me?
-Of course you can.
-Please take it.
-I will. Thank you.
-Hold on to it, please.
-Thank you for everything.
I think
I'm going to carry this memory
with me forever.
So thank you.
We thank you for coming.
Have a safe trip home.
I think I've just been blessed.
Last day of business.
Business as usual.
"Bring back my old elementary school days
through the flavors of now."
-The age of the guest…
-Around my age, I think.
I'm going to take saury,
a fading memory from our tables,
and make a saury rice bowl.
Who could it be that went
to elementary school back in the old days?
Hello!
It definitely brings back old memories.
Would it be weird if I cried now?
Yes. Please don't cry.