No, no. You can't do this to me.
We had an agreement.
- What are you doing?
- Please?
I'm just trying…
- to look cute.
- That won't work on me.
Please, Handsome.
I need a spy.
After I do this, we'll call it even, okay?
Yes, I promise.
I'm Andres Malvar.
Were you the captain
of Marina Pacifica in 2004?
How did you find out all of this?
I told you I'm doing everything
I can to find Jun, remember?
Miguel, I'm planning
to take Mickey to the UK.
Okay. I think it's for the best.
No, no, no. There's something wrong.
You even had the entire house
surrounded with security,
and now you're okay with us leaving?
I have a new job for your group.
I'm sorry, sir. I would have to decline.
Is that why you turned down
the kidnap-for-ransom contract?
You probably thought
it wasn't connected to him.
That it wasn't connected to Raven.
[theme music playing]
I don't believe in coincidence.
There's just one thing that bothers me.
- Isabel Escalera said something to Andres.
- [unsettling music playing]
What is it?
Raven is alive.
[dramatic music sting]
So, she knew Raven.
[unsettling music continues]
[laptop chimes]
[phone thuds]
[man] I'm not the one you're looking for,
but I hope you find him.
[unsettling music continues]
One of you was the captain
of the ship Jun was on.
I'm going to find him.
[engines revving]
[Gab] Tomas.
Can you hear me?
Okay, good.
Do you see the woman
you saw at the restaurant?
[Rafael] Okay.
Breathe into it.
[whispering] Yes, I see her. She's here.
[Gab] There.
Okay, good.
[Gab] That's my dad's mistress, okay?
[Tomas grunts]
[Rafael] Breathe into it.
Hold it.
[Rafael] Feel the heat.
Embrace it.
Where's the yoga instructor?
[Rafael] Let's open up
that heart space, everyone.
Tomas.
Tomas, answer me.
[whispering] He's here busy teaching yoga.
Relax, okay?
[Gab] Okay. Okay, good.
You should always answer me.
I think there's something going on
between Shari and that yoga instructor.
You have to report everything to me.
I want to know their every move,
and how they interact with each other.
Report them to me.
[Tomas breathing heavily]
Copy.
But can you just check the camera?
I'm struggling over here,
No noise allowed here!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[Rafael] Okay.
[unsettling music playing]
[exhales heavily]
[unsettling music continues]
What did I get myself into?
Max.
I know that look.
You have something to say to me.
Just say it.
It's nothing, really.
I just wanted to check on you.
[patrons chatter indistinctly]
I'm okay.
Here.
They asked me to give you these cupcakes.
- [JB chuckles]
- [soft music playing]
Thank you.
You know,
they're really worried about you.
Actually, even me.
I mean,
- after what happened--
- Because of what happened to my dad.
[soft music continues]
I'm okay, Max.
For now, I'm managing.
[Max] Thank you.
Here you go.
Do you want extra cream or sugar?
[soft music continues]
It just reminded me of Sevi.
He stopped asking,
he'd just add cream and sugar.
He said he was good at making coffee…
so I just let him,
even though sometimes
I actually wanted it black.
[soft music continues]
[teaspoon clatters]
These go well with coffee,
no doubt about it.
- [chuckles softly]
- [utensil clinks]
Exactly. And as they say,
sweets make people happy.
[soft music continues]
[Rafael] And deepen the stretch…
And…
Whoo… Hold.
[Tomas pants]
[Tomas breathes heavily]
[whispers] Look, look, look…
Look, he's touching the…
He's touching the…
[Rafael] And release…
- He's touching her…
- Perfect.
Oh, wait. No, I got it wrong. My bad.
It's okay. It's fine.
There's still more later. Yeah.
Just make sure
your body cam captures them, go.
[breathes heavily]
Where is it?
I can't see anything. What is this?
Fix your body cam!
[playful music playing]
[grunts] There, can you see it now?
Nothing, just butts. What is this?
There it is, see? I'm fixing it now.
Tomas, get it right, okay?
[Rafael] Almost there…
Good job!
Nice.
Can you see it now? Can you?
[playful music continues]
[chuckles nervously]
[Tomas] He's smiling at me too.
- [Tomas] Yeah.
- Okay, and…
Release…
[Tomas exhales heavily]
[playful music continues]
[exhales heavily]
[grunts softly]
Uh… Bro?
Take off the shirt, man.
[mumbles, panicked breathing]
I agree.
Let your skin breathe. It's okay.
[Tomas] No, I'm fine. I'm just…
I'm just still getting used to this.
It's pretty hot in here.
[Tomas] But I'm fine.
- Tomas, what's going on?
- [Tomas] Hold on.
Hey, I can't see anything.
I'm okay, bro.
I just feel a bit dizzy.
I'll just step outside for a bit
to get some air.
Hey! What do you mean you'll go out?
Don't leave! We haven't
gathered any evidence yet.
I haven't recorded anything useful.
Tomas, stay there.
- [grunts] Ow!
- Oh my goodness!
- [Tomas groaning]
- Hey!
- Oh, sorry!
- You should've been careful.
- [Tomas groaning]
- [quirky music playing]
- Monkey!
- [Rafael] You should sit down.
Hey, Monkey!
- [Shari] Sit down first.
- She's so nice.
- [Shari] Huh?
- She's actually nice.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
Ugh! You're as annoying as ever!
Ugh!
- Have some water first.
- My goodness.
[Tomas breathing heavily]
[Rafael] You okay? Do you need a medic?
I told you to lose the shirt.
- No need. I'll be fine.
- Really?
- I feel better now.
- [Rafael] Okay.
[Rafael] You sure?
Phew.
[knocking on door]
- [Luis] Grandma.
- Mm-hmm.
[Luis] We're back.
[Esang] Oh, come in.
- Hey.
- Grandma.
[Esang] Alright.
[Andres groaning]
- I'll take care of it.
- Alright.
[phone chimes]
Hey, who is it?
Is it the captain?
Take a look.
[stirring music playing]
Oh, it's really from the captain!
- Mm-hmm.
- He finally replied?
Does that mean we'll finally find Jun?
[Luis] Whoa!
Hold on.
I'll message him.
You really fainted?
I didn't faint, I almost did.
Good thing Shari was there.
She saved me and gave me water.
Okay. And?
Well, here I am, still alive.
I'm not asking about you.
I'm asking how Shari
and her yoga instructor acted.
Nothing.
They weren't sweet with each other?
No.
What--[scoffs]
So, they're good at hiding it, huh?
Well…
Shari seems nice.
- What did you say?
- [quirky music playing]
- She's nice?
- Yeah.
Just because she gave you some water?
She didn't just give me water.
She even held the bottle for me.
[laughs]
And she's actually pretty up close.
Look, all I'm saying is…
they don't seem
to be doing anything suspicious.
They both seem nice.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- You know, Gab…
- [quirky music continues]
you're too judgmental.
- What did you say?
- I'm not finished.
You're too judgmental.
She's not doing anything wrong.
She's just doing yoga,
but you keep
thinking bad things about her.
You know, if I were you,
you should really get rid
of that nasty attitude--
What if I get rid of you instead?
The nerve of you to call me judgmental!
- Hey, wait!
- [scoffs]
I'll never forgive you for this!
Come on.
- Judgmental, huh?
- I'm just saying--
- Jerk!
- Gab!
[quirky music playing]
- [engine starting]
- [knocking on car door]
[engine revving]
[quirky music ends]
Yes, Captain.
Thank you so much. This is a big help.
Yes, be careful.
Thank you again.
So, what did he say?
Cristine Cunanan.
She's a social worker at BSWP.
Bureau of Social Welfare and Protection?
So, Jun was taken there?
That's what he said.
T-That means Jun is alive!
[soft music playing]
We'll finally see him again!
I have a feeling he's alive, Grandma.
[both laugh]
We'll finally see Jun!
Hey, Luis!
- [Esang] Come join us!
- [Andres] Come on!
- Let me join!
- Yeah, you're also family!
- [chuckling]
- Finally--Oh, sorry.
- I'm okay.
- We'll finally see Jun!
Oh, Jun…
- [chuckling]
- Thank you, God.
[Miguel clears throat]
- [taps]
- "I'm on my way."
[exhales deeply]
Miguel Tecson?
You're under arrest for
the murder of Jake dela Cuesta.
- [foreboding music playing]
- That again?
Haven't I told you?
- I had nothing to do with it--
- You were captured on CCTV
near the crime scene,
which contradicts your alibi.
I really had nothing to do with it.
[officer] Handcuff him.
[Miguel sighs]
[foreboding music continues]
You're under arrest for murder.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be provided for you.
Is that clear?
Christine.
Don't.
Listen to me.
Go back to our son.
- I'm serious.
- What are you talking about?!
Christine…
Wait. I'm still talking to her!
Go back to Mickey.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Keep an eye on Mickey, please.
You're out of your mind!
Of course, I'll go back to Mickey,
but after I make sure you go to jail.
- Take him.
- Christine, please.
I'm not kidding, Christine.
Take care of Mickey.
Go back to him!
[music turns dramatic]
Boss, we waited until morning,
but nothing.
[dramatic music continues]
"Nothing"
Of course, nothing.
He got arrested.
He's now in jail.
The cops beat you to it.
If Tecson rats us out,
it'll be the end of our group.
Why don't we just show the video
of him fleeing the crime scene?
That will solve our problem.
Oh, really? Are you dumb?!
You're stupid!
We need the money, okay?
Because if we fail to get it back,
we'll get in trouble with our bosses.
Do you understand?
[dramatic music continues]
Yes, boss.
What's our plan, boss?
[dramatic music intensifies]
Go to his ex-wife's house.
That way, we'll know what's happening.
[dramatic music crescendos]
How are you, JB? Any news?
Still the same.
I'm okay.
That's good. I have news.
Good news, actually.
I found this program in the US
called cutting-edge gene therapy.
It's for patients like you.
What kind of therapy is it, Trina?
Is it another clinical trial?
But this time, it has promising results.
It can stop the progression
of your disease.
[somber music playing]
I know it's not a cure,
but it's a great help
for your quality of life.
So, US?
Mm-hmm.
You'll stay there for a year
for therapy and follow-up.
One year?
[somber music continues]
It's still your decision, JB.
But I want you to know all your options.
[somber music fades]
- Greg, this is--
- General Nocum.
Of course, sir.
We have a contract for your group.
Sir, if this is about the
kidnap for ransom operation,
my answer remains the same.
You know, I was thinking
you rejected the contract
because it was too small.
But Greg, this is
a high-priority operation.
[unsettling music playing]
Kenji Lee.
He murdered Benicio Avila,
a prominent senator
and was rumored to run for presidency.
And now, he's on the run.
Last I heard he was hiding in Kaigen.
Greg, he's a wanted criminal,
but we need him alive.
[unsettling music continues]
[chair scrapes]
- Gentlemen.
- Look.
If we fail to bring Lee home,
we won't know the motive
and mastermind behind Avila's death.
He has information that could
change the election's outcome.
Greg, this is not just about one man.
This isn't about Avila.
This is for our country.
[music turns suspenseful]
It's getting harder, JB.
I'll find a way. I'll get you out of here.
So, you're telling me,
there's a possibility
I could get reinstated in service?
This is Kenji Lee,
a highly-trained assassin.
This is a capture mission.
We need him alive.
That is, if we bring him alive
together with the information he has.
We're not just going to face a killer.
I'm sure there's a huge
organization operating there.
- [whooshing]
- [kick lands]
He's here in Kaigen.