You're getting married right away?
And you give me what's mine.
And you finally let me be.
Thanks for this.
We're business partners now.
- Let's call it even?
- Yeah.
[both chuckle]
Who from El Cano is protecting you?
I don't know what
you're talking about, bastard!
- [gunshots]
- [Dexter whimpers]
Manuel…
Manuel Aguinaldo.
Manuel Aguinaldo?
I have AI prediction tools.
We can find out what he'd look like today.
Max, I think I've seen him before.
You said that you remember
you have a brother, right?
All I can remember is
that I was wearing a bonnet,
and I was waving to this boy.
It's Jun.
I found him.
- Really?
- Marcelo knows Jun!
[both laugh]
[theme music playing]
[pensive music playing]
Isabel Escalera
wants to tell you something.
"The Raven's alive".
[unsettling music playing]
[Greg] This contract is crucial.
I know, Noah.
The whistleblower that we're protecting…
He can tell us who's
the leader of El Cano in this country.
So we can't afford to fail here.
Lion and I will keep a lookout.
You lead them.
Just make sure you move
the package to the safe house.
[unsettling music continues]
Raven.
Is there a problem?
Nothing, sir.
I know you.
You have conviction,
that's why I'm entrusting the team to you.
Be careful.
[unsettling music continues]
All units, proceed as planned.
- [rapid gunfire]
- Aah!
[Enrique] They killed all of our comrades!
I'm going to kill all of them!
How did they find out where we are?
[gunshots]
There's a traitor among us!
[pensive music playing]
[gunshots]
[loud booms]
[indistinct chattering]
[Enrique groaning]
Aah!
[unsettling music playing]
So, have you killed all of them?
Package secured.
The job's done.
[unsettling music continues]
[breathes heavily]
[gun cocking]
[groans, huffs]
Let's go.
[unsettling music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[huffs]
[groans]
[Greg] You sold out
the lives of your comrades.
You'll pay for that, Manuel.
[unsettling music intensifies]
- [keyboard clacking]
- [unsetting music fades]
[foreboding music playing]
[Max] You had someone watch Kenji, right?
So there's nothing for you to worry about.
I hope that Manuel Aguinaldo
really leads us to El Cano.
Well…
He's not on social media.
I can't find any
articles about him either.
But you know what?
His name sounds familiar.
Yes.
Because he was listed in the army.
A soldier, huh?
[sighs] I really hope he's
the person we're looking for.
[foreboding music continues]
[man] Sir, the boy seems decent.
I asked around,
and no one said anything bad about him.
[cicadas chirping]
Who are his parents?
What's their business?
Where did they graduate?
[man] He's an orphan, sir.
A man from Recto adopted him.
He calls him "uncle".
Recto?
[man] Yes, sir.
The thing is,
his uncle got involved in a scam recently.
But he got off scot-free.
He seems used to it.
Are they planning to scam my daughter?
Let them try.
[dramatic music swells]
[Tomas grunts] Ow.
Jeez.
[breathes deeply]
[Philip] Tomas Guerrero.
The groom.
[ominous music playing]
Can we talk?
[Tomas exhales deeply]
[pensive music playing]
I'll give you enough
money to get away from here.
Leave my daughter.
Sorry, sir. What?
Are you deaf?
Get away from Gabriela.
I'm sorry, sir, but we're getting married.
You can't stop us now.
[pensive music continues]
Don't you dare hurt or
use my daughter for money.
[scoffs] You think I'm after her money,
just because we're poor?
Sir, if you have nothing nice to say,
let's stop this.
- Let's call it a night.
- Wait.
[Tomas sighs]
If it's not money, what is it?
Why are you marrying my daughter?
With all due respect, sir,
but isn't Gab asking
you to give her freedom?
To erase you from her life?
[chuckles wryly]
Sir, this isn't just
about getting inheritance.
We can find other ways to earn money.
[scoffs] But Gab
wants to get out of your life
because it seems
that's what you want anyway.
Aren't You and Shari are
already living a happy life?
Your daughter is hurting
every time she sees you together.
I mean, damn. Come to think of it.
We even had to put on a fake wedding
so she can get away from you.
[chuckles]
What kind of father are you?
[pensive music continues]
Shit.
[pensive music intensifies]
[pensive music crescendos]
[reporter on video]
At least 30 corpses were found
at an estate in Kaldiva Island.
The identities of
the victims are still being confirmed.
There is an ongoing
territorial dispute for the said island
among the Philippines
and other Asian countries.
The authorities are still
investigating the incident
to determine the motive
and people behind the murders.
[unsettling music playing]
[phone ringing]
Yes, General?
[Mariano] Have
you been thinking about my offer?
[unsettling music continues]
Yes, sir.
If we come to an agreement,
you know what to do.
[unsettling music crescendos]
A fake wedding?
Sir, can I ask a favor?
Can you not tell Gab? She'll get upset
if this doesn't go her way.
You mean, getting
her inheritance and freedom?
[breathes sharply]
Yes, sir.
She won't forgive me
if she finds out about this.
[stirring music playing]
Okay.
Fine.
Go ahead with the wedding.
You're going to fool Gab?
We are going to fool her.
[chuckles wryly]
Wait. Won't it hurt Gab even more?
Only if she finds out.
I'm not as bad as you think.
She will never know.
[stirring music continues]
Go on with the fake wedding.
And…
this conversation never happened.
[stirring music continues]
[Tomas breathes deeply]
[foreboding music playing]
Sir.
[dramatic music sting]
[foreboding music continues]
[sighs deeply]
Thank you.
I was right about giving you that job.
Thank you, sir.
[chuckles]
[Enrique] Let's have some coffee, okay?
[cup clinks]
[foreboding music continues]
[Enrique exhales loudly]
It's confirmed.
Greg Paterno is the Contractor.
General Mariano has him
on call for off-the-book missions.
He has an excellent team.
I know Greg.
I worked with him before.
You worked with Greg?
[exhales sharply]
We parted ways during our last contract.
Greg has skills.
But he doesn't think big.
He doesn't see things the way I see them.
And I'm sure…
he keeps taking
contracts to go against the El Cano.
Why?
[music turns suspenseful]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Greg huffs]
[Greg sighs]
The license plate of the motorcycle
I saw at the cemetery was fake.
We don't have any new leads, Greg.
Manuel is really cunning.
[sighs sharply]
[suspenseful music continues]
He has stirred up
a lot of trouble for El Cano.
- Timor, the masterlist.
- [music turns foreboding]
He also had Muñoz killed.
I'm sure he didn't take
those contracts for money.
[foreboding music continues]
What do you want me to do, sir?
[chuckles]
Nothing.
You've done your job.
I'll handle Greg.
Sir, you know
that I'll do anything for you.
That's the least I can do
to thank you for helping me
ever since I became an orphan.
[foreboding music continues]
I know.
[chuckles] I know.
Sit.
[chuckles]
[foreboding music builds, fades]
- [clamoring]
- Thank you.
You can count on me.
[chanting] Gov.
Selo! Gov. Selo! Gov. Selo!
Hello!
[chanting] Gov.
Selo! Gov. Selo! Gov. Selo!
At your service.
[clamoring]
Gov! Gov!
[clamoring continues]
- [Andres] Gov!
- Thank you.
Number 2 on the ballot.
[panting] Sir.
It's okay.
How are you?
How can I help you?
Sir, I know that you remember me.
I want to know.
Who were you talking to at
the restaurant the other day?
[dramatic music playing]
Were you following me?
That was my brother, right?
I repeat.
- Were you following me?
- Am I right or wrong?
Was he my brother?
[dramatic music builds]
[Tomas exhales loudly]
Tom, wait. Relax, okay? Calm down.
Calm down, okay?
You're being dramatic.
You don't know how
Gab's father can be, Uncle.
Don't mind him. It doesn't matter.
He's not going to be
your real father-in-law anyway.
Yes, I know but…
- Just relax.
- They're here. They're here.
- That's her father?
- Yes. Be nice, okay?
Sir, this is my uncle.
- Hi.
- [quirky music playing]
- [both chuckle]
Oh, I didn't know
Gab's mother is so young.
I'm not her mom.
- [Tomas chuckles awkwardly]
- Is that so?
- [inhales deeply] Sir.
- Well, I have to say,
you have great taste.
[breathes deeply]
You've still got game.
Uncle, okay, that's enough.
- Why?
- Sir, I'm sorry.
- He's just--
- Tomas.
Sir, can we talk privately again?
- Talk privately again?
- Mm-hmm.
Why? Have we ever talked privately before?
[chuckles awkwardly]
- Sir, it's about…
- [footsteps approaching]
[gentle music playing]
[gentle music continues]
[clears throat]
Oh.
[gentle music continues]
[breathes deeply]
[exhales sharply]
[music becomes quirky]
[Tomas clears throat]
[panting]
[quirky music continues]
[man] Help is here!
We will be giving out
help from Governor Selo!
- [cheering]
- [car horn honking]
[man] You will all receive help!
[clamoring]
Please fall in line!
There's enough for everybody!
[man] Don't push each other!
[man] No need to worry!
There's enough for everybody!
[clamoring]
- Come on!
- Friends, get yours here!
[crowd exclaiming]
Hey, hey, hey!
- [pensive music playing]
- [people clamoring]
[man 2] Thank you! Thank you!
[crowd clamoring echoes]
[sentimental music playing]
- [sentimental music builds]
- [crowd clamors distantly]
[sentimental music slows]
[crowd clamoring indistinctly]
[sentimental music fades]
[soft uplifting music playing]
Is that you, Jun?
A-Andres?
[soft uplifting music continues]
[young Kiko] You can do better than that!
[young Andres] Should I play louder?
[young Kiko] Alright!
[Young Andres]
You're making fun of me again!
[Young Kiko laughs] Oh, yeah!
[soft uplifting music swells]
I've spent a long time searching for you.
- [inaudible chatter]
- [soft uplifting music continues]
[soft uplifting music continues]
[soft uplifting music swells]
[soft uplifting music fades]
I now pronounce you, husband and wife.
[suspenseful music playing]
I finally found my brother.
My grandson Jun!
- Really? Congrats!
- Congrats!
How is Andres's brother
related to Manuel Aguinaldo?
Manuel adopted him.
You already knew about his brother,
but you just let Andres
struggle looking for Jun?
All I knew was if Andres
managed to find his brother,
I would find Manuel, too.
[suspenseful music continues]
That's Manuel Aguinaldo.
…in position.
Come on, let's hurry.
- [car engine revs]
- [tires screech]
What's going on? Why are you here?