[Miguel] We got a lot of money
for my son and for your grandma.
We can't leave this behind, Andres.
No matter what happens.
Sir, I think we've
already passed by here! We're lost.
What are you doing, Tomas?
Sir, elders say we have
to turn our clothes inside out
when we're lost in the woods, right?
- Tomas, don't move.
- Sir?
- [hissing]
- Sir.
- Tomas!
- Sir! Aah!
[thud]
[Tomas exclaims in disgust]
If nosey Tomas, isn't your type,
what's your type then?
A plant.
- [chuckles]
- I got none.
[gallops]
- The money!
- No!
We can still catch him! Let's go!
- [Rita shrieks]
- [loud thud]
Come on!
[Rita] Let go of me!
[Rita screaming]
- [Rita] Let me go!
- Andres, no.
Let's go.
[theme music playing]
- [loud thud]
- [sobbing]
- Ow!
- Get up!
- [sobbing]
- [goon grunts]
[Raul] shh…
Are you working with those thieves, Rita?
Tell us. Hmm?
[Rita breathing heavily]
- I see.
- [gun cocks]
You told them about
our hideout, didn't you?!
- Fess up!
- I don't know anything.
And I don't care
what you're talking about!
[Raul chuckles]
Sir Sameo was so good to you,
yet you still betrayed him.
- Good?!
- [laughs mockingly]
You blinded us with your money!
You manipulated us and
poisoned the minds of the kids,
just like you did to my brother!
[sobs, breathing heavily]
You didn't want to join me and Emer.
- You want revenge?
- Where's my bro--
- [thwacks]
- Aah!
- [whimpers]
- [goon] You dare raise your voice?
[goon] Shut up and stay down.
Andres, we don't have to get involved.
- Hey!
- No.
We have to help her. Come on.
[Andres] Come on.
- [Rita screaming]
- [blade swooshing]
- [thwacks]
- [Rita whimpering]
[suspenseful music playing]
[whispers] Don't.
Andres, let's just go. Come on.
[sobs, breath quivers]
[gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
- [Rita screams]
[gunshots]
[screaming]
Go!
Shark!
[radio static]
- Shark!
- [radio static]
We're engaging hostiles!
Tell me if you need backup.
Give me your coordinates.
[gunshots]
Jaguar!
[JB] Team. Do you copy?
Jaguar.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Rita wails]
[gunshots]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [muffled gunshot]
- [thud]
[sobs, exhales loudly]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[music fades]
[exhales] Targets are down.
[somber music playing]
Okay.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Rita sobbing]
[somber music continues]
[Miguel exhales]
You can go home now,
wherever that is, okay?
Let's go, Andres.
[somber music continues]
[Rita crying]
[Monching] Keep your eyes peeled!
Stay alert!
They can't have gotten far.
Come on! Move!
[suspenseful music playing]
Team.
They know we're here.
They're hunting us down.
Well, shit.
They want the money back.
Shit.
Team.
Team!
Sir, maybe the comms are down.
The signal here is unstable.
[both panting]
Where did Champ go?
[Max exhales]
Maybe he went that way!
Come on!
[Max] Let's climb up.
[suspenseful music crescendos]
Champ!
[Max grunts]
[brooding music playing]
[Max panting]
He's not here!
[huffing]
Where did the gunshots come from?
No idea.
[Max exhales]
The money…
You should've firmly
secured the rope, Max.
It was your job
to keep an eye on Champ.
I did secure it.
But I got distracted
because you brought up
the topic about love.
We could still chat while
you're watching the horse!
[Max sighs sharply]
You know what, there's nothing
we can do anymore.
- We've already lost Champ.
- No, we'll find him.
We're going to find him and get the money.
Let's go this way.
[brooding music continues]
[Tomas grunting]
[Tomas] Ow.
[Tomas grunts]
[brooding music continues]
[Tomas exhales]
[Tomas] This is…
for the money.
[Tomas grunting, panting]
[brooding music continues]
[sighs] We're getting farther
away from the exit point.
Maybe we should just let it go.
Are you still wearing
your comms earpiece?
Huh?
[Gab] It's gone.
Shit.
We've lost our comms!
Fuck!
[Gab huffing]
You know what?
It's over. We've lost our comms.
We won't be able
to contact them anymore.
What about the money, Max?
Are we just going to let it go?
I need the money, Max. Please!
[sighs deeply]
Let's go find Champ.
I'm sure he's just around here.
Damn it.
Didn't I tell you to go home?
Why are you still here?
I'm not going home.
I'm looking for my brother.
He works for Sameo.
And you?
Who are you guys?
Are you police? Soldiers?
Whoever you guys are,
I'm guessing you're enemies of Sameo.
You should get out of here.
Come on.
[Rita] Please help me.
[Rita breathes heavily]
This is Emer.
He's my brother.
If I'm right, that you're after Sameo,
did you go up to their hideout?
Did you see my brother?
Did you see him? Is he still alive?
[sobs]
Your brother's still too young.
He is.
[crying]
They poisoned his mind.
No.
We haven't encountered any kids.
So, for your own safety,
I suggest you go home.
Just go, okay?
It'd be dangerous if you kept going.
[Tomas]
I'm giving the money to my uncle, sir.
Those bastards won't take
this money from me.
[grunting]
[Tomas] You okay, sir?
[JB exhales heavily]
[grunts]
[bag thuds]
- [groans]
- [bag thuds]
Drop your guns!
[foreboding music playing]
Drop them!
[Tomas chuckles]
Do we believe him, sir?
Drop them, or I'll blow your heads off!
Whoa, calm down!
Drop those bags, too!
Why, do you own these bags?
Just drop them!
- Whoa!
- I'll shoot you!
Calm down, kid.
Do you even know how to use that?
- You might hurt yourself.
- Drop them now!
Now, chill out, kid! I'll drop them.
Don't push me, or I'll kill you!
[Tomas]
Where do you live? How old are you?
- Mind your own business!
- Whoa.
What happened back at Sameo's hideout?
You two are here, which means…
you fought him and his men.
Did you kill him?
[breath shaking]
I'll assume you did.
In that case, you have my thanks.
This world is rid of one more villain.
[somber music playing]
And if you can't help me,
I understand.
[breathing heavily]
[footsteps receding]
[clicks tongue, sniffles]
[sighs]
Andres, let her be.
[somber music continues]
You know exactly what it's like
to lose a brother.
Right?
[exhales]
I hope she finds her brother.
[somber music continues]
I'm going to kill you!
Drop those bags!
Calm down!
Do you even know how to fire that?
- Just do it!
- Don't shoot yourself.
Dude, just relax!
I'm going to drop them down.
- This kid…
- Do it now!
I'm going to kill you!
You think I'm afraid of you?
Alright, I'll drop everything I have.
- Tomas…
- I'll shoot you!
Just do as he says.
- Look.
- Get this over with.
One wrong move, and you're dead!
Look at me-- Whoa!
[gunshots]
[tense music playing]
- [body thuds]
- [Emer groaning]
- Help!
- [Tomas] Quiet!
- [JB] Tomas--
- Argh!
- You stupid kid!
- They're here--
Stop being so stubborn!
- You're making this difficult!
- [muffled] Ouch!
- Hold him down, Tomas!
- [blows landing]
- You--
- Let me--
- Restrain him!
- I don't have the rope.
[JB] Stop hitting his head,
and restrain him.
You punk! How dare you point a gun at us?!
- Think you're brave, huh?!
- Tomas, just tie him up!
Think--Think we're scared of you?!
- [blow lands]
- Go, I'll handle him.
[Emer muffled] Help!
- Just go!
- Let me go!
- Stop--
- I said, let--
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
Tomas, I'll take it from here. Now, go!
- Patrol the area.
- [coughing]
- See if his group is there.
- You--
[morose music playing]
- Look everywhere, Tomas!
- [groaning]
[coughing]
[breathing raggedly]
[coughs]
- Let me go--
- Stop talking.
[voice straining] Help--
[breathing heavily]
Just do what we tell you,
and you won't get hurt.
- Understand?
- Let go of--
Help!
- Somebody help!
- Shut it!
[Emer breathing heavily]
[Max] Look.
We'll find the exit point down this way.
- Let's go.
- No, Max.
Let's find those bags.
Gab, we won't find them again.
Just let it go.
No, Max. We need to find them, come on.
[foreboding music playing]
[sighs] We heard gunshots, remember?
I'm sure they're following our trail.
Well, where are they?
Because I don't see anyone.
Max, if you don't need the money, I do.
It's easy for you to leave it
because you don't need it.
Gab, look. Our comms are down.
We lost contact with the group.
If we don't get moving,
we'll be left behind.
[foreboding music continues]
Well Max, I'm going to find those bags.
[Max] Gab!
[JB exhales heavily]
[Tomas] Shark, the area's clear.
I looked everywhere, and I found no one.
Good.
[Emer gasping]
[Emer grunts]
- [tape rips]
- [groans]
[spits]
[breathing heavily]
We split up to find your group.
When the others find you,
they'll kill you.
Want me to break your face?
Want me to kill you?
[scoffs]
[Tomas chuckling]
- [Tomas] So cute.
- [grunts, clicks tongue]
[Emer grunting]
How old are you, kid?
Seventeen?
Eighteen?
[somber music playing]
[exhales deeply] Sixteen.
You can still do
many things with your life.
Stay away from your group.
Why? Who do you think you are, huh?
What do you want me to do?
And for what?
To make things worse?
For those rich bastards
to keep stepping on me?
If I'm with my group, I can earn money.
I can achieve something.
And I'll be able to fight.
[somber music continues]
I know that you need money.
We also need money. We're all the same.
But you're still young.
Leave that group.
Before it kills you.
[somber music continues]
[JB exhales deeply]
No, I will kill you. Especially you.
- [Tomas chuckles]
- [music turns dramatic]
Shall we go, sir?
[clears throat] Let's leave him here.
[panting]
You're leaving me?
Do you think you can get out
of this place alive?
[Emer] We will kill you. Especially you.
- [Tomas chuckles]
- I'll blow your brains out!
Bye, bye.
Bye. [laughing]
[labored breathing]
[dramatic music continues]
The path down the back
is slippery because of the rain.
The only way they can get out
is through Sitio Magdalo.
[dramatic music crescendos]
[woman] They will give us 5,000 pesos
if we finish this.
Maybe Sameo is really
running in this election.
I hope he wins
so we can get more financial aid.
He'll just steal money
and you want him to win?
Well, we'll have money
if he wins so why not?
You know what?
Your mind has been consumed by money.
Do you not care about the lives
of the people who got ruined by drugs?
Amado, your son decided
to ruin his life with drugs.
Why are you blaming Sameo?
What did you say, you bastard?
- Huh?!
- [grunts]
People like Sameo only exist
because of bastards like you!
Say it again. Say it again!
Amado. Pokyo.
Stop it.
We shouldn't be fighting.
- He started it.
- Oh.
Benjie's here.
Please, let's just keep our mouths shut.
Good day.
We need your help.
Uh, sir, anything for you.
[dramatic music playing]
Andres.
When we reach the community,
we can't let them see these bags.
But we can't leave them
no matter what happens.
Because this…
is for my son.
And yours is for your grandmother, right?
So we need to be careful.
Outsiders?
No one's passed here, Benjie.
[dramatic music continues]
We'll stay here for now.
We need to wait for something.
[dramatic music continues]
[dramatic music crescendos]
All of us make our own decisions in life.
It's up to you whether it's
right or wrong.
It depends on your principles.
I hope she finds her brother.
You know, Andres,
you can't save everybody.
You're blaming yourself for
what happened to your brother.
I wonder where they are now.
We're near the exit point.
Let's just rest here, Tomas.
Tell your men
to block all the exits
around the mountain.
We'll go there. Let's meet.
[yelps]
- Gab!
- [screams]