We need to get
the master list quickly.
- [gas hissing]
- [alarm blaring]
You need to get out
of that area.
None of the other areas
have toxic gas.
Copy. Andres,
go get the hard drive.
I'll take care
of the situation here.
[gunshots]
- [thuds]
- You bastard!
[objects clatter]
- [kick lands]
- [groans]
[blow lands]
- [objects clatter]
Who are you, huh?!
[gunshot]
[body thuds]
What is this, dognapping?!
Yes! [giggles]
You found Bud and Dy!
That's the package.
Up! Good boy!
[man] Hey! Stay there.
- Don't try me! I'll shoot!
- You're not getting away!
Bye! Sorry!
I'll text you!
[Miguel sobbing]
Papa, stop crying.
Don't worry.
I'm a big boy now.
- [gunshots]
- [metal clanging]
Are you from CIB?!
Where's the master list?!
I won't give it
to you willingly.
If you want it, you'll
have to kill me first.
[theme music playing]
- [gunshots]
- [object clatters]
[grunting]
- [kick lands, blow lands]
- [body thuds]
[gunshots]
[body slams]
[grunting]
[blow lands]
- [head smacks]
- [body slams]
[blow lands]
- [grunting]
- [objects crashing]
- [blow lands]
- [grunts, thuds]
- [alarm blaring]
- [tense music playing]
[heavy crash]
[tense music continues]
[breathes heavily]
Max, what is the status?
[tense music continues]
[keyboard clacking]
[Max]
JB, we have a problem.
Someone's attacking Andres.
[alarm blaring]
[tense music continues]
[panting]
Max!
Where are you?
[Max] I'm back.
JB!
[blows land, grunting]
[gunshots]
[body thuds]
Andres! Andres!
Andres! Wake up!
[JB] Andres. Andres.
Andres, wake up!
- [alarm blaring]
- [tense music continues]
Andres. Wake up!
Andres!
[alarm blaring]
Andres! Andres!
Andres! Wake up.
- Wake up, please.
- [coughs]
Max, did you get the hard-drive?
- [coughing]
- [JB] Let's go.
- [JB grunts]
- [Andres groans]
[coughs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Andres groans]
[suspenseful music crescendos]
[cicadas chirping]
[exhales heavily]
[pensive music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
Hello.
[pensive music continues]
[sighs heavily]
Let go of him, Dad.
I can't believe this.
You should've just asked
me for your dog.
I don't care about you.
Mama gave BudDy to me.
Hey, let him go already.
- Hey!
- [exhales heavily]
[clears throat] Alright.
I'll let this slide
But one more thing, Gabriela,
I'm warning you,
I'll go all out next time!
What is he to you?
Your boyfriend?
- What?!
- No way. Boyfriend?
As if!
Albert, go ahead, let him go.
[pensive music continues]
Hey, hey, you, yeah, you! Huh?
You'll get what's coming to you.
Okay?
I know what you look like!
Don't you ever come back!
The two of you better
not cause trouble again.
If you do,
you'll end up in big trouble!
[pensive music continues]
Now leave!
You're so slow!
He's young.
[pensive music continues]
[door opens]
We got it.
[breathes deeply]
[chuckles softly]
- [alarm blaring]
- [dramatic music playing]
[coughs]
[grunting]
[groans]
- [alarm blaring]
- [dramatic music continues]
[groaning]
[dramatic music continues]
- [alarm blaring]
- [dramatic music continues]
[keyboard clacking]
- [computer chimes]
- [groans]
[upbeat music playing]
[computer chimes]
- [upbeat music continues]
- [server shuts down]
[laptop whirring]
Come on.
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
Max, just do that tomorrow.
Rest up first.
No, I can crack this tonight.
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
Just go. I got this.
I'll let you know
when I've cracked it.
[keyboard clacking]
I'll leave Max to you.
I have to go.
Alright.
Keep me posted.
I will.
[keyboard clacking]
[JB sighs deeply]
[laptop beeps]
- Hi, Nanny!
- Hi, Mickey!
Hi, Mama!
Hi! [Christine chuckles]
- How was your day?
- It was fun!
I rode a bike!
Then, we bought
some snacks!
Really? That's good!
[chuckles]
Mickey,
now go to your room.
You need to rest, okay?
Okay.
Thank you for today, Papa!
This is my gift for you!
- Wow!
- Let's do this again, okay?
Yes.
Sure.
Okay. Good night.
Go upstairs now.
Nanny?
- Good night.
[Tomas] I was compromised!
[smooches]
They saw my face!
[smooches, coos]
Are you even listening?!
Gab!
You didn't even tell me
what the package was!
You could've informed me
it was two big dogs!
Didn't you learn anything?
A package can be anything.
Money, people… Anything!
- Right?
- I could've used a heads-up!
How hard is it to say,
"Tomas, sorry.
They're too heavy.
I need help carrying them"?
I could've prepared properly!
He's so dramatic, isn't he?
So freaking dramatic!
What are you yapping for?
The mission's done.
They're here now.
You could've told me
- that was your father's house!
- Shh!
[whispering]
You're stressing them out.
Bud and Dy hate being stressed,
so keep it down.
You had me steal from your dad!
What did you say? Steal?
Steal what?
Excuse me?
They're mine dogs, okay?
I didn't steal anything.
Besides, my father
is much worse!
He's been luring people
into gambling since forever.
My father is evil, okay?
No need to feel guilty.
You know, my uncle
isn't a saint either.
But I'd never steal from him.
Well, we're different!
- Damn right, we're different!
- So?
Because I won't compromise
a teammate like you just did
and leave them
in enemies hands!
I hope you understand that.
I already paid you, alright?
Paid? Oh, right.
[chuckles dryly]
Screw you.
Alright, Bud.
Say goodbye now.
Goodbye!
Goodbye! Get lost!
Right?!
I missed you!
Technically, what you did
was kidnapping.
Biologically, I'm still
Mickey's father.
I have a right to see him.
[Jake laughs]
[claps]
What's so funny?
You.
You're a joke, Miguel.
There's nothing funny
about what I said.
Mickey is my flesh and blood.
And you?
What are you to him?
You're just my wife's lover.
Leave us alone.
Leave my family alone!
Stop calling Christine.
And stop seeing Mickey.
Just leave!
Tell him not to get
on my nerves
before I snap.
You have no right to
come near our family.
And if you still won't stop,
I'll take them far away.
[Christine] Jake.
What did you say?
I didn't quite hear that.
You know I have the power
to take them away if I want to.
Babe!
Somewhere you can't find.
You'll lose your mind
before you ever find us.
- [blow lands]
- [Jake grunts]
- Miguel!
- Yeah?! Just you try!
- Damn you!
- [blow lands]
- [blows landing]
- [Jake yelps, grunts]
[Christine] Enough!
- [blow lands]
- [body thuds]
- Well?!
- Stop!
Just you try!
You good for nothing bastard!
You're worse!
Just you try to take
my family away from me,
I'll kill you!
I will kill you!
Just go away!
[sobbing] Jake.
- [Christine sobbing]
- [tense music playing]
[phone buzzing]
Hello, ma'am?
How can I help you?
[Taki] Andres, Esang begged me
not to tell you,
but I think you should know.
Emil won't leave her alone.
[suspenseful music playing]
[uneasy music playing]
[reporter on video]
A warrant of arrest
has been issued against
religious leader Rema Muñoz
following the multiple
corruption, child abuse,
sexual assault, and most
recently,kidnapping cases
the Department of Justice
filed against him.
Muñoz has been
hiding from authorities.
And according to reports,
an influential family is
allegedly protecting him.
[uneasy music continues]
[dark music playing]
[vehicles revving]
Okay. I'll let Father know.
Problem?
A hold departure order
has been issued against you.
You can't leave the country.
[Rema sighs deeply]
[Rema sighs]
[line rings]
[Domingo] Hello?
Domie.
I thought you've
smoothed out everything.
We can't leave the country.
I'm sorry.
I did everything I could
to block the warrant, but…
But what?
It's all out now,
everything you did.
People are outfor blood,
your blood.
I know.
It's a good thing
that I'm prepared.
Remember, Domie.
If I go down,
I'll drag you down with me.
I'll arrange a way
for you to exit the country.
Just lie low and wait
until the situation dies down.
[dark music continues]
Jerry.
I'm already being hunted…
…by all the law enforcement
agencies throughout the country.
I'm sure there's also
a big bounty on my head.
People will be coming
for me soon.
Father…
Where do we go now?
[sighs deeply]
[dark music continues]
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
[sighs sharply]
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
Ugh!
It's not working!
[huffs]
[JB] Eat first.
[Max gags]
Does your stomach hurt?
I've tried all the
decryption keys I know.
None of them worked.
This hard drive is secured
by a strong encryption system.
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
I asked if your stomach hurts,
but it seems you didn't hear me.
Come on. Just grab a bite.
[Max gags]
- Max, are you okay?
- [Max clears throat]
Yeah, I can manage.
[keyboard clacking]
I should be able
to crack this!
I've done this
a million freaking times.
But I can't decode it.
- Take a break first.
- JB, what the hell?
Max, you haven't eaten anything.
You obviously aren't
feeling well.
You need to rest.
Get some sleep.
I can't sleep.
Not even a wink.
You know what?
I might as well do this.
I can't fall asleep anyway.
- [pills rattle]
- Take two tablets.
They will surely
knock you out.
Get some sleep, Max.
- [tongue clicks]
- [Max sighs softly]
All your reports are useless!
Get lost!
[Andres] Emil.
You don't learn, do you?
Why won't you leave
my grandma alone?
Easy there.
You're too tense.
Acting like a victim
when you've also drawn blood.
I already paid
for what I've done.
I've served my sentence.
That's not enough!
You took my brother's life.
I'll make you pay with yours!
[tense music playing]
Why don't we finish this
once and for all?
Meet me tomorrow. 6PM.
I'll finish you off.
[tense music continues]
Thank you for staying
at La Vida Royale.
- Thank you!
- Enjoy!
- Hi, Ma'am Ellen.
- Hi, Clara!
Hi, babe. Don't worry.
I'm on my way home.
[gunshots]
- That's it!
- Andres can't beat us now!
I'll finish you off, Andres.
I'll make sure the Manalastas
won't ever mess with us again.
How?! By taking another life?!