For Jaguar!
[gunshots]
[both grunting]
Max!
[knife slashes]
[gunshots]
[body thuds]
Whoever gets in my way will die!
This is for all the lives you ruined!
- [loud roar]
- [objects shattering]
Proceed to exit point.
Target eliminated.
Rest now. Rest now.
["Liwanag Sa Dilim"
instrumental music playing]
[theme music playing]
His call sign suited him perfectly.
Jaguar.
[melancholic music playing]
Patiently stalking his prey.
And before you even know it,
you've already been caught.
His precision as a sniper was insane.
No one could beat him.
[melancholic music continues]
[chuckling]
Someone can.
Gin and beer.
- [chuckling]
- Idiot.
Just kidding, Doc. I love you.
Tomas.
This drink…
…it was Miguel's favorite, right?
Every time I see it, I remember his face.
[chuckles]
I miss that old guy.
But Miguel…
he would do anything for his family.
[melancholic music continues]
Especially for his son.
Even if it meant giving his life.
[melancholic music continues]
He wasn't perfect.
But he was a good man.
And a good father.
[melancholic music continues]
[Tomas sighs heavily]
He always listened.
He was the one…
the one who balanced our group.
[melancholic music continues]
A good friend.
Someone who never left you behind.
[melancholic music continues]
[Andres exhales deeply]
[Greg] For Miguel.
For Jaguar.
- For Miguel.
For you, Doc!
Wherever you are,
I hope there's lots of orange juice!
[chuckling]
[music becomes triumphant]
[triumphant music continues]
- [music ends]
- [Armando] Job well done, Greg.
You dismantled one of
El Cano's biggest operations.
Thank you, sir,
but this is just the beginning.
Their group has scattered
all throughout the Philippines.
Their leader? Still in our country.
Still nameless.
That's why this group
has a long way to go.
But you've showed everyone
that nothing is impossible.
Thank you, sir.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[birds chirping]
So slow!
Hurry up! The attorney is waiting for us!
[exhales heavily]
Where are we going?
Good news.
The annulment is moving through.
Let's drive!
- I'll drive--
- Ouch!
I said I was…
Ugh, that hurt.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I am.
Um…
What if we don't?
What do you mean?
What if we don't do it?
- Do what? Drive?
- No.
Let's not go through with the annulment.
Why?
Let's just continue…
[clears throat] being married.
Because?
Because I love you. [chuckles]
- [slaps]
- Ouch!
- [chuckling]
- [light-hearted music playing]
[chuckling] What was…
- [chuckling] I'm going to cry.
- [chuckling] Huh?
[laughing]
I think I love you. You're really cool.
What was that?
I can't feel my face.
[laughing]
Ouch.
- [laughing]
- That hurt.
[light-hearted music fades]
[gentle music playing]
[rake scratching]
Andres!
Hmm?
M-My grandson!
It's Jun!
[gentle music playing]
[breath quivering]
[Esang sobbing]
[music turns somber]
I just came to visit so
that you won't look for me.
[somber music continues]
[somber music fades]
When I saw you at the camp…
I thought it was my imagination.
Is that why you didn't look for me?
You chose to prioritize the children.
That was your mission, right?
Mm-hmm.
It was for the kids.
I know.
You know, because of that…
I feel like I woke up.
I remembered everything you told me.
That I was a victim of human trafficking.
So why was I
supporting people like Manuel?
I remember…
Whenever I would look
at the kids we picked up.
I fully believed that they were
going to have a bright future
because of what we were fighting for.
Because I'm the same as them.
[birds chirping]
But when I met you…
something changed.
You made me feel that kids like me…
they still have a chance
to turn their lives around,
as long as they had siblings, parents,
friends to be with, or a brother…
that wouldn't give up on them.
[somber music playing]
But despite that,
It's hard to let go of…
the mindset I grew up with.
I've changed.
[somber music continues]
I'm no longer
the brother you used to love.
Time has changed me.
There are things
we can no longer take back.
[somber music continues]
[sighs deeply]
You're right.
And I understand.
But…
Have you considered starting over here?
[somber music continues]
Um…
You know…
You spent
your whole life searching for me.
Just so you could meet and hug me.
But now…
allow me to change myself for you.
I just don't know when or how.
Or if I can do it at all.
So, Andres…
Go back to Grandma.
[music becomes tender]
No.
[tender music continues]
I want to watch you leave.
Until you're completely out of my sight.
So at least…
I'll know which direction you're headed.
Not like the last time I lost you.
[Andres] Mm?
[tender music continues]
[sniffling, breath quivers]
Take care.
[Diego sniffles]
[Andres sighs deeply]
[tender music continues]
Diego!
One day…
if you change your mind.
Or when you're ready.
You're always welcome here, okay?
[tender music continues]
[sighs deeply]
- [sniffles]
- [music fades]
[sniffles]
Max.
I decided…
to finally get treatment in the US.
That's good.
[JB sighs]
As of now, the treatment
is still experimental but at this point…
what else can I possibly lose?
[Max] Mm.
Remember when
we almost failed our mission in Cerdova?
I really thought that was it for me.
But we kept fighting.
JB, we've always lived on the edge.
But our biggest enemy…
is ourselves.
It's fear.
We're able to fight war.
Why not fight sickness?
[sentimental music playing]
JB.
Make it a mission to save yourself.
Yes, ma'am.
[both chuckle]
[sentimental music continues]
Thank you.
But seriously, get well soon.
You're already really special to me.
Max.
I may not show it to you,
but I hope you know
that you're special to me too.
Thank you.
I'll get better. I'll be better.
I won't stay too long in America.
I promise you that.
And I'll be here.
[sentimental music swells]
[sentimental music continues]
[waves crashing]
- [birds calling]
- [sentimental music fades]
What do you plan to do now?
I'll go back to our place
up in the mountain.
Can we really leave
this kind of life behind?
I bet we'll miss it.
[JB chuckles]
The body pain?
[JB laughs]
You think we'll miss that?
[both laugh]
Sir!
[chuckles]
Sir.
[chuckles] Andres.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
[grunts]
- Hello!
- Hi.
Hello. [giggles]
- The ladies are here.
- How are you, Gab?
[giggles]
I'm good. Don't worry about me.
Hi, JB.
- You good?
- How are you?
- Wow.
- Hello.
Wow, Max, your bangs are still straight.
Your lucky I still hugged you.
[laughter]
You know, I'm glad we met up.
Especially before JB leaves.
[Gab] What?
- Is he going on vacation?
- Where are you going?
Uh…
I have a personal
matter to attend to in America.
America?
My shoe size is 10.
- Size 10?
- Just go with him.
[Tomas] Great idea!
Contracts.
- Contractor.
- Contractor!
Good to see all of you.
Well?
Are we ready for a new contract?
[birds chirping]
(Sings gibberish
to the tune of "Liwanag sa Dilim")
♪ You are the light in the dark! ♪
["Liwanag Sa Dilim"
by Pablo of SB19 playing]
- You sang it wrong.
- Yeah.
- How are you, sir?
- How are you?
You seem to be in a good mood.
["Liwanag Sa Dilim" continues]
[pin clicks]
[grenade clatters]
[loud explosion]
[cheering]
[phone buzzing]
[tense music playing]
Snake, I need a new sniper.
Someone as good as the last one.
Let's meet in person.
I'm on my way.
[thrilling music playing]