[grunting]
[JB] Where is my money, you bastard?!
Answer me!
Your dad's case is a lost cause, JB!
I found out something.
General Dexter Tienza.
The El Cano is protecting him!
[singing "Wedding March"]
Hey, you look like a different person!
- So handsome!
- [Tomas chuckles]
What are your favorites?
- Do you have pets?
- Dogs.
Don't tell me you have two big dogs.
No, they're small dogs.
Their names are Mini and Tiny.
Mini and Tiny? [chuckles]
You know, it's just funny
how people seek balance,
only to ruin other people's lives.
I love Philip.
- We love each other.
- Go. Keep saying that.
You might actually believe it.
Miss?
Is Ma'am Marichu in?
Sorry, she's not here.
[theme music playing]
I'm sorry about Lyn.
She's just following protocol.
I'm Marcelo.
But you can call me Selo.
[unsettling music playing]
Andres.
You want to talk to my mother?
Yes.
I have something important to ask her.
Can I ask what it is about?
It's about an adoption
certificate that was sent to me.
About the boy Manuel Aguinaldo adopted.
[unsettling music continues]
Interesting.
People usually come here to look for work,
apply for scholarships,
or seek assistance.
Not to inquire
about adoption certificates.
But, anyway, Mama's not here right now.
[unsettling music continues]
I'm just hoping your mother can help me.
You see, I'm looking for my brother.
His name is Francisco Malvar.
We call him Jun.
[unsettling music continues]
[unsettling music builds, fades]
Do you want me to take you home?
No need. My father's waiting for me.
[car door closes]
[rain pattering]
[Tomas clears throat]
Hello, sir. I'm Tomas.
Um…
Thank you so much.
- Need a ride?
- No, sir. I can manage.
- Thank you.
- Are you sure?
- [Agnes] Bye, Tomas.
- Bye
Take care.
[diners chatter indistinctly]
[Tomas sighs]
[keyboard clacking]
- "HOW ARE YOU?"
- [beeps]
[rain continues pattering]
"I love your father." My ass!
Like I'd believe you, bitch!
That fucking bitch!
[slams]
[breathing angrily]
[phone chimes]
[Tomas] How are you?
- [indistinct chatter]
I'll just come back some other day.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll tell Mama about
your concern when she comes back.
Okay.
Hang on.
Sir, we need to go
before traffic gets bad.
Alright. Prepare the car.
- Okay.
- I'll be right there.
If you need to contact me,
here's my number.
I'll be going now.
- Take care.
- Thank you.
[dramatic music sting]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music builds]
[unsettling music fades]
A new contract?
Yes.
Secretary Ella Barrios of BENR?
She needs protection.
Agency's orders?
No, she reached out to me herself.
So…
VIP protection?
Covert VIP protection.
Even her security
detail mustn't know about it.
Secretary Barrios
has made a lot of enemies.
This has become bigger
than her environmental advocacy.
She's challenging
long-standing industries.
Mining corporations,
logging firms, energy companies.
Which means,
she's made enemies out of big names.
Including the Velasco Mining Corporation.
They have a pending
case for mercury contamination.
- They're also facing complaints
- [dramatic music playing]
for hiring minors to work in mines.
Secretary Barrios is
ordering for their shut down,
so Velasco retaliated with a libel case.
And yet, she's still standing.
Yes, and not only has
she upset private businessmen.
She has also caught
the ire of some government officials.
[dramatic music continues]
People like her are rare.
Bribery and threats don't work on her.
That's why she's a target.
I'll take the job.
Thank you, Greg.
- [exhales deeply]
- [dramatic music builds, fades]
[grunts]
Pain level?
[inhales deeply]
Um…
Six out of ten?
[inhales, exhales deeply]
It depends. Sometimes, I wake up in pain
at level seven, eight, or nine?
[doctor] Your muscles are stiff
and you have a limited range of motion.
While Doc Trina is away,
maybe you can visit me more often.
[JB huffs] Doc…
can't you give me anything right now?
Anything.
So I can move properly.
This is an intramuscular relaxant.
Injectable?
[doctor]
Yes, but it's for emergency use only.
I don't want you to rely on it
because this is addictive.
Don't worry, doc.
I won't be dependent on it.
Should we go with… I'm thinking either
smoked salmon crostini's
or truffle quiches? What do you think?
I think quiche is good,
but salmon is better.
That's true. It's much lighter, right?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Salmon it is.
- Mm-hmm.
And for dessert,
should we go with panna cotta
or is it too basic? I don't know.
Whatever you like, my love.
[Philip] I'm okay with,
whatever our baby likes.
[both chuckling]
[Gab] Baby?
[hesitates] Gab.
What?
What's this?
[Philip] I was about to tell you.
Uh, but I was just--
Gabriela.
Dear!
[Shari sighs]
Hey.
- Just a sec.
- Yeah, go talk to her.
[Philip exhales]
[somber music playing]
Gabriela.
[sniffles]
[Gab exhales]
What?
What more do you want?
I want you to understand.
I did.
I fully got it.
Your family is complete now.
- Our family.
- No, no.
I'm not part of it.
You know that very well.
Because you don't want to.
You don't want to accept us.
How, Dad?
[somber music continues]
How?
Teach me how to accept your relationship.
The two of you are happy together.
But my mom is dead!
- [Gab sniffles] She's dead!
- Dear…
- [Gab cries]
- I can't bring her back.
I know! Exactly!
And it's been eight years,
but I'm still hurting every day!
[cries, exhales]
I miss her!
[somber music continues]
[sobbing]
[sighs deeply]
No.
[somber music continues]
Let's just forget about this. [sniffles]
[cries]
This father-daughter
shitty thing that we have.
I'm done.
[sobs] Just give me her rest house.
Give me her house, all of her things.
I want her memories with me.
Just forget about me.
You'll never hear
anything from me ever again.
Just pretend like I never existed.
Like I never was your daughter.
[Gab cries, sniffles]
- [Gab sobbing]
- [somber music continues]
[exhales deeply]
No.
You won't get what you want.
[somber music fades]
- [engine idling]
- [phone ringing]
[Joris] Hello.
I've sent someone to meet you.
He'll give you all
the intel on Dexter Tienza.
We traced the address of his mistress.
You better be telling the truth.
You think I'll screw you over again?
I could barely stand up
from the beating you gave me.
I'm glad you know.
[engine idling]
[ominous music playing]
You can go.
[ominous music continues]
[ominous music fades]
[cicadas chirping]
Okay.
I can walk away without any of it.
Fine!
[soft music playing]
You'll get what you want.
Your inheritance,
Your mother's house…
[Philip sighs]
O-Okay.
[exhales]
Okay. When will…
When can you get the papers done?
You'll only get it…
once you're married.
What?!
Me?!
A husband…
What?!
A wedding…
Wha--
Without that…
you won't get anything.
[mellow music playing]
[Gab breathes heavily]
F-Fuck!
- [breathing deeply]
- [mellow music continues]
[sobbing]
[mellow music fades]
- Mm-hmm!
- Huh?
- Success!
- Yeah! [laughing]
Now, you can start, cooking.
Oh, I thought you meant get married.
- Alright then.
- You're too much!
- [Luis] Just joking, Grandma.
- [Esang] It's done now.
[Luis] Perfect timing,
the sinigang's ready.
[Esang] Oh, you're here already.
Oh…
- So, how did it go?
- [exhales heavily]
Did you talk to Secretary Marquez?
[Andres sighs deeply]
No.
Oh.
I ended up talking to his son, Marcelo.
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you know what I noticed?
He has a cigarette burn here.
[dramatic music playing]
Do you mean the same kind as Vincent,
The one who went missing with Junjun?
Yes. Didn't Vincent say
everyone he was with had the same mark?
[dramatic music continues]
Mm!
It feels like,
something's really off here.
With everything happening, it's like…
Could it be…
the BSWP people are messing with us?
After everything…
Was Secretary Marquez
the one who adopted Junjun?
And Marcelo?
Could he actually be your brother, Junjun?
[dramatic music continues]
Let's meet ASAP.
This is it.
[dramatic music sting]
This is what we've been waiting for.
[dramatic music continues]
- I'll call you.
- Oh, son!
- Ma!
- Oh, you're here already.
How are you? Hmm? [smooches]
Come on, let's eat, I'm starving.
Ah, Ma, I just had
to take care of something.
Enough with work, son. Let's eat first.
Oh, by the way,
Lyn said someone came by looking for me?
Ma, people are always looking for you.
Nothing new there.
Well, you're right, but who was it?
[dramatic music intensifies]
No one, just someone asking for aid.
[dramatic music crescendos]
Maybe he sent his people to trick us,
making it seem like Junjun's gone so…
they wouldn't have to return your brother.
[pots clattering]
I really don't know, Grandma.
But if you think about it…
Marcelo should be around Junjun's age?
Oh!
So, did you see…
Does he look like your brother?
Is there any resemblance?
They were fair-skinned like Jun.
[Esang grunts acknowledging]
and by now, he would be
about the same height too.
But doesn't a person's
appearance change as they grow up?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, exactly.
Wait, did you introduce yourself?
Did he… did he recognize you?
Well,
he was young when he disappeared,
so maybe he doesn't remember.
[breathes deeply]
[foreboding music playing]
But Andres,
why were you sent
that adoption certificate?
It feels like, it was intentional.
[foreboding music continues]
[breathes deeply]
I don't know.
Maybe someone from
BSWP with a conscience sent it?
Maybe…
they know Manuel Aguinaldo
adopted someone else, right?
And maybe Secretary Marquez
is giving us a hint.
Who would care that much,
and how would they even know about Jun?
[foreboding music continues]
I really don't know anymore.
This whole situation is so confusing.
The more unanswered questions we have,
the more it feels like
we're losing Junjun all over again.
[foreboding music continues]
[foreboding music intensifies]
[Esang sobs quietly]
[foreboding music continues]
Their family's whole now.
They even have a new child.
And you know what he said?
I'll only inherit Mommy's house
if I get married.
Then maybe I should just marry you.
I just have this feeling.
I feel like I've seen my brother before.
Dexter probably
knows the leader of El Cano.
There's no way such
a big group could be taken down.
- [groaning]
- [taser buzzing]
- Don't move!
- [gunshots]
[grunting]