[Greg]
You'll go to the summit of Mt. Talimba.
That's where you'll find Sameo Patel.
[gunshots]
- Target eliminated.
- It's confirmed
- this is Sameo Patel.
- Good job.
Congratulate everyone for me.
Whoa! That's a lot.
- Woohoo!
- [Miguel laughing]
- Eagle, Sparrow, go on ahead.
- Let's meet there, JB.
- Take care, guys.
- Okay!
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- Yup!
- [laughing]
- Yeah!
We have a problem.
The house was attacked.
Sir Patel is dead.
They took almost all of the money.
Surround all the mountain's exits.
Kill anyone who isn't from here.
Copy. Let's go.
- Emer! Use your gun!
- [rapid gunshots]
Ah!
Take this!
I can do it, sir. I'll kill them!
- [gun clacking]
- [whimpering]
- Do it.
- All units, listen up.
Stick to the GPS, especially now.
We're moving slowly because of the loot.
If we lost comms, everyone
proceed to the exit point.
- Copy.
- Copy that.
Copy.
[theme music playing]
Miguel, what are you going to do
with your money? [panting]
I'll use it for my son.
- [birds chirping]
- [pensive music playing]
No matter how much there money is…
it's still not enough for my son.
Mickey is such a nice kid.
Even though I'm a failure.
I'm actually very lucky…
to have such a nice kid.
He still loves me.
[pensive music continues]
He takes after you.
Well, I hope not.
Please, no. [chuckles]
I hope he doesn't take after me.
[chuckles]
[thud]
[pensive music continues]
- [grunts]
- [bag thuds]
[bag thuds]
[music becomes suspenseful]
[grunting]
Are you okay, Tomas?
I'm doing great, sir.
This is actually quite relaxing.
If you want, I'll even carry your bag.
- Alright.
- Just kidding.
[grunts]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [grunts]
- [bag thuds]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[suspenseful music crescendos]
[grunting, panting]
What about you?
[birds chirping]
You don't have a wife yet.
You don't have kids either.
What will you do with this?
I have to buy back a piece of land.
I will return there with
my brother and my grandma.
You really amaze me, Andres.
You never give up.
I made a promise to my father.
If I don't keep that promise,
he might haunt me.
[both chuckle]
[Miguel exhales sharply]
[somber music playing]
We got a lot of money.
We'll divide it equally
for my son and for your grandma.
Okay?
We can't leave this behind, Andres.
No matter what happens.
[somber music continues]
- [music fades]
- [birds chirping]
[bag thuds]
Team, all units,
how are you?
Shark, everything's okay.
There's nothing to worry about.
[Gab] We're not okay.
What?
What happened to you?
Where are you?
We're still trekking.
The money's so heavy. We're exhausted.
I knew it.
You're slowing us down.
Do you need help?
Hey, Tomas. What did you say?
Thanks for your concern,
but you didn't have to belittle us.
You jerk.
I'm concerned about the money
you're carrying. Not you.
You bastard!
I'm not worried about you either.
I'm worried about the money.
And for your information,
we won't share this with you.
This is just ours.
[birds chirping]
[Andres grunts]
[JB] Eagle.
Will you be okay?
We can meet somewhere.
No need. We can handle this.
We'll meet you at the exit point.
Copy that.
- Well, Tomas?
- Let's go.
I'll leave these to you.
Help me carry them.
I was just joking.
- You said you can carry them.
- I can't, sir.
Did you hear what he said?
He's such a jerk, right?
That guy is so annoying.
He never changes.
Just let him be.
I'm sure he's also struggling
to carry his bags.
That monkey is the worst!
At least we have Champ here.
You've changed.
You're not getting annoyed.
I'm being serious.
Something's changed about you
ever since you came to HQ.
You've become more carefree.
I wonder why.
You've become easygoing.
Maybe.
I don't want to be nosy, but…
honestly, I don't know much about you yet.
[pensive music playing]
Let's just say…
I'm trying to move on.
From a man?
My ex-fiancé.
He died while on a mission.
Shit.
Sorry.
You know, life goes on.
I just try to think about it like that.
[pensive music continues]
[Gab sniffles]
- Are you okay?
- [Gab] Hm?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Um…
I just remembered my mom.
She died in a car accident.
But it is, what it is.
[sighs] You know what they say.
The price of love is grief.
You grieve forever.
[pensive music continues]
[Gab huffs]
I'm sorry about your mom.
It's okay.
Well, loving is expensive.
Right, Champ?
- Yeah, Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- [horse snorts]
- [horse clomping]
- [pensive music fades]
[grunting]
[Tomas grunting]
[groans]
- [Tomas exhales loudly]
- [JB] Tomas.
Sir?
Are you okay?
I'm okay, sir.
A-okay!
- [pants]
- [huffs]
[Tomas whimpering]
[grunts]
Hmph!
[grunting]
[exhales sharply]
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
[Miguel grunts]
[exhales sharply]
[Miguel panting]
[gasps, grunts]
[water sloshing]
[panting]
Let's take five.
[Miguel clears throat]
[panting]
Miguel.
I just want to ask.
Are you still upset with me and JB?
- [panting]
- [somber music playing]
[sighs deeply]
To be honest?
It really doesn't matter anymore, Andres.
Because…
I understand that we all have our reasons
for each of our choices.
Right?
[somber music intensifies]
- [water splashes]
- [somber music fades]
- [thud]
- [exhales]
Stay here, okay?
Good boy.
[Max grunts]
It took me along time, you know.
And it was so hard.
There were times when I wanted
to follow him to the other side.
But look at me.
I'm still here. Still fighting.
I'm proud of you.
Even though we aren't that close.
[both chuckle softly]
- How about you?
- Hm?
How's your love life?
[snorts]
- Nope.
- Really?
Really.
So, if nosy Tomas isn't your type,
what kind of guy do you like?
The serious type?
[chuckles]
- I'd rather date a plant.
- [chuckles] A plant?
Come on, Gab.
Well, love is all fun at the beginning.
But when it falls apart,
it'll ruin you forever.
It'll wreck your whole world.
I was raised by that kind of love.
So I'm already a mess to begin with.
You think I can handle a boyfriend?
[scoffs]
Hey, I'm not a masochist.
[pensive music playing]
- [Tomas huffing]
- [music fades]
[birds chirping]
[grunts]
[groans]
Sir, wait.
[bags thud]
- Tomas!
- Hang on, sir.
[JB] Hey! Where are you going?
- Tomas!
- Just wait, sir.
What are you doing?
Sir, I think we've passed here before.
I think we're lost.
Tomas, don't you trust me?
I do trust you, sir. But I remember
this fence! I've seen it before!
You know what Tomas?
That's just the fatigue speaking.
You're delirious.
- No, sir.
- We're not lost. Let's go.
[backpack thuds]
What are you doing, Tomas?
Sir. Elders say we should turn our clothes
inside out if we're lost in the woods.
Tomas, stop this nonsense.
- Let's go.
- Okay, I'm done.
Tomas!
- Don't move.
- Sir?
- I said, don't move!
- Why, sir?
- [foreboding music playing]
- Sir?
- [snake hissing]
- Something's on my shoulder.
Don't move.
[snake hissing]
Sir?
- Tomas!
- Sir! Aah!
- I'll kill it!
- [gun cocks]
- No, no!
- But sir!
- [snake hissing]
- [foreboding music intensifies]
[panting]
- [exclaims in disgust]
- [music fades]
Let's go.
I'm not going back there, sir.
[Tomas exclaims in disgust]
We're almost at the exit. Come on.
[both grunt]
Are we going that way, sir?
Yes. What about it?
But the snake went that way.
- Sir…
- Why? You scared?
N-No, sir. But…
You go ahead. You have the GPS.
I'll be right behind you.
[JB] Just avoid the snakes.
[grunts]
[ominous music playing]
Aah!
- [leaves rustle]
- [thuds]
[gun cocks]
Let's go!
- [ominous music continues]
- [Miguel grunts]
[gasping, groaning]
Ah!
[groans]
[grunts]
[coughs]
- [grunts]
- [bags thudding]
Okay, let's go.
[music turns suspenseful]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Miguel panting]
[Rita distantly] Let go of me!
[Rita screaming]
- Andres.
- [Rita] Let go!
Ignore it. Let's go.
[Rita] No! Let go!
Andres.
- Wait, wait.
- We have to stick to the plan.
I said, wait!
[Rita grunts]
[whimpers]
- Ow! Ah!
- Get up!
[crying in pain]
[Raul] Shh.
Are you working with those thieves, Rita?
- [Rita breathing heavily]
- Tell us. Hmm?
[suspenseful music continues]
- I see.
- [gun cocks]
Did you tell them about our hideout?
- Fess up!
- I don't know anything!
And I don't care
what you're talking about!
[chuckles]
Sir Sameo was so good to you,
yet you still betrayed him.
Good?!
You blinded us with your money!
You manipulated us and
poisoned the minds of the kids.
Just like you did to my brother!
[sobs]
[suspenseful music continues]
You didn't want to join me and Emer.
- You want revenge?
- Where's my brother--
Ah!
- [whimpering]
- You dare raise your voice?
Shut up and stay down.
Andres, we don't have to get involved.
- Hey.
- No.
We have to help her. Come on.
Ugh!
- [Rita screaming]
- [blade swooshing]
[thwacks]
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [Rita whimpering]
[crying]
[gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
- [Rita screams]
- [rapid gunfire]
- [Rita screaming, whimpering]
[distant gunfire]
[Champ neighing]
[hooves clomping]
- The money!
- No!
- [distant gunfire]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Max] He's getting away!
- [Gab] He's too fast!
- [Max] Shit! Shit!
[Gab] We can still catch him! Let's go!
[rapid gunfire]
Shark!
[radio static]
[Andres] Shark!
We're engaging hostiles!
Tell me if you need backup.
Give me your coordinates.
[gunshots]
- [rapid gunfire]
- [Rita crying]
[JB] Team.
Team!
Do you copy?
Jaguar!
[bag thuds]
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [leaves rustling]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [gunshots]
- [suspenseful music intensifies]
[Rita crying]
[gunshots]
Champ's gone with our money!
Why didn't you secure his leash?
You're in charge of watching him!
We're straying too far
from the exit point.
Forget about it. Let's just let it go.
Is your comms working? Mine's missing.
We have no other means to contact them.
Sir, we've passed this place before.
I think we're lost, sir.
Who are you? Sameo's enemies?
You need to get out of here.
I have to find my brother.
They have no other choice
but to go through Sitio Magdalo.
We'll rest here for a bit.
We're waiting for someone.
Put your weapons down!
Your bags too.