They still have Takako,
which means we don't have a choice.
We need to kidnap Donato Escalera
on Azur Island.
I have a fever.
Wait. Please wait, okay?
We need to move fast.
This is the satellite image
of Azur Island.
These are the entry and exit points.
The mission is to extract
Donato Escalera alive.
We have less than 24 hours to do it.
Bonifacio is in command.
Because I can't see everything
happening in the field,
you all need to stay sharp.
You need to move fast
and avoid creating any commotion.
The slightest noise
can compromise the entire operation.
- [BODY THUDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
Jaguar, take high ground.
The Escaleras have eyes everywhere.
The comms are down!
It's like we're entering
the eye of a storm.
Hostile outside the nest.
See you all on the other side.
Complete and alive.
- Verify the target.
- Wolf.
- Identity confirmed.
- Confirmed.
We got Ace of Spade.
Eagle, where are you?
Eagle at your six, coming in hot!
[GUNSHOTS]
Move out! Move out!
What do you want? Money?
Money? Idiot, it's you we're after.
Let's move.
Ah! They got Donato!
We were infiltrated.
They kidnapped Donato.
Let's go.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
Hold.
[ENGINE REVVING]
- Go! Go! Go!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Run!
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAN 1] Idiots! We lost them.
They're still around here.
[MAN 2] Find them! They're still close!
[MAN 1] They might have
gone deep into the forest.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Search to your left!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[DOORS CLACKING]
[BODIES THUDDING]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [MEN SHOUTING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- Diamond!
- [DIAMOND] Oh my God!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[DIAMOND] Clover, kill them!
I swear I will kill all of them!
Damn them!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE WINDS DOWN]
We need to start walking from here.
We're about to infiltrate the community.
Get ready.
We need to reach exit point Alpha.
[GREG] Roger that.
Let's move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [HORSE NEIGHING]
- [GATE CLANGS]
Go on. I can manage.
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
Come on, sit up.
[WATER SPLASHING]
I'll just wipe your face, okay?
I can't find any medicine.
But this will help you feel better.
You don't…
Um… Uh…
Understand… Understand Tagalog?
[SIGHS]
Let me take care of this.
Ah!
- Ouch!
- Oh…
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TAKAKO WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
Auntie…
What?
My… Papa…
is waiting for me.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I want to be with my Papa.
Because we have plans…
ma'am.
My birthday is soon.
We're going home.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry…
When your dad
finally gives Señor what he wants,
you can go home.
I need your help.
I know you Filipinos are helpful
and good.
I have faith in your people.
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Please, Auntie.
[TAKAKO] Please.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Your foot is badly hurt…
so you won't be able to go far.
Are you going to help me?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[JB] Eagle, set parameters.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JB] We are entering the village.
[GREG] Confirming that.
[JB] Approaching Alpha.
[GREG] Standby.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRONE BUZZING]
[JB] Noah.
We're inside the village.
[GREG] Roger that.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GREG] Be vigilant.
There are civilians in the area.
We don't know who among them
are our allies or enemies.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROOSTER CROWING]
[JB] Stay sharp, boys.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GROANS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [MEN GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [THUDS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MAN GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
- [GRUNTS]
Hostiles on your left.
- [MEN SHOUTING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [KICK LANDS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MEN GRUNTING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [KNIFE WHOOSHES]
- [GROANS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[GROANS]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GROANS]
- [KNIFE SLASHING]
[THUD]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
Move!
Go left. Go left.
[JB] Go, go, go!
Area is hot.
Multiple hostiles were engaging.
- Aah!
- [MAX] Hostiles on your right.
[GUNSHOTS]
[JB] Keep moving!
Go! Go! Go!
[GUNSHOTS]
Move! Move! Move!
Cover!
[GUNSHOTS]
[JB] Move! Move!
[EXPLOSION]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAX] Area hot. Hostiles inbound.
[MAX] Hostiles on your right.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [MAN SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- Hey!
- [GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[KNIFE SWOOSHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MEN GRUNTING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [MAN GROANS]
- [MAN] Aah!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUD]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[THUD]
- [GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
[GUNSHOTS]
Where is Spade?
Spade is missing!
- [GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
- Aah!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GROANS]
- [THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JB] Eagle, locate the package.
[TRACKER BEEPING]
Package is with the hostiles
300 meters going north.
[MAX] Go right.
They're getting away!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXPLOSION]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Take cover! Take cover!
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOTS]
- Where have you been?
- Heart!
- [CLOVER] Untie him.
- [DONATO] Take this off.
Take Spade with you.
Take him away from here.
Let's get out of here.
Go. I'll take it from here. Go!
Let's go!
[MAX] Package is on route
250 meters northeast
from our extraction point going to a boat.
[DONATO] Hurry! We have to go!
Jaguar.
On my command.
[GUN COCKS]
Send it.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
[JB] Engage!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DONATO] Boys!
Get on board!
Slowpokes!
[GUNSHOTS]
Fine! I'll go ahead.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOT]
[DONATO GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go ahead. I'll blow his brains out.
[DONATO GRUNTS]
[GUN COCKS]
Put your gun down.
[DONATO GRUNTS]
Do you think I care about my cousin?
I don't care.
In fact, I want to kill him!
[GUNSHOT]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Aren't you going to release me?!
A total of 1.5 million.
Nice working with you.
I just want to share
the blessings that I got.
I'm the one who called earlier
about the wedding.
Love, I can't come.
You will die a disappointment
if you don't stop what you're doing.
You're the only one I have left.
You won't lose me. Trust me.
How long are we going to deal
with people like Timor?
We're just getting started.