[CHINESE FOLK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHINESE FOLK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HOST] A lovely evening, everyone!
We welcome you all
to an unforgettable evening
of art, culture,
and camaraderie in celebration
of Yangdon-Philippines Friendship Night!
Papa.
You promised me.
Oh, I know, I know.
The vacation.
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's talk later.
Without work,
or phone calls,
or any distraction whatsoever.
Just my daughter and I.
- Okay.
Thank you.
These shoes are killing me.
[GIGGLES]
Ambassador Rai.
Minister De Vera.
Well, the Philippines
has the most beautiful islands.
Unfortunately,
not a single port is capable
of accommodating cruise ships.
Yes, yes, yes. Um…
Well, as we have mentioned before,
Minister De Vera,
we are indeed willing to invest
in building a new port.
That's good news.
[DOOR OPENS]
- [CHINESE FOLK MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FOOTSTEPS]
Sir, how can I help you?
- [GUNSHOT]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[SCREAMING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
This way, sir!
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [TAKAKO] Papa! Papa!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Ma'am, this way!
- Papa! Papa!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TAKAKO WHIMPERS]
Papa!
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GUN COCKS]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[BODYGUARD] Stay close, Miss Takako.
[GUNSHOTS]
[VASE SHATTERS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COUGHS]
[YELPS]
[WHIMPERS]
Papa!
Takako.
Takako! Ta--
- No. No.
- Takako.
[TAKAKO SOBBING]
- Please.
- [TAKAKO SOBBING]
Please.
What do you want?
I'll give you whatever you want!
Just don't hurt my daughter!
What do you want?!
- [TAKAKO SOBBING]
- [JIGME] Please!
[GUNSHOTS]
[TAKAKO] No! No!
- [TAKAKO] Papa!
- Takako!
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
No!
[SOBBING] Papa! Papa!
Papa!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
No! [SOBBING]
No! No! No! No!
[SOBBING]
No! No!
Papa! Papa!
[ENGINE REVS]
Yes, Mr. President.
They want us to release
the imprisoned terrorists.
Yes, sir. I understand.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Ambassador Rai.
I have already briefed the President
on what the terrorists are demanding
to release your daughter.
And what's the President's response?
The President won't negotiate
with the terrorists.
I get it. I understand. I…
If I were in his place, I'd…
But, there's a private elite team.
One we have worked with
in situations like this.
They can help.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
My resources are at your disposal.
- [JIGME] Don't hurt my daughter!
- Papa!
Takako!
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
Papa!
No! [SOBBING]
No! No!
[PHONE BUZZING]
- General Novilla.
- Greg.
Have you watched it already?
Yes, General.
We need help.
There are diplomatic
ramifications in the case.
So I contacted you, Greg.
Have you identified the kidnappers?
We got a tip that it was Escalera's group.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
No!
[SOBS]
No! No!
No! No! No!
Papa!
No! No!
[SOBBING]
Come here! [GRUNTS]
No!
No! No! No!
[SOBBING]
Walk.
- Go.
- [WHIMPERS]
Walk.
[NOVILLA] They're not after money.
They want the release
of three foreign nationals
that were arrested by the government
for their involvement in terrorism,
including a Filipino,
who's a nephew of Timor Escalera.
The government cannot give in
to the demands of the terrorists.
So, I recommended
your group to Ambassador Rai.
After all,
you've been helping the military
in situations that we
can't get involved with
and that are out of our jurisdiction.
Greg.
Name your price.
The ambassador is willing to pay.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
[MAN] Just relax, bro,
we'll get the money.
- [THUDS]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTS]
[GIRL CRYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
I'm already at the location.
[GUNSHOTS]
I'm close to the package,
I'm working on it.
Give me two minutes.
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[MAN YELLS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[THUDS]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[KNIFE SLASHING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
[GRUNTS]
[GIRL CRYING]
[GIRL SOBBING]
[GIRL BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR SMASHES]
[GIRL SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING]
Don't be scared.
I'm not a bad person.
I'm here to save you.
Come on.
Mommy!
- Dear!
[CRYING]
We thought we wouldn't see you again.
Are you okay? Does anything hurt?
[CRYING]
Two million pesos, complete payment.
Thank you for saving my daughter.
[GIRL CRYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Hello?
One beer.
Contractor…
JB
Thank you.
[GLASSES CLINK]
JB, I have a job for you.
About time.
What is it?
Timor Escalera's men kidnapped Takako Rai.
Here's the problem…
they don't want ransom.
So, money is useless.
What is it, extraction? Rescue?
We're going to kidnap Timor's only child.
Donato Escalera.
In short, head swap.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
High stakes, high reward.
This is just right for me.
[MOUTH CLICKS] Well, here's the thing.
This time, you're not working alone.
You'll have to work with a whole team.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know I work alone.
I know, but…
you'll just have to trust me this time.
Who are my teammates?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDS]
[CHOPS]
[HOSE RUNNING]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAN 1] Let's get the chick, dude!
- [MAN 2] Hurry!
- [MAN 3] Come on!
Even if you keep running, we'll catch you.
Hey, just give us your name--
- Where are you going?
- Just your name, miss!
[CHUCKLES] Hey, hey!
Grab the bag!
Please, leave me alone!
Just come with us!
Let me go!
We just want to get to know you.
- Stop it, please!
- [MEN CHUCKLE]
- Just come with us!
- Let me go!
- Hold her!
[WOMAN] Let me go, please.
This is fun!
- Come on, join us!
- Help!
Help! Help!
Stop it!
I said stop it already!
Hey!
Why are you interfering?!
Who do you think you are?
Do you know her?
What do you want? Huh?
What do you want?!
Do you know her? Huh?
Do you want to come with us?
Do you want to come?
What do you want, buddy?
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- There's the bastard!
- Hurry!
Out of the way!
[MEN YELLING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
[GLASS BREAKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[SPITS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
What, that's it?!
Get up! What?!
What?! You want more?! Huh?
You want more? You want more?!
I've had enough.
[PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you want to get hurt too?!
[YELLS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNIFE POPS]
- [STABS]
- [GROANS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GRUNTS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you okay?
Yes, but how about you?
- Do you need help--
- Go home.
Oh.
Sir, are you sure you don't need help?
Sir, thank you.
- Thank you so much--
- Just go.
Be careful, okay?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TAKAKO CRYING]
[MAN] Walk!
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHRIEKS]
[SOBS]
[TAKAKO CRYING]
Please take me back.
[CRYING]
Get up!
Walk.
- [CRYING]
- [DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WAILING]
Listen… just walk!
[CRYING]
Rehab?
Yep.
What is he, an addict?
Alcoholic.
- But he's sharp.
- [JB SIGHS]
2019.
Rapid Bus Transportation Hostage Crisis.
Moving target, one-shot kill.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
- [WOMAN CRYING]
- Hurry up, don't look around!
- Let us out now!
- I said hurry!
[SIRENS WAILING]
Do you have eyes on the target?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Negative, sir.
I don't have a clear shot.
The hostage is too close to the target.
We're out of time!
He can't reach the city,
or he'll detonate the bomb!
- [HOSTAGES SCREAMING]
- Quiet!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Take the shot!
That's an order!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUN COCKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't even know,
he might've been drunk at the time.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
One of the best doctors in the army.
If you look at him,
he seems ordinary, right?
Don't be fooled.
He's the best of the best.
You got my message?
I don't have a job, not a thing.
Of course, I'm in, sir!
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
- [STAB]
- [GUARD] Hey, enough of that!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[THUDS]
[BLOWS LAND]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[BLOW LANDS]
[HEAD CLANGS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
Wait! Wait!
Wait, we were just ordered to do this!
[PANTING]
By who?
Who?!
Manalastas.
[MAN] Oh, Buguias! Buguias!
Who's coming down here?!
[TAPS ON BUS]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
Grandma.
Oh, Andres! [GIGGLES]
How are you?
Oh.
- What is that? Trouble again?
- Grandma…
It's nothing, just my style.
- Oh, come on!
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Anyway, let's get you some food.
You must be hungry…
- after such a long trip.
- I'm really hungry, Grandma.
Alright.
Thank you, Grandma.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Good thing the weather's nice, right?
Nature is on our side.
Your right.
Good thing it's not raining.
[SIGHS]
Hey, beautiful. [CHUCKLES]
Just keep at it, you can handle it.
I'm managing,
but my body can't take it anymore.
[GIGGLING]
Wait, where's Andres?
Uh, I didn't let him come.
I told him to rest,
he just got back from camp.
Oh, just because he's a soldier
doesn't mean he won't farm anymore.
Uh, okay, I'll call him quickly.
Oh, no.
I'm just kidding.
Did you know that I'm proud of your son?
Actually, the both of you.
You're the pride of our tribe.
- Alright!
- Okay.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I've told you so many times,
but you're all so stubborn!
The true owners of this land
are the Manalastas family!
The court has already
released the document!
We all know that you forged the documents.
You can't just take this land.
We're kicking you out! Go away!
Exactly! You're the ones who should leave.
Alright, people!
Oh, so you really want trouble? Let's go!
- Alright! Beat them!
- [KICK LANDS]
Hold on! Wait! Wait!
[GROANS]
Go away! Get out of here!
- [CROWD CLAMORING]
- [KICKS LAND]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
Andres!
The Manalastas family is here again.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUDS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [WOMAN SCREAMING]
- [BLOWS LAND]
That's enough!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTING]
I said that's enough!
Stop hurting each other!
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
- [THWACKS]
- Hey! Hey!
You bastards!
This is our land!
I said that's enough!
This is our land.
[GUNSHOT]
[SORROWFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- What's it going to be?!
- [GUN COCKS]
- [THWACKS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Pa!
[SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANICKED BREATHING]
Andres…
Don't let go of the land.
Your sibling will return.
[SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
They need a home to come back to.
[LABORED BREATHING]
Yes. [SOBS]
[SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
[SNIFFLES]
Pedro.
Son!
- [SOBBING LOUDLY]
- [SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Andres!
You'll pay for this!
Remember this!
- Stand up!
- Hey!
- Let-- Let go of me!
- Why? What's this?
No!
Where are you taking my grandson?!
In violation of military discipline
and conduct unbecoming of an officer…
Guilty beyond reasonable
doubt of homicide.
Face the back. Turn around.
["LIWANAG SA DILIM" INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
When will you visit your father's grave?
Maybe tomorrow.
["LIWANAG SA DILIM"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
[SNIFFS]
- Grandma.
- Mm-hmm?
Wait a minute.
I've got a surprise for you
Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
- Grandma, happy birthday
- Whoa!
- [GUSHING]
- Happy birthday, Grandma.
- Yes.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
Thank you.
I'm only letting it slide
because it's your birthday.
Hey, we're both just as stubborn.
[GIGGLES]
Grandma, what I mean is,
I want you to be healthy
until we get back on our land.
I hope so too.
And I hope the day comes
when you don't have to hide
just to visit me.
Someday, Grandma.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
We will return to our land.
We'll take back the land
that was stolen from us.
So when my sibling comes back,
wherever they are now,
they'll know there's a place
for them to return to.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
I'll call you from time to time.
Take care.
Andres, you're the one
who needs to be careful.
Yes.
And keep yourself out of trouble.
Come on, Grandma,
I'm not looking for trouble.
Mm?
Trouble always seems to find me.
Really? [LAUGHS]
But for you, okay. Hmm.
Take care, Grandma.
Okay. Take care!
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
You have a nerve to come here.
Your life is not enough
for killing my cousin.
I've been locked up before, right, Emil?
What else do you want?
To kill you!
[GASPS]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
[GUN CLATTERS]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Get him!
[GROANS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [YELLS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[BLOW LANDS]
[GRUNTS]
- [THWACKS]
- [GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BODY SLAMS]
- [GROANS]
- [THUDS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GUN COCKS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
Andres!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- [BODY THUDS]
["LIWANAG SA DILIM"
BY PABLO OF SB19 PLAYING]
Colonel Paterno. I know you sir.
I lead an elite
private military company.
Where is this job located?
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
I don't know what's more disappointing.
What you've done
or what you're doing right now.
- Sir!
- Isn't that what you always teach me?
To stand up and fight
for what I believe in?
Always take care of yourself.
Where are you going?
This is your chance to serve the nation.
And we will be working incognito.