[Diego] Don't panic, Tomas Guerrero.
You don't want this
to be his last birthday, do you?
That's what you'll use
to kill Josephine Barrios.
[Andres] Team, Monkey's not answering.
Something's happening to him.
[Gab] Guys, if I save his uncle,
you can complete the mission
and you can save Monkey.
I'll go to him now.
[JB] Go, Sparrow. Finish the job.
[inhales sharply]
- [grunts]
- Get moving!
I knew this would happen! Go! Catch him!
- [men grunting]
- [groan]
Eagle.
- Cut the CCTV.
- Copy.
We lost the CCTV connection.
If they want to do
this face-to-face, so be it.
[Tres] You're going back in there?
Your brother might get suspicious of you.
I know. But if he's involved in this,
I'll be his distraction.
Execute phase three now.
Wolf, I thought your brother left.
Why did he come back?
[Diego] Barrios is coming out of her room.
[gun cocks]
You know what to do.
- [loud footsteps echoing]
- [heart beats loudly]
I want her dead.
[dramatic music playing]
[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[Andres] Jun.
Jun! Jun!
- [groans]
- [body slamming]
[Andres breathing heavily]
Whatever you're planning, stop it.
- I don't know what you mean.
- Don't play dumb!
I heard you!
You're planning to kill Barrios!
Why are you here?
Why are you using a fake name?
I'm here to stop you.
Are you with her second layer of security?
You're with the group
planning to kill her!
[breathing heavily]
I know exactly what I heard, Jun.
You're stopping this. You're leaving.
- Let go of me!
- Come here!
[both grunt]
[breathes heavily]
We're the same. We're doing the same job.
I don't kill innocent people.
Barrios isn't innocent. She's corrupt.
[tense music continues]
What are you talking about, Jun?
Is that what your father told you?
You were a victim of a syndicate.
You were taken from us, that's the truth!
Why are you acting all righteous?
You take on contracts too!
Maybe your contracts
are even worse than mine!
I took contracts to find you.
I don't accept illegal jobs.
[grunts]
[groans]
[blows land]
- [grunts]
- [breathing heavily]
[clattering]
- [tense music continues]
- [breathing heavily]
Jun. Jun. Wait…
Let's go.
[breathing heavily]
[Barrios] We're all here,
not just to celebrate,
but to stand up for those
who can't speak for themselves.
- [dramatic music sting]
- [loud footsteps echoing]
Many ask why I'm here.
They say I should
stick to environmental issues.
But wherever they place me,
I'll support causes like this,
for the youth robbed of their rights
and the families
destroyed by human trafficking.
Monkey, don't do it.
Uncle… Uncle, please forgive me.
[foreboding music playing]
- [Barrios] We won't stop…
- Monkey,
- don't do it.
- …not while abuse exists.
[foreboding music crescendos]
- [breathing heavily]
- [tense music playing]
What did Manuel do to you?
Don't drag my father into this!
[tense music continues]
You know…
my brother, Jun…
he was a good kid.
I'm not the Jun you knew anymore.
Pedro…
our father,
he was a good man.
I don't know him.
My adoptive father, that's who I know.
Jun…
Manuel,
is a bad man.
He's manipulating you.
[ominous tone playing]
So what?
What will you do, Andres?
[ominous tone continues]
Kill me?
[dramatic music sting]
[somber music playing]
[somber music continues]
[sobbing quietly]
You know what I remember?
[sniffs]
The time…
rats were chasing me in the streets.
In the sun, in the rain…
I was out there.
[somber music continues]
My feet were full of
wounds because I was barefoot.
[somber music continues]
But you know what was the hardest part?
Hunger.
I was so hungry.
That's what I remember.
[somber music continues]
Those times when I waited, hoping…
someone would come back for me,
hoping someone would look for me.
[somber music continues]
I looked for you, Jun.
But you didn't come!
Papa, Papa came into my life.
[somber music continues]
It's not too late.
We can fix this.
I'll go with you.
I'll help you.
[music turns ominous]
That's why I'm asking you…
tell your people to stop this.
Okay?
Let's end this.
[ominous music continues]
There's nothing more you can do.
If it's not Barrios,
many innocent people will be hurt,
including their loved ones.
Now you choose.
One casualty or a massacre?
- [dramatic music sting]
- [ominous music crescendos]
- [kick lands]
- [thud]
[Diego grunts]
Jun!
What?! Think you're tough?!
[man] You're not scared.
You're really not scared?
What if I shoot you right here?
Let's see if you're
still fearless then, huh?
- [gunshots]
- [man grunts]
- [gunshot]
- [body thuds]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [gunshot]
- Well?! Who's tough now?!
[Gab breathes heavily]
Uncle, can you manage?
- Yeah.
- You sure you can manage?
- We need to hurry, Uncle.
- [groans]
- Hold on.
- [grunting]
- [Gab breathes heavily]
- [grunting continues]
Uncle, be careful!
- Where are we going?
- Over here.
Just stay low. Stay low.
[dramatic music playing]
[Andres grunts]
- [thud]
- [heavy panting]
Come here.
[dramatic music continues]
Enough!
[thuds]
[loud clattering]
[dramatic music crescendos]
- [thud]
- [panting]
Andres, enough!
[pensive music playing]
Andres, you're my brother.
I love you, no matter what.
Please, let's stop fighting.
Andres, I've had enough.
[Andres pants heavily]
[grunts]
[panting]
[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
Jun, let's stop this.
You're coming with us, okay?
[dramatic music ends]
Okay?
[Josephine] And all of
you will help me make a change.
[tense music playing]
Protect the package.
I won't do what they ask.
Shark.
Miss Barrios,
you need to get out of here right now.
I'm part of the second layer of security.
Miss Barrios, excuse me.
Miss Barrios, I'm part of
the second layer of your security.
There's a grave
threat to your life right now.
You need to get out of this venue.
- [crowd murmuring]
- [tense music continues]
Miss Barrios!
- You need to get out right now!
- Okay, okay.
Get out!
Let's go, let's go.
[gun cocks]
[suspenseful music playing
[gunshot]
[ominous music playing]
- [crowd clamoring]
- [ominous music continues]
[gunshot]
[thuds]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [distant gunshots]
- [crowd clamoring]
[glass shattering]
[clattering]
[thuds]
- [rapid footsteps receding]
- [suspenseful music continues]
[inaudible choking]
Ma'am!
Ma'am! Ma'am please!
[woman shrieking] Ma'am!
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ma'am!
- [JB] Take her to the hospital!
- [woman] Ma'am!
Hurry!
[suspenseful music continues]
The package is down.
I repeat, the package is down!
[grunts]
Monkey! Let's go to the exit point!
Come on!
Wolf, where are you?!
I'm sorry.
This had to happen.
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[bullets clink]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [gunshot]
- [shattering]
[suspenseful music continues]
[rapid footsteps receding]
[phone ringing]
Max.
Sir, the package is down.
[suspenseful music continues]
Who did it? Was it Monkey?
[Max] No. It was somebody else.
It was an usher.
She was killed by Barrios's security.
[Greg] All units, begin exit strategy.
Stay safe.
[suspenseful music crescendos]
[clamoring, screaming]
[foreboding music playing]
Team, we're compromised.
Threat confirmed.
Barrios's second layer of security
has been alerted. Evacuate now!
Wolf, where are you?
Wolf?
[unsettling music playing]
[footsteps thump]
[gun cocks]
[unsettling music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[Gab] Uncle is safe.
We're on our way to the hospital.
[unsettling music continues]
- [music swells]
- [Tomas breathing shakily]
- [breathing shakily]
- [dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[engine revving]
- [breathes heavily]
- You good? Are you good, Uncle?
Yes, I'm okay.
Ah. [exhales]
[breathes sharply]
[Tomas breathing heavily]
Thank you. Thank you, Gab.
[dramatic music continues]
Ah.
[Gab breathing heavily]
Are you still good, Uncle?
[breathing sharply] I'm fine.
[groans, breathing heavily]
I, I have so many questions.
But…
You can answer just this one.
[heavy breathing continues]
Is Tom safe?
[dramatic music continues]
- [gun clicks]
- [gasps]
Throw your gun away.
[gun clatters]
[breathes sharply] Jun.
You need to get out of here.
You know who I am.
That means you're one of them.
[exhales] Jun, listen to me.
You need to save yourself.
Get out of here, let's go. Come with me.
- [kicks land]
- [gunshots]
[Diego grunts]
Jun! Stop it!
- [gun cocks]
- Jun!
- [gunshots]
- [inaudible scream]
Argh!
[gunshot]
- [inaudible scream]
- [body thuds]
[dramatic music continues]
[music turns ominous]
One thing that my papa taught me
is that when I kill someone,
I should look them straight in the eyes…
[ominous music continues]
to let them know it's not an accident.
[gunshot]
[ominous music continues]
[ominous music fades]
You good? Are you good, Uncle?
[breathes sharply]
Uncle, I hope you can forgive me.
[Miguel] Monkey, go to your uncle!
- Quickly!
- [breathing heavily]
[sinister music playing]
[gunshots]
- [gunshots]
- [people screaming]
Get the car ready.
No one must know that we're here.
[gun cocks]
[dramatic music playing]