Monkey, Sparrow.
I see one Tango moving
at your one o'clock.
- Engage!
- [rapid gunfire]
[gunshot]
[panting, grunts]
[Gab] Looks like the rain's
going to get heavier.
[Max] Perimeter clear.
You can now proceed to the target.
[gunshots]
Target eliminated.
Confirmed, this is Sameo Patel.
Contractor, the order is complete.
Sending you photos and
videos for confirmation.
Good job.
Congratulate everyone for me.
Whoa! There's so much!
[chuckling]
[theme music playing]
Ooh! You're the answer to all my problems!
[chuckles] I love you, money!
That's right!
[Max] Only take what we can carry, okay?
[Tomas] I got this! Relax!
Tomas, it's a long walk.
Are you sure you can carry that?
Of course, I can! [chuckles]
No worries, we'll figure it out.
Want me to do a backflip
while figuring it out?
[Tomas and Miguel cackle]
[Gab grunts]
Eagle, Sparrow, go ahead.
Alright.
We're taking the same route,
we'll meet you there.
- Are you sure?
- [Andres] Yeah.
We can wait for you.
[Tomas groans] Why?
You need my help, just admit it.
[chuckles]
You really think I need help?
Yeah. I mean, your bag is bigger than you.
Just look at it.
You're so annoying.
[Gab] Let's go, Eagle.
See you at the exit point,
if you make it there.
- [Tomas chuckles]
- [Gab] Tch!
- [Max] You good, Gab?
- Yep.
[Gab grunts]
[foreboding music playing]
You know, Tomas…
[Andres] I see it!
A little piece of advice…
You joke about everything.
How do you expect women
to take you seriously,
if you're never serious?
W-what? Why are we talking
about women now?
This--this is what's important
right now, okay?
And besides, I'm not attracted to her.
Liar.
[ominous music playing]
Hold on.
We're heading back. How's it going?
All good.
Quiet.
The rain's stopped.
What about the shipment?
[Benjie] We're unloading more.
We have a 72-hour window
to complete the shipment to Malaysia.
[ominous music continues]
The wind's picking up.
It won't rain again.
We'll be back soon.
Let's go.
[ominous music continues]
[Gab] Ugh, Tomas is so annoying.
You know, "Monkey" suits him
because he literally looks like an ape.
[Max giggles]
Why do you always seem
so worked up over Tomas?
I mean, just look… [scoffs]
just looking at his face is irritating.
He's like a living nightmare.
[huffs]
- My god!
- [Max scoffs]
The things he says, right?
He's so loud! Such a show-off.
Okay. [chuckles] Sure.
What's that?
Nothing.
What do you mean "nothing"?
You guys seem to really repel each other.
If I didn't know you…
I'd think you actually liked each other.
Yuck!
Yuck, Max!
- Ew!
- Overacting!
Gross.
But that's how it is sometimes, right?
At first, you think
you don't like someone…
then you realize you actually do--
Max, you really don't know me yet.
Guys like that? Not my type!
And they never will be, ever.
He's the worst.
Okay.
If you say so.
I really do.
[foreboding music playing]
[Gab] Damn, this is steep.
[breathes heavily]
Let's get the bags first.
Hold on, hold on. This way.
- Alright.
- [Gab grunts]
There. Whoo.
Okay, stop! Stop! Stop!
[groans]
Alright, your turn.
- Give me your bag.
- Okay.
Alright.
[foreboding music continues]
[grunts]
One at a time.
- You good?
- Aah!
Yes.
- [ominous music playing]
- [exhales deeply]
- Nice.
- Shoot.
The path collapsed.
- We got this.
- You sure?
- Of course.
- Be careful.
Okay, I got this.
[grunts]
What?
I mean, I can do it by myself,
but it'd be a waste
to leave the money behind.
- Get up, get up--
- [Gab grunts]
[groans]
Alright, we need to find another way.
[exhales sharply]
Let's look for another path.
That way.
- Is there another way?
- There has to be.
[grunts]
Let's go this way.
Uh, we're good to go.
Alright, you guys go ahead.
We'll take care of things here.
[Grunts] See you there, JB. Stay safe.
[Tomas] You, too.
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[both panting]
- Let's go?
- Let's go.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Miguel grunts]
[grunts]
[panting]
- [Andres grunts]
- [bag thuds]
- [grunts, pants]
- Come on.
- Alright.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music continues]
Shark, there was
a landslide on our route.
See you at the exit point.
[JB] Copy that.
Let's go.
[panting]
- [Tomas] Just a bit more.
- We need to go.
[Tomas] Hold on, sir.
This could help a lot of people, sir.
And it's better for us to have this money.
Right?
[Tomas grunts]
Hurry up, Tomas.
- Yes, sir.
- That's enough. Come on!
Alright!
- [Tomas grunts]
- [suspenseful music continues]
[grunts] It's heavy.
I can do this. [chuckles]
I'm built for this. [grunts]
[grunts]
Ugh!
I'm coming, sir.
[chuckles, groans]
[groans, grunts]
[JB] Tomas!
Sir!
It's so heavy!
[JB] Hurry up, Tomas!
- Come on!
- [Tomas grunts]
Give me a second, sir. It's really heavy.
But I've got this. [grunts]
- [JB] Get up here!
- [Tomas grunts]
- [music crescendos]
- [JB] Hurry!
[Tomas grunts]
Enemies! They're here!
- Enemies are here!
- Hey!
Sir!
- [ominous music playing]
- I told you to fix your stance!
Sir, enemies attacked…
They attacked Sir Sameo's house!
[breathing rapidly] Sir.
- Raul!
- Sir!
[ominous music continues]
We're under attack.
Move, goddammit!
- Sir…
- Come on!
Goddamn addict.
[ominous music continues]
[grunts]
[grunts loudly]
Whoa!
- [Max] Oh my god.
- [Gab laughs]
[both panting heavily]
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- Yup!
Shark, meet you at the exit point.
We'll get there first!
[Gab exclaims]
[Gab] Jackpot!
- [both pant]
- [Gab] Hello!
Hello!
Hi!
We're your friends.
It's okay.
- [horse snorts]
- He's a good horse!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
[horse snorts]
- Okay. Hey, you.
- [horse snorts softly]
- We hit the jackpot!
- Yes!
- [Gab] Okay, calm down.
- [Max] It's okay. It's okay.
[Max] It's okay.
[Max sighs loudly]
Boss, what if Emer is just high?
[suspenseful music playing]
Come here!
[suspenseful music continues]
Do you have something to say?
Move!
[suspenseful music continues]
- [Miguel] Andres.
- What?
[Tomas grunts]
Don't worry about me, sir.
I'm fine.
Just a bit sore, but I'm fine.
- [JB grunts]
- [bag thuds]
[suspenseful music continues]
[grunts]
[Miguel panting heavily] I got it.
[JB grunts]
All units…
- [pants] Listen up.
- [suspenseful music crescendos]
[JB] We can't take the same track back.
Stick to the GPS.
Copy that.
[JB] I repeat, stick to the GPS.
Especially since the loot
is slowing us down.
That's what they think.
It's slowing you down, but not us!
If we lose comms,
everyone proceed to the exit point.
[JB] We'll meet there.
[Andres] Copy.
[both grunt]
[unsettling music playing]
Eagle, Sparrow, do you copy?
- Copy.
- Copy that.
- [Gab giggles]
- [hooves clattering]
I can't wait to see Tomas'
face when he sees this.
[laughs]
We outsmarted him.
They underestimate how smart we are.
They didn't see this coming.
Right, Horsey?
[both chuckle]
- You're right.
- Yeah.
[unsettling music continues]
Let's move, Tomas.
[grunts]
[Gab] Come here.
Come here. [clicking tongue]
There you go.
He came to me right away.
The horse we got is so obedient.
So cute!
You know, I'll take you to my
and my mommy's rest house.
- The one I will buy.
- [Max] Wow.
- [Max] You'll buy a rest house?
- Yes. [laughs]
[Gab] Actually,
the money we got isn't enough.
But it's enough for the down payment.
Are you still bothered because
we took the money?
I'm just wondering
if you'd like to take my share, too.
Huh? Your share?
That's yours! I mean, with this money.
- Our lives will change with this money.
- [horse snorts]
[Max scoffs]
That's true.
[hooves clopping]
What will we do first when we get home?
Hm? What will we do?
When we get home, do you want to…
Do you want to…
share the horse with me?
Borrow him. Who knows?
He might make your dad happy
when you get home.
- Right?
- [horse pants heavily]
[horse pants heavily]
[Max] Aah.
I don't know if he'll be happy.
[Gab scoffs] Why?
Because I don't know him.
Oh, shit.
I actually don't know who
my biological parents are.
I was still a baby when Mama
and Mommy adopted me.
Soldiers saved me during
a military operation.
Shit.
- Sorry.
- No, it's okay.
So you've been through a lot too, huh?
We all have.
Damn, you have two moms?
- Yeah. [laughs]
- That's cool!
- They're the best.
- So do it for them instead.
I'm sure they'll like Champ.
- Right, Champ?
- Wow, Champ.
- Yeah. I already named him.
- [laughs]
Right? Champ suits him. Am I right?
[laugh] That's cool. Champ.
- [Max] I like that.
- [Gab] Champ.
[suspenseful music playing]
[hurried footsteps]
They killed him.
[growls]
- [exhales sharply]
- [radio beeps]
[suspenseful music continues]
[beeping]
[over the radio] We have a problem.
What?
The house was attacked.
Sir Patel is dead.
[suspenseful music continues]
The money?
Let's go.
[creaking]
[suspenseful music continues]
Shoot!
[breathing heavily]
We were screwed over, Raul.
Damn it! We were ransacked, boss.
[radio beeps]
They took almost all of the money.
[static crackling]
What the heck! That money is ours.
Those bastards!
They stole from the wrong people.
[suspenseful music continues]
Surround all the mountains exit points.
Kill anyone who isn't from here.
Copy. Let's go!
We need to find them. Hurry!
Hurry up!
[suspenseful music continues]
Listen up! Listen!
We'll search in groups.
Some will go up north.
Others will go through the back!
We'll surround the area. Is that clear?!
Take your positions!
Hurry up!
[suspenseful music continues]
Emer!
[panting]
- Sir.
- Haven't I told you
- to fix your posture? Huh?!
- Yes, sir.
- Huh?!
- [thud]
This gun. This!
[gun clacking]
- You shoot this!
- [rapid gunshots]
- Ah!
You don't just hold it!
- Take this!
- [panting]
[gun clacking]
Sir. I can do it, sir! I will kill them!
- [panting, yelping]
- [gun clacking]
Do it.
[panting]
I will. I will.
Raul!
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[suspenseful music crescendos]
We got a lot of money.
We'll divide it equally.
We can't leave it behind, Andres.
- No matter what happens.
[galloping]
He's getting away!
I'm sorry!
We can still catch him. Let's go!
We've been here before. Are we lost, sir?
Keep your eyes open.
They can't be far away.
Let me go!
Andres, don't.
- We agreed.
- Hold on!
We don't need this.
Put down your weapons! Your bags too.
[rapid gunfire]
They have nowhere to go but Sitio Magdalo.
Team, they know we're here.
They've found us.
- [gunshots]
- Engaging hostiles!