[Greg]
Gab, Tomas, Miguel, you're on recon.
It's also your job
to bring in our weapons.
We have to do it discreetly.
Tomas! I knew it was you! How are you?
[scoffs] Matthew?
Since when did you become Matthew,
Tomas Guerrero?
I'm Lisa, remember?
We went to Torres High School together.
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else. I don't know you.
[JB] Manuel works for El Cano.
Jun's life will be in danger
as long as he's with that group.
Sir, I'm doing this for my brother.
I want you to promise
me that Jun won't get hurt.
I promise.
I'm meeting with Jun.
Manuel will be there too.
Papa wants us to meet somewhere else.
- Where?
- Just get in.
Come on.
- Manuel Aguinaldo.
- I'm Andres, sir.
I heard you wanted to meet me.
Sir, if you don't mind, I have a question.
Hmm?
What do you do for a living?
My line of work won't interest you.
You used to be a soldier.
What do you do now?
You know what?
I know what you're doing.
I know why you're here,
and what your motive is.
[theme music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
What is it, sir?
You want to know what kind
of person adopted your brother,
the people who have influence on him,
and the environment he grew up in.
I just want to know more about Jun, sir.
- You're his guardian, right?
- [Manuel] Mm-hmm.
You raised him.
Well, now that you've met me,
do you still have doubts?
Are you still worried?
[unsettling music continues]
[mouth clicks]
Well, Jun said that you're a good person.
[chuckles wryly]
"A good person?"
You know that being
good is subjective, right?
What's good for you,
may not be true for others.
What's bad for you,
may be good for others.
[unsettling music continues]
How important is
being good to you, Andres?
I just want what's best
for my brother. That's all.
Then you have nothing to worry about.
Your brother is in good hands.
He's living a good life.
He went to school
and he's never without food.
And he has purpose.
[unsettling music continues]
In that case, thank you, sir.
I just have one request.
I hope that I get the chance…
to be part of Jun's life.
That's all I ask.
No problem, Andres.
Anyway, I better get going.
I'll leave you two to catch up.
Yes, Pa.
[unsettling music continues]
[engines revving]
[unsettling music fades]
[bag zips]
See you!
- Tomas.
- Hmm?
Who was that woman
you were talking to earlier?
[chuckles]
She was just being friendly.
- And?
- I avoided her, of course.
We're on a mission.
- Okay. Good.
- Why?
Are you jealous, wifey? [chuckles]
Stop that, okay? Stop joking around.
- I'll go now.
- Okay.
- Take care.
- Send my regards to your uncle.
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music fades]
I'll have someone drive you.
- Where are you going from here?
- Huh?
- You're going somewhere?
- I have errands to do.
Let's stay here for a bit.
I can't, I have to go. It's urgent.
You haven't eaten yet.
Let's eat first.
No, I'm good.
I'll see you.
I'm free today. How about I go with you?
[foreboding music playing]
No need.
I'll be fine. I really have to go.
Maybe next time.
[foreboding music continues]
Okay.
- Andres.
- Hmm?
You said you were a former soldier?
Do you want to earn more money?
How?
In Papa's business.
Maybe we can discuss it next time.
I'll talk to Papa first.
Okay.
I'll go now.
[foreboding music crescendos]
[suspenseful music playing]
[engines revving]
[engine revving]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [engines revving]
[engine revving]
[car horn honking]
[suspenseful music continues]
[engines revving]
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Greg] JB, left.
[suspenseful music crescendos]
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[dramatic music continues]
[gate clangs]
[deep breaths]
[dramatic music fades]
So, Max…
All you need to do is attend the hearing.
[pensive music playing]
You just have to be present.
Are you sure?
[pensive music continues]
They've set the schedule.
When is it?
Let's give it three weeks.
If everything goes well
and your case gets dismissed,
then that's it.
That's it?
That's it.
[pensive music continues]
[paper rustling]
[Enzo sighs deeply]
[pensive music continues]
Welcome back, Captain.
[pensive music intensifies]
[pensive music fades]
The important thing
is we've found the base.
I know Manuel, he's very unpredictable.
He's got a lot of security with him,
even if we don't see them.
- [door opens]
- [footsteps approaching]
You found him?
Yeah. What did he tell you?
He knows I used to be a soldier.
[dramatic music sting]
He even tried to offer me a job.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
[tense music playing]
Next time he offers…
take it.
That could be our chance.
[tense music continues]
Beer?
[music turns foreboding]
[Tomas] I deserve this…
Acid for the stomach.
- [Tomas] What's that?
- [man 2] It's expired.
[Tomas] It's expired?
[Tomas] Yeah, that's it. Thanks.
[foreboding music continues]
[foreboding music intensifies, fades]
Wow, so predictable! You're here again.
- Why? Jealous?
- Looks delicious. Of course!
- That was quick!
- One hotdog, please.
Make it a little burnt.
Here, take this, I'll cover Uncle's too.
Oh.
You look sad, all frowny. You good?
- I'm fine.
- Oh? Oh, really?
Alright. Hold on…
You're stressed again,
you'll end up even balder at this rate.
- You testing me?!
- Okay, okay. Chill…
Come on, I'm just joking.
It's my birthday, isn't it?
Bir--Birthday?
It's tomorrow! You're too early.
- Why not celebrate now?
- Wait, my hotdog!
- Are you coming?
- I can't.
I've got work.
But I'll try, I'll really try to come.
It's your 70th birthday.
Of course, I have to be there.
Remember, if you don't show up,
forget about…
Forget about what?
- The money I owe you.
- Wow, nice try!
- Huh?
- Yeah.
[muffled] Hey, that's not fair! Come on…
Make sure to bring Gab, okay?
I'm not even sure if they'll allow her.
- Why not?
- Not sure if she'll be allowed.
But you said you'd bring her?
I just want the whole
family there for my birthday.
You just want Gab and
me to treat you, don't you?
What do you want as a gift?
Just tell me already.
- What?
- What else? Obviously…
- [laughing]
- You already know what I want.
- Let's go?
- Alright.
Miss, keep the change.
- Let's go, let's go. Let's go.
- Okay, okay.
[foreboding music resumes, crescendos]
[somber music playing]
[somber music continues]
[upbeat cultural music playing]
[upbeat cultural music continues]
[car engine revving]
[camera shutter clicks]
[inaudible dialogue]
[car door closes]
[camera shutters clicking]
[upbeat cultural music continues]
[clattering]
[camera shutters clicking]
[car engine revving]
[upbeat cultural music continues]
[camera shutters clicking]
- [bright cultural music continues]
- [guest chatting indistinctly]
[clattering]
[upbeat cultural music continues]
[engine revving]
[music becomes suspenseful]
[camera shutters clicking]
[suspenseful music continues]
[clattering]
[camera shutters clicking]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[suspenseful music continues to build]
[suspenseful music continues]
Out of everyone you've taught,
Raven's the worst.
A traitor with no sense of gratitude.
Okay, I'm in.
Madam's in the area.
She's entering the ballroom.
I am so in awe…
by someone as
fearless as you, Sec. Barrios.
You've made enemies with many.
The congressional hearing is on the way.
Maybe that's where
everyone will learn what I've uncovered.
[JB] Wolf, what's your brother doing here?
- Diego Aguinaldo?
- Aguinaldo?
- As in, connected to…
- Yes!
Is he a threat?
Keep eyes on him.
- How are you?
- Cool off.
All elements are set, standing by.
Manuel Aguinaldo still adopted him.
Be careful, Andres,
he can't find out who you are.
Remember, you're undercover.
He won't see me, don't worry.
But I'm not leaving either.