- I made a mistake.
- We made a mistake.
Me too.
I apologize.
Just don't let it happen again.
It won't happen again, Miguel.
That was my last contract.
I'm leaving the group.
We'll still see each other.
Maybe it'll be more fun to
hang out outside of work.
- Yeah.
- We'll be more relaxed.
JB, do you know the details
of our new contract?
No.
Let's wait for the Contractor.
He'll tell us all about it.
I miss Andres.
I sent them to a shipping vessel.
Marina Pacifica.
It's nice to imagine a life
where you, me, and Junjun
are living happily together.
Grandma…
Don't worry. I believe that will happen.
[theme music playing]
[Greg] Andres.
Sir?
What brings you here?
There's a new contract.
I want you in.
[dramatic music sting]
Sir, I left the group
because of what I did.
I haven't agreed to your leaving.
Sir.
But I already told you.
[Greg] Let's go.
We'll talk as I drive.
[engine revving]
This is Mt. Talimba,
it's a very steep mountain.
That's where Sameo Patel's
hideout is located.
He's a drug lord.
Supplier of drugs in Asia.
Patel?
A foreigner?
His father is a foreigner,
his mother is Filipino.
He said he grew up in the Philippines.
But I think he only came here
to smuggle drugs.
Mayor, aside from drugs,
is he involved in other illegal
activities in your area?
There's a chance they're also
involved in human trafficking
and exploitation of local workers.
You mean there are people
living on that mountain?
He brought them in to use and sell drugs,
which caused an increase in crime rates.
Do you think he has
connections with other groups
in and out of the country?
I'm sure he has.
But I don't know which group.
Is there a way for us to identify them?
Like tattoos or any form
of identification?
He uses his wealth
to manipulate everyone.
He makes donations left and
right here in our province.
In fact, most people see him
as a philanthropist.
Aren't your people
capable of dealing with him?
Or even the local police?
Our forces are no match against him.
We don't have enough arms
and manpower to take them on.
We've tried many times,
but each attempt had the same outcome.
Bodies of our men found lifeless
at the foot of the mountain.
[foreboding music playing]
[man] Sir Benjie.
I'm sure Sir Sameo's win
in the upcoming election
will further widen the scale
of our operations.
We must give out more money
to influence voters
especially in the neighboring towns.
Sir Sameo will soon file
his candidacy for governor.
[foreboding music intensifies]
Are these new?
[gunshots]
I don't want any mistakes.
[foreboding music continues]
[man] Take those men
to the foot of the mountain.
[foreboding music continues]
That's why I need you and your team.
I need your help.
[foreboding music fades]
- [Miguel] You're so…
- [Gab] Contractor's here!
[Tomas] Contractor!
- [Greg] Team.
- [Miguel] Sir.
[Tomas] Oh!
You're back!
- Andres!
- [Greg chuckles]
My boy!
Is that really you?!
Oh my god!
It's like I'm looking in the mirror!
[Tomas, Andres chuckle]
Thank you, sir.
I didn't know you had a heart.
Come here.
[Greg chuckling softly]
You smell good, sir.
[upbeat music playing]
[Tomas] The band's back together!
We're complete! Let's go!
- I got you something, dude.
- All that?
Of course! We have here
pan de coco and pan de regla.
We also have different flavors of hopia,
mongo, baboy and ube
special ensaymada,
and your favorite, strawberry cake.
You think it's my favorite?
- It's not?
- No.
Damn, who said that was your favorite?
- I'll take the coffee.
- Okay. Sorry, dude.
I got it wrong.
Honestly, dude?
I'm so happy you're back.
I feel whole again.
And…
What made you come back anyway?
Wait. Maybe I should ask,
why did you come back?
Wow. [chuckles]
I see.
You're a man of few words, aren't you?
[both chuckle]
But seriously. Come on, dude!
Stop acting so nonchalant.
I know you're just acting strong.
But deep, deep down inside you,
I know you missed me.
[chuckling]
You missed us, didn't you?
I mean, didn't you miss…
[inhales deeply]
…Sir JB's deep, thoughtful breaths?
[imitating JB] Team! Move! Move! Move!
[chuckles]
Didn't you miss
Sir Greg's mission updates?
[imitating Greg] Hello, Team?
[makes radio static sound]
[imitating Greg] You're on your own.
And then he'll arrive
once the enemies are down.
[both chuckle]
He only shows up
when the mission is over, right?
How about Miguelito's confusing commands.
- Hey.
- I'm not shaming him for it.
Sometimes it's funny.
[imitating Miguel] Stand! Down! Soldiers!
Does he want me to stand up or stay down?
Didn't you miss those?
How about Max's octopus bangs?
[chuckles]
[imitating Max]
Enemy on your left. Enemy on your right.
- It sure is distracting.
- [chuckling softly]
How about Gab's curls?
Didn't you miss them?
And how about my style?
I've got one heck of a mullet.
What? "Mullet"?
- Yeah.
- What's that?
A mullet that's curly.
[both laugh]
But you know what?
If I were to leave, I'll miss you dearly.
Because you're like my second family.
I mean, can you imagine?
I gained two sisters,
three brothers, and…
And an uncle.
[both laugh]
What if they hear you?
I don't care. I can say it out loud.
[laughs]
But I'm really excited.
And, come to think of it,
in your search to find your brother,
you found six cool siblings.
You found six incredible siblings.
Sorry, I meant five siblings
and one uncle.
[Tomas laughs]
[sighs deeply]
Eat up.
Go ahead. You can take this.
- Looks like you want it.
- Actually, it's my favorite.
- I knew it.
- [both laughing]
It's my favorite.
You can have it.
Mm!
It's good!
The uncle is busy.
He's managing his kids.
[both chuckling]
[pensive music playing, fades]
This is where you're going.
The summit of Mt. Talimba.
[suspenseful music playing]
From the last stop,
it's a 50-kilometer trek.
It's going to take you
around two days to get there.
That's where you'll find Sameo Patel.
A notorious druglord.
[trilling]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Greg] And this is Benjie Alcazar,
the right-hand man of Sameo.
[trilling]
[suspenseful music continues]
And lastly, Monching Santiago.
He's the head of security
at Sameo's place.
[trilling]
A few hundred meters
away from his house,
is where the hideout
of Sameo's men is located.
There is a meth lab on-site.
[trills, pings]
And according to intel,
Sameo Patel is often alone.
Very reclusive and mysterious.
The people know him only by name
because of his donations.
They've never met him in person,
which means he uses money
to get whatever he wants.
[JB] Sir.
Yes, JB?
Do we have a local asset there?
No.
According to the mayor,
all the undercover cops he's sent
have been found dead
at the foot of the mountain.
So we have no assets at the moment.
Now, there's a community near them.
In Sitio Mandalo.
All of the people there
are loyal to Sameo.
Because of all the food supplies,
donations, and favors
he's been giving them.
Clearly, it's just a strategy
to get the locals to cover up
his illegal operations.
Wow. Manipulative.
I know a person.
[Greg] That's why we can't
trust anyone in that place.
The goal is to eliminate Sameo Patel.
Are you in?
- Definitely, sir.
- Yes, sir.
[Greg] Good. We will do this
clean and quiet.
For now, take care of any
unfinished business you have.
I don't want anything getting
in the way of this mission.
[suspenseful music continues]
We leave tomorrow at 0400 hours.
Any questions?
- No, sir.
[suspenseful music fades]
[dramatic music stings]
[birds chirping]
- [faucet running]
- [plates clinking]
Leave it to me, Grandma.
Did Mister Domeng say how much
the land is selling for?
[Esang]
Oh, it only costs 20 million pesos!
Where on earth will we
get that kind of money?
Twenty million?
How is that possible?
[Esang] I don't know!
My god, even if we all
chip in and work together,
we'll never be able to afford it.
[water splashing]
[plate clinks]
What are you thinking, Andres?
Don't tell me you have 20 million pesos?
And where would he get that huge amount?
[Esang] Gosh, this kid.
[uneasy music playing]
[plates, cutlery clinking]
[chuckles softly]
[inhales deeply, sighs]
"I'm truly in awe with
the person you are becoming."
[somber music playing]
[sniffles, breathes deeply]
[somber music continues]
Are you sure about this?
Yes, I am.
[chimes]
[Max sniffles]
[somber music continues]
Fifty million.
[foreboding music playing]
[exhales]
Fifty million?
Isn't that too much?
There are plenty of people we need to pay
in order to pull some strings.
Bro.
If you really want them
to release your father,
it can be arranged.
[foreboding music continues]
[exhales deeply]
Fifty million…
[breathes deeply]
Get it done.
[foreboding music intensifies]
[birds calling, chirping]
[phone buzzing]
Update me.
[man] We have a lead on Agno.
Is that verified?
Yes. There's no doubt about it.
Send me the details.
[pensive music playing]
[rapid gunshots echo]
[man yells]
Come on!
- [gunshots]
- [pensive music continues]
They killed all of our comrades!
I'm going to kill them all!
How did they find out where we are?!
[gunshots]
Goddammit! There must be a mole among us!
Lion! Giraffe!
There's an alternate exit to the left.
I'll cover you.
- [gunshots]
- [pensive music continues]
Screw it, Noah! Go on ahead!
I'll kill these bastards!
[Lion grunts angrily]
[gunshots]
[Lion groans]
Lion!
[pensive music continues]
[gunshots]
[booming]
[grenade pin clicks]
[boom echoes]
[groans softly]
[labored breathing]
[man] Go on! Take him away!
- [Greg gasping weakly]
- [footsteps echoing]
[breathing faintly]
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music intensifies]
Uncle, where are you going?
Somebody pressed charges against me.
I'll find a way to settle this.
You won't get imprisoned.
Jake just died.
Whoever killed him
might come back for you.
Why would they go after me?
JB will be in command of this mission.
I won't be joining you.
One shot, one kill.
We can't be seen. So for now,
we have to keep on moving.
If we go straight, we'll be at
the south entrance within an hour.
We need to go around.
The south entrance
is swamped with enemies.
We're here now.
If we do that, it'll take us three hours.
Your call, JB.
We need to get out of here.
- [man yelling]
- [gunshots]
[booming]