General, give me all the channels, assets,
and intel pertaining to El Cano.
They dragged my
men's families into our fight
I can't just let that slide.
Sir, this isn't about the job anymore.
This is personal.
I just want to say, Dad,
that I love you so much.
God, I wish I said it sooner.
Each day, I prayed that you would wake up.
Now that your brother is gone,
I can't possibly leave
you to face this world alone.
I love you so much, you bastard.
I love you more.
None of this will be in vain, Dad.
I promise you that.
A few days ago,
we received a message from a boy
who had been missing for nearly a year.
His name is Pio Magnaye.
We traced it to a remote
location in Lakandula.
General.
I will end El Cano.
I'm going to kill Manuel.
Andres, someone is looking for you.
Andres!
[theme music playing]
[inhales deeply]
Wow.
- [distant birds chirping]
- [sniffs]
What a breathtaking view.
[wind whooshing]
I'm pleased you were
able to get this back, Andres.
Well…
I'm just here to check up on you.
See how you're doing.
Ask if you're safe out
here with your grandma.
We're doing fine.
Good.
With how quickly everything happened…
we never really got to talk.
We never got the chance
to meet as a group, you know.
How's life treating you, Miguel?
Funny you should ask.
I'm okay.
I'm lucky, Andres.
I was able to send my wife
and child out of the country.
But the families of our friends?
Well, not so much.
After the job order
we received for Barrios
and what happened to your brother,
Manuel Aguinaldo ordered
a massacre on our team.
Andres.
Both of Max's mothers are dead.
[unsettling music playing]
And so is Tomas's brother.
The man who raised him?
Badly injured.
And as for Gab…
Her father is fighting for his life.
But her stepmother…
She's dead.
She was four months pregnant.
They were mercilessly hunted down,
shot, bombed…
Burned to the ground.
- [crying softly, sniffles]
- [somber music playing]
And Gen. Bonifacio, JB's father…
[sniffles]
He was brutally killed in his cell.
Andres.
[somber music continues]
You know me.
[sniffles]
I know we've had…
many differences in the past.
But… you know me.
It's never personal for me.
I'm a sniper, I work from afar.
[Miguel sniffles]
But when I saw…
how our friends' lives were destroyed,
only one thought ran through my mind.
All of you.
[somber music continues]
My team.
You're my tribe.
My people.
[whimpers]
And my family.
[somber music continues]
[frustrated groan]
[yells]
Damn, Andres.
[sniffles]
This time…
it's personal.
[somber music continues]
[stirring music playing]
[Miguel] Andres.
Thank you for granting my request.
Let's go.
[stirring music continues]
Andres, a lot has happened.
On our last mission,
we were compromised, and unfortunately,
we had casualties.
[dark dramatic music playing]
I'm really sorry for what happened.
And I take full responsibility.
Manuel and El Cano are the enemies.
I will make things right.
[dark dramatic music continues]
I'm with you, sir.
Thank you.
[music crescendos]
[Manuel] You all know why you're here.
You're not kids anymore.
Here, you're soldiers of change.
I'll teach you how to stand your ground,
face your fears.
and fight anyone.
Up!
Down!
March!
Up!
Aim!
Keep it steady!
Down.
Turn!
Kneel.
Up!
Turn.
March!
[Manuel] Here…
you'll learn things
they won't teach you in school.
[dark dramatic music playing]
And while the world
turns its back on you…
[man] Don't slow down!
- One, two..
- [knives swooshing]
- [Manuel] In here…
- [knife swooshing]
I'll give you a reason to live.
- [man] Six!
- [knives swooshing]
- Seven!
- Eight!
- [knives swooshing]
- Nine!
- Ten! Faster!
- [knives swooshing]
- [dark dramatic music continues]
[Manuel] Each one of you is important.
And someday…
you will usher in a change to the system.
I want to go home.
My family's waiting for me.
[sniffling]
[dark dramatic music continues]
[sobbing]
Don't cry.
Don't cry. Come here.
Excuse me.
[sniffles]
I just want you to know that…
we're your family now.
They are your new family.
[dark dramatic music continues]
And I want all of you to know that…
if you leave through that door…
I won't be able to protect you.
And you won't just be
endangering yourselves…
You'll be endangering your loved ones.
[dark dramatic music continues]
[dark dramatic music ends]
[Miguel exhales heavily]
Sir.
They're all coming, right?
["Liwanag Sa Dilim" instrumental playing]
[Miguel] Guys!
- How have you been?
- Hi.
[Miguel] Everything's going to be okay.
Right?
- What's up, doc?
- Hey, bro. Good to see you.
["Liwanag Sa Dilim"
instrumental continues]
Max, hi.
["Liwanag Sa Dilim"
instrumental continues]
[song fades]
We've all lost someone.
[unsettling music playing]
A father, a mother…
[unsettling music continues]
A brother…
A friend…
They were people
who weren't part of the fight.
People we promised…
to protect.
And that's not the only thing we lost.
We also lost a piece of ourselves.
[unsettling music continues]
This is all Manuel Aguinaldo's doing.
And to think…
he was once one of us.
Wait, hold on. "One of us?"
You've worked with him before?
Yes.
I trusted him.
But he betrayed the group
because we have different beliefs.
What do you mean?
To him, everything is rotten.
The system, the government, and justice.
He believes the freedom we're fighting for
is just all an illusion.
[unsettling music continues]
He believes that if
the masses have the power to speak,
everything will be
plunged into further chaos.
[unsettling music continues]
So what does he want to happen?
He wants to abolish everything.
[unsettling music continues]
He wants discipline and blind obedience.
He wants respect that comes from fear.
[unsettling music continues]
Ultimately,
he wants control.
[unsettling music intensifies]
I'm in.
Me too.
I'll kill all of them.
I'm going to make them all pay.
[unsettling music continues]
That being said,
I have a plan.
[unsettling music continues]
[music turns dramatic]
[dramatic music continues]
[vehicles revving]
[dramatic music builds][
[door opens]
[engines revving]
[Greg] This operation just escalated.
We need more boots on the ground.
Black Viper Tactical
will be our reinforcement.
They're also Filipinos.
But they are stationed in North Carolina.
They specialize in counterinsurgency
and hostage recovery.
[dramatic music crescendos]
Lakandula is a place
destroyed by a violent war.
But we can't be complacent.
It seems quiet on
the outside but a lot is going on inside.
Is that it? Let's do it.
We'll leave no man alive.
It's not easy.
There are kids that could be involved.
I've long been following them.
I know their capabilities.
You need to talk to your people.
[gun cocks]
I got my frags, my flash, and my smoke.
Same, same.
Wolf, do you need help?
Let me just remind
you that this is not just an operation.
This is war.
[theme music playing]