- [gunshot]
- [gun clicks]
I'm out!
[gun clicks]
Where are they?
I'm almost out!
- [gunshots]
- [gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[tires screeching]
[grunts]
Go, go, go!
[gunshots]
- [yelling]
- [gunshots]
- Cover!
- Andres!
- Let's go!
- Move! Go, go, go!
JB, go on ahead
to the landing zone!
Secure the package.
- I'll handle this.
- Copy!
Where are you?
The police are coming.
You guys have to move faster.
We're trapped in a crossfire.
If you're not here in
15 minutes, they will leave you.
- [distant gunshots]
- [gun cocks]
- Just leave me here!
- [distant gunshots]
No, Max!
Hang in there.
We're not leaving you.
- [gunshots]
- [grunting]
Friend on your six.
[grunting]
- [blows landing]
- [grunting]
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
[muffled] I'm Timor!
They are not only after us.
They want to kill you too.
You have 10 minutes
to finish the job.
You need to go
to the landing zone now!
[helicopter blades whirring]
[theme music playing]
[soft dramatic music playing]
[soft dramatic music continues]
[Miguel] Max.
Are you okay?
- She'll be fine.
- Yeah, I'm good. Thanks.
She's excited to be reinstated.
You're good, right?
I'm just making sure.
- I'm alright.
- You're a tough one.
General's men aren't here yet.
- [bag thuds]
- [Tomas huffs]
[line ringing]
General.
We have the package.
Where are you?
Greg.
Keep the package secure.
Don't bring him to me
until I say so.
The President is
getting involved.
What? Why?
Timor's group
is making its move.
Just lie low for now.
Okay, we'll be on standby.
As for Timor,
keep him alive.
[unsettling music playing]
Team.
Change of plans.
JB.
Follow me.
- [Max] Let's go.
- [JB] Let's move.
Let's go.
[Tomas] Hurry up.
I don't have time for you.
[soft dramatic music playing]
[car engine humming]
[soft dramatic music continues]
[car door opens, closes]
- [music stops]
- [birds chirping]
[car doors open]
[car doors close]
- [birds chirping]
- [footsteps thudding softly]
Let's go.
[door shutter opens]
[door opens]
- Where to?
- Upstairs.
JB, where are we?
Contingency plan.
This way.
[footsteps thudding softly]
[door creaks, closes]
[helmet thuds]
[door closes]
[rope rustling]
[gun clicks]
[door closes]
[Tomas] I didn't realize
this was your house, sir.
Who lives here?
No one.
Your house is nice.
Good architecture.
- Sir.
- Team, let's regroup.
First things first,
a lot of things happened
in Cerdova.
What happened to you guys?
Sir, I want to make
something clear.
The opportunity
presented itself.
I had to make that call.
That's on me.
Someone got hurt.
Max almost died.
I didn't intend for someone
to get hurt, sir.
No one wanted it
to happen,
but unfortunately,
that was the result.
That's why it is important
our every step is calculated.
One wrong move
will surely put one of us
in danger.
Let this be a lesson
to all of us.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Sir JB's a hotshot.
Did you see his achievements?
[chuckles]
It's a lot.
[birds chirping]
Sir JB, idol!
Sir JB, I don't know if
I've mentioned this before,
you and your father are my idol.
[chuckles]
Sir, how does it feel to be
the son of a general?
[JB] Tomas, this isn't
the time for idle chitchat.
Man your post.
Stay sharp.
Yes, sir.
I guess that's how it is when
you're the son of a general.
You're always being told
what to do.
- But, you know what?
- [quirky music playing]
When I join the military,
I'll do everything Sir JB did.
I'll follow in his footsteps.
- Everything?
- Mm-hmm.
- Everything.
Including how he was dismissed?
You were dismissed too, right?
You're ex-military, too.
Watch your mouth.
Get back to work. Go.
- Sorry.
- Hop to it.
[Tomas mumbling] So grumpy.
[Gab sighs]
[quirky music continues]
[unsettling music playing]
[knocking on door]
- [thud]
- [grunts]
- [gun clatters]
- [groans]
- [kick lands]
[door slams]
[suspenseful music playing]
[thud]
[suspenseful music continues]
[hurried footsteps]
[sighs sharply]
[suspenseful music continues]
[tires screeching]
Get in!
Stop resisting!
[tires screeching]
[unsettling music playing]
Where am I?
I said, Where am I?!
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[unsettling music continues]
Oh, shoot!
You're ruining my life!
I know.
That's why I don't understand
why you're having me followed!
All I want is for you
to have the best life!
Really? Is that so?
Is that why you're
making me your puppet?!
Controlling and living
my life for me?!
I'm only doing what's
right for you.
"Right?"
- "Right?"
- Yeah.
To the point that you
destroyed my name
to get me fired
from service?!
- Because you're killing yourself!
- [scoffs]
This is not
the life I want for you!
Right.
- Okay.
Okay.
I am disowning myself!
And I am not allowing it!
Gabriela!
- [grunts]
- [kick lands]
Stop it!
- [blows land]
- [groans]
[grunts]
- [kick lands]
- [groans]
That's enough!
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
Enough!
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
[vase shatters]
Aah!
- [kicks land]
- [groans]
I said enough!
- [kicks land]
- [groans]
Gabriela, enough!
Bye!
[groans]
[tense music playing]
[groans in frustration]
You call yourselves men,
and yet a kid beat you?!
[morose music playing]
[car approaching]
[sighs] So?
I need money.
How much is the contract
worth again?
[morose music continues]
It's a good thing
I kept this.
- Is that really necessary?
- Of course.
Come on.
- Can you manage?
- Yeah.
Okay.
[JB exhales sharply]
So, what happened
to this house?
It's nice,
but it seems
it was abandoned.
[inhales deeply]
Exactly that.
Abandoned.
[sighs deeply]
Thank you.
For what?
For this.
Oh.
Max.
Get enough rest, okay?
We can't afford to lose you.
[somber music playing]
Do you remember…
whenever I got hurt,
you'd get upset?
You don't want to see me
getting hurt.
[melancholic music playing]
Don't get mad, okay?
[melancholic music continues]
[plate clinks]
[Andres sighs]
Go eat.
[Timor breathes sharply]
[unsettling music playing]
[Man] A tattoo of a sword
with fire.
All of our abductors
have it.
[unsettling music continues]
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
[groans]
Did you have something to do
with my brother's disappearance?
[laughing]
You think that's funny?!
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
- [Andres] Answer me.
Tell me! Did you have
something to do with it?!
You don't want to answer me?
You monster!
- [thud]
- [groans]
Where is he?!
You still don't want
to answer?!
- [blow lands]
- Where did you take him?!
- [Timor groans]
- Answer me! Where is he?!
You still won't answer, huh?!
- [blow lands]
- Where did you take him?!
[Timor groans]
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
You bastards!
How could you
abduct children?!
- [blow lands]
- [groans]
Andres! What's going on?!
Andres! That's enough!
Stop it!
[Andres] You still don't want
to talk?!
- Enough!
- Tell me! Where is he?!
- You bastard!
- Stop it!
You bastard!
Where is my brother?!
- Where is he?!
- Enough!
Where is he?!
- Andres.
- What did you do to him?!
- That's enough!
- You monster!
- Andres, enough!
- I'm going to kill you!
Calm down. Relax.
[breathing heavily]
Andres, calm down.
What's the problem?
Sir, he had something to do
with my brother's abduction!
It's the reason
I joined your group.
I'm looking for my brother.
- [tense music playing]
- [Andres breathing heavily]
You keep asking me what
I was doing in Cerdova, right?
I was looking for my brother!
I agreed to do the job order
to abduct Timor
because he's connected
to human trafficking!
That's what I was doing!
[tense music continues]
- I'm still the father.
- Yes, when you're sober.
But when you're drunk…
I'm alcohol free!
Until when?!
No! Don't leave!
Don't die on me!
Don't leave me!
You can come to me
if you have problems.
We're a team here.
What are you willing to do
to save your brother?
- What do you want?
- Let me go.
I'm the only one
who can help you.
Andres, I have an army
of people working for me.
Am I wrong or am I right?