HEAVENLY EVER AFTER
Hey, Jang Gi-hwan!
I know you're in there,
so stop pretending and open the door!
Why did you borrow money
if you couldn't pay it back?
Hey. Open it.
Who are you?
Are you Jang Gi-hwan's mom?
Yes, why?
He's inside, isn't he?
He went to the Hangang River.
Your excuses never change.
We already checked the Hangang River.
Move aside.
Why would you lend money
to someone who can't pay it back?
The one who doesn't pay is the asshole,
not the one who lent it.
She sure worked hard raising such garbage.
Do you consider yourselves good sons
by making money this way?
Were your folks delighted when you bought
them gifts with the money you made?
Fucking hell.
Lady.
What are you trying to do?
You kids have nothing better to do
than intimidate people.
That's right.
Then why don't you pay your son's debt,
Ms. High-and-Mighty?
Yes, it's only right.
I have nothing but this body of mine.
So take me and use me however you want.
Seriously. What are you doing?
I said, take me.
You won't find a single penny in here.
Get me out of here. Just take me.
Come on! What the hell are you doing?
-Take me.
-Damn it.
What a shitty day.
Lady.
I'll be back.
See you then.
Geez.
HORSE RACING NEWS
Pegasus! You shouldn't have tripped…
What is it? Did I wake you
from your horse-racing dream?
What's wrong?
How much did you borrow from them?
Was someone here?
I mean those rough-looking guys.
Well, about 30 million.
Gosh, that's a lot.
When? Before me?
I guess so.
What about my money?
How much was it?
You initially borrowed 600,000 won.
You paid well the first month
then disappeared without a word
last month.
It's 650,000 won now
including the interest.
You see…
I couldn't work
because it's been raining a lot.
Rain didn't stop deliverymen
from delivering parcels and food.
Those muscleheads are still young,
so they can keep coming.
So let's settle
this old lady's debt first.
Come on!
This old hag just won't quit. Damn it.
I'll pay back your lousy 600,000 won,
so just leave.
Right? You're loaded anyway.
My money doesn't mean jack shit to you,
does it?
"Jack shit"?
I didn't know you knew how to curse.
That's not all.
I kill people too.
See? I'm wearing rubber gloves.
Kill me if you want.
Go ahead. Do as you please.
You're not reading the room, are you?
What room?
-What's that?
-Which one should I use?
What?
Damn it!
Hold on, sir.
Let me explain…
Ma'am?
No…
Wait. I…
This is all I have.
I'm telling the truth.
Pickle it.
Wait. Pickle what? What?
Why?
I gave you the money.
More salted seafood.
Why are you making kimchi?
And in someone else's house too!
I told you our mister's eyes burn
when we do it at our place!
-Should we pack it now?
-Yes.
What a nasty old hag.
There they go again.
Damn it.
Hey, did you just splash water on us?
No.
I was just emptying the bucket.
I'm sorry.
You think you won't need money
just because you've paid it back?
Some may never borrow money,
but nobody borrows just once.
I'll see you again, valued customer.
You're lacking one day.
Tomorrow, you'll owe me two days' worth.
Remember that.
Daily payments mean daily.
See you tomorrow.
What a nasty old hag.
Do you have a death wish?
Go to a bank
if you want the royal treatment.
You're the one who borrowed money from me
because you couldn't get a loan.
Don't expect special treatment.
Who's asking for that?
Stop by when there aren't customers.
It's embarrassing.
Who's embarrassed?
Me, who everyone talks badly about?
Or you, who borrowed
from someone they badmouth?
Geez. Here.
Take it and go.
Why associate with those
who barely act human?
You better watch your mouth!
Do you want to die?
Should I crack your head open
like this watermelon?
You gave me excess money.
Forget it!
Are you trying to be nice now?
I don't want money for it!
I want a new one.
The way it split so cleanly
shows it's perfectly ripe.
Here.
Come on. Do you really think
this gets rid of bad energy?
Words carry energy.
We can't let all those nasty things
we hear and say outside latch onto him.
Let me.
I'm home.
I made some fresh kimchi
just the way you like it.
I'll get dinner ready right away.
No.
"Yes, that's the flavor."
-Bowl.
-Right.
It looks delicious.
-You forgot to bring utensils.
-Right.
You're so in love.
You see him every day,
yet you're so eager to see him again.
I'm not eager.
I just pity that poor soul since
I'm the only one who'll take care of him.
Honey, I'm coming in.
You're back.
I made some red bean noodle soup
and fresh kimchi, your favorites.
Gosh, it must've been a lot of work.
It took some time
to make the dough from scratch.
You must be hungry. Did you wait long?
I wasn't waiting for the food.
I was waiting for you.
For me? Why?
Isn't it obvious?
Because I missed you.
Goodness.
Let me raise your bed.
I'll raise it now.
I did it the usual way,
but I'm not sure how it turned out.
I knew it.
I wanted to buy freshly salted seafood,
but there was none.
So I used the one at home.
It's so delicious
I almost jumped out of the bed.
Geez!
I can't stand your jokes!
I'm serious.
Should I try to get up then?
It's not working.
Maybe I didn't eat enough.
Is this really that funny to you?
What about your meal?
Well, I'll just eat with Young-ae
after you finish.
Goodness.
Here.
Oh my, this is embarrassing.
What's embarrassing about a husband
feeding his wife? Here.
That's true but…
No, stop it.
I don't want to.
I don't know! I'm so embarrassed!
This won't work for today.
MORNING, AFTERNOON, NIGHT
I know you're not sleeping.
Why do you always do this?
You've taken these your whole life.
That's exactly why
I want to stop taking them now.
It's not like taking them
is suddenly going to make
my legs move again.
I've lived a comfortable life,
thanks to you.
So I should at least cut down
on medication costs now.
I'm not doing this because of your legs.
I don't want the burden
of looking after you alone in my old age.
Don't worry.
I won't give you a hard time.
I won't be sick for long.
I'll go quietly when the time comes.
You better.
Or I'll follow you and nag you forever.
Now, why would you follow me?
You'll finally be free from this burden.
So fully enjoy the spring breeze.
You can take your time in joining me.
What spring breeze?
Sonya.
Your dad is unbelievable.
He talks about dying so casually.
Of course, I know he's just joking.
He used to play pranks like that
when he was younger too.
He'd put red pepper paste on his finger
and pretend he'd cut it off.
But then, one day,
he had actually gotten into an accident.
It would've been hard if I'd always
thought I was caring for a sick person.
But I just think
he's still trying to mess with me.
And that makes it less difficult.
You don't have to do this.
What? Why not?
I'm also part of the family.
I'll do things like that
while I'm still alive.
-I'll be going now.
-Okay.
Be careful.
It might rain,
so take an umbrella.
Geez, I definitely could've blocked it.
Ms. Lee, how do you predict it every time?
It's not a skill to be proud of.
And definitely not one to teach others.
Let's go.
Please teach me anyway.
That way,
I can protect you when you grow weak.
What?
That old man passed away.
Stay here.
Why?
You're not dressed for a funeral.
Are you going in there?
I have to.
But he passed away.
He might've died, but his debt remains.
Still…
It's not like he drank
and gambled away his money.
He just needed help
with his hospital bills
since his daughter was struggling.
I feel sorry for him.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
My husband's accident left him paraplegic.
I started giving out loans
using his insurance money
before I was even 30.
I get humiliated at the market every day.
They say I'm heartless and cruel.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
I do. It's the saddest thing.
Your father borrowed money from me.
What?
Are you here to collect money?
If you borrow money,
it's only right to pay it back.
"It's only right"?
Then is it also right to rush over here
and demand money from the dead?
Your father borrowed
a total of 370,000 won from me.
I don't need your money, so take it!
Do you think you'll live forever?
Won't you be ashamed to see him
when you die?
I hope you go straight to Hell
with that money!
I'll pray and pray for you to go to Hell!
Unbelievable!
Go to Hell!
Do you think
Heaven really exists?
Heaven? I'm sure it does.
Don't you think
Heaven would smell sweet like this?
-Right?
-Right.
It must exist, right?
It'd be unfair if it didn't.
It'd be very messed up if bad guys
and those who lived righteous lives
ended up in the same place.
Then I guess Hell must exist too.
There has to be one.
People who were evil and got away with it
have to end up there.
It's only right to gouge out their eyes
and cut off their tongues.
Why do you ask?
Something happened at the funeral home.
Those bastards…
No, that's not why.
I was just wondering
what happens after we die.
Why?
Are you afraid you'll go to Hell?
No, I'm not afraid.
You see,
my husband lived a righteous life.
Are you worried
you won't see him after you die?
It's not exactly that.
You'll go to Heaven too.
-Me?
-Yes.
Why?
Honestly, I don't know about others.
But you're nice to me.
Geez, I'm destined for Hell.
Instead of having you pay me back,
I'll just take your daughter.
That contract gives me the right.
Hurry up and stamp it.
What is this?
Gosh, what is this?
Honey!
Honey, there's a fire!
No!
Honey…
Goodness.
Did you have a nightmare?
No.
It seems like you had a scary dream.
Do you need my hand?
What?
Why are you coming out of that room?
Did you two…
You must be crazy.
Can't a married couple share a room?
Right. You're married.
What's that on your face?
He must've played a prank on you.
Do you want a hand mirror?
It's okay. Look at how happy he is.
-Who's here at this hour?
-I'm not sure.
Who is it?
I'm here to see the lady who lends money.
I even thought about
just ending it all with my kids.
But I thought I should persevere.
Young-ae.
Go get the juice bottles
she brought with her.
The box as well.
Okay.
So I want to join the loan business too.
I've seen you around the market
many times in the past.
I thought you were amazing.
Wait. Why aren't you drinking that?
Give me the box.
Take this back and focus
on getting your life back together.
But that's exactly why I'm here.
You don't have it all that bad yet
if you can bring gifts like this.
You can only do this job
when you don't even have the decency
to bring something like this.
Does that mean I shouldn't do it either?
-Do what?
-This job.
You said this job is only for those
who don't even have
the decency to bring gifts.
Is this a job you want to do?
After witnessing everything with me?
I know it's immoral,
but this is all that I know.
That doesn't mean
you should continue doing it.
You should try to learn something better.
Didn't you say it all started
with you collecting money from someone?
I received a tiny amount
as my husband's compensation.
Then someone asked to borrow it
because their son had an accident
and needed surgery.
We were in the same boat.
How could I not lend it? So I did.
But they never paid me back
and made countless excuses.
They called me their savior
when I lent it to them
but swore at me
when I came by to collect their payment.
I should have been there.
Back then, my heart would race
even when someone's voice
got a little louder while talking.
But now, there's nothing that scares me.
Except for one thing.
Which is?
My husband.
I'm afraid he might die later than me.
That's what scares me.
You have me.
That's what I'm terrified about.
Is the owner here?
Yes, hello.
Do we look like a joke to you?
No!
What? No?
What's the name of this flower?
They're trumpet vines.
They're beautiful.
They're very beautiful.
Aren't they?
Their beauty caught my eye.
The back of the flowers
looks just like you from behind.
The back?
Are you saying
I look prettier from behind?
No.
We see faces
all the time
when we're talking
or looking.
So we quickly notice the beautiful parts.
But the back of the head is different.
You need to care and have affection
to even notice the back of someone's head.
Then tell me
how the back of my head looks.
It's something
I'll never get to see in my lifetime.
It's saddening.
It's beautiful because it's saddening.
What does that mean?
I see
the 60 years of your life
that you wasted
because of me.
That's why
it's saddening
and beautiful.
You say the strangest things,
calling an old lady like me
pretty and whatnot.
People will think you've lost your mind.
Let them think what they want.
I can say that my wife is pretty
if I want to.
You were pretty at 20.
And you were pretty at 40.
But you…
You're the prettiest now.
Perhaps living together
makes my love grow with each passing day.
But you're the most gorgeous
you've ever been right now.
Yes.
And you're the most handsome
you've ever been right now.
ACCEPT JESUS AND GO TO HEAVEN!
HWADUNG CHURCH
I don't care where I go.
But please allow my husband
to go to Heaven.
And if possible,
let me go with him.
No, you don't need to send me there.
Oh my.
No, not my husband!
No!
Father! Lord!
Oh my.
We don't even go to church.
Is it okay for us to stick a cross here?
You have to believe to go to Heaven.
Sonya needs to go to Heaven.
Animals go to Heaven too, don't they?
I hope so.
Sonya.
Thank you for protecting my husband.
Stop right there!
-You bastard!
-Damn it.
Stop right there, you bastard!
Where do you think you're going?
Let us pray.
We pray that
Mr. Jang will pay off all his debt
before going to Heaven.
Amen.
Where are we going?
Father…
Not the face!
Leave it.
The stain won't come out
if you don't wipe it right away.
Your umbrella doesn't have holes, does it?
I guess my time is almost up too.
You could tell
that he was pretty athletic.
The kimchi juice was a curveball.
He didn't throw it straight.
Let's buy some chives and clams
and make some pancakes.
CHEOLSEONG MART
Should we go grocery shopping?
What's the matter with you?
I had a rough day, so cut it out. Geez.
What's wrong?
Really?
Are you really going to give me
a tough time?
Ms. Lee, what's wrong?
I just came home after a long day,
and he's pulling a prank again.
Whatever, I don't care
if you get up or not.
Is he gone?
Yes.
That was long.
That took…
a long time.
Ms. Lee…
Did you take your medicine?
Yes, I did.
You're not lying to me again, are you?
I'm taking it on time, so don't worry.
Geez, she didn't…
RICE CAKE MILL
Hello.
What can I get for you, ma'am?
Where's the owner?
Are you looking for my mother?
She's at the hospital
for knee replacement surgery.
So she has money
for knee replacement surgery
but none to pay me back.
What are you doing?
Right. You…
Gosh, they're heavy.
My arms hurt.
How about this one?
No, I want one in pink.
-Pink?
-I need a large size.
Hello, ma'am.
RICE CAKE MILL
Does it fit?
Yes, it does.
But it feels a bit awkward
to wear a dress.
You look pretty.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Like this?
Yes.
What are you doing?
This dress is uncomfortable.
Try to walk more modestly.
I'm going to stop by another shop.
Go inside and take your time.
In there? Why?
What?
Am I supposed to go in there?
What? Do you not want to?
No, it's not like that but…
Damn it! What the hell?
Pay back my money!
Damn it! Come on!
Why aren't you paying me back?
Give me my money!
Give it to me! Pay up!
-Pay me back!
-What are you doing?
-Let me go!
-Just go.
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
What are you doing all of a sudden?
What do you think?
I'm doing what I always do.
But I didn't ask you to do that.
Why did you lie to me?
About what?
He said you promised
to forget about the debt they owed
and offered to help their mill
with the money you've saved up!
That's because I thought--
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
You suddenly made me wear this dress
and introduced him to me!
That's because I thought you liked him.
That's not what this is about!
You're planning to leave me behind
before you go off on your own!
Everyone dies when they get old.
Who doesn't know that?
I'm so hurt and upset.
I know you'll die one day,
but you shouldn't try so hard to leave.
I'm tired of taking care of people now.
I want to stop.
I'm all grown up now.
You don't need to take care of me.
I'll take care of you from now on,
so don't worry.
You don't need to.
Then at least teach me
how to use an umbrella.
Water ahead.
To the left…
Kimchi juice.
To the right…
Croaker.
Behind you…
Mackerel.
That's not right for mackerel.
Is it different?
Of course, it is.
Mackerel is a blue-backed fish,
so it has good elasticity.
So, when it hits the umbrella,
it bounces off like this.
Since croaker is a white fish,
it bounces off the umbrella like this.
I see.
One is fresh while the other is frozen.
You're starting to get it now.
You've mastered it now.
THE LATE LEE HAE-SOOK
CHIEF MOURNER: LEE YOUNG-AE
MAY SHE REST IN PEACE
Were you a client of Ms. Lee's?
Yes, we knew each other for a long time.
I know all of her friends,
but I've never met you before.
You wouldn't know me.
I knew her
before you even met her, Ms. Lee.
Oh, you know my name.
Well…
Of course.
THE LATE LEE HAE-SOOK
Lee Hae-sook.
Am I…
Am I dead?
Goodness. What's happening?
Oh my…
What's happening to me?
It's because there's no gravity.
Every soul that dies
asks the same question.
Do you understand now?
Yes…
There. That should do the trick.
Does your body get this light
when you die?
Gosh, I'm asking questions again.
It'd be nice if you'd think before asking.
Anyway, you need to leave this world.
It would be hard
if your body was heavy, right?
Wait. All my pain is gone too.
I was just thinking out loud.
You're a bit clever, aren't you?
Well…
When you die,
you can't take anything with you.
Not even your illnesses.
That's a relief.
My husband must've gone without pain then.
You don't know him, do you?
My husband passed away last year.
Mr. Ko Nak-joon.
How did you know?
I escorted him as well.
Let's go.
Sir!
Do you know what'll happen
if you cut this?
You'll neither go to the afterlife
nor meet your wife again.
Is that okay?
Will you be the one
who'll escort her when she dies?
Probably, since this is my turf.
In that case,
could you tell her
that I walked to the afterlife…
on my own
when you see her?
Are we done with questions now? Let's go.
-Hold on.
-What now? What?
What is it?
Where am I going?
You're dead,
so I'm guessing either Heaven or Hell.
But why are you upset?
Because you keep
asking questions so painfully.
Everyone dies for the first time.
No one is experienced.
I'm only asking
since I have no experience.
You're right.
-That was my mistake.
-Right.
Yes, you're right.
All right then.
Taxi, bus, bicycle, airplane, subway.
Pick one.
This must be like a personality test.
Like "what would you bring
to a deserted island?"
No. What transportation
do you want to take?
Are you going to walk to Heaven?
Will you fly to Hell?
I see.
Is it a premium taxi?
I could never afford anything expensive.
Give me your hand.
I'll untie that so you can fly away.
No, that's okay.
The others make me nauseous,
so I'll take the subway.
Subway it is.
-You can't change it now.
-Okay.
AFTERLIFE SUBWAY
THE SUBWAY TO THE AFTERLIFE
IS OPERATING NORMALLY
All right.
It'll be here in three minutes.
THE LATE LEE HAE-SOOK
Are you the Grim Reaper?
They used to call us that,
but not anymore.
Those were the good old days.
Everything's automated now,
so they don't need Grim Reapers anymore.
We just make sure the dead
don't float away due to zero gravity.
When I was little,
I thought the Grim Reaper harvested crops.
You know, since they're called "reapers."
Do Heaven and Hell really exist?
Yes, they do. They absolutely do.
I already told you so.
My husband probably went to Heaven, right?
I don't know.
Am I going to Hell?
I'm just anxious.
The judgment process is automated now too.
You'll know
whether you're headed to Heaven or Hell.
Your body will react.
If your body suddenly moves
at Hell Station, you're going to Hell.
If not, you'll go to Heaven.
There it comes.
Thank you for everything.
Is there a rating system?
No, there isn't.
What a shame.
-Our Father in Heaven…
-Father.
-…hallowed be your name.
Your kingdom come.
Your will be done,
on Earth as it is in Heaven.
-Father…
-Give us this day our daily bread.
Forgive us our debts,
as we also have forgiven our debtors.
-Father…
-Lead us not…
Attention, please.
This train is bound for the afterlife.
We are currently passing Sacheon Mountain
and crossing the Samdo River.
All passengers should remain calm
and wait for further instructions.
Thank you.
In a moment,
our train will arrive at Hell Station.
Please remain seated, everyone.
Will it be all right to sit?
-Let's sit for now.
-We can't get off.
-I can't go to Hell.
-Please…
Please, no…
I should've gotten off the train.
Our train has now arrived at Hell Station.
What?
What's wrong? Why am I moving?
I volunteered my entire life!
Why is this happening to me?
No!
-Hey!
-Help me!
Don't let go!
Ma'am!
Please grab onto me!
Please hold onto me!
I regret disappointing my parents.
Help me!
Lord…
Am I…
Am I going to Heaven?
Am I allowed to?
After all I've done?
Our train will soon arrive
at Heaven Station.
All remaining passengers,
please prepare to disembark.
You can't take anything with you
from here on.
Leave everything behind.
Leave what behind?
PREMIUM MATH FOR 10TH GRADE
I can't leave this.
If you don't, you can't enter.
My dog and I spent 20 years together.
I can finally see him now.
I need to meet him now, but without this…
You can leave it here.
You'll be able to meet him soon.
You can't take that with you.
I had no money, so I had to send
my children to an orphanage.
I worked like a dog and saved every penny
so I could get my children back.
But…
I died before I could even
give this money to them.
I'll leave this here.
So please…
Please…
Please give this to my children.
Okay?
I beg you…
Please don't let them
follow my footsteps
because of having no money.
This way.
You can put down the oxygen mask.
Please put it down.
No.
This isn't for me!
It's for that girl! That girl!
I'm at the emergency stairwell
on the sixth floor.
The door to the rooftop is sealed.
I can't see anything due to the smoke.
I'm currently with a child.
I have
five minutes of oxygen left.
Captain!
We're clearing a path to you now,
so hang in there!
Let's wrap this up quickly
and have some soju and pork belly.
Sounds good.
The other firefighters
are on their way.
Hang in there a little longer, okay?
I promise
I'll save you.
Please tell me
if the girl survived.
That's all I ask.
Hey. You're…
I'm sorry
I couldn't save you.
I'm sorry…
Why are you sorry?
It's my fault
that you're here.
They said I have to go alone
without Mom or Dad from here on.
I can't even sleep alone yet.
Can you come with me?
Protect me like you did before.
Do I have anything on me?
Please come forward.
Oh my.
I… What was that?
You may enter.
What?
Why don't I have anything?
Did I throw it away?
Did I forget to bring it?
Please go ahead.
Ma'am, please head over there.
You'll have your individual consultation.
Just answer a few questions,
and everything will be over.
Hello.
Ms. Lee Hae-sook born in 1945, correct?
Yes.
Okay. I need your signature of consent
on the part highlighted in yellow.
Flip through the pages.
There's quite a lot.
Please sign it.
Now, you'll make some decisions
regarding some matters
related to living in Heaven.
I'll ask you two questions,
and you just need to answer them.
Did you sign it?
All right then.
Here's the first question.
Welcome. You have arrived in Heaven.
Who would you like to live with?
You can't change your mind
once you make your decision.
And you can't live with them
if they're not in Heaven.
And of course, you can only live with them
if they agree as well.
Excuse me.
Where is Mr. Ko Nak-joon?
Mr. Ko Nak-joon?
One minute.
Mr. Ko Nak-joon, born in 1940,
is in Heaven.
Thank goodness.
Then--
And Mr. Ko…
He chose you as well,
so you can live together.
Okay. Here's the second question.
You have arrived in Heaven.
What age would you like to appear as
during your time here?
Once again, you can't change your mind
once you make your decision.
I looked my best at 20 and 25.
Should I pick 25
since that's when I met my husband?
Perhaps living together
makes my love grow with each passing day.
But you're the most gorgeous
you've ever been right now.
I pick 80.
Okay, 80.
Eighty… Eighty?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Are you really sure about this?
Absolutely.
It's been a while since I've had
a case like this. One minute.
Let's see…
Here you go.
What's this?
It's a narration button we give
to those who are 80 or older.
Press it,
and you won't need to struggle to speak
since it'll speak for you.
You know, it's that voice in your head.
The one that chatters nonstop
inside your mind.
It's meaningless, unhelpful,
and only caused problems in your life.
Right.
You could be a bit annoyed at first
since it sounds different
than when you heard it inside.
But…
Why do I need this?
Well…
You'll probably be short of breath.
You'll need it for a while.
The button will naturally disappear
once the voice in your head
no longer bothers you.
Hae-sook's heart was already racing.
Hae-sook's heart--
Hae-sook--
Here you go.
Hae-sook's heart was already racing.
What would she do first
when she meets her husband?
She'll hold his hand
and gaze at the face
that she missed so much.
-Then she'll passionately kiss him--
-This is nuts.
Stop.
I won't keep you for long.
How would you like to travel?
So there's the fast option,
the faster option,
and the superfast option.
Hae-sook wanted to ask
for the superfast option
to see her husband.
But she was embarrassed.
She's crazy. Goodness.
Isn't it convenient
having it speak for you?
She's just making things up.
Hae-sook wanted to pretend
like it wasn't true.
You must miss him a lot.
The fast option is for traditional methods
such as ship, airplane, train, and so on.
But since Heaven is so vast,
it'll take several days.
It could even take over a month.
Then what about the superfast option?
It's very humane
while being the fastest method.
Then I want that one.
But there are some risks involved.
Would that be okay?
Risks?
Yes, well…
You might get misdelivered
or have to live with a complete stranger.
I don't care. I'll do it.
Understood.
Please wait a moment.
WELCOME TO HEAVEN, EVERYONE!
Wait, why did she choose that age?
Ms. Lee Hae-sook! Wake up!
Oh my.
Ms. Lee.
You've arrived safely.
You met a talented magician.
It's rare to get here in one go.
All right.
This is the Heaven User Manual.
Enjoy your reunion
with your husband today,
and please visit
the community center tomorrow.
Have a nice day then.
-Wait.
-Yes?
I don't know where he lives.
Right.
Walk around a bit first.
Once your heart starts racing
and you feel excited,
continue walking in that direction
to find him.
Simple, isn't it?
Where my heart starts racing?
Goodness.
Oh my, it must be that way.
Her heart races like when she was 20,
but her knees are painfully frail.
Just hang in there for today.
I beg you.
You know that stone wall you talked about?
I'll neatly build one along the path.
And to make you feel welcome,
let's plant some trumpet vines
that you said were pretty, okay?
Like a traditional Korean house
yet also like a Western one,
let's put two houses together.
Let's also have a small garden
where you can grow
lettuce and perilla leaves
without exhausting yourself.
"This is the exact house
my husband described."
"He's waiting for me in there."
But suddenly,
anxiety sprouts in Hae-sook's heart.
"Could he really be waiting for me?"
"What if he's forgotten about me?"
"What if he left me behind
at Heaven's checkpoint
where everyone leaves everything behind?"
KO NAK-JOON
LEE HAE-SOOK
"Of course."
"He'd never do that."
"He'd never forget me."
Who is it?
"It's him!"
"I could never forget his voice."
"But…"
One minute.
Honey…
Sorry?
Hae-sook… What?
I'm screwed.
Right. What?
HEAVENLY EVER AFTER
So why is it only me?
This is no Heaven!
Everyone else has turned a new page
while you're all shriveled up…
We're too old to be acting like newlyweds.
He wanted to start over
young again with me.
-Honey. I want to show you something.
-What is it?
-Choco!
-Come here!
-Hong!
-Bbomi!
Heaven isn't a reward.
It means if you mess up here,
you can still end up in Hell.
They say sometimes
people come here by mistake, right?
If I'm in the wrong place,
then is someone coming to get me?
-What's that?
-What?
I'm so anxious for no reason.
Who are you looking for?
Nak-joon, is that you?
Nak-joon!
Excuse me. Hold on.
I'd rather be in Hell
than be like this, you jerk!
Subtitle translation by: Sooji Kim