The shape of the hairpin on Sun Mei’s head
is exactly the same
on Zhang Yun Li's left arm.
Tang Zhenyun
What are you doing?
Uncle.
Mind your own business.
Don't make trouble.
I didn't do anything.
Is your uncle crazy?
How dare you talk about others?
What did I do?
What’s wrong with me?
Commander.
I’ve done
you asked me to do.
Commander.
Take a look.
The headline of the newspaper.
can be written like this?
The major Chamber of Commerce invests in theaters.
The capital of entertainment has a bright future.
So literary.
The Chinese citizen
to let the people see
what they want the most.
is the weapon that caused
on Zhang Yun Li, Liu Shuang Zhu, Shen Ruchun,
It looks like the hairpin on Sun Mei’s head.
Sun Mei played the role of "Legendary Love of Dust Sea".
Liu Shuang Zhu’s colleague said
Liu Shuangzhu liked Sun Mei’s movie very much.
Now?
It's not easy.
Is it possible that
Sun Mei used her role as a movie star
to lure Liu Shuang Zhu into the trap.
That's easy.
You can bring her to interrogate her.
Maybe you can even find out
the strange house.
It's not that easy to catch people.
I'm afraid to alert them.
Police.
Let's go inside.
You two study it yourselves.
The lower class.
Stop pretending to be pure.
Kong Shun.
Tang Zhenyun.
You caught him at Red Moon House?
I'll welcome him when he gets out.
Why did he come out?
You'll go to jail if you kill someone.
and kill many people.
That means he's acquitted.
The law
is to restrict people like you.
Master Tobio is unhappy after spending money.
That's your fault.
Mommy.
My friend likes her.
Master Fei.
You can’t take her away.
You?
I'm not qualified.
I'm afraid the special agents will be unhappy.
Last time, the special agent came here for a drink.
He likes this girl.
Maybe
take her to enjoy her life.
You're threatening me with a special agent?
I'm a courtesan.
I wouldn’t dare to do that.
Master Fei,
Please be generous.
Why would you
like us?
Master Fei is good.
Come here.
to apologize to Master Fei.
You are generous.
Old man.
Mommy, buy some news.
Not enough.
A movie star like Sun Mei
can stand in Shanghai.
Is he backing up?
What do you think?
Who is her backer?
Sun Mei’s backer.
That’s really a mountain.
Take a guess.
The people first.
What task is Commander Zhao assigning to me?
Don't worry.
He'll tell you.
Why are there rats again?
What's wrong with you two?
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear me?
What did you hear?
There's noise.
This is a haunted house.
It's normal to hear noise.
It's a mouse
It's normal to have mice
No, the sound comes from the wall
from the wall.
Come on.
Pay if you break it.
Give it to her.
What is this?
Is this the place where the old mansion holds treasures?
There are so many things in your house.
That head, that hand and leg.
Cut the crap.
Flashlight, let's go inside.
Why do you have to follow me?
It's treasure hunting. How can I not come?
Be careful.
Wait
Women's footprints
The distance between the footprints was tight.
They should be careful.
The footprints were messy when they came back.
A big step, a heavy step.
I think he's running.
No matter who it is,
She was curious when she went there.
She was flustered when she came back.
I'm sorry.
Who could it be?
Hongxiu.
I... I don't know.
I... I saw nothing.
I saw...
What did you see?
Where is the secret passage to?
The secret we're looking for should be ahead.
Don't destroy these footprints.
This secret tunnel is quite long.
You know how to do this?
My family used to run a pawnshop. Why not?
What do you mean?
Don’t move.
Why does Sun Mei
looking outside the screen?
She is pleasing her backer.
The people ranked first.
Commander Zhao.
You can't take the film.
Why?
Use your brain.
If you take it,
all three of you will die.
You, Tang Zhenyun,
and Xia Yingqi.
Xia Mo.
She's right.
Back then,
you failed to protect me.
Now you have to protect Yingqi.
Do you think she's right?
Okay.
I'll listen to her.
Where did you come from?
Hurry up.
Miss Gao.
Where is the bathroom?
This way.
Commander Zhao is waiting for you.
Let's go.
Go.
Commander Zhao.
Miss Gao.
Once you enter this door,
I’ll treat you as my family.
Thank you, Commander Zhao.
Do you remember what I told you yesterday?
Yes.
Commander Zhao appreciates me.
and wants me to work for you.
If you work with me, there's no turning back.
A man with a narrow mind
can't live long here.
There's no reason to turn back even if the Arrow of Arrow is broken.
I understand.
Father taught me
to open this box.
Stocks.
This is
to open the cash cabinet in Shanghai.
to integrate the entertainment resources in Shanghai
to launch this World Entertainment Stock.
Chairman Tang,
Zhabei Chamber of Commerce is very important.
Do you have a plan?
Don’t worry, Commander Zhao.
We’ll do our best to cooperate.
President Zhang of the stock trade guild
He can give him whatever he likes.
Got it.
Commander Zhao.
Chairman Zhang is on board.
The stock commercial guild
is the last puzzle.
It's time to carry out the plan.
Within a month,
within a month.
I want this World Entertainment Stock
20 times more.
Great!
Commander Zhao gave us the money.
this stock will be 20 times higher.
Right?
Yes.
Just tell me if you have any questions.
It turns out
the movie selection in Shanghai
The reputation of Zhuque Hall
and the so-called quote age.
It's just a trick.
The final show
is this stock.
Su Sheng,
I was right.
your heroic daughter.
Once the money cabinet opens,
someone has to move it.
related to
the Yongli Private Bank
to you.
You can deploy
are at your disposal.
What's wrong?
I dare not answer.
Thank you, Commander Zhao.
Okay.
Cheers.
Wish our great success.