Who are you?
We can get out of Hongwan.
It's only a matter of time to find you.
Is this 401 package?
You are?
Mr. Luo.
0286.
Here.
Thank you.
Why are you so rude to Dr. Na?
You have a gift.
Give me the present.
You went to find my daughter?
It's easy to find you.
Looking for your daughter
to find your daughter.
But it's okay.
Her home address
the location of the school,
Including who I meet every day.
the activity track
of the activity.
Listen carefully.
If you touch my daughter,
I won't let you off!
Don't worry.
For now,
I won't touch her.
The premise is your result.
You have to satisfy us.
The package is here.
Please sign here.
Mr. Mo.
I don't see anyone outside.
Dr. Na.
You know that man outside, right?
I can let him in.
You should know what to do.
Pay.
You must sign it yourself.
Officer Ning.
Why are you here?
Hongwan is so far from here.
No one came to you?
Yes.
My wife's
relatives, friends,
And you.
Jiang Yan's men didn't come to you.
I told you.
Hongwan is so far from here.
Why did they come to me?
You...
worried about this.
If there's nothing else,
please leave.
Excuse me.
What happened to your hand?
Nothing.
It's just
I twisted it when playing basketball.
Dr. Luo.
Aren't you hiding something
to leave Hongwan at this time?
You think too much.
Every year at this time,
I come to my wife's hometown
to mourn my dead wife.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Stop!
Don't move.
Police!
Get down!
Officer Ning, right?
We are local police.
Here.
Thank you.
Captain Cao has informed us.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Come back with us to make a statement.
and tell us what's going on.
Detective.
There might be a misunderstanding.
I'll cooperate with your testimony.
It's all handcuffed.
Officer Ning.
Thank you.
You came so far for this.
Don't worry.
I'll make it clear
to the local police.
Let's go.
Officer.
I put my ID in the car.
Take it.
Officer Ning.
You came here for nothing.
I've achieved my goal.
Mo Bei.
Luo Yin.
Mo Bei is here for you.
Did you finish the deal?
I don't understand why you did that.
The person who was killed by the porpoise
will never rest in peace.
Tell me the truth before the trial.
It's not too late.
I always suspected that you had something to do with the abyss.
Even when you were questioned,
during the interrogation,
I still suspect you.
But now it seems
you are the only one
You've cleared your name.
Chief.
Yeongjin.
Are you going back to the station tomorrow?
Yes.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Do you need a few days off?
No.
I can go back tomorrow.
Ning-jin.
Actually, you played a great role
you did a great job.
You found the key evidence.
These
are precious experiences
as a police officer.
You're still young.
Take your time.
There will be another chance.
Don't worry, sir.
When I go back,
I'll do my best.
Okay.
If you need anything,
if you need anything.
Okay.
Dr. Luo is back
Xiaoqiao
Do you have many reservations recently?
If not,
go to the back.
I don't feel well here.
Okay.
I've arranged it for you.
But one patient
made many reservations.
She keeps asking when you'll be back.
What do you think?
As usual.
Okay, Dr. Luo.
025196.
Yeongjin.
Director.
You look good.
Take a few days off.
and check
in the district.
Okay.
Welcome back.
I'll go first.
Ning Zhen.
You're back.
How is the police? 025196.
How is the police team 25196?
How is the police team?
It's a big case, right?
I just went to help.
I didn't do anything.
Okay.
I'll leave you to it.
025196.
If someone comes to me these days,
just tell them I'm not back yet.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm Lu Fan from the Criminal Investigation Unit.
Is Ning Zhen here?
He's not back yet. 025046.
If he comes back,
please ask him to find me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bro.
Such a beautiful girl.
Are you sure you won't meet her?
If it were me, I would have gone after him.
Stop gossiping.
Go to work now.
Okay.
Ms. Jiang.
The trial will be held at the end of the month.
The former Judge Yoo
has been suspended.
We have a new judge.
and new evidence.
have been submitted to the court.
As long as we have new evidence,
It doesn't matter who the judge is.
Just finish it by the end of the month.
OK, Ms. Jiang.
Well done.
Come here and I'll reward you.
The time for the corporate retrial is confirmed.
When the result is out,
I’ll tell you immediately.
Why is there another trial?
Did Kang-yeon do something again?
The investigation of the case is over.
Leave the rest
to the prosecution and court.
Hello, ma'am.
How can I help you?
This is my first time here.
I've been asking you out.
But your assistant said you were on a business trip.
Yes.
I've been busy lately.
I just came back.
Tell me about your situation.
What are you...
You're an expert in my daughter's psychiatric appraisal.
My daughter will be
for intentional assault.
So please
please forgive me.
If the money is not enough,
tell me your number.
You know that
He has a serious mental illness.
I didn't kill anyone.
And...
I can get out soon.
I don't understand why you did that.
The person who was killed by the porpoise
will never rest in peace.
Please help me this time.
She's still young.
and immature.
Dr. Na.
Sister Li.
Yes, I'm Nid.
It's okay.
It's just a visit.
Thank you.
(The trial is today. Don’t you want to know the result?)
Excuse me.
According to your judgment,
if the flute
when he committed the crime?
Yes.
Liar.
Silence!
The early stage of the disease didn't treat in time.
So the fluid schizophrenia
is very serious.
(Luo Yin testifies for the porridge.) [A mental patient who restricts criminal responsibilities]
Doctor Na.
Hello, Detective.
Why did you do that?
Because of your paper evaluation,
all our efforts will be in vain.
What did I do?
There's no schizophrenia at all.
Why did you help him?
Did Jiang Yan threaten you?
You can tell us.
Tell us.
We can help you.
I'm not threatened by anyone.
You did it voluntarily.
to stand with Jiang Yan.
Ning Zhen, that fool.
He thought you were threatened
and went to you desperately.
How stupid.
Detective.
I did what I should do.
If you don't understand, read more.
If you can't figure it out,
think about it again.
Bye.
The committee is investigating
According to the report Zhang Hua submitted on June 15, 2024, History.
1. While he was a forensic psychologist,
Human property, psychiatric report, violation.
The trial continues.
We will now begin the trial.
The facts found in court
is the same as the prosecution's accusation.
The court believes
the defendant, Kang Woo, committed intentional murder,
will be punished according to the law.
Based on the criminal nature and plot of this case,
social threat,
and the opinions of both defenders.
According to the Criminal Law of the People's Republic of China,
Article 57,
Article 48,
Article 232,
The verdict is as follows.
All rise.
[Defendant Kang Woo committed a intentional murder,]
sentenced to death.
and deprive of political rights for life.
Okay.
Fluffy.
Stop it.
Officer.
Where is the key?
Can you give me the key?
Please.
Officer,
Give me the key.
Where is the key?
Jiang Yan.
Tell the police.
Hurry!
I'm innocent.
Fluffy, stop it.
I will find a way.
Officer, I'm sorry.
Give me the key.
I'll talk to them, okay?
Sister.
Tell them
Tell them.
Sister.
What happened?
Luo Yin was reported
is suspected of fabricating the psychiatric evaluation report.
At the same time,
the analysis report
is also fake.
Ning Zhen.
Why are you avoiding me?
Why are you here?
Are you giving up?
I have good news.
My borrowing period is over.
Go back.
Stop!
What do you mean?
Your mother's case
and the abyss
and the abyss.
This is my personal matter.
How is it your own business?
Have you forgotten
Have you forgotten?
Marco Lu.
This is not as simple as you think.
Kang Woo got a report from the psychiatric evaluation.
He'll soon escape from the law.
and the abyss will appear again.
And now I think
is more dangerous than the abyss.
Captain Cao is right.
What are you talking about?
Kang Woo was sentenced to death.
What?
The porpoise was sentenced to death.
Luo Yin was reported
of another case.
[Suspected of fabricating a psychiatric analysis report]
and found out the psychiatric analysis of porpoise.
was also forged.
I asked about the investigation.
It was actually Luo Yin.
who made the opponent's lawyer report.
Because of the confession,
and it didn't cause any actual impact.
Luo Yin should be fine.
But his job and medical qualification
to practice medicine.
Alright.
Think about it.
If you still don't understand,
think again.
Officer Ning.
Dr. Luo.
Were you threatened
because
to sign that document.
If I had found out earlier,
I wouldn't be like this.
At that time,
I had no choice.
Can you stop caring about it?
But now,
back to
the list of suspects in the abyss?
In this world,
love and hatred
for no reason.
To catch the abyss,
you need to know
how he became an abyss.
Everyone related to the naked body case
Everyone.
If one appears, he will kill one.
In the end,
the police
to the naked body case in Kubei.
So I believe
the real identity of the abyss
is hidden in this case.
I know what you're thinking.
My wife died of illness.
and no family was killed.
Do I have a reason to be an abyss?
I want to know the truth too.
Dr. Na.
The naked body case in Kubei is over.
I've been transferred back to the police station.
When we were kids,
we...
There are always a few kids in our class.
Every time the teacher announced the correct answer,
they would raise their hands and say,
I have different solutions.
There are many ways to solve one question.
With Officer Ning's personality,
he won't give up.
Sometimes we are only
to success.
Who is the one hiding it?
Jin Jie has no immediate family.
And for so many years,
no one has ever cared about the progress of the case.
Wu Ke Ran appeared at the same time with the abyss.
So it can't be her.
Who is this person?
Why?
Why is this happening?
I'm going to succeed.
You could do anything before
Why not now?
Ms. Jiang,
We did our best.
No one knew something would happen to him.
I understand.
You just want me to die.
If I die,
my sister will be free.
Three days.
with Jiang Yan.
Flathy.
Ms. Jiang said
don't do anything stupid.
Call, call.
Please open the door.
A special role.
Special cast.
Special show
Actor.
Friendship.
and actors.
Zhang Zhen.
Li Fugui.
The production team.
Hello. Hello.
Lighting Team.
Mobile team.
Photography company. Shandong CIT Co., Ltd.
Team B.
Props team.
The styling team.
Action team.
[The behind-the-scenes team]
The post-production.
YZONE.
Win Taizhong and
Beijing won Taizhong and Movie and Media Co. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.
Audio production.
Kuck Time (Beijing) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Special effects production.
Transfer culture.
Turn around (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
MingXie brand.
Costume.
Ming Xie.
Qingdao West Coast New District Film Development Center
Qingdao Chengyang District Court
Momo Entertainment (Qingdao Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
Beijing Yuntae Investment Co., Ltd.
Conductor,
Dongyang Qishu You Yu Culture Co., Ltd.
Exclusive announcement.
Dongyang Qishu Yu Culture Co., Ltd.
exclusive data strategy.
Two Pitt Tech.
[Zhijiang Film Co., Ltd.]
Zhijiang Film Co., Ltd.
Fish (Shanghai) Cultural Investment Co., Ltd.
Guangdong Shanghai Yuntian Film Group Co., Ltd.
Peng Hua Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Zhongguang Tianze Media Co., Ltd.
Dongyang Qishu You Yu Culture Co., Ltd.
Wuwei Network Technology (Haikou) Co., Ltd.
Beijing iQIYI Technology Co., Ltd.