How's your head, brother
It's so good that you don't need to worry about it
You see what you said
Don't I care about you
You care about me, right
You care about yourself first
You made my dad mess today
Isn't it awkward
I didn't give him any steps, did I
Do you think
Uncle has been busy dealing with me
I don't have time to take care of you
You see what you say about me
What kind of person have I become
I'm not that kind of person
Let me tell you something serious
I was at the hospital today
Meet a girl
Special, special
Anyway, when you have time,
Why don't you come with me and have a look
Come on
I have something to do now
I don't want to listen to your nonsense
Hang up
Is that how to save the phone bill
You'll be fined five drinks
Let me have a drink for you first
Carlo
Sit down
What are you saying you're running around for
Do you have any idea how much I worry about you
If I hadn't come in time,
I don't even want to talk about it
You said you were killed by that woman
Caught and sold to a dog dealer
How can I find you later
What do you mean
Stop licking
I know
You're worried about me, aren't you
But I'm a big living person
Strong-bodied
What's there to worry about
You should be more worried about that
Background panel
Do you know
I'm telling you
Carlo
You really can't run around anymore
You look at some people
Simple on the surface
Grow a silly white sweet
The harmless appearance of people and animals
In fact, their hearts are darker than anyone else's
Why don't you listen to me
Dinner will be served soon
I really miss you so much
I missed you so much
Don't do this again
Do you know
Eat when you listen to it
You are more excited than anyone else
Isn't it
Cute cute
Are you all right
Rocky, it's okay. It's okay
Are you all right Wen Jing
Rocky
Pick up the dog gently
It's okay. It's okay
Come, come, give it to me
Look what's wrong with it
You guys wait here. Okay
Dad, is he gonna be all right
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Our hospital doctor
It's the best
Is it going to be all right
Nothing, nothing
Silver Fox Rocky Male
Four and a half years old and thirteen kilograms
Reconstruction of gastric volvulus
Silver Fox Rocky Male
Four and a half years old and thirteen kilograms
Preparation for gastric volvulus reduction operation
Dr. Oda
I'll go out first
How's Rocky doing
Loki is preparing for surgery normally
But
We're going to have to do it with another doctor
Change doctors
Where is it on the operating table
Temporary substitution
I
I'll do it
Dr. Tian Tian, she is the first
Check it
A basic situation of Rocky
Our operation
It was originally scheduled to be done by Dr. Chen
You see Dr. Chen
He's all set, isn't he
Dr Chan
Give it to me
Is it okay for her to just leave
Don't worry
Little sister, do you know
This Dr. Chen Yifan
In our place, there are
The title of Hundred Flowers Hand
Do you know what a hundred flower hand is
Is to have done hundreds of operations
Every time he had an operation
Are all successful
Our hospital
Except for that
Outside Dean Laotian
Just count Dr. Chen Yifan as
The best
Just for the sake of
Saving Rocky is more sure
That's what Dr. Oda asked for
Uncle Chen came to take charge
Of course
Just say if you guys
If you don't want Dr. Chen to do it,
We can also
Change Dr. Oda back
No, no, no
We need Dr. Chen
That line
Don't worry about it
Dr Chan
I'm sure the operation will be successful
Okay, it's okay this time
Dr. Chen is very powerful
Don't worry, don't worry
Nothing
Carlo
Carlo has eaten
Carlo came
Eat
Why aren't you hungry
Then eat it
What do you mean
Do you know that
How much effort did I go to
Cook this meal
What's the matter
It's not all about you
Do you like food
Still don't eat, do you
Are you going to eat or not
You, you, you don't even look at it
You don't respect me very much
Okay, you won't eat, will you
I eat
Shall I eat
Dad
I can't save Zaizai
Zaizai is gone
It's all my fault
Children
You did your best
Don't cry
Still can't
So
I want to take advantage of your father's rest
Escape
This is not an escape
The matter of resigning
I will officially
I went home and mentioned it to my dad
Tianlin Hospital has just been expanded and renovated
It's only been a few days since it opened
Your dad's down
You're quitting, too
What would your father think
Aunt
One can't afford it
Attending physician of scalpel
It's just a decoration
It's no use
Your dad told me
What about Zaizai's operation
Even if it were for him to do it
Neither did he
A hundred percent assurance
He was comforting me
My dad, he never
Failed any surgery
But your dad
He's always going to retire
Aunt
I've been around since I was five
My dad took me with him
Treat all kinds of small animals
At that time
I also believe what my dad said
Think you have talent
But what if my dad is wrong
I have no talent at all
Stop imagining things, baby
Thank you, aunt
Still don't eat, do you
What are you looking at
Why don't you eat
Mi Zong
I'm on the hot search in Weibo
I saw this video
It seems that we really misunderstood
That girl
Carlo
She really saved you
Am I really wrong about her
All right, all right
I got it. I got it
So what do I do now
It's so late now
The hospital must be closed
If I want to apologize,
I can't go empty-handed either
Isn't it
Row
I see
Lao an
Buy me a new mobile phone
As soon as possible
Are you satisfied
Are you satisfied this time
Tian Tian, why are you here
I'm not saying let your aunt
Is it all right to bring things here
My dad had a stroke like this
Why only tell me
He's hypoglycemic
No
Then my dad
How is he now
How's it going
Sit down
Mom is not mom is not trying to hide from you
I just want to
I wanted to tell you later
I'm I'm afraid
Afraid of what
You make me worry more like this
I'm more afraid. Do you know
That
My dad is ill
He's already lying inside
I don't even know what's going on
This is
I'm afraid
When you know it,
And forced myself to embarrass myself
Mom
You know everything
Your aunt told me
She said that originally
Are you going to tell your dad today
The matter of resigning
Since Zaizai disappeared,
You go to work every day
They are all unhappy
I heard Yu-hyun say
You can't even do surgery
It's been half a year
You come home from work every day
Not even a smiling face
You know
How worried Dad is about you
Mom, I was wrong
Mom, stop it. I was wrong
It's my fault
I'm too ignorant
Don't blame you
Things you decide for yourself
Just do it
No matter what decision you make
Both parents support you
How did you guys
Mom
Tian Tian
No matter what decision you make
Your father will understand
And those who support you
We will all support you, too
Xiaowen
Doctor Chan
How is the turnover today
Today
Doctor Chan
You are usually free
Don't they all hide in the office
Do you look at stocks
How come all of a sudden today
Concerned about the operation of the hospital
I'm not right away
Are you going to be the dean
You have to get familiar with the business in advance
Experience life
Good dean of the hospital
Help me change the tea leaves
OK, thank you
Dean
Excuse me, who sealed this dean
I'm not asking your brother
Do you feel at ease to recuperate
Our hospital is now
When there is the most shortage of people
Critical moment
Someone must be on top
It's up and down, inside and out
I've counted it all
Come on, you go over there and take pictures
You two go over there
Give me that medical equipment
Don't move. This has just been set up
Hold fast, hold fast
What do you guys do
My last name is Wang
Where are we, Mr. Hu
Is an investor in your hospital
I want to inform you now
We Hu always have to withdraw our funds
Your hospital account
Has been frozen
This is for money
What to do
Which one of you is in charge of this
You're in charge
I
No
Our dean has just been ill in hospital
You will make trouble
This is too much
Say so
You're in charge
A lot of talk, you
Who is in charge
I am
Brother Wang drinks tea
At the beginning
Mr. Hu decided to invest in your Tianlin
That's also a fancy to your dad
This golden signboard
Yes
Half the customers in your field forest
It's all for him
But now your dad's down
This brand is just
Pour down
Although my dad is not here,
But there's me
I grew up following him
Words and deeds
Don't say you can
100% true biography
But I
But can you do the surgery
Girl, I've already looked into it
But there are still many in our hospital
Stop it
Don't say it either
I bully you little girl
In this way
I'll give you seven days
Two choices
You can either raise the money
Buy back your Tianlin
All the shares
Or
I'll put you Tianlin
Bankruptcy liquidation
Don't forget
You broke the contract first
I can follow the contract
Let you pay liquidated damages
Think about it, you
Group second quarter
Profits in various industrial chains
They all appeared
Different degrees of growth
But what about the total profit of the group
But there has been negative growth
What's the problem
The problem lies in the research and development department
In recent years, the group
For the R&D department
Invested one after another
More than 80 million
Of course
It is normal to invest in research and development
As a group
Head of audit department
In line with shareholders
Responsible attitude of employees
Actually, what I'm most worried about is
Or did Mi always put forward it
Pilot hospital scheme
According to the general statement,
After the targeted drug came out,
It should be used by pilot hospitals free of charge
Then
This piece
Costs borne by the group
Have you ever thought about it
Can you explain it to everyone
Is there any explanation for this
Any enterprise group company
There are no more than two results
Either make a profit
Or a loss
That is to say
It doesn't matter if the group loses money
Cancer in cats and dogs
The fatality rate is very high
Our new drug
Once the research and development is successful,
Put it on the market
It will cause a great sensation
And social effects
That's why
Our Lvchuan Group has been
You can still stand still
Root cause
What about the pilot hospital
Do charity work
Shen Zong
You know
We are in the same city
Pet hospitals large and small
How many do you have altogether
You must not know
Then I'll tell you
A total of 126
Every pilot hospital
Will be on the front line
Connected with countless pets
And the owner behind them
Do you know what this concept is
Once our
Pilot hospitals are open
All pet hospitals will
In order to be in the first time
Get our medicine
Try your best
To fight for the pilot hospital in Lvchuan
This brand
Isn't this
The profits of the company
Isn't this money
And this brand
Will go from a city
To the whole province and even to the whole country
But that's not the point
What's the point
The point is
We just need to
Within a year's time
Let Lvchuan Group
All medicines produced
Occupy the market in an all-round way
End the mixed fish and dragons
The mixed situation
I don't know if you understand me
Am I going into enough detail for now
Get out of the way and let me in
Everybody wait a minute
I have something to make clear today
Manager Zhao, what are you fooling around about
Shen Zong
I would like to express my gratitude to you and all the senior officials
Report and expose Shen Mi
Abuse of power for personal gain
The thing that framed me
Don't spit on people
Out
Uncle Hang on
I need to know
What did I set him up for
I'm curious to know
You go on
OK, then I'll say it
Not long ago
I handled it
A contract from the R&D department
There is a mistake
Does cause the company
Lost hundreds of thousands
But I dare not neglect
The first time
Report to the audit
But he told me
Recently, the audit department has been keeping a close eye on him
Want me to admit
These hundreds of thousands are me
Kickbacks taken by individuals without permission
And let me write in black and white
Write it down
I worked hard in the company
I have worked for more than ten years
A family of old and young
Waiting for me to feed
That's good
There's no way
I can only write it down without conscience
I didn't expect this to be written down
He turned his face against others
You have to force me to say
Unless at your behest
Or I'll be fired
Does Shen Mi have such a thing
What do you say
Let me explain it for the manager
Shen Zong
What is this
Is this the material you wrote
Yes, I made it up
But he made me write it
That's a bit of a coincidence
According to Manager Zhao
A story made up in the material
It was verified one by one
As a result, every account
I found out everything
In everyone's hands
There are details I have listed
Record of every rebate
And transfer records
It's all clear
Clear and clear
Good boy, you cheat me
Manager Zhao
Find always let you leave safely
It's already for old employees
The last tolerance
If you don't cherish this opportunity,
Then I have to represent
Group Legal Department
To file a lawsuit against you
When the time comes, check it out
Look who's behind it
Gave you the courage
Zhao Jianguo
Go out and wait for treatment
Shen Zong
Get out of here
Meng Nan
I think so
How much did he eat
Make him throw up
As for litigation
I think forget it
Old employees
Don't expose your family's ugliness
I said too much just now
My throat is a little uncomfortable
But what you said is too reasonable
That's true
Don't publicize your family's ugliness
Bring it here
Carlo is so good
Go
It's time to eat
Do you want a vegan
Animal fat and protein
Bad metabolism
It will hurt your heart
Burden-causing
You're not fit to eat those
Play by yourself
I'm not really particularly hungry
Why don't you eat it
Just now
You cut Shen Hongyuan some slack again
What do you think I can do
He is my uncle after all
But I'm afraid
He didn't want to recognize you as a nephew
That's right
Grandpa asked you to take time off to go home
I'll give you a ride
What is it
He knows you
About being hospitalized yesterday
How did he know
I said that
Why are you saying this
You have to let
Is his old man worried
Then can you in the future
Don't do anything that worries us
All right
Advance
Han lawyer
Find the total things and buy them
Let's go. Okay
I'll get busy first
Where are you going
I have something to take care of
Change the time
Can't be changed
I'll see Grandpa myself
That's it
Goodbye, Carlo. Gone
I seem to have been for a long time
I didn't apologize to anyone else
I didn't say I wasn't going to apologize
Why are you so excited
Really
Okay, okay, I know
Why is he here again
Don't you talk
Don't talk
Don't scream
No one is here
Where did you go
Is that Carlo
Carlo
Carlo, are you in there
It's the sound of it
Carlo
Carlo, are you in there
Carlo Carlo
Why are you here again
What a coincidence
Don't scold me
I'm all day today
It's bad luck enough
Give me a break
I brought Carlo to see a doctor
See a doctor
Carlo, come and have some
Why doesn't he eat like this at home
Is it that hard to understand
Everyone likes to eat something better
What's more, dogs
You know I'm at home
Was it fed anything
Whatever it is
Facts speak louder than words
It just loves my cooking more
Okay, there's nothing wrong with it
You can take it back
A total of 205 grams
Give you a change
Here's thirty yuan for you
How to pay
Scan code
The machine won't work after work
What about swiping your card
The card reader is even more useless
You, you open a hospital
I can't even settle the bill
What hospital do you run
You're still so tough
That
I'll pay you personally
I don't have a cell phone
You forgot
After you scolded me yesterday
It's time for dog thieves
It's broken
That's why I
No, I can't give up
Carlo, come on, Carlo
Carlo Carlo's awake
You were the year
The man who saved Carlo
It's me
Then what do you mean by this
Do you remember when
You are in our school
Is it particularly famous
Everyone takes you as an example
So do I.
So I put this pen every day
Take it with you
But now I don't take it
I don't want it either
Because I didn't think
You are an indiscriminate
Use stray cats and dogs
A man who earns dirty money
And
I don't want the money
Thirty yuan is for you
Dogs are also healthy
Why don't you take it back
And
Don't come to me again
Go back with your master
Thank you for saving Carlo
Should
Here you go
No, I'll give it to you
Lao an
You look into it for me
Information of Tianlin Animal Hospital
Send it to me
Thank you as soon as possible
Miss Tian, I'm sorry
The information you provided
Fail to pass
Our company's guarantee audit
I'm really embarrassed
Why don't you take a closer look
No, no, no
That's nothing
I'll get busy first
Good
Refueling
I'm too hard, aunt
It's really hard for me
You are crying and robbing the land now
The one who gave up me before
Where's the momentum
That's not driving ducks to the shelves
Be ordered in the face of danger
I have to go up.
There are customers now
Stabbed this matter into the group
Do you know how many people
Shouting to return
Our stored value card
How much
More than 130
The WeChat group has exploded
They all told us to refund the money
No, the account has been frozen
We have no money to refund if we want to refund it
And
Is
Those new doctors who have just arrived
It seems that it is also discussed in private
Say you want to leave
This is my dad's painstaking efforts
Who's on the phone
Sister-in-law Tian Tian, where is she
Good good
I'll put her on the phone
Mom, it's okay
I broke my cell phone
I forgot to tell you
Am I worried
I ran to Tianlin to have a look
Rest assured
You have to trust your daughter
I'm done in a minute
Just go and see Dad
I'm still busy here
I gotta go
Hang up, hang up
Did Grandpa really make a decision
I've been with the old man for so many years
It can be said that many of his decisions
I looked through his eyes
You can understand
This time
He is absolutely serious
Grandpa is at his age
I really can't continue like this
Worried about the company
But if he is like this now
Give me the position of president
I'm afraid some people won't agree
This is our common
Things to worry about
Arguably
His position
It really should be
Your uncle will sit down
But the old man didn't choose him
I chose you
I think this in your heart
Should know better than me
Shen Hongyuan said in particular today
There will be a research and development meeting for new drugs
He may have heard it
Something about it
If he plays this game of chess,
Coming up is bound to storm
Do you want to think about it
How should we deal with it
If you only attack but not defend in chess,
I'm afraid it will just be easy to fold