♫ Cotton candies floating in the sky ♫
♫ Following the light breeze ♫
♫ I take a pinch. It melts in the mouth ♫
♫ I always feel a mixture ♫
♫ Of excitement and fear ♫
♫ Maybe you understand ♫
♫ The sleeping glacier is slowly melting ♫
♫ Light gently touches the crack ♫
♫ Thinking, it makes me excited ♫
♫ Holding you in my heart ♫
♫ Totally in love with you ♫
♫ I hope you understand ♫
♫ Standing with you in the rain,
waiting for the rainbow together ♫
♫ Gazing at the starry sky with you,
dreaming our dreams ♫
♫ At this moment, all the pain is forgotten ♫
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
♫ I want to give you a unique love ♫
♫ I don't care about others' jeering
of our relationship ♫
♫ I can laugh with you and be crazy with you ♫
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
♫ I want to give you a unique love ♫
♫ I don't care about others' jeering
of our relationship ♫
♫ I can laugh with you and be crazy with you ♫
[My Precious]
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
[Episode 35]
It's really serious.
It's unlikely to be completely cured.
Although the tumor is currently incurable,
if newly developed lymphoma
targeting drug is used,
it can continue
to inhibit the growth of cancer cells
and even reduce the diameter of tumors.
So, you mean…
It is possible
to survive with tumors.
To survive with tumors?
Then Champion can be saved, right?
If it survives with tumors,
can it have a normal-aged life?
I can't guarantee this.
But according to the current situation,
if it sticks to the medication,
its life can be extended
by at least five to six years.
- Dr. Gu.
- Mr. Yan.
Dr. Gu, thank you.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for Mr. Shen and Tian Tian,
the new drug could not have been developed.
You should thank them.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Thank you, Dr. Tian.
This is what we should do.
But I have to remind you,
Champion
can't compete now.
I know.
Could you please take me to Champion?
In fact, I can feel
it's his last competition.
Champion's body
is long past the peak.
A lot of people told me
to replace it earlier
with a new pacemaker.
But I don't want to.
So I still let it accompany me to compete.
It accompanied me
to win trophies.
I know,
it doesn't want to leave me either.
But now I realize
I was being too selfish.
It must have felt
that this is its last competition with me.
So each time we trained,
it worked harder than usual
and didn't even show it was sick.
I want to thank you all
for saving Champion's life.
Although it can't accompany
me to the competition,
as long as it can survive,
as long as it can stay with me,
that's enough.
[Tianlin Animal Hospital]
Come in.
Hello.
[Resume]
Six years of working experience.
Why are so many people here
for interviews today?
I guess there are many people
who have seen the Pet Vet Competition
and want to seek a job here.
You've been here for a while.
Help me analyze
who's better.
From now on,
I can't keep making decisions for you.
Why?
You know,
I have to go back to Lvchuan sooner or later.
In fact, we have experienced so many things
during the time spent in Tianlin,
no matter you, or others,
or even the whole Tianlin Hospital,
have slowly developed.
So I think it's time for me
to let you make your own decisions.
As a shareholder,
I'm done making decisions for you.
But as Miss Tian's boyfriend,
I can still give you some advice.
Okay, boyfriend.
Come in.
Why are you here?
You are here.
I came to tell you something.
There are two things.
One is that after Champion used
the lymphoma targeted drug,
so far all is well.
In the best case scenario,
its life can be extended
by at least five to six years.
That's really great.
And starting tomorrow,
the R&D department of Lvchuan
will send two new staff over
to guide you on the new drug
for one month.
I believe, in this one month,
you guys could at least master it.
I thought you would come.
That's the second thing I want to tell you.
I have submitted my resignation application
to the HR department of Lvchuan.
Why?
So sudden?
All things must come to an end.
My mission in Lvchuan is already completed.
There's no point in staying any longer.
So, are you going back to the UK?
No, I'm going to Thailand.
Do you still remember the last time
we went to the Animal Medicine Summit together?
It wasn't perfect, though,
it left me
with fond memories.
Fond memories?
So, is the person
you have such fond memories of
going with you?
Well,
I have to keep working on it.
But now that you two are getting along so well,
I'm relieved.
See you.
Thank you. Good luck!
Mr. Shen, you asked me before
to investigate that Tian Tian,
and I've got everything sorted out.
Tell me.
Tian Tian, 25 years old,
graduated from the Agricultural University
with a major in Veterinarian.
After graduation, she started working
at Tianlin Animal Hospital,
which her dad, Tian Dongqing, operated.
Tian Dongqing, 53 years old,
is the legal representative
of Tianlin Animal Hospital.
When he was young,
he worked as a vet at the veterinary station
in Lin'an for ten years.
Then, he switched his career
to run Tianlin Hospital.
From what I found,
his medical ethics and character
are highly praised by all.
Go on.
Tian Tian's mother, Lin Zhi, is 52 years old.
She's a homemaker and doesn't have a job.
Tian Tian also has a younger brother,
Tian Yuxian,
who also works at Tianlin.
[Wu Jie]
That's the kid who shaved a square haircut for the dog
at the Pet Vet Competition.
Did Tian Tian know Shen Mi
before he took over the hospital?
Well, I didn't find that out.
From what I know so far,
it seems like they met
when you asked Shen Mi
to take over the hospital.
Mr. Shen, are you listening?
That's it.
Take a look.
What is this?
Father's birthday is coming up soon.
This is the menu arranged
by the executive chef of the club.
See if it is okay.
[Longevity and Happiness]
Why is this Five Blessings excluded?
That's just Duck Blood in Chili Sauce.
Isn't it good?
It's got shredded eel in it.
Do you forget that Shen Mi is allergic to eels?
Is that so?
Of course.
Do you forget?
When Mi was three,
we had a meal with elder brother's family,
and there came a dish, Eel in Hot Oil,
Shen Mi just took a bite,
his whole body was swollen
and he couldn't even breath.
We took him to the hospital together.
How could you forget that?
[Menu]
Put it here, I'll take a look at it.
You take a good look.
[Longevity and Happiness Menu]
[Tianlin Animal Hospital]
Champion.
Do you miss me, Champion?
Come on.
I've been missing you.
I brought you something tasty.
Come on.
I know you want to go home,
but you have to be good.
You must listen to the doctor.
I miss you so much, Champion.
I really miss you.
Remember, you have to take your medicine,
do you hear me?
I'll take you home in a couple of days.
And we can start training together again.
Be good, Champion.
Thank you for taking care
of Champion during this time.
This is what we should do.
Mr. Yan, how's the competition?
Right, Mr. Yan.
Is everything going well?
I don't want to talk about it here,
in case Champion would hear it.
Let's go outside.
Be careful.
Congratulations to Mr. Yan
for another gold medal.
Give me, give me.
Sister, do I look like a champion?
No way! All you know is
playing games and being lazy.
This is what the gold medal looks like.
It is so beautiful.
It's so heavy, this gold medal.
Mr. Yan, here you are.
Without the participation of Champion,
it actually doesn't mean
much to me.
And I don't want to tell Champion.
Why?
Because I don't want it
to know that this gold medal
was won without it.
During this period of time,
thank you for taking care of Champion.
This is what we should do.
I'll come tomorrow.
It seems that Mr. Yan
is still disappointed
that Champion did not participate in
the retirement competition.
Look at him now,
he's not only disappointed.
I think it becomes a heart knot to him.
If it cannot be solved,
I'm really afraid he won't
have the courage to keep running.
Well, let's get him out of it.
How?
Let the champion run again.
This is the road map I designed.
Why does this route look like a circle?
Because it's a circle.
This is the road map to the park.
I've looked up this route.
The competition that Mr. Yan participated in
with Champion for the first time
actually wasn't a real marathon,
but a national event in this place.
Right. The circle represents
both the beginning and the end.
So for the Champion's last run,
it's meaningful to hold it
where its dream began.
And then?
And then we have to make it feel like
it's actually in a competition
under limited conditions.
[First Tianlin International Marathon]
[First Tianlin International Marathon,
Starting Point]
Now the problem is,
how can Mr. Yan and Champion
participate in at the same time?
What should we do?
Let's use this.
That could work.
The challenge is
to find a balance
between pushing and pulling.
Also, we need to remind him
with words and body language
about changes in the road ahead,
like uphill, downhill, steps,
manhole covers and others,
in order to prevent accidents.
Also, the speed of the runners and Mr. Yan
should be as consistent as possible.
- Consistent?
- But,
we're all amateurs.
How can we keep up with the world champion?
So I arrange a relay run.
So there's not much running to do
for everyone.
How long will we be running?
Probably over ten kilometers.
Let's just call it ten kilometers.
So the six of us have to run
average 1.7 kilometers each.
Not six,
but five.
- Five?
Who's not running?
Shen Mi had heart surgery before,
so I didn't let him participate this time.
I can't go with you, though,
I'll take care of
all the logistics, so don't worry.
So each of us
has to run more, right?
Mr. Chen, Peilan.
I know this is
way above your job description.
Especially the hospital work
is so heavy these days.
- So--
- So,
we have to do this.
Well, it's not the first time
Tianlin has done something like this.
Aunt, come on and sit.
- Sit.
- Come here.
Aunt.
At your age,
it must be hard to run two kilometers at once.
Why don't you, Mr. Chen, run some for her?
I can take care of it for you.
I don't run for nothing.
I'll run three kilometers.
Tian, you're young.
Don't you want to run an extra kilometer
for Wen Jing and Tian Tian?
No need.
When I was at school,
I was the girls' 3km race champion.
Two kilometers shouldn't be a problem.
You are that great?
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Wen Jing, then you can run more for me.
Can you be a man?
- You're a man.
- Can you be a man?
You're the only young man.
You should run an extra two kilometers.
Chen Yifan, you push me.
Come on, I'll push you.
Is it okay?
Okay.
Well done.
Let's try it for Mr. Yan and Champion.
Come on, okay.
Let's do it again.
Come here, this way.
Wheelchair!
Come on.
Are you okay, Mr. Chen?
Are you okay?
Mr. Yan and Champion
are really having a hard time.
If you are okay, let's try again.
Let's try it again.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
Director Zhang, thank you
for your support of this event.
Mr. Yan is the champion of our first
national long-distance running competition.
And you're trying to fulfil his wish.
We must fully support
such a meaningful event.
Thank you.
[First Tianlin International Marathon,
Starting Point]
Champion, you are doing well.
Today you're going to sit in your wheelchair
and race with everyone else.
This collar
can report your health to us at any time.
Mr. Yan, Champion is fine.
Today our car will follow you the whole way.
Don't worry, we have
necessary medicines in the car
to prevent emergencies.
And we'll be with you
on the last leg of the relay.
Thank you
for doing so much for Champion.
I'd like to say something to it
before the competition.
You used to run with me,
let me accompany you
to finish this last competition this time.
Are you ready?
Okay, I got it.
Ready.
♫ Let's go home after a walk ♫
♫ I'm playful like you ♫
♫ The evening wind always sways the buds ♫
♫ Just like me and you ♫
♫ Let's nest together on the sofa tonight ♫
♫ You're on the left, popcorn on the right ♫
♫ The picture tells a fairy tale ♫
♫ They watch over each other ♫
♫ I think you would do the same ♫
♫ Now you are still with me ♫
Turn left ahead.
♫ Traveling through time together ♫
♫ I have seen so many separations ♫
♫ Which makes me more aware of ♫
It's Wen Jing's turn now.
Would you like some water, Mr. Yan?
No.
- I'll do it.
- It's fine.
I'll help you.
The slope ahead is too steep.
Let's do this together.
Be careful, we're going downhill, Mr. Yan.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
Champion, don't be afraid.
Good work, brother.
- Well done!
- I'm exhausted.
Wen Jing, keep going!
Wen Jing, Tian Peilan is ahead, keep going!
Little train.
♫ Only enough to accommodate me ♫
We're running a marathon.
Hello, hello everyone!
Cheer them on.
We're running a marathon.
Good job, Champion.
Let's go.
I'll do it.
- You should rest in the car.
- Be careful.
♫ I have seen so many separations ♫
♫ Which makes me more aware
of the value of companionship ♫
♫ It's worth cherishing ♫
♫ We exchange each other's time ♫
We almost reach Mr. Chen.
Over here, Tian.
Tian.
Good work.
You're the best.
Keep going.
Mr. Yan, have a drink of water.
Okay, thank you.
Aunt, I really envy you that you have water.
♫ No matter how things change ♫
♫ It can't take away
your innocence and kindness ♫
♫ Give me strength ♫
Mr. Chen is getting slower.
He helped my aunt run a kilometer more.
So he has to run five kilometers in total.
He is the one running the most among us.
How many kilometers has he run now?
Not even four kilometers yet.
I don't think he can do it at his age.
What did you say?
Y-You are this young,
and you ran yourself out, didn't you?
You did a good job in running.
Just shut up.
This is the last leg.
This is not going to work.
Stop. I'll replace him.
- Can you do it?
- Yes, I can.
- I'll do it.
- Thank you.
You'd go rest.
Mr. Yan, you've worked hard. Keep going!
Champion, keep going!
Mr. Chen, good work.
- Good work.
- Have some water.
Hurry up.
- Are you okay?
- Hurry up, keep going!
I'm fine.
Just so embarrassing.
As a grown man,
I feel embarrassing to let a girl run for me.
I don't think it's embarrassing.
You've been trying so hard, anyway.
I think you've already helped
Mr. Yan and Champion.
So, just try your best.
Mr. Yan, are you okay?
Yes.
Tian Tian.
- Tian Tian.
- Dr. Tian.
Tian Tian.
- How are you?
- I'm okay.
Are you okay?
- You go down first.
- You're bleeding.
- You need a sterilization.
Can you still run like this?
Definitely not.
It's hard for her to even walk now.
No, you can't run anymore,
replace with someone else.
Dr. Tian, you are injured. Let's stop running.
No, you've all done your job,
we must persist.
You should stop.
I'll do it.
But your heart…
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Yuxian, bring Champion up here.
Cover it, beware of infection.
Help me check, don't press on her wound.
Come on, leash it.
- Let's go.
- Are you seated properly?
- Okay.
Go.
Be careful.
What about the car?
Can't you drive?
- Me? Tian.
- Don't look at me.
I-I can't drive at all.
I'll do it.
I just got my driver's license.
Wen Jing, you've learned a lot of skills.
Skills will never be burden.
Hang on.
How is your heart?
Do you have any chest discomfort or uneasiness?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Mr. Yan, try to keep up and be careful.
Okay.
Champion, hang in there.
We are about to reach the finish line.
- Champion.
- What's wrong?
Champion.
I got it.
You want to accompany me
to finish this last run.
Let Champion go.
Let Champion accompany
Mr. Yan to finish the last run.
So many of us have worked so hard
just to fulfil Champion's last wish,
right?
Champion.
Mr. Yan.
Let Champion accompany you to the last run.
Thank you.
Champion, keep going!
Old mate.
Let's get going.
Let's go.
Go for it!
Mr. Yan,
we'll run the last leg with you.
- Let's go!
♫ Traveling through time together ♫
♫ I have seen so many separations ♫
♫ Which makes me more aware of ♫
♫ The value of companionship ♫
♫ It's worth cherishing ♫
♫ We exchange each other's time ♫
♫ Maybe it's not that long ♫
♫ No matter how things change ♫
[Second International Blind Marathon]
♫ It can't take away your innocence and kindness ♫
♫ I can't imagine ♫
[Tianlin International Marathon]
♫ I can only hold on to you ♫
♫ Now you are still with me ♫
♫ Traveling through time together ♫
♫ I have seen so many separations ♫
[First Tianlin International Marathon]
♫ Which makes me more aware of ♫
♫ The value of companionship ♫
♫ It's worth cherishing ♫
♫ We exchange each other's time ♫
♫ Even if the time is too rushed ♫
♫ No matter how things change ♫
♫ It can't take away
your innocence and kindness ♫
Congratulations, Champion!
♫ As long as you're still by my side ♫
Mr. Yan.
♫ My call echoes ♫
Thank you.
♫ There will always be a day ♫
♫ I'll be completely forgotten by the world ♫
♫ Leaving no trace ♫
♫ Only you will still remember ♫
♫ My appearance ♫
You've examined several times.
I'm really okay.
Don't rush. Don't you know
how your heart condition is?
Don't be so willful again.
Why is your heart beating
so fast all of a sudden?
Because of you.
I don't see anything wrong with you.
I shouldn't be so worried.
♫ Cotton candies floating in the sky ♫
♫ Following the light breeze ♫
What are you doing? We are waiting for you.
Coming!
Let's go.
♫ Maybe you understand ♫
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Coming.
Come on.
Chen Yifan.
Good boy, Champion. Come, sit.
Move a bit to the center.
Come on.
♫ Gazing at the starry sky with you,
dreaming our dreams ♫
♫ At this moment, all the pain is forgotten ♫
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
♫ I want to give you a unique love ♫
[Tianlin Animal Hospital]
♫ I don't care about others' jeering of our relationship ♫
[The Story of the Animal in Tianlin]
♫ I can laugh with you and be crazy with you ♫
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
You're really smiling happily.
Well, it wasn't for nothing.
Indeed.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
Are you secretly thinking about marrying me?
Are you thrilled just thinking about it?
What?
We have to have a wedding anyway.
You're shameless.
It's too exhausting
that you're running around all the time.
Why don't you go talk to your parents
you become my personal doctor again?
Your heart's healed,
and you're even healthier than me.
Do you still expect me to
be your personal doctor again?
After all that preparation,
none of them were used.
Did you buy something?
Carlo, we're back now.
Carlo.
What stuff did you buy this time?
They are useful.
[Professor Yang Li, Heart Health]
Professor Yang's Heart Health?
And this one.
Electrocardiography From Beginner To Expert.
Alright. These are all
must-read books in cardiology.
Can you understand them?
Why can't I?
Where there's a will, there's a way.
I will read them carefully.
I can't be a fake doctor
forever.
Right, Carlo?
In the future, I can take care of you
and the dog.
What a perfect girlfriend I am.
By the way,
the new electronic collar
that you applied for Champion,
can you get one more from Lvchuan?
Who are you going to use it for?
I want to give it to Carlo.
Doesn't it have a history of heart disease?
And it gets older now.
I want to get one for it to monitor it anytime.
Alright, I'll have An arrange it tomorrow.
If it's so convenient,
can you get one more?
- For who?
- For you.
What have you been thinking about?
I have been thinking about you.
In this way, I can keep up to date
with your health,
then I'll feel relieved.
Where are you going?
To take medicine.
Carlo, you're going to wear a collar tomorrow.
Are you happy?
Shen Mi, does your heart hurt again?
I'll get your medicine.
Thank you, Shen Mi.
We are good brothers, will never apart.
Carlo.
Do you think we should help Shen Mi
pick out a suitable outfit?
Alright, let's go see.
Let's go and see.
As expected, all the clothes are white.
Look at this one.
Look, all are black and grey.
And he said he has clothes in other colors.
What a liar! He doesn't have any.
Miss Han Mengnan,
here is the result of the test.
[Test Report]
[According to the DNA results, Shen Mi
and Shen Rongxian aren't related by blood.]
Hello, may I ask
if this result could be wrong?
Impossible.
The one who told you
that I liked you
has gone.
[Fu City Guangzheng
Forensic Identification Center]
Mengnan.
You scared me. I wonder who.
I just learned a new song today.
I'll play it for you.
This song is about a young man
proposing to the young lady,
and she agreed.
If you don't believe me,
let's make a pinky promise.
A hundred-year unbreakable pinky promise.
Whoever changes is a little wild boar.
Shen Mi, you're finally back.
♫ Your gaze is unwavering ♫
♫ Only enough to accommodate me ♫
♫ I have been melted by you countless times ♫
♫ Yet I'm at a loss for what to do ♫
♫ I can only hold on to you ♫
♫ Now you are still with me ♫
♫ Traveling through time together ♫
♫ Someday, I'll be completely
forgotten by the world ♫
♫ Leaving no trace ♫
♫ Only you will still remember ♫
♫ My appearance ♫