♫ Cotton candies floating in the sky ♫
♫ Following the light breeze ♫
♫ I take a pinch. It melts in the mouth ♫
♫ I always feel a mixture ♫
♫ Of excitement and fear ♫
♫ Maybe you understand ♫
♫ The sleeping glacier is slowly melting ♫
♫ Light gently touches the crack ♫
♫ Thinking, it makes me excited ♫
♫ Holding you in my heart ♫
♫ Totally in love with you ♫
♫ I hope you understand ♫
♫ Standing with you in the rain,
waiting for the rainbow together ♫
♫ Gazing at the starry sky with you,
dreaming our dreams ♫
♫ At this moment, all the pain is forgotten ♫
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
♫ I want to give you a unique love ♫
♫ I don't care about others' jeering
of our relationship ♫
♫ I can laugh with you and be crazy with you ♫
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
♫ I want to give you a unique love ♫
♫ I don't care about others' jeering
of our relationship ♫
♫ I can laugh with you and be crazy with you ♫
[My Precious]
♫ Let this love, love, love surge ♫
[Episode 18]
By the way,
how are those two piglets doing?
I gave them medicine before I went to sleep.
They're not having diarrhea anymore.
It's good.
By the way,
the wound on my face
won't leave a scar, right?
It won't.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
Don't think too much.
- Good night.
Good night, Carlo.
Shen Mi.
I'm here.
Why did you come here?
I couldn't sleep,
so I came out for a while.
Are you not sleeping?
I can't sleep either.
Let me accompany you.
I haven't really looked at the night sky
for a long time.
At night,
it's so quiet in the countryside.
Actually,
this sort of life away from the bustling world
is really comforting.
But someone like you,
a workaholic wound up like a clock,
probably wouldn't understand
the joy of slow life.
I can.
When Gao Zhuo and I
were young,
it was like this for us.
At that time, we were carefree,
never thinking about
what might happen in the future.
We just focused on the moment.
The most we were thinking about
was how to fill
our stomachs.
In fact, I really envy
those elders.
They are happy every day.
Not like us.
As soon as we wake up,
it's all about reports
and proposals.
And performance.
Every day I wake up,
it's all about performance.
And profits.
It's been a long time since I saw you
so happy.
Actually, I can feel
that since you came back,
you haven't been really happy.
Everyone has got some emotional wounds,
more or less.
I'm no different.
It's like an old scar
that hurts from time to time
to remind you of it.
But that scar
has long healed.
It's just that we can't go easy on ourselves.
In front of Gao Zhuo's grave,
I told you
he certainly wouldn't want you
to be like this.
What about you?
When will you pick up the scalpel again?
I once read a comic.
It said
after a pet died,
it actually went to heaven
and stayed at the edge of a cloud,
watching its owner day and night,
hoping
and waiting
to, one day,
reunite with us in heaven.
What about the departed people?
Where's their final resting place?
They must also be in some not distant stars
watching us and waiting for us.
Shen Mi, let's make a bet.
Bet what?
Let's bet
who can let go of the past
and start over first.
Deal.
Pinkie promise.
Does it still hurt?
Not as much as before.
Don't worry. It won't leave a scar.
Dr. Tian,
Dr. Tian, time to eat.
Dr. Tian, come eat.
Okay.
You stayed up late last night, right?
I went to see you earlier in the morning,
and you were still sleeping,
so I didn't wake you up.
Where is Mr. Zhao?
He's gone to dig up some vegetables for you.
Later, we'll catch a few chickens
for you to take away.
You guys enjoy yourselves here.
Tonight, I will cook a nice meal for you.
You guys can stay a few more days
and have fun here.
Thank you.
We didn't come here for fun.
You didn't come for fun?
Then why did you come all the way from the city
to this countryside?
We came to find someone.
Our pet hospital
wanted to collaborate with a big kennel,
but the owner
turned us down, not even letting us in.
Recently, we've heard
the owner is often seen
near Xiangshui Mountain,
so we thought about trying our luck.
What kennel is it?
It's "Panghu Kennel".
Old man,
come over here now.
I'm coming.
Dr. Tian, look.
This is the vegetable,
and this is our raised chicken,
all grown and raised by ourselves.
Take them when you leave.
You are too kind. Thank you.
You put it down first.
- Call your son now.
- For what?
They came to seek collaboration with Panghu.
Now you know it.
Why didn't you tell me before?
- You call him now!
- Old woman.
Actually, the owner of the Panghu Kennel
is my son.
Really?
Exactly.
Listen, boy.
Dr. Tian
has healed
two sick piglets at home
and also checked on others that were unwell.
What's wrong with helping them out?
I don't care what you think. I'm telling you.
The matter is settled.
If you don't do them the favor,
never come back home again.
Yes.
Dr. Tian,
it's all settled.
Later,
go to the kennel to see him.
That brat
must help you.
- But
- But what?
Say thank you to them.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
It's just a matter of saying a few words.
No need to say thank you. Come on, eat.
We don't have much here,
just some plain food.
- Mr. Shen
- How did the discussion with Guo Fan go?
I just wanted to report to you about it.
They didn't agree.
What's the reason?
You couldn't agree on a price?
It's not about money at all.
As soon as Professor Guo heard
it was for animal lymphoma targeted drugs,
he immediately said no.
Thank you.
You always eat the same thing with me.
Don't you get tired of that?
Of course not.
Moreover, my favorite
is the taste of the food in this restaurant.
Enough.
It's a bit disingenuous.
It's true.
And I think
if we have more chances
to get to know each other,
you'll find that we have more in common.
[Tianlin Animal Hospital]
Ms. Pelan,
so Tian Tian and Mr. Shen
really spent last night together?
That's right.
My sister-in-law personally told me.
Shen Mi was on a video call with my brother.
Think about how late it was.
Now that both
of them haven't come to the hospital,
maybe they stayed there last night?
You're quite gossipy.
Lower your voice.
Mr. Shen, the things are here. I'm leaving.
You've worked hard. Thank you.
Chen, this…
I'm sorry
for making your e-bike look like this.
No problem.
I'll get a cloth and some water
and just wipe it.
Let me help you wash it.
No need. I'll do it myself.
Alright, then I'll go park.
Shen Mi,
come here.
Last night,
you were staying outside with Tian Tian, right?
Yes.
Sleeping in one bed?
Good for you, Shen Mi!
Great.
Stop making a fuss,
and get your mind out of the gutter.
We just slept and didn't do anything else.
What do you think we did?
You didn't do anything?
No.
I thought as much.
Tian Tian is a good girl.
How could she consort with someone like you?
But she was chatting and watching the stars
with me at night.
Is this fun for you, bro?
Don't pick up this call--
Mr. Han.
What is so urgent that I have to return now?
Alright, I got it.
You come back. Where are you going?
I didn't finish talking! You come back.
- I'll return when I'm done with my work.
- Good.
Shen Mi,
open the door.
Shen Mi.
Shen Mi,
you've got such a poker face and a cold heart.
Are you still my brother?
It's infuriating. You cruel man.
Dr. Gu,
this meal should've been offered to you
a long time ago.
Mr. Shen, you are too kind.
Dr. Gu,
could you do me
a little favor?
Please go ahead.
Before the new drug release,
the company will conduct a series
of promotional activities.
You're now famous
on the Internet.
We want you
to participate
in some promotional activities.
Mr. Shen,
I'm just a developer.
My main job should be product development.
As for the promotional matters,
I think I won't participate.
Dr. Gu,
from what I observed,
you're not the sort of person
who is focused solely on research.
What do you mean by that?
I saw it at the company.
You've been getting close to Mengnan.
I heard that after you guys went abroad,
you ate
and played by the seaside together.
You're in a good relationship.
Mr. Shen,
are you worried
that I will establish some kind of relationship
with Shen Mi through Miss Han?
I'm not worried about that.
Didn't you say when you entered the company
that you were not interested
in the complex interpersonal relationships?
I did say that before.
I'm still maintaining it now.
I just simply
admire Miss Han.
Mr. Shen, if there's nothing else,
I will go back to the company.
Thank you for your lunch.
Compared to the number of lost lives,
you have saved more lives,
right?
Carlo has woken up.
That's why Carlo survived.
You gave him a second life.
To Carlo,
you are his hero.
Cut in vertically,
and then cut horizontally.
Zaizai, wake up.
Wake up, Zaizai.
Only through relentless trials
can one become truly strong.
For every lie Pinocchio told,
his nose would grow an inch longer.
His nose got longer and longer.
Pinocchio cried from fear.
When Pinocchio told a lie,
his nose would grow longer.
The Blue Fairy called for a woodpecker
to peck at Pinocchio's nose.
Finally, they managed
to return his nose to its original state.
There's not a big issue.
Come back again for a follow-up next Tuesday.
Be good.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Tian.
What's up?
Come close.
I know a huge secret in our hospital.
What secret?
It's about Shen Chen.
What happened to him?
He…
You two are always whispering sweet nothings.
We are discussing work.
You're not hiding it from others anymore.
I was telling the truth. Tian,
show me the patient records from last month.
Why are you staring at me?
I'm just here to get some water.
You guys carry on.
Come and tell me now.
Well,
Shen Chen is Shen Mi's younger brother.
Do you have any proof?
It's true. I overheard it at the door.
Shen Chen called Shen Mi "brother".
Why?
What a stupid piece of gossip.
I'm telling the truth.
Shen Chen has no filter.
No matter who he meets,
he can shoehorn them into being family.
He calls everyone "brother".
I've heard him
calling Shen Mi "brother" several times.
Are Shen Mi and Shen Chen
pursuing our director?
They argue frequently.
So what?
Considering Shen Mi's position,
isn't it an easy thing for him
to fire such a rival in love?
That's because Shen Mi is generous.
Not like you,
niggling about every little thing with me.
Why are you involving me
when talking about someone else?
Fine, let's just talk about Shen Mi then.
I think
Shen Mi is the elite type.
As for Shen Chen,
he's always making light of life,
almost equal to Tian Yuxian.
I think
he and Tian Yuxian
can't be more like brothers.
Where is he?
Boring.
Bro, what's going on with you?
You've lost five games in a row.
I don't want to either.
I'm not in the mood now,
so I can't fully focus on the game,
and I can't win.
Isn't it all because of my sister?
Exactly.
It's because of your sister.
Your sister even
stayed overnight with Shen Mi.
Of course.
I don't distrust Tian Tian.
But if things keep going
like this,
and their feelings develop over time,
your sister may not be able
to hold back anymore
and fall for his tricks.
He'll replace me
as your brother-in-law.
I don't want that poker face
to be my brother-in-law.
Yuxian, it's comforting to hear you say that.
When are you going to take me to our house
to see our father and mother?
- Stop, that's a different story.
- How can it be different?
It is really a different thing.
The day you take me to see Xing Tao
will be the day I take you to see my parents.
OK, Tian Yuxian.
If that's what you want.
Set up a meeting with Xing Tao for me.
He left the group.
When did he leave the group?
You don't know it?
I didn't know. Bye.
Why did he leave the group?
How would I know?
I have other ways to let you meet him.
[Rebirth Birthday Party]
Rebirth Birthday Party.
What does this mean?
Don't you know once you go to it?
- Can I go?
- Can I go to our house?
If you take me to the birthday party,
I will certainly take you to my house.
Of course I will if you take me--
Dr. Shen, emergency. Hurry up.
I'm coming.
Dr. Shen is here.
Dr. Shen.
Sit down and don't worry.
Chen, how's it?
Its blood pressure is already high. 180.
Its mouth smells of urine.
Abdominal fluid accumulation.
It might be uremia.
It's shivering.
Get it on oxygen now.
- Wen Jing, Valium.
- Okay.
It's shaking severely.
Hurry.
Be good and hold on. Come on.
Here it is.
- Here you are.
- Hold it down.
Be good and hold on.
It's okay.
Doctor, how is Sunny doing now?
Look at this.
Bilateral renal echo enhancement,
renal parenchyma thinning.
Poor demarcation
between the cortex and the medulla,
which is to say
its kidneys
lack normal structural features.
W-What does it mean?
Preliminary diagnosis.
It's kidney failure.
Doctor, how is Sunny doing now?
Sunny is suffering from acute uremia
caused by kidney failure.
And there is a large amount of ascitic fluid
in the abdomen.
I have already given it two injections
of ethacrynic acid.
But its blood creatinine and potassium
far exceed the normal range.
Just tell me how to treat it.
We can only
try peritoneal dialysis and see how it goes.
But because the condition
of the kidneys is bad,
the results might not be good.
To tell you the truth,
Sunny is already 13.
Dialysis does have some effect,
but renal failure is irreversible.
Sunny also has multiple complications.
Continuing like this
will only increase its pain.
Dr. Shen is saying
that based on Sunny's current condition,
we can at most only prolong its life.
You mean to suggest
that I should give it up?
Euthanasia is the best option.
No.
I won't give it up.
No matter what the cost,
you have to help me save it.
Doctors, I beg you.
You must save it.
Let me tell you, there are so many of us.
- You're here.
- You came. Sit.
Shen Chen.
Take your time eating.
What's wrong with you?
You're always late.
Is it any of your business?
This is…
Tian Yuxian, my little brother.
My good buddy, Shi Kai.
- Hello.
What's going on today?
He has been missing for four months.
He suddenly invited us to this party.
What is his intention?
Ice Blue Rose.
- Do you know?
- Beats me.
I've asked around and no one knows.
Do you know?
I don't know.
Ice Blue Rose is a man.
A man playing as a woman.
You two wait a moment.
Come.
Let me introduce her.
My girlfriend, Lulu.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Lulu?
This is for me?
[Lulu, I love you]
This firework is specially prepared
for you.
Who is Lulu?
The Lulu from "Lulu, I love you".
You don't have to say it out.
You are so lucky.
He is Jerk Kai.
He's a good guy.
If you don't know how to talk,
can you just shut up?
I wanted to. Never you mind.
- What?
- What's going on?
Hello, everyone.
- Xing Tao.
- What's going on?
- Hello.
- That is Xing Tao?
Yes.
Where are you?
Do any of you miss me?
You still didn't show up. Who would miss you?
Take it easy.
Let me treat you to this meal, okay?
Just a meal, huh?
I don't want to eat.
Where are you?
I think I heard someone cursing me.
- Yes, it is you.
- We are cursing you.
- Yes, we are cursing you.
- What's wrong with that?
Let me tell you.
The food in this restaurant
is very delicious.
I ordered all your favorites.
Bullshit. I hate cake the most.
Shi Kai,
have you seen that little suckling pig?
I ordered it specially for you.
Then you ordered it wrong.
You should have ordered oysters for him.
What Lulu or else?
- Thanks a lot.
- Don't mention it.
Shen Chen,
you told me
you'd brought my fan.
- His name is…
- Isn't this him?
Tian Yuxian.
I'm here!
Did you bring him?
I believe you have done it.
Hi, Tian Yuxian.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry for the lack of care. Enjoy the food.
- Where is he?
- What's going on?
- He must be here. Let's call him out.
Out!
What?
- Xing Tao.
- What's going on?
What happened?
Yeah.
What's up? Can't you recognize me?
What happened to you?
What?
I'm fine. What can happen to me?
Four months ago,
Tao suddenly fainted at home.
They found out he had a late-stage brain tumor.
Now the tumor is compressing his optic nerve.
He can hardly see with his eyes.
Mom, it's not as serious as you said.
I'm fine. Don't listen to her.
Ma'am, if you need any help,
just tell us.
There are so many of us.
Yes, we are here.
That's so icky.
Enough.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have kept it from you.
Okay, to express my apology.
Shi Kai,
you've always wanted
my limited edition graphics card, right?
I'll give it to you.
Shen Chen,
I'll give you my game account.
There are still a lot of tickets and points
from the official competition left.
Can you redeem them for skins for everyone?
Luo Yun
and others, if you want any skins,
just tell Shen Chen.
Mom,
I have a few more words to say to them.
My buddies,
you have all had your meal
and got your outfits.
As the saying goes,
there's no such thing
as a free lunch.
So next,
you guys must do me
a favor.
After I'm gone,
take care of my mother.
Tao.
Mom,
ever since you divorced my dad,
you've never remarried.
You sacrificed too much for me.
Mom, but your love is too heavy.
I can't bear it.
I know you want me
to be a good child,
but I have let you down.
No.
Yes.
All these years,
I have been a burden in your life.
It's okay now.
I have to leave early.
What are you talking about?
I won't be a burden to you anymore.
In the future,
you won't worry about my future anymore.
You can live
your own life, okay?
What nonsense you are talking about?
Stop.
Go back with me.
Mom.
Tao.
Are you okay?
I heard
what the doctor told you.
Didn't the doctor say two months ago
that I wouldn't survive for two months?
Mom,
it is the 61st day.
I got a bonus.
Please listen to me, Tao.
Let's go back to the hospital.
Mom, I don't want to go back.
Mom, don't.
Let's leave.
Tao.
Xing Tao.
Tao, are you okay?
Mom,
I…
I have one last wish.
Tell me.
I can do anything.
I can do everything for you.
I want to bring Sunny back.
Tao.
- Tao.
- Xing Tao.
Let's go back to the hospital.
- Go back to the hospital.
- Xing Tao.
So what he was referring to was that Sunny.
Now both of them are in a bad condition.
What should we do, Chen?
Aren't the man and the dog fine?
Stop nagging.
But Xing Tao said at the Rebirth Party
he wanted to take Sunny back to a place.
We have to figure out a solution for him,
don't we?
Even if the hospital agrees to bring Sunny in,
he can't take a step
without the dialysis machine right now.
What can we do?
Chen, I have a way.
[Tianlin Animal Hospital]
Tian Tian, you go get some rest
and I'll keep an eye on it.
Okay, replace the dialysate in two hours.
Okay.
Chen,
make sure that you bring everything
Sunny needs for peritoneal dialysis.
Everything is packed up.
But not telling your sister about this
makes me feel uneasy.
My sister will definitely not agree.
But if we don't do this,
I'm afraid we won't get another chance.
Go for Xing Tao!
Go for Sunny.
Let's go.
What happened?
Sunny's dead.
No. You are kidding me, right?
Sunny,
Sunny, don't fall asleep.
Sunny.
There must be a way. It can't be.
It's not true. Check it again.
Could you please check again?
Could you do
cardiopulmonary resuscitation on it?
- Can you? I'm begging you.
- Yuxian,
it's really gone.
No, you're lying to me.
There must be a way.
Tian Tian,
Sunny no longer has any signs of life.
Chen, we must have a way.
Yuxian.
Sunny, wake up, please.
Don't fall asleep, Sunny.
That's enough.
Let me say thank you
for Xing Tao.
Ma'am,
where exactly did Xing Tao want
to take Sunny back to?
Back to that sea.
Our old home was in a small town by the sea.
When his father and I chose
to get a divorce,
Tao couldn't accept it
and had suicidal thoughts.
♫ Your gaze is unwavering ♫
♫ Only enough to accommodate me ♫
♫ I have been melted by you countless times ♫
♫ Yet I'm at a loss for what to do ♫
♫ I can only hold on to you ♫
♫ Now you are still with me ♫
♫ Traveling through time together ♫
♫ Someday, I'll be completely
forgotten by the world ♫
♫ Leaving no trace ♫
♫ Only you will still remember ♫
♫ My appearance ♫