What the hell is wrong with you
Can you tell me something about it
I'm okay
I used to
Had a dog
Is one
Abandoned small border herdsmen
Called Zaizai
When I first came home,
Less than three months
It's just this big, isn't it
Dad, is this for me
Do you like it
Like
Then give it a name
Then I'll call you Zaizai in the future
When I came, I was pitifully thin
Don't let touch or hold
It took me about half a year
Just let it gradually adapt
My new master
Intermediate process
It's really hard
Slow down
That's right
The one for Carlo now
Fresh grain
That's when I was
In order to make it grow up well,
Try it over and over again
Matched out
I really love it
It can be said that
When I was growing up,
It spent it with me
I thought we'd be
Like this all my life
Be happy and be happy
But I forgot
Man's life is for dogs
It's too long
Wake up Zaizai
Zaizai, wake up, wake up
Wen Jing, hurry up
Hemostasis, hemostasis
Get the gauze quickly
Wake up, wake up, wake up, boy
Since then
I can't afford it anymore
The scalpel is gone
Where's Tian Tian
How's Huzi
Massive hemorrhage of spleen
I couldn't save it either
Rupture of spleen
There are no symptoms in the early stage
And Huzi
Large area infection of whole body
It can last until now
It's not easy already
Even if your father is here today
He can't come back to heaven either
You didn't expect it, did you
I am a man
Such an unqualified doctor
No
You are
You don't have to comfort me
I didn't comfort you
The reason why heroes are heroes
Because they have
A high degree of professionalism
Self-esteem
An extraordinary sense of responsibility
You did your best about Huzi
You never gave up from beginning to end
Just like that one time
When everyone
When I gave up saving Carlo,
Just you
Be insisting
No, I can't give up
Carlo Carlo, come on
Carlo
Carlo got it back
Saved back
That's why Carlo survived
You gave it a second life
For Carlo,
You are its hero
Compared with those who left unfortunately,
The life you saved with your own hands
Isn't it more
Their owners are also good
And the ones you saved
Small animals are also good
Will remember you
So we
Can we reach a consensus
I thought
You don't think about cooperation anymore
You saw it, too
I am a man
Dean who can't get on the operating table
Will affect
Customer's judgment on Tian Lin
If you Lvchuan
Have concerns
These questions
It's not something you should think about
Fear and Difficulties
Aren't they all surmountable
Thank you for your trust
Happy cooperation
Han lawyer
Dr Koo
What a coincidence
It's really a coincidence
I met you on my first day at work
Welcome to Lvchuan. Let's go
Do you have a work card
Don't mention it
Some things
Not overnight
Can be changed
But it's okay
Lvchuan R&D Department is on the sixth floor
You're not too tired to get up
Dr Koo
Last time you said
Do you want to invite me to dinner
Of course
Any time
Carlo
Carlo, come here
Hug
How good
I miss you so much
Do you miss me
I'm sorry
I don't have that much time to spend with you
Or I'm not going anywhere today
How about accompanying you
Don't go, okay
Sit down
Sit Carlo
Good boy, sit down
You weren't at the company today
At home
Do you have any plans for the evening
At night
Uncle Zhou's side
I don't know
What should I tell him
Tonight
Let me go with you
I'm at night
There are some important things to do
Let's make it a little earlier in the afternoon
Let's meet for dinner
What's up
You forget that today is
What day is it
Okay, I got it
I'm sorry, Carlo
I still have something to go out
I can be at home alone
All right
Not wronged
I was wrong, okay
I'm sorry
You have to practice if you don't want to be bullied
Understand
Come as soon as you start
My heart is dying
Take a break
Come
Get some water
Good
Then
Tell me about you and Han Mengnan
What do you want to hear
I can do whatever I want
Just talk about you two
When did you meet
January 10th
How nice
After going back,
You must introduce us both
Cognition
Of course
You are sure to become good friends
Let's do it again
Don't let me catch you
I
What the hell is this
Tradition of Tianlin Hospital
Reward love
This hasn't changed much
Yeah it hasn't changed at all
A little something
Wait a minute
I also made an appointment with someone else
Who is it
Gu Mingze
Did I ever tell you
About the R&D department
I don't want to get involved anymore
Why do you want to
Make decisions without authorization
Because I'm doing it for your own good
Gu Mingze's development of new drugs
And how important is the layout in the later period
It's not like you don't know
I can't just watch him
Fall into the hands of Shen Hongyuan
I thought
Before we
The place where we met for the first time
At this time of the year
Let's at least
You can have a good meal
Anyway, all these years
You are in a hurry
As if completing a task
Have dinner with me
Rather than this
We might as well talk about business
At least this meal is good
There are still some meanings
Miss Han
Dr Koo
Please sit down
Mi Zong
Dr Koo
Today
I'll welcome you on behalf of Lvchuan
By the way, I'll show you this one
I like the small shop for many years
You are welcome to be
A member of Green River
By the way
I also introduce you to Mr. Mi
After all, he used to
Is the head of the research and development department
For the whole workflow
And future deployment
It's very clear
So I'm today
Miss Han
In fact, before this,
Mi Zong and I
We've already met
It's just a face-to-face meeting
Although it was only once
But Mi Zong's actions that night
It's really impressive
You know I don't like it
Let's talk about business outside
If it's nothing, I'll go first
You eat slowly
I'm sorry, Dr. Gu
If you want to go after him
I don't mind
Huzi
I'm okay
As soon as Hu Zi left
Uncle Zhou
I lost my only partner
At least in this world
And you think about him
Caring for him
Think of him
He's not alone
Isn't it
Small animals are just like humans
Life is too fragile
If
I can save Huzi today
You can definitely become with it
A very good friend
If he's still alive
It should be, too
Is it as sad as Tian Tian
Do you remember him
Don't you like mangoes
This bowl is for you
Delicious
It smells so good
Shen Mi
Are you homesick
I think
I miss my grandpa
I miss my dad
I miss my mother
I also miss Han Mengnan
Gao Zhuo, it seems to be pregnant
What are you going to do
None of us are enough by ourselves
You still feed it
She's pregnant
It's going to have a baby
That won't work either
When you first met me
Why do you share the food with me
You are a man and he is a dog
Can it be the same
It's all life
What's the difference
We eat less and we can't die of hunger
But it
I'm sure I can't hold on
Give it
Come
Carlo, do you know
The dog we saved at that time
Is your mother
It seems to be dying
Really
This little guy is still alive
Looks like you don't have a home either
Why don't you let it come with us
The last puppy alive
It's you
Dad
Are you feeling any better
Better
Tian Tian
I heard that
You cried today
Dad
Do you also think
I'm pretty vulnerable
Tian Tian
A truly vulnerable person
It won't be easily shown
Can you be frank
Express one's intense emotions
It's not easy
You can cry
Just shows that
You put the profession of doctor
Look very sacred
This shows that you
Be grateful for life
Heart of awe
These
It's just you
The driving force to keep moving forward
Got it, Dad
Dad believes in you
Come to Carlo and shake hands
How good
Coming
Go Carlo
Management plan of animal hospital
How are you getting ready
It's ready
Get ready right away
Signed a cooperation agreement
It's quite fast
Which hospital is it
Tin Lam Animal Hospital
Never heard of it
Is it bad
The situation is particularly bad
Now poor and white
Will soon face bankruptcy
Children
What you do to yourself
It's really ruthless
I can't help it, grandpa
Since this is a test,
I have to treat myself
Drop a hard hand
Prove my own ability
Otherwise
In the end, there was no one
Take out the results
How can we convince everyone
Not bad
You can have this persistence
That's what I want to see
Come on
As long as you can succeed this time
The way forward
It will be much easier to walk
Got it Grandpa
Then let's do this first
Take care, Grandpa. Bye
The audit department's money has been approved
It should not be enough
Definitely not enough
Shen Hongyuan
You won't lend me money easily
But it doesn't matter
I've already given up
From my personal
Out of savings
Your uncle is too difficult to deal with
Say it is to
See the return on investment in three months
Tian Tian is still
My personal doctor
I think it's necessary
Think of a way as soon as possible
Divert his attention
Don't arrive at the time
Come to Tian Tian's hospital
Get in the way
Please sign, both of you
Do you need to be so formal
This is what Sister Perrin specially explained
The service is in place
All right
Shake hands and take a picture
It's not necessary, is it
This is Sister Perrin, too
Specially confessed
Said to hang in the hospital in the future
Look at me
Laugh, both of you
Wen Jing Wen Jing
What's the matter, Dr. Chen
Bring me the prescription food
Coming
Can't think of a signature
Take Tian Lin from
Saved from the fire pit
Now show me around
Row
Then I'll take you
Get to know each other formally
Tian Lin's employees
Walk
Come with me
Aunt
This is Tian Peilan
The front desk of the hospital
You've met before
Sister Perrin
Shen Zong Hao Shen Zong Hao
What about the big and small things in the hospital
You can all ask her
She knows all about it
Yes, I am a know-it-all
Ask me I know everything
I'll write it down later
I'm afraid I forgot
Gentle and quiet
Can you take a look at the front desk for me
I'll go out with Aunt Guo
You are busy first
This is Wen Jing
Shen Zonghao
What about our hospital
For these foster pets,
There is a walk service
What about this business
Tian Peilan is also responsible
You see
This piece is
All kinds of pet snacks sold
Are you nuts
Let you run
Sister help me
Run
Uncle Wang
I'll shave one for you today
We have something to discuss
You put down the fader first
Easy to discuss
That's easy for you to say
Go and see my dog
How did he shave it
Say
How to discuss
It will grow back in three months
I can't change my look next time
You have another time
Tian Yuxian, shut up
Uncle Wang
How about this
What about my trim this time? It's free
And then give it to you
Cleaning ear canal and cutting toenails
There are also three beauty 30% off cards
Is that all right with you
Oda
I'm doing it for your sake
Just promised
Yes yes yes
I'm so embarrassed
Gentle and quiet
Coming
Quickly
Do it for Uncle Wang
Three-time beauty 30% off card
Good
Uncle Wang
Really
Let's go, Uncle Wang
I'll shave you like this next time
Then take off your banner
Don't don't don't
It's hard to get it
You can't do this aesthetic either
You've been shaved
That's a unicorn
What do you know
You're young
Work experience
It's quite rich
Have worked in so many hospitals
Yeah
Because I grew up
I especially like small animals
Determined to engage in pet medicine
The reason
Working in so many hospitals
Also for the sake of
Learn from the strengths of many families
Dean Chen
Do you think I can do it or not
I think
Yes
In this way
You for a while
Go and find a nurse named Wen Jing
Just say
I told you to go through the entry formalities
Thank you, Dean Chen
You're welcome
This is Dr. Chen
Rich clinical experience
Work especially seriously and responsibly
You are busy first
Dean Chen
Then I'll go to the job
Sure
What about this way
Is the central disposal area
And the bathroom
Wait
Are you new here
Yeah, right away
Who are you
This is an investor in Shen General Hospital
The thermostatic fader is broken
Coming
Hurry up and fix it
You are Mr. Shen
Nice to meet you
Can I have a look at that
Of course
You were at Tintin Pet Hospital
How is Dean Liu recently
He's very nice
And we have a very good relationship
He sent me a message today
Want me to go back to work
Is it
Come on, it's okay
Then I'll go
Go ahead
How enthusiastic
Your hospital recruits people
Is that so casual
The one named Yue Yue
My perfume smells so heavy
How can it be in
What about working in a pet hospital
Girls
The love of beauty is understandable
And she's today
First day at work
Should be attached great importance to
Let's get her out of here
Her resume is false
Tintin Hospital
There is no Dean Liu at all
There's one more thing I don't understand
As a hospital
Recruiting people even the most basic
Don't you even do back tune
That could be
Chen Yifan is busy forgetting it
My first day as dean
What about him? He's a little unconvinced
This is the decentralization
Let him take care of the recruitment
And he recruited all these people
It's not so good if I'm going to open it.
Or
Let's just stay and try it out
If something goes wrong again
Can you fire her again
You promised me
Things big and small in this field
It's all by the two of us
Joint consultation
You call them over
Let's have a meeting
And why
Say one question at a time
You always have so many
What about excuses and reasons
I
It really is
I endure
This way
Shen Zonghao
My equipment here
Don't say Lvchuan
It is first-class in the whole country
It seems that Mr. Shen
It's really hard work
After all, the R&D department
It determines the future of the group
These people
From now on
At your command
Other departments of the group
If you need to
Will also cooperate with you
All right, Mr. Shen
After all, new drugs are on the market one day earlier
Small animals benefit one day earlier
You have a heavy burden
Mr. Shen, you can rest assured
What about recently
Tianlin has experienced many twists and turns
My father
That is, during the sick leave of the old dean
Where's Tian Lin
I also closed the store for a month
We lost a lot of customers
So this time it reopened
I hope everyone can struggle
Bring a new atmosphere to Tianlin
Today, I want to start from the business philosophy
As well as the scope of management and other aspects
Give it to everyone once
New rectification
I hope everyone can cooperate
Below
Please welcome Mr. Shen
Tian Lin's investors
Tell you two sentences
Actually
I don't have anything to say either
Anyway, the next thing
What about all the work
I will fully cooperate with Dean Hao Tian
Then let's work together
Work together
For the construction of Tianlin
Contribute one's strength
OK, that's the end of the meeting today
Do you think I should
Stick a toughened film
What about you, Mr. Chen
I'll post it for you
Which one is easy to use when you go
How can you just say these two words
Dr Koo
Han lawyer
Haven't got off work yet
Stay up late together
Sure
Han lawyer
How long have you been with Green Chuan Company
Coming right after graduation
There is a problem I think
Ask you for advice
You ask
You're in the legal department
Why do you care so much
Progress of R&D Department
What is your relationship with Shen Mi
The two of us
Family is a family friend
I have known each other since I was a child
Because of the research and development
About the future of Lvchuan
So I will care about Shen Mi
Got it
Understand
I understand that you are concerned about him
But sometimes it is inevitable to misunderstand
Support wrong feelings
What do you mean
Han lawyer
I actually quite understand
What you do
I also know
Many companies have it
Complex interpersonal relationships
Family businesses like Lvchuan
Definitely more so
But my job requires
Study wholeheartedly
Can't have any distractions
I don't want to participate in the infighting of the company
I don't want to ask more inside information
Dr Koo
I don't think you are
What is the misunderstanding about Shen Mi
I can explain
Shen Mi, he is not
The kind of person you imagine
How about we
Let's talk about something else
You said there was a meeting during the day
I thought
You have a lot to say
It turned out to be me
Come on, come on, talk a lot
What was the sole purpose of the meeting
Is to establish your prestige
Look at Chen Yifan
I won't accept you
And the operation of an enterprise
It is better to have only one decision maker
There can only be one person talking
Otherwise, there are so many people talking
Who exactly should they listen to
Don't even know
As for what I have
What kind of ideas
I'll tell you in private
Then it's private now
Why don't you tell me something about it
Your management of Tianlin
Do you have any suggestions
There are a lot of suggestions
I'll talk to you slowly later
Where are we going to eat
Be right there
Thank you
Delicious
Where were you just now
Before your store
Recharge activity
It's a thousand for two hundred
But don't you think two hundred
For customers
Is the allure too low
So I think
Change it to fill 1000
It is more appropriate to send a 20% discount card
Although the essence of the two is the same,
But I think
What about 20% discount cards for customers
Theirs
There will be more room for imagination
And with preferential strength
You can also pull
Other aspects of consumption
I remember this
On top of this
I think adding another one
Charge eight hundred
Send a 10% discount card
Then who will choose a 10% discount card
Of course not
That is
Further, in order to set off
Charm of 20% off card
And pull the stored value strength
You are very resourceful
I didn't expect you to be interested in running a family
A small hospital
So hard work
Enterprises are big or small
What about the business philosophy
It is also interlinked
What is the idea
Is the framework or the constraint
But the most important thing
Do you know what it is
What
Is a talented person
Speaking of talents
Do you think
How is Tianlin's talent reserve
Are all of them unique
Actually, I was just about to tell you
This matter
Say it
What's the matter
Now Tian Lin
These employees may want to
Full dismissal
Leave none