Speaking of talents
Do you think
How is Tianlin's talent reserve
Are all of them unique
Actually, I was just about to tell you
This matter
Say it
What's the matter
Now Tian Lin
These employees may want to
Full dismissal
Leave none
What did you say? Say it again
All expelled
Leave none
Don't eat you, man
The sausages are in your head
Right
It's not you, is it
What's wrong with it
What did they do wrong
Why should I be fired
You almost stabbed me
Do you know
You poked me in the heart
What did they do wrong
Why should I be expelled
Good
I'm telling you
Chen Yifan steals rape and plays tricks
Don't do practical things
Tian Peilan
In addition to prying for gossip,
Is to ask for gossip
Tian Yuxian has a cranky personality
Disobedience to management
Where's Yue Yue
It is full of lies
To resort to deceit
Am I wrong
What about Wen Jing
She is hardworking and willing to work
Why should I fire her, too
You didn't see what I just said
In all the scenes,
Did you take her with you
What's wrong with that
Employees needed by enterprises
Is to be able to focus
Focus on your major
And fast-growing employees
And not someone like her
No principles, no planning
I can only be a good old man
Such a person
In the company
It's fatal, you know
You
Row
You are eloquent
You're all ready
One set after another, right
Then I'll hear you out today
You almost stabbed me just now
You have to tell me you're sorry
Me and you
Who told you to fire them
I'm sorry
Have no sincerity
Don't go too far if you say it or not
You know
Lvchuan is studying a project
For cats and dogs
Experiment of lymphoma targeting drugs
Know
Once this drug is successfully developed,
Green Chuan will choose
A number of pilot hospitals
Carry out publicity and promotion
In the process of publicity and promotion,
Selected hospitals
You will get a lot of exposure
But that's not the point
The point is that in a short time
Can become a new drug
Hospital designated for use
So in my plan
Tianlin itself is the first in China
Isn't that a good thing
But now Tianlin is not worthy
This pilot hospital
Must be
The most professional and highest standard hospital
Who else will serve you
That's why I told you today
All the demands made
I'm doing it all for
Strive to develop in this direction
So I hope Tian Lin's future
Can be more specialized
Brand standardization
Can you understand what I'm saying
I know all the truth
But it's impossible to drive people
Why can't you understand
How can I understand
Tian Lin now
The operation mode of is
It's a family style
Management mode
It is operated by interpersonal relationships
And all the relationships
It all comes from your father
Equivalent to your father
Is using his own personality charm
To run the hospital
Do you think there is no risk in this
The risk is too great
Once your father falls down,
The hospital is equivalent to no more
Do you understand
I just hope
Can you learn from this matter
Learn some lessons
Don't repeat the same mistakes
I know
I told you to change
I'll make you a substitution
It will definitely bring short-term pain
But I think for Tian Lin,
In terms of future development,
You must endure this pain
I'm sorry
I can't bear the pain
How can you not understand
What am I talking about
Is that you don't understand
Tianlin has been established since then
Personnel changes often occur
But we never did
Voluntary dismissal
Any employee
Do you know what this is called
Called the Virgin
It's called human touch
What's the use of human touch
Human touch can help you
Improve performance
Can still help you
Get the qualification of pilot hospital
Human touch
For the future development of farmland forest,
Does it have any effect
It's useless. It's useless, okay
But they can be in the hospital
In a precarious situation
Stick to it until the last moment
This is called human touch
They are all human beings
This hospital has feelings
Selfish and MoMo like you
A man who doesn't even have a friend
You can't understand it at all
You want to fire them, you can
Then you fire me first
Emotion is emotion
Work is work
I won't tell you
You eat your intestines
Shen Zongzao
Get out of the way
Sister Perrin
Busy
Let me ask you something
Ask
What's the matter
Mi Zong
With our dean
What relationship
As you can see
This relationship between them is unusual
Why is it unusual
Between this man and woman
What else is unusual
It is impossible
They were just like enemies
Who doesn't pay attention to who
It's on again
Dr. Chen will give you some water
Is this stock fun
You don't manage money
Wealth ignores you
Please, can you be a little lighter
Why don't I give it to you on the second floor
Let's get a separate office
Save you from squeezing in my house every day
Interaction reduces efficiency
What is this
This is Tianlin's current cash flow
A hundred thousand
Why is there so little left
So you're still going to
Decorate one for me alone
The office
No
Have no money
Tian Tian Emergency Department
Coming right away
Hello
I'll take his temperature first
41.2 degrees
Doctor
Is it serious that our family is happy and strict
Don't worry yet
Does it have any lately
Symptoms such as diarrhea and vomiting
No, ah
Diet defecation
It's all quite normal
So this is it
Let's do a blood routine first
See if there is anything wrong with the blood phase
If there is no problem
It should be no big deal
Row
Then you go outside first
Take a rest and wait
That's hard for you
Don't be afraid
Don't move, baby. It hurts a little
I'll do it. I'll do it
No need
It's enough for me and Wen Jing
Why don't you get busy with something else
It's okay. I'm not busy, Dean Tian
I was originally a physician assistant
Assisting you is not
It's my job
Right, too
Then this is for you
And
Cephalosporins may be used later
I want to give it a skin test
Good
Tian Tian
Grandma Wang called and said
Their fat ball is sick again
Answer the phone quickly
Good
You take care of it for me
Darling oh
Grandma Wang, she's here
Grandma Wang
What's the situation now
To
Are you saying
Vomiting is yellow-green, right
What about defecation
It's like water, right
Are there any other features
OK, I get a general idea
Don't worry about Grandma Wang
I'm ready to come right now
Good
All right, I'll see you later
I have to go out to see a doctor
Go on, go on
This place is yours
Take it here
Yue Yue
It's the thin one
I know
Gentle and quiet
Take the blood routine results
Show me
Are you going to make a home visit
I'm afraid the fat ball will get small
Go and have a look
Normal hemoglobin
Lymphocyte hyperplasia
Looks like a viral cold
Yue Yue is not inflammation
You don't have to test it
Good
You go quickly
I'll call it later
0.5 ml of Tonglian
Okay, that's yours
See you later
Why are you here
You're not
Do you need a car in an emergency
Get in the car
OK, thank you
It's quite good
Isn't it quite good
It's cat plague
Fortunately, there is no blood in the stool
Or you'll be in trouble
Grandma Wang, where are you going
I'll I'll boil a pot of water
Let me make you tea
It's okay. Don't bother
No trouble
Thank you, Grandma Wang
I especially want to drink tea
We'll drink when you're ready later
Good
Why are you so thirsty
I thought you needed an infusion
Can you hurry up
Urge. Urge. Urge. What
There is a process here
Hold it for me and hang it up
This is about the same
It will take more than an hour
If you have something to do, go back first
Then I do have
A lot of things to do
And my schedule
Particularly busy
But
I've already declined
So would you like to
In this hour's time,
Have a small chat with me
Just talk
What do you want to talk about
Talk about the two of us
The relationship between
Relationship
Aren't we just
A cooperative relationship
What I want to talk about is
Between the two of us
A cooperative relationship
How to talk
I think so
What about a good cooperative relationship
What is it based on
Is based on long-term stability
Knowing and trusting each other
On the basis of
But now for you and me
Almost zero
The two of us barely have
So I think we
It is necessary to communicate well
To learn more about
Each other's inner thoughts
Or ours
Some things in life
Do you know what I mean
Row
Then how do you understand it
How to communicate
Particularly simple
Just ask each other a question
OK, then I'll ask first
How did you shape this
Of an inhuman character
Why did you ask first
I, I brought it up. I asked questions first
Do you still want to
Enhance one's feelings
Don't answer and pull down
OK, I'll answer you
You tell me
How did you do it
Go anywhere
Meet anyone
All right
What about love so overflowing
You haven't answered my question yet
Did I just answer
It's unreasonable
Tian Tian, I'm telling you
You're gonna talk to me like this
Our partnership
There will never be improvement
There will never be development
Do you know what I mean
OK, then I'll change it to a simpler one
Do you have a girl you like
No
How many girlfriends have you talked about
No, either
None of them
You don't grow up
Haven't even been in love, have you
Why
You don't like women
What about you
Have you ever had it
Have you ever been in love
How many boyfriends have you had
You tell me to come
One
None of them
Why
Why don't you think about it
What about your own problems
Like you
How can anyone like it
Who said that
There are so many people who like me
From childhood to adulthood
I don't want to talk about it myself
I am afraid of delaying my study
What are you laughing at
Where's Gu Mingze
Ever chase you, too
Gu Xuechang
How do you know him
That day
You're done drinking
I saw him like this
I'm holding it out for you
I drank too much that day
People help me to be normal
You said how did you
So I don't care about you.
Drill into other people's arms when you are drunk
What about safety awareness
Have no guard at all
Do you know him well
You
More familiar than you
And said that I
What about lawyer Han
Han lawyer
With the two of us asking questions today
Does it have anything to do with it
At your grandfather's house that day
She has an aggressive look
Almost ate me alive
There is a problem at first sight
You go with the cat
You play with the cat
Our topic today
That's all for now
Don't say a word
I don't want to tell you
You go see the cat
I was going to see the fat ball
It's still hello
Much better than that man
Compare with whom
Who do you compare cats with
You're not even as good as a cat
That's better than one
People who no one likes are better
I
I told you there was
Thank you, Mr. Shen
Send me there in spite of my busy schedule
What are you doing
You calm down
We are treating
Don't do it
Who are you hitting
What kind of hospital is this
Stop
What are you doing? You guys
Chen Yifan
What the hell is going on
Doctor Chan
What's the matter
Huanhuan is dying
Doctor Chen, come and have a look
How come it's in shock
What did you give it
I don't know
Nurse Wen injected it
Tong Li'an
It's just like this
It is impossible for Tong Li'an to go into shock
Where's the medicine
That
This is not Tong Li'an
This is a cephalosporin
What are you doing
How's Huan Huan
Dr. Chen has treated it very well
It was injected in time
Adrenaline
Samethasone sodium phosphate
I just hung up on glucose
It has stabilized
What about Huan Huan's master
After all, it was our hospital's mistake
I think he
You can't let us go easily
You don't have to worry about this matter
I've settled it through negotiation
They also signed the confidentiality agreement
No one will put this matter
Divulge
Shen Zong really has good skills
Since Shen always puts this matter
Handle it so thoroughly
So perfect
Then it's nothing
Let's withdraw
Wait a minute, wait a minute
I didn't say completely solve it, did I
Do you know that
This matter if
If it is not handled properly,
Will be on the hospital
What are the consequences
So in order to
Avoid such a thing
Happens again
I think
Wen Jing Yue Yue
Between the two of you
One must stand up
Take full responsibility
I
Shen Zong
It's not that I pass the buck
I've been assisting Nurse Wen all the way
In the end, she was operating it all
I injected the medicine. That's right
But
The medicine is smoked by Yue Yue
How can it be that I took the medicine
I just handed you the needle
That cephalosporin
I haven't even touched it
You're not all alone
Operated
Yue Yue
How can you turn right and wrong upside down
No
That
How could I not tell
What about cephalosporin and Tolliam
Then according to what you say
I've worked for so many years
Can't I tell the difference between these two medicines
I
Shen Zong
I think this thing
It can't be Wen Jing's fault
Experienced in Wen Jing
This little Wen
In our hospital
It has been working for many years
Her professionalism
Everyone is also obvious to all
Right
So this low-level mistake
She can't have committed it
I also stand gentle and quiet
What do you say, sister
I
You are all acquaintances
So you bully
I'm a new comer
How do you talk
No
That's not what we meant
That
Shen Zong
I didn't do it
Mr. Shen, you have to believe me
What should Mr. Shen do
It's very simple
Both are open
What
No
The other man is innocent
Better kill a thousand than put one
What do you mean
Who you kill and who you release
I'm telling you
If you fire Wen,
Just get rid of me first
Get out of the way
Nothing
I advised him, Mr. Shen
Elder sister
Tian Lin is really boring now
I quit, too
Tian Yuxian Tian
I apply to resign
Gentle and quiet
So
Are you admitting that you did something wrong
Is it
That medicine
It's really not my mistake
I-I just don't want
Dr. Chen and them
Because I'm leaving here
It really shouldn't be like this
Gentle and quiet
Let me ask you a question
Haven't seen it
Never touched it
Is that right
I definitely didn't
Let's get her out of here
Mr. Shen Shen
What does that mean
Is the medicine ready
All right
Cosmetic color number
I don't particularly understand
But if you look at it
The color of this bottle
With the lipstick she used
Are they the same
Yue Yue, sorry
Please immediately
Pack up your personal belongings
Leave Tianlin Hospital immediately
Go and go
Who wants to be here
Get out of the way
Thank you, Mr. Shen
You don't have to thank me
You should thank those who want to thank
Trust your colleagues
And
You have to remember
No matter in the future
Anything happens
You have to know
What should I do
Stick to your bottom line and principles
Things you shouldn't do
It's not something you should do
Learn to refuse
Get it
I'm going to thank them
I told you so
That Yue Yue, right
Yes yes
The resume is false
You didn't listen at that time
And now
Yes
And
Chen Yifan Tian Yuxian
You see
What's their attitude? To me
I saw it
But they're today
Willing to
Sacrifice yourself to save others
This is what it is
The human touch in your mouth
So I think
Let's both take a step back
Take a step back
Let me set you a performance
As long as you can finish it
I won't fire them
What performance appraisal
Make a profit within three months
Three
Three months
Row
Isn't it profit
That's right
Hospital hush money
Take the hospital account
What kind of person is stingy
Yes
Carlo, why are you here
Carlo
Why are you here
What are you doing here
Don't let me work
Isn't it
Go
Let's go over there
Carlo, look at it. It's okay
It didn't get that heavy
Carlo
Isn't it
Fat and heavy
What's the matter
Don't let me work, do you
What else is there
There are many more
That, that upstairs
That one, two or three or so, that one
How's it going
Old money
I know why old money divorced
Why why why
Because it's a woman
What
Female
Little three
Who ah who ah
You, you said
I'm sure I won't tell
My goodness
Who is not good to find? Why find her
I saw her
Lots of boyfriends there
You
That Aunt Guan
That cat food
It's selling so well on our side
It's gone
Shall I call you
Just the one with the tail number 38
Isn't it
Hurry up and eat it.
I'll call you. Call you
Thank you. I'm leaving.
I'll call you. I'll call you.
All right
This cat food is really
It's selling so well. Really
Wei, thank you. I'll do it. I'll do it
It's a mess. It's too busy. Really
All right
It's a mess. Clean up
Boss
Call everyone to the meeting
Good
I'm going to call it now
Immediately
What about this one
I specially prepared it for you
I'll tell you about it now
Approximately
What are you doing
Do you want to play golf
The hospital is for you
Where you play golf
Doctor Chan
I'm talking to you
Can you show me a little respect
Can you turn around
Yes, I'm listening
Go ahead
Revenue equals traffic
What is the flow equal to
The so-called traffic is equivalent to
All the guests
Come to our shop
What is the conversion rate
Existing these
After the guests arrive at our store,
Like our stay
Don't like our walk
After establishing a relationship with us,
Then there is our next
Guest order rate
What do you like for lunch
Old place
Sure
No, let's order takeout
I want to eat fried eel with shrimp
I eat fried rice cake
Let's all talk about it
Let me make a statistic
I, I, Zhajiang Noodles
Then order me a piece of Sichuan
Do you want some noodles
Before I finish my words today,
No one will leave this room
What does that mean
Is this going to grade us
Since macroscopic things
You're not interested
Then let's talk about a little microscopic
What about starting today
I introduced a new assessment
What about this assessment
Out of 100
Passing line 60
Scores of assessment
With your monthly salary
Direct hook
If your assessment
Achieve full marks
You will get a corresponding bonus
But if you are
If you fail
No bonus
Wages can only be paid to you
Seventy percent
Why is this
None before
Such a regulation
Dean Tian, isn't he
Why change it now
I
This is Dean Tian and me
Unanimously decided
Is that right
What about this assessment mechanism
Not for
Deduct everyone's treatment
Pure to get our hospital
Take a step further
For the development of the hospital
Let's be considerate
Understand it
You
Shen Zong
I have one here
It's on page two
The third big article and the third small article
It is forbidden to chat with customers
I'm a receptionist here
Is that I communicate with customers
That's me
It is a good way to maintain customer relations
A very important means
You won't let me communicate
Don't let me chat
How can I do my work
You as a receptionist
What you talk about is linked to business
Of course there is no problem
But
You little book
Do you mind if I have a look
Thank me
Come
Let me have a look at what you usually remember
What are they
Turn a page casually
What's all this
Lao Qian and Lao Zhang next door
Rear-end collision insurance claims
Mao Mao is in a hurry
Run away from home with a dog
What do you mean
You keep recording these things
What to do
Do you want to be a detective
And
September 3
Zhao Jie of Haojing Yueting
Driving a new Porsche
Follow-up with edamame
You even have people
I remember my name clearly
My daughter's new private middle school
The tuition fee is 250,000 a year
Are you kidding me
You remember all these things
What are you doing? You
What are you doing
I'm telling you
You as a receptionist
You will meet every day
All kinds of people
What you need to do most
Is what they ask you
What do you give them
It's as simple as that
Why do you want to
To record these things
I don't understand
You pry into other people's privacy
Does it make sense
Before you learn
How to be a good front desk
I'll keep this book for you
All right, you go back
Tian
Tian Peilan
Sit down
One thing I don't understand
You put a few of us
It's all arranged clearly
Then what standard should I take
What about you
The criteria for assessing me
Particularly simple
At least three months to complete
Half of the turnover
What is this
This is
Our current performance requirements
Brand promotion plan
Since what
Tian Lin has asked me
Take over in an all-round way
So all the plans
I did it all over again
And you have to know
We don't have
So much time to settle down
A good brand
It takes ten years to precipitate
Even decades
But you didn't
You only have three months
And now
One of the most difficult problems is
The whole hospital goes up and down
Just a doctor in Chen Yifan
This is a big trouble
You're only half
Then according to what you say
Our Tianlin Hospital is nothing
Of course not
There is also a huge advantage
It was adopted by Tian Lin
Stray pets
You won't
To use these stray animals
Do publicity
That's right
I mentioned it in the plan
The concept of a support fund
What about all the people who come to Tianlin Hospital
All right
Donate if you want
No way
This is not with you Lvchuan at the beginning
Do paid adoption
Is it a property
What's wrong with paid adoption
Of course there is a problem
That charity
How can it be used to make money
It's not called making money
Can you not be so narrow-minded
Lvchuan is also good, Tianlin is also good
We're just creating
More opportunities
Let caring people
To unleash their love
You can't even connect them
The right to release love
Have you taken it all away
Kick well
I'm surprised
Shen Zong
The environment is basically finished
Just small animals
Hard work
That's right
I also want to
Dean Jean Tian
Take a shot of holding a kitten
And then our interior
It's basically over
I'll lead the team to shoot on location
That's right
Let me introduce you
What about this one
Is our Dean Tian
Hello, Dean Tian
Hello
I've worked hard for you for a while
I
Ka
Dean Tian
Smile again
A good director
I'm sorry. I'll do it again
Okay, let's do it again
To prepare
Three, two, one start
Ka
Let's have another one
Dean Tian
Do you remember it
What was it like when it first came
What's it like now
It changed so much
Have such a warm home
It's all because of you
So you should be happy
Then I'll try again
Director
Let me have one with her
Okay, no problem
Okay, come on, let's get ready
Come
Three, two, one start
Yes, just sweep it here
To give you a card
Row pair
It is also a stray cat to play with
Yeah, we've been here for a while. Yeah
This is your thing
Okay, go well
Thank you
Stethoscope
OK, thank you
Nothing
Next
Come on, do you want to cut it
Right
A little long
Give it a shave
Row
Its hair is so long
Little darling, darling
You can choose something
Go to check out
Okay, okay, okay
Thank you
Thank you for your love
Honey, you're playing here
The hair is knotted
You can't do this at ordinary times
It's not good for it
I have some hair to cut
Shen Zong
What are you doing
I'm ready
Put this area
All for stray animals
A place to do that kind of free activities
Let them have a
Play space
Save some time when someone says I
Take public welfare money to do black things
How come this man has such a good memory
What are you looking at
Can you pass me those pliers
To
Do you have something to pay back
It's okay. Why don't you go to work first
I'm just a little unaccustomed