tomorrow's final
I'll play too
See you at the stadium tomorrow
Come on
See you tomorrow
Finished
This teacher Zhao used to
teach us clinical
Very powerful
What to do tomorrow
I'll take you somewhere
Why did you bring me here?
You'll know if you come with me
Unexpectedly, it has been so many years
The layout of the place
Nothing has changed
That year I was
stand at this place
Watching you save Carlo
Dr. Zhao
Get some adrenaline now
No, it's too late
No, I can't give up
Carlo Carlo wakes up
So no matter who the opponent is
What is his identity?
What kind of qualifications and background
I believe you
as long as you don't give up
keep at it
I believe you will stand out
you can
Just like back then
You didn't give up on Carlo
I see
thank you
Unexpectedly, our Mr. Shen
I fell in love at first glance
I am determined and persistent
that time
Just make a secret promise to me
what are you doing
Look how big your face is
It hurts
you don't let go
they are gone
Woohyun is still in the hospital
He's probably worried too
Tomorrow's game
Probably
What a person he is
Although usually lazy
But for the things you care about
Still very caring
Even if he is allowed to go back at this point
He can't sleep either
Let him practice
Are you staying here tonight?
This is close to the competition venue
I won't bother anymore
Then I'll stay with you
Why
who let
I'm Dean Tian's boyfriend
how can you tell
If you are so not ashamed
Don't look, don't look, don't look
Not suitable for children Not suitable for children
I have a headache from memorizing the test questions
I'm coming out for some air
Take the dog for a walk
continue
please continue
Go quickly Go quickly Go quickly
what do you have to say
Can you say it all at once?
Tian Peilan prepared the hot pot
Are you interested in joining us?
You two are also staying in Tianlin tonight.
What do we call us?
You live here too
Yes
The scene is so close to the hospital
We won't bother anymore
If you both feel
If we are in the way here
We can go
is not it
Where is Wen Jing?
Why don't Wen Jing come to dinner?
right
I saw her just now
Why doesn't she come to dinner?
Doctor Chen Doctor Chen
Tian Tian
Doctor Chen
There is an emergency
Where is the patient?
patient
Can't come
How long has it been since her water broke?
Probably more than half an hour
Its belly has been shrinking before
I checked online
Biscuits are having contractions
But I can't give birth
So I just
let me see
what do you want to do
I want to check
The condition of its birth canal
Doctor
How are the biscuits doing now?
Fetal malposition
It's breech
So it's stuck in the birth canal
Can't give birth
That
What to do now
Cookies come
Let's get up and take a walk
Let's go slowly
Walk
Can I take a walk?
OK
I let it walk slowly and slowly
Restoring the birth position
In this way, natural products are the best
It's really not possible
Just take it to the hospital
Had a caesarean section
caesarean section
Come
Take a walk slowly
Slow down, biscuit
Come
Slow down
Biscuit is a stray dog ​​in the community
Originally I just fed him once a day
Later found out
Its belly is getting bigger and bigger
I'm worried about its safety
I just brought it home
Then if it's a caesarean section
How much does it cost
You don't have to worry about money
Let me help you solve it
Thank you
Mr. Shen, are you so aware?
Of course
After all, I am now
But Dean Tian’s people
So since you are so aware
Just go make some goat milk.
obey
okay
How simple. Soaked
Have you tested the water temperature?
Have to try it on the back of your hand
It’s fine if it’s neither hot nor cold
Of course I tried
Walk
Let's do it again
Walk slowly
The water temperature is just right
don't worry
I have contractions
Ready for production
Come on, walk slowly
Come cookies
Come
Cookies come on
biscuits
come on! Come on
Come on, it's almost time
Cookies come on
Thank you, Dr. Oda
If it weren't for you today
I don't even know what to do
No need to thank me
It would be great if mother and son are safe
And the puppy is so cute
Right
This is my business card
if you have anything
Just call me
good
Then let's go
Walk slowly
thank you bye
goodbye
Walk slowly
Dr. Gu
Hello
I want to make one
DNA identification
is it ok
good
Wait for the results to come out
I will inform you
Thank you
should
Shen Mi, where have you been?
I'm in the audience
Why did you go to the auditorium?
I'm so nervous now
My legs are a little weak
We yesterday
Didn't we just review it?
I'm just afraid
not performing well
After all, this is the final
It is related to the future of our Tianlin
So I pay special attention to
It's not you who says you are the only one
Fearless of heaven and earth
Dean Oda
Just one
Medical competition finals
You can't control it anymore
I understand everything
But now
Still very flustered
It doesn’t matter
Then let me give you some reassurance.
Come on Tian Lin, defeat Xi Chong
Come on Tian Lin
Why are there so many people?
Come on Tian Lin, defeat Xi Chong
Come on Tian Lin
thank you
thank you all
Did you see it? Tian Tian
these are you
people who have helped
They all came here specially today
Cheer you up
cheer for you
Cheer for Tian Lin
Right
And Xiaozhu asked me to tell you
Although she couldn't come to the scene
But she will be in her heart
cheer you up
Shen Mi
You are really
How can you be so annoying
Originally
I'm already nervous enough
You still do this kind of thing to make me cry
Silly, why are you crying?
Actually there is another person
thank you too
Who?
I
you
thank you for letting me
found me once
Things lost in the heart
What's the meaning
what is inside you
Throw away something
my secret
secret
I'll tell you after the game is over
Play well
come on
Pre-war mobilization rally, come on
Hurry up Hurry up
Here you go, sister
Okay, everyone is here
Let me tell you
Finals game process
first round
Comprehensive pet grooming
Tian Yuxian
are you ready
rest assured
You kid is going to lose to that Amu
See how I deal with you
I'll cut it with scissors
Even better than him pushing with a clipper
Close your eyes and you'll win
What about the second round?
It's a knowledge contest
The rules of the knowledge contest are
Bonus points for correct answers
Points will be deducted for wrong answers
So there must be
Full certainty
Go and answer again
clear
The third round follows the rules
It's better for the three of us to go
Lao Chen and I Wen Jing
rest assured
Can't make it to the third round
second round
Just take them
But
Without this third round
Then I'm so amazing
Deep medical literacy
There's no way to show it
Comrades
None of this is important
As long as our Tian Lin wins the championship
I'm Chen Yifan
soon
Good luck in love and career
Lao Chen, then you and my aunt
Isn't this a sure thing?
Who to nail? Where to nail?
How to nail it?
Please sit down
OK OK
No kidding
Let me tell you something now
Very serious matter
I also found out temporarily
Xichong found a foreign aid
I know this foreign aid
it was me before
When I was studying at Agricultural University
Teacher Zhao
He is very powerful
He is taking us
clinical experiment course
Also at Agricultural University Hospital
Served as attending physician
This is fine
Isn't this cheating?
This is too despicable
that is
When I first got the news
as angry as you
but
Someone told me
No matter what the identity of the other party is
You'll know just by listening to the prelude
It's the poisonous chicken soup given by Shen Mi
who wants to listen
This is when you are in love
It will inevitably emit some
sour smell
but
this taste
I like it very much
It's a bit sour
stay away from me
Don't infect me
one two three
Come on Tian Lin
Defeat the favorite
Dear guests
ladies and gentlemen
dear friends
Welcome everyone
Pet Medical Competition
The scene of the final
first
please allow me to introduce to you again
Those who came to the scene today
Guest judges
They are
Editor-in-Chief of Pet Fashion Magazine
Ms. Zhang Lin
welcome
College of Veterinary Medicine, Agricultural University
Dean Lin Nianzhi
welcome
Vice President Mr. Liu Zengming
Famous veterinary medicine expert
Dr. Shi Mingyuan welcomes you
Adult animal medical devices
Group Chairman
Mr. Feng Jinyi
welcome
and Chinese Veterinary Medical Association
Ms. Qiao Li, Senior Researcher
welcome
Mr. Shen
In fact, during the preliminaries
Dr. Shi and Mr. Feng should be allowed to
Brush Tian Lin down
Then play this game
What else does it mean
Two contestants, please take your seats.
our
The content of the first round of competition is
by contestants
For these two cute Bichons
Get full body care
Including fur, mouth, head
and hair trimming
good
i declare
The game officially begins
good
Tian Yuxian
Okay
right
I think Tian Lin
It must be no problem
nice
It's over
Why are you so behind here?
a bit slow
Amu is deliberately putting pressure on
But Tian Yuxian
not affected
no disruption
own steps and rhythm
I believe within the stipulated time
He can definitely do it
Can
The rhythm has caught up
Why hasn't he started yet?
how do you feel
His hair clipper is out of power, right?
This should be checked before the game.
That won't work
Hello
Our player tools
Something went wrong
can you help us
How many AA batteries should I replace?
I'm afraid this won't work
Contest rules
After the contest starts, the players
No one is allowed to enter
no
Then this is an emergency.
We can't do this
Tian Yuxian, come on
Doesn't anyone care about this?
Come on Tian Yuxian
come on
you can
he won't be
Use scissors the whole time
Use scissors for this
Do you have enough time?
Say it again
It can't be cut evenly.
this round
The outcome has been decided
good
we can see
Xipetfang has taken the lead
finished the game
Let us applaud and congratulate him
Awesome pet
well done
Okay, Tian Linfang, don't be anxious.
Hope it can work steadily
within a limited time
Complete your work better
Nine
eight
seven
six
five
Four
three
two
one
Game time is up
Ask players to put down their tools
Waiting for review by judges
This player
Please put down your tools
Waiting for review by judges
Isn't this against the rules?
time has come
Future grades will not count.
Yes
Completion on time is a hard condition
He is no longer qualified to judge
Dean Lin
what do you think
Score, just say the score
But I would like to see it
his works
What happened in the end
Ask him to continue
good
Tian Linfang has completed the game
Congratulate him with applause
come on! Come on
Now let’s invite the judges
Works for two-bit contestants
Score
Mr. Shen
Our five judges
Give us forty-four points
Tian Lin zero points
Not a point
We've won this game for sure.
Editor-in-Chief Zhang, please rate the Tianlin team
ten
Congratulations to Team Tianlin and applause
Now we invite Editor-in-Chief Zhang
Rate the team
zero points
Why
What is the situation? This is
Thank you
big screen
Please show us
final score
It seems that Editor Zhang
Thoughts on this game
and other judges
There is a big difference
Now can you please
share it with us
what do you think
First of all, I want to tell you
Explain
why did i give
This favorite player has zero points
Usually we give puppies
while taking a bath
The water temperature will be controlled at
Between thirty and forty degrees
But this player
Just skipped the temperature test step
Flush the puppy
Already produced
severe stress reaction
a pair of puppies
Players without any love
here with me
Only deserves zero points
but on the contrary
This player
Just done it right
throughout the care process
The puppy doesn’t feel any discomfort
I think
He really means it
Taking care of puppies
instead of attending a
A win-or-lose game
Then I want to tell you something
This player from Tian Lin
This look is made for a puppy
Indeed
It looks like this shape
deviant
but i want
everyone
They all have different aesthetics
Needless to say this
I think from a technical perspective
Let’s analyze it for everyone
why i
Give this player full marks
Give a simple example
Use a pair of electric shears to make a board size
It's a very simple thing
But if you use one
ordinary scissors
It's very testing
This player’s control
and accuracy
everyone can see
This puppy’s face
was cut into one
Beautiful square shape
regardless of hair
edge uniformity
Still close to
ninety degree right angle
It can be said to be close to perfect
So I gave him full marks
Of course this player
May be past game time
but i still
I really appreciate your superb skills
and caring attitude toward pets.
So I appreciate you very much
Of course
my score
may not change any outcome
But I still want to tell you
you did really great
good
OK thank you
Thanks to Editor Zhang for his wonderful sharing
Now we invite the audience
Rate the two players
Support the Xi Chong representative team
Please rate
Please highlight
Support Tian Lin’s team
Please rate
Please highlight
OK thank you
Now we are about to have a
exciting moments
will be presented to you soon
The final result of this game
XiChong International Animal Hospital
Scored forty-eight points
Tianlin Animal Hospital
Scored forty-six points
I hereby declare
XiChong International Animal Hospital
Win this game
good
Then pass
The results of the two players
As can be seen
Completely opposite to the judges’ ratings
Our live audience
Voting status
only twenty spectators
Voted for Xi Chong
but others
one hundred and eighty spectators
Everyone voted for Tian Lin
among five judges
When all scores are zero
Tian Lin was only two points behind
lost the game
this is really
It's incredible
Tian Yuxian
what are you doing
I am the winner
Tian Yuxian
Blame me
before i go on stage
Just check the battery again
What's the big deal?
It's just a game
Yes or no
And you did a great job
do you know
we all saw it
you made one
Professional pet groomer
everything to do
Yes Woohyun
you hear everyone
Any cheers for you?
And your performance
everyone has seen it
Much better than that Amu
Let's have a good match in the next game
win over
We'll always get over it and get the points
no big deal
we will definitely win
will definitely win
Will definitely win
Come on Tian Lin
Defeat the favorite
i have bad news
Physicians participating in quizzes
The professional qualification certificate must be at least one year old
That's over
Wen Jing is less than a year old
she can't attend
What about this third round?
is a supplementary rule
Just posted this morning
It should be my uncle
What the heck they did
There is no limit to the third round
As long as the number of people
No more than four will do
no
I can't even compete in the second round.
And the third round
Isn’t this aimed at our Tian Lin?
So what should I do now?
Who else can come to the rescue now?
No matter who you are looking for now
It's too late
Twenty minutes left
The game is about to start
There's simply not enough time
I just
We also protested against the temporary adjustment of the rules
But I guess
Nothing will change
Mr. Shen
This trick of yours is killing people
It's really high
It seems that Tian Lin
It's up to me to take action.
elder brother
Shen Chen
Your boy arrived just in time.
Do you know we are in trouble?
Come and save us from fire and water
Seriously
I never looked like
Thinking about you now
Lao Chen
Miss me so much
Your hands are a bit strong
I thought there was no me
You can't handle the preliminaries at all
Didn't expect
Let you sneak into the finals
I heard that the rules of the competition have been changed
Thoughts of our colleagues
Let me stop by and take a look.
Knew it
You just can't do it without me
It is conceivable
how important i am
right
too important
The second round starts soon
Players from both teams are invited to enter the venue one after another.
Came at just the right time
Of course
Now everyone is here
Let's prepare quickly
Go down and compete
Walk
Let's go
Wait a moment
What are your plans?
What are you nervous about?
The second round starts soon
Players from both teams are invited to enter
The first to enter is
Happy pet team
welcome them with applause
The entry now is
Tian Lin team
welcome them with applause
Defeat the favorite
Come on, defeat Xi Chong
Come on Tian Lin, defeat Xi Chong
Mr. Shen, isn’t that your son?
What does it mean to draw fire under the cauldron?
Killing people is the only way to feel happy
Come on Tian Lin, defeat Xi Chong
Invite players to take their seats
The game officially begins
Please look at the first question on the big screen
Beijing 2008
at the 29th Olympic Games
Mascot five Fuwa dolls
The appearance of one of the mascots
is a fish
So may I ask what the mascot’s nickname is?
what is it
A Beibei
B Jingjing
C Huanhuan
D Ying Ying
please answer
Did I read that right?
Is this a pet knowledge contest?
This topic is also
I choose A Beibei
answer
correct
Add 100 points to your favorite pet
Hi Chong, well done
good
Please look at the next question Big screen
Often seen in Chinese Pharmacopoeia
after solution
The symbol marking one bar and ten
I know this question
What does it represent?
A represents the density of the liquid
B serial number
C stands for volume concentration
D stands for liquid purity
Please
Choose C
represents volume concentration
Answer correctly
One hundred more points for happy pets
Next question
in dog saliva
Are there digestive enzymes?
A Yes
B No
please answer
Answer Correct
Tian Lin plus one hundred points
Tian Lin is awesome
Engaged in Animal Cranial Cavity Thoracic Cavity
and abdominal animal clinics
More than a few are needed
Get a licensed veterinarian
What about the people with qualification certificates?
A five
B six
C three
D four
please answer
This Doctor Shen
How from the beginning to now
I won’t grab a single question.
Isn't he unable to answer?
yes
How is it possible?
My brother is so professional
I must be able to answer it
Press it
Press quickly
Stay steady
This is just the beginning
It's not the critical moment yet
Are you still able to keep your composure?
Please
D four
answer
Mistake
100 points deducted for happy pets
It should be three
Then Tian Lin’s players
Do you want to continue answering?
Please
C three
Answer correctly
Tian Lin plus one hundred points
Tian Lin is awesome
Tian Lin, come on
good
Come on Okay
Tian Lin, come on
Mr. Shen
Is your son going to the end?
When will we do this?
Yes, I can keep my composure
Dear audience friends
our game
Already entered
white-hot stage
Tian Lin and Xichong
Both scored 3,200 points
enter together
The fight for the last question
Please look at the big screen
Dog eats spoiled fish
After meat, yogurt and other foods
Will suddenly vomit and have diarrhea
tearful itchy
I feel like their question
Will definitely answer
So can't
Give them the upper hand
I'll come
please answer
Wait a moment
This question
don't worry
good
Take a look first
Do you know this question?
I came into contact with it when I was in school
But I'm not sure the answer
Shen Chen, can you?