(Cheese in the Trap)
You should've been more careful.
Do you want to go for food? Let's go.
Come to your senses, Hong Seol.
You can't let that smile fool you.
- Mad Hair.
- Are you out of your mind?
(Seo Kang Joon, Lee Sung Kyung)
- That's such a great idea.
- I know, right?
(Park Min Ji, Nam Joo Hyeok)
(Cheese in the Trap)
- Seol! Congratulations.
- Bo Ra.
I heard you got a scholarship.
- I'm proud of you, Seol!
- Eun Taek...
Let's celebrate!
Seol, you look amazing today.
Seol, treat us to food.
Jung. That's Min Soo, not me.
Why are they acting like that?
Hey, Mad Hair.
I heard about the scholarship.
Congratulations.
That's In Ho.
Jung.
- Jung.
- Seol!
Congratulations.
Let's go for dinner.
Yes, let's go.
- Nice!
- Yes!
That's not me!
She's not me.
Where are you guys going?
Don't go.
What was that about? What a crazy dream!
(Oh Yeong Gon)
Gosh, is he really crazy?
Is Seol not answering my calls?
Why isn't she picking up?
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached.
Fine.
You'll find out who the real jerk is
when you see this text message.
Will you be able to handle the truth?
Please.
I really hope that you can see the truth.
Open your eyes, Seol.
(Episode 9)
Even if small problems
shape up like little waves,
they're just little waves
that will disappear.
I can get through them
just like everyone else.
Hey, Hong Seol! Hong Seol!
Seol, wait! I have to talk to you.
Hey, come here.
Gosh, seriously!
Hey, I'm going to get you!
Stop! I have something to tell you!
Gosh! That girl is driving me nuts!
Gosh, I stayed up all night
at an internet cafe!
Go away, seriously!
Sang Cheol.
Why haven't you sent it yet?
Well, Jae Woo was supposed
to do half of it and send it to me...
Why is Jae Woo doing it? It's yours.
Well, give me more time.
How can you ask for more time
when you already got extra time?
Plus, the extended deadline passed.
It was three days ago.
Trust me, I'm working on it now.
I'm just finishing it up.
I'll send it to you by 11pm tonight, okay?
Everyone else has already sent theirs.
- You must send it by 11pm tonight.
- Okay.
- This is really the last time.
- I got it.
Trust me, Seol.
But if those little waves
keep snarling and slapping you,
you can't just sit there
and endure it all.
Hey, Seol. I'm so sorry for
not getting in touch with you.
I had a family emergency.
Gosh, I can't believe
Jae Woo refused to help me.
You saw it too.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Is this our presentation script?
Wow. I'll memorise it quickly
and do a good job at the presentation.
Gosh, this is so neat.
You never disappoint me, Seol.
Wait.
Hold on.
I took your name out.
I told you last time.
You didn't participate,
so I omitted your name.
Hey.
Are you kidding me right now?
Did I intentionally not work on it?
I told you that I had a family emergency!
Look.
I'm in my senior year,
and my dad has retired.
Plus, I'm the eldest son.
Seol.
Do you really have to do this to me?
- Sang Cheol, keep it down.
- You stay out of this.
Do you have to be this mean?
That's none of my business.
- What?
- Do you expect us...
to do everything for you
because of your personal matters?
We all have personal matters.
I already told you last time,
and I won't change my decision.
- What did you just say?
- Seol is right.
Gyeong Hwan and I
also agreed to take your name out.
I can't believe you guys.
How dare you?
Gosh, this is crazy.
Listen.
Add my name right now.
You should've at least
given me the heads up!
- You could've called me at least!
- Stop it, seriously!
- I'm happy about Seol's...
- Gosh, I'm really...
Sang Cheol.
The professor will be here shortly.
Are you taking her side
because she's your girlfriend?
You don't care
since it won't affect your grade.
Good luck with the presentation.
Goodness.
Hey, add my name right now.
Stop yelling.
You guys should've at least
given me a heads up about this!
He's so loud.
- Jae Woo!
- What?
- Min Soo.
- Yes?
What time is it?
- You should have told me.
- Why?
It's 9:58am.
- Thanks.
- What are you going to do?
- Is it my fault?
- Be quiet already.
- I'm going to fail again.
- Hello, everyone.
What's all the noise about?
I could hear you
from the end of the hallway.
You must be all prepared.
I can see that you're excited.
Aren't you thrilled to present?
Aren't you exhilarated?
Yes. I'm looking forward
to your presentations too.
All right.
We'll start with group one.
Group one, come to the front.
Why are there only three of you?
- Sang Cheol.
- Yes.
People don't change easily, do they?
Okay, let's start.
Hello. My team did a research
on organisational behaviour...
and transactional leadership.
I'm Hong Seol, and I'll be leading
my team's presentation.
We'll go over the concept
and conditions of being...
a transactional leader,
then show you images and examples.
Let's define the concept first.
A transactional leader is someone...
who exchanges what he or she
wants with what others want.
This type of leadership compensates
people for their effort and...
promises performance-contingent rewards...
in order to acknowledge
their achievements.
According to Hellriegel
and Slocum's definition,
the ability
to predict future trends is one.
Other characteristics
include leading others while...
empowering them to become good leaders.
Now, let's look at a few examples
of transformational leadership.
I'm Son Min Soo.
Yes, Min Soo.
Don't stutter this time.
I hope you're well prepared.
Terry Fox is another example
of a transformational leader.
Seol, isn't that what we did?
Our presentation from last year.
He was a cancer research activist.
- I'm sure it's just similar.
- With his artificial right leg,
he embarked on a marathon
to raise money and awareness...
- for cancer research in 1980.
- It's too similar.
In the process
of preparing this presentation,
we learned that transactional
and transformational leadership are...
It's not just similar.
Look, it even has the same typo.
Do you remember that typo?
Personal gain is what motivates it.
In transformational leadership,
the elements of motivation...
are vision and value.
She's copying you
even in her assignment now.
Thank you for watching our presentation.
I didn't expect
that you'd cover the differences...
between transactional
and transformational leadership.
That was impressive.
As you just saw...
If I say something now,
it'll only complicate matters.
Submitting materials
to prove myself will be a hassle.
I might end up
upsetting other classmates too.
All right.
Feel free to ask questions.
But...
I don't want her
to take credit for something I did.
Your presentation.
Did you put it together yourself?
Pardon?
I'm asking because the content
is too similar to my presentation,
Understanding Leadership, from last year.
That's impossible.
May I say something?
The comparison between
transactional leadership and...
transformational leadership
comes up all the time.
- I don't appreciate that question.
- That's right.
I don't know why you're doing this to me,
but I hope it's not
because of personal feelings.
You have no proof,
so you have no right to accuse me.
What did you say? It's obvious
that you plagiarised her work.
Over there.
Let's take a look at the typo.
That's the exact same typo I made.
I put it up on a website
without being aware of the typo.
Don't you think it's a bit too
coincidental to have the same typo?
You didn't even proofread it.
All you did was change the font
and copied and paste the contents.
No! I put this all together myself.
- That's Seol's presentation!
- That's enough!
I don't know why I have to
listen to you guys arguing.
Group three's presentation
showed the analysis very clearly,
and the chart at the end was great too.
However, if you actually copied
someone else's presentation,
it's a completely different story,
isn't it?
Son Min Soo.
And you two.
Meet me in my office after class.
Okay?
All right, everyone.
Good job today.
I don't know if all of you are happy
with how your presentations went.
Doing a team project isn't easy, right?
Because it can be challenging,
I trust that you could learn a lot.
We'll wrap up today's class here.
- Thank you.
Min Soo.
What is this mess?
I knew that it would
turn into a mess like this.
But I don't care about how people
will judge me. I can no longer...
put up with Min Soo or Sang Cheol.
No, Jung helped me put it together.
Jung! Please say something.
You picked the topic
as well as the presentation file.
I didn't pick anything.
I told you about a website to refer to.
Plus, no sensible person would...
present or submit someone else's work
without changing a thing.
Don't you have any common sense?
Min Soo. How can you even think
to blame it all on Jung?
Gosh. I get so frustrated
whenever I'm in the same team as you.
Don't you know
that everyone is calling you a fake?
You dress like Seol,
and now you even copy her work?
Why would I copy Seol?
Stop it already.
Look, Seol. Are you happy that you ruined
our team's presentation?
You're really scary, Seol.
You could've talked to us after class.
Did you have to bring it up
in front of Professor Kang?
Don't you think that was too harsh?
Listen.
She only spoke the truth.
- Why are you blaming Seol?
- You stay out of this.
You were so mean to Sang Cheol too.
Why couldn't you just include his name?
Did you have to be that extreme knowing
that he'll lose the mark?
Goodness.
If you're that kind and thoughtful,
team up with him next time
and give him all the credit, okay?
Gosh, you're really unbelievable.
- Shut your mouth.
- I'm talking to Seol, not you.
I'm sick and tired of you.
Stop blaming others.
Hey, I'm so sick of
even hearing your voice, okay?
I hope you get a D on the presentation.
What? It clearly says
that it's 50 percent off.
Why are you asking for 50 cents more?
The ones on the left are on sale,
not the ones on the right.
What?
Then you should've specified it
in the discount sign.
Just take this and stop creating a fuss.
Gosh, thank you.
Shall we have a quick chat outside?
How much for this?
He's not stylish,
but he sure is dressed American-style.
- Maybe he's from a rich family.
- Pardon me?
I'm really grateful
for what you did earlier.
I want to repay your kindness.
Can you give me your number?
Well, that's not really necessary.
Are you a business major?
Yes. But why are you
talking to me so casually?
Then you must know Yu Jung.
I'm in the same year as him.
Then do you know where he is now?
I'm not that close to him,
so I wouldn't know.
Right! Ask that girl over there.
She's his girlfriend.
What? His girlfriend?
So...
he got a girlfriend after making me
become a mess like this?
I'll get going now.
Hong Seol, I can't believe
what you did to me.
Hey!
I'm so sorry! I didn't see you at all.
Get up.
Get up now.
Why are you doing this to me?
- I meant to grab your clothes.
- Goodness!
- Gosh, what's wrong with my hand?
- Stop.
What do you want from me?
I heard that you're Jung's girlfriend.
Pardon?
Why is Jung dating a loser like you?
He must have lost his mind.
I'm not Jung's girlfriend.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm not done talking!
It's Hong Seol.
You should be talking to her, not me.
Go find her if you're here
to beat up Jung's girlfriend!
Did I say that I'd beat you up?
Why are you making me look like a mobster?
Whatever your name is,
I guess you didn't know that you needed
my approval to date Jung.
I'm so sick of playing the same piece
over and over again.
- I honestly can't believe...
- I hope that today was...
Goodness, what is she...
Has Jung lost his mind?
How can he date a girl like this?
- Are you mad?
- What are you doing here?
Hey! You!
Listen, you! I'm going to get you.
You, red curly hair. Look at me!
You, curly hair!
I'm going to come back and find you.
Brace yourself!
You better be prepared! In Ho! Hey!
Do you want to get locked up?
Why are you causing a scene here?
Jung, that jerk, is telling me
to move out of the condo!
That jerk is starting to get on my nerves.
Mr. Yu told me to listen to Jung
and gave me only 10,000 dollars.
- 10,000 dollars?
- Gosh.
That's a lot of money!
That's more than enough
to find a new place, you spoiled snob.
How can it be more than enough?
I've used up most of it already.
I'm going through
such a rough time right now.
All the brands I love are pouring out
their new collections.
Do you even know how it feels
not to be able to buy any of them?
How would I know? How in the world
could I understand you?
By the way, why are you here?
Are you also here to see Jung?
It's none of your business.
Gosh, I'm completely baffled.
Why is Jung dating that ugly girl?
Did he get hit in the head?
What are you talking about?
- You mean that girl?
- I knew it.
He's definitely been acting strange
these days.
What was her name? What a joke.
My purses and clothes!
I'm sure she's getting all of them
instead of me.
Gosh, I really can't allow that!
Stop! You better not
show up here ever again.
Why are you on the campus anyway?
Just go shopping. Get lost.
Gosh, how can I go shopping...
- when I have no money?
- Just leave.
Come on.
- Thank you, Professor.
- Take care.
What's going on with Min Soo?
She didn't even show up.
She'll get penalised.
She's getting what she deserves.
You said that you're meeting Jung now,
right?
It must be nice to see him.
You made it.
I almost forgot your face.
I guess you missed me.
Yes.
By the way, I'm sorry.
I ruined your team's presentation.
Don't worry.
Everyone worked hard.
She shouldn't have cheated like that.
I finally feel alive.
Me too.
We literally just met,
but we have to say goodbye now.
I feel lifeless again.
Me too.
But what can you do?
You have to go to work.
Then shall we hang out after I'm done?
Do you have time though?
Of course.
I'll call you.
I really don't want to go.
Hey, Hong Seol!
- What do you want?
- You keep ignoring my calls,
so I had to find you like this.
What do you want from me?
Just take a look at this.
You'll regret it if you don't see this.
Forget it.
Whatever it is, I'm not interested.
This!
It's related to Jung, okay?
I won't go on about it.
Just have a quick look at it, okay?
You should know who the real jerk is.
Look.
This is who Jung really is, okay?
I think Seol likes you.
Tell her how you feel about her.
What about getting her a gift?
You should go to the same institute
as her to see her during the break.
Seol likes you too.
She's just playing hard to get.
Hey.
Bring it back! Open this door!
I must check. I'm not sure
what's going on, but I need to check.
One, two...
Oh, I did it! Darn it.
Gosh, why do you keep calling?
Aren't you that jerk from last time?
Who is this? Isn't this Yu Jung's phone?
Yu Jung?
- Who is this?
- You tell me first.
I asked you first, okay?
I can only tell you
after you tell me who you are.
- My name is Hong Seol.
- Open the door!
I'm calling to see
if this is Jung's number.
Hong Seol? You're Hong Seol?
You must be obsessed with Jung.
How did you get this number?
Do you know me?
Finding out who I am
will make your stomach cringe.
- Shell I tell you?
- Hey, open up.
I'm Jung's girlfriend.
I heard through the grapevine
that you think you're his girlfriend.
Don't be so delusional. I highly
recommend you go see a therapist.
Gosh! Open up.
I didn't know you were this strong.
Give it to me.
Did you call this number?
Did the woman pick up?
Did you talk to her?
Wow, I'm surprised
that she answered the call.
Hey! That's Yu Jung's other girlfriend,
you fool!
(Seol)
It's okay.
Get in.
How's it going?
Are you enjoying the internship?
I think I'm adjusting pretty well.
That's great.
You wanted to try it, so do your best.
It won't always be easy.
Working with other people...
will make you realise that you're not
the centre of the world.
I thought I was the smartest person
in the world, but...
I learned that this world is full of
people who are smarter than me.
There are lots of scary people too.
Not everything in the world
will go your way.
You should accept the fact now.
You're an adult now, right?
Yes.
It sounded a lot like In Ho's sister.
And she said that it was Jung's phone.
No.
I shouldn't trust what Yeong Gon said...
or what that woman said.
I need to ask Jung about it first.
Seol.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I was worried.
What's the matter?
Jung.
Yes?
Last year,
I asked you about Yeong Gon.
Do you remember?
Yes.
And you're aware of...
what I went through last year
because of him.
You know, right?
Yes.
I know.
Today, Yeong Gon...
showed me text messages
which are supposedly from you.
Those text messages,
did you really send it to him?
The person who sent those texts
saying that I like Yeong Gon...
Was that really you?
Jung.
Yes, I sent them.
Then, why did In Ho's sister
answer the phone when I called the number?
And...
she said that she's your girlfriend.
- How will you explain that?
- That's not true.
Baek In Ha.
She answered the call because
she took the phone I used to use.
She said those things to you because...
she probably wanted
to give you a hard time.
If that's the case,
why did he give his phone to her?
So don't worry about what she said.
Then Jung did send those text messages
to Yeong Gon.
Then what about those text messages?
Did he give his phone to her
after sending those texts?
Why did you send those text messages
to Yeong Gon?
When I asked you last year,
you said that you just listened to him
when he was being delusional.
But to me, it doesn't look like
you were just listening.
It actually looks like
you instigated the whole thing.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
It's all my fault.
I took it too lightly.
I didn't know
that it would blow up like this.
You didn't know?
You know what Yeong Gon is like.
Are you saying
you didn't know how he would react?
You really didn't know?
I had no idea.
You had no idea?
Really?
You really had no idea?
That's right.
I didn't know.
I'm serious.
No.
Jung clearly hated me last year,
and there's no way he sent those messages
with no motive.
What was his motive?
Seol. I know that you're angry.
I understand why.
But he misinterpreted my messages
and put you through all that.
I think that part is his fault.
Plus, why is he talking about
those messages from last year now?
He did it to tear us apart.
Let's not fall into his trap.
It's all in the past anyway.
Jung, you really haven't...
changed at all.
From the way you reacted
to what Mr. Heo said to now,
nothing has changed.
Is that all?
Did you really tell me everything?
Really?
What do you want me to say?
Jung, tell me.
What kind of person are you?
How long does he want me
to practise the basics?
It's crushing my pride.
Goodness.
What are those two doing over there?
Did they have an argument?
Gosh. Why would they argue
on a street like this?
I can't go this way because of them.
Let's...
give each other some time.
What do you mean?
Whenever we go through these things,
I don't know what to do.
I can't understand you.
I want to get closer to you,
but it's so hard taking a step forward.
- Seol.
- This time, I hope you can...
really think about everything
that has happened.
I knew it.
Everyone knows how Jung is.
He's probably breaking Mad Hair's heart.
Her heart will probably
be shattered to pieces.
Whatever.
Who cares?
She got herself into this mess
in the first place.
But why is she...
Why is she with him
when all they do is fight?
I should really mind my own business.
Let me stay here for a little while, okay?
Because of someone, I got
kicked out of the place I was living in.
If you won't let me, I'll have to
move back into Mr. Yu's place.
Go ahead and do it
if you want my dad to estrange you.
He won't be thrilled when he finds out
that you spent all the money.
What? You knew that he gave me money
to look for a place?
I'm the one who told him
to give it to you.
I knew you'd be like this.
So, you did it so that I wouldn't try
to get more money off Mr. Yu?
You're using your brain for a change.
Hong Seol.
She called me today.
I thought the name sounded familiar.
She's the one you were trying
to set that idiot up with, right?
Gosh, I thought she was your girlfriend
or something like that...
and got all tense for a moment.
What are you plotting now?
Tell me whenever you want to
get that clingy girl out of your life.
It'll be a piece of cake for me.
If you let me live in the condo again,
I'll also...
Why are you taking the phone away from me?
Do you still not get it?
Who is the clingy one that I can't stand?
Who? Who...
Me? Are you saying
that I'm clinging to you?
If you know, keep your mouth shut
and behave yourself.
I don't want to.
Let me show you what being clingy means.
You won't be able
to get rid of me that easily.
Okay.
Then do whatever you want.
Just know that...
I'm doing my best not to get angry at you
for what you did today.
It'd be wise to stay away from me.
Hey!
Open the darn door!
What did I do to deserve this?
Is she really your girlfriend?
Hey, stop! Come back here!
Gosh, what am I going to do?
He got in the elevator!
Tell her how you feel about her.
What about getting her a gift?
You should go to the same institute as her
to see her during the break.
You know that girls play hard to get
even if they like the guy, right?
Seol likes you too.
She's just not showing it.
You two would make a very cute couple,
so keep hitting on her.
Was I right about Jung last year?
Am I being fooled?
Even if I am,
will I be able to break up with Jung?
I need to focus.
Focus, Hong Seol.
(I miss you...)
(I hope you'll have a good day...)
Good luck with the exam.
Hey, Seol.
Are you going to school this early?
Oh, hi. Yes.
I have an exam today.
Why are you here?
You're not the only one.
I have a lesson too.
Let's go together.
I see.
By the way, why do you look so haggard?
Did you always look like this?
Yes.
This is what I look like.
Drink this.
This should help alleviate
the anger you have towards your boyfriend.
How did you know?
Did you see us?
Did the two of you really argue?
Gosh, I should become a fortune teller.
I already told you.
He makes all his girlfriends cry.
So what did you fight about?
You know that I know him very well.
I can give you advice...
Gosh, I know exactly what you'd say.
You'll just badmouth Jung.
Right.
I don't have anything good
to say about him.
See? Look at you.
I knew it.
I'll take this.
Thanks.
Why is she talking so casually to me?
Hey, don't drink it.
- I spat in it.
- Gosh, this is delicious.
Give it back to me!
You should be grateful for me.
Hong Seol is here.
Seol.
Good luck with the exam.
It's so awkward.
Did you break up with Jung?
I told you. I'm the only one
who sincerely cares about you.
- Min Soo.
- Yes?
You haven't apologised to Seol
about the presentation yet, right?
Why should I?
I know I copied her work,
but she doesn't deserve an apology.
Goodness, Min Soo.
This is why things never work out for you.
Let me give you some advice.
What are you doing now?
Well...
I tried playing something else
for a change.
Fine, I get it.
I'll practise it over and over again.
Fine, then.
I was going to give you
another piece to practise.
I'll practise this.
I'll do my best.
- I really will.
- Keep practising the basics.
What's this? This is "Fur Elise"...
I want to play something more challenging.
It's such a fun piece.
Give it back to me if you don't want it.
Wait, I'll do it.
That grumpy old man is so impatient.
I'll start practising it now.
- It's done!
- Gosh, the exam is finally over.
- Seriously.
- It's finally done.
Did you do well?
Don't ask me that kind of question.
How was it for you?
- I don't know.
- I'm sure you did well.
Hey, Seol.
I want to talk to you
about my presentation.
I want to apologise to you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to copy your work.
You'll accept my apology, right?
Well, are you sorry about anything else?
What do you mean by that?
What else did I do?
What is wrong with her?
I apologised to her. Why does she have to
hold a grudge like that?
Seol. You were harsh enough to her
on the day of the presentation.
You're really weird.
Totally. It's also ridiculous
that she thinks Min Soo is copying her.
I know. Her style of clothes
is all over the internet.
Yes! I admit
that I did copy her presentation,
- but my clothes are really...
- Yes. Don't worry.
Don't even apologise to her.
You girls are being ridiculous.
Listen. Pretending to be sorry like that
isn't an apology!
- Gosh, Bo Ra. Stop it.
- Have some shame.
- How dare you?
- Is she yelling at me right now?
Stop getting involved
in other people's business!
- Let go of me!
- They're like two peas in a pod.
You, fools.
Get a taste of this!
Gosh, I'm so annoyed.
Hey, what shall we eat?
Sorry, I have plans for lunch.
Eat with your friend. Bye!
- What plans?
- Sorry, Da Young!
Hey!
Gosh, I'm so annoyed right now.
I'm jealous that you have a boyfriend.
You have a boyfriend too.
He's quite good-looking.
Is he younger than you?
- What?
- Just tell me. I saw it.
The wallpaper on your phone.
Isn't he your boyfriend?
Right, that photo...
Yes, he is.
Really? Good for you!
You have a boyfriend now? Who is he?
How old is he?
Well, he's younger than me,
and he's very handsome and cute.
He tells me
that he's totally in love with me.
He's so good to me.
- Min Soo, show us his photo.
- I'll show it to you later.
You don't want other girls
to know how cute he is?
Are you already trying to control him?
No, that's not it.
- I'm so jealous.
- Gosh, I'm hungry.
- What do you feel like eating?
- What shall we eat?
Well, I can't really say that I lied.
I could end up going out with him.
Listen. If you're bored,
help your parents at their restaurant...
instead of coming to my school.
Why? Don't you like me visiting you here?
Well, I have to study for my exam,
but I can't focus because of you.
Go now.
Hey, Ah Young.
Shall I...
quit my school in the States
and transfer here?
Then we can go to the same school
like when we were in high school.
Joon. Weren't you so excited
about going to school abroad?
Well, that was...
I just thought that it'd help me find
what I want to do.
But it's not fun at all.
Plus, I keep thinking about
this person in Korea.
Kumquat, I thought about you so much
when I was feeling lonely there.
Stop calling me Kumquat!
Why are you calling me that?
You look like a kumquat.
What else can I call you then?
You haven't grown much ever since.
Plus, don't you think
it's a cute nickname?
- Whatever.
- I should call Seol.
I'll ask her to buy us food.
No, no. Let's call Jung...
and plan a double date.
Joon. Just go home if you're going to
keep talking nonsense.
I'm going to go to the library to study.
- Why?
- You keep disturbing me.
Where am I supposed to go, then?
Just stay here.
- I don't want to! Go now.
- Just study here, okay?
Gosh, Seol.
She's actually quite pretty looking
at her from this angle.
She has a small face.
Gosh, she's actually very stylish.
Why didn't I notice it sooner?
Gosh, you startled me.
- What are you doing now?
- Was this yours?
It was on the floor.
I didn't know whose it was.
Hey, where are you going? Wait for me!
Seol.
I thought about it and...
Seol, listen to me.
Stop!
Stop and listen to me.
Wait, I want to talk to you.
- Gosh, seriously...
- Goodness! Let go of me!
You're too much.
I told you everything.
You now know what kind of jerk Jung is.
You know the truth now, right?
- Send this to me after, okay?
- You think it's you?
- Yes.
- Stop being so delusional.
I've changed a lot.
I've gotten quite popular in school,
and my family is well off too.
Aren't I good enough to be your boyfriend?
What's that now?
I'm going to break up
with Da Young soon too.
I was just using her anyway
to make everyone like me.
I'll break up with her as soon as
you make up your mind...
What are you two doing?
- What are you doing here?
- You're beyond ridiculous.
I'm actually beginning to pity you.
- What?
- You're such a loser.
I've never seen a loser like you
in my entire life.
- Great. We're almost there.
- Did you just call me a loser?
- He's going up to her.
- Just hug her now.
You, witch.
- Just wait.
- That rat...
We're almost there.
Keep quiet.
You want to get a hug from me, don't you?
Okay.
I'll hug you.
- Come here, Seol.
- That rat...
- Gosh...
- Come here.
- Come here, you pervert!
- Gosh, why is he here?
Stop right there, you rat!
Gosh, stop following me!
Did you record everything?
- What was that jerk doing?
- You ruined everything!
Goodness.
Let me see.
Gosh, it's that guy's fault.
He ruined it all.
What did I do?
You've lost your mind.
You're crazy.
Going through all those things
must've made you become gutsy.
Stop it already.
We're inside the library now.
What? Evidence? Let me do this.
You frustrate me so much.
A rat like him needs
to be beaten up, okay?
Gosh, seriously.
You're being so noisy.
And after I'm done here,
I have to go and study for my exam.
You should go home without me.
No, I don't want to do that.
It's dangerous at night.
That lunatic can show up anytime.
You know what?
You should learn self-defence from me.
You're too weak.
Right, you need a weapon.
I'll buy you pepper spray.
If anything happens,
I'll use this book as my weapon.
I don't need a special weapon.
You can't defend yourself with a book.
Let's just go back home together
all the time.
That will make me feel better.
Gosh.
What are you doing now?
I've been thinking.
How about you take the qualification exam
for university entrance?
What?
Study for the qualification exam
and get into university.
Then you can study music too.
Forget it.
I never studied even as a kid.
I'm not taking that exam.
What's wrong?
Your sister.
Was she really close to Jung?
Listen.
Why do you keep bringing up this topic?
You're weird.
Well, I was just curious.
It looks like they still talk.
That's all.
There's nothing more.
They're not going out at all,
so don't even worry.
Sometimes in life,
you meet enemies
whom you just can't be separated from.
That's how life is.
Okay.
By the way, anyone would know
that you two are siblings.
The two of you resemble each other.
She's pretty,
- but she has such a foul mouth...
- We don't look anything alike.
How am I like my sister?
That's such a harsh thing to say.
She's such a scary person.
I'm telling you this just in case.
If you ever bump into my sister,
just run.
If the situation doesn't allow you
to run for whatever reason,
then grab her hair.
When you fight, you must intimidate
your opponent from the get-go.
You have to do as I say.
If not, you might actually die.
Gosh, that won't happen.
Right, it shouldn't.
Why?
What is it? Where are you?
What's going on now? Goodness.
Hi, In Ho.
I have nowhere to go.
- So?
- Could you carry my suitcase...
and take me to your place?
Let's go now.
I'm hungry.
Where are you going?
That heartless jerk.
He lives in such a shabby building.
Have some instant noodles.
Why does your place smell like this?
Which room do I use?
Is this the bathroom?
There are no cockroaches, right?
How am I going to live here?
You're being so ridiculous.
There are no bugs, right?
Why are you so calm?
This isn't like you.
In life, you need to know...
when to be vocal and when to lay low
in order to live off other people.
But it doesn't mean that I'm not angry!
You haven't changed one bit.
Oh? What are these?
Hey, don't touch them!
Did you start playing the piano again?
- Goodness!
- Hey!
Oh, no! It slipped off my hands.
- You must be out of your mind.
- I can't eat the noodles you made.
I'm sorry.
Can you make the noodles again for me?
I want jajangmyeon noodles.
Know your place, Baek In Ho.
You probably still think you're a genius.
Do you still dream
of becoming a world-famous pianist?
You're not going
to freeload here forever, right?
How did you end up like this?
I know, right? How did I become like this?
I miss the old days.
Hey, let's go skiing.
You wish.
Did you memorise all of this?
- No.
- Then memorise it now.
Let's go! Let's not do this boring stuff.
Jung!
What should we do?
I lost your fountain pen.
Gosh, well do you want
to hold onto the lid?
Hey, that was a bit harsh.
It's okay.
There's nothing we can do.
Jung, how is this okay?
Isn't this important to you?
You got it as a gift.
- You need to pay him for this.
- Jung is okay with it.
Who are you to cause trouble about it?
You're the one who's causing trouble,
you jerk.
Are you crazy?
Have you become that cocky
because of your rich friend here?
Why are you two so cocky, then?
Do you have gangster friends
who have your back?
Gosh. Who knew that gangsters
could attend our school?
That's enough.
Stop it.
He's saying that he lost it.
There's nothing we can do.
You heard that, right?
Know your place, you jerk.
I'm going now.
Why do you put up with that?
Are you going to be a pushover forever?
You know he's lying.
He's probably going to sell it online.
- Doesn't it make you angry?
- It's just better this way.
It'd be weird
to fight over a fountain pen.
What's weird about it?
It's not weird at all.
Those jerks are the weird ones.
- Really?
- Of course.
If something like this happens ever again,
just hit them.
I can explain it to Mr. Yu for you.
Got it?
- Are you telling me to fight?
- Yes, you fool.
I know that you can beat them
all up easily if you want to.
Look at your build.
You're wasting your talent, seriously.
Just hit them! Don't hesitate.
Goodness.
What was that?
You said I should hit people.
- Yes, but why are you...
- You told me to do it.
I see.
This is how I should do it.
Don't hit your friend!
Hit those jerks, you fool.
- Wow.
- Gosh, it's beautiful.
- Hey, open your mouth.
- Gosh, don't even try.
Did you skip
the tutoring session for this?
Jung! What took you so long?
What are you going to do
if my dad finds out?
Gosh.
You're so boring.
We're on vacation.
No one will scold us
for having a bit of fun after studying.
I'm jealous of you two.
You're allowed to do whatever you want.
Jung, you should live freely too.
Life is short.
It'll light up and vanish like fireworks.
Have some fun.
Look at her. She is so carefree.
- She's too carefree.
- Watch your tongue!
Hey.
What do you think
we'd be doing 10 years from now?
Well, I'd still be playing the piano.
You'll inherit your dad's company.
We'll skip our work
and have fun like this.
In Ha is the problem.
I see no future for her.
None at all.
Why are you asking this anyway?
We don't even know what tomorrow
will bring. A decade is a long time.
No matter what we end up doing,
I'm sure we'd still be friends.
Jung, I'm sure
you have a lot of stress too.
You should let it out.
Hey, let's light those up too.
Everything will be in a much better place.
Right, Jung?
I can't understand you.
I want to get closer to you,
but it's hard to take a step towards you.
Let's...
give each other some space.
In the beginning,
I thought you were just like me.
That's why I started liking you.
But we're very different.
You make my heart bounce,
my heart is fluttering
I'm scared that you might find out
Is she high or something?
You make my heart bounce, bounce
- Bounce, bounce.
- Hey, something is fishy.
Did something good
happen to you overnight?
Just get lost if you're going out anyway.
I'm in a good mood for a change,
so don't ruin it.
Don't do anything stupid.
You better not skip the classes.
That data entry and bookkeeping.
You need to get that certificate...
to be able to earn a living yourself.
Gosh, just shut it and go away!
Goodness.
Clean up after you finish eating!
You're a real piece of work.
Darn it. Did he figure out
that I made a deal with Jung?
He's like a ghost sometimes.
He's quick-witted.
That's a skill he picked up
from his tough childhood.
Let's look at my phone.
Jung.
Today, I'll carry out...
the first step of the plan.
Expensive clothes.
How much for this?
Surprise!
I told you
that I would repay your kindness.
I don't like owing people anything.
- Well...
- Why? Are you disappointed?
Shall we go and eat something delicious?
No, it's okay.
Why? You don't want
to buy me delicious food?
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Let's go!
Thank you.
You must know Yeong Gon
if you're in Business Administration.
You asked about Yu Jung last time.
It sounds like you know
many guys in my department.
I heard about him from a friend
and I'm interested.
Yeong Gon has a girlfriend.
He has a girlfriend?
Where can I find them?
Are you good friends with him?
- Where should I go to...
- I'm not really friends with him.
I see, you guys aren't close.
But I'm sure you have an idea.
- Do you know what restaurant he...
- Can we stop talking about him?
I'll give this back to you.
- Gosh, my stomach is upset now.
- Hey.
Hey.
Where are you going? Tell me where he is.
Are you not going to focus?
This will be on the exam tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll study.
I wonder who's this from?
It's been a long time.
Who is this?
Do you remember me?
I'm Yu Jung's girlfriend.
What is this now?
Hong Seol is his girlfriend.
Gosh, I'm his real girlfriend.
Have you forgotten
talking to me on Jung's phone?
My goodness.
Listen. Are you going to keep making me
be suspicious of you?
Don't make me doubt you.
Show me now.
Women shouldn't be nosy about what men do.
Shut it. Just give it to me.
What is it?
What does my Da Young want from me?
- Show me your phone.
- Why are you doing this?
You're still such a loser.
Well, this is just the first step,
so I'll leave it at this.
Yu Jung.
You'll be in for a surprise.
Why? Because I'm Baek In Ha.
Seol! Come and sit here.
Let's sit here.
Why do you want to sit at the front?
Gosh, just go in.
Hurry up.
Just go in.
You're so slow.
Why am I slow?
Gosh, I don't like sitting at the front.
Jung, what's going on with Seol?
You two had a fight, right?
No, we didn't.
Gosh, did you two break up already?
Who would want to date
a difficult person like her?
Jung is just too understanding.
Seol. Did something happen
between you and Jung?
- No.
- Shush.
- It looks like something happened.
- Be quiet.
- Do you know what happened?
- You're so slow.
I'm going to get coffee.
Do you want anything?
No.
I'm going to ace the exam.
I really need to focus.
How could he ignore me like that?
I already had too much coffee.
Min Soo. If you have something to say,
just say it.
Why are you so paranoid?
Stop lying!
When will you stop bothering me?
You're the one who started it.
Wait. Are you Hong Seol?
Are you Jung's girlfriend?
Did you approach her to make Jung mad?
- Do you like her?
- Hey!
- Your face is...
- Gosh, don't do that.
Your face is really red right now.
I won't rush you.
If you can try to understand me,
I can keep waiting for you.
I just want you to come back.
Yeong Gon was a total lunatic last year.
This year, he's gotten
even more aggressive.
- But what will you do with this?
- Baek In Ho?
I'm trying
to get rid of that loser for you.
Look forward to it.
- Did you guys make up?
- I think I can...
understand Jung a bit more now.
This crazy girl
is Yu Jung's real girlfriend!
So you're going to stay there
while I try to get closer to you?
Will that resolve everything?