(Cheese in the Trap)
You should've been more careful.
Do you want to go for food?
Let's go.
Come to your senses, Hong Seol.
You can't let that smile fool you.
- Mad Hair.
- Are you out of your mind?
(Seo Kang Joon, Lee Sung Kyung)
- That's such a great idea.
- I know, right?
(Park Min Ji, Nam Joo Hyeok)
(Cheese in the Trap)
To be honest,
I resent Sang Cheol, too.
That's why I pretended
not to know about it.
So how could I criticise you?
You did it because of me.
From some point in time,
I think that I started thinking
it's okay...
as long as you're not
doing it to me.
But...
you know that the heartaches
you cause...
will eventually
all come back to you.
I don't want you to
do those things to other people.
To me, you're such a good person.
You can be like that
to other people, too.
Right?
(Episode 15)
(Baek In Ha)
Your girlfriend seemed
pretty shocked yesterday.
I hope you know now.
You'll be in trouble
if I spill the beans.
(Guest List for Hanyu Group's
New Product Launch Party)
What's going on?
Why is he silent?
Everything at his school and work
must've turned into a fiasco by now.
He must've had a fight
with that girl, too.
Hong Seol, that girl. She's a lot
more persistent than she seems.
So this isn't enough for you, is it?
I need to come up with
a more solid plan...
Mr. Choi! Hello, it's In Ha.
I'm calling because I'd like to
arrange a meeting with Mr. Yu.
There's something
I have to tell him.
Is he on a business trip?
I see. When is he coming back?
Gosh.
Gosh, who's calling
this early in the morning?
Hello?
Yes.
Why are you calling so early?
You're here.
I'm so sorry about
what happened last time.
Oh, that? Don't worry about it.
I spoke to the president for you.
I told him that you had
a personal emergency.
Go in and tell him the same thing.
Right. I heard that you know
people in Taerang Group.
Why didn't you tell me?
I had no idea.
Anyway, give your best
when you start working here.
- Pardon me?
- Come with me.
- Where are we going?
- You should go see the president.
- Are you not going to work?
- The president?
Wow. Someone must be thrilled.
She doesn't have to worry about
money or getting a job.
Hey, Seol. Have a seat.
Sit down.
Is the rumour true?
Is Jung's father really
the president of Taerang Group?
Wow. I guess it's true.
You fooled all of us.
Gyeong Hwan.
You had no idea either, right?
Seol. That's the reason why
you started dating him, right?
Keep it down so that we can study.
We have an exam.
This is a lot more important
than the exam.
Hey, Seol. Tell us.
Everyone, be quiet.
Is the rumour really true?
You should've at least told us.
I feel betrayed.
I'm sorry.
It looks like people will
give you a hard time for it.
What are you going to do?
I'm more worried about
how you'll do on the exam.
I've been too easy on you, it seems.
You're being so cheeky.
Hey.
Do you really have
that much to talk about?
Are you not going to take the exam?
Isn't Seol like Cinderella?
Are we going to the same school
as the chairman's son?
I'm telling you. Seol knew about it
from the get-go.
Wasn't she single her whole life
before that?
Why else would she have been
so motivated to date him?
Had I known about it, I would've
dated Jung myself.
- Me, too!
- Same here!
Goodness.
You girls are too much.
By the way, I think Sang Cheol
didn't get into Taerang Group...
because of Jung.
- Why?
- Didn't you hear?
I heard that Sang Cheol caused
a scene at Taerang Group.
From what I heard, he was demanding
Jung to show up, saying that...
he didn't get the job
because of Jung.
So did he intentionally tell him to
apply just to reject him?
- Exactly.
- That's crazy. Goodness.
- Why? What happened?
- What's going on?
Sang Cheol basically harassed Seol.
Why would Jung want him
to work at his dad's company?
Even I was being asked
by everyone all day long.
People whom I've never even seen
came up to me...
and asked if Jung's father
really owns Taerang Group.
People are so nosy.
This is probably why Jung has
kept it a secret all these years.
People were all over him
even when they didn't know.
It would've been a lot worse
if they knew.
Totally. I'm glad that Jung isn't
on campus on a day like this.
Seol, don't worry too much.
We'll pretend that we don't know
anything in front of him.
Thanks.
What are these?
Are they matching rings?
I told you that she'd be surprised.
I figured I needed to let the world
know that Bo Ra is my girlfriend.
Don't ever pretend that
you're single, okay?
What? What kind of person
do you think I am?
I'm happy for you two.
Why didn't you start dating sooner?
What kind of person?
You're my girlfriend.
Jung.
Thank you.
You have a lot of meeting notes
to organise, right?
Shall I help you
if there's too much?
It's okay. It's my job.
Would you like to join us for lunch?
You always eat at the cafeteria.
There's a really nice
Italian restaurant nearby.
Come with us.
I heard the food's nice.
No, thanks.
Okay.
Jung.
Are you here for coffee?
Yes.
No. You made it for yourself.
I'll make another one.
Thank you.
Isn't the third round of interviews
in two days?
My cousin applied, too, you see.
He did really well in college,
and he's a great guy.
Could you put in a good word?
Thank you for the coffee.
He must feel more uncomfortable
than me.
Going to practice?
What?
Yes.
You're so strong.
That hurt.
You're stick thin but...
so strong.
You're weak, that's all.
Thanks.
For hitting me.
Oh, no. We're late.
We have to wait 20 minutes
if we miss the 45-minute train.
Run.
Wait up.
What? Hey.
I haven't seen you in so long.
You've become even more handsome.
How about a beer later?
Stop it, girls.
Don't spend his money.
Jung. Why are you here?
I'm here to hand in my final paper.
Really?
Excuse us.
- But...
- Bye.
A beer...
Did I do well?
- You looked bored.
- Well done.
Jung. Let's talk.
Wait here.
Don't worry. It's just a chat.
My senior at Sunju...
was pleased that he got
a Taerang contract.
Was that the price...
of getting me in?
Was it?
You mock me to the very end.
I know I acted like a fool.
But right now,
I can't bring myself to thank you.
Is that...
all you have to say?
You make it tough for yourself.
Do you think people don't know?
You may think you
keep everything well hidden,
but everyone here knows
what you think of them,
and why you treat them
the way you do.
They all know
you don't show how you feel...
and that what you do show is fake.
You aren't the only one who judged.
We all judged you as well.
So don't belittle or taunt everyone
who tries to befriend you.
Some of them actually liked you.
Some of them...
really just wanted to
be your friend.
Sure.
We'll never meet again.
Sorry...
for everything.
What did Sang Cheol say?
Well...
Nothing much.
Okay.
Right.
I heard he got into
Sunju Logistics after all.
Isn't that a relief?
It is.
- Seol.
- Yes?
Holidays start right after
the finals, right?
Shall we go on a trip?
A trip?
You'll be really busy
once you start your fourth year,
and so will I.
Okay.
The mountains or the sea...
I want to go anywhere
and eat good food...
and see pretty things.
But can you stay out overnight?
Right...
You probably can't, right?
But don't most people...
lie when they go on such trips?
Think about it.
No parent would let
their daughter...
go on an overnight trip with her boyfriend
just like that.
We don't have to go
if you don't want to.
I didn't say that.
What?
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Jung.
Give me your hand.
My hand?
Quickly.
Is it too small?
It fits.
What kind of guy
doesn't buy his girlfriend...
a ring when they've been dating...
for over six months?
I couldn't stand it,
so I bought a pair.
Ta-da.
Say something.
Don't you like it?
No. No...
Thank you.
What should I do?
Don't ever take it off.
And don't lose it either.
Okay.
Bye.
What are you doing?
Are you dressed for an interview?
I guess you could say
I'm trying to get a job.
Wow. I can't believe
you're up so early.
Good for you.
Have a nice day, In Ho.
Don't change so drastically.
It's a bad omen.
Bye.
Mr. Choi, it's me, In Ha.
Yes. I should go to
his office, right?
I rented it for exactly one hour.
Practise as much as you can.
Okay?
That was great.
Who are you?
I have this space for one hour.
No, no.
I'm just happy to see you here.
We met once a long time ago
at Professor Noh's house.
I also saw you in
Professor Shin's office once.
I was sad because I didn't
get to say hi to you.
Since I was a kid, I have always...
idolised you.
I need to practise.
You're attending
the piano competition, right?
I'm actually one of the judges
for the preliminary round.
Professor Noh asked me to do it.
Professor Noh asked you?
I'm so looking forward
to the competition.
By the way, your hand...
Right, I'm keeping you from
practising. I'm sorry.
You know that we installed
a titanium rod when we were doing...
the operation for your open fracture
five years ago, right?
Yes.
But why is this happening
all of a sudden?
There was nothing wrong
a few months ago.
That was the case then.
But now, I see an infection around
one of the screws.
It's causing inflammation.
By any chance, did you recently
hurt your hand?
It could've been a scratch or a cut.
- Yes.
- Don't worry too much.
Getting a re-operation
will take care of the problem.
- Another operation?
- Yes.
After the operation,
it will take about two months...
for the bones to heal.
You should get the operation done
before the infection worsens.
And you must avoid doing anything
strenuous with your fingers.
Okay.
Please don't tell
Professor Shin anything for now.
I don't want to worry him.
Sure, I won't.
(Lesson Room)
What an idiot.
Goodness.
I'm so tired.
I need to focus now.
Coffee.
I need coffee.
What's this?
This is mine.
It's warm.
Jung is acting very strange
these days, isn't he?
He's being excessively sensitive
and on the edge.
I think that girl is
really influencing him.
I actually know her.
I think she approached him knowing
that he will inherit Taerang Group.
I really didn't want to
get involved in these things,
but this is just not acceptable.
You already know about
what happened here, right?
That also happened because of
a favour she asked him.
I just thought you should know.
Jung!
The chairman is looking for you.
Is he back already?
I think he changed his schedule
around to come back earlier.
What are you doing?
Go to his office now.
Come in.
I heard that you wanted to see me.
I heard about everything that
happened here while I was gone.
I'm sorry.
Have a seat.
I checked with Mr. Moon too.
The applicant named Kim Sang Cheol.
We let him pass the first screening
because you asked.
To my face, you pretended that
you'd never do these things.
Have you been
telling people who you are...
and taking advantage of it?
All because of a girl?
I knew that you were dating someone,
but I had no idea that...
the girl would be this much
of a negative influence to you.
- I'm not sure what you mean.
- Take a good look at yourself.
I knew that something was up
when you started talking back to me.
And you even caused a scene
at work.
You're becoming a troublemaker.
I heard that you're being cold
towards In Ho and In Ha...
because of that girl.
I was just thinking that
they did something to upset you.
I thought that you'd be...
well aware of the situation
you're in at least.
Do you really think you have
time to waste like this?
With a girl who approached you
because of your background?
Please don't talk about her
that way.
It's In Ha, isn't it?
It looks like you need to know
who is the one that actually...
approached me because of
my background.
How dare you talk to me like that?
Seeing you now...
made me realise
whom I should believe.
It's done.
Break up with her.
As soon as you become
a full-time employee,
I'm sending you to
our branch in Europe.
- Father.
- The whole company knows.
Everyone's talking about
how you rigged the interviews.
I think it's best that
you leave Korea for a while.
This event...
will be your first and last
official event in Korea.
Right. I told In Ha to attend
as well.
So watch yourself.
Don't disappoint me any further.
Get out.
Look over here, please.
Thank you.
What happened?
I was nice to her.
But she kept bothering me
and broke my toy.
So that's why you pushed her?
Didn't I tell you that it's bad
to express your anger?
Honey, stop it.
You stay out of this.
Jung. People are looking at us.
What should you do?
Yes. You should smile.
Will you be nice to her from now on?
I'm sorry for pushing you.
I'll forgive you
if you play with me.
And hold my hand.
Okay. I'll do what you want.
Let's play over there.
Okay. Let's sit down.
What's your bear called?
Teddy.
It's my favourite bear.
What are you doing here?
Are you playing with a girl?
Give me that.
No.
Gosh. I have to get another cup.
Do you want some juice?
Yes.
It tastes strange.
It's okay. That's normal.
Drink the whole thing.
Did you say you wanted it?
I'll give you an arm.
Now that I think about it,
I don't want it any more.
Your son acts...
just like you did at his age.
Don't most children his age
act like that?
Before I met you,
I wasn't able to control my anger.
But Jung has never gotten angry.
That could be even more dangerous.
Sorry?
I noticed that he shows his anger
in his own way.
If that continues,
he may never be able to maintain
a normal relationship with anyone.
Then what should I do?
It would be nice
if he had siblings...
he could be around.
Oh, hello.
To what do I owe this call?
What did you do?
I let you off once.
I know.
Didn't that mean I could continue?
That's how I took it.
You...
crossed the line.
That was the last straw.
Jung.
There's something you don't know.
I lost my patience a long time ago.
I told you to watch out.
Bye. See you at the party.
Hello, Mr. Choi.
I'd like to add
a few more names to the list.
Yes, they're with me.
I'll email you the names,
so please add them.
Thank you.
Joon, where's my dictionary?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
What should I do?
You're smart.
You tell me.
Hit the books.
Do you...
really want to study...
Business Administration?
See? What will you do
after you graduate?
Figure that out first.
Do what you want to do.
You used to be talented and
good at a lot of things.
You used to have many dreams.
You aren't like me.
You can't let Dad control you.
Think about what
you really want to do.
Where are you?
Dad told me to ask
if you're looking at colleges.
Hey, Kumquat.
Hi, Joon.
- Hello.
- Why are you here?
Hey, did you make this?
No. I'm helping the seniors.
Is he your boyfriend?
No way.
Yes way.
We're dating.
It's about time.
What? We really aren't dating.
What are you studying?
Excuse us for a moment.
I'm studying her.
Don't be silly.
Why are you here?
They're all guys.
Hang out with the girls.
We're entering a competition
as a team.
A competition?
Yes. My professor liked
what I made last time,
so he got me into their team.
It's a huge honour
to be able to work with them.
Good for you.
You must be busy then.
Of course. You saw us.
I can't think about anything else.
What have you been up to?
I've been really busy.
Oh, have you been getting drunk?
No.
Why are you really here?
I'm here to see my sister.
What for?
Stop asking questions.
See you.
Hey, don't drink too much.
A movie?
What's taking her so long?
Hello.
It's mine.
Hey, aren't you getting in?
How could I ride that?
Get in. Everyone drives
these nowadays.
- Do you know where I'm going?
- Get in.
You midget...
- Come on.
- Hey!
Get in. This car is actually
quite popular.
Oh, goodness.
- Careful.
- Why...
Okay.
I thought he was rich.
I guess I was fooled.
- What?
- Nothing.
How do you know Jung so well?
We grew up together,
like a family.
Mr. Yu treats me like
I'm his own daughter.
- Why do you ask?
- No reason.
I'm worried about you.
If Jung complains about
what happened,
tell me and I'll teach him...
You're pretty cute.
- Let go.
- Don't worry.
We're going through a rough patch,
but it won't last long.
I'm sure he knows by now that...
he can't control me
the way he does others.
How do I look?
Do I look nice?
What? You look beautiful.
Where are you going?
I'm going to a party where a lot
of important people will be at.
I have to look the part.
I've been bored these days,
so this is awesome.
You haven't been to
a party like that, right?
No.
We're here. Pull over.
Pull over a bit far away.
I don't want to be embarrassed.
- Right here?
- Yes.
Thanks anyway. I'll tell you
all about it afterwards.
Well, but...
(Artist Choi Ji Soo,
Solo Exhibition)
Should I have asked her to
check out this exhibition with me?
This is my style.
Gosh, I can finally breathe.
Jung.
You made it.
Thanks.
Cheers.
This is the type of place
that suits you and me.
We need to be at a fancy
and upscale place like this.
This is delicious.
By the way, I'm surprised.
I didn't think you'd come today.
You hate occasions like this.
Oh, no.
Mr. Yu must've scolded you
because of what had happened.
Don't worry.
I can talk to him and
make him forgive you.
Let's just have fun today, okay?
Okay.
I think I can do that today.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Baek In Ha?
How did you get in?
Not anyone can get in here.
"Anyone"?
That's what I want to say.
Your father owns a small company.
How did you even get the invitation?
Hey, by the way,
who's your current target?
What does he do?
He's someone you can never
be compared to,
so just mind your business.
Wait, excuse me.
You...
Hey, do you know her, too?
I toyed with her for a short while.
I was nice to her because of her
pretty face. Then she got obnoxious.
Hey, Baek In Ha.
- How many guys did you mooch off?
- Hey, hey.
Stop it. Calm down.
Don't get angry over
a girl like her.
I can't believe I let that witch...
Gosh, I'm beyond embarrassed.
Hey. What did you just say?
Did you call me a gold digger?
Didn't you buy me gifts
and beg me to date you?
Where do you think you're going?
- Apologise immediately.
- Get lost.
He should be apologising to me.
- You little...
- Let go!
- Apologise!
- She's unbelievable.
- Let go! Let go of me.
- Hey.
- Let go!
- Gosh, seriously.
How dare you little...
I don't want the guests
to be disturbed.
- Drag them out of here, okay?
- Who do you think you are?
Do you think you can get away
with treating me like this?
Do you know who I am?
I'm the daughter of Mr. Yu,
the chairman of Taerang Group.
You guys are the ones
who should know your place!
- Okay?
- You can't raise your voice here.
Please come with us.
Mr. Yu...
- Please come with us.
- Mr. Yu.
- Come with us.
- Let go of me.
- Please come with us.
- Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu!
- Let go!
- You need to come with us.
Mr. Yu. Mr. Yu!
Come with us.
Jung.
- You need to leave.
- I was surprised to hear from you.
- Let go!
- Thanks for inviting me.
Right, you know Jun Soo, right?
Hey, Jung also invited me.
Is that right?
Have a seat.
We haven't talked in a while.
- Have you guys been doing well?
- Of course.
Right, I heard that you recently...
What's this now?
Baek In Ha!
What's this mess?
Jung, that jerk.
I'm going to kill him.
How dare he...
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Baek In Ha. In Ha!
What is wrong with you?
Hey, get up.
In Ha. Why are you acting like this?
Look at me. Look at me now.
What happened?
Why are you like this?
Tell me.
Tell me now!
Jung!
It's really late.
Why did you come all the way here?
I wanted to take you home.
Did you go somewhere today?
You look totally dashing.
I think I smell alcohol, too.
I had to attend an event for work.
I didn't drink that much though.
You didn't drive, did you?
I called a relief driver.
Let's go.
But I live really far.
That's even better.
I guess you're right.
What time do you finish
your exam tomorrow?
In the morning.
After this, I'll be done.
This semester feels
exceptionally long.
You did a good job this year, too.
You, too.
By the way, are we really
going away tomorrow?
Have you spoken to your parents?
Yes.
I said that I'll be staying over
at Bo Ra's.
What would we have done
without Bo Ra?
You're right.
So are you saying that Jung...
plotted behind your back again?
But Mr. Yu...
didn't even say a word to me.
I was literally being
dragged out of the party.
He acted as if he didn't know me
at all.
Tell me that didn't happen.
This is a dream, right?
That's just impossible.
Mr. Yu loves me. Aren't I right?
Do you still not know?
To them, we're just...
pets.
He used us so that his son with
issues could grow up normally.
No, no.
- I'm going to go to Mr. Yu.
- In Ha.
I'm going to tell him
that Jung planned all this.
- In Ha.
- If I tell him how...
wrongly accused I feel,
he will hug me and say sorry.
In Ha!
Come to your senses, please.
Okay?
Look at me.
I'm begging you.
What am I going to do
if you're falling apart like this?
Baek In Ha.
You should...
You should get some rest.
Go to your room and lie down.
Get up now.
He's not answering.
After making a fool of
my sister like that.
This jerk infuriates me so much.
Get out.
Get out of the car, you jerk.
Open this now.
Let's talk.
Get out of the car now.
Get out!
Tell me.
Why are you doing this to us?
Is it because I like Mad Hair?
Is that why you had to
make a fool of In Ha?
Okay, I'll quit.
I'll do as you wish and get lost.
So please...
leave us alone.
Can you two...
just leave me alone?
- What?
- Ever since you moved in...
You've done enough.
You needed to impress my father.
I get that.
I don't care if you...
made me look bad on purpose.
It's in the past.
What are you talking about?
I didn't want to go that far.
But if I didn't, In Ha...
would have never given up.
Tell her this.
If she ever talks nonsense
about Seol again,
I might go off the deep end.
What did you do?
Gosh.
No.
I won't give up this easily.
After all I did to keep it...
You must've been very upset
yesterday.
I'd dealt with those kids before
because they gave Jung a hard time.
They took it out on me.
You know...
how I used to take care of
the kids who bothered Jung.
In Ha. Let's end it here.
I'm telling the truth.
You have to believe me.
Those young men...
didn't seem to have
a problem with Jung.
You were the one
they had issues with.
I already knew what you were
up to,
but I wasn't expecting this.
Everyone there knew each other.
Did you not think
that would become an issue?
Did Jung say that?
I didn't have that kind of
relationship with them.
Don't believe what he says.
You know that he's a bit weird.
Weird?
Is that what you thought of him?
Is that what you tell everyone?
Mr. Yu...
I shouldn't have welcomed you.
What do you mean?
You said you wanted us to be family.
- You let me call you "Father".
- That was when...
I thought you could help Jung.
Now, you're just hurting him!
Do you expect me to abandon him...
to coddle you two?
Mr. Yu...
I don't hate you.
You are Doctor Baek's grandchildren,
and we've known each other...
for many years.
Let's...
cut our ties.
What do you mean by that?
Let's cut contact.
Mr. Yu.
No. I don't want to.
From now on,
please don't...
call or visit me.
That goes for...
Jung as well.
I'll kill you, Jung.
The exams are over!
You're leaving for your trip today.
Do you have what any girl needs...
when going on a trip
with her boyfriend?
- What?
- Do you?
What do you mean?
- Let's see. I'll have a look.
- Hey, what are you doing?
What should I have?
A book, laptop and dictionary.
What?
Those are a must.
When you think
things are getting a bit weird,
open up your textbook.
You look scary when you study.
You little! You're so mean.
I'm going.
Have fun.
Buy me something.
Stay safe.
Bo Ra. Do you want to
check out my laptop?
I have books, too.
Jung! Come out.
Yu Jung!
Come out. Yu Jung!
Open up.
I know you're in there!
Come out. Jung.
Come on.
I know you're in there!
Mr. Choi, could you come over
to my place?
Jung! Come out right now.
In Ha. How low will you go...
You jerk.
How low will I go?
How low can I go?
I've hit rock bottom!
- So what?
- So I'm blinded with rage!
Let go! Let go of me!
Jung.
You know why I'm doing this.
You should know.
You know how I feel...
That ship has sailed.
Not for me.
You're doing this...
because of...
that witch, Seol.
Do you think she'll be
any different?
She doesn't know you well yet.
I'm the only one who knows
the truth about you...
- and still understands you!
- So?
Must I love you then?
- What?
- In Ha.
Let's never meet again.
That's best for the both of us.
No. I can't do that.
After all those years I spent
being your puppet,
what did you say?
Did you leave me for
someone like her?
I accepted the twisted you,
and I cleaned up your mess!
You can't abandon me.
I won't let you do that to me!
You scumbag.
You of all people
can't do this to me!
- How dare you?
- Stop it.
- I can fight back, too, you know.
- Get out of here.
- Get her out!
- How could you?
- You of all people can't do this.
- Let's get her out of here.
How could you?
Let go!
Jung. Let go of me!
Let me go!
Go home.
- Let me in.
- Just stop it already!
Let me in!
Hey! Open the door!
Let me back in!
No!
How am I going to live?
Open this!
Open the door!
I spoke to her,
so I'm sure she'll understand.
I'll clean this place up
as soon as possible.
It's okay.
You can leave it for today.
- Just call someone tomorrow.
- Okay.
Well, then. You should rest.
Don't be surprised.
I'm on my way to your place now.
That's right.
I can't be the only one
who loses everything.
Yu Jung.
It's only fair that you lose
everything, too.
Don't you think so?
Die.
It's all your fault!
If you didn't exist...
I wouldn't have had to end up
like this!
None of this mess would've happened
if you didn't exist!
It's all because of you!
Let go!
A person got hit by a car!
Gosh, is she going to be okay?
Goodness, someone
call the ambulance, please!
Don't be surprised.
I'm on my way to your place now.
Seol. Seol!
If something happens to Seol,
I won't forgive you.
I'll kill you.
You should've just left
when I first asked you to.
How can you even ask to see Seol?
- I'll take responsibility for this.
- How will you do that?
Why did I hold Jung's hand
at that moment?
Why did I not know sooner?
After this happened to you,
I finally...
It's your fault for dating
someone like her to begin with.
She wouldn't have had to go
through this if she didn't date you.
Bring In Ha back now.
Where is In Ha?
Where is she now?
He asked me for help
because of Jung.
How dare he lock me up here?
Have you been
telling Mr. Yu everything?
Am I the only one who did that?
You did the same, too.
I wish I had given it to you sooner.
How long will you be able to be
patient with me?
You can't carry
all the burden, Seol.