Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote
any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Inspector.
Mr. Anuwat seems to have already fled.
Here.
Today, the police -
received a tip from a concerned citizen,
about finding the body of a middle-aged woman.
Aged approximately 40 to 50 years old.
Believed to have been hit by a car that then fled.
CCTV footage is currently being reviewed.
Shit.
Where the hell did you come from?
I came from the ER.
Just finished my shift.
This shift was a total shitshow.
Do you think they'll catch the driver?
It'll depend on the driver.
How rich they are.
You answered with great social insight, Tyme.
Hey, Tyme.
I have something exciting to tell you.
What?
I've never told anyone outside the department before.
But I'm telling you first.
I kept information -
on patient experiences that had a cardiac arrest before.
Wicked right?
That's interesting.
Of course it is.
I'll use a larger sample size than in past research.
I guarantee.
My research will be published internationally.
(Nutcha)
Better leave you with your girlfriend.
Later man.
Hello?
What's going on?
You've been busy lately.
Yeah, very busy.
You've changed a lot in the past two years.
What, Nut?
I've always been like this.
I've always supported you.
Help take care of your grandmother's diabetes.
Did everything you wanted me to do.
Why don’t you care about my feelings?
Okay.
I understand.
Then we have nothing else to discuss.
I ordered them to delete all the CCTV footage.
Great.
And?
You hit and killed someone with your car.
Still not realizing how serious this is?
If I weren't close with the police,
you would've been in jail by now.
You just don’t want it in the news.
For your company’s reputation, right?
Great.
Great, thank your dad.
For taking care of everything.
Thank you.
You ungrateful son.
I almost had to grovel to the police.
And this is how you act?!
Wait, wait.
Hello?
Tle.
What the hell is this clip?
How did Dome record you and View?
Yea let's put that aside for now.
I'm almost at your condo.
Why are you coming?
Oh, you'll find out soon.
I have something fun for you to help with.
Hey!
Hey.
Who told you to get out?
Hey, Tle.
Hey, Tle don't!
So, what’s the deal, Great?
Are you gonna help me or not?
Great.
Hey, Great.
Why didn't you,
why didn’t you call your dad’s men for this?
No way.
I don't want him to know.
He's so annoying.
Come help me carry him.
C'mon.
Okay.
Carry his legs.
Shit.
Do you think the police will catch us?
Catch who?
Dome was stressed.
Jumped in the water and killed himself.
Don't worry, my dear friend.
If the police were to arrest someone,
they wouldn't come after us.
Let's go.
Let's go drink.
Drinks on me tonight.
C'mon.
Where shall we drink?
Hey.
You're still stressed?
Of course.
Someone died, you know?
Hey, Tle don't!
Hm.
Today I have 3 cases.
I'm at the hospital. I’ll go in right away.
Okay.
Doctor?
A document for you to sign.
Oh.
What is your name?
Pacharawit Sriwatsombat.
Any drug allergies?
No.
The doctor prescribed sleeping medication
and a stress reliever.
And also paracetamol for pain relief.
You can take every 4 to 6 hours as needed.
You're all set.
Careful bumping into anyone else with all that drinking.
I'm the doctor you bumped into at the hospital.
You followed me?
Nope.
I was coming here anyway.
Can I sit next to you?
I'm Tyme.
Great.
Do you come here often?
Pretty often.
This is my first time.
What's good here?
Liquor.
I think there's something else more interesting.
What?
You're so drunk, can you do it?
Wanna give it a go?
Let me use the bathroom real quick.
Sir, sir, have you seen this?
Sup dad?
I never thought you’d be like this.
Who's the guy in the clip?!
The guy in the clip?
Who was it?
I don't remember.
Get out of my face right now.
Go!
I have to go now?
Go stay with Aunt Ging for now, Grandma.
And also,
if it's not urgent, don't go out. Understand?
You have something, but aren't telling me, right?
No, Grandma.
It's just -
I've had busy shifts, and hardly been home.
You’re old now and need someone with you.
I was gone for just a bit,
and you forgot your meds again.
Stay with Aunt Ging so she can care for you.
And I can work with peace of mind.
It's not just that.
There's nothing Grandma. C'mon, let's go.
Tyme.
Grandma.
Consider doing it for your grandson.
You know right, Tyme?
That I love you very much.
I know, Grandma.
I love you very much too.
Come, get in the car.
It's getting late.
Let's go.
Let me know when you get there.
Okay.
Bye bye.
You found me pretty fast.
Quite bold of you to do that.
What do you want?
Pakorn and Amornrat.
Sound familiar?
When I met you then,
you were just a little child,
Tyme.
Good.
No need for reintroductions.
Take this money and use it as you like.
Take Grandma out of that rat hole.
And buy a nice condo.
Or take her to a good private hospital for diabetes.
If you mess with my grandma, I'll expose everything.
I won't.
If you take the money.
And back off from my family.
I won't back off.
Until you admit you killed my parents.
And quit your vile business.
You don't know.
What else I can do.
I didn't kill your parents.
And another thing.
If you're thinking about exposing my vile business.
In the end, it’ll lead back to the source.
That the truth is,
the owner who started this gambling business,
was your parents.
You're lying!
If you don't stop.
You will face the truth that...
is better left unknown.
Your Grandma will be so heartbroken,
if she knew the house she's lived in,
came from that vile money as well.
Another warning.
The other partners aren't as nice as me.
If I were you,
I'd do nothing.
Great.
What are you doing here?
Picking up my meds.
Why haven't you answered my texts?
Step aside.
Let's have dinner tonight.
No way.
We can go to your favorite spot.
It's nothing.
Can you eat this?
If you can't, then leave.
Of course I can.
Why can't I?
Order 2.
Excuse me,
2 orders of chicken noodle soup with extra chili
and lots of crispy garlic, please.
Um, excuse me.
I can't eat spicy.
And I don't like garlic.
And can I get it without pork blood?
- Come, come, come, sit.
- And no innards.
You gonna eat it or not?
Hey, hey.
You really don't know?
Don't know what?
About the clip.
I was about to ask.
Why haven't you posted it on OnlyFans?
So you could make money.
Hey, aren't you embarrassed?
The one who's embarrassed is Dad, not me.
Did you do it to get famous?
Oh, but I forgot.
The clip doesn't show your face.
So why did you do it?
Because your family's business is shit.
Huh?
Go tell you dad, take the money back.
I don't want to use dirty money.
Are you fighting with my dad?
Wow, wicked.
Did you come up with the plan all by yourself?
Wow, impressive.
I can't believe it.
Why are you walking?
Why won't you let me drive you?
Why, when the train's so close.
You can go home, Great.
You're still afraid of dogs?
I'm not afraid of dogs.
Who said I was afraid of dogs?
Hmhmm.
Ah.
And you say you're not afraid.
And the reason I know,
is because I did my research.
Wow.
No need to be a doctor if you're this nosy.
Go be a detective.
Stop talking.
Let's go.
There shouldn’t be any dogs around here.
I'm gonna go.
Where are you going?
Home.
Wanna hook up?
Didn't you jerk off before leaving the house?
Weren't you dying for me that day?
Great.
I'm being serious.
We shouldn't see each other again.
Let's part ways here.
Hello.
Where are you Korn?
Can we meet at the same place?
C'mon.
Okay, see you soon.
I'm being captured. Help me.
Help me!
Ow!
Finish up here.
Yes sir.
Go.
Agh!
Where is Nan?
Who the hell are you?
I said where is Nan?
Where is Nan!
I asked...
Answer!
Hey!
Great!
Don't let him escape!
Where is Nan?
Who is Nan?
The person your brother captured, where is she?
What are you talking about?
If you want to tell the police, then do it.
If you don't tell me where Nan is,
then get out of my face!
Tyme,
I'm going in.
You've got some guts.
To mess with me.
You guys killed my friend.
You gonna tell me or not?
No.
Who did you send the info to?
Tell me!
- No!
- You wanna get hurt?!
I won't speak.
Tell me.
Who did you send the info to?!
Kill me then.
Kill me now!
You fucking scumbags!
I'm giving you one last chance.
You're daring me?
Better off dead!
Hey.
Get up.
It was you, right?
Who Nan sent the info to?
Where did you save it?
Who did you send it to?
Scum.
Utterly useless.
Just go die with Nan, then.
Hey! Hey, stop!
Want to get your wound treated?
No.
Excuse me for telling a doctor what to do,
but you should get your wound treated.
How can you wait till morning looking like this?
Huh?
Hey, where are you going?
Oh.
I forgot.
Thank you so much for helping me.
But not for helping Nan.
How could I have helped her?
They had guns.
You sure you couldn't?
When you came and stopped them.
Everyone stopped and listened to you.
And if I got shot, what then?
So you just let someone die -
because of your cowardice?
People like you...
all deserve to fucking rot in hell, you bastard!
Hey, wait.
Don't follow me!
Then go die like the other one, you fucker!
What did you say?
What did you say?!
Motherfucker!
Just moments ago,
we received information from someone collecting evidence -
to expose a well-known logistics company.
Involved in illegal gambling and online betting operations.
Additionally, there are shareholders who are politicians.
And many high-ranking police officers as well.
Mr. Korn.
How long can General Warit delay things for us?
Not long.
You must get everything done by tonight.
Do you know who exposed us?
Probably the person Nan sent the info to.
I saw him last night.
But Mr. Great, your brother,
helped him escape.
Great?
Why would he do that?
You should go ask your brother.
Still not done? Hurry up!
Get everything off the wall.
What are we going to do now?
It'll be okay.
A team is already on standby.
I'll have them hurry up and go there.
Anything you want to tell me?
Nothing to tell me?
I can't believe it.
That you would do something like this.
It's because of something like this.
So we could have a company.
A home.
And money.
For you to waste like it's nothing!
We have to do this Great.
We've almost gone bankrupt before.
- So you saved the company by killing people?!
- Great.
Then you both take responsibility for it then.
I'm leaving.
Great.
Wait, Great.
Great! Stop, stop.
Great.
I beg you.
Go back and apologize to dad right now.
You just order me around.
You never ask me if I want to.
I'm not ordering.
I'm just telling you what you should do.
I'm just telling you what's best for you.
Best for whom?
For you?
For dad?
For the company?
For the family's reputation?
And how about me?
In the end, it's always what's best for you.
Why can't you see it this way?
Just getting angry.
And frustrated.
And distancing yourself from me.
It took me a long time to get to this point.
I had to fight.
If I didn't,
You and me,
we would have to live in hiding.
In a tiny house by your dad.
You'll end up being the mistress's child.
I've done all of this.
Why can't you understand me? This is all for you.
I beg you.
Great, believe me.
Go up and apologize to dad.
Let's go.
Great, Great.
Great.
Great!
No, Great!
Great, open the door right now.
Great
Great!
Don't do this.
Don't, Great!
Great.