[The Divine Healer]
Episode 19
[Bloody marriage]
Lord Jiuming
Langdu
You ambushed me last time
I must avenge
this grudge
Shopkeeper, be careful
I may not have much ability
But before I die
I can say I've done something for you
No
Something's happened to little Isatis
Prince Ye has decreed
Whoever captures a precious herb
Will be handsomely rewarded
Run, quick
You killed my clansmen
I'm gonna kill you
Astragalus
Little Isatis
You must not let them capture you
After hiding for so long
In the end, we still can't avoid it
That's a Millennium Ginseng
Whoever captures it
Will be rewarded with a hundred taels of gold
Elder
Little Isatis
Ganoderma
You guys, quickly
Run
Quick
Elder
Ah Jiu
Greetings to Lord Jiuming
Jiuming
Do you know who I am?
To dare get on my bed
Lord Jiuing
You're incredibly bold
I'm sending you to the Supreme Clarity Division now
You, a herbalist
How come you're so skilled in martial arts?
If a spirit threatens human lives
Of course, it must be
captured Jiuming