You like Nita?
You can barely bring yourself to walk past her,
and yet you want to chase after her?
You! What's your beef with me?
You don’t want me anywhere near Nita.
I’m not keeping Nita away from you.
We're not getting back together.
If you think you don't stand a chance with Nita, just give up.
You asshole!
Why are you here?
I came to apologize for yesterday.
I know you don't like me very much.
Who said I don’t like you?
Fine, I’ve forgiven you.
I will teach you how to pursue someone.
But I won’t do this for free.
You will charge me?
No.
But I want to join the debate club.
Why?
What are we doing here?
Eating.
Yeah, I figured that.
I’ll be back to take your orders in a moment.
A Vietnamese restaurant.
What else could it be?
What do you want to have? Let's order.
I'm not familiar with this type of food.
Just get it in your mouth,
chew,
and swallow.
Joke, this is not funny.
And we haven't finished our conversation yet.
What’s more to say?
Think about it.
If I'm part of the debate club, I could be the bridge that connects you and Nita.
Plus,
my tongue's always getting me into trouble.
Maybe joining the club will let something good come out of my mouth.
I haven't even brought up the subject of your joining the club.
Oh?
There goes my chance to help you.
But that's okay, even if it stings a bit.
We can stay as just classmates.
I guess I could talk to Wave about it.
But if you manage to join the debate club, you have to help me.
Joke!
If you can eat the dish I’m about to order…
I've told you, I don't know how to eat this stuff.
No deal, then.
Hello.
Hi there.
Are there any openings on 10 May?
I'm planning to bring my family.
We only have three spots left. Should I reserve them?
Yes, please do.
Hey, kid. Are you going to order anything or not?
If not, step aside. The guy behind you wants to order.
Yes, I’d like to order please.
May I have basil chicken with a fried egg over rice, without the basil?
How is the reservation coming along?
Thank you very much.
Basil chicken with a fried egg over rice, without the basil.
You always order the same thing.
Yes, I do.
Dig in.
Come on.
I can eat anything here, right?
Can't I just have this drink and be done with it?
Give it a try.
It's delicious, trust me.
Joke, I can’t.
Dip it in the sauce. It can help with the smell.
Give it a go. It's really good.
Don't you trust me?
I promise you, it's delicious.
For Nita!
You're overreacting. It's really tasty.
Can you make fresh spring rolls?
Fresh spring rolls?
Yes, ma'am.
This is a small food stall.
We can't make every dish a customer asks for.
Oh...
there was no need to be mean about it.
How much is the basil dish?
40 baht.
Here you go.
Wait a moment.
Zo!
Are you going to actually eat that or just play with it?
Hey,
I asked Joke to help me win over Nita.
What did he say?
He agreed to help, but only if he could join the debate club.
Doesn't that seem strange to you?
Yes, it does.
Right?
But don't overthink it. He might just want to help.
You think so?
Did you mention this to Wave yet?
You shouldn't have any issues. You're his golden boy.
He's my peer mentor. Of course, he's nice to me.
Piece of cake, then!
You betcha!
Let's eat. I'm starving.
No!
Wave, Joke wants to join the club to improve himself.
Improve himself or…
It’s a no.
Wave, why can’t he join?
The recruitment period was over.
How’s your assignment coming along, Zo?
Hmm?
The VTR that we discussed in our last meeting.
I've started working on that.
Did you send the information to Som-O?
We need that to post on the club’s page.
Oh, right. I’ve emailed it.
Let’s look at it right now.
Alright, everyone, let's start the meeting.
This is the rough draft of our VTR.
[VTR to promote the debate club]
I will be the MC
and Wave and Nita will introduce the club.
I think Pok should be the MC.
Zo, you should be on camera with me and Nita.
You can introduce other parts of the club.
I have a question.
I overheard Wave and Zo talking about Joke wanting to join our club.
Sorry for the eavesdropping.
But I joined after the recruitment period was over too.
Shouldn't that same rule apply to everyone?
Also, we need more members.
What do you all think?
Wait a minute, Joke? Joke from Public Administration?
I think he should join.
Actually, we should open another recruitment round.
Joke is good-looking. He could be good for the VTR as well.
But does he have any debate experience?
I rarely see him talk to anyone.
Will we have time to finish the VTR?
Joining this club requires skills.
Everyone must take a test as per the rules, no exceptions.
So, if Joke passes the test, he can join the club.
Pok!
Here are the lecture notes.
Thanks so much, Zo.
I completely forgot I'd asked you for them.
Good thing I ran into you in time.
Are you in a rush to go somewhere?
I have an appointment, so I need to hurry.
Who are you meeting?
Never mind.
Feel free to ask me for notes on any subject.
Thank you so much.
Hey, when did you and Joke become friends?
More like acquaintances.
Just recently?
He's asking a lot of questions.
We've known each other for a while but just started talking.
Joke wants to join the debate club, so I was asking around.
My peer mentor is the best!
No doubt about that.
Every time I give you a compliment...
Weren't you in a hurry?
Right.
Go ahead.
See you later.
Hey, one more thing.
I didn't mention to Wave yet that I have a friend who can shoot videos.
He can shoot, huh?
Could he help us out?
I can ask him.
Great, thanks.
I've got to go. See you later.
See ya.
Bye.
Take care.
Hey, Joke.
Meet me at the debate club,
now.
What am I doing here?
Didn't you want to join the club?
You’re not allowed inside yet.
Come on in.
Now that we’re here when no one’s around,
what's next?
I will make sure you can get in.
What does that mean?
And what am I supposed to do?
You will debate in front of Wave, my club president.
You will get in if you have the votes of the members.
Why is it so complicated?
It just is.
Do you want in or not?
Coming here doesn’t makes me more eloquent.
You said I needed to debate, right?
Yeah.
How do I rebut?
Is it like when you return a ping pong ball?
Smart ass, you can play ping pong over there.
But first, I need to coach you.
Go, grab a seat.
Good morning, everyone, judges, and members of the opposing team.
My name is Jeeranai.
Hey,
wake up!
Good morning, everyone, judges, and members of the opposing team.
Well….
When you speak, look forward.
Sweep your gaze across the room.
Don't just look at me.
Start again, but this time, be more relaxed.
I've had enough.
What's wrong?
I've repeated this line so many times.
But you haven't perfected it yet.
You're still not getting it right.
Open your mouth more when you talk. It can help.
If you don't try to get it right, you won't pass the test.
I’ll practice more when I get home.
Are you trying too hard to coach me?
I'm not preparing for a debate championship.
We made a deal,
so I need to focus.
By the way,
how did you end up in this club?
Do you enjoy debating?
You could say that.
But there's something I want to show you.
Follow me.
Don't touch.
You can only look.
Isn't it beautiful?
One day, this award will be mine.
[NOVA Champion]
And the winner of NOVA,
the national debate competition among the political science faculties, is….
Zo!
Congratulations on your achievement, Zo.
Thank you, Joke.
Instead of a thank you, how about…
Hey! Where did you drift off to?
Anyway, that's my dream.
Why this one?
You're such a buzzkill.
Never mind. Let's practice some more.
Keep practicing.
No.
An army marches on its stomach.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
An army can also march on its feet.
We need to practice.
No, let’s get something to eat.
I'm starving.
Come on! My treat.
All right.
Every time I see you, you're always drinking chrysanthemum tea.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
But I'm okay with anything as long as it's not sour.
Kind of like how you always drink roselle juice as if it's your lifeline.
I also like this.
Stir-fried macaroni with squid and salted egg yolk.
Want to try some?
No,
you eat yours.
I have mine.
If you're not going to try,
I'll feed you.
What are you doing, man?
Just try it. Come on.
It's yours.
Have a bite.
Or I'm going to feed you.
It did look tempting at first.
But you forcing it on me makes it less appealing.
How is it? Good, right?
It's okay.
It's delicious, huh?
It's fine.
Let's get back to practice after this.
Hey,
I'm human.
I get tired.
You can't expect me to talk all day.
It's just talking. I'm not asking you to do hard labor.
You should learn to find balance.
Nobody becomes good in a day.
I understand that.
Sorry if I pushed you too hard.
No need to apologize, as long as you understand.
I understand.
But let's practice more tomorrow.
Thanks for the ride.
See you tomorrow evening.
I’ll be singing at Trin’s place tomorrow night.
Can we reschedule?
I'll meet you there.
Why would you come there?
It's not the right place for practice.
I'm hired to sing.
You’ll see.
Catch you later.
Bye.
Hello
Hello, hello, hello.
My name is Jeeranai. Hello.
I’m Jeeranai or you can call me Joke.
Today, we will discuss one, two, three, four, five.
Hello, hello.
What are you doing?
None of your business.
Oh, I know.
I heard somebody wanted to join the debate club.
Were you practicing?
How did you find out about that?
I have my ways.
Do you want a way for my foot to land on your face?
I'd rather not.
What are you doing here?
I came to give you the key card.
Auntie Mouth left it with me.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Where are you headed?
Nowhere. I’m going straight home after this.
I’m off.
Joke, go, go! Joke, go for it!
Joke, go, for it! Joke, go, go!
And yet, you’re still here. Go!
You, go, go!
It’s running low.
Let me know if we run out of anything, okay?
Hello.
Hey, what’s up, Joke, my lovely mentee?
Why are you here so early?
I've got an appointment.
An appointment...
with that dude?
How did you know?
How could I not?
He came, sat down, and said he was waiting for you.
Look at his drink.
It's a soda.
This is a bar, for Christ's sake.
Is he Wave’s mentee?
I didn’t know you guys were close.
But be careful of those guys.
Go get ready.
I’ve got things I need to handle.
Sure.
How much is left?
Have a bite first.
Tell me.
Why did you come and meet me here?
Let's practice.
No. I've told you, I'm here to sing.
I'm not asking you to practice now.
When you're on stage, do you say something as a segue to a song?
Yes.
I say it all the time.
Really?
Say it as you would, and I’ll give it a listen.
Also, do you remember the gazing technique I taught you?
Use that when you’re speaking.
How can I compartmentalize?
You can do it.
Just go with your gut.
But I need you to be more serious.
Most importantly, extend your speech.
You can talk about the song you're about to sing,
why you picked it.
I don't think I can.
I only know how to entertain.
You can do it. Try to speak from the heart.
Trust me,
you can do it.
This is your home turf.
You have nothing to fear.
Trust me, you can do it, Joke.
Go for it.
All right.
Rooting for you.
Hi, everyone. I’m Joke.
Normally, I don't say much.
But somebody asked me to speak more today.
So I'm going to say something long here.
I don’t think anyone realizes how fast my heart is racing now.
I feel like I have a crush on someone,
and I'm about to confess.
Talking isn't something I'm comfortable with.
Singing, however, is a different story.
This song I'm about to sing really captures what I'm feeling right now.
♪ I know it’d all end up the same no matter what ♪
♪ I know you’d choose them no matter what ♪
♪ I know you’d forget about us no matter how much I beg ♪
♪ Because they are better ♪
♪ But I’ve already fallen in love with you ♪
♪ I know, I know you have to go ♪
♪ But I want to beg you one more time ♪
♪ Please love me, love me, I won't make you sad ♪
♪ I know I can't compete with someone you have ♪
♪ But choose me, choose me, I'll take good care of you ♪
♪ Please ask your heart again, because my heart still only has you ♪
(Great job!)
Your speech on stage was good.
Did you just compliment me?
No.
I'm just saying it was good enough.
How are you getting back home?
Do you need a ride?
No, thanks. I saw you had a few drinks.
It was not even half a glass.
I knew I had to drive.
That's what drunk people say.
I'll give you a ride.
I swear I only had a sip.
I can drive, Zo.
No, you can’t. It’s too dangerous.
I’ll drive you home.
Why?
Are you worried about me?
Yes, I am.
If anything happens to you, who’s going to help me with Nita?
I see.
Joke, what’s wrong? Are you sulking?
Who’s sulking?
Wait for me!
What on earth are you doing?
I've changed my mind. Come here.
Come.
Here.
Okay,
let’s go.
Don’t forget this.
Where is it?
Here, let me.
I feel like I’m helping a child.
Okay, let’s go.
Hold on,
were you messing with me on stage earlier?
No,
I wasn’t.
Why were you talking about having a crush?
You said you were done teasing me about Nita.
I just…
I’m feeling the same way.
Feeling the same way?
Are you in love?
Who is your crush?
Tell me who.
Who is it?
I’m not telling you.
Who?
Come on, man.
I promise I won’t tell a soul.
Who is it?
I’m not telling you.
I told you who my crush was.
You told me voluntarily.
I didn't ask you.
Let’s go.
Never mind.
The debate is tomorrow.
Don't be late.
We don't tolerate tardiness. Okay?
Can we go home now? You're talking too much.
I'm tired. Let's go.
Be nicer, or you won't get a ride.
But that's my motorcycle.
That hurts.
Do you know how to ride?
Of course.
Hold on a sec.
Twist it.
I am.
I mean, twist the key.
Oh, I need to twist that.
Let’s go.
Zo!
What’s that?
Huh?
I couldn’t hear you.
I’m just really happy you’re here with me.
What? Say it again.
Nothing, just be careful.
Ready? Three, two, one, action!
Hello, We're here representing the debate club.
Today, we’re excited to give you an intro to what we do.
Let's dive right into it.
What does the debate club do?
Our bread and butter is hosting debate events on campus.
But that’s not all we do.
We also have regular meetups to sharpen each other's debating skills.
We also participate in off-campus activities.
Three years ago, we won a national inter-university competition.
And the award was…
Was…
A scholarship to study in Finland.
Woah, that's super exciting!
So, are there any off-campus events on the horizon this year?
Absolutely.
Our club is all set to bring home the championship for our university this year.
So, don't forget to cheer us on!
Hey, why is this class still going on?
This teacher always pushes it past the bell.
We're already 10 minutes over time.
I’ve just realized our time is up.
Please make sure to finish the assigned reading before our next class.
Class is dismissed!
Where are you dashing off to?
Gotta run!
Hey!
Okay, that's a wrap.
Wave and Zo, you two were very smooth.
You did a great job as well. Let’s pack up.
Where’s Joke? He’s not here yet?
If he’s not here, I’ll leave.
Wave, let me try calling him first.
I’m heading out.
Did I make it in time?
Just in time.
Ready when you are.
Why would you want to join this club?
I don't get it at all.
I'll explain later.
I’m ready.
Who would you like me to debate with?
It’ll be…
Zo on the topic of a relationship with a hidden agenda.
Is it right, or is it wrong?
Why?
What's the problem?
We can skip this test altogether.
Wave, I think…
Never mind.
Zo, you go first
as an existing member of our club.
Personally, I think it's wrong.
To start any relationship,
there should be no room for secrets or hidden motives.
If there are, that person could very well harbor ill will.
I disagree.
When you’re starting a relationship with someone,
I don’t think we need to declare everything out in the open with the other person.
Why?
Don't you think they would be more hurt if they found out later?
That depends on the situation.
Some things can come out sooner or later, and it doesn’t really matter.
The timing should be when the person is ready to share it.
But intentionally hiding something...
It can happen.
But we need to consider the reason behind it.
For instance,
let's say I want to get close to a friend.
I happen to hate eating vegetables.
Do I need to announce that right from the start?
There's no harm in telling your friend.
In fact, sharing such things is part of forming a bond.
Knowing your quirks like your dislike for veggies can even strengthen your friendship.
It’s not wrong.
But I don’t think it’s necessary.
Say I have a flatulence issue because I often have indigestion.
Should I disclose this to everyone?
But that hardly counts as a hidden agenda.
What is it, then?
To me, a hidden agenda is a secret.
Something you can’t tell anyone.
Why wouldn’t flatulence or vegetable-hating count?
Well…
Okay, let's leave it at that.
Now, I'd like everyone to cast a vote on the winner of this debate, Joke or Zo.
All in favor of Joke, show of hands, please?
And Zo?
It’s a tie.
So, am I in?
Anyone with more than half the votes gets into the club.
That’s all for today, guys.
You were great!
I just followed your advice and spoke from the heart.
You did a great job, buddy.
Buddy?
Absolutely, you're the buddy I coached who made it into the club.
Just don't forget the little favor I asked you for.
What favor?
Joke, don’t mess with me.
You very nearly fell flat on your face.
Are you all right?
Yes.
That was a dramatic fall.
You really need to watch where you're going.
What are you doing?
Come here. Let me help.
Just fixing your shoelace.
Thank you.
As clumsy as ever, I see.
So, you'll help me, right?
Help with Nita?
What else?
Don't tell me you've already forgotten your promise to help me win over Nita.
Well…
I’ve actually already started.
When?
Rule no. 1, know your personality.
If you want to catch someone's eye, you've got to stand out from the crowd.
Try asking me out.
Would you like to go on a date with me?
Remember, the key is to make her heart flutter.
Today, I'll be evaluating your date performance.
If you were Nita, you probably wouldn’t ride with me on the companion saddle.
This is me, not Nita.
I would never let someone I love face danger alone.