Ever been here with anyone else?
I had this friend, Puen.
That jerk?
Zo, it’s been a while since we last met.
I'm really sorry.
Give her time.
I've never brought anyone home before.
If he backed out because of this, you guys wouldn’t last.
We’re not dating.
You need to step up your game, Joke,
because I’m kind of fond of this one.
Thank you for being my boyfriend.
Like these?
Noticed you've been eyeing them.
Yeah,
as I keep staring at them,
I feel like the vases keep changing their appearances each time I look.
Do you feel that too?
Are you even listening?
Yes, I am.
Loud and clear.
So why aren't you looking at the vases?
I’ve put them right in front of you many times.
For me,
the vases…
are not as cute as you.
You …
Come on, let’s go to bed.
Bed?
Are you sleeping here tonight?
Mind if I do?
Why the intense gaze?
Can’t I look at my own boyfriend?
I'm trying to sleep.
Your staring isn't helping.
If you want me to go to bed,
a good night kiss might do the trick.
What kiss?
No! No! Go to sleep! Sleep! No!
No!
Please.
Someone is calling.
That number again.
Again?
What do you mean "again"?
I've received multiple calls from this number,
but no one speaks when I answer.
I just hear them breathing on the other end.
Don't believe me? Answer it.
I'm not sure this is a good idea.
Hello.
Shit, this is scary.
See? I told you.
Is this a phone scam?
I don't know.
Hand me the phone.
What are you up to?
Let me tell you, I’m going to block this number now.
This could be the safest way for you.
Eliminate the risk.
You care about me, huh?
Duh!
And I'm worried about me too.
We spend so much time together.
If he had a grudge against you and knew we were together,
I could be an unintended victim.
You are not a romantic.
Here you go. Let's go to sleep.
I said you didn't have to drop me here.
But I wanted to.
Look at the way you're dressed. People are looking.
Who cares?
I just wanted to see my boyfriend off.
That's all.
This is where you stop.
I see my friends there.
I can walk you over. It's only a few steps away.
No need.
With your outfit, it’d be best if you went back to sleep.
I don't want to explain things to them.
Before I go…
What now?
I could use a goodbye hug.
Let me recharge.
No way!
Please.
Too many people here.
What’s that?
Too many people here. I can’t.
It’s alright.
It’s embarrassing.
Can't I just get a hug from my boyfriend? Please.
That's enough.
I'll pick you up after class.
See you then.
Okay.
I’ve got to go.
Bye.
Darling, I miss you.
I miss you too.
I do not want to go to class, Joke.
I hate being away from you.
The pain of missing someone is real.
Serioulsy, guys?
We were copying you.
It's just an imitation.
Nothing beats a genuine hug.
Absolutely.
Don't you guys have something better to do than tease me?
Not really. I only have one class today.
I'll go back to gaming soon.
Yeah, and I’ve got football practice.
How are you both so relaxed
when I'm running between faculties all alone?
You should’ve followed my advice to have a packed schedule in senior year.
But you wanted to graduate early
because of the debate competition.
[Joke: Feeling a bit lonely?]
[Zo: So you think you've got me figured out?]
[Joke: Sure, I do care about you, you know.]
[Zo: Ugh!]
[Joke: Made any friends in your class yet?]
[Zo: Not really.]
[Joke: Shoot me a text after, I'll come pick you up.]
[Zo: Okay.]
Excuse me, is this seat taken?
No, it’s free.
Mind if I sit here?
Go right ahead.
Thanks.
Alright, everyone, let’s get settled.
Ready for the lesson?
You here by yourself?
I wanted to finish all my credits before senior year.
Turns out, none of my buddies felt the same.
I see.
I’m Poom, by the way.
From Humanities.
I’m Zo, Political Science, IR major.
You’ve come a long way, huh?
Why are you here alone?
Same reason as you.
I feel you.
In that case, mind if we stick together this semester?
Sounds good to me.
[Zo: Looks like I’ve made a friend.]
You might think this class is a breeze,
but I've heard from seniors that there's a ton of homework.
Really?
I guess I didn't look into it enough before signing up.
Word is, after the first week, there's an assignment due every single week.
Seriously?
Did I just shoot myself in the foot?
Anyway, are you free now?
Want to grab something to eat somewhere close?
I'd love to, but I’ve already got plans.
Always on the go, huh?
You're teasing me already.
Hold on a sec.
Sure.
Hello.
Where are you? Done with class?
Just finished. Heading out now.
Why didn’t you let me know?
I said I’d come get you.
Oh, right!
I'm so sorry.
I got caught up in a conversation with a new classmate.
Meet me by the Humanities Building.
I'll be right down.
Alright,
I'm on my way. Just hang tight.
Will do.
Catch you soon.
Why don't we walk together…
Is he an alien or what?
Hi,
I'm here.
Cool, just wrapped up class. Be down in a sec.
I'm at our spot.
Hurry, can't wait to see you.
[Mew: Hello, there. Do you remember me?]
[Jeng: How could I forget?]
[Mew: Great to hear! I was hoping to get some advice on what to study next.  Would you mind helping me with that?]
What were you doing?
I was standing there watching you for a while.
Well, ummm...
Just got a text from my friend about some last-minute law work.
What's wrong with you? I'm starving here.
Hey,
Pok.
I wasn’t being honest earlier.
During the open house, a high schooler asked for my IG, and I gave it to her.
She just hit me up for study advice.
Why did you lie?
You could have told me.
I didn't want you to worry.
And I thought it might strain things between us.
Thank you for telling me the truth.
Don't fret.
If you’ve got no hidden agenda, we're good.
You said you couldn’t wait to see my face.
Here's my face right in front of you.
Let's head back to our place and find something to eat. I'm famished.
Please.
You mean food, right?
Yes, food.
Okay.
Let’s go.
What are you in the mood for?
What’ve we got left in the fridge?
Man, I'm stuffed.
Well, you should be.
You basically cleaned out every stall in China Town.
I had classes all day, okay?
Needed to refuel.
Hey, no judgment here.
Seeing you happy and full
actually makes me happy.
You've been spouting some real Hallmark lines lately, you know?
Hey, I can't help it.
Plus,
I only say that stuff to you.
What?
You biting back now?
Of course.
I didn't see your new friend when I came to get you.
Who is he?
His name's Poom, from the Humanities faculty.
I was kind of thrown off, too.
He vanished the second I picked up your call.
Did he have to rush off or something?
I don't think so.
He'd actually asked me to grab a snack with him.
Then poof, he's gone.
Like he was beamed up by a UFO or something.
Maybe just ask him about it next time you bump into him.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Not worth fussing over.
Anyway, I need to shower. I feel gross.
Just a shower.
Mind if I join you?
Let go, or I swear I'll bite you.
Go ahead.
You’re as menacing as a puppy.
Do it, bite it off.
Let go already.
It’s shower time.
Let me join you, Zo.
No sleeping in my class.
Now that you’ve finished the Psychology for Leadership course,
it’s time to put it to the test.
Team up in pairs and select a leader.
Analyze their personality using what you’ve learned.
This assignment is due next Friday.
Class dismissed for today,
so you've got some time for research
Thank you.
Shit!
Poom, what the hell, man?
Just messing with you.
You nearly scared me to death.
Why are you so late?
Attendance was ages ago.
Missing attendance is small potatoes compared to exams and assignments.
Speaking of assignments,
we just got one. We need to pair up,
pick a leader, and analyze their personality using the theory learned.
The deadline is next week.
And we need to present it in class.
See? I told you.
Who did you pair up with?
Do you even need to ask?
It's not like I've got a friend list to choose from here.
Where should we go to work on this?
I don't have a lot of free time these days.
The library.
Today. Let me check the availability.
Sounds good.
Do we have a shot?
It's fully booked!
I’ve got a roommate.
Any other ideas?
I think I know a spot we could use.
Great, where?
You’re bringing your friend to your place?
Yeah, just to work on an assignment.
Is this friend trustworthy?
Yeah, he’s cool.
Don't worry.
Fine. Call me if you need anything.
Will do.
Okay.
Bro!
Are you there?
Jeng,
what are you doing here?
You’re the reason.
Diving into online shopping now, huh?
What are you even talking about?
Come on, bro! Tell me what you bought.
Or…
That was uncalled for!
Your mind's in the gutter.
I did not order anything.
If you didn’t, then explain this.
I saw it when I was picking up my package, so I grabbed it for you.
Seriously though, this is weird.
[ JOKE ]
No one in their right mind would write your name like that.
Why don't you open it?
Don't you want to know what's inside?
Got to sniff it, huh?
Who would do something like this?
Zo!
Where are you going? Wait for me!
So, you’re into ceramic sculpture?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
You into it?
Not much at first.
But as I kept going, it turned out to be fun.
Looks like you went with someone special.
Your smile says it all.
I should head out.
I'll leave the assignment with you for now.
Sounds good. We'll present it together next week.
Let me walk you out.
Okay.
Where’s my key?
I just used it to get in.
Need help looking for it?
Nah, let me walk you out first.
Let's go.
Hold on a sec.
Good thing I left a spare key here. Come on.
Okay.
Let’s move.
Zo!
Joke, why are you yelling?
You're going to wake up the whole building.
Are you alright?
I couldn't get a hold of you.
I thought something had happened.
I just got out of the shower, so I missed your calls.
Where is your study buddy?
He left a while ago.
Want to grab a bite?
Something wrong?
Come on, let's go out.
I've got something to tell you.
Wait, the stalker?
I think he's back in action.
But you and Nita caught him, right?
Nita and I knew who he was.
But we didn’t have enough evidence to pin him down.
I've received threats like this before
when Nita and I were fake-dating.
Then he vanished.
Why would he come after us now?
I seriously have no idea.
What I know is that we’ve got to be careful from now on.
I don't know if he's holding a grudge against me
and is planning to harm people around me or not.
Are you scared?
Don't worry,
I'll take care of you.
Here you go.
Open your mouth.
Thanks for walking me home.
Of course.
Are you sure you don't want me to stay with you?
I am sure.
I’ll be fine on my own.
Alright,
sweet dreams.
And call me.
Will do.
Safe trip home.
Catch you later.
Bye.
Joke!
Zo!
What happened?
Well…
Who did this?
No clue.
The key that I used to get in with my friend earlier is missing.
So I'm using my spare key for now.
I still can't find the original.
Your friend.
Hello,
are you there?
Oh, my. I lost track of time.
I was too focused on studying.
I'll head over now.
Okay, bye.
See you soon.
Hello, what’s up, Zo?
Where are you?
I need a favor.
I’m at a snack shop. What’s up?
Something urgent came up. I need to head back to my hometown.
Could you grab the assignment from my place and hand it in next week?
Sure thing.
You going to be gone long?
Yeah, I think so.
You remember where my spare key is, right?
Yep.
Grab it tonight if you have time, so you don't forget.
Sure. On my way.
What are you up to, James?
Joke?
You set this up?
We set this up to catch you in the act.
You stalker!
Stalker?
Tell him, Zo. I'm here to get our assignment, like you asked.
I'm thinking I'll have to redo the assignment.
Since my 'partner' isn't even enrolled in this class.
What's the deal, Poom?
Or should I say, James?
Well, I…
I feel bad for Nita.
Joke is gay, but he’s using her as a cover.
Can't you see how miserable she is because of you? You bastard!
Let’s calm down!
Just stop!
Stop!
Want to beat me up?
Enough!
Stop! That’s enough!
Nita,
I’m doing all of this for you.
Really?
Then you can explain it to the police.
Nita!
You alright after that fight?
I'm fine, and he started it.
I'm glad you're okay.
Thank you, both of you.
No problem. That's what friends are for.
I feel like I can finally breathe easy.
I've been having a weird feeling for a while now.
I can’t believe your IG story set him off,
thinking you broke my heart or something.
Who could've guessed he'd take it that way?
Thank you so much.
I should get going. Don't want to intrude any longer.
Get home safe.
- Safe travels.
- Bye.
Should I be jealous of you and Nita?
There's no reason to be jealous. Let's head upstairs.
What are you looking at?
The sky looks amazing after the rain.
Don't trust a stranger too easily, okay?
If something comes up, we always talk, alright?
I promise.
Something wrong?
I can wait if you're not ready.
I just…
I'm not sure.
That's okay.
Until you're ready,
I can wait.
Joke.
Huh?
I’ve never…
What’s with the smile?
It makes me self-conscious.
I promise that when you’re with me, you’ll feel good.
You trust me, right, Zo?
Yeah,
Joke, I trust you.
What's the matter?
When are you going to tell me?
Tell you what?
Why did our relationship have to start with a lie?
I'm moving back to my old place.
Can you please not do this?
The problem is, I don't know where I fit in your damn life!
Think about it; there was nothing bad.
So you don't think you're wrong?
Seriously, I don’t think this is enough for me.