[Breaking the Shadows]
[Episode 16]
[Jinhuan]
From now on, call me Wangtian.
What are you laughing at?
Why do you want to be named after a tree?
Wangtian is great.
It can grow up to 70 or 80 meters tall.
No one can block its light.
This way, when you hear Wangtian in the future,
you'll think of me.
You'll remember the days we spent here.
Then I'll call myself Jinhuan.
What's Jinhuan?
The banded krait snake.
It's the most venomous snake
in this forest.
Why do you want to be named after a snake?
To guard the Wangtian tree.
If anyone comes to cut down the tree,
I'll bite them.
[Delete contact]
[Please wait]
[Settings]
Xueman.
You're here?
Come in.
How come you have time to visit me today?
It's been too tiring lately.
Captain Fang gave us a day off.
Xueman,
can I drink this?
Of course.
I'll get you a glass.
Has the case been solved?
No.
Wasn't Wang Xuehua
from the hardware store killed by you guys?
If he's dead,
isn't the case solved then?
We didn't kill him.
He committed suicide.
I still remember
when I sent you to the police academy.
I truly believe that was
the wisest decision I've ever made.
Han Qing,
you're a good police officer.
You'll definitely solve this case.
You know, I always have
this image in my mind.
You're standing on that stage,
while everyone's applauding for you.
You've received an honor
and you're saluting everyone.
I know for all of this,
you've lost everything.
Your father,
your mother,
your mentor,
and Zhong Wei.
If only I can trade myself
to bring them all back.
Do you think it's possible?
It's not.
They can never come back.
Xueman,
is there any more wine?
I'll go get it.
Among all the people in the world,
only the two of us
have the same blood flowing in our veins.
You don't care about those honors.
You care about those who can never come back.
Zhong Wei,
your mentor,
and maybe me too.
I really will die before you.
Do you believe that?
Come,
dear sister.
My dearest sister.
Xueman,
you're all I have left.
I'm the one who caused Dad's death.
It has nothing to do with you.
The day you came back,
I asked Dad to stop on the highway.
I just didn't want him to pick you up.
So, I...
You...
When you arrived at the hospital,
I wanted to tell you the truth, but I didn't dare.
I... I was afraid you'd hate me.
I was afraid you'd abandon me.
Because I knew
at that time...
Dad had died.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have been so selfish and made you stop the car.
It's my fault.
it's all my fault.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Please wake up.
I'll get along well with Xueman from now on.
Dad, please wake up, Dad.
Dad.
So many years have passed.
We've all grown old.
Does the truth still matter?
It's been so many years.
This matter has been weighing on my chest,
suffocating me.
I...
Every time you confessed in front of me,
I felt extremely guilty, I...
I really wanted to tell you the truth,
but I didn't dare.
Every time you were at the grave,
you'd confess to Dad and say
it was you who caused their deaths,
it was you who made me lose my parents.
But it's not like that, I...
I was wrong, Xueman.
I really was wrong.
You're right.
First, it was Mom and Dad,
then Mr. Zhao...
Zhong Wei.
All of them
have left me.
I'm the only one left.
I'm sorry, Xueman.
You still have me.
Sister,
don't go.
You're all I have left.
[Ward 4]
That was the first time you called me "Sister."
I thought to myself at that moment...
My annoying little sister was so pitiful,
even more pitiful than me.
At least I still had my mom,
even though she was out of her mind
and didn't know anything.
I really miss them.
Can we leave this place?
Forget everything.
You won't be a police officer.
And I...
I won't be who I am now either.
It'll be as if nothing ever happened.
We can start over
and begin a new life.
Let's be sisters,
for real.
Can we?
As if nothing ever happened.
Please say yes.
Okay.
As if nothing ever happened.
We'll start over
and begin a new life.
Let's be sisters.
[Yamei Colour Studio]
Xueman.
You're awake.
Did I wake you up?
No, I woke up on my own.
Have a seat.
No need, you sit.
I remember you used to love eating shiitake.
Here, drink this first.
It's been a long time since I cooked.
I don't know if it tastes good or not.
I've made up my mind.
Let's go to Dali.
What for?
Didn't we agree last night?
We'll leave this place and start over.
I need to think about it more.
If I really quit my job as a police officer,
I don't know what else I can do.
I'm not like you.
You've been bold and good at business since you were young.
You even stopped studying back then
and went off to do business elsewhere.
Yes.
I remember
that summer
was particularly hot.
I went back home once before leaving.
Do you remember?
You're back.
I heard from Dad that you're going out to work.
Where are you going?
To Rongdu.
Is it far?
It takes a day and a night by train.
That's quite far.
Will you come back?
No.
That's pretty good.
I was really annoying back then.
Yep.
You didn't go alone, did you?
With your boyfriend?
I didn't have a boyfriend.
It was someone from my hometown.
Who? Do I know them?
You don't know them.
It was a relative from my mom's
hometown.
I remember after you went to Rongdu,
Dad often talked about you at home,
saying you gave up your studies
and went to do business elsewhere.
You were too young then.
You probably don't remember.
Every time I asked Dad for my tuition,
he would have a big fight with Auntie.
I didn't want to be a burden to anyone.
The world is so big.
I could totally earn money to support myself.
So I went to Rongdu with that relative,
hoping to earn money with my own labor.
Wen.
Come here.
A Mr. Zheng is coming to pick up some goods.
I need you to collect the payment for me
and give him the goods.
What kind of goods?
Wen, I can't do this.
I wasn't comfortable with it at first either.
But you get used to it over time.
But this is hurting people.
Yes,
but it also makes a lot of money.
Girls
can also rely on themselves
to create their own world.
Even without a beard,
you can still be a king.
He gave me direction in life
and helped me grow up.
Gradually,
I started
learning how to do business from him.
What kind of business?
Selling construction materials.
He taught me how to negotiate and contend
with clients.
Soon, I was able to handle things on my own.
After that, the business
kept getting better.
We opened a storefront in the construction materials market
at Hongmenlou.
He asked me to manage it.
Then,
we moved to a
larger construction materials market.
He said he wanted to expand overseas,
so he went to Singapore.
He asked me to go with him,
but I didn't agree.
I didn't want to give up the business I had.
So, he left by himself.
For supplies, find Kyaw Myint Tun.
He's reliable.
After arriving in Singapore,
his business continued to thrive.
Later,
the next news I heard about him
was that he had moved from Singapore to North America.
Later, he passed away there.
What happened?
Cancer.
By the time it was discovered,
it was already in the late stages.
[Police]
He was afraid of worrying me,
so he arranged everything by himself.
Before he died, he entrusted me
to continue his life's journey
on his behalf.
What about you?
How did you end up in the tea business?
At that time, I really hadn't decided what to do.
I thought that if I came back,
I'd have to start all over again.
I was quite familiar with Rongdu,
so I stayed there for a while.
There were many teahouses there
and business was good.
As soon as I settled down,
I started to inquire about the market.
[Recording Hall]
I wanted to find a place to stock up.
I always wanted to prove
that I could run
a successful business by myself.
People there loved drinking tea
and the teahouse business thrived.
I thought this was pretty good,
so I found a teahouse
and started working there.
Later, I became good friends with the owner.
He taught me a lot about running a teahouse.
After that, I went to Yun'an.
Yun'an?
Where in Yun'an?
Fu'er.
Have you heard of it?
No.
I just heard
that there's a place in Yun'an
called Mengla.
That deceased hardware store owner, Wang Xuehua,
seems to have had something to do with that place.
We're investigating it.
Xueman, where in Yun'an did you say you went?
Fu'er.
Fu'er is famous for its ancient tree black tea.
When I arrived there,
I set my sights on a tea farmer.
I negotiated with him about becoming an agent,
but he thought I was too young and inexperienced.
He wouldn't give it to me.
So I just
refused to leave.
I picked and roasted tea,
working hard for the entire tea season.
Only then did he agree to give me the agent position.
[Somewhere overseas]
Where's Tang Wen?
He got arrested.
I'll be in charge from now on.
With him as a supplier,
I felt secure,
so I came back.
I opened this teahouse
and gradually built it up to what it is today.
It's been so difficult.
Nothing in life is easy.
It's the same for you as a police officer.
You've sacrificed so much.
So, as we agreed yesterday,
about leaving this place
and starting over,
does it still stand?
Let me finish this case
completely first.
Okay.
I'll wait for your news.
I'm Han Qing,
from the Municipal Criminal Investigation Unit.
[Exit] [Slow down]
Is that you in the photo?
Young lady,
where did you get that?
What about the person next to you?
Is that your girlfriend?
Why?
Are you interested in her?
She's my sister.
Your sister?
Tell me about it.
What's the deal between you and my sister?
That's ancient history.
Why are you asking about this?
You dated my sister?
I guess so.
But not for long.
A flower can't bloom in cow dung forever.
You know what I mean?
Did you know Chen Bin back then?
Yes.
We were bouncers together at that time.
So my sister knew Chen Bin too?
Yes.
Why?
You and my sister broke up
because of Chen Bin?
It was between me and your sister.
We would have split up with or without him.
So he was involved.
If you say so.
Did my sister have a relationship with Chen Bin?
Chen Bin pursued her,
but it didn't work out.
Why?
You know your sister.
She's so strong-willed.
She would never go for
small-time thugs like me and Chen Bin.
She wasn't with us for long
before she left.
We didn't keep in touch after that.
I think she went out of town
to learn about business.
What kind of business?
I don't know.
Does Chen Bin know?
Not sure.
I never ask about
things that don't concern me.
Do you know about King of Hearts?
Who?
Is it related to me?
Chen Bin.
That's his nickname in the drug trafficking circle.
Chen Bin?
He's called King of Hearts?
You know what?
Given his luck with women,
that name suits him well.
King of Hearts.
Hello.
Your mom is in the room.
Qing.
Speak.
The Mengba Prefecture Police Department
arrested a major drug lord from Sishiu named Tang Wen
[Mengba Substation]
in 1998.
He was executed in 1999.
The files mention he had two long-term associates,
a man and a woman.
The man was called Hua.
[Mengba Substation]
"Hua" as in Wang Xuehua.
Is there only a name?
What about other information?
Nothing else was mentioned.
The file only has this one sentence
about his associates.
But I heard from the old colleagues here at the bureau
that Tang Wen used to frequent
the border area around
Mengla, Mengha, and Jinghuo.
I'm planning to go there and investigate now.
Send me the relevant information about Tang Wen.
I've already sent it to you.
Okay, I'll hang up now.
[Lin Jiajia]
[Fingerprint Card]
[Tang Wen]