[Breaking the Shadows]
[Episode 6]
Mrs. Dong, you're here.
Is Mr. Chen in his office?
Mr. Chen was just working out.
I'm not sure if he's in his office yet.
Then, I'll go check.
Carry on with your work.
I'm with you now.
Stay focused.
Let me see who's looking for me.
Be good.
What's wrong?
Do you have other women besides me?
[Mrs. Dong is here!!!]
My wife is here.
Hello, Mrs. Dong.
Hello.
You're the new dance teacher here, right?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
You're so beautiful.
What's your name?
Jiaqi.
That's a lovely name.
Is Mr. Chen in?
Yes, I've just finished scheduling classes with him.
That's all. You can go back to your work.
Okay.
Goodbye then, Mrs. Dong.
Goodbye.
Honey.
You've come at just the right time.
I think I'm the one who came too early.
What did you say?
What do you mean by that?
I don't mean anything by it.
Then, you're really no fun.
Right?
It really is quite boring.
Your chest workout today really paid off.
I worked on my legs today.
Did Xueman bring you the new tea?
She said the new tea from Fudong
is better than previous years.
The rainfall has been abundant this year.
I still have the tea she brought before,
the one from Yun'an.
She hasn't sent the one you mentioned to me yet.
Honey,
did you watch the news today?
No, I didn't. What's up?
The Public Security Bureau has issued a reward notice.
That receptionist of yours, Bai Xiaohui,
has been kidnapped.
Did you know about it?
Bai Xiaohui?
Who would kidnap her?
What for?
The police already came to ask questions?
They did, but they didn't mention anything about kidnapping.
Then what did you tell them?
What could I say?
She's just an employee. How would I know anything about her?
But I think
this Bai Xiaohui is quite interesting.
She's usually so dull and unremarkable,
yet she's tangled up with a murderer.
You...
How do you know it's a murderer?
Didn't the news say
that person killed two other people as well?
Didn't you say you didn't watch the news?
Yeah, I didn't watch the news.
Then how did you know?
When I was working out earlier,
two guys were talking about it.
I just overheard them talking about it.
Now you're telling me about it too,
so I put two and two together
and realized that you were talking about the same thing!
Why are you getting all worked up?
Do you think Bai Xiaohui
might have already been...
What's it got to do with you?
Why are you worrying about this?
You're not a cop.
I'm just worried.
I'm afraid what happened to her
might drag us into it.
Drag us into it?
What are you trying to say?
They've been on your case for so long
for that missing police officer earlier.
You know that.
I'm thinking that if something
also happens to Bai Xiaohui,
that would give them another chance.
Hello.
Are you Dong Jie?
Yes.
Who are you?
We're from the Municipal Criminal Investigation Unit.
My name is Han Qing.
[Police]
Oh, you're Han Qing.
I'm good friends with your sister.
She often talks about you.
Give me a moment; let me park my car.
Okay.
Do you want sugar, Han Qing?
She doesn't drink coffee.
I'm sorry.
Then I'll get you some water.
No need. Don't trouble yourself.
It's alright.
Please, have a seat.
Here.
Thank you.
Do you know Bai Xiaohui?
Yes, I do.
She works for my husband.
But I think I heard
that she hasn't been to work these past few days.
She's been kidnapped.
No way.
When did this happen?
Haven't you seen the news?
I really haven't been paying attention to that.
Oh my God, how could this happen?
If something happens to her,
what will happen to her child?
You know about her child?
Yes.
Because Bai Xiaohui borrowed money from me.
She said it was for her child's medical treatment.
How much did she borrow?
I lent her 50,000 yuan.
When did she borrow it?
Could you describe to us what happened at that time?
It was...
early March.
Yes, early March.
We agreed to meet at a café.
Hello.
Please, sit.
I'm Dong Jie.
I know.
I heard that your child is sick, right?
I think you might need this.
Take this.
No, no, no.
Mrs. Dong, this...
I... I can't take it.
Don't be so polite.
You work at Chen Bin's company,
so we're all family here.
Your child's treatment is important.
Come on, take it.
Are you very close to her?
Why would she borrow money from you?
Not at all. I didn't even know her before.
So, when she came to me,
I actually thought it was quite out of the blue too.
But I could understand.
After all, she works for Chen Bin.
I suppose
she must have heard about what I've been doing.
You've been doing something?
What have you been doing?
I've been doing charity work.
I've been doing this for ten years now.
We also have a chat group for our wives,
where we frequently organize charity events.
Your sister is also in the group.
Then, has Bai Xiaohui
ever contacted you again since that time?
No,
she didn't contact me after that.
To be honest,
I don't expect her to pay back
the money I lent her.
And we've already agreed within our group
that when it's time for her child's surgery,
we'll provide additional financial support.
Has Chen Bin ever mentioned
anything about Bai Xiaohui to you?
No.
Chen Bin, this man,
I think he probably...
he probably doesn't even know
about an employee like her.
Is that so?
When I asked him about it,
he seemed quite aware.
Really?
Well, that's not surprising.
After all...
Bai Xiaohui is the receptionist.
She often takes clients
to Chen Bin's office.
It's normal for him to be well aware of her.
Qing,
I think
there may be something off about Dong Jie
lending money to Bai Xiaohui.
What is off?
The 200,000 yuan that Bai Xiaohui gave to Fan Lingling's parents
probably didn't come from Fan Lingling's jade gambling earnings.
I've looked into it.
Fan Lingling never invested in any jade business.
So, you mean Bai Xiaohui is lying?
I also asked
the doctor who's been doing dialysis for Bai Xiaohui's child.
The doctor said Bai Xiaohui was very eager to get a kidney transplant for her child
and had even said that as long as there was a kidney available,
the money would be ready immediately.
The cost of a kidney transplant is over several hundred thousand yuan.
Plus the 200,000 yuan given to Fan Lingling's parents,
that's a huge sum of nearly one million yuan.
If she has this million yuan,
why would she need to borrow 50,000 yuan from Dong Jie?
Not bad.
You've been investigating quite a bit behind my back.
I'm just learning from your spirit, Qing.
Always digging a little deeper.
But you've overlooked one thing.
What's that?
Time.
Time?
The time Bai Xiaohui borrowed 50,000 yuan
from Dong Jie was on March 2nd.
But the lead about her having a million yuan
came up only recently.
These two time points
are more than two months apart.
If she had not had the million yuan two months ago,
then that 50,000 yuan would have been a huge amount for her.
Didn't you say it yourself?
This was the largest amount she'd ever had
in her account since it was first opened.
Two months ago, Bai Xiaohui's child
was receiving treatment at another hospital.
The attending physician said
Bai Xiaohui clearly stated
she couldn't afford the kidney transplant at all.
Even the ten or twenty thousand yuan for the hospitalization deposit
took her a week to scrape together.
I'm convinced.
Completely convinced.
You're still more thorough in your work, Qing.
I'll keep investigating where Bai Xiaohui
got that million yuan in cash.
You're here.
Have a seat.
Americano?
Thank you.
This is
all the information you wanted on that woman.
How long have they known each other?
Less than a month.
She's married?
To be precise,
she's juggling several men at once.
Quite impressive.
What are you going to do about it?
I'll handle it myself.
Thank you for your hard work.
My pleasure.
There's one more thing I need your help with.
Do you have her name?
It's just her WeChat username.
Deng Jiaqi.
This is for this month. Please take it.
No need, really no need.
As I've said before, I really don't need payment
for working for you.
This is what you deserve.
You haven't told anyone else that I asked you to look into
Bai Xiaohui before, have you?
Rest assured about this.
I won't tell anyone
about your private matters.
Thank you.
[Guangchang Road] [East Ring Road]
[Missing Person]
All this coffee
and tea this morning
is bothering my stomach.
I just noticed
that the boss lady downstairs is pretty stylish.
She's probably not from around here, is she?
Good eye.
I'll introduce you later.
You know her?
She's my sister.
Your sister?
Your real sister?
Half-sister, same father.
Is it because we don't look alike?
My sister is much prettier than me.
You're beautiful too.
You two have different vibes.
Oh, right, Qing,
at the entrance,
you posted the missing person notice for Zhong Wei, didn't you?
Yes.
Limin Lane, where he disappeared,
is just behind this teahouse.
Any leads?
[March 16, 2017] [Limin Lane, T-junction]
None.
None of the residents here have seen him.
I've reviewed the teahouse's
surveillance footage many times as well.
Xueman.
I thought it was you when I saw you.
I've made you a pot of good tea.
Let me introduce you.
This is my new colleague, Lin Jiajia.
Nice to meet you, Xueman.
Nice to meet you.
Just in time, I've brewed some Gushu tea I just received.
Try it.
You don't usually come to find me.
Since you're here, you must have something to discuss, right?
Xueman,
are you familiar with Dong Jie?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Do you have a group chat for rich wives?
For doing charity?
Yes.
Are you going to include Bai Xiaohui's child
in your support program?
I don't quite remember the specifics.
We came to you to understand
the situation for a case.
You have to answer everything
you know honestly.
Yes.
I know. I'm being honest.
About Bai Xiaohui,
I really can't remember her clearly.
Did Dong Jie ever mention
including uremia patients
in the fund's support plan in the future?
Here is the thing.
We did support Fei before.
Later, I suggested this
to Dong Jie too,
but she didn't give me a direct answer,
so it just fizzled out.
How is Dong Jie's relationship with Chen Bin?
You mean her husband?
Pretty good.
Pretty good?
Chen Bin keeps mistresses,
not just one.
If you know about this
and still think their relationship is good,
what's your reason?
You know about it, right?
Yes, I do know.
Actually,
Dong Jie knows about it, too.
She's fully aware of it.
Whenever Chen Bin has another woman, she deals with them.
No woman who's been involved with Chen Bin
escapes her notice.
As long as she wants something,
she'll get it.
She's maintaining her marriage
[Ming Is Me] [Transfer amount; 20000]
in her own way.
[Wexin Pay]
Why would Dong Jie tolerate this?
She loves Chen Bin.
She thinks it's fine for a man
to fool around outside,
as long as he doesn't take it seriously.
And Chen Bin,
he has never taken other women seriously.
Do you know that many of the women Chen Bin
couldn't get rid of later
were all dealt with by Dong Jie on his behalf?
I think the reason
Dong Jie can be so tolerant of this
[Stay away from my husband!]
is because she feels
she owes it to Chen Bin from the past.
Owes it to Chen Bin? Why?
She was pregnant
with Chen Bin's child.
But at that time,
she was too young.
She wanted to continue her dance career.
For the sake of her figure,
she decided not to keep the child.
And she didn't tell Chen Bin about it in advance.
Is Dong Jie really not angry?
Who would not be angry?
I guess she's come to terms with it.
She has her own way of venting.
She listens to music, does charity work,
[Okay, Mrs. Dong, I'm sorry.]
and helps people in need
to forget about these unpleasant things.
I really can't understand it.
Knowing Chen Bin is like this,
how can Dong Jie still be with him?
Human emotions are just complicated.
That kind of feeling of loving and hating him at the same time,
wanting to kill him,
but still unable to live without him.
All these feelings can coexist.
Hello, how are you feeling now?
[Police]
What's your name?
Where are you mainly injured? Here, right?
[Police]
Relax, relax. Stay calm.
Easy, easy, come on.
Up.
Relax yourself; don't be nervous.
How do you feel?
You've injured your head. Does your chest hurt?
We're going to the hospital right away.
Don't be nervous.
Lift it up a bit more, a bit more.
It's okay; don't be nervous.
Calling the command center, please respond if you hear me.
There's been a car accident in the development zone.
The license plate of the accident vehicle matches
the plate of the suspect vehicle in the dismemberment case.
The license plate number is Jiang C85K92.
I repeat.
The plate number is Jiang C85K92.
Shitou.
[Service Station]
I'm asking you, where did you get the license plate?
Shitou,
your license plate is connected to a homicide case.
Where did you get it?
Stop asking questions. The patient needs surgery.
Stay here and don't cause trouble.
Forget it.
This guy...
He said, "Lyu Jianmin!"
What?
Lyu Jianmin, just these three words.
Once we received your call,
we immediately rushed to the repair shop.
But
Lyu Jianmin had already left.
His phone is also turned off.
This is one of the workers from their shop.
He was also present at that time.
Why did he suddenly have to leave?
He received a phone call.
After that, he said he had to go.
I've got to go now. I'm hanging up, okay?
Jianmin, you looking for me?
Yes, well, I have something to attend to.
I need to be away for a few days.
Please take care of things at the shop.
Keep an eye on everything.
Okay.
Jianmin,
when are you coming back?
It'll probably take a few days.
I'll call you if anything comes up.
The keys are here, okay?
Thanks for the help.
Who called him?
I-I don't know.
Lyu Jianmin has left you in charge of the shop.
Has this kind of thing happened before?
No, this is the first time.
Has he shown any other unusual behavior recently?
If you don't say, you're covering for him.
I really don't know.
Lyu Jianmin is suspected of a major criminal case.
My questioning today is very important.
You need to cooperate fully with our investigation.
Don't get yourself implicated in this.
I'll ask you one last time.
Has Lyu Jianmin
shown any other unusual behavior recently?
Zhuzi?
Zhuzi!
A few days before you came to the shop to investigate,
he asked me how to adjust the surveillance camera.
How do you set the shooting time
for the cameras?
There's a recording schedule here,
[System Settings] [Time Settings]
and there's a custom setting over there.
[Video Time] [Custom]
Custom.
See? It's all here now.
Below, you can adjust it for each day.
Whenever you want to start,
[System Settings] [Time Settings]
and when to stop,
it's right up here. Just drag the mouse over this area.
You can adjust everything.
You can go back to your work now.
Alright.
Why is the video for this period missing?
[Smart Surveillance System]
Did you set this?
I never touch it.
Have you seen this car?
[Dongzhou Municipal Public Security Bureau Surveillance Screenshot]
No.
Have there been
any new parts for this car in the shop in the last couple of days?
We haven't had the parts,
but I think I saw something in the scrap pile.
What did you see?
The body panel,
just like this car.
Come on, here.
One, two, three, go!
Can you be sure it's the same car model?
It should be,
because we often repair this type of car.
The specific model might be different,
but the car type is the same.
What about the color?
It's this same silver-gray color.
[Dongzhou Municipal Public Security Bureau]
[No Smoking]
Send out the notice to all bureaus.
Thoroughly investigate Lyu Jianmin's whereabouts.
Anyone who has been in contact with him must be checked.
[Suspect: Bai Xiaohui, female, 30 years old, currently missing.]
[Between May 5 and May 10, 2017, three major crimes occurred in our city in succession.]
[Suspect: Lyu Jianmin, male, about 35 years old, around 1.74 meters tall.]
[Co-Investigation Notice]
[To Tongling]
Qing.
[Bai Xiaohui; Employee of Power Fitness Club]
The registered owner of the phone number that called Lyu Jianmin,
1508, has already passed away.
Clearly, the number has been stolen.
Apart from their call today,
[Call Date][Call Time]
there have been multiple call records recently.
I've marked them all.
May 9th.
The day before Bai Xiaohui was kidnapped.
[Call Date] [Call time]
May 12th.
The second day, we first went to Lyu Jianmin's
repair shop.
May 13th.
Lyu Jianmin...
went back to Dongzhou to borrow money.
And this morning.
Shortly after the car accident occurred.
[To the Shuang'ou Road] [to Tongling]
He called Lyu Jianmin.
All these are at critical time points.
Right.
The other ends of the 1508
must be thoroughly checked.
Understood.
Preparing for a long night.
Mom, I miss you.
Mom, I'm the bravest.
Mom, don't cry.
How old is your son?
He's five.
What illness does he have?
Uremia.
Can you promise not to scream?
Stay away from my child.
I'm begging you.
I'll do anything.
Really.
I'll do whatever you want.
Just leave my child alone,
okay?
I'm begging you.
I really...
I'll do anything.
I'm begging you.
[0]
[Sending]
[Sending to multiple recipients]
[0]
8377 is unreachable.
[Bai Xiaohui, Employee of Power Fitness Club]
[0]
4491 is unreachable.
[1 new message]
[Message opening]
[0]
[1 new message]
[Message opening]
[0]
[Bai Xiaohui, Employee of Power Fitness Club]
0230 is unreachable.
5974 is unreachable.
3862 is unreachable.
[Bai Xiaohui, Employee of Power Fitness Club]
[Zhang Yong]
Qing,
why are we
always one step behind?
[Borrowed money?] [Acquaintance] [Zhang Yong]
[Enter]
As soon as possible.
Understood.
I'll be going then.
Open it and let me see.
I can't pull the bolt back.
Pull harder.
Pull with all your might.
Still can't pull it back?
How can't you pull it back?
[Pick up the goods]
It's really heavy.
[Waste Sorting; Everyone's Responsibility]
[Other Waste]
Who are you looking for?
Is Zhang Yong here?
He's inside.
Stop dawdling. Come on, hurry.
You're not an honest player. Put it properly.
Who is Zhang Yong?
That's me. You want to rent equipment?
We're police.
We're from the Municipal Criminal Investigation Unit.
We need to ask you a few questions.
[Police]
What's this about?
It's about Lyu Jianmin.
Lyu Jianmin?
Didn't you already ask about this over the phone?
Get out, get out, get out.
Hurry up, hurry up!
Come on, both of you, come on.
Sit, sit, please sit down.
Lyu Jianmin came to see you on the 12th, right?
[Honesty Wins the World]
Yes, he did.
Well...
Didn't I already
tell you everything over the phone?
What did he want from you?
What else could it be? He wanted to borrow money.
How much?
200,000 yuan.
That's a big ask, right?
To be honest, I was shocked.
How could he ever pay that back?
Did you lend it to him?
Even if I wanted to, I'd need to have that amount of money, right?
I'm struggling financially myself.
You all saw it, right?
All those cranes and excavators
parked in my yard.
I haven't been able to rent them out for months.
And this place.
It may look like just a big piece of wasteland,
but the rent isn't cheap at all.
And the construction companies
owe me a lot of money.
I can't get any of it back.
They act like I'm the one who owns them.
They will finally pay me
when their final payment comes through.
On top of that, I still have to pay for the vehicles...
Can I check that?
Why are you here?
[May 12, 2017, Friday, Office]
I need to talk to you about something.
Go, let's go outside to talk.
[May 12, 2017, Friday, Office]
[May 12, 2017, Friday, Wanhe Machinery Rental Company Yard]
What did you two talk about outside?
About borrowing money.
What else could we talk about?
[Honesty Wins the World]
Goodbye, officers!
I won't see you out!
Thank you!
Don't mention it! It's our duty!
[Wanhe Machinery Rental Company]
Qing, why did you bring me here?
This is Wufang Street.
What are we investigating here?
This red location marker is...
The last location of 1508 before turning off the phone
after a call to Lyu Jianmin.
This is our current position.
Everything within a one-kilometer radius is in range.
Got it. How should we investigate?
You investigate Wufang Street, and I'll go monitor Dong Jie.
We'll meet up later.
Keep me updated if anything comes up. Don't act rashly.
Okay.
How should I investigate?
Use this, use this.
[CCTV]
[Dongzhou Juvenile Relief and Protection Center]
[Dongzhou Children's Welfare Institute]
[Gymboree; Preliminary Education for Children aged 0 to 6]
When did this happen?
Just today.
At the fitness club.
It's a new member.
That was fast, huh?
That's why I hurried to find you.
No need, no need.
Take it.
Thank you.
Good girl.
Eat a little. We can't be picky about food.
Come on.
Good girl.
Forgive my bluntness.
Mr. Chen is so unrestrained
and completely disregards your feelings.
It's indeed quite outrageous.
You're a strong woman.
You won't confront him over these things.
But if this keeps going...
you'll be the one who ends up getting hurt.
I'm sorry.
I said something I shouldn't have.
I'm really sorry.
We should stop meeting so frequently from now on.
As we agreed,
let's meet once a month.
Okay.
I'll follow your arrangement.
Nothing else, right?
I'll be going.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
[Honey]
Hello,
the number you have dialed is currently powered off.
[No Smoking]
Who are you looking for? Who are you?
An Lian?
You remember me?
Of course, I remember.
What are you doing here?
I want to show you something.
Why did you take these photos?
I know you two just got married recently,
and what he's doing
is really unacceptable.
If in the future
you want to take any action,
like divorce, for example...
these photos
will definitely help you.
I don't need this kind of help.
I think I'm the one who came too early.
What do you mean by that?
I didn't mean anything by it.
Then you're really no fun.
Let's go.
Mr. Zhang, we've been waiting for you for so long today.
[Phantom Footprint; Cinema-Style Foot Massage]
We've been waiting for you to come and enjoy today.
This red location landmark is...
The last location of 1508 before turning off the phone
after a call to Lyu Jianmin.
[Phantom Footprint; Cinema-Style Foot Massage]
This is pretty good.
This? You can have it.
We have everything you want.
Welcome!
We've also
prepared a large private room for you.
That's a must.
We have everything you could ask for.
See anyone you like?
You're acting as if I've never been here before.
Do we have any familiar massage therapists here?
Anyone will do.
Alright, please have a seat and rest for a while.
The therapist will be here soon.
Thank you.
Hello, sir.
Sir, you're not here for a massage, right?
I know, I know.
[Police]
I'm investigating a case.
Please cooperate with me.
I'll cooperate.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Why does everyone in your line of work
look so handsome?
Delete the photo later.
What did you just say?
I...
I said you look handsome.
I'm asking why you said "Everyone?"
Qing!
She's inside.
Hello.
I'm from the Municipal Criminal Investigation Unit.
My name is Han Qing, his colleague.
Hello.
You said you
saw a police officer here before.
The one you just mentioned,
another police officer who came here before.
Yes, I saw one.
Could you look at this?
Was this the person in the photo?
Yes, that's him.
He had also been listening there before.
Hello, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'm investigating a case.
[Police]
Please cooperate with me.
Do you have a cup?
Yes.
Thank you.
[A really handsome police officer came in]
Would you like something to drink, sir?