[Breaking the Shadows]
[Episode 7]
When the car accident happened,
Zhang Yong's activity was detected
[March 6, 2017, Monday] [Second-floor corner]
within the signal location of 1508.
You called to tell me about the car accident.
Two minutes later,
Zhang Yong received a phone call.
Go wait for me outside.
According to the masseuse's testimony,
after Zhang Yong answered the call,
he immediately made another call.
Have you finished the call?
Yes, I have.
I still need to make another call.
Mr. Zhang, aren't you too busy?
Can't you just relax and enjoy the massage?
-Zhang Yong's expression changed as soon as he finished the call.
-Get lost!
Since he cursed at her, it left a strong impression.
The timing of Zhang Yong's call
perfectly matched when Lyu Jianmin received the call
from 1508.
Was 1508 Zhang Yong's phone number?
No.
Did Zhang Yong's registered phone number
have any call records
at 5:50 AM yesterday?
No.
Did the signal location of 1508
ever appear near Zhang Yong's rental company
or his home?
No.
But, Captain Fang,
before Zhong Wei went missing,
he was already watching Zhang Yong.
The masseuse confirmed that
Zhong Wei was eavesdropping
on the next room.
She even
messaged her friend on WeChat about it.
This Zhang Yong
is definitely suspicious.
And he might be connected
to the case Zhong Wei was investigating.
Otherwise, Zhong Wei
wouldn't have looked into him for no reason.
But Zhong Wei never sent back
any evidence or investigation report
on Zhang Yong.
We also don't have solid proof
that Zhang Yong used 1508
to make those calls.
All of this is just your speculation.
You know the bureau won't issue
a search warrant.
I can try to fight for it
but don't get your hopes up.
How about this, Captain Fang—
just pretend you don't know.
No way. Absolutely not.
Han Qing, don't be so stubborn.
Right now,
this is our only lead.
If we're right,
we can track down 1508,
find Lyu Jianmin, Bai Xiaohui,
and even the mole leaking information.
If we're wrong,
I'll take the fall alone. Deal?
No. No way.
Absolutely not.
Come in.
Yong.
Well...
Why'd you bring me to your company?
What are you panicking about? Sit down.
You're back home now.
This place is safe, don't worry.
The police won't find you.
The police are looking for me?
They've already issued a search notice.
Wait—
bro,
what's going on?
What do you mean by "hey?"
Did you send him away?
He's gone.
Better make sure he never comes back.
Don't worry.
I'll handle it.
Clean it up properly.
Understood.
Who was that on the phone?
My boss.
So what he just said
on the phone—
"Better make sure he never comes back."
What did he mean by that?
Jianmin,
I've been keeping you here in Dongzhou
without my boss knowing.
Otherwise...
Yong,
I've done everything as you requested.
But now...
What's really going on?
You're my boss.
You...
can do anything to me,
but I beg of you,
please take good care of my son.
Find his mother and bring her back.
Brother,
as for your family,
no one can take care of them better than you.
Just stay here and be at ease.
Chen Bin,
someone's looking for you.
What's up?
Come back home.
Give me my coat.
Get it yourself.
I'm leaving.
Chen Bin.
Let's go home.
Mr. Wang.
Ms. Han.
What are you doing here?
Weren't you living at the end of the alley?
Are you...
investigating a case?
Have you found Mr. Zhong?
Not yet.
I've kept the photo you gave me
on the counter.
I'll notify you as soon as I have any news.
Thank you.
I won't bother you anymore.
Mr. Wang,
you dropped something.
I'm leaving then.
[Man Lost]
I'm asking you a question.
What do you want?
How did you know I was there?
When did you find out?
The police are watching us so closely lately.
You'd better not go out recently.
What's the deal with the police?
I haven't broken any laws.
Why should I be worried about them?
Then why are the police watching us?
What are you trying to say?
I'm asking you to stay at home for now.
After the heat dies down,
you can do whatever you want.
Stop meddling in my affairs from now on!
You think I like to interfere?
Babe,
next time I'll spend more time with you, I promise.
You think I like to interfere?
You said on the phone
that you're also friends with Dong Jie, right?
Yes.
Actually, I'm not in that line of work.
I've known Dong Jie for a long time,
so I helped her out
as a favor.
You're also Dong Jie's friend.
If there's anything you need help with,
I'll try my best.
Can you tell me
what kind of trouble it is?
It's Dong Jie's trouble.
I'm Han Qing,
from the Municipal Criminal Investigation Unit.
Don't worry, I'm not here to cause you trouble.
That's funny. What kind of trouble could I have?
You're in quite a bit of trouble.
Under the Public Security Administration Punishments Law,
Article 42,
anyone caught peeping, filming, eavesdropping,
or spreading another person's private information
could face detention for up to five days
or a fine of up to 500 yuan.
In more serious cases,
the punishment could include detention for five to ten days
along with a fine of up to 500 yuan.
According to the Civil Code,
Articles 1032
and 1033,
no individual or organization
[At the door of the private room]
may infringe
upon another's privacy rights
through prying, harassment,
disclosure, or other means.
This includes, but is not limited to,
filming, recording, publicizing, peeping,
or eavesdropping on private activities.
Although the Criminal Law doesn't explicitly address
secret filming,
if it severely infringes on someone's privacy,
portrait rights, or reputation,
criminal liability may be pursued
under the relevant provisions of the law.
There are too many articles to list.
I've just given you a brief overview of a few.
You're making money fast enough.
Last night alone was about 20,000, right?
And you still think you're not in trouble?
Do you know this person?
Yes, I do.
Who is she?
Bai Xiaohui.
How do you know her?
Was it Dong Jie
who asked you to investigate her?
We'd like to see
all the photos you've taken of
women related to Chen Bin.
Is that okay?
[An Lian Photography Studio]
Be careful with your head.
What you're looking for
is all here.
When did you start
secretly photographing Chen Bin?
It's been a few years.
A few years?
Are these the only photos?
There should be more, right?
It started when they got married,
and has been on and off since then.
What's inside here?
This is the darkroom
where I usually develop photos.
All the materials you need are there.
May I go in and take a look?
Thank you.
I have a favor to ask.
She has no idea about any of this.
Please don't tell her.
No problem.
We've got an unexpected discovery.
Isn't this Zhang Yong's car rental company?
What are they looking under the car for?
I don't know.
You go through girlfriends pretty quickly. How do you even keep up?
Cut the crap.
Where is it?
Follow me.
Take a good look.
See where I put it for you.
There.
When was this photo taken?
Last May.
It makes sense.
Chen Bin knows Zhang Yong.
Zhang Yong knows Lyu Jianmin.
Lyu Jianmin is Bai Xiaohui's ex-husband.
And Bai Xiaohui
is Chen Bin's employee.
They all seem to be connected,
but it doesn't prove anything.
What do you think?
We need search warrants
for both Zhang Yong and Chen Bin.
It's going to be difficult.
We need to find something more
to prove these people
have a deeper connection.
I've reported it to Director Hou,
and he thinks
the timing is not right yet.
If we can't get the search warrants,
we should at least implement surveillance measures.
Director Hou suggested that
we should focus on peripheral investigations for now.
But Bai Xiaohui can't wait any longer.
I know.
By the way,
there's one more thing I need to tell you.
Yu.
-Did you find anything?
-Captain Fang.
[Dongzhou Traffic Real-time Data Monitoring Platform]
Captain Fang.
On the night of the car accident,
Song went to the location area of 1508.
Are you sure it was Song?
Yes.
[Dongzhou Traffic Real-time Data Monitoring Platform]
[Meilin Residential Complex] [Garage 5]
Song?
He leaked the information?
It's not certain yet.
The guy who met with him
was captured by surveillance cameras
on the night of his car accident,
[Screenshot of surveillance footage from Dongzhou Municipal Public Security Bureau]
within the location area of 1508,
right near the massage parlor
you were investigating for Zhang Yong.
What did Song say about it?
He didn't explain anything.
He didn't mention that guy
at all.
Song?
Why is he doing this?
I'd like to know that too.
Han Qing?
W-What are you doing here?
Do you need something from me?
Are you the mole?
Why aren't you saying anything, Song?
I have nothing to say.
Does the disappearance of Zhong Wei
have anything to do with you?
Don't forget,
he saved your life.
[Wan Haiqiang Murder Case]
[Crime Scene]
[Brave and Wise]
[Police]
[Crime Scene]
What's the relationship between Dong Jie and Bai Xiaohui?
What kind of relationship could they have?
What about you?
What's your relationship with Bai Xiaohui?
Are you here to look into the case
or just snoop into my personal life?
Do you need something from me?
The 50,000 yuan from Bai Xiaohui
was borrowed from me.
She didn't know about Bai Xiaohui's child
in the group chat,
and she hadn't planned to include the dialysis
in the funding plan.
I might have remembered it wrong.
Since I'm getting older, my memory isn't as sharp anymore.
You're still lying.
[Interrogation Record]
Do you feel guilty toward Chen Bin
for the miscarriage?
Han Qing,
don't think
knowing someone's privacy
gives you the right to act recklessly.
That's why you've been indulging him,
letting him mess around outside,
then secretly investigating those mistresses
and cleaning them up regularly.
I'm just trying to
keep the man I love
close to me as much as possible.
Can you do that? You can't.
You don't even dare to bring it up.
Sorry,
I'm not interested in your privacy.
These are all things your sister
forced into my ears.
Let me put it this way.
I know nothing
about Bai Xiaohui.
As for my relationship with Bai Xiaohui,
if you're interested,
go investigate it yourself.
[Men's Perfume]
Boss,
you were right.
That female police officer really showed up.
Notify our men
to keep an eye on her.
If she discovers anything,
make her disappear
like we've done before.
[Mi Xiaohu]
What's the rush? What do you need from me?
Oh, right, Qing,
do you remember Taotao?
Yes, I do.
You said he inquired about Qiu Hailong's address,
right?
I ran into him on the street just now.
It seemed like he was going to buy drugs from someone.
He was acting suspiciously all the way.
I followed him here
and saw him go inside.
He's definitely not getting away this time.
Where is he?
[Wuma Street No. 8]
Don't move!
I...
If I hadn't slipped, you wouldn't have caught me.
Let me tell you,
back in middle school,
I was the sprint champion.
Try using drugs for two more years and see.
Even an old lady could catch you. Get up.
Ouch!
Be gentle!
Han Qing.
Where have you been?
Captain Fang,
I caught the person who was inquiring about
Qiu Hailong's address.
Who is it?
It's a street drug dealer with the nickname "Chun."
He had a drug user named Taotao
inquire about Qiu Hailong's address.
He confessed everything.
Does the name Chun
ring a bell?
Captain Fang,
we've gathered information
on the street-level drug dealers,
but we don't know much
about this particular person.
Ask our colleagues in the Anti-drug Unit.
Got it.
Do we have a photo,
or do we know what he looks like?
No.
Taotao has never seen him.
They only made transactions through WeChat.
Chun sent Taotao a live stream link.
[Witch Lisa's Live Stream Room]
After Taotao entered the live stream room,
[San Taizi: Do you know about the Rolling Stone Disco in Dongzhou?]
he would find transaction code words in the comments
and then go to the specified location
to complete the deal.
There are two people who have sold drugs
to Taotao.
One is a young boy wearing a snapback cap.
He usually makes the deal
with his back turned.
The other is a young girl with ear studs.
She's with the boy in the snapback cap.
When Chun asked Taotao to inquire about Qiu Hailong's address,
he gave him a phone number.
He told him
not to call unless absolutely necessary.
This is the number.
[Mobile Organizational Chart]
5974 is Chun's number.
Qiu Hailong died from high-purity drugs.
Chun asked Taotao to inquire about
Qiu Hailong's address.
Chun is a lower-level operative under 1508.
1508 is a lower-level operative under 6940.
If Chun is a street-level drug dealer,
then 1508
[Mobile Organizational Chart]
must be a major drug dealer in the city,
and 6940
must be a regional-level drug lord.
[Mobile Organizational Chart]
This is why they have
high-purity heroin
that we can't get on the market.
In other words,
the people who killed Qiu Hailong, Fan Lingling,
and kidnapped Bai Xiaohui
could be part of this secret drug trafficking group
we've never heard of
in Dongzhou.
We should investigate further,
following the lead of Zhang Yong and Chen Bin.
They are very likely
involved with this drug trafficking group.
[Mobile Organizational Chart]
[You're being followed by the police.]