(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2=
=Episode 6 (Part 2)=
(Queenstown's Heartbeat Journey)
(New Zealand, Queenstown)
Let's go.
This...
The weather is perfect today.
Beautiful.
Lin Yi.
Xingxu.
Morning.
Are you two on your honeymoon?
Couple time.
So nice.
There is even a fitness area here.
Lat pulldown, see?
Yeah.
I know.
How to use? Sit down and pull it?
It's that kind of...
You know, that kind of...
Swing.
Horizontal hover.
Like this.
(Fitness boy starts training instantly)
Right.
This tests your core strength.
Not bad.
Lin Yi's feet
can shuffle around on the ground.
(Long legs with nowhere to rest)
Lin Yi looks super bright today.
Handsome.
I had a good rest.
I meant the clothes.
Fei.
Hi.
Morning, Fei.
Morning.
Eggplant Spirit.
(That's so charming)
Don't.
Purple sweet potato.
Say something nicer.
You're a bit handsome today.
Rat Spirit.
[*Sounds like "purple sweet potato" in Chinese]
Ox Spirit.
Tiger Spirit.
Rabbit Spirit.
(An impromptu verbal flourish for you)
Let's go.
Let me show you around our place.
Welcome to our home.
This is our home.
It is so cozy.
It's really nice.
This was drawn
by the original owner's kid.
So cute.
Come and sit for a bit.
Would you like some tea?
Go make some quickly.
(Duke mode activated)
You're a guest now that you're here.
Okay.
Let's go.
What's up with you?
Let me see and touch it.
It's so perky today.
Really.
It could prop up a bottle of soda.
My pelvis tilts forward.
Why are you dressed so pink today?
At an older age...
Dressing fancy even at an older age.
I really want a bowl of noodles.
Me too.
Eat before jumping.
If you eat noodles before jumping,
they will come out of your nose.
Yesterday, we already overlooked
the magnificent scenery
of Milford Sound.
Next,
we will push our limits,
break through ourselves
and gain courage in extreme challenges.
Today, we'll build up our energy first,
test the waters,
and experience paragliding
and hang gliding.
Let's set off.
(Just thinking about it feels amazing)
Are you going to do it?
I can't do it.
I really don't dare to do it.
(Honglei is scared)
I'm just scared.
You go ahead.
What about you?
I definitely won't do it.
Tsk.
Boring.
(Tsk?)
I've done it before.
You've tried before,
so why are you scared now?
Precisely because I've done it before,
I'm never doing it again.
It scared me.
(Jingfei is scared)
(Thinking...)
How about I join you?
(Naiwen is also scared)
I can't decide between the paraglider
and the hang glider.
(This one even wants both)
Actually, the hang glider
is a bit scarier.
I'll go for the hang glider.
(Excited)
We're here.
(Arriving at the paragliding
and hang gliding experience base)
Let's go.
So cool.
This is so cool.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Cool, so handsome.
It looks fine.
This paraglider should also...
Also...
(Language system has malfunctioned)
What are you talking about?
Mom, it's a bit scary.
What's so scary?
I'll jump straight off.
Jump straight off without any glider.
I'll go with the hang glider.
(Ten minutes ago)
I definitely won't do it.
I'm brave now.
(Jingfei feels confident again)
You feel confident again?
Yeah.
Feeling confident all of a sudden?
I think I can handle it.
Back to confidence.
(So brave all of a sudden?)
Nice one, Jingfei!
You're awesome, bro.
I've checked out this slope.
I can sprint down.
I'll go with the paraglider.
(Naiwen got confidence too)
(What made you confident
all of a sudden?)
I'll go with the hang glider.
(Honglei can do it too)
Just now, in the car, Honglei...
(Ten minutes ago)
I really don't dare to do it.
I'll check with the coach later,
as long as I land
without injury.
(The only one afraid of heights,
Wry smile)
(Decided to challenge +1)
Then just do it.
I'll try it.
Anything is fine. Let them pick first.
Paraglider.
Hang glider.
(Paragliding: Li Naiwen, Liu Yuning,
Chen Xingxu, Wang Yuwen)
(Hang gliding: Sun Honglei, Guo Jingfei,)
Hang gliding, never tried it before.
(Lin Yi, Zhou Ye)
Then let's put on the gear.
(Expectant, Excited)
This is a hang glider.
Yeah.
So who's flying with me?
Honglei.
Okay.
You fly with me?
Nice to meet you.
Hold it like this.
And put your feet
through these leglets. Yeah.
Yes, one, two.
Put that up nice and high.
Honglei.
You said you wouldn't do it,
but now you are all geared up.
Love it.
(Happy face)
(Anxious hands)
Sir.
- Yes?
- No problem?
No problem.
Okay.
(Stretch the hands and shake the feet)
(Spin left three times,
then right three times)
(Everything is ready)
You're copying me again, copycat.
Do you know why I chose the hang glider?
No.
Because I'm Lin Yi.
(Yi = Yi)
[*"Hang glider" pronounced as "Hua Xiang Yi"]
I guessed that.
If your name were Lin Xiang,
would you choose the paraglider?
[*"Paraglider" pronounced as "Hua Xiang San"]
My name is Lin San.
Lin San.
Hello, man.
How are you?
Nice to meet you.
Good.
What's your name?
Nice to meet you.
Naiwen.
(Truly call him Never)
Naiwen, I'm Andreas.
Never give up.
(179 Boy's slogan)
Fantastic. There you go.
How are you?
(Still mentally preparing)
No. Not fine.
Not fine?
I'm scared.
You are scared? Why?
First time.
This is your first?
Yeah, first time.
I say one, two, three.
One, two, three.
You walk.
Walk.
Two.
And then run together.
Run together.
We two together.
Together.
Yes.
(Fluent bilingual communication)
Together.
Run together.
Okay.
Okay?
Alright.
(I can do it)
Okay.
You can do it.
(I can do it)
Yes, I can do it.
You can do it.
Alright? Go for it.
(Goofball)
Go for it.
Hehe.
This is for you here.
Okay.
It's actually fine.
Not bad.
Close up. I love your colors.
Very nice.
Thank you.
Like a backpack now.
No, like a backpack, like this.
Okay.
How is it, Yuning?
Not bad. Okay.
Is this your first time?
Yeah.
Yes, okay.
I'm fifty-one years old.
(You can't tell, right?)
Okay. Good job.
Super young.
(You read my mind)
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sixty.
Really?
Good diet.
(Just kidding)
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ron.
Hello.
Chen.
I'm Yuwen.
Yuwen.
Yes.
Do you want a roller coaster?
I want it.
(Going for the hard mode)
You want upside down?
You want it?
Okay.
I'm not nervous.
(Fully anticipating)
When I say,
"One, two, three"...
(Chinese speaker)
You can speak Chinese.
Run fast, run together.
I want to follow him.
Thanks, I want to follow him.
I'll follow you.
Yeah.
- Okay.
- No problem.
Should I go first?
(Can't wait a second)
We're first.
We're first, okay.
Alright, I'll watch you guys.
Okay.
Come on, Yuning.
I can do it.
We'll be down there with you.
Don't say such unlucky words.
"We'll be down there with you."
No.
I'll give you a little knock.
(Tease Fluffy to relieve stress)
Are you afraid of heights?
Yes.
You're afraid of heights, but still
daring to try this? You're amazing.
Okay, Xingxu is about to fly.
Who's about to fly?
Xingxu goes first. Awesome.
Xingxu.
Go for it, Honglei.
Love you.
Okay, are you ready?
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Three, two, one.
Walking forward.
(Shooting with full safety backup)
It just pulled him right up.
So cool.
Yeah.
Run.
So exhilarating.
Cool.
Not bad.
It looks like he's flying on his own.
Yes.
Okay.
Good.
Chen, welcome to my office.
Where? Where is your office?
It's right here.
Good.
It's so beautiful here.
We got panoramic views.
It's remarkable.
Look.
Across the valley,
there are the big mountains.
Queenstown is behind us.
Queenstown Lake to our right.
Right.
And we're flying this way to Arrowtown.
Cool.
See, it's actually not scary.
So cool.
Ready?
Yeah.
Go for it, Nai.
Easy.
Feeling good?
Excited?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's do it.
I'm covered in goosebumps.
(Deep breath)
Alright, three, two, one, walking.
Go for it, Nai.
Yeah.
Run.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Yuning.
Let's go.
(Not afraid)
(Still afraid)
Yuning, go for it.
Go for it, Yuning.
Are you ready to go, my friend?
I'm ready.
(I can do it)
Okay.
Launching.
Let's start walking.
Walk.
Beautiful.
Run.
Come on.
Very good.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Awesome.
(Hang gliding team ready for takeoff)
Are you ready?
Ready.
(Hold tight to the coach)
Okay.
Take a breath.
(Feeling nervous in sync)
Are you ready?
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Run.
(Hang gliding team departs)
High five.
Okay.
Keep running.
I'm like a bird.
Bird.
Great.
First time in my life.
Hang gliding challenge successful.
Thanks to my decision.
How did you like your first flight?
Yes, I love it.
I love it so much.
Great!
Is it fun?
Yes.
So much fun.
Do you want to drive?
No.
I can teach you.
Okay.
Very easy.
Do you want to try?
I'll hold the camera. Look.
Okay.
Hold this one.
Take the other one here.
Like this.
Yeah.
Alright. So look.
Your hands up.
It's like full speed,
okay?
Okay.
And when you pull
one of them like this. Look.
If we pull the right side,
let's go right.
Pull this one like this.
And this one up like this.
Yeah.
Now, let's go to the left.
- Come on!
- Come on.
Let's go there now.
Okay, go.
(Surrendered your courage to the clouds
and the sky is within your reach)
Very good.
Ah!
(The hang gliding team
is totally showing off their skills)
Ah!
So excited.
(Zhou Ye, Lin Yi)
Oh, wow!
Aha!
(Wang Yuwen, Lin Yi)
There's wind!
(Chen Xingxu, Wang Yuwen)
Oh, my!
Very good riding!
Okay.
Do you like it?
Very good.
It's okay, not that scary.
It's just not very high off the ground.
So it's okay.
I feel like I can do it again.
Looking down is amazing.
This is much more comfortable
than my first skydive.
This is more stable.
And it really feels like a bird.
I want to know
why you can speak Chinese.
You learn?
Ah, my ex-girlfriend.
Oh, no, man?
Your ex-girlfriend?
Yes, she's from China.
Oh, so...
I know a little bit.
Well...
I love you.
I love you, babe.
I know Chinese...
I love you, baby. Right?
Yes.
I know there's a Chinese song.
♪I want to fly higher♪
Yes, I can fly higher.
- ♪I want to fly higher♪
- ♪Fly higher♪
Alright, we're going
to start getting ready for landing.
Okay?
Okay.
(Landing point)
Say bye-bye then.
Bye-bye.
Here?
Yeah. Just here.
Okay.
Feet up.
Stand.
Perfect landing.
Perfect landing, high five.
Yeah!
Okay.
Stand up.
Yeah, I did it.
We did it.
Yes.
So exhilarating.
So exhilarating, guys.
So thrilling.
Yes, we landed.
Okay.
Take a few steps.
Run.
How was it, Nai?
So exhilarating.
Right?
No feeling of weightlessness at all.
Not at all.
Very interesting.
And he took me around for a long time.
Awesome.
I saw you guys swaying
back and forth in the middle.
You made it, my friends.
Yeah.
Goodbye, congratulations.
Thank you.
No worries.
Thanks.
Is that Yuning?
Yes.
He's doing good.
He's good.
He must be very happy now.
He conquered it.
Yuning.
How was it?
Great.
Okay, get ready to take
a couple of steps.
Okay.
Stand up.
Get up.
Take a few steps.
Okay.
How was it?
Not bad.
Exhilarating.
Very fun.
How was it, my friend?
You saved my life.
Thank you.
You are the best.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
It's okay. Alright.
It's just not that scary.
No.
Not even a bit of weightlessness.
Yeah, no weightlessness.
None at all.
But I kept crying up there.
No.
Tears kept streaming down.
It was due to the wind.
Hang glider.
It's already coming down.
Can you tell who it is?
It's Lin Yi.
Lin Yi.
Such a long strip of a white person.
Come on.
So smooth.
It's a bit like
an airplane's trajectory.
It has wheels.
Nice one.
(Brake by chest)
Cool.
Cool!
How was it?
Thrilling?
Great.
It got thrilling
when coming down at the end.
Yeah.
So cool.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, sir.
Who is this?
It's probably Ye.
Only she can make that whistling sound.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
How was it?
Exhilarating.
People just can't resist being egged on.
I had it all figured out in the room.
No way I was going to glide.
But once I got here,
I thought, "Why not?"
Since everyone is doing it.
Challenge is successful.
Happy.
(Wang Yuwen, Oreo Fresh Ambassador)
The World Vlog, action!
Don't forget
the Wow The World gift pack.
It's Oreo!
Twist
to unlock a fresh day.
Give it a lick.
(Sweet but not cloying)
You can even dunk it.
(An ultimate flavor upgrade)
Come join the fun.
(Lick)
Twist open an Oreo,
(Dunk)
and we're instantly connected.
Delicious.
Fun.
Fun and Delicious Oreo!
(Play with Oreo)
Next,
we'll head to the next location,
Cromwell.
Let's go.
(Arrived at Cromwell)
We're here.
Let's go.
This is beautiful.
How can he drive so smoothly?
Isn't it usually bumpy?
It's not the sea.
The sea has waves.
That's why it's bumpy.
It'll only be bumpy in the sea.
Yeah.
The Cromwell town where we are now
was once a major mining town
born from the gold rush.
Due to the construction of a dam,
the original commercial center here
was submerged at the bottom
of a man-made lake.
(Cromwell is a historic heritage town in New Zealand)
The old buildings we see now
(It shows New Zealand's pioneering era)
were moved here from the original town
for tourists to experience
the gold rush history
of the 19th century.
Today's Cromwell
is famous for its
fruit growing industry.
It's known
as the "Fruit Bowl of the South"
and the "Gateway to Queenstown".
Today, we're also going to have
a fruit-related challenge here.
It's called the "Lemon Queen Chase".
Okay.
(Lemon Queen Chase)
There are two groups of four people.
Each person carries a balloon.
Each group designates
one "Lemon Queen" internally.
Pop the opposing team's
balloon of "Lemon Queen",
and you win.
If you attack the wrong person,
the attacker is eliminated.
So, it's actually still a game
of figuring out who the Queen is.
Right.
Every three minutes,
you must feed your team's Lemon Queen
a slice of lemon.
If you exceed the time limit,
the Lemon Queen's identity
will be immediately revealed.
During the process,
finding a surprise lemon
can exempt you from eating a lemon once.
The surprise lemon
(It's me, Chewy Lemon)
is a lemon you can chew and drink.
Now, form your own groups.
Then let's just split into two sides.
How about we draw lots?
Drawing lots is fun.
Let's draw.
Yeah.
Because I haven't seen
Honglei and Naiwen
on the same team for a long time.
(Just here for the show)
(Missing their sweet bickering)
Since Fei came,
the two of them have been split up.
Yeah.
Yes. It's been a while.
Come on. I'll draw first.
I'll take one too.
You take one.
Come on.
Open it and see.
I'm One.
You're Lin Yi.
I'm Zero.
What about you?
One.
You two are in a group.
We two are in a group.
The two "old timers" really
are in a group.
Forming groups by age?
(Average Age: over 50)
How are we supposed to play this?
Who else is One?
Come on, Ye.
You really are One?
This time,
your mission is heavy.
(Green Team: Honglei, Naiwen, Jingfei, Zhou Ye
Yellow Team: Yuning, Xingxu, Yuwen, Lin Yi)
(One supporting three)
Oh, my!
How can the three of you catch us?
(Liu Yuning: A tall guy,
fresh air at 1.9 m)
(Lin Yi, Beijing Sport University,
defending the six-pack abs honor)
(Chen Xingxu, fitness pro
120kg bench press, all-round athlete)
(Wang Yuwen, bold yet meticulous,
a smart and fearless girl)
We'll just run them around.
We'll just keep running.
We're right here.
Come and catch me.
This is a game of wits.
Right.
But when it comes to physical fights,
think about it, for example,
if we were to fight
these three gentlemen,
we might not even defeat them.
That's true. We can't.
They've eaten more rice
than we have salt.
Exactly.
We must eat really salty.
That sounds more and more off.
Right?
Yuning suddenly became so humble.
I was afraid you'd feel uncomfortable.
But it's even more lethal now.
We are going
to consider their feelings, right?
High EQ.
(Fine)
Don't force a bitter smile.
(Braving it out)
She is forcing a bitter smile.
Zhou Ye,
we will win for you.
Just watch.
Okay, guys.
Come on.
Let's each discuss our tactics, okay?
(Fighting spirit ignited)
Could you please leave for a moment?
Okay, no problem, Honglei.
Good luck, friends.
(Gloating)
Don't lose too fast.
No matter whether it's him,
I'll pop his balloon first.
This looks like that scene
from Red Dead Redemption.
The place where they buy horses, right?
Let's find a shady spot.
(Battle plan deployment)
Personally, I think
the Lemon Queen of their team
will probably
be Fei.
Liu Yuning has long arms and legs.
Right.
You can't even reach his balloon.
If Liu Yuning holds the balloon,
how can you pop it?
He's 1.9 meters tall.
He'll just dodge back and forth
like this.
He'll run you around.
Yeah.
If Liu Yuning holds it up this high,
who can reach it?
Right.
(The Yellow Team
has a significant advantage)
Who should we choose?
Think about ourselves first.
You.
Me?
I'm old. I can't run much.
(Saying this)
That's why you should be the Queen.
No.
We need someone who can run.
Then this one. He can run.
(You run)
You do it.
I...
He's strong and fit.
(He runs)
Full of energy.
You are from a sports university.
(It still takes someone
from a sports university to run)
From sports university...
Do I look like one?
(Yes, you really look like one)
You do it.
You really look like an athlete.
No, do I look like a Queen?
If...
(Is that really the point?)
It doesn't matter if you look like Queen.
Not important.
We just...
You run fast.
As long as you act well, it's fine.
(Yellow Team designated
the Lemon Queen: Lin Yi)
That team is definitely full of tricks.
(As you expected)
Don't overthink them.
You go eavesdrop first.
Right?
I think this game
is just a two-step move.
Just yes or no.
Now, just forget about it.
Now, just remember, "I'm the Queen."
The Queen.
(A false alarm)
(Something's off)
We'll count on you this round.
You need to run properly.
You better run, hear me?
Well...
Right.
(Awkward eye contact)
(Oh, this is so English)
You naughty one.
Naiwen is over there.
He's been listening.
(Completely exposed)
Now we need to switch.
Who did they choose?
Did you overhear?
At first, they chose...
It should be Lin Yi.
Now I think they switched
to another person.
Sure enough, full of tricks.
Where's your balloon?
(Many more tricks up their sleeves
Green Team's Strategy 1: Balloon Vanishing Art)
This way, I can free my hands.
Let's first find a big piece of cloth.
Cover up and eat.
Yeah, cover up and eat.
(Green Team's Strategy 2:
Mouth Shape Vanishing Art)
Got it.
Let's do this.
So for this round, who will it be Queen?
Naiwen.
I'll be the Queen.
(Green Team's designated Lemon Queen:
Li Naiwen)
(Alert)
Keep your voice down.
(Among us four, who will be the Queen?)
You.
Not me.
Fei and I are the same.
We'll be noticed.
They'll think we're the ones
to play tricks.
Xingxu then.
Why can't it be you?
I can't hide my expressions.
Honglei will see right through me
and know I'm lying.
Oh, no, I just feel...
Xingxu is the same.
Xingxu can't hide
his expressions either.
I don't look like a good guy.
We're really done for.
Three people can't hide
their expressions.
This one can't hide their expressions,
and this one is naive.
As for me, I don't look like a good guy.
And you...
(Self-evaluation)
My mind goes blank, right?
Not really.
I can't hide my expressions either.
(No one can hide their thoughts)
But this is our advantage.
They won't know who it is at all.
Can we all just show our expressions?
We all look very worried,
and we just run away from the start.
That can be a tactic.
(Yellow Team Strategy: Everyone runs to confuse)
All of us will run.
Just see...
In terms of stamina,
they won't defeat us.
Yeah.
Let's do this.
You will be "Queen" this round.
I'll be "Queen".
(New Lemon Queen: Chen Xingxu)
(Eavesdropping again)
You will be "Queen" this round.
I'll be "Queen".
You be it this round.
(Hearing the key information:
Their Lemon Queen is Chen Xingxu)
In this universe,
I have the super brain.
Zhou Ye,
we will win for you.
Just watch.
(The hero returns)
Xingxu.
(Syncing the latest intel)
But their tactic is to run.
We can choose not to chase them.
So when the time comes,
they have to come to us.
Okay.
Then we will defeat him.
(Victory is assured)
(Unaware of being exposed)
You can make the first move
and pop someone's.
It's best to use your "life" to test it.
For example,
you pop Zhou Ye's.
If she's not,
okay then,
she won't catch up to us three.
Right?
Then I should first pop the balloon
of someone who can catch up to you guys.
(You mean...)
Who can catch up to us?
Actually, none of them...
Indeed, they can't catch up.
We are young and beautiful.
How could we lose?
(Liu Yuning, Chen Xingxu, Yuwen, Lin Yi)
The Lemon Queen Chase
(VS. Sun Honglei, Naiwen, Jingfei, Zhou Ye)
now begins.
Run, kids!
(Strictly implementing
the random running plan)
(Entering the game and probing roles)
You can make the first move and pop someone's.
(One strike hit the real Queen)
(Our Queen is in danger)
You scared me too much.
(Pretending to play around)
You are so stupid.
Why?
You just run.
If we don't chase you,
(Calmly defusing)
you would come to us.
That makes sense.
I won't run anymore.
(Suspicion level decreased)
(I'll run then)
Xingxu.
Then we will defeat him.
(Coming to them)
(Heading straight for their Queen)
It's him.
Stop Xingxu.
(Seeing off with a gaze)
(My stamina is already exhausted)
He is really running.
Fine, I won't follow him anymore.
Let him run by himself
and wear himself out.
(The physical tactic
is beginning to show results)
Attention.
Lemon feeding time in the first round
has only one minute left.
(Lemon Queen Li Naiwen
needs to be fed lemon)
(Confirming the opponent
has been invisible)
Jingfei.
(Suspicious)
(But not too suspicious)
(Calmly passing by)
(Without looking sideways)
Lemon, give it to me.
(Mission to feed lemon slices
within three minutes completed)
(It's about hiding in plain sight)
Now randomly showing
surprise lemon.
Find and drink it,
and you can avoid lemon feeding once.
(Looking for the surprise lemon)
Where is it?
(Passing by and feeding another bite)
(Love it after just three bites!)
(The Yellow Team is exempted
from lemon feeding once)
(I'm chewing the lemon)
Go for Xingxu.
I think Xingxu is very suspicious.
(Unaware of being exposed)
Come on.
Go for Xingxu.
(Running first)
(Launching like a bullet
as a sports university graduate)
(Sports university graduate coming to rescue)
It's him.
Stop Xingxu.
(Guarding)
He can't run away. Block him this way.
Lin Yi got eliminated.
(Lin Yi got eliminated)
What happened?
Lin Yi got eliminated. Why?
Wait.
(No way?)
Who?
Whose balloon got popped?
Lin Yi got eliminated.
He can't run away.
Block him this way.
(Where's my big balloon?)
(Balloon exploded)
Lin Yi got eliminated.
From sports university...
You can run quickly.
You really look like an athlete.
Why?
It popped by itself.
Why...
This grass has thorns.
(It backstabbed me)
We're right here.
Come chase me!
We'll just lead them around.
We'll just keep running.
I'm so useless.
We are young and beautiful.
How could we lose?
(I have my own way of losing)
Are you an idiot?
I am.
(Leaving with regret)
I just got fired up
and then got extinguished.
Became cannon fodder.
(Liu Yuning, Sun Honglei, Chen Xingxu, Li Naiwen VS. Sun Honglei, Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei, Zhou Ye)
Lemon Queen Chase.
It must be Chen Xingxu.
Alright, now we have the advantage.
(The Yellow Team lost
one of its key players)
(Pressing the advantage)
Which way is the road over there?
He can run through.
It's him. He can't run away.
Block him this way.
(Lemon Queen in danger)
It must be Chen Xingxu.
He is very good at running.
(Turning around and running)
No need to chase him.
It's not Liu Yuning.
I'll go down to look.
Find a lemon drink.
Are you the one, Ye?
I am.
Then I'll pop it.
Go ahead.
Give it back to me.
Whose balloon?
Ye's.
Can you revive me with that?
Tell me who the Queen is.
If you don't tell me,
I'll pop it now.
Buddies.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
She doesn't dare to pop it.
(I dare not pop it?)
Tell me, is it you?
Can I pop it?
Pop it.
She's getting anxious.
Perhaps she's pretending to be anxious.
(Dare not speak)
(Is it you, Ye?)
You can make the first move
and pop someone's.
It's best to use your life to test it.
Quick, pop it.
Quick.
(Wrong attack)
Wang Yuwen eliminated.
(Lemon Queen Chase:
Liu Yuning, Chen Xingxu, Wang Yuwen, Lin Yi VS. Sun Honglei, Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei, Zhou Ye)
(I find it good)
I'll drink this first.
(The Green Team is exempted
from lemon feeding once)
(Yellow Team lost two key players)
What about the two of them then?
We can't go on, right?
It's okay,
you are much more valuable than me.
We are young and beautiful.
Why are we so timid and useless?
I'm young and reckless.
I'm too reckless.
(Young but reckless)
You are too reckless.
We will win.
(Believe it first)
(Zhou Ye, Chen Xingxu, Guo Jingfei,
Liu Yuning, Li Naiwen, Sun Honglei)
(Green Team initiates final attack)
Whatever, let's take out Chen Xingxu first.
Okay.
(Targeting the opponent's Lemon Queen)
(Outflanking from the front)
(Chen Xingxu's balloon slips)
Pop it!
Pop it.
(Observing from a distance away)
Chen Xingxu's balloon popped.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't sit here, get up to go.
Go down from here.
(Chen Xingxu's balloon popped,
whole team eliminated?)
(Lemon Queen Chase)
Guo Jingfei eliminated.
Oh, no.
So they know who it is now.
I told you it's Liu Yuning.
We are young and beautiful.
How could we lose?
No.
Me.
(The real Lemon Queen: Liu Yuning)
We are so young and beautiful.
(Taking out lemon for feeding)
They are down there.
(Stuffed directly into the mouth)
(Mission to feed lemon slices
within three minutes completed)
Pretend to eat.
(Full of details)
(Zhou Ye's POV)
They are down there.
(Witnessed the whole
lemon feeding process)
Liu Yuning.
Buddies.
(Process all wrong, results all right)
Chen Xingxu was taking out lemon
to give to Liu Yuning, really.
I saw it.
(Stuffing a lemon in mouth by the way)
Buddies.
Not Chen Xingxu, it's Liu Yuning.
I think it's Liu Yuning.
Because Liu Yuning...
Just now Chen Xingxu
took something out
and gave it to Liu Yuning.
(But what was that I heard?)
Him taking out lemon
doesn't mean it's him.
I told you it's Liu Yuning.
I'm over here.
I'm blocking him from here.
(Lemon Queen hiding alone)
(Chen Xingxu, Li Naiwen, Liu Yuning,
Zhou Ye, Sun Honglei)
(Encircling Liu Yuning
from all directions)
Bro, you can't outrun me.
Catch Liu Yuning, go catch Liu Yuning.
(Indeed can't outrun)
It's okay.
Liu Yuning is out of lemons.
When three minutes are up.
(You take a bite first)
(Precise encirclement)
Yuning.
Take him down first.
Brilliant.
(Liu Yuning's balloon slips)
It slipped.
Quick.
Pop that.
Yuning's balloon flew down.
Pop it here.
Quick, pop it.
You pop it.
Okay.
(Sun Honglei, Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei,
and Zhou Ye have won)
Complete victory.
Didn't expect that, right?
Didn't expect that, huh?
So weak.
So tired.
This is our Loser Corner.
What are you doing here?
This place is only for losers
to stay.
I'll leave then.
This is called the Elimination Cage.
Xingxu,
come hide in here.
(Assembled)
We are young and beautiful.
Now we're young and reckless.
(I feel I'm being reckless)
How does that saying go?
Donkey dung shines
on the surface, right?
Yeah, donkey dung.
So who among you is the one?
I'm dying of sourness.
The two of them...
(Sourness unknown to anyone else)
Those few
fed me a bite every few seconds.
They fed me a bite every few seconds.
(Time's up, take a bite)
(Passing by, take a bite)
(Analyzing clues, take a bite)
(Almost ending, take a bite)
(Sneaking a bite in the chaos)
Don't worry, just take a bite first.
Meticulous care.
Who popped yours?
Don't ask me, bro.
Well, who did you switch with?
A plant.
(A plant)
He popped his own balloon.
Popped his own.
It's okay.
After walking around society,
I found young people nowadays
are super weak.
(Super weak)
Totally.
This...
- Crushing.
- Dimensionality reduction attack.
Alright.
We have already won.
Let's not humiliate the opponents
like this anymore.
They were trying
to taking care of our health.
- Of course.
- Right?
Of course.
Lin Yi said
he just got fired up
and then got extinguished.
Our styling also beat you guys.
Look.
With our four
stunningly beautiful faces,
it would be a pity to cover them up.
Yuwen.
(Only the mouth is stubborn)
Covering them, and the ratings will drop a bit.
Right.
Covering them,
and the ratings will drop a bit.
Okay, let's go back and rest for a bit.
That was really tiring.
Your training wasn't for nothing.
You run really fast.
(Energy is long gone)
I can't run anymore.
The game was really thrilling.
Compared to feeding lemons,
I still prefer
Yili Yoghurt's Chewy Lemon.
(Tempted)
You can taste the lemon juice
(Pulp and peel)
and chew on the pulp and peel.
Chew and drink,
sour and refreshing with substance.
Gets better with each bite.
(Agreeing)
Indeed.
I like it.
Cheers.
Let's go. let's go.
Let's go back and eat.
(Returning to the B&B)
Let's eat.
Dig in.
It's okay, I'll go over and pick some.
What do you want?
I'll get it for you.
I want that.
Got it.
Give me your fork.
Thank you.
So tender.
Delicious.
This is so delicious.
Not bad.
Really quite good.
So delicious.
Really tasty.
Today's meals are also very tasty.
This potato has a sunflower seed flavor.
It really does.
You described it very accurately.
The potato?
Yeah, very tasty.
She described it quite aptly.
It's because of the milky flavor.
(Savor carefully)
It's really the flavor
of sunflower seeds.
Sunflower seed flavor.
Isn't it?
I didn't taste it.
What flavor do you taste?
Describe it.
Just potato.
Besides potato flavor?
That's it.
You can't ask him.
He, he only guesses.
(Very understanding)
Because he can't taste any flavor.
I'm full.
How about we pursue a bit more?
Where?
Look, Guo Jingfei is numb from winning.
He has no feeling at all anymore.
Really? Is that so?
We let you down, Jingfei.
I never wanted to win.
(Look at that)
Look, it just happened.
These younger brothers and sisters
aren't quite up to it.
In the spoilers, they said
whenever they see
the three of us together,
we must have lost
and are receiving punishment.
(Great reputation)
It was the first time
I saw a killing intent
in Xingxu's eyes.
Such a well-behaved kid.
Before you were about to do it,
you stared me
with those big fluffy eyes.
Fluffy.
Cute but fierce.
(Fluffy)
Xingxu ran so much he lost weight today.
We sweated a lot today.
Really.
Lin Yi and I didn't sweat a drop.
You didn't sweat, right?
(Keep it down, okay?)
I have nowhere to sweat from.
Why are you so happy?
No, he said he is
from a sports university.
He needs
to show his specialty.
Besides, Lin Yi runs incredibly fast.
So if we want him to run,
even if you try to catch him, you can't.
As long as he runs...
I'm so fast.
I was so fast that near me,
a sonic boom occurred,
which just popped
my balloon.
Naiwen.
So tragic.
In order to win,
actually eating one every three minutes
is enough.
But he ate one every three seconds.
(Extreme desire to win)
He just kept on eating.
Trying to sustain his life.
Why eat so much?
Nervous.
I was afraid
that if I didn't eat on time, I'd lose.
It's like when you only used 2%
of your battery,
and you just charged it, right?
Charged it, yes.
Just opened WeChat,
charge.
Everyone is almost done eating, right?
Yeah.
Today, everyone completed
the extreme challenge
of paragliding and hang gliding.
Next, we'll switch arenas
and start Improvised Acting Showdown.
(Improvised Acting Showdown: Everyone improvises under the given scenario. The two groups assign roles themselves and determine a bomb topic for the other group.
During the performance, if any member of the other group mentions that topic, that member is eliminated)
For each round of the game,
we will give different scenarios.
Members need to be split
into two groups of four.
You will engage
in improvised performance
under the given scenario.
Each group will determine a bomb topic.
For example,
if one side's bomb topic is numbers,
once someone in the opposing camp
says a number,
that member is eliminated.
The eliminated person needs
to stay in the scenario,
stand up naturally and reasonably,
and stand behind the chair.
The scenario is as follows.
(Scenario)
The eldest and second eldest families of the Pretty Sheep family
are happily
having New Year's Eve dinner together.
Who knew, after three minutes of eating,
they start to fight
over the management rights
of Pretty Sheep Ranch.
An undercurrent of family conflict
officially begins.
(Deciding team division)
- Come on.
- Let's get one.
God of Variety.
Bless us.
Flip the card.
One.
We two are not in the same group.
Nope.
You are
with Honglei.
(Two naughty boys combined)
It's over.
I see that side is very strong.
(Team division: Liu Yuning, Li Naiwen, Chen Xingxu, Lin Yi
Sun Honglei, Zhou Ye, Wang Yuwen, Guo Jingfei)
We need to first
discuss a forbidden word.
We are talking
about management rights.
Should we
think of some
business-related topics?
Wouldn't the business aspect
be
a bit too narrow?
Should we have a specific one?
Maybe it's actually better.
Business plan.
Something plan-related.
Plan-related.
Is that a little evil?
Anything about plans.
As soon as they talk about
some kind of plan they have,
they lose.
(Bomb topic: Mentioning plans)
I'm the eldest sister.
This is my husband.
No, it's better if I play your son.
Because I can talk
about my dad's business.
Okay.
I'm the eldest brother.
You are the second brother.
I'll be the eldest brother.
Let's swap.
(Eldest son, Mom, Second daughter, Youngest son)
The eldest brother, second sister, youngest brother.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Alright.
I'll play the sheepdog.
(Broadening acting range)
Dog.
You can't even get on the table.
(Is there no dog-friendly restaurant?)
- Let's...
- Let's think of a sensitive word first.
Management.
I think intelligence is a very good one.
Okay.
(Bomb topic: related to intelligence)
But we shouldn't lead them to it.
Right, we must present ourselves
as extremely smart.
First, we defend.
(Tactic: Defense as offense)
Then you throw out some completely unrelated directions.
After chatting for a while,
they'll become numb.
They talk a lot.
(Clear weakness)
The more you say, the more mistakes you make, you know?
If they keep mentioning something,
you must pay attention.
Okay.
I'll play the eldest brother
with a bad memory.
(Enriching character details to lead opponents to elimination)
He will think,
"Is there something wrong
with your brain?"
Then I'm the dad.
(Dad)
You are the silly son.
(Eldest son)
Second silly son.
(Second son)
Third silly son.
(Third son, everyone is in the game)
Just like that.
Dad.
Mom.
That's it.
Exactly.
All silly sons.
(Ranch Family Feud)
(On a fine New Year's Eve night,)
(the eldest and second eldest families)
(of the Pretty Sheep family
are gathered here.)
(The undercurrent
of inheritance quietly surges.)
Come out, let's negotiate.
About what?
Let's enjoy
the New Year's Eve dinner first.
Come on, let's have a toast, come on.
Happy holidays.
Here.
Cheers.
Come on.
Happy Lantern Festival.
What time is it now?
(Taking the lead to ask)
(Alert)
Happy New Year.
What time is it now?
It's been a year since we last met.
(Not taking the bait)
Long time no see.
(Left team bomb topic: plan-related)
It's been a year since we saw each other.
(Right team bomb topic: intelligence-related)
I can't even tell who is who.
Let me introduce myself first.
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Sister's House,
Eldest Son Z Sheep)
My mom.
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Sister's House,
Eldest Sister Wen Sheep)
My second sister.
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Sister's House,
Second Daughter Ye Sheep)
My third brother.
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Sister's House,
Youngest Son Lei Sheep)
Hello, cousins.
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Brother's House, Eldest Brother Yuning Sheep)
This is my eldest son.
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Brother's House,
Eldest Son Yi Sheep)
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Brother's House, Second Son Xing Sheep)
My second son.
(Character details)
(Pretty Sheep Family, Eldest Brother's House, Youngest Son Nai Sheep)
Three sheep bring bliss.
Mom.
Yes.
("Foolish son" starts acting instantly)
What?
(Completely defenseless)
(Scheme loading)
You are...
I'm the eldest brother.
(What does it mean?)
You are the mom.
You're a fool.
(Guo Jingfei mentions intelligence,
triggering the bomb topic)
(Holding back, can't expose)
(Completely unaware)
Are you my older cousin
or my younger cousin?
Fei
got eliminated.
(Guo Jingfei eliminated)
(What did I say?)
(Holding it in)
(Keep a straight face, don't laugh)
(Emergency facial expression management)
How did this happen?
(The strongest brain
was eliminated first)
That was too rash.
I got it.
We can't ask
about the status of the three of them.
(Guess: Can't talk about the other party's status)
He called him a fool.
(Bomb topic in danger)
I know what they are up to.
You are so smart.
(Wang Yuwen mentions intelligence,
triggering the bomb topic)
(Surprise)
(Wait)
(Cheerful alone)
What did you just say?
Repeat your last sentence again.
Yuwen.
(Wang Yuwen eliminated)
Eliminated.
I realized what they were trying to do.
And then...
What?
(Goofy)
As soon as I said it, I knew
I definitely fell for it.
I had already...
The moment before, I had realized
what their trigger keyword
was.
And I said it.
Is it what I said?
(No hints)
You can't say anything else.
We can't praise them.
(Guess: Can't praise the other party)
We can't praise them for being smart.
Alright.
(Eliminated players must leave reasonably)
What happened to those two?
How come you just left
without saying a word?
(Never Out Of Character)
Where did they go?
We...
Went to eat grass.
Went to settle the accounts.
(Leave a hint, talk about the plan)
Went to look at our plan.
(Lei Sheep received)
I want to eat grass.
Who's in charge of your family now?
My second eldest sister.
I'm in charge.
Why?
(Questioning me?)
Because I'm smart.
(Zhou Ye mentions intelligence,
triggering the bomb topic)
Zhou Ye!
(Zhou Ye eliminated)
Ye is eliminated.
What happened?
(Standing up and cheering, goofy)
Our topic
can easily counterattack them.
(Don't worry, we will win)
But we only have him now.
(The only heir of the family)
I...
I can't even say less now
even if I wanted to.
Come on, say it.
Well, then,
who's in charge of your family now?
(I'm in charge)
(Youngest son Lei Sheep bears the heavy family responsibility,
the youngest in seniority but the oldest in age)
(You can do it, younger brother)
With that brain of yours now,
(Continuously guiding towards intelligence topic)
can you manage to be
the head of such a large business?
Do you know the main purpose
of our New Year's Eve dinner?
(Lei boy, believe in yourself)
Everyone, today let's talk
about the future.
(Guiding to talk about future plans)
What are you thinking for the future?
Let's talk.
I, I'm fine with anything.
You're fine with anything?
This also counts.
Fine, this intelligence.
(Sun Honglei mentioned intelligence, triggering the bomb topic)
It changed to him, right?
Are we still playing?
Honglei.
(Sun Honglei eliminated)
Eliminated.
(Couldn't hold back)
One topic was enough.
(Complete victory)
Impressive.
So impressive.
We acted as fools.
But they turned out to be the fools.
So impressive.
Lin Yi, what a great idea!
(Amazing)
Absolutely brilliant, Lin Yi.
The second scenario is
(Scenario)
a class reunion twenty years later.
Alright, okay.
A class reunion twenty years later.
Spread out, quickly!
Spread out!
Come on.
Truly brilliant.
Lin Yi is truly brilliant. Awesome.
Impressive.
Lin Yi is really young and promising,
full of achievements.
(Opponents are convinced)
Not only does he play the game well,
but he also accurately
grasped our personalities.
No talking
about trending internet memes.
(Extremely targeted)
Talk about gossip.
Gossip.
Emotional kind of stuff.
For this,
the entry will be slow.
But it's a bit interesting.
Fun.
(Bomb topic:
mentioning emotional gossip)
Here's something fun.
As long as you belittle someone.
(Bomb topic: saying bad things about the other party)
Belittling the other party.
It's written in their instincts.
Attack.
They love to attack.
(Mainly for the thrill of battle)
As we talk, they'll be finished.
Let's talk.
(Classmates)
(Students of Class 1, Senior Year, Earth High School,)
(after twenty years,)
(welcomed a long-awaited reunion.)
(Scenario reenactment, just for fun)
You four
came together?
You arranged this?
Everyone's here?
(Daring not to speak)
How long has it been since we last met?
(Left team's bomb topic: love gossip
Right team's bomb topic: trash-talk)
(Cautious and silent)
(Even more unrestrained)
How long has it been since we last met?
How many years has it been,
Ye?
(Suddenly targeted)
They're so cautious.
(The classmates dare not
recognize each other)
Fei.
What work are you doing now?
(Calm and composed)
First, tell me,
when we were in college,
did you steal my leather jacket?
I can only say I'm a collector.
(Responding calmly)
Did you collect my leather jacket?
I can only say I have some habits.
(I didn't see that)
I later asked many classmates,
and it was you
who took my leather jacket.
Alright,
let's not talk about it.
Why not talk about it?
(Actively igniting the gossip flame)
Everyone already knows.
So don't play dumb.
I deserve an explanation.
Right?
(On guard)
Talking like that embarrasses him.
Right, he...
We're all here.
Don't bring this up openly.
It's rare for us to gather like this.
Right?
Today we have to clarify things.
So you have a problem with him?
(Seizing the opportunity to counter-cue)
You three have a good relationship,
and you're isolating me.
Did you three do it together?
You four are a little clique.
(Such strong attack power)
I dare not respond to that.
This is a reunion.
Let's talk about happy things.
Yes.
Talk about something happy.
(Waiting for gossip)
What happy things are there?
(Coming back to that)
For example, that leather jacket.
Who do you say took it?
Whoever took
the leather jacket, let them.
(A table's full of schemers)
It's a gift to them.
What are you busy with these days?
What are you busy with?
(Opportunity knocks)
Busy with blind dates.
(Urgently managing emotions)
How did it go?
(Chen Xingxu bit the love gossip bait.
bomb topic triggered)
How did it go?
(Immediate assist)
Which one caught your eye?
He said I'm ugly.
What?
Slap him!
(Without any doubt, even empathizing)
What an awful person!
(Holding it in)
(I'm involved too?)
Lin Yi, back then you and who...
The big apple.
Rice.
Xingxu,
you're out.
(Chen Xingxu out)
(What did I say?)
I have diarrhea.
(Don't say it)
Slap him.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Let's have a drink.
Come on.
You guys drink.
(Daring not to move)
It's been years. Well...
What's wrong with you, Sun?
Sun?
(No idea.
We haven't rehearsed this part)
What's wrong with him?
(Gossip)
Look.
Take a good look.
Take another good look.
Why don't you even dare to speak?
We are dumbfounded.
We are captivated.
Captivated.
What's that?
What do you know?
You know nothing.
(Sun Honglei trash-talked,
triggering the bomb topic)
(Sun Honglei out)
Honglei, you're out.
It's over.
Let's not
dig our own grave.
The more words, the more mistakes.
(It wasn't all for nothing.
At least he got tired)
Come on, bro.
Too hardworking.
Did you go to move the car?
Where was Xingxu just now?
Where did he go?
You were blocking
the motor vehicle lane.
You're so quiet, Fei.
(Guo is quiet)
Back then in the class,
weren't you the most talkative?
Say something.
Well?
You even remember this?
(Catching a whiff of gossip)
Why do you remember it so clearly?
(Daring not to speak)
No reason.
He wrote a diary.
(Yes)
I wrote a diary.
What diary did you write?
(Do you even hear what you're asking?)
What diary?
What diary could there be?
(How to explain "diary" to you?)
What's there to explain about "diary"?
He wrote about chasing those girls.
Who chased girls?
(Li Naiwen talked about love gossip,
triggering the bomb topic)
Chased who?
It couldn't be me, right?
Ye in our class.
He couldn't get her.
And then...
He thought I sang too well.
Right.
He wanted to win me over.
(He's genuinely curious)
Then why couldn't he win you over?
Why?
Because at that time, there were
other boys who also liked her.
I just liked those
who sang worse than me.
Yes, she liked bad singers.
Who sang worse than you?
(Sensitive)
Make it clear.
You.
(Zhou Ye trash-talked,
triggering the bomb topic)
Ye and Nai,
(Li Naiwen and Zhou Ye out)
you're both out.
Double kill?
(Scary, right?)
What did you just say?
(What did I say?)
Who chased girls?
Chased who?
What did you say?
It seems like saying "like"
and "dislike" is not allowed.
(No comment)
What's wrong?
You drank too much?
He was blocking the motor vehicle lane.
I have to...
(Plot continuity)
I can't let him move the bicycle.
I'll drive my car away.
I sang better than you.
Retired from the music scene.
Let's continue talking
about the singing thing.
(They're targeting me)
Back then, between you and Zhou Ye,
who actually sang better?
I did.
I changed careers.
I am
a dancer now.
(A loss to the music world)
(Tremble, dance world)
I remember you didn't have
any talent in this area.
(Wang Yuwen trash-talked,
triggering the bomb topic)
(Unbelievable)
I danced so perfectly when I was young.
I danced so well.
When did you ever dance standardly?
We were dance partners. You forgot?
When did that happen?
We partnered up when we were little.
When we were little,
I wasn't even in your eyes.
(Wang Yuwen out)
Wang, you're out.
(What did I say?)
I'll go pay the bill.
You get the invoice later.
It's just the three of us men left.
Let's all stop being so tense.
Exactly.
Yes.
Let's wait for him.
(We're playing a defensive game)
Well...
Do you have...
You guys...
(Have what?)
(Forcing gossip when there's none)
Do you have any,
you guys?
(You, me, him, that thing)
Wait.
Fei, I find you're so clingy now.
Wait,
look at him.
I've never felt in my life
that speaking is so difficult.
Don't be nervous.
The leather jacket thing.
Does it have anything to do with Ye?
Ye?
Was it because you had to
dress up handsomely to chase her?
Why are you so sure
he was involved with her?
It was him.
Why?
He lived in the same room as me.
Then why don't you suspect
it was your wife who stole it?
It was the college dorm.
College dorm.
You're sick.
(Guo Jingfei trash-talked,
triggering the bomb topic)
Fei, you're out.
(Guo Jingfei out)
We beat them!
Fei, you didn't know?
I thought I shouldn't say
"not remembering".
Way off.
So what's the rule?
No trash talk is allowed.
Fei at least
committed 50 fouls.
He kept belittling us.
Yes.
At least 50 times, I feel.
Every sentence was belittling.
Actually, it was a bit hard
for our team.
(Blind guess of the keyword)
Hit?
Slap?
Whip?
Hit people?
Gossip.
The talk about gossip.
Then he performed a set of Bagua Palm.
Look.
Take a good look.
I was helpless.
If he said Bagua Palm,
he would also be out.
Yes.
Did I talk about gossip?
I said I was on a blind date.
You said, "With whom?"
(Chatting away)
Who chased girls?
Chased who?
Who in our class?
Why am I so gossipy?
Today, in our Heartbeat Journey,
we experienced
mutual encouragement,
unity, and cooperation,
and amidst laughter,
we once again enhanced
the bond between
the Earth Group family members.
Tomorrow, we will take on
even more difficult challenges
that require more encouragement
and tacit understanding between you all.
Let's look forward together
to tomorrow's Extreme Journey.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Great work.
(Next Episode Preview)
Seven-Second Heartbeat Word Guessing.
With Lin Yi, they can't win.
Trust me.
I have an extremely high play IQ.
But today is my home ground.
I want you to instantly jump up
on your right foot
to copy my previous move.
Then go "hehe"
and tilt your head.
You still can't guess it?
The audience has already guessed it.
And you still haven't.
(It's your turn)
A big scoop.
Then a big scoop.
Then open your hands and laugh.
Okay.
Done scooping.
What is he doing?
Do you still think it's simple,
Yuning?
I know this one.
But what is it?
♪Maybe let's just forget it♪
It's really quite fun.
(The soul has left the body)
Say something.
What's wrong?
Wake up.
Fine, I'll jump.
Come on.
Just don't look down.
I'm starting to regret this a bit.
This is really a bit scary.
(Stay tuned for the Earth Group's
extreme experience)
Each team will act
as an a cappella choir.
We are bound to win.
I like their baffling confidence.
Can four people pull it off?
Glory or disgrace rests on this battle.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the excitement is about to begin.
(The a cappella showdown
is about to begin)
This time, we are starting
the Romantic Journey in Paris.
Welcome the all-around ace,
Ms. Song Qian.
This title sets the bar
a bit high for me.
Whisper Word Guessing.
You smell.
Spray something.
A kind of breakfast.
A group of what?
- I hear a sound here.
- Who?
There's something.
What did you guess?
I'm stopping him here.
Wait, how can you guys play this game
so badly?
His description only had one sentence.
Keep going,
and my IQ would be too low.
I've experienced all these things.
Where is this?
Notre-Dame de Paris.
Quite spectacular.
Now we've reached the top
of Notre-Dame de Paris.
This is it.
The spire.
What is this?
Is this the Seine River?
The Seine River.
The Seine River bank.
These are Île Saint-Louis
and Île de la Cité.
So many people.
Paris at sunset.
The next game
is
a little related
to acting.
You didn't expect me
to come so quickly, did you?
This matter has nothing to do with her.
This matter is absolutely because of me.
Mom,
no, I mean, ma'am.
She is the woman I love most.
It's you?
Why is it you?
Who is this?
I don't know him.
My lady.
(Secret)
I...
Wang Yuwen.
She looks down on us.
Destroy them.
How did it suddenly...
A complete reversal.
(How will they act it out?)
(Extra Episode Preview)
Play a round of psychological warfare.
What if we still win this round? Right?
That's basically impossible.
Do you need us to go easy on you?
Thank you, Yuning, for going easy on us.
Alright.
Don't lose too fast, okay?
Come out.
Come over here.
Is it you?
Stop arguing, guys.
Make your move.
(Which group will win?)
(Special Extra Episode Preview)
Everyone, give yourself
a new name too.
Then I want to be called
"Potato Mound Calf".
I'm called "Four Yili Horses
Outside the Door".
You can pick whichever two you want.
I'm called Sun Honglei.
I'm called Li Naiwen.
Don't call yourself Li Naiwen.
It's bad luck.
I'm called Guo Jingfei.
Even worse luck.
Let's go by age.
You must find one person to watch.
Then it's enough for me
to watch one person.
You want to eliminate seven in one go?
How many rooms
do you want to live in alone?
Three, two, one.
(Who will win in the end?)
The first meeting
between both sets of parents.
Sister-in-law.
Younger brother.
Grandson.
The other side is a bit noisy.
This is my first blind date.
I'm a bit nervous.
Aren't we about to get married?
You scumbag!
What do you mean?
You two were even love rivals before?
(How will they act it out?)
(Wow The World, show schedule)