The Earth
holds within it the most captivating
symmetry and connection.
Divided by the equator and its meridians
into the Northern
and Southern Hemispheres,
the two halves follow
entirely opposite seasonal rhythms.
With their vastly different
geography, texture,
and climate,
they have given rise to civilizations
of strikingly distinct character.
The vast continents
of the Northern Hemisphere
nurture a depth of cultural heritage
and character.
The expansive oceans
cradling the Southern Hemisphere
give rise to clarity and raw vitality.
The natural wonders it nurtures
are nothing short of rare treasures.
This time,
the Earth Group
will unlock the Southern Hemisphere,
following the thread of
the 40th parallels north and south,
exploring through differences,
and understanding through connections.
(Christopher Luxon, Prime Minister of New Zealand)
Wow The World S2.
(Lu Nan, Member of
the New Zealand Parliament)
Welcome to New Zealand.
(Lewis Upston)
Here in New Zealand,
(Minister of Tourism and Hospitality, New Zealand)
you will experience breathtaking landscapes.
From majestic mountains
and crystal-clear lakes,
to dramatic coastlines,
and ancient forests.
We are confident that
the natural beauty of New Zealand
will gift you with
unforgettable memories.
And we warmly welcome
more visitors from China
to come and explore New Zealand.
Our doors are always open.
And we really look forward
to seeing you here.
We've waited, waited,
and finally, the day is here.
In Season 1, we crossed
(Sun Honglei)
the Great Wall to connect with the world.
This time, we're crossing latitudes
to connect with the world.
I'm much more relaxed than in Season 1.
And I know better
how to explore the world.
I get to reunite with old friends again.
For me,
this trip isn't just
about seeing the sights.
It's also a unique journey
(Gong Jun)
into different cultures.
It's a 'Wow' journey
to reconnect with the world,
to rediscover its diverse
customs and ways of life.
(Auckland)
(Rotorua)
(Queenstown)
I'm out here to broaden my horizons,
(Paris)
to see different cultures and customs.
(Marseille)
Different everything.
I'm happy and excited.
Well...
(Guo Jingfei)
How did I suddenly become speechless?
Actually, I'm quite cultured.
New Zealand is a beautiful country,
sparsely populated,
filled with the sounds
of nature everywhere.
The wind,
the chirping of insects,
and the waves.
(Li Naiwen)
And many birds.
All of it together
makes you feel
an incredible sense of inner peace.
(Liu Yuning)
I think my real trip abroad
was just with Wow The World.
New Zealand may be full of
extreme sports,
like skydiving, bungee jumping,
that sort of thing.
But they're just not meant for me.
We take everyone to
all corners of the world.
(Wang Yuwen)
Every meeting is a moment.
And we also hope that we can share
some of our own Chinese culture
with people from other countries.
Broaden the view of the world.
(Lin Yi)
Whether physically
or mentally,
we want people to experience
the integration and connection
between Chinese culture
and the cultures of the world.
I think we take
our stories there,
(Chen Xingxu)
and then bring their stories back.
It's no longer about watching
from the sidelines.
We're in it,
connecting with the world
as participants.
The Earth is truly
one big family.
Let us live together on this planet
and grow more united.
Having seen the vastness of the world,
yet still tender toward
the green of the grass.
In the span of a breath,
we see the expanse of heaven
and earth beyond the latitudes,
listen to the mountains and seas,
and watch the rise of civilizations.
The world is just
that concrete, that vivid.
- Wow The World!
- The whole world is right here!
=Episode 1(Part 1)=
(Welcome Ceremony for the Earth Group)
(In 2026,)
(the Earth Group is back,)
(gathering at the highest point
in the Southern Hemisphere,)
(Auckland's landmark, Sky Tower,)
(for a mystery mission.)
One!
Let's go!
Naiwen.
(I can trust you guys)
(with missions, right?)
(Leave it to me, and you'll be a mess)
(This time,)
(what method will the Earth Group use)
(to welcome the new members?)
(New member welcome ceremony)
(The condensed "mastermind" version)
First,
(See the early preview for full detail)
we need to figure out
how we're going to
welcome them.
We need to plan it out.
Honestly, it's kind of like...
Actually, the way we did it
with Xingxu last time
was the best.
You know? Bro.
(Some memories)
Are you messing with me?
(The Earth Group's signature welcome)
No, how are we going to deal with Fei?
Let me talk about Guo Jingfei.
(Target analysis in progress)
First, Guo Jingfei is very sensitive.
Very smart.
(Trick-proof)
Bro, he's hard to fool.
Really.
I'm just afraid that
whatever we come up with,
in his head, he just won't care.
So he's got all of you stumped?
This Guo Jingfei...
- Is he really that powerful?
- Bro, come on.
Think of a way to handle it.
Is Guo Jingfei
really that immune to awkwardness?
Can the cold actually freeze him?
[*'Cold' can refer to 'Awkwardness' in Chinese]
(Freeze plan)
He's immune to awkwardness.
He can amuse himself anywhere.
Send someone
who doesn't know him that well
to go in first.
(Manipulation plan)
We can make someone behind the scenes direct,
telling him what to do step by step.
He'll find out instantly.
- He'll definitely find out.
- Fei will find out instantly.
Would you record an ID
for that friend?
Then just have him record one
(ID plan)
like for a real estate opening.
Then he'll refuse.
We'll fix
a special bowl for Fei,
with an extra-large
amount of chili.
(Feeding plan)
Then he won't eat it.
I think all of this is useless.
These can fool a guy like Xingxu,
(And now, cue Xingxu)
but they can't fool him.
Then how about this?
I'll just say,
let's all shoot some videos together.
I take him along for the dance.
After that, I'll say,
"Fei, forget it."
"Maybe you shouldn't do it.
No, it's not right."
(Emotional roller coaster)
Make him invest his energy.
- Right.
- Invest his passion.
(Hype, in waves)
Get him fully involved.
Involved.
(Emotional roller coaster plan, Target)
Okay, that's one move.
I know.
Why not just announce it directly?
(Official announcement?)
Then how...
Come on. Go ahead.
What do you mean by
"official announcement"?
Just have Yuwen and Xingxu
pretend to be in a relationship.
Then we're all shocked.
So it can explain
(The Earth Group and their families gathered
the day before) why is your mom here,
(You, You)
and your mom is here too.
(Pfft)
Lin Yi's mom is here too.
Or maybe it's the feeling of him
catching the two of you.
Wait.
What should we do
to make him think
we're dating?
Like playfully teasing each other.
Teasing?
At the homestay, I say,
"Xingxu,
come catch me!"
(Xingxu, come catch me!)
Then...
Then Xingxu,
covering his eyes,
be like, "I'm coming to get you!"
Isn't that like going crazy?
No, no.
But let's just act it out, I think.
I think it's okay.
Let's go for it, Wen.
Okay.
(Fake couple plan, Target)
Alright, the plan for Fei
is taken care of.
(Merit)
What about Lin Yi?
Bro, how about this?
For example, you say,
"I'm starting a clothing brand,
a streetwear brand,
and you guys can wear
some of the stuff
on the show for me." Kind of this.
Then we'll have Lin Yi, at night,
the rest of us
will be in suits at dinner,
and he'll be wearing,
like, a tank top...
(So vivid)
and slippers
or something.
(Streetwear makeover plan, Target)
Sounds good.
(Locked in)
(Not sure what's hyping up)
That camera...
Honglei, I...
I don't understand
what your expression means.
Isn't it cool?
After we enter the venue,
we'll rehearse the dance first,
and then we start acting.
Let's do a rehearsal first.
Alright.
Okay, let's go.
So should we go now?
Yes.
(Guo Jingfei is about to
arrive at the guesthouse)
(The 'Yi Guo duo' operation
has officially started)
(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2=
(Guo Jingfei is about to
arrive at the guesthouse)
What are they doing?
They just arrived too.
We'll be all sitting here.
Or
(The couple group is preparing)
should we go somewhere else first and wait?
And they call us later.
Let's go sit somewhere else first.
No,
you can start chatting first.
(Crew pretending to rest)
Right, anything will do.
The car is here.
(Target appears)
So should we now
start dancing?
Alright, let's learn it first.
(Pretending to rehearse; Naiwen scouts;
crew pretends to rest; everyone in prep)
(Chatting warmly)
Actually, I've only
recorded a show with Gong Jun,
and I've acted in a drama with Naiwen.
I'm not really familiar with the rest.
But I guess we'll get close soon.
(Target approaching)
You look sneaky.
Sneaky.
The car is here.
(The car arrives)
Fei,
go in first.
We'll start filming later.
Okay.
You guys aren't
setting any trap, are you?
(Extreme vigilance)
Impossible.
It's cool out here.
(Here comes the trap)
Don't film.
Arrived.
Young man, you've lost weight.
Why are you so late?
This yard is nice.
What, thinking of buying it?
They're already here.
Already here.
They are
practicing some dance?
Practicing a dance?
Some dance for the pilot episode.
It's like this.
Like this.
Right.
(Target mission arrives)
Fei is here.
Say hello.
(The smart one arrives)
Fei.
Why are you
so late?
I...
I finished my makeup long ago.
Hello everyone, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I'm now in...
What's this place again?
Auckland.
I'm in Auckland...
What's this place again?
Hello everyone, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I'm...
I'm in Auckland...
Auckland, New Zealand, right?
Hello everyone, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I'm now...
(Forget it, Fei)
Look so cool.
Uncle.
(Guo Jingfei stars in 'Uncle')
(Struggling to hold back laughter)
(Thinking of all the sad things
1000 times)
(This one can't hide it at all)
(Bright)
I originally thought
I'd arrive this afternoon,
so I'm in a white suit.
It's already yellow now.
(Found a reason to laugh a bit)
Where's Lin Yi?
Not with me.
Weren't you two setting off together?
No.
It's okay, let's just wait for...
Wait for the food.
What time is it now?
Almost nine o'clock.
(Go, bro)
(Not starting yet?)
(Hurry up)
(Get some tissue)
(and wipe my sweat anytime.)
(Romantic love is about to begin)
(Subconsciously wipe hands first)
No, I've used this one.
(Immediate NG)
So what if you've used it?
Why can't I use it if you've used it?
That's a bit malicious.
Tonight you still have to
go into the water.
Who said that?
Play games?
No, I've used this one.
I've used it.
Just go with it, okay?
No.
(Hope we're not caught)
(Fei found out instantly.)
(He's really hard to fool.)
Let's just go with it.
Not going along with it.
I have chips in my car,
(Totally unaware)
big bags.
Like animal feed.
It's okay, they're preparing dinner.
Come,
Yuwen.
What's up?
Get that...
(Smoothly moving the process along)
Go through that dance.
Right.
(Playing along)
Rehearse that dance.
Fei is here.
Should I dance too?
We're going to dance.
Let's record
that kind of dance.
Then we'll post it later.
(Dance?)
(Clip from the TV drama 'Uncle')
I...
I can do it.
(Confident in dance)
(Immediately button up and get ready)
No, babe...
No.
Wen, you take this
(Only focused on dance)
and give it
- to Fei.
- Wait.
Look first.
(Stage fright)
(Ignored)
Have you seen this before?
No.
When it gets to this part,
right, together.
Everyone is just chatting in front.
Start with the left leg first?
Yes.
Yes, start with the left leg.
Left leg, right hand.
I remember the first move.
(Starting to dance)
Yes.
Great.
Uncle, you're awesome.
Not the starting part.
None of the starting part.
Start from here.
Right.
(Immersed)
Nice, Fei.
Nice, Uncle.
Quick learner.
I've taken body movement classes.
The hand moves.
Not bad.
Awesome.
Nice.
(Getting more pumped with praise)
He learned much faster than you guys.
(Holding back laughter)
Don't block the camera.
Right.
(Camera on)
Learned so fast? Okay.
Almost there.
Okay, watch it again.
Come on, let's go.
Hurry up.
(Pretending to be impatient)
Okay.
I'm hungry, really hungry.
Alright.
(Reading the room)
Come on.
I think Jingfei,
the newcomer...
I think
this dance, let Jingfei...
(Serious face)
I think his part is totally fine now.
- The effect is good anyway.
- We haven't started recording yet.
You're starting to mess around already?
(Trying to lighten the mood)
(He's actually pretty nice)
Can we learn first?
You...
You know him too well.
Testing the waters.
The key is,
he keeps blinking
when he's messing around.
(Cheerful)
(Really can't handle it)
What do you want?
You want Fei to stand in front?
You...
You know us too well.
Let's do one first.
Who's recording?
I'll record first.
I'll record first, come on.
Well...
Isn't Yuning dancing?
I'll skip for now.
He'll record.
Record one to see.
Get a feel for it.
How about this?
I think let Fei stand in front.
- You stand here.
- We...
I'm not the center, you...
I'm not the center.
I...
One, two, three.
Yes.
I...
I'm at the very front?
This is too embarrassing.
(I've got my pride)
It's okay.
This is really not appropriate.
It's fine.
No,
babe...
Well,
Wen,
you...
you stand here.
Stand here.
(Love drama begins)
Right.
I'm not going.
We...
I think we should...
Well...
Don't stand together.
No.
We shall avoid suspicion, right?
(Finally noticed this act)
Just stand here.
You two have...
We're filming a drama.
They are a combo.
Then standing with me is the most
suspicious-avoiding.
(Absolutely safe)
- You stand with me.
- It's okay, Fei.
Let's dance like this first.
It's fine, Fei.
Let's go, come on.
Alright.
Then how do we
suddenly know when to lift our feet?
(Very serious about the stage)
Five, six, seven, go.
Yuwen,
you shout.
Just look at me.
Then you shout.
Okay.
Come on.
We start with chatting, right?
Yes.
Casual chatting.
- Alright.
- Let's go.
Listen up, yes.
We just pretend to
just gesture.
one, two, three,
go.
(So sudden)
Five, six, seven, eight.
What are you doing, bro?
(Apologetic laugh)
Where's seven, eight?
Where's five, six, seven, eight?
- I really didn't hear it.
- Right.
So you fake talk,
like extras,
just move your mouths without speaking.
You watch me turn.
No time left, really.
(Pretending to be angry)
Let's hurry up.
Quick.
Okay.
Let's be serious, okay?
(Come on)
No, just listen to me.
I say,
watch me turn,
then everyone turn together.
Okay.
Alright? Let's go.
Come on.
Little flower.
Get ready.
(Liu Yuning's camera position)
(Perfect timing)
(Thunderous camera work)
Spin.
(Liu Yuning's camera position)
Spin,
Spin.
Flower hand,
(Liu Yuning's camera position)
flower hand.
Okay, cover your neck,
(Adding freestyle)
(Perfect ending)
Pretty good.
(As expected of me)
Actually, it doesn't have to be too in sync.
Got me sweating.
Let me see.
I'll wipe it.
(Relationship drama again)
I can't dance at all, really.
Are you hot?
Yes.
(Only focused on dance)
- Why are you sweating so much?
- You...
How should I know?
(Performed for ages, no one watching)
As long as the dance is in sync.
Okay.
(When it comes to dancing,)
Yuwen, take a look.
Take a look.
(Ignoring)
Okay, no problem.
Really hungry.
Eat something.
I'm
(Acting up)
getting a bit of low blood sugar.
Look, I'm already drinking,
(Easily trusting)
Want some chips?
I'll get you some.
I'm still on a diet.
Fei,
you in the front look a bit like...
What's it called?
(Hard to say)
Well...
No.
It is just right if I dance ugly.
Really?
You're intentionally
going for this effect.
I'm not doing it on purpose,
but I really am
naturally ugly.
No, it's not ugly.
I think it's good.
How about we go through the moves once
and then shoot?
Maybe forget it.
I don't think it's good.
Kind of awful.
(Confidence melts like cream)
Kind of awful?
Why?
What's the problem? What's wrong?
He thinks it's kind of awful.
(Awful?)
(I think it is awesome)
Feels a bit...
A bit not presentable.
That's the idea.
No,
they're counting on this for promotion.
Okay, let's do it then.
Do another take.
Then I won't...
I won't...
(Voluntarily quit?)
Then I won't...
I won't unbutton.
(No obligation to quit)
Would that be better?
No,
it falls...
It rides up.
Another take.
How about...
Yuwen,
you stand in front.
Right.
No.
I'll be behind you.
Come on, listen to me.
You can't go wrong.
Right.
I'll be behind you.
Really?
Yes, or we two...
(Thinking about what to say later
makes me laugh)
- We two in front.
- Because our clothes are white.
Alright, then we...
No, who's filming?
Who's filming this time?
Still Yuning filming?
How about let Fei film?
Alright.
(Reluctantly agreeing)
Fei, you film.
Okay.
Wait, then Fei...
Fei isn't dancing?
He won't dance.
I'm not dancing.
- That's okay.
- That works too.
Okay then.
Good.
(Confused but accept)
(Immediately takes the job)
(In full performance)
Don't you need to wipe?
That's isn't that oil?
Who's oily?
(Playful banter shows intimacy)
Come on, chat first.
(Lei pushes again)
Come on.
Chat.
Get ready.
Let's try it.
No need to try.
We'll make Honglei mad.
(Kind)
You know?
Okay.
Just go for it.
Come on.
Come on, get ready.
When do we run?
Can't run.
Run...
- First...
- Don't run, don't run.
Just like this.
Film first.
Let's go.
Take it as it comes.
Sorry, bro.
Sorry.
Play it again.
Sorry, bro.
Come on.
Okay.
Ready.
Okay, go.
Okay.
(Guo Jingfei's camera position)
Ready.
(Shooting seriously)
Right.
(Sneak a laugh)
(Sincere)
(Guo Jingfei's camera position)
(Close-up camera movement)
(Forgot the dance moves)
(Chaotic dance, off beat,
completely miss)
Then directly...
(Each dancing their own)
(You danced...)
Okay.
Good.
No, bro,
don't point the camera right at me,
I'll laugh easily.
It's fun.
Add some camera movement.
(Blame)
I can't get around.
I'll just come over.
This take,
how is it?
(Definitely not as good as my dancing)
Good.
Actually, Liu Yuning's version
hides the flaws.
(Urgently campaigning for his own dance)
His version...
The footage I shot
kind of gives away your flaws.
Because I
just set up the camera there.
(Subtly recommending himself)
The one he shot is hiding our flaws.
(In character)
We were pretty in sync.
Right.
Okay.
(Dance center position is surely mine)
Then let's use this one.
Then this one it is.
Just go with this one?
This one's fine.
Well, I jumped for nothing.
Then you...
This take of yours is a pass?
(Playing the good cop)
Then what about Jingfei?
(Pretending the atmosphere is awkward)
That's okay.
It's fine.
I was...
Lin Yi wasn't here either.
No,
you...
Well...
He is not in it,
then I should not be in it either.
If I am,
(All about self-consistency)
it feels like Lin Yi...
Just you old members.
It's fine.
Shall we run? Shall we?
Didn't you say you were
from a dance academy?
Trap after trap.
(Can't hold it anymore)
You two really...
I really...
Can you stop talking?
What are you doing?
I didn't say anything.
What are you two doing?
(confused)
(Trip)
No, you tell me...
(Hahahaha)
Have you ever gone all out
for a variety show?
Wow The World.
This is too hard.
How do we naturally run away?
But right now,
the topic should be heating up nicely.
What's wrong?
These two...
(Steady)
Holding nothing back.
Anyway, we haven't started
recording yet.
Young people...
Well...
Wait.
Impulsive.
Impulsive, bro.
Yes.
(Yeah)
You have no idea.
You have no idea how close they are.
(A huge scoop falls from the sky)
They got together?
They're in a relationship?
They've known each other
since childhood.
I think Yuning
or someone should go tell him.
I'll go tell him.
(Secretly pleased)
Why hasn't anyone called us back?
(Has anyone ever cared?)
Are they pranking us?
No,
let's go back.
Wait.
What's up?
(Knowing smirk)
You two are enough.
Really.
You two...
Naiwen.
(Male and female leads are in position)
(Extras are in position)
(Only one audience member)
(Guo Jingfei's perspective)
(Front-row spectator)
(Jun's laughter can't hold back)
(Extras adding details)
You two are really...
There are so many cameras,
and what are you doing?
They're not filming.
The problem is...
(In-the-know pose)
The problem is we're uncomfortable.
I'm really...
Sorry.
(Uncomfortable)
Yes, I want to stay away from you two.
My spot here is perfect.
A viewing spot.
Yes, just watching the show.
Yuwen.
Yesterday because your mom was here,
you were very restrained.
Now your mom isn't here,
but you...
I suggest you
be a little restrained too.
Okay?
Wait.
So what?
Wait, you...
Wait, I want to ask
can't you rein her in?
I want to ask you.
Aren't you a domineering CEO type?
That's just acting.
(Today's script: 'Little Pepper
and Little Delicate Husband')
Just go back and flirt with each other.
You two...
Yuwen, it's fine, just go ahead.
It's fine.
I've got your back.
(Holding the same gossip,
instantly inseparable)
Why do you, Jingfei?
How do you?
Wait, how do you?
I'll say...
You say you set this all up.
Yes.
I'll say
I forced them
to be together.
I get it.
Can't hold back.
('Passionate', can't control it)
'Passionate'.
Your fans,
they even come to my Weibo
asking about it.
Really?
(Really)
Yes, really.
They asked me
to play matchmaker for you two.
I said no matchmaking needed this time,
they've actually
been together all along.
It's been less than a year, right?
(Never got this question's answer)
How...
How long have you two been together?
(I don't know either)
(I know even less)
How long have you two been together?
How long have we been together?
(Pressure backs on this side)
You're asking me?
A trick question.
(How to do)
You don't know?
(I'll make this answer)
Over a year.
Should be over a year.
Over a year and still so clingy?
(Completely believe)
Still so clingy?
(Time to end this act)
Have a strawberry.
Let me feed you.
Let me feed you a strawberry?
(Time to end up)
Don't be so gross.
Let me feed you.
Lei is being subtle.
(Joining the act)
How annoying.
(Run quickly)
Let's first...
Let's first do that.
Open your mouth.
I catch you.
Don't run.
(Still purely smiling)
(Hurry up and act)
Xingxu,
catch me!
How annoying!
This is like one of those
really cheesy skit endings.
Endings.
Wait for me! It's like that.
Aren't you two running?
Why aren't you two running?
Why would we run?
What's this?
What's this supposed to be?
Just come and catch me!
Come and catch me!
(Going all out)
Quick, go catch him!
(Must we do this)
Catch him!
Quick, go catch him!
Quick!
(Going all out)
Quick, go catch him!
You catch me.
Quick!
Quick, catch!
Honglei!
I'm coming!
I didn't wear a belt today,
or I'd definitely whip it off.
That's funny.
(Sure you're not messing with yourself)
These guys...
I think this is about enough.
Fei.
Welcome to Wow The World.
Everything from start to now was fake.
Really?
We really have no time left.
Why don't we let Fei shoot?
You two are enough.
You don't know them...
'Passionate'.
Everything just now was acting.
We two really aren't...
I really don't know.
I absolutely don't know
when we got together.
(Really a big production)
Did you feel something was off?
I really love this kind of surprise.
She asked me.
Asked me when we got together.
I was completely baffled.
So funny.
You can guess
which parts were real?
That dancing part was 'picking on' me,
making me do it over and over.
And finally we didn't let you attend.
Yes.
Honglei's acting was just right.
You know?
Many details.
He made me a bit nervous,
because he got angry.
Yes, he got angry.
Hurry up. Yes.
The pressure was applied perfectly.
Yes.
Let's go.
Take you somewhere.
Take you somewhere, Jingfei.
We'll take you
to our 'Prank HQ'.
They acted pretty convincingly,
just that...
That sort of look.
So it seems
I've passed the test, right?
My character has no problem, right?
No problem.
But when I was going down the stairs,
were there cameras there?
No cameras, right?
No.
That's great.
I just made a bad comment there.
(Revenge in every gap)
If Jingfei made any bad comments at all,
it must have been about us two.
We two just now
almost throttled each other to 'death'.
They acted
really flawlessly.
Great.
I really like this opening.
I overestimated you, Jingfei.
I really overestimated you.
Jingfei, seriously,
we thought
you'd figure out every part.
We really
felt like
you'd see through us every second.
Really?
(Once thought so highly of me)
In the afternoon,
we were simulating over and over,
whether Fei would notice this
or notice that.
We pushed
and overturned everything.
Yes.
We all thought
you'd definitely catch on.
I didn't catch on anything.
So if we were actually dating,
why last night...
Your mom was here.
Nai.
Because Nai said it just now.
Nai is amazing.
I said it.
(Best improvisation flashback)
Now your mom isn't here,
but you...
I suggest you
be a little restrained too, okay?
That one from Nai
was particularly amazing.
Flawless.
That was too amazing.
That one was inserted perfectly.
So impressive.
Nai, you're awesome.
(Just learn it)
We studied for nearly three hours.
How about this?
Give me some face too.
Actually I figured it out long ago.
You set it up well.
All the crew were outside,
each busy with their own tasks.
Yes.
And there were extras too.
Because there were no cameras
filming seriously here.
(Perfect)
Perfect.
This kind...
Wait...
(Warmly)
Warmly deceived.
You know?
Isn't it
(Fairy-tale feeling)
has a fairy-tale feeling?
You know?
It's like...
When I'm in this kind
of feeling,
suddenly I feel like
(Pink)
my soul is pink.
Look at Jingfei's emotional value.
He gave us a perfect score.
The three-hour study wasn't for nothing.
Indeed.
Welcome, Jingfei.
Welcome.
You gave me gifts,
so I have to give something back to you.
Okay.
Now, we need to figure out
how to welcome Lin Yi.
Take a look at the streetwear brand.
(Earth Group custom-made)
They even customized Bad Lei for you.
Bad Lei!
(Costume department
emergency hand-sewing)
This is so real.
You really put thought into it.
Bad Lei, seriously.
(Too bad)
This is impressive.
They even registered the trademark?
This shark is good. Put it on him.
Kiss the shark.
Why don't you wear it?
(So suitable for you)
You wear it.
You're "mischievous" one after another.
I think this outfit is for Lin Yi.
Lin Yi's own clothes
are even more abstract than this.
Tomato-scrambled-egg?
(A combination
even AI rarely recommends)
(Let's go with this set)
Lin Yi has arrived.
Everyone, get in position.
I'll go over first,
and set the stage.
We checked your profile today.
Prince of Theater.
(I am the Prince of Theater)
Right.
You can't tarnish your reputation.
If you get caught...
Then I'd be a lousy player.
(Just having fun)
Then I'll go.
Okay.
(Prince of Theater welcomes Lin Yi)
Go ahead, Jingfei.
Alright.
Good luck, Jingfei.
Good luck.
He's sitting there waiting.
Wouldn't this opening
be a bit awkward?
(Just relaxed)
Actually, we could have one more person.
We can do it at any time.
I'll come out in a moment.
How about this? Whenever you feel
it's your scene,
just step up.
Okay.
(Honglei, the act came so fast?)
Anyway, make him feel
that sense of reality, presence,
(Boosting realism)
Sense of reality, presence.
Right.
Walk-through.
You're the type of actor
who does walk-throughs.
Walk-through
(Walking through others' shots)
means walking through.
(Walking through)
Why are you here too?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to give you a perfect assist.
Let's just pretend.
You wait over there,
then and I'll be here,
washing something or whatever.
Why isn't he here yet?
I can't keep washing forever.
I'll wash the skin off soon.
(The act hasn't stopped)
So serious.
When people are pranking others,
they really don't mind the effort.
(Amazed again)
I've never seen everyone so serious.
Just very excited.
(This one is even more so)
This is the camera?
(Excited)
Here he comes.
It's him, right?
(Walking through the shot)
(Lin Yi welcome ceremony 1)
(Prince of Theater warmly welcomes)
He's here, right?
(Prince of Theater in position)
(Dishwashing Lei in position)
(Target Lin Yi appears)
(The philtrum gets excited first)
Our clothes look good.
We're in "couple outfits."
(Target has arrived)
You look so good today.
Prince Charming.
His voice...
(Who stepped on his tail?)
What's wrong with your voice?
It just
gets worse than last night.
The meal last night
was too indulgent.
I think his appearance
is already hilarious.
Very happy.
And I get to see everyone again.
Right. Sorry.
I...
Over the New Year, I just
got sick.
I just recovered,
and my throat hasn't fully recovered.
But,
well...
The fever is gone.
Yeah.
They haven't arrived yet?
They went out again
(Prince of Theater handles it easily)
to record something else.
Can you sing now?
(A stroke of inspiration)
Sing?
With your throat like this,
can you still sing now?
As long as you don't hit me, I can sing.
Hahaha.
I think today, you and I,
(Starting to assist)
plus... Let me see who sings well.
Gong Jun. The three of us in a group.
Singing well?
What's that got to do with me?
I sing well.
(Good thing I prepared early)
Actually, today,
I've been practicing my vocals,
learning singing techniques properly
with Yuning.
(Studied under Liu Yuning)
What songs can you sing?
I
can sing most of the songs.
Which song are you most familiar with?
The most familiar?
♪Love♪
(Vibrato, throat singing, vibrato)
♪Love you till death♪
(Real voice, triple electronic voice)
♪No regrets, no holding back♪
(The master is unhappy)
So pitiful.
(Feeling pity)
I've always...
I love singing.
(A self-starter)
Do you know about Naiwen?
What's up?
(Improvising a plot)
His kidney stones flared up.
He hasn't been able to pee all day.
(Endure)
Really?
Yeah, he's in a lot of pain.
That really hurts.
That's why...
The reason we waited so long today
is because he...
Partly because of him.
But we have to continue recording.
Maybe, he
won't be able to make it tonight.
(Actually believed it)
I think we should let him
take some painkillers first
and finish recording.
(Performing worry)
(Genuinely worried)
Did he go to the hospital?
If he has stones...
I think he should just
get
an IV drip, and he'll be fine.
But I don't know,
whether this is a bit...
100 percent kidney stones.
I...
I've had them before.
I was in so much pain.
In the end, I was so backed up
I flew from Yunnan,
the border,
towards
Kunming.
Oh, my!
In the end, using my force,
I managed to push it out.
(Naiwen also hurts this much?)
(Can Naiwen push it out?)
I think I should go,
pretending to have kidney stones.
(You can't go)
He said you won't make it tonight
just now.
I'll say I already peed out the stone.
I need to clear my name.
(Laughing so bitterly)
Did you get the same disease
as Qin Lan had?
Thanks, Jingfei.
I don't know.
Anyway, during the New Year,
I had inflammation and a bit of fever.
I think you just...
(Can't hold back laughter)
(Twinkling)
(He is so cute)
Oh, no.
Feels like he can't keep acting anymore.
What's wrong?
What are you laughing at?
(Can't keep her own conviction)
Huh?
He's so cute.
I'm leaving. I'm going over there.
(Prince of Theater
can't fool a sincere kid)
(Haven't had enough yet)
Jingfei is done playing?
Alright,
then let's go.
Let's go.
Hello.
Good luck in the Year of the Horse!
Still in pain?
Do you have a sore throat now?
He's not in pain.
He's not?
Just purely hoarse.
(Caring)
The vocal cords can't close properly.
Are you okay, Naiwen?
(Caring about Naiwen)
They said you
went to the hospital for an IV drip.
You're back after the drip?
(Didn't react?)
What happened?
I don't know.
(Then just go along with it. Pain)
Mm...
Kidney hurts.
Kidney?
Kidney stones, right?
Can the stones come out?
I don't know.
You're even sweating.
(Teasing the kid again)
It hurts now?
It hurts.
(What to do)
After we finish recording,
you should go back to the hospital.
Are you going back
to the hospital after recording?
Right, I was thinking...
(Should I go back
to the hospital or not?)
It depends
on the situation.
(Continued concern)
Sweating from the pain.
My kidney hurts.
Your kidney hurts?
Where's the kidney, Naiwen?
(Stabbed in both ribs for the kidney)
I can't stand you.
(It doesn't hurt?)
I really can't stand it.
He's playing along with the act.
No. He asked me with genuine concern.
I could just
cooperate a bit more.
Did you figure it out?
You didn't.
Not at all.
Kidney hurts?
What?
I think if you sing
Love Until Death like this,
it'll sound better than usual.
How do you know
I am going to sing Love Until Death?
We...
Did you hear that just now?
You were outside
and you heard it, right?
You just found out?
Did he just find out?
What does that mean?
What we have here...
Everything is fake.
What?
So what is real?
Why are you so cute?
(Too cute to bear to lie to you)
Then tell me.
What is real?
Let me show you around.
The room assignment is real.
You and Naiwen share a room.
(Improvising)
Over there.
Inside.
(Tease again)
This is good.
Yes. You and Naiwen are in this room.
(Voluntarily walks to the small bed)
You're so tall.
You're wasting it.
(Can't bear it)
You'll feel uncomfortable sleeping here.
(Since I'm here, let's settle)
It's fine.
You two play rock-paper-scissors.
Right.
If you lose
the rock-paper-scissors game,
you'll share a bed.
Whose punishment is this?
A punishment for both.
Whose punishment?
This is good.
Hey,
well...
Did Honglei tell you?
(Streetwear costume change plan)
Yes.
That outfit...
We'll do it in a bit.
We'll put it on him later.
There's going to be
a streetwear brand.
Honglei started his own brand
for clothing.
Right.
You guys...
Are you serious?
Why are you holding back laughter?
It shows on your face.
I don't have it on my face.
You have another mission?
I meant this is fake.
What is fake?
You sleeping here is fake.
But you didn't see it at all.
(Among many lies, find some mixed lies)
Your room is really on the second floor.
On the second floor.
Then who lives in this room?
He does.
It's Naiwen's.
He really can't tell
what's real and what's fake.
He believed everything.
I'll just sleep here.
Not sense of achievement.
None...
(Lower your voice. Is it glorious?)
(Bad Lei is approaching)
You all received the clothes, right?
I got them, yes.
Alright, that's fine.
Jun, it's fine.
It's okay if you have a competing brand.
(Smooth turn)
Do you have a competing brand?
Do you endorse a streetwear brand?
No, that's not.
That's not.
It's fine.
Let me tell you something
about my streetwear brand,
(Ah, serious)
and how to play along,
okay?
Okay. Fine.
What's it called, the brand?
It's called...
(Bad Lei)
It's called Bad Lei.
Bad Lei.
(Ya, eh, oh)
But taste-wise, I...
Can't agree?
Bad Lei.
Just a hat and a top.
Then let's change clothes.
Okay, thanks.
No problem, Honglei.
No need to thank me.
Your room is on the second floor,
the one next to Jingfei's.
This one is mine?
This one.
Right, this one.
This.
Bad Lei.
So cool.
(Love it)
Yeah.
But you...
Bad Lei.
Your hair doesn't look good.
You need to figure something out.
Just show it off...
The logo has to be visible.
Right.
The logo has to show.
And then a top.
Okay.
Just wear it during dinner.
After dinner...
You designed this, Honglei?
Yeah.
Can I wear something underneath?
(Innocent)
Yes.
Okay.
Just try on a hat and a top.
Of course.
Thanks.
I'll go change then.
(Hmm, hmm, haha, hmm)
Bad... Bad Lei.
Lay back.
(B, L)
B... L...
(Change quickly)
Oh, my! This waistband is so big?
This doesn't fit.
Sigh...
(Concern)
Naiwen is really sick.
His OOTD
didn't even last ten minutes.
He just
changed into...
That white suit.
Such a simple kid.
Too simple.
So tricking him feels a bit guilty.
(What about me?)
What about you?
We were messing around
in the first episode.
Honglei was also thoroughly pranked.
Honglei and Xingxu were the funniest.
Who was directing that?
Jun.
Jun, right?
Quietly mischievous.
(I have a say)
The one before me was Honglei.
I was scared of him in the first place.
And then,
he was so scary.
(Is that so?)
Because it was the first time I saw
someone so talented.
You know?
Yuning?
Yeah.
As
an actor,
he is very talented,
keeps switching gears all the time.
That emotional switch
is extremely intense.
What's this?
Is this a fly or a bee?
Such a big fly.
Great.
There's a cricket here.
There's a big katydid.
(Easily startled system)
What's this?
(Hi)
What is this?
Amazing.
Let's start our plan.
(Getting down to business)
Let's go.
Let's head out.
Go out looking cool.
Looking cool.
Memory erasure technique.
Right.
Why is it just me?
(Bad Lei's yellow vibe coat)
(Bad Lei's super low-rise pants
create visual contrast)
(Bad Lei-style)
West Coast.
(Bad Lei brand perfectly exposed)
(Bad Lei)
(Bad Lei hype)
This looks pretty good.
It has his own design language.
(Two peas in a very weird pod)
(Hanging by a thread)
It's a bit big, but it can stay on.
(All about fashion sense)
It's a bit big. I can't wear it.
Why is it just me?
This was a gift from Xingxu.
He said he hand-knitted it.
This looks nice.
(Suit squad 2026)
(Suit squad stunning ending)
You didn't change.
Only I changed.
(Memory erasure technique)
Why are you wearing this?
Why are you dressed like that?
What does that mean?
Bad Lei.
Bad Lei?
- What Bad Lei?
- Streetwear brand.
What does Bad Lei mean?
It's actually quite nice.
Honglei's clothes.
(Speak up for me)
I don't know.
This is Honglei's streetwear brand.
What is this?
When did Honglei get a streetwear brand?
Yeah. How is that possible?
(Forcing it)
Honglei...
You forgot? You just said it.
Bad Lei.
What's wrong with you?
When did I say that?
(Here's the evidence)
Bad Lei. Look.
Bad Lei.
(Hahaha)
(Wishing to confirm via blood)
How could I
(Voice cracks)
have written this myself?
Honglei, your name is right here.
When did I say that?
(Completely devastated)
What?
Here.
Get this footage for me.
(Footage won't go bad)
We have the footage here.
At such a young age,
why do you like
such flashy clothes?
Exactly.
What?
Is this part not over yet?
(You've been driven to tears)
Tell me, what is real?
(You win)
Okay.
Enough.
That's enough.
(Love you, bro)
You worked hard.
Thank you.
That wasn't easy.
Welcome ceremony.
(Everything from now on is real)
The welcome ceremony.
We have two new members.
Welcome.
Take it off quickly.
Just keep it on.
It's cold.
You might be cold.
(Shy)
My shirt inside is not warm enough.
Keep it on.
Why are your pants
falling down like this?
(Falling to the West Coast)
I can't put them on.
They are too big.
You've really made it
into a streetwear brand, seriously.
West Coast.
He's all about egg fried rice.
(West coast flavored egg fried rice)
Let's have a hug.
Poor baby.
Welcome.
Are you healthy?
Very healthy?
Healthy?
Yeah, healthy.
You're fine?
(Repeated confirmation)
Yep.
Welcome.
Wait.
Our colors.
The colors of our clothes match.
Honglei.
It's not about that.
Come on, it's okay.
We don't care about the center position.
We never do.
If so, you can stand there.
I'm standing here already.
I'll even stand in front.
Impressive.
Let's eat.
I'm really hungry.
Friends,
I'm starving.
Hi, friends.
I also brought a new friend.
This is your first time too.
How about I take you to meet everyone?
(But)
But I can't go empty-handed, right?
(Troubled)
Yili Yousuanru with chewy lemon.
You can taste the lemon juice at first,
and chew again, there's pulp
and peel, providing a layered texture.
Let's take it over for them to try.
Let's go.
Let the new friend
make a grand entrance.
What a handsome guy.
(Lemon tycoon)
What a big lemon.
You're so handsome, I'm jealous.
(Keep it down)
Come on, everyone can have a taste.
From now on,
we'll have enough chewy lemon
to go around.
Chewing and drinking at the same time.
It's so addictive.
You can't stop at all.
My throat
was definitely like this earlier.
(Declaration)
It was like this before drinking.
And with this,
after drinking it, I got better.
I'm all better.
Nice, it has a good chew.
It's so funny.
So much fun.
Lin Yi, you want a piece?
Sure.
Thanks, Honglei.
Thank you.
I really like this place.
Look at that one there.
Lin Yi, your family and your friends,
do they think you're fun?
No.
I don't think so.
They all kind of, they all say
I'm a bit silly.
Take it off quickly.
Lin Yi is so cute.
He's born with it.
So adorable.
Really.
Coupled with your voice,
you're invincible.
When we were here earlier,
Lin Yi was asking about my kidneys.
He was still concerned about my kidneys.
I just saw
Naiwen, he...
he was sweating all over.
(Observing)
You're breaking out in sweat.
(Looks genuine)
Were you
too deep into character?
He's just weak.
You're weak, Naiwen.
All sweaty.
That's not kidney pain,
it's kidney deficiency.
He's scarily naive.
It's terrifying.
Have you ever encountered
a telecom fraud?
Really.
He'd fall for every trick.
(Scarily naive)
What happened to your voice?
One year while filming,
I got a lung bacterial infection.
Then, suddenly it became like this.
After that,
whenever I get sick,
it gets to my throat.
How many times has this happened?
Like this?
Probably the fourth time.
(Ha ha ha ha ha ha)
Before,
I filmed a drama together
with Zhou Ye.
During the promotion,
it was meant to be
a very sweet romance.
But when we were promoting it,
I had this voice
the whole time.
If you mess with me,
(Brace yourselves)
you've just kicked cotton.
(Lin Yi cracked his voice)
My voice is hoarse.
There was no romantic vibe at all.
I don't know why.
Is it a Shenyang thing,
that everyone gets it in the throat?
Yeah.
Look, Qin Lan is also from Shenyang.
Right.
Maybe we should all talk like this.
Okay, no problem.
Anything is fine.
Exactly.
(Ah ha ha ha)
Donald Duck.
By the way, Jingfei,
we actually gave
this operation a name.
Can you guess what it is?
It's related to both of your names.
Yi and Fei to the Sky?
That was spot on.
That was our first option.
Really?
But it felt too lucky.
Yi and Jingfei's Jump Scare?
That's good.
That is a good one.
Yi and Jingfei's Jump Scare.
That's not it?
Nope.
Fei and Yi's Only Choice?
Three characters.
I'll give you a hint.
Oh, three characters.
(I got this)
Yi and Fei Fly Together.
(I'll smile it off)
This phrase is often used
police and gangster dramas.
Police and gangster.
One Fell (Yi Guo)...
One Fell.
One Fell what?
One Fell Swoop (Yi Guo Duan).
Yes.
(Yi Guo Duan boy band is forced to form)
Yi Guo Duan.
We're going to get you
in one feel swoop.
I like it a lot.
I can do it, I mean.
Volunteering, I can do it.
Fei today...
He's had it slightly worse.
It was worse for him.
Slightly worse.
Because you were a bit resigned to it.
(The more rebellious, the worse;
the more you struggle, the deeper you sink. Lin Yi)
The deeper you sink.
(So likable)
Who discovered Lin Yi?
Who invented Lin Yi?
So cute.
Next, there is
a tacit understanding challenge
concerning the new members.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
=Wow The World=
Lin Yi is so fun.
So hilarious.
When he speaks Cantonese,
I'm telling you,
nobody can understand him.
No one can understand him.
Yuning did.
Because they're both from Liaoning.
Right.
Only Northeasterners
can understand it, right?
What's with these kayaks?
Should we bring our passports?
What if we cross the border?
There are chairs prepared behind
for the two new members.
Do you want to sit down
and listen to the rules?
No, thanks.
We'll stand.
No, they're asking us.
Okay.
Come on.
Come on, let's close it up.
Let's close this up.
(Unity is strength)
Let's do it.
Come on, let's start.
The six of us will play.
Let the game begin.
Next up
is a tacit understanding quiz.
(Tacit quiz)
We will ask questions to Fei and Lin Yi.
The six veteran members need
to guess their answers correctly.
If answered wrong, they need
to move forward one flag.
We've prepared kayaks for everyone.
Once you reach the sea,
you'll have to row.
There are two sets of rules.
Two sets?
First set of rules.
They sit here and don't move.
(Rule 1: Old members answer correctly, stay.
Rule 2: If old members answer correctly, Guo Jingfei and Lin Yi step forward.)
You'll answer the questions.
If your answers
match theirs,
you don't move.
If they don't match,
you take a step forward.
Okay.
Second set of rules.
If they match,
they also take a step forward.
I like the second set.
(BBBBB)
Do we even need to discuss it?
The new guests need to feel involved.
(Sincere)
No, we're democratic.
Right, democratic.
There are six of us.
We can vote.
They have six people, and we have two.
How is that democratic?
(No problem)
No problem, very reasonable.
Very reasonable.
(No problem, no issue, very reasonable)
Very reasonable, no problem.
Those in favor of the first set,
please raise your hands.
We'll definitely raise our hands.
But it's meaningless.
It's meaningless. We raised hands.
Those in favor of the second set,
please raise your hands.
Here.
Let's only raise three hands.
Only three.
A narrow victory.
(How not a surprise!)
Narrow victory.
A dishonorable win.
Sorry, it's a dishonorable win.
Three to two, narrow victory.
Very dignified.
Look at that.
I want to ask something.
If their answer
is too outrageous,
can we object?
As long as there's any connection,
per our game rules,
(Final interpretation belongs to Yi Guo Duan)
as long as it has any connection,
we win.
That's unfair to us.
When you were playing us,
was it fair for us?
(Yes.)
(The roles start to reverse.)
(When a newcomer enters a group,)
(they are usually observed,)
This spot.
Right here.
(arranged,)
(Badlei? What badlei? What is Badlei?)
(with rules set for them.)
Should we let Fei shoot?
Okay.
(At this point,
the mission belongs to others.)
(But when the newcomers
start to take control of the rules,)
(their sense of control
greatly increases.)
The hint is right there.
(Someone else's mission)
(becomes our mission.)
(Now, the role-reversed mission)
(begins.)
(Tacit Quiz)
First question.
Wait a moment,
will Guo Jingfei princess-carry Lin Yi,
(Guo Jingfei carries Lin Yi or Lin Yi carries Guo Jingfei)
or will Lin Yi princess-carry Guo Jingfei?
Choose one of the two.
(Later, will Guo Jingfei carry Lin Yi
or will Lin Yi carry Guo Jingfei?)
(Answer separately)
They have to walk so far.
We'll just say the name.
Yes, just say the name.
We'll say it's Fei.
Then...
He'll ask you to decide on one.
It's Fei.
Fei is the one who picks up Lin Yi.
Yeah.
Or Fei is the one being picked up.
Then he can argue the same way,
and we'll be here till dawn.
Right?
You see?
The enemy is too cunning.
There's no definite answer at all.
No.
No, I'm wondering
if he'll write a third answer.
A mutual hug is an option, right?
(Third answer under development)
I really wonder
if there is a third answer.
(We won't let them)
We won't allow it.
Only two choices.
One of the two, right?
Okay.
(Development forced to terminate)
Normally,
they would think that I will carry you.
Right.
Now, we have to think
one step ahead of them.
That would be me carrying you.
Go above them.
My gut says I carry you.
So it's not easy for them to guess.
Right.
(Mischievous, lazy)
Because they know I'm mischievous and lazy.
(New member's answer:
Guo Jingfei picks up Lin Yi)
(New members' answer: Guo Jingfei carries Lin Yi. Old members' answer: Lin Yi carries Guo Jingfei)
Lin Yi carries Guo Jingfei.
We've completely figured it out.
Lin Yi.
Guo Jingfei.
Lin Yi does what to Guo Jingfei?
(Completely not fooled)
Lin Yi and Guo Jingfei.
(Seen through at a glance)
He's playing clever.
Lin Yi.
Lin Yi princess-carries Guo Jingfei.
Lin Yi princess-carries
Guo Jingfei, right?
I am the princess.
Come on.
(New member wins)
I told you we have to think
one step ahead of him.
We're playing at a higher level.
I don't believe you can carry him.
You can't lift him.
Whether I can lift him or not,
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll even do a squat.
Come on.
Make way for us, come on.
(Awesome, awesome)
Alright, let's go.
One small one each.
Now I'm proud to be a new member.
(Carried to victory)
I chose the right side.
Second question, quickly.
He thought exactly the same.
Right.
He thought you couldn't carry me.
Just like you said, you're lazy,
He thought I'm lazy, right.
Thought you didn't want to carry.
(What are you doing? Come back)
Where are you going?
The question hasn't been asked yet.
We drowned in the joy of victory.
We want something super difficult.
Come on.
How many abs do Guo Jingfei and Lin Yi
have in total?
Wow, impressive.
(How many abs do Guo Jingfei
and Lin Yi have in total?)
No, don't.
You don't need to calculate seriously.
I'm telling you, we happened
to have checked
each other's abs last night.
No.
But they
won't answer according to that.
He'd say when I'm relaxed,
it's one pack.
That works.
When I sit, it's two packs.
Upper and lower.
Right.
What about folded?
Then we'll be arguing till dawn again.
I'll search it.
(Seeking outside help)
Search for Guo Jingfei's
old photos.
Does he have any ab pics?
There really is.
There are.
How many?
Normally,
with his body fat, probably four packs.
(From the drama The Darker, how many abs does Guo Jingfei have?)
Wait.
One, two, three, four.
Four packs.
Just type in
(TV series The Darker: how many abs does Guo Jingfei have?
How can two men have a hundred abs?)
Under what circumstances would two men
have a hundred abs?
It says in human anatomy,
the maximum is eight.
Eight each, right?
I only have seven.
Why?
Where's the other one?
It's just...
Some people are naturally,
asymmetric.
You have seven, right?
I haven't counted, yeah.
But I'm not
the standard eight packs.
Then let's say eight.
If we win this time,
it will be thanks to your
freaky physiology.
Do you count as one?
Yes, I do.
Look.
You can't see any abs on me.
Right, so that's zero.
This is...
Yeah.
It counts as one. A round one.
(Learned something again)
I'll say six plus four.
Six plus four is too many.
Six plus one is enough.
Six plus one.
Okay.
Seven packs.
If we're going to do it,
we'll do it convincingly.
We just looked it up.
Let's use science.
Seven or five?
Seven.
Let's go with five.
(Old members' answer: 5)
We have eight.
Eight.
(New members' answer: 8)
Right.
Eight.
Prove that.
I count as one.
Lin Yi has seven.
I said this win
would be because of his
weird physiology.
Seven? I don't believe it.
I want to verify the cards.
Verify, I want to verify them.
Verify.
The card is fine.
Hurry up.
Let's see.
I'll show you.
Let's feel them.
(In-depth understanding of new member)
Yes, that works.
Go ahead, Naiwen.
Feel them.
How come you're the representative?
Only you get to touch them?
I want to touch them too.
Alright, we won't touch.
Just show us.
Okay, fine, show us.
I won't look.
(Full understanding)
I am such a decent woman.
Three, four,
five.
It tickles.
(Tickle reflex out of control)
Six.
You only have six, not seven.
(Lin Yi actually has 6 abs)
Then we were wrong too.
The card is wrong.
We swear to the God of Variety.
Am I the God of Variety?
You're the God of Cheating,
now.
No matter what,
you didn't guess right, right?
How about this?
We all take one step forward, okay?
We all take one step forward.
Fine.
That's okay, right?
- Yes, you're right.
- Alright.
Those two are yours.
All schemes.
(Arrogant)
Getting farther and farther, guys.
(Pure experience)
No, we just want to go kayaking.
Six people.
Six people's wits.
Against two people.
You're about to go to Australia.
(Congrats in advance on going into the sea)
Really, it's a pity.
We're kangaroos.
Everyone, you can
see the sea clearly now.
How many stops until we reach the sea?
- One more stop.
- Two stops.
Two more stops.
Come on.
Okay.
Who do Guo Jingfei and Lin Yi
think
has the best looks among everyone?
(Turn around and leave
Who has the best looks among everyone?)
Just to make it clear.
Does it mean philtrum
(Philtrum or Everyone)
or everyone?
(Coming for me)
Whose philtrum is the prettiest?
Best philtrum looks.
Upper lip, right?
Okay. Even if it's the philtrum,
what's the difference?
(I'm asking though)
He can explain.
Your philtrum looks nice.
- This curve is very elegant.
- It all depends on them.
It's not about objective facts.
(Oh, right)
So it's the same logic as rock-paper-scissors
with six options.
No problem.
It all comes down to their thoughts.
What they think
has no...
Has nothing to do
with objective reality.
No connection.
(Yi Guo duo reserves the right
of final interpretation)
Yes.
- What do we do now?
- We just can't let him...
Guess who?
(Don't look at me)
They think we won't tell the truth.
(Exactly predicted)
We can just
tell the truth, right?
Honestly, everyone is good-looking.
Yes.
So they'll definitely name one.
Should we bring Wang Yuwen into this?
(Will Yi Guo duo choose Wang Yuwen?)
If you want a tactful answer,
it would definitely be Yuwen.
(The Cheating King's tacit)
The only girl.
Yes.
(But)
No, they don't need tact.
They just want to win.
Yes.
Wait.
For the title of Visual King,
they definitely know this.
I...
(But)
He doesn't know Visual King.
How could he not know?
They don't know.
They'll definitely think
the two of us will choose Sun Honglei,
Visual King.
(Knows very clearly)
Is this...
Is this Bad Lei's clothes?
Really Bad Lei?
This color is so bright.
I borrowed it.
This is Guo Jingfei's clothes.
This is good.
We'll make them concede willingly.
(New member answer: Secret)
Okay.
Let's go with him.
- Okay.
- Right.
Nai?
(Old member answer: Li Naiwen)
(Uncle tier crush, challenge on)
Say the opposite.
Guess the opposite.
Say the opposite?
It's not the opposite.
(Burning with anger)
Is it that opposite?
What do you mean?
Fallen out.
Well.
These six people.
Look.
- That's not what I meant.
- You've exposed yourself.
Okay, each picks themselves.
And then...
For example, if he picks me,
then I win.
You four move forward.
(Listen to what you're saying)
(Waiting here for this)
Still fell out.
We'd better go back
(Team style is clear) - to individual battles.
- Yes.
They turned on
each other.
Infighting breaks out.
It collapses on its own.
Like this.
If they don't pick me,
I'll cry right here.
You turn and leave.
(Loading plot)
I'll quit filming.
Just quit filming.
Too heartbroken.
Yes.
Then we just pick Yuwen.
Alright, pick you.
Then it's you.
As soon as I leave,
you should pull me back.
No.
We won't pull you.
Can't pull you at all.
Just fly back directly.
Go back to the room and sleep.
I quit filming right now.
Film or don't, I don't care.
Come on.
Who? You two, right?
(Seems to mediate, actually stirs)
(What's going on?)
Both of them have filmed with me.
I'm your leading lady.
And you treat me like this?
(Delighted)
What? They're fighting now?
Everyone's claiming
to be the best-looking one.
Of course.
So you...
(Defuse conflict tactfully)
(Testing)
You two wouldn't skip picking the girl, right?
(Pre-selecting Wang Yuwen)
Should we bring Wang Yuwen into this?
(I've predicted)
I think they'll pick Yuwen.
(One step ahead)
Li Naiwen will definitely think
I'll pick Wang Yuwen.
(Visibly pleased)
Let's say it first.
We're classy.
Okay.
Say it.
Three, two, one. Say it together, okay?
Okay.
(Time to reveal the list)
Three, two, one, go.
- Wang Yuwen.
- Liu Yuning.
- Yuning.
(Smiling)
Straight into the sea, right?
Let's go.
- No.
- Are you admitting it or not?
No.
Everyone, don't be mad.
Ladies,
gentlemen,
brothers.
No need to explain.
Listen to me.
Just let them be mad. It's fine.
(Among us, there is a traitor)
This was Lin Yi's choice.
I think it's
very convincing.
Come on, you explain.
Lin Yi,
you picked him, right?
Lin Yi, you picked him, right?
He picked... No.
(Listen to my explanation)
(On one side, years of close friends)
Close friend in the industry,
Wang Yuwen.
(On one side, devoted brothers)
Xingxu's appearance unsettled some people.
This was Lin Yi's choice.
(Stirring the pot)
How do you explain that?
(Anxious and eager)
(Lin Yi's friendship is too crowded) - Lin Yi, you picked him, right?
- Lin Yi, you picked him, right?
(Listen to my explanation)
Everyone here...
Everyone here
is good-looking.
(Whose kettle is boiling?)
All are top-tier looks.
So why?
We are a group
that combines both looks and talent.
(So right)
(Strongly agree)
Speaking of looks,
it reminds me of...
It reminds me of
(Stunned)
the lamb soup Yuning made last time.
It was delicious.
(Thoroughly enjoying)
Yuning is really good at cooking.
In terms of the amount of salt he uses...
[*"Looks "and "salt" sound the same in Chinese]
In terms of the amount of salt
(Looks)
he uses,
(Salt Value)
Yuning is definitely the best.
(Can it be like this?)
(Huh?)
(Not finished yet)
Undeniably,
Yuning is also really good-looking.
Double top.
Dodged the philtrum,
but couldn't dodge the salt value.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
(The most willing episode)
Is there still another round?
Or are we going into the sea directly?
Do we have any more?
Shall we
head straight over?
One more question.
The last question.
(If old members miss one more question,
they go into the sea immediately)
If you're just one step away
from going into the sea...
Do we need an "if"?
(Say something we don't know)
Would Lin Yi and Guo Jingfei
feel bad for you
(Feel bad for us)
and call you back?
(Such unfamiliar terms)
(Bad ideas generating)
No. Would they feel bad for us
and come into the sea with us?
(Logic computing)
If they say,
"Yes, we'll join you",
we'll go together.
It's like this.
(Good boy)
You're...
This trick works.
Yuning.
(Recognition from the opponent)
It's good, right?
Really smart.
Handsome and smart. Good boy.
For this question,
we only check if both sides
have the same answer.
Yes.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's discuss.
(Heartless back view)
It's a binary choice.
They'll say no.
(Read his back)
I also think they'll say no.
Probably no.
Let me get used to this first.
Feels like we're about
to go into the sea.
Maybe we should
put on the rain boots first.
So we don't waste time later.
Bring me the paddle too.
We will lose our way later.
We're already hopeless, right?
- No hope at all, bro.
- Can't win.
We'll just say yes.
(Any brilliant ideas?)
Morally blackmail them.
(Really out of ideas)
How about this?
(Full-scale blackmail)
Paddle in while saying yes.
A sympathy trick, right?
Yes.
We don't listen to their answer.
- We just leave.
- Yes.
Put on the rain boots.
Let's go down.
(Old member answer: Yes)
To be honest,
we'd feel bad.
(But)
But they...
If they say no,
we won't respond at all,
and just leave.
Okay.
I think this round,
we don't cry or make a fuss,
but just turn around and leave.
Right.
True disappointment
isn't making a big fuss.
Let's be cool about it.
Make them feel bad.
Yeah, right.
(Completely unaware)
They'll definitely think,
after talking it over,
we'll choose yes.
Or they don't care at all.
They have to go into the sea.
Guo Jingfei.
Lin Yi.
Goodbye!
You're not giving us any chance at all,
are you?
Goodbye.
Straight into the water.
(I agree)
So heartbreaking!
Be happy.
Cheer up.
It's just life.
Life holds nine disappointments
- out of ten.
- Out of ten.
We've come to know you two.
(We haven't answered yet)
Look into my eyes.
(Trying to evoke the last bit of friendship)
Tell me your answer.
It's fine if you
don't let me look into your eyes.
You're the worst.
Our answer is yes.
(Hey?)
(Things unexpectedly got better)
We will keep them.
(Still confident)
We'll just say yes.
(Looks like it won't be needed)
Then we won't have to go into the sea.
You guys go.
We chose yes.
Really?
Their answer is yes.
We got it right.
Come on, take a step.
- Come on.
Come on.
Rain boots.
Hurry up.
No.
(Double-check)
We'll stop them, right?
Yes.
(Smart brain has disconnected)
And then...
If I say no...
Then we'd go into the sea directly.
Go into the sea.
Yes.
See, we've already put on the shoes.
(Overdid it)
(What just happened?)
Come on, put them on first.
It's a bit cold.
(Thoughtfully provided)
It's a bit cold underwater.
Come on, swap shoes now.
No.
I'm fine.
This brings bad luck. Don't change.
(Obediently put it down)
It's bad luck
if you don't change your shoes.
Let me tell you.
See, we won after we switched.
Yes.
We always have to be against you.
Barefoot fears not the shod.
Come on, both sides.
Same question.
We go into the sea?
- If they have to go into the sea...
Would you call them back?
Feel sorry for them.
Another calculation question.
Yes.
Right, you discuss first.
(Cool turn)
You discuss first.
(What is he being cocky about?)
It's hard.
But we're still one step ahead.
My gut says they'll choose no.
I want to pick no too.
(Let me think it over)
The kayak looks fun.
(Character persona, The reason we lose)
But for the character persona...
(It's a matter of public persona)
The six of us need to talk it over.
It is a bit tough for the six of us.
I think we have to choose yes.
Yes, probably.
The correct answer should be yes.
If we choose no
and still lose, it'd be awkward.
(This is on another level)
He's right.
Really.
This logic is correct.
You have to look at it this way.
It makes us look kind.
Yes, we are kind by nature.
I think it's just for show.
We felt no pity for them,
yet we got our comeuppance.
You know that feeling, right?
Like this.
Let's look into the camera
and sincerely say yes.
Okay, come on.
At least we'll be dignified.
Sincere.
Three.
- Two.
- Be sincere.
Three.
No.
(Not aware)
Yes.
(The brilliance of humanity
Old member answer: Yes)
Come on.
Do you have an answer?
What's your gut?
(Encrypted call)
Okay.
We'll look at them.
(Confidence strikes)
Three, two, one. Say it.
Three.
- Two.
- One.
- No.
- Yes.
(Yi Guo duo achieves ultimate victory)
(Leaving)
Why do you think
(No need to ask)
we don't care about you?
It doesn't matter.
Don't want to know the reason, bro.
(It doesn't matter anymore)
Let's go into the sea.
No choice.
Must we stare at you
- with eyes full of disappointment?
- Don't say it.
Don't want to hear it.
Don't say anything.
Stop talking.
Don't say another word.
Let's go.
Be careful.
(Silently helping)
Put your hands down.
Dirtying your boat.
(Companion type)
(Helping type)
Sit tight.
- Ready?
- One, two, three, you pull, I push.
Okay.
I'm steady.
It's actually fun.
This is really fun.
- This is really fun.
- I'm getting the hang of it.
This is so fun.
So interesting.
Thank them.
It does look really fun.
There's a shark.
Then you can kiss the shark.
Look.
Stargazing here is quite romantic.
Where are the stars?
There are stars in the sky.
Oh, there are.
Bump into you.
(Next, they will set off from here.)
(Exploring this fresher world together.)
We'll prove with actions
that we'll wait for you.
(Flip the longitude and latitude,
restart a fresh journey)
(Next Episode Preview)
Cross the line, and you're out.
The most handsome person in this room
goes out.
You're so handsome,
and good-looking.
Liu Yuning is the most handsome.
Just say that keyword and I'll leave.
This guy really
can't handle compliments.
Letting Naiwen win is no fun.
He's really dangerous.
I...
Should we eliminate those two first?
She wants to eliminate us two.
What did she say?
Eliminate us two.
Eliminate her first.
This game is just cruel.
(Who will stay till the end?)
We're going to Bird Island now.
So beautiful.
Oh my! These two.
Just bickering, right?
It's just like Gong Jun
and Liu Yuning, right?
This mission is called
You Know What I Mean.
Guo Jingfei.
Woo-hoo!
Chasing from behind.
Chen Xingxu wants to rebrand himself.
You control his hands.
(Control)
Wang Yuwen is back there, saying
- It's too expensive.
- it's too expensive.
Next,
you'll experience road tripping
and backpacking,
two travel styles.
(Arrogant)
Hitchhiking?
(Backpacker Team, Road Trip Team)
Pretty happy.
(Show-off)
Hope you have a great trip!
One, two, three, go.
(All about relaxation)
Right, left, right, left.
Going on an outing.
(Target is coming)
(Whizzing by)
Let's switch someone out.
As soon as I stand here,
the cars disappear.
Here it comes.
(Can the Backpacker Team
successfully hitch a ride?)