Gui Fang
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
For making you face so much criticism.
In the end, it's all because of me.
Why are you apologizing?
This isn't your fault.
The ones who should apologize are those people online.
Right, they should apologize.
I've thought about it.
This whole thing started because of me.
I have to help resolve it.
I know what kind of people you and Xiaocan are.
Better than anyone.
Don't worry, I'll definitely clear things up for you.
These are the Weibo posts they wrote.
I plan to clap back at every single one.
Take a look.
Are my comebacks okay?
If the comebacks are fine,
I'll post them on Weibo right away.
She's just a young-looking mom
with a good relationship with her son.
How can these people have such dirty minds?
Good comebacks.
If you really want to help,
let's print out all the screenshots.
And slap them right in their faces.
Look at this bunch of people.
They all look like decent human beings,
but how can they do such dog-like things?
That's not right.
You're insulting dogs.
If we want to capture all the malicious screenshots,
it'll take a lot of time and energy.
We need to make a plan before acting.
My dear Sister Rui,
what kind of plan do we need for this?
We just snap-snap screenshots,
rush into the police station,
and report the case immediately.
Just arrest them.
Nowadays, the burden of proof is on the claimant.
Whether reporting to the police,
or suing,
we still have to collect evidence.
And filter the information.
Everyone,
everyone.
Look here.
We have a new helper.
He's the main culprit.
If Wei Mingtian wasn't so famous,
there wouldn't be such a huge impact.
Right, blame him.
For things to escalate to this point,
you have to take full responsibility.
Come, come, take a look.
How many of your fans are on here?
Look at what they're saying.
And another thing.
Seeing you hang around my Godmother every day...
...just makes me angry.
How do you have the nerve to come here?
You're getting a bit personal there.
It is a bit obvious.
Is it that obvious?
Everything has two sides.
Maybe Wei Mingtian coming here...
...can actually help us out a lot.
Can you post a clarification statement on Weibo?
Yes.
I can post it.
Don't be mad, Brother Maizi.
Me, mad?
What right do I have to be mad?
I... How many times have I said it?
How many times did I tell you not to post a statement?
Do not post a statement.
But you, just as I got you off the trending topics...
...you spoke up.
Seriously.
I... I have no right to be mad.
I'm just a lowly agent.
You're the hot superstar.
Do you know?
Just this behavior of yours...
...how much trouble it brings to the company?
Do you know that because of this one Weibo post...
...how much overtime we all have to work?
Is there anyone else in our company?
Just me, just me, just me.
Do you know how much overtime I have to work?
But rumors need to be clarified.
I think the statement is pretty good.
Pretty good.
For the next couple of days...
...that account of yours...
...don't log into it.
I'll manage it.
I'm so pissed off.
My account has been sacrificed.
A glorious death.
Your sacrifice is valuable.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Coming.
Didn't go to class with Mom?
We'll study together tonight.
Isn't that too tiring?
I'm recording this.
Keep talking.
Go on, go on, go on.
You have the right to remain silent.
But every word you say now...
...will be used as evidence in court.
Sorry, buddy.
I, Li Wai, am a terrible person.
What I did to Godmother...
Don't mention it.
You're not allowed to laugh.
Don't laugh.
Reposted and called her an "old hag."
Think that's okay?
Even one sentence isn't okay. Screenshot it.
What about ones that don't name names...
...but are sarcastic? Can we sue if we screenshot them?
Screenshot it.
Then categorize them by severity.
Check if the reposts exceed five hundred.
Over five hundred counts as defamation.
The more reposts, the greater the liability.
Right.
We can sue for anything insulting.
Although the specific sentencing...
...depends on legal regulations.
But these people must be punished severely.
What we need to do...
...is find them all.
Right.
Xu Rui's method really works.
As soon as I said I was recording...
...no one dared to speak.
I finally got some peace and quiet.
Auntie.
My uncle asked a lawyer about it.
He's handled this kind of case before.
He has experience.
Take a look at this case first.
Let's make an appointment to see him in a couple of days.
This...
How could this...
Thank you all so much.
Thanks to you guys.
It's all my fault.
I've taken up so much of your time.
How can you blame yourself?
Blame those lowlifes for talking trash.
Those lowlifes...
They're so two-faced.
Each one curses filthier than the last.
Click on their homepage,
and it's all "peace and love".
They turn others' lives into a mess,
but want to live the good life themselves.
Dream on.
That's the internet world for you.
Everyone thinks
it's safe to hide behind anonymous accounts.
They dare to say any vicious thing.
What kind of people are they?
Why do you look even angrier than me?
Screenshot it.
Auntie.
You, as the person involved, have to do the sorting.
The ones you think aren't that serious,
drag them into this folder.
These people,
we can file a civil lawsuit in court.
Demanding compensation and an apology.
The ones you think are more serious,
drag them into this folder.
These people,
besides having to respond in court,
we also have to call the police.
Stop.
Is there a problem, Auntie?
Yes.
Can you stop calling me Auntie?
It sounds really awkward to me.
I just keep feeling like
I'm taking advantage of you.
Gui Fang rolls off the tongue better.
Exactly, I was suffocating.
My god.
Fang.
Gui Fang.
Fang Fang.
Isn't this much better?
Everyone's happy.
Come on, let's do this.
Let's do this.
Go, go!
Just get it done.
It's so late.
Hurry, stop working, let's go eat.
Forget it, instant noodles are fine.
One Braised Beef, thanks.
Plus one.
Plus two.
Stop adding!
Nothing should get in the way of a meal.
Let's go, hurry back.
Mom will cook for you.
Let's go.
Mom is cooking!
Going home!
Xiaocan, look what they're saying.
Help me, quick, help me think of a comeback.
It's so awful.
Come in.
We're home!
Quick, change your shoes.
Li Wai is here too.
Just put it here.
Say hello.
How come you guys are here?
Hello.
Wait.
Xu Rui, why are you here too?
Xu Rui, why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I want to wear this pair.
We bought ingredients.
We're all having hot pot together.
Wait.
What time is it? You're eating now?
We were all busy working together just now.
Didn't have time to eat.
So we bought ingredients to cook something together.
Guests are here.
You entertain them first, I'll just...
Li Wai.
Hurry and entertain them.
Okay, okay, okay.
Kong Xiaocan, come help me with the ingredients.
One-eighty.
Hurry up.
Where is there 180?
Let me set up the table first.
So cute.
Cute, cute.
This looks so much like Fang.
This doesn't look like her.
How did his eyes get smaller as he grew up?
Didn't he have double eyelids when he was little?
This also looks like Fang. This looks like Fang.
Her balcony is like a little vegetable garden.
Oh my god.
My god.
What is this?
This is green onion, right?
Green onion.
Scallions.
Celery.
Fang really...
Does she really need to buy groceries?
She's so clingy with her son, it's definitely unhealthy.
In the future, what good girl
would want to be with her son?
If my mom clung to me like that, I couldn't stand it.
Xiaocan.
Do you think...
...that Mom is too clingy with you now?
You've got that backwards, right?
Who's clinging to whom here?
I'm the one clinging to you.
Do you think I'm too clingy with you?
Are you teasing me?
I've realized that now...
...you've really grown up.
I... I'd rather hear that I've grown taller.
Smells so good, so good.
It really smells amazing.
This slice of luncheon meat is mine. I'm starving.
I reserved it. It has my name on it, nobody take it.
I'm starving to death.
It's not cooked yet. Wait for the pot to boil.
Darn it, darn it.
Take a sip, take a sip, take a sip.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat tripe.
If you ask me...
...you guys are so efficient.
Does that mean tomorrow...
...we can hand the evidence over to the police?
Not just the police side.
We need to file a report.
There are many other steps to take too.
First, we go to the local notary office.
To get all these posts notarized.
You have to go there in person.
Then go to the court to file a lawsuit.
Requesting the real information of the infringer.
If they provide it...
...we'll settle before the trial.
Then sue those who posted.
These parts can be handled by a lawyer.
So...
Is the legal fee expensive?
You don't need to worry about that.
You can demand that those who hurt you...
...cover your legal fees.
It costs money to notarize the posts.
You need to keep the invoices.
And any costs incurred during the lawsuit...
...keep the invoices for all of them.
We'll make those bad guys reimburse you later.
Okay.
Sister Rui.
You are so amazing.
Did you secretly study law or something?
Thank you for your hard work.
Just eat.
Here, Sister Rui, I'll eat more on your behalf.
You need to keep a clear head at all times.
I think I just scrolled past Wei Mingtian.
It looks like he's clarifying things for Gui Fang.
I just want to say...
...what's being said online isn't true.
Gui Fang is really a wonderful person.
I was the one who dragged her into this.
I hope you all...
Stop pulling my hair.
How many times have I told you?
I told you not to get involved, not to get involved!
You just had to stir up trouble for yourself, didn't you?
Do you know what's most important right now?
It's the truth.
The truth?
Does the truth pay your rent?
Does the truth send you to college?
Does the truth pay your tuition?
Do you really think those people...
...care what the truth is?
Let me tell you.
The truth right now is...
...that you rely on the company for everything.
You rely on me.
I am the company.
Then I quit.
Anyway, I won't be an accomplice to this.
I quit.
Fine.
You've seen the contract.
You know how much the penalty is.
You pay the compensation to them.
I'm done earning this money.
Get out.
Look at you acting all tough.
Starting a rebellion?
I'm telling you, for the next two days...
...don't go to school.
As for work...
...I'll pick you up and drop you off.
You're not allowed to go anywhere.
I'll ask for leave from the school.
Ms. Kong,
the platform has already provided us with
the real information of the anonymous accounts.
Based on the list we've compiled so far,
the ones with the most serious impact
are the operator of this account,
named Zhao Chuyi,
and the rumor mongers who posted the most initially,
as well as a few leading accounts.
Ms. Kong, let me confirm with you again.
Regarding your request,
do you wish to sue everyone?
Or just sue these few?
My child has already taken me to report it to the police.
Can I still sue everyone?
Hold on.
It's like this.
Of course you can.
The police handle the public security punishment.
Right.
The court handles civil compensation.
Yes.
It's just that the waiting time might be longer.
Right.
So, do you...
want everyone to bear your costs
and demand compensation?
Or mainly demand it from these few people?
If you demand everyone to bear it,
it's too scattered.
And hard to enforce.
Then let's just go with these few people.
All costs will be borne by them.
Is it okay if the others just apologize?
Hold on.
I'm not very close with her either.
Let me summarize.
All posters
need to delete the defamatory posts
and publicly apologize to Ms. Kong.
Right.
These few people
need to bear your litigation fees, legal fees,
notarization fees, and emotional distress damages.
Yes. Is that okay?
Is that okay?
Will this punishment go into their permanent records?
This...
might depend on how the school handles it.
Also,
I still suggest you contact
the other involved party,
Mr. Wei Mingtian.
If you can act as co-plaintiffs
and sue together,
it will definitely further expand the impact.
Yes.
Let's not do that.
Don't drag him into this anymore.
Otherwise, it'll just get more confusing.
Actually, I tried contacting him.
But his phone either goes unanswered
or is just turned off.
I don't know what's going on.
Thank you, thank you.
You're welcome.
I didn't really help much.
Just used a bit of data.
Where are you going?
Brother Maizi.
I have a teacher who is very strict.
Three leaves count as one absence.
I really have to go to class today.
Isn't this a special situation?
The teacher will surely understand.
For the next couple of days,
stop thinking about classes.
In about half an hour,
go put on a face mask.
Your skin isn't looking too good.
Focus your mind on work, right?
Yes.
Brother Maizi.
I think you're absolutely right.
Lately, I...
I'll just focus wholeheartedly on work.
I won't go to school for now.
Why are you pushing me?
I want to sit right here.
And why are you shouting?
I...
It's just...
My dialogue teacher said...
that even in daily life,
we should keep practicing our lines.
That way, when we get on stage,
interacting with the partner will be more natural.
You should have told me sooner.
I could've just been your partner.
Let's practice, let's practice, let's practice.
It's good that you figured it out.
Tell me,
isn't going to school just for getting a good job?
And now you already have a good job.
So why bother going to school?
Right?
Yeah.
Don't worry, I'll work hard.
I'm not going anywhere.
That's not necessary either.
Recently,
I was thinking about
booking you for a couple of variety shows.
Let's keep the hype up.
No need.
I appreciate your kindness.
Appreciate what?
This is your job.
I just feel that...
too much exposure recently isn't good.
Makes sense.
The internet hasn't been peaceful lately.
So no variety shows.
Forget it, forget it.
Better to keep a low profile.
Okay.
If we get into a lawsuit...
you know?
Surely...
we'll be on all kinds of trending topics.
Exactly.
It will definitely blow up.
So, keeping a low profile is better.
Good that you understand.
It seems your dialogue skills
have made significant progress.
But you are still young.
The road ahead is long and hard.
Alright.
Brother Maizi, I'll go put on a mask now.
You sit here by yourself.
Okay.
I'm leaving now.
Go ahead.
Say no more.
Go.
Go, good boy.
Pour me a glass of water.
Pour one for yourself too.
The kid wants to do stage plays recently.
The stage builds character, but...
the money comes too slow.
This is too hard on the agent.
Xiaotian.
Pause your dialogue lessons for a couple of days.
It's hard to get TV roles if your lines are too good.
Excuse me, classmate, coming through.
This is Donghu Police Station.
Gui Fang has sued you. Come by when you have time.
What's wrong?
For real?
Gui Fang actually sued me.
What?
They said I need to go over there too.
But I just reposted it, that's all.
How am I involved?
I only reposted one thing.
Yeah, they told me to go too.
Hello?
I just reposted it, that's all.
I'll have a stain on my record.
Then how will I find a job?
Hurry up and check.
Is it that serious?
Is it really necessary just for saying a few words about her?
It is. Of course it is.
People live for their dignity.
If you don't fight for your own dignity,
who can you count on?
Okay.
I know about this now.
The school takes this matter very seriously too.
Gui Fang, all I can say is...
the school's position...
is definitely to protect the students.
No, no, no.
No.
Why, why, why is she suing us?
We're victims too!
I don't know.
Maybe she's mad at me.
What kind of temper is that?
Brother Maizi, you don't know her.
Gui Fang is really resilient.
She's someone who used just one year
to raise her math score from the teens
to over a hundred points.
She's quite remarkable.
And she won't give up easily.
Unless she sees a result.
You... you... you... you really are...
Why did you provoke her?
Look, look, look.
It's number three on the trending list.
Do you know what trending number three means?
What does trending number three mean?
This is a good thing!
I can even raise your price.
That's right, seriously.
I got dragged in by your emotions.
What a great opportunity.
Come on, give me your classmate's number.
What's her name again?
Gui... Gui Fang.
Give me the phone number.
I'll contact her.
Right now...
this is the best...
chance to operate.
We'll go with her...
to the court...
and let the state uphold justice for us.
We'll take the moral high ground
and just stand there.
Then your status will shoot right up.
Yeah, yeah.
Brother Maizi, you're so smart.
You know, you...
still have a lot to learn.
In the entertainment industry...
the art of turning danger into safety...
bringing the dead back to... What are you doing?
The phone number, right?
Xiaoyin, I'm here, I'm here.
I'm waiting for you right here.
Hello.
Can I have a word with you?
You are?
I'm Zhao Chuyi, a senior.
I'll post a clarification and publicly apologize to you.
Please drop the lawsuit.
Can you please not make me go to the police station?
You're the one behind the Duda Confessions account. You...
What you're doing is wrong.
Apologizing and deleting the post are mandatory.
But you also have to take responsibility
for what you've done.
I will. I definitely will.
This is the money from my part-time job this month.
I'll give you my whole paycheck next month too.
I run this account
just to earn some tips.
My mom is in poor health.
Monthly medical bills have drained the family.
I can't count on my dad.
I know I was wrong this time.
But I just don't want my mom to know.
I'm afraid she'll be sad.
It hasn't been easy for you, kid.
You think you're the only one with a hard life?
Life isn't easy for anyone.
Just because you're struggling
doesn't mean you can guilt-trip others here, right?
Let me tell you something.
Even for the sake of argument,
even if your life is really that tragic,
you can't make money by exploiting others.
Is that how your mother raised you?
I'm sorry.
Gui Fang, I was simply amazing just now.
That was simply the most...
...successful argument of my life.
Let's go, eat something good to celebrate.
Let's go.
That was so satisfying.
Classmate, take a look at our Haidu Media.
Classmate, check it out.
Classmate.
It's okay, there's probably no one here.
Why don't you rest for a while?
Classmate.
Please take a look.
Classmate, Auntie.
I am the one...
...who reposted a post online.
But I really had no bad intentions.
I just used inappropriate words.
Just following the trend.
Please drop the lawsuit, Auntie.
Auntie, I didn't mean to either.
My parents sold everything to send me to college.
My family is poor to begin with.
Gui Fang.
It's me, Senior Cao.
I-I-I just reposted it.
How can you be so heartless?
My dad was just diagnosed with cancer last month.
He's just hoping I graduate well and find a good job.
How can I explain this to him?
My mom passed away right after I got into Duda.
In the hospital, she hoped I would graduate well.
So what am I supposed to do now?
You should have some basic logic when playing the victim.
You said your dad runs every morning and is fit as a fiddle.
Don't fight, don't fight, don't fight.
Stop fighting, the Student Union will deduct credits.
Mom.
Mom, get up.
What are you doing?
Get up.
Alright, stop fighting.
Get up. Fighting...
What are you doing?
Writing so much here...
People like this are just trying to grab attention.
We probably don't need to...
Mom.
Look at the situation now.
These young people...
They're all like this, following the trend.
I... I also follow trends when I'm bored.
Exactly, exactly.
Yes, it's not good either.
But...
It's not that serious, right?
Let's just catch the first few people...
The ones who started rumors and took photos.
We just sue them.
No.
Following the trend makes them perpetrators too.
Yes, but... but...
We can't guarantee, right?
Whether among these people there are some with bad intentions.
People who hold a grudge.
What if they pull some dirty tricks?
Wouldn't we be at a disadvantage?
There's no need, let's just avoid it.
How can you say that?
Good people get hurt and have to be careful everywhere?
While bad people go unpunished and swagger around?
You are aiding and abetting evil.
You've heard of a thief stealing for a thousand days.
Have you heard of guarding against a thief for a thousand days?
Can we guard against them?
Guard every day?
That's why we must catch those thieves.
Make them pay the price.
So they dare not do it again.
Fang, let's go.
That's my mom.
Would I really
do anything to her?
Don't be mad. Don't be mad.
Don't lower yourself to his level.
Don't hold it against him.
Fang, let me show you something.
Did you see what she's wearing today?
Like an exploded shrimp cake.
That jackfruit from Class 4.
She seems to think she's so fashionable.
Dressed so weirdly.
It's really embarrassing.
I started reading fashion magazines when I was little.
When I was in middle school,
I started trying to make my own clothes to wear.
I made them and wore them myself; I didn't hurt anyone.
But I don't know why,
one day,
suddenly someone on the school forum
started a thread to mock me.
I was too young back then.
I didn't dare to fight back.
Thinking about it now,
I just feel very regretful.
I should have grabbed them by the hair back then
and fought them hard.
Otherwise,
this incident would just become a
wound that will never heal for me.
What they said was too much.
Did your parents not handle this back then?
My mom thought I was in the wrong first.
Instead, she wouldn't let me touch the sewing machine anymore.
My dad actually went to school to find the teacher.
He also got a few boys to come out and apologize to me.
But I knew they weren't sincere.
Later, when they saw me at school,
they would still make faces at me.
Fang,
just like among those people coming to apologize to you,
some are seniors looking for jobs
and don't want to get disciplined.
They aren't truly repenting.
Gui Fang,
I don't want you to be like me
and be left with a wound like this.
Don't feel aggrieved. Don't feel aggrieved.
No more feeling aggrieved.
Hello, Auntie.
We are here to apologize.
Yes.
We thought Xiaotian... that student...
was being bullied.
We were upholding justice.
We were one-sided.
We hope you can forgive us.
Yes.
You thought
Wei Mingtian was being bullied?
No, no, no.
No, no.
Where did you get that idea from?
Besides,
spreading rumors about me and helping him,
is there any connection between the two?
Look, Auntie,
you can't be so unforgiving.
Don't you just want us to apologize
and pay you money?
Stop talking.
How much money do you want?
We'll just pay you.
We'll give it all to you.
You... you can't be so ruthless.
You can't let us actually get disciplined
just so you'll be happy.
Alright, stop talking.
Um, Auntie,
we didn't mean that.
We are sincerely apologizing to you.
Then we won't disturb you anymore.
Get back to your studies.
We're leaving now.
Bye-bye.
Come here, come here.
What are you two doing?
Arguing with her like that.
You, why were you so aggressive with her?
No, she just... she...
We can't suffer this loss for nothing.
And besides, in the school,
surely it's not just the three of us who hate her.
We have to be steady, you know?
Wait for this to blow over.
We even bought a fruit basket.
What a waste.
Watch out.
Student, are you okay?
Careful, she might fake an injury.
Watch out, she might sue you.
No,
yes, they were jumping on the bandwagon with their mockery.
But don't stoop to their level.
What if they didn't mean any harm?
Who hasn't made a mistake before?
Have you never badmouthed anyone?
I... that's not what I meant.
I just went through your Weibo.
This post.
And this one.
Are these things you said?
That was back when
that happened, and I stepped in to help.
Why... why are you digging up my past?
Because I wanted to know if you jumped on the bandwagon too.
If you also hurt others without realizing it.
That's why you think
those minor hurts don't matter.
Anyway, I've never talked about others.
Never been mean-spirited.
And never judged anyone.
From my perspective,
people like me
are the majority, the normal ones.
If the remaining minority
cannot restrain their words and actions,
then let the law restrain them.
What's wrong?
Coach.
What happened?
You're finally here.
Xu Rui has been running like this all night.
I can't even stop her.
Good.
What a fighting spirit this is!
Truly moving.
Let me tell you,
in her,
I see a shadow of my younger self.
No, Coach.
She can't keep running like this.
Shouldn't we
increase the training intensity a bit?
Makes sense.
Very promising.
But
a person's stamina has a limit.
You can't keep the training string too tight.
If it's too tight, isn't she likely
to get injured?
Is your foot okay?
It's just a scratch. I'm fine.
Auntie, don't be sad.
You were protecting your legitimate rights.
It wasn't malicious revenge.
Don't take their words to heart.
I just feel that...
because of this mess,
caused you and Xiaocan to fight,
and brought up bad memories for Xiaoyin.
Is it worth turning a good life into a mess?
I'm really tired.
I just hope this blows over soon.
Let's not make it any bigger.
So everyone can live happily like before.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Gui Fang.
Gui Fang! Gui Fang!
Wait a second, Gui Fang.
I really did it this time.
I can finally help you too.
You... what did you do?
You're totally famous now.
On the path of fighting cyberbullying,
Ms. Kong has shown us
unparalleled resilient spirit,
becoming a role model for countless people.
Let's also hear
the public's opinion on this matter.
Excuse me, student.
What do you think about the recent events
regarding Ms. Kong Gui Fang?
You mean about Auntie Kong Gui Fang?
Yes, yes.
This matter has caused a sensation in society.
I think
this auntie did a great job.
She taught me how to handle such things.
First, collect evidence.
Public prosecution, suing.
Learn to use the weapon of law to protect oneself.
This is what I learned from this matter.
Finally, I want to say to the auntie:
Auntie,
you have elevated my understanding
of the law.
Go Auntie!
Keep it up! I support you!
Okay.
Many thanks to our "Student Elevation."
We strongly agree with his remarks.
But his behavior on the escalator...
we strongly advise against imitating.
You're talking about Kong Gui Fang?
Yes, yes.
I was just watching it.
Young people these days...
they have no idea of the immensity of heaven and earth.
Sir, don't get excited.
If you ask me, they just... just... just...
just have it too easy.
Don't get excited, sir.
They have nothing to do,
so they think about bullying others.
They should be punished by the law.
Make them fear!
Be afraid!
Okay sir, please don't get excited.
Thank you very much for supporting
our interview.
Okay, many thanks to "Mr. Excited"
for his excited remarks.
But his excited remarks
have also brought Ms. Kong Gui Fang
very strong support.
Okay.
Hope everyone follows and likes.
Thank you, everyone.
Did you hire a team to do this?
You're so generous.
It wasn't me.
Brother Maizi contacted them.
But he didn't let me film.
It's a bit of a pity.
They even did street interviews.
That's so thoughtful.
Brother Li Wai spoke well, right?
And him too.
Li Wai?
Which one is him?
They are all him.
Hello, Professor Wang.
Gui Fang.
The TV station's program team came to the school.
They proposed filming a special episode.
So tomorrow,
all students involved in this matter
will be gathered in the lecture hall.
The school hopes you can cooperate with the TV interview.
I said before,
the school's stance is always to protect the students.
They are also students of the school.
These are the Weibo posts they wrote.
I plan to clap back at every single one.
Take a look.
Is my comeback good?
Who's clinging to whom between us?
I'm clinging to you, right?
Do you think I'm too clingy?
Are you calling me out?
Why do you guys look even angrier than me?
Gui Fang, I don't want you to end up like me,
left with a wound like this.
But Gui Fang,
you don't have to do what anyone expects.
I know that in your heart,
you have your own sense of justice.
Regarding this footage,
we'll shoot the exterior again later...
I told you the school would step in.
After all, they are the school's students.
The law can't punish the masses.
We have to stick together.
I know how this works.
Okay.
Student Kong,
how are you feeling right now?
Will you accept a settlement with your classmates?
If there are classmates today
who sincerely apologize to me,
I accept.
Yes, our Student Kong
is still very friendly.
And she also...
But regardless of whether they apologize,
I will not accept a settlement.
I believe the law and school regulations
will give me the fairest result.
I think this auntie did a great job.
Some people just have it too easy.
Go for it! I support you!
Is my hair okay?
It's fine.
I have experience with this.
I previously filmed
a promotional video for the Public Security Bureau.
I've got experience.
I'm a veteran actor.
They should be punished by the law!
Make them fear!
Fe- fear!
His passionate remarks
have also given Ms. Kong Gui Fang
strong support.
Let's interview
the next enthusiastic viewer.
Is there something wrong with you?
Let me see.
Look at the people you found.
No, no.
You smashed my phone like this.
Sister, I'm sorry.
Why did you get so excited?
I just got caught up in the emotion.
I... I didn't mean to.
I can't believe this.
Let Xiaotian buy you a new one.
You dropped it, you pay.