(Ace of Ace)
(THE NEW SIX)
(The CrewOne)
(8TURN)
(ONEUS)
(YOUNITE)
(CRAVITY)
(TEMPEST)
(Road to Kingdom: Ace of Ace)
They will battle with songs of three different groups...
(Round 1 VS Mission, triple match)
(A merciless battle between 3 teams)
(We'll forget about seniority and fight with them.)
(We have already forgotten about it before coming up to the stage.)
(CRAVITY seeks revenge through their first team performance.)
(The CrewOne prepared to strike back with gritted teeth.)
(Who is the special guest visiting The CrewOne?)
(Ju Yeon of THE BOYZ)
(Sharing great tips as the previous winner)
(He gave us the tip when we weren't sure with the direction.)
(We'll put on a great performance.)
(How will The CrewOne's performance that became richer...)
(with the previous winner's advice turn out?)
(Cheering)
I'll watch this 30 times once their performance airs on TV.
(ONEUS is back with impressive stage manners.)
(It's a "Kingsman" theme.)
(How will the birth of a new hero...)
(reinterpreted through an action performance be?)
That's insane.
(And the long-awaited CRAVITY's first team performance)
(They more than made up for the Evaluation Match.)
(How will CRAVITY's performance that drew admiration look?)
(It's beautiful.)
(Revealing the final rankings of Round 1, VS Mission)
(Team Ranking, Ace Ranking)
(It's purely shocking.)
(How can the results turn out like that?)
(It's not over until it's over.)
(Another benefit that the ace must win?)
(Is it a battle?)
(What's the result of Round 1 that left everyone in shock?)
(Road to Kingdom: Ace of Ace)
(For Round One, they performed in front of on-site judges.)
(To win 1,000 benefit points,)
(they begin the real competition.)
(The scores from Round 1 and Round 2...)
(will be combined to determine the elimination candidates.)
(I'm suddenly getting nervous.)
(Their teams' pride...)
(hangs on the Round 1 VS Mission.)
(The opening act of the VS Mission, the Stray Kids Match)
(As always,)
(we will win.)
(As always! Oh, my.)
(That really made me mad.)
(I really want to win.)
(THE NEW SIX picked a B-side track that wasn't as well-known.)
(I think they made the rap part.)
("Phobia" was recreated with a unique charm by THE NEW SIX.)
(The production is amazing.)
(Impressed)
(TEMPEST selected a well-known mega hit.)
(Look at the scale.)
(TEMPEST created a strong performance with "MANIAC.")
(They produced a good dance break.)
(But it's too similar.)
(The two teams created similar stages...)
(for the Stray Kids Match.)
(Who will win the Stray Kids Match and take the benefit points?)
(The second match, the ENHYPEN Match, follows.)
(They don't need to announce who their ace is.)
(Who is 8TURN's ace?)
(8TURN and YOUNITE came on stage with opposite themes.)
(8TURN emphasized their clean, powerful choreography.)
(They're perfectly synchronized!)
(8TURN showed the drive and energy...)
(of the youngest team with "Future Perfect.")
(They focused on the choreography over the composition.)
(I'm kind of excited for the next team.)
(Unlike 8TURN, YOUNITE used many props.)
(It made me regret for a second.)
(EUNSANG started the performance with some amazing acting.)
(It's so intense.)
(YOUNITE shocked the audience with their flashy "Bite Me" stage.)
(I think they're really insane!)
(The on-site judges vote to decide which team wins.)
(Who will win the 1,000 benefit points?)
(Voting closed)
(The results of the VS Match was delivered to each team.)
(THE NEW SIX wins the Stray Kids Match.)
(YOUNITE wins the ENHYPEN Match.)
(This time,)
(we won.)
(Enjoying their victory)
(We lost the VS Match.)
(But the final results for Round 1 are not in yet.)
(How will the team and ace rankings for Round 1 turn out?)
(Stray Kids, THE NEW SIX wins, TEMPEST loses)
(ENHYPEN, 8TURN loses, YOUNITE wins)
(Road to Kingdom: Ace of Ace)
Road to Kingdom.
Round One VS Mission.
We expect this match to be the most intense.
This is the most interesting match.
This must be so interesting.
- I'm curious. - I'm so curious.
They will battle with songs of three different groups...
for a triple match.
(Screaming)
(Hi!)
How many are there?
The stage is so full.
There are so many of them.
(Through their smiles,)
(everyone can feel their tension and nerves.)
Oh, triple.
I'm most excited for this match.
- Me too. I'm so excited. - Me too.
I'm glad our team isn't part of that.
I kind of feel that way.
I think there will be the most to see.
- They're all different songs. - Right.
They have to battle each other with songs...
of different artists.
I think that'll make it very exciting.
We don't know what the audience will prefer,
so that'll be the biggest match.
In the Evaluation Match, HWAN WOONG...
got first place in the Ace Battle.
The CrewOne's Lim Jimin got second place.
We didn't see CRAVITY's performance in the Evaluation Match.
I'm curious what performance they'll show us.
I think that's the main event.
Before the three teams perform,
please tell us your goals for Round One.
We'll show you what kind of team ONEUS is.
We're very determined.
We'll show you the force...
of a big team.
Let's go.
ONEUS debuted earlier than us.
The CrewOne is the youngest group.
Today, we'll forget about all of that...
and compete as equals.
(He's no joke.)
Sparks are already flying.
He's saying, "This is a competition."
This is going to be a bloody fight.
Forget about seniority? We're all equals now.
Not you.
You're not there.
I see. Okay.
(I will forget about seniority one day too!)
Please introduce your ace for Round One, ONEUS.
(Who is ONEUS's ace for the triple match?)
Who could it be?
- I'm so curious. - Who is it?
ONEUS's ace...
He did so well as our ace for the Evaluation Match.
The winning team of the Ace Battle is...
(ONEUS's HWAN WOONG got first place in the Ace Battle.)
(Exclaiming)
(An impressive feat for it being their first time on Road to Kingdom)
Because the Round One scores count,
we need to win the Ace Battle.
So maybe HWAN WOONG should be the ace one more time.
ONEUS's ace for Round One's VS Mission...
is HWAN WOONG.
(ONEUS's strategy meeting after the Evaluation Match)
We're only done with the Evaluation Match now.
But we did pretty well, right?
(They got 1st in the Ace Battle and 3rd in the Team Battle!)
But even though we did well, we got zero points.
- Because the points don't count. - Right.
And we have to battle the teams we wanted to avoid the most.
The two teams with lots of members.
I was surprised.
(ONEUS was third to choose their match.)
(The match selection continued.)
(The 1-versus-1 matches filled up first.)
What?
(Their happiness was short-lived as they suddenly became worried.)
(Only the triple match was open.)
(Only CRAVITY and The CrewOne, the two largest teams, remained.)
We don't have enough members.
We wanted to avoid that team the most.
Despite having many members,
they have strong energy as one.
I think that's a big advantage.
As for CRAVITY,
I didn't know what kind of strategy they had.
But they're famous for being good dancers.
They have many talented members.
We were worried about those two teams.
The next day, we stayed up all night picking a song.
- Right. - Right.
"Lemonade" came up.
- And "Baggy Jeans." - "Baggy Jeans."
"Fact Check" came up too.
NCT has many units.
So we had many options for which song to choose.
(They selected the song with many options in mind.)
I think our weapon...
- is stage presence. - Right.
I want people to feel the energy...
of our live performance in person.
It could be dangerous,
but we chose "Kick It."
"Kick It" performed by ONEUS.
- What? - What?
(NCT 127's mega hit with a memorable and intense theme)
"Kick It" is a very famous song...
covered by many idols.
That means it's a very risky choice.
Let's show them the power of a well-known song.
(NCT 127, "Kick It," a hip-hop dance song...)
(with energetic vocals, this title track of their 2nd album...)
(became popular for their dynamic martial arts performance.)
With "Kick It,"
the Asian costumes were so memorable for me.
Should we face it head on and enhance the song's colour?
Or should we change directions and show our own take on it?
I think going with our own take on it would be a bit better.
A new take is more fun for those watching.
- Right. - Right.
Since the title includes the meaning of hero...
Is there a cool hero?
Who will be Bruce Lee?
(Laughing)
The Hulk. Iron Man.
Heroes wear special suits.
Superman wears his underwear over his pants.
Do you remember what we did when we first debuted?
That...
(What are you talking about?)
"Kingsman?"
(ONEUS did a "Kingsman" theme when they first debuted.)
(How about this?)
They're heroes in a way.
Right. Wearing suits could be nice.
I can't really imagine it.
No team has performed "Kick It" wearing suits.
Right.
We made a bold choice and picked "Kingsman,"
which could be seen as the complete opposite theme.
Gentle but kind of fun.
This could fit this song well.
I think the umbrellas would be best for the dance break.
With two people, we can hook the handles.
Sliding out like this from below...
I think sliding would be cool.
Yes, something like this.
And then...
(It's looking good.)
We used as many props as possible...
to help the audience understand our theme.
This is the secret room...
of ONEUS's "Kick It" stage.
Into the secret door!
One, two, three.
Ta-da.
(KEON HEE was here, but now he's not?)
(Here I am.)
We tried to make a performance...
full of many visualizations.
Let's start ONEUS's rehearsal.
This shouldn't be here.
Yes. That's perfect.
Is there something uncomfortable in the back?
I'll try it now.
(They thoroughly check their lines of movement.)
In the Evaluation Match,
we made a few mistakes with the props.
(ONEUS made some mistakes with the props...)
(during the Evaluation Match.)
Let's make sure we don't repeat the same mistakes.
That thought was really in our heads.
We couldn't help...
but be nervous and tense.
Team ONEUS.
I knew it.
- A second time. - He's doing it again.
- He needs to be better than before. - Right.
He must be very nervous.
("Kick It" by ONEUS)
(A new take on the original Asian theme with a new hero)
Manners.
(A performance with dynamic action)
Maketh.
Man.
Is it "Kingsman?"
It's a "Kingsman" theme.
That scene.
Man.
The cup will go flying!
- Oh, he changed! - What is this?
How did he change so fast?
This isn't right!
They prepared something like this?
- What? - He went up there.
- When did he get up there? - This is insane.
So cool.
Let's go!
(ONEUS's ace, HWAN WOONG)
(You can view the full version of this performance on YouTube.)
(The number of views will be reflected in the Finals.)
- ONEUS! - ONEUS!
They did well.
They have a vibe that comes from their experience.
Yes. They definitely had a different energy.
Right.
I could feel they were more experienced than us.
- I'm burning up. - I should stretch my back too.
I'm getting nervous.
(ONEUS finished their performance with no mistakes.)
That was so nice, wasn't it?
I even had fun in the middle.
That was the first time I had fun...
performing on a competition show.
I think we performed...
as much as we prepared with no mistakes.
I felt a sense of accomplishment after this performance.
It's been a while since we had a successful performance...
- at a competition. - Right.
- That was fun. Good work, everyone. - Good work!
(They can only clap.)
Bruce Lee.
I never imagined...
- this version of "Kick It." - Exactly.
I think HWAN WOONG is so talented.
Totally.
I think he'll get first place in the Ace Ranking.
No. What am I saying?
- Hey. - YUN GYU is first.
- What am I saying? - But seriously.
(Suddenly feeling like he lost)
How dare you?
Do you want to go get some air, YOON SUNG?
What am I saying? Get it together.
What am I saying?
I get why they didn't change their ace.
- Right. - He's confident.
He's confident and talented.
To be honest, the other four members seemed...
a bit too timid.
I don't know how it felt watching it in person.
It felt...
like a performance centering around the ace.
Instead of the team supporting the ace,
it felt like the ace was carrying the team on his back.
HWAN WOONG was the most memorable.
- Next is the largest group. - Exactly.
You're right.
That's the order.
The CrewOne. Let's get it.
Next is the second team of the triple match.
The CrewOne's performance will begin now.
(Very excited)
Okay. This is the first time...
for us to perform live for the audience.
We will no longer get 6th, 5th, 4th, 3rd, or 2nd place.
- We have to get first now. Okay? - Okay.
Let's prove ourselves!
- Let's show them. - Let's go.
Go!
We will never experience the humiliation...
from the Evaluation Match ever again.
Automatically, The CrewOne gets sixth place in the Team Ranking.
(6th place, The CrewOne)
It's okay.
- It's not okay. - That's disappointing.
Did our performance deserve sixth place?
We got sixth place,
but that means we were last out of the teams that performed.
I thought our performance had better attention to detail.
Getting sixth place was very disappointing.
I felt dejected, angry, and irritated.
I'm so mad.
I'm irritated.
I thought the Streaming Evaluation had a big influence.
Because that was 70 percent of the final score.
I felt rushed.
- Like we didn't have time. - Right.
We need to win over the public soon.
Round One's mission is VS.
- What? - Three teams will battle?
I'm sure everyone will avoid the 1-on-1-on-1 match.
Let's avoid the triple match.
We must avoid that.
I made my selection.
(But YOUNITE took the last spot for a 1 versus 1 match.)
(The 6th and 7th place teams automatically got the triple match.)
We have to go against CRAVITY and ONEUS.
No.
(Their opponent teams are well-known and talented.)
This is pretty tough.
This is the group of death.
How did we end up in a group like this?
If only we were a bit higher...
Seriously.
We really wanted to avoid them.
Thinking of competing against them...
This won't be easy.
Both teams had very high scores in the public popularity evaluation.
They were the strong teams.
They were at the very top.
In the initial public popularity vote, CRAVITY got...
- first place. - First place.
CRAVITY really is popular.
ONEUS got first place in the Streaming Evaluation.
I thought their experience and teamwork made them strong.
And the fact that they were well-known.
We think they have a good balance of all three factors,
but...
we could still have a chance.
Okay.
- Then we get THE BOYZ. - Yes.
- It's okay. I like it. - I like it.
Things went according to plan.
Let's do THE BOYZ.
THE BOYZ also has 11 members, just like us.
And we thought their music fit our image well.
We want to add many conceptual elements.
(Very relieved)
I like THE BOYZ.
I went to show everyone...
how great of a performance we can deliver.
We'll receive the energy of Road to Kingdom's first kings...
and win the triple match.
That's what we were thinking.
Starting Round One, there'll be a live audience.
- Right. - In terms of energy,
I think we're quite strong.
What song we pick is important.
I personally like "Maverick."
- I see. - I see.
I also like "TATTOO."
Their debut song, "Boy."
We thought a lot about how to share the energy...
the 11 of us have.
Their most recent song, "WATCH IT."
"WATCH IT" is nice.
"WATCH IT..."
- has a dark charm to it. - Right.
There were many elements that could be cool on stage.
For the VS Mission,
we chose "WATCH IT" by THE BOYZ.
This is the first performance the public will see.
"Be careful not to fall for our charms!"
This is the message we want to send.
That's partially why we chose "WATCH IT."
(Ready to be sexy)
(The dark charisma of THE BOYZ's transformation into bad boys...)
(stands out in the song.)
(The bassline adds an irresistible charm...)
(to the title track of their 2nd full-length album.)
We settled on the song, "WATCH IT."
But for this performance,
the performance of the ace member...
will be considered for the evaluation.
- That's important. - Right.
- That's true. - In my opinion,
someone who suits the song perfectly...
ought to be the ace.
Then I'd like to recommend someone.
(Whom will he recommend?)
It's Seunghwan.
(Surprised)
When you think of this song,
this irresistible and sexy vibe comes to mind. You know?
- I see. - Okay.
They haven't seen Seunghwan's sexy side yet.
They will go wild then.
Here's the strength of Seunghwan.
It's his eyes.
He's good at making these facial expressions...
that draw you in instantly.
Should I say his killer smile?
He's got that smile that can win over the hearts of women.
Should I keep going?
(Should we keep showing off his charms?)
I can even...
put myself on fire if it means it will help our team win.
(Oh, my. He's an ambitious guy.)
I could feel that he had been ready all this time...
- when he was looking at me. - My gosh, what a passionate guy.
Actually, if I had a chance,
I wanted to be the ace member at least once.
(Jeong Seunghwan of The CrewOne will be the ace for Round 1.)
(They start practising with him as the ace.)
Now that we know that the score from the ace is...
as important as the score the team receives,
I gave a lot of thought to our theme.
While doing that,
I tried to think about what I could do...
to deliver a great performance to the audience as the ace.
(How can I execute a great job as the ace?)
(He practised non-stop to be ranked high in Round 1.)
This isn't it.
Focus.
Five, six, seven.
(The CrewOne is working hard to practice the choreography.)
(Working on the details of the choreography...)
(and synchronizing the movements)
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Everyone is focused on their practice.)
(Zooming by)
Is there an instructor inside?
(There's a visitor?)
On eight,
we have to grab our fist and then extend it with the step.
- Yes. - Okay.
Should we try that again on our count?
- Yes. - Yes.
- What? - What is it?
(Surprised)
(Peeking)
- What? - Gosh.
(Ju Yeon of THE BOYZ makes a surprise visit.)
(The atmosphere gets hot as the handsome idol star shows up.)
(He's the main dancer and the center of the performance.)
(He's the main force that led his group to victory.)
(Ju Yeon, the undisputed and proven ace among aces)
- My gosh. - There's a celebrity.
(Shy and flustered)
(Thank you for coming.)
I hope the preparation is going well.
- It is. We're working hard. - Yes.
But I heard.
- Heard what? - What?
Your ranking from the Evaluation Match.
(Unable to face him)
I'm sorry.
It was embarrassing and humiliating.
I felt bad too.
- Is this Round One? - Yes.
We're going to perform your song, "WATCH IT."
We thought that it'd be a great song for us to tell our story.
- That's great. - My gosh.
The bottom line is that this is a competition.
So you guys need an intense song.
- Yes. - Right.
Can you show me what you got?
(Nervous)
- All right. - Okay.
Performing it in front of the original singer...
was the most nerve-racking for me. It made me very anxious.
(Can they receive good feedback from the original singer?)
Let's go!
(They nervously demonstrate the progress run-through.)
(Focused)
(The CrewOne gets immersed into the performance more than ever.)
(Gosh, it's finally over.)
Thank you.
(The progress run-through which was more nerve-racking...)
(than the actual performance is over.)
How long have you been preparing for this?
- Two days? - Two days.
(How will Ju Yeon evaluate their performance?)
(Nervous)
It felt like it was your song.
(What a relief.)
But...
doing a good job is more important on this show.
To be completely frank,
I wasn't shocked or anything by your performance.
I should be getting goosebumps.
I just thought that you were cool and did a good job.
That was it.
I felt bad that we weren't able to show him a clear direction...
we wanted for this performance.
We had nothing to say.
The audience can't just go,
"They're great. That's cool."
It can't end there.
- Right. - Yes.
When we performed "Danger,"
we had a clear goal.
We wanted to surprise the audience every 15 seconds.
(The legendary performance, "Danger," is still talked about...)
(for its clear theme and fantastic stage setup.)
It's important to get the audience to feel this.
It was a huge turning point for us.
Afterward, when we were going over our performance,
his advice was very helpful.
We'll have to see what to improve upon while practising...
- our choreography. - Right.
I think it will all come down...
to how we express ourselves on the stage.
Initially, our performance didn't showcase our individual charms.
So we decided to come up with a performance...
that will demonstrate our distinct charms.
At the Evaluation Match,
we got a disappointing result.
So we'll use our rage and passion as fuel for this performance.
- Let's go. - Yes.
All right, everyone. Look sexy.
Let's seduce everyone.
(Their charms were incorporated into the performance.)
(How will their version of "WATCH IT" come out?)
My gosh, look at The CrewOne and the dancers.
The stage will look full.
They might not have used dancers.
But I'm certain they did.
They probably did it to make the stage full.
But if they fail to pull it off, it might look messy.
I wonder what kind of performance they'll show us.
Team The CrewOne.
They're starting.
This is making me nervous.
("WATCH IT" by The CrewOne)
- What's that? - What are they doing?
- What is that? - Are they hanging upside down?
They're dangling there.
Are they bats?
(With the vampire theme, they created a dynamic performance.)
(It shows their determination to get the audience...)
(to fall in love with their irresistible charms.)
My gosh, Jimin. Get in there.
He really bit Seunghwan!
They're vampires?
I get it. He's the ace, so he took the intro.
They're good. It's nice.
Gosh, their performance is really cool.
(Won Bin)
Their performance is choreography-driven, not props...
- like ONEUS's performance. - Yes.
(Won Bin)
That must be the clock.
My gosh, Bain.
They all look like ace members.
(Lee Geonu)
How far did he fly?
What is that?
I'll watch this 30 times once their performance airs on TV.
(Bae Hyunjun)
(The CrewOne's ace, Jeong Seunghwan)
(You can watch the full version of the performance on YouTube.)
(The number of views will be reflected in the Finals.)
(You can find "WATCH IT" on music streaming services.)
(Impressed)
Watch it.
- They did well. - That was good.
The stage looked full.
- They make the best case for it. - Right.
They just focused on the performance like ONEUS.
That was all about the performance.
But contrary to what I expected, the ace member...
- didn't stand out that much. - Right. He didn't.
- The ace member didn't stand out. - Right.
The only thing I remember is Geonu's vocal ad-lib.
Everyone is so good.
So the ace didn't stand out much.
- Right. - Exactly.
I thought everyone on the team was exceptional.
They tried to show a lot with their performance.
I think that actually backfired in the end.
But they must be more disappointed...
- than anyone. - I agree.
- They made a mistake. - After watching that...
He couldn't get up there, right?
- I think so. - Did he fall down?
- He couldn't make it up. - He couldn't climb up.
He tried, but he fell off.
What a bummer.
(Meanwhile, The CrewOne comes down after the performance.)
Darn it.
(This member seems especially miserable after the performance.)
Gosh, darn it.
It felt like it was unfinished.
I was really angry after the performance.
Actually, when we were performing on stage,
we made small mistakes here and there.
Despite all the effort we put into this performance,
we failed to show everything we had prepared.
It was really disappointing.
And we wanted to perform,
so our ranking could climb up.
But we're worried that the viewers...
might think negatively of our mistakes...
and we may end up with a low ranking.
That's worrying us indeed.
(What will be the result of Round 1 for The CrewOne?)
- It's already the last performance. - It is.
Already?
But I'm having so much fun.
Why is this so fun to watch?
They are the last team to perform for the triple match.
CRAVITY will perform now.
(Anticipating)
- Gosh. They'll finally perform. - Here they come.
CRAVITY!
They must be really nervous.
I'm looking forward to this team.
We've never seen them perform before.
"How did they end up in seventh place before?"
I wanted to rock this performance,
so that would cross their minds.
Our goal is coming in first, no matter what.
After being ranked seventh,
only getting ranked first will be acceptable.
(The day of the strategy meeting for CRAVITY)
(They gathered for a meeting, but they seem down.)
We prepared a lot for the Evaluation Match.
But we couldn't perform.
(HYEONGJUN from CRAVITY, 7th place)
(As they were ranked last, they couldn't perform.)
To be honest, I'm still angry about it.
To describe how I feel right now,
I just want to show them...
because we still haven't shown them anything yet.
We won't even get a chance to pick.
(As they were ranked last, they couldn't even pick the artist.)
But it doesn't matter which match we end up with.
We can pull off anything.
It doesn't matter whom we get.
- Aren't you confident? - I'm confident, period.
- I'm confident in everything. - Seriously.
To win the whole competition,
we'll have to beat everyone.
We're not here to make it to the final.
We're here to win the whole thing.
I think we can win...
no matter whom we go up against.
In a way,
no one knows what we can do.
- Right. - Yes.
It could actually work in our favour.
You're really optimistic. I like that.
I'm itching to perform now.
Your blood must be boiling.
This has a good influence on us then.
It's motivating all of us to work harder.
This is nice.
We'll have to go beyond ourselves and bring more than what we have.
We should let the result speak for itself.
Yes. Great.
After getting placed seventh,
I don't want us to be ranked bottom again.
It actually helped me focus.
It wasn't all bad that we ended up on the bottom.
Then we need to prepare for Round One.
- Yes. - The subtitle of the show is...
Ace of Ace.
(Triggered by the word, "ace")
My gosh, it's already torturing me.
I think I got traumatized by that.
So we have to pick another ace member for Round One.
- The ace for Round One. - Yes.
(Then silence settles over the room.)
(Glancing)
You know what?
It was a traumatic experience.
He can't just stay down.
Right. He ought to stand up and fight back.
- He must fight back. - Of course.
I'd like HYEONGJUN to try again.
Overcoming this trauma might be good too.
If we back down after getting punched like this...
and change our ace...
- It looks like we're running away. - Right. It does look like that.
Right.
If we do that, it'd hurt our pride.
- It has to be HYEONGJUN's call. - Are you okay with this?
- It must be up to him. - Well...
- Your opinion matters the most. - Yes.
Well, this is really iffy.
My gosh, I'm a bit scared.
- I see. - We get it
That's possible.
After experiencing how important the ace's role is,
it's giving me a lot of pressure.
(The members can understand that...)
(as they know the weight of being an ace.)
To be honest, no one is blaming you.
- Right. - Yes.
I hope you will come back from this...
and show them...
- it didn't affect your spirit. - That's right.
As for the format of Round One,
the ace will have to stand out in our group performance.
We'll support you in the back.
"In the back" doesn't sound right.
- By your side. - By your side.
We'll be your family right by your side.
- Right by your side. - A family by your side.
- A family by your side. - Yes.
We won't just stay in the back.
- My family on both sides. - Yes.
We have great synergy when we perform as a group.
What do you think about trying this out together?
(The members endlessly cheer for him. What will HYEONGJUN say?)
Let's have a revenge match of the Ace Battle.
(He works up the courage and will perform as the ace again.)
(That's what I'm talking about.)
It's settled then.
The members believed in me...
and said they would support me...
- by my side. - You got this.
Their encouraging words...
turned the pressure into confidence.
I became more motivated.
That made me determined to show people what I could do.
Let's take back first place this time around.
- Yes. - Sounds good.
HYEONGJUN is the perfect guy for the theme of the artist...
we ended up with.
(As they didn't get to choose the artist,)
(they ended up with TOMORROW X TOGETHER.)
(They represent the 4th-generation idol groups...)
(and are known for transcending the limitations of genres.)
(Which song by TOMORROW X TOGETHER...)
(did CRAVITY pick?)
The song selection will be very important.
It has to match the story we're trying to portray.
That will draw people in.
- It will draw people in. - Right.
How about "Sugar Rush Ride?"
YEONJUN also recommended this song.
- What? - What?
We can get help from your friend?
- We can get help from your friend. - We can.
(Hey, we'll be performing your song on Road to Kingdom.)
(- Really? Which one? - We haven't decided yet.)
(- Any recommendations? - "Deja Vu?" Or "Sugar Rush Ride?")
(YEONJUN: Or "Sugar Rush Ride?")
(They listen to the song intently as they seem to agree on it.)
- The devil said - The devil said
We can go with a strong theme for this.
We were ranked last.
We'll cut a deal with the devil.
- With the devil? - Yes.
We'll be the devil then?
- We'll have a deal with the devil? - So...
Will we be tempted by the devil's whisper?
We've gone dark and come back with the devil.
But you can't go into business with just anyone.
Right. It's not what you think.
- The song is youthful and sexy. - Right.
We rarely executed sexy performances.
I don't remember performing...
- with sexy themes. - Right.
- We can show people something new. - Yes.
Then we'll have a deal with the devil too.
- It's not a real deal. - With the devil.
How about the power of the devil?
- You like that. - This is resonating...
with my geeky heart.
- I got a vision for this. - You did?
We can go with a strong theme for this.
This will be the perfect song...
to perform on stage.
This song has the most fun elements.
(It's about a young boy, drawn in...)
(by the devil's irresistible temptation.)
(The title track of their 5th mini album exudes...)
(a dreamy and sensual vibe.)
Are you all ready to join the dark side?
- I'm already there. - I already did.
The main theme of the song is the whisper of the devil.
It will match our story of determination.
I think we can incorporate what we're feeling in the song.
There's a task I must fulfil...
as the ace.
I thought this was our chance to climb up the rankings...
and to show them what we could do.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Eight. Yes.
"We shouldn't have messed with them."
"They're determined to win after placing bottom."
That's what we wanted the other groups to think.
We were certain we could win first place...
the whole time we were practising.
I thought, "We can show them."
"I can feel it."
I practised even harder for this.
We included a new style of dance called tutting.
The lines and shapes of our hands and the aesthetics...
of our dance were so important for this choreography.
We had to work together to complete our performance.
That was really tough.
I really wanted to do a killer job.
We have to win, no matter what.
We don't want the bitter taste of defeat again.
(CRAVITY worked hard to perfect their performance.)
(How will their performance come out?)
Be on standby.
Play the music. Three, two, one. Start.
I know they're our opponents,
but I'm curious about their performance.
And I bet they are determined to win this battle.
- They must've been angry. - I bet they worked so hard on it.
(Focused)
I'm curious, though.
It's their first performance. I bet they prepared a good one.
What a surprise.
(This song is...)
It's "Sugar Rush Ride."
- It's "Sugar Rush Ride." - It's "Sugar Rush Ride."
The arrangement of the song is insane.
(Nervous)
(As three groups are competing in this match,)
(they focus on every little detail.)
That's nicely composed.
Their movements are in complete sync.
- That's what they're known for. - Right.
Their movements were perfectly synced up.
(As it's better than expected, he gets more nervous.)
- They did well. - They're great.
It's like a performance at an awards ceremony.
My gosh.
Why did they prepare such a great performance?
We're going to remind them...
once again that CRAVITY is...
a force to be reckoned with.
That's what we ought to do.
Let's go. Remember...
- Who we are! - Who we are!
Okay.
(How will their version of "Sugar Rush Ride" turn out?)
- Go, CRAVITY. - Go, CRAVITY.
- They chose him one more time? - Gosh.
- Again? - Again.
That's a huge challenge.
- To do it again. - It requires great courage.
He's back to make people pay...
- for the humiliation. - That's right.
- Go, CRAVITY. - Go, CRAVITY.
Team CRAVITY.
They were so good during the rehearsal.
I look forward to their stage the most.
I'm curious how they'll perform.
They must be so nervous.
I'm nervous myself.
("Sugar Rush Ride" by CRAVITY)
Come a little closer
Swallow it
The sugar rush
(A depiction of boys falling for the sweet temptation of evil...)
(using eye-catching performances and intuitive objects)
Is that what I think it is?
That's from "Talk to Me."
- You know that movie, right? - Yes, I do.
- You see ghosts if you do that. - That's right.
- It's from a movie. - What's that?
How did he stop like that?
- What's that? - How did he do that?
What's that?
- This blows my mind. - That was smooth.
Here it comes.
- This part. - This is the cool part.
I admit it.
That looks nice.
It's beautiful.
The hand.
- What was that? - Gosh, what was that?
Wait a second.
It's like we're at an awards ceremony.
It looks like Homigot.
Is there more?
- It isn't over yet. - What?
It isn't over.
(CRAVITY's ace, HYEONGJUN)
(You can watch the full version of the performance on YouTube.)
(The number of views will be reflected in the Finals.)
("Sugar Rush Ride" by CRAVITY will not be released...)
(due to copyright issues.)
The acting was insane.
It's like watching "MAMA Awards."
That was impressive. I got goosebumps.
It was perfect for them.
I really enjoyed the movie "Talk to Me."
I knew it was from the movie as soon as I saw it.
I got goosebumps at the end...
when they all gathered around.
- That was something. - It was insane.
They did so well.
I seriously got goosebumps.
The ending was smooth.
It was a great idea.
There is absolutely nothing I can find fault with.
They did a really good job.
The directing was amazing as well.
Yes, the directing was well done, and it's memorable.
The members of CRAVITY...
stand out the most.
Right.
- The directing was good too. - That's right.
They didn't have many props,
but they were imposing.
That's right.
I think...
this is the performance of a bigger group we worried about.
It's hard for each member to stand out.
But they did a good job.
- They're good. - They did well.
I have nothing to say.
I honestly want to make a negative comment as an opponent.
But I have nothing to say.
(CRAVITY successfully finishes their first stage as a team.)
I feel so relieved that it's over.
Good job, everyone.
- Nicely done. - Good job.
- Good job, everyone. - No mistakes, right?
Out of all the performances I did,
this gave me...
- I know. - the greatest sense of achievement.
- Yes, it did. - I've never felt this good...
- about a performance. - Right.
That was insane.
I felt sure of it...
when I stepped off the stage after performing.
- A weight was lifted off my chest. - That's right.
I felt relieved that we successfully pulled off the performance.
Out of all the stages I performed on ever since my debut,
this was the most thrilling.
It's been five years since our debut.
I felt something novel...
during our performance today.
(The result of CRAVITY's stage everyone is satisfied with?)
We will now begin the VS voting...
for ONEUS, The CrewOne, and CRAVITY,
the three teams that competed in the triple match.
I personally got goosebumps during the stage...
by CRAVITY.
- Me too. - I personally...
- liked CRAVITY's stage the best. - Me too.
(Strikingly dark and sexy with a diverse performance)
(Will "Sugar Rush Ride" by CRAVITY win?)
I liked ONEUS' stage.
Me too. I think it was the most unique and impressive.
(The song with an Asian vibe...)
(was reinterpreted into an action performance.)
(Will "Kick It" by ONEUS win?)
I'd vote for The CrewOne.
(A powerful and dynamic performance by the team with the most members)
(Will "WATCH IT" by The CrewOne win the triple match?)
I don't know how the vote will end.
I don't think we'll lose.
We're here to compete.
Who would want to be in second place?
Since our goal is to win first place,
we should win the triple match.
(It's hard to predict the result of the close triple match.)
Five, four,
three, two, one.
(Voting closed)
The voting is closed.
(The 3 teams receive the result cards.)
- Good job. - What's this?
(As soon as they return to the green room,)
- Why? - Come on.
(they see the result card.)
They can't have the result already.
(CRAVITY arrives at their green room at the same time.)
It's over.
- You all did a good job. - What's this?
- Good job. - What's this?
- What is it? - What is it?
Good job, everyone.
- The result. - What?
- What? - Come on.
Stop lying.
What's this?
- Gosh. - The result.
- This is too much. - Why?
- Unbelievable. - The result is out already?
- I don't want to see this. - Let's go.
- Who else doesn't want to check? - Come here.
Let's sit first.
I thought it was a gift.
(He is dazed already.)
- Unbelievable. - Should we check it now?
- Go ahead. - Really?
We have to check it?
(Everyone is nervous after seeing the result card.)
- Announce it. - All right.
In 1, 2, 3.
Here we go.
(The die is cast at the same time in ONEUS's green room.)
This is insane.
Wait, I'm nervous now.
- I honestly bet we won. - We won.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Did ONEUS win or lose?)
(HYEONGJUN of ONEUS is holding the result card.)
I was expectant and scared.
Losing here would really mean we weren't good enough.
- Let's check it together. - Let's just go for it.
(Taking a deep breath)
(Failing)
Like we said, we have no regrets...
- regardless of the result. - That's right.
- Seriously. - We have no regrets.
- That's right. - Okay.
(The triple match of Round 1's VS Mission was fierce to the end.)
- One, two... - Don't be expectant.
(Which team won in the triple match and earned the benefit?)
Three.
(CRAVITY wins the triple match.)
(The joy of winning...)
(and tears of relief hit together.)
- We won. - Gosh.
Seriously.
We won.
Even JUNGMO is crying.
Although we put on a performance we were so confident about,
I was terrified to check the result.
What a relief.
(It's such a relief they were acknowledged with a win.)
It felt like all the weight...
was lifted off my chest.
HYEONGJUN, whom we put our trust in once again,
did such a good job.
I was very grateful to him.
I was so proud of the other members after checking the result.
We were in last place.
And we had to compete with two other teams.
When we won,
I realized how desperate we were.
I realized how determined we were as we practised for the stage.
- Come here. - You all did great.
- Group hug. - Come here.
Come on.
We all did a good job.
- Right. - Good job.
- Gather together. - Pat yourself.
- We all did great. - Good job.
One, two, three.
(ONEUS and The CrewOne...)
Three.
(didn't get the result they were hoping for.)
Is there something behind this?
- Lose. - Lose?
We were in sixth place in the Evaluation Match.
We wanted to do better in Round One.
We had to do better.
The 1,000 benefit points means a lot to us.
So I was quite angry.
(Their high expectations led to a greater disappointment.)
I could tell the other members were angry.
I couldn't believe it.
I wondered if we focused too much on the vividness.
My blood was boiling.
(CRAVITY gets a benefit of 1,000 points.)
The 7 performances for Round 1 are over.
Now it is time to determine their destiny.
For Round 1, Self-Evaluation takes up 30 percent,
and the evaluation of on-site judges takes up 70 percent of the score.
Please vote for the three aces that were memorable...
and three teams that put on the best stages...
out of the seven performances.
We will begin voting.
(The voting was conducted in the presence of observers.)
(Mr. Choi, 20s, Gyeonggi Province, Mr. Park, 20s, Gyeonggi Province)
(Please)
We desperately want this.
Please.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
(Voting closed)
The voting is closed.
We lost in the VS Mission.
But we don't have our total team score yet.
If I were to choose three teams that did the best,
I'd choose ONEUS.
I still had hope in a corner of my heart.
We didn't have to feel discouraged yet.
Road to Kingdom: Ace of Ace.
The performances of Round One you all prepared hard for are over.
(They applaud one another for their hard work.)
You all worked hard.
- Yes. - I feel satisfied.
(Round 1 is the beginning of the competition.)
(Which team will get a chance to win?)
The moment you cannot avoid has come.
The result announcement is waiting for you.
(Groaning)
No.
There is no way to know.
I'm scared.
Out of the Ace Ranking and Team Ranking,
I will start with the Team Ranking.
Just like that?
- I hope we're in the top four. - Please.
I really hope we're in the top four.
- Fourth place... - I don't want to be fourth anymore.
(THE NEW SIX doesn't want to be in 4th place anymore.)
This reminds me of a nightmare.
- I'm really nervous. - Me too.
(Will CRAVITY succeed in getting a higher ranking?)
The three teams that won in the VS Mission...
gained 1,000 benefit points.
(The winners of the VS Mission)
(CRAVITY)
(YOUNITE)
(THE NEW SIX)
(VS Mission result)
Thank you.
(The winners are 1,000 points ahead before the ranking is revealed.)
Yes, 1,000 points.
- I'm jealous. - I'm jealous.
They are starting with 1,000 points.
As the 1,000 benefit points were given out,
I'm sure you're all curious about the final ranking.
Let's check the ranking of THE NEW SIX, YOUNITE,
and CRAVITY, the winners of the VS Mission.
(Why are we first?)
I'm so nervous.
- What? We're going first? - We're going first?
My heart rate that slowed down is going up again.
(His heart is racing.)
One of them must be in first place.
What if they win 1st, 2nd, and 3rd?
- Even if they won the match, - You never know.
they might not have gotten votes for the team voting.
Show us the ranking of the winning teams.
Please.
I don't have any expectations at all.
(He is expectant with his whole body.)
Are we allowed to get nervous now?
I just don't want to see the number "seven."
Seriously.
(CRAVITY is more desperate because they were in 7th place.)
Please.
I feel weird. I don't think I can watch this.
(Round 1: VS winner team ranking, 1st, 2nd, 3rd)
- What? - What's this?
(What?)
- What's this? - What's this?
- Are they 1st, 2nd, and 3rd? - What?
Could they be in 1st, 2nd, and 3rd places?
What's this?
The winning team ranking...
is 1st, 2nd, and 3rd.
(Shocked)
We're one of them.
- We aren't in 4th place anymore. - We aren't in 4th anymore.
(The winning teams bask in happiness.)
My heart isn't beating.
They're in the top three.
(The other teams are automatically in the lower rankings.)
I'm suddenly nervous.
- I'm scared. - The fact that ONEUS...
isn't in the top three is surprising.
I guess 1,000 points makes a big difference.
I was hoping for a plot twist.
We will reveal the team rankings...
from 1st to 7th place for Round 1 all at once.
(Is it seriously moving this fast?)
This is insane.
Please.
This is so cruel.
Show us the final rankings.
Let's win first place while we're at it.
I want to win first place.
(Meanwhile, the teams that lost...)
(are very nervous.)
I can't watch this.
Please let us not be in last place.
Let us be at least sixth place.
(What will the result of the Team Ranking for Round 1 be?)
(Round 1 Team Ranking)
(1st place, CRAVITY, 10,769 points, CRAVITY wins 1st place.)
(1st, CRAVITY, 10,769 points)
(They all jump to their feet.)
Seriously.
(Moved)
I'm sure they tried very hard.
They went from last place to first.
This is a total plot twist.
(HYEONGJUN can't take his eyes off the results.)
My legs feel weak.
- Good job. - Good job.
I was so happy.
We were placed seventh for the Evaluation Match without performing.
We performed for the 1st time and won 1st place in Round 1.
That was so satisfying.
We showed them how good we are, so we'll stay in first place.
- We won't back down. - We won't let you take it.
YOUNITE got a really high score.
(2nd place, YOUNITE, 10,249 points, YOUNITE's score stands out.)
We were in seventh place for the expected ranking.
(During the Evaluation Match)
(Not only was their expected ranking for the Evaluation Match 7th,)
(but they also ended up in 5th place for the Team Ranking.)
(Sad)
We would've been in 2nd place even without the 1,000 points.
We've gone up a lot.
There isn't that big of a difference between us.
We did it.
I can't congratulate them whole-heartedly.
Fourth place is a bit...
(4th place, ONEUS, 6,997 points)
My pride is hurt.
What a bummer.
- Bummer. - What a bummer.
- It's a bummer. - It's a bummer.
We'll have to try harder.
(5th, TEMPEST, 4,756 points)
We were almost in last place.
(6th, The CrewOne, 4,585 points)
We're standing still.
(They're in the same ranking as the Evaluation Match.)
Oh, no.
How could we be in seventh place?
(7th place, 8TURN, 4,423 points)
(With their refreshing and powerful performance,)
(8TURN had won 1st place in the Team Battle.)
(They dropped to 7th in Round 1's Team Battle.)
From 1st place to 7th?
It's the total opposite.
(It's hard to accept the change in ranking.)
This is unbelievable.
8TURN went from 1st place to 7th.
8TURN was in 1st place last time.
They switched with us.
You're right.
The ace plays an important role.
I feel responsible.
We revealed the Team Ranking.
But you know this isn't the end, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
We still have the Ace Ranking.
Could it be very different from the Team Ranking?
I think it could be totally different.
I'll hope for this.
Our ace did a really good job.
(Nervous)
Here is the Ace Ranking.
I will now announce...
the first three teams.
- Goodness. - I didn't think I'd be nervous.
Why am I so nervous?
I can't breathe.
I'll look forward to this one.
(Nervous)
(EUNSANG seems far more humble.)
I think our team is in it.
You did well.
I believe that we're in it.
YUN GYU might save us.
Whatever the outcome is,
you're our number one.
Ace Ranking of Round One.
Please reveal the top three teams.
Please.
(The members who are watching...)
(are also nervous.)
Please be there.
(Startled)
(Who are the top 3 members of the Ace Ranking?)
(EUNSANG, HWAN WOONG, and HYEONGJUN)
(CRAVITY is in a high rank followed by the Team Ranking.)
- Well done. - My legs gave out just now.
Top three!
I'm in the top three!
Thank goodness.
Just the fact that I'm in the top three...
makes me feel grateful.
(YOUNITE is also in the top three in Team Ranking and Ace Ranking.)
(We're proud of you, our ace.)
I believed in you.
He's in it.
- Well done. - It's fine.
I want to go home.
- This is so tough. - There you go.
(He's relaxed and now exhausted.)
One of these three teams ranked first in the Ace Ranking.
I think it's YOUNITE.
Me too.
Or it could be HWAN WOONG.
HWAN WOONG had a bigger reaction on the site.
If CRAVITY takes first place,
- they take all the high points. - I know.
Please reveal the final rankings of these three teams.
All of them?
Please.
Please be first place.
This is driving me insane.
I'd like to place first.
I want it.
(Who's number 1 in Round 1's Ace Ranking?)
(Ace Ranking 1st place, ONEUS, HWAN WOONG)
(Too bad.)
- Well done. - You did well, though.
Third place?
It's not bad.
- Gosh. - I'm so proud of you, buddy.
Great job.
- He placed first last time too. - Yes.
He's the number-one ace twice in a row.
He's tough to beat.
A lot of people...
told me that I stood out as the ace member,
so I'm glad.
I hope to put our team...
in first place next time.
Thank you.
Great.
You're modest too.
YOUNITE placed second in both Rankings.
- That's a lot of points. - Right?
I don't exactly feel bad. I'm just thankful.
I'll do my part as the leader to the end.
- Awesome! - That was great.
It's a party for YOUNITE today.
Now, here are the bottom four teams.
HWI from THE NEW SIX,
LEW from TEMPEST,
YUN GYU from 8TURN,
Seunghwan from The CrewOne.
Now, please reveal the final rankings...
of Round One's Ace Ranking.
No pressure.
You know that, right?
I hope we placed higher than sixth.
This is so nerve-racking.
I was mad at myself,
and I felt bad for my members.
(Ace Ranking, bottom 4 teams)
(HWI, LEW, YUN GYU, and Seunghwan)
We were in trouble.
Could I have placed last?
But I doubt that we're last.
I was hoping that we didn't place seventh,
even in the Ace Ranking.
(Ace Ranking, bottom 4 teams)
(HWI, LEW, Seunghwan, and YUN GYU)
(HWI, 6,465 points)
Gosh. That's a relief. Good job.
(LEW, 6,025 points)
- Still, you did well. - Well done.
You're number one in my heart.
(Jeong Seunghwan, 4,674 points)
At least we're not last.
- Did we place sixth in both? - Yes.
We're always sixth.
The point difference wasn't that big from seventh place.
We really might be eliminated.
But I am shocked...
that 8TURN placed last in both of them.
That's crazy.
This is driving me crazy.
(They placed 7th, which is last, in Team Ranking and Ace Ranking.)
It hurts my pride so much.
My heart aches today.
(Staring)
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
- No, don't say that. - No.
- Hey, I told you not to say that. - No.
Never say that again.
I was very frustrated.
If other members...
performed as the ace member,
we might have different rankings. That was also on my mind.
(Ace Ranking: ONEUS, YOUNITE, CRAVITY, THE NEW SIX, TEMPEST,)
(The CrewOne, and 8TURN)
(Team Ranking: CRAVITY, YOUNITE, THE NEW SIX, ONEUS, TEMPEST...)
Here are the final rankings...
of Round One's VS Mission.
(Team Ranking, 1st, CRAVITY, Ace Ranking, 1st, ONEUS)
First place in the Team Ranking is CRAVITY.
First place in the Ace Ranking is ONEUS.
I'm jealous. I hope they give us 500 points.
The number-1 team in Round 1 will obviously be given benefits.
The number-one team gets benefits?
- Okay. - There's more?
The number-one team...
(The number-1 team's benefit)
gets to decide on the cue sheet for Round Two.
The cue sheet!
(Okay.)
That's huge.
The last team on the cue sheet placed first again.
I'm jealous.
I believe...
it's a great power to decide on the cue sheet.
You naturally forget...
about the previous performances.
But two teams placed first.
(But there are 2 teams in 1st place, ONEUS and CRAVITY.)
There's only one benefit,
so we will have to determine the winner.
- Are they having a battle? - No way.
(Why? What is it?)
Is it a battle?
They're having the Ace Battle now?
- Ace Battle? - Oh, the Ace Battle...
No way!
Please don't. Come on, Mnet!
The ace members of the two teams,
who brought victory,
will have a single-round match...
of the Ace Battle.
(Is this really happening?)
And the final winner...
will decide on the cue sheet for Round Two.
This is really happening.
(Screaming)
Mnet!
(Furious)
I feel like someone hit me in the back of my head.
- First place and seventh place. - First place and seventh place.
That's amazing.
(After the Ace Battle in the Evaluation Match,)
(the two aces had drastically different results.)
- If HYEONGJUN wins this one, - Yes.
- does he become the best? - It'll be a new history.
HWAN WOONG has always placed first in Ace Battles.
He's a tough one.
Let's beat him once.
It's about time.
He's placed first enough.
I'll win, while we're at it.
- Please do. - Yes.
You've got this.
My team placed first,
but I placed last as the ace member.
I want to place 1st, not just be in the top 3.
Good luck.
- Go on. - Just have fun.
We've decided on the cue sheet before.
- Yes. It's not that important. - We got the benefit last time,
so it's fine if I lose.
- Get out there and win. - No?
- Oh, come on. - Just have fun.
If I'm being honest,
I'm relieved that CRAVITY placed first.
They chose us as rivals...
in the Evaluation Match...
and placed last, so I was a bit upset.
(In the Evaluation Match on the first day)
(Which team would you like to defeat?)
We choose...
(CRAVITY chose ONEUS as the team they want to beat.)
(I believe they're a high mountain that we'll once have to beat.)
(We'll show you why we're...)
(a high mountain.)
(The two teams have had a war of nerves ever since.)
(CRAVITY put ONEUS as the first team to perform...)
(with its right to decide on the cue sheet.)
(On pins and needles)
(SERIM.)
(Are you sure you can beat me in the Ace Battle?)
(This is tough.)
But they placed first,
so it was clear to me which team to go for.
I like that.
(The ace members' single-match performance battle)
(Their Ace Battle begins now.)
- What? - What?
They're both barefoot.
- They're both barefoot? - Barefoot?
Barefoot versus barefoot?
They look similar.
They're both wearing white too.
How do they look so similar?
It's crazy how they have similar themes.
I got chills that we even have the same outfit.
He looked similar, so I was nervous.
What a quirk of fate.
- This is interesting. - It's so interesting.
This is so entertaining.
It's always more fun to watch others fight.
CRAVITY's ace member,
HYEONGJUN, will perform first.
- Okay! - Okay!
Let's go!
- HYEONGJUN! - No pressure.
- Defeat him once. - Good luck.
He's been in first place for too long.
Do what you always do.
He placed seventh last time,
so he must have come thoroughly prepared this time.
You shouldn't lose in this battle.
- Why? - Because you'll lose your position.
Going from 7th place to 1st place...
is a great narrative, though.
To redeem myself...
as the ace member,
I was determined to show everyone what I've got.
I stepped in with spite.
I meant to do my best.
We're proud of you, HYEONGJUN.
Thank you for always doing your best as the ace member.
Let's go.
Ace of CRAVITY.
Let's go!
- Go, HYEONGJUN! - You can do this!
But he doesn't have any props.
I think he's only sticking to dancing.
He's going head-to-head.
I'm so nervous.
Please.
(Holding his hands tightly)
("Dance With the Devil" by HYEONGJUN from CRAVITY)
His body...
So cool.
- Nice! - Well done.
- That was elegant. - So neat.
Gosh.
(You can watch the full version of the performance on YouTube.)
(Cheering)
So cool!
- He's very flexible. - He's a great dancer.
His dancing lines are so neat.
He turned into a totally different person.
You killed it!
Our little devil.
He did so well.
- Nice and neat. - Great job.
I was worried about causing harm...
to my team,
but I was relieved...
to know that I did my best and finished the performance well.
I can't believe it's similar.
He did contemporary dance, which was similar to ours.
I thought, "That's too similar."
"It might turn into a situation that we were worried about."
The amount of pressure was certainly different.
He's got props.
(HWAN WOONG's props are brought on to the stage?)
What's that? A sandcastle?
What is that?
What is it? A well?
There's a flower inside.
He came prepared.
It literally cost him blood and sweat to prepare for this.
I'm sure he'll do well.
He's got confidence.
He's obviously the ace.
I can't wait to find out what he'll do.
He was completely the Joker last time.
But he's such a good dancer,
so I'm excited.
There was pressure,
but I was confident.
Ace of ONEUS.
I am curious, though.
I wonder what it'll be.
("Sovereign Shadows" by HWAN WOONG of ONEUS)
It's the same. Contemporary dance.
It's on his face.
He's good.
All right!
- This is so shocking. - That's insane.
It's not over yet.
(You can watch the full version of the performance on YouTube.)
I got chills.
(HWAN WOONG's performance ended with an intense ending.)
(They can't help but get up.)
That was legendary.
My heart almost dropped.
That was insane.
How would anyone beat that?
No way.
What was that?
Come on, HWAN WOONG!
I'm proud of you!
- He did so well. - He killed it.
Well done.
He actually gave his all.
It was like he gave everything for this one performance.
It wasn't a simple dance.
It was like a ceremony.
HWAN WOONG.
You would have been disappointed...
if you hadn't gotten the chance to do this Ace Battle.
He really would have been disappointed.
Considering how much he prepared.
How did he come up with that in such a short time?
He had great ideas, and it was incredible.
But I wonder where the gunpowder exploded.
- Something exploded. What was that? - Right?
How did he do that?
He must have had a killer in front of him.
(And one boy is attacked by the killer.)
- Well done. - That was great.
You also did well.
The performance wasn't done only by myself, actually.
KEON HEE pressed the button at the perfect time.
(The hidden assistant)
(KEON HEE got the gunpowder trigger right before the performance.)
Cover it for now.
Just hide it.
Don't pay too much attention to it.
I'm nervous.
- Who? - Me.
Don't be nervous. Get a grip.
(That's how the hidden ace, KEON HEE, collaborated with him.)
There you go!
(That was close.)
- It was perfect timing. - It was perfect.
(The hidden helper of the Ace Battle)
The Ace Battle between CRAVITY and ONEUS has ended.
The winner of the Ace Battle...
will be determined by the Self-Evaluation...
by the ones who watched these performances.
I'm torn.
I know, right? How should pick one?
Only considering the dance,
HYEONGJUN's performance was my type.
I'm definitely choosing HWAN WOONG.
(The 5 teams finished casting their votes.)
(A total of 30 members voted.)
Now, I have the result of the vote.
Which team will get the right to decide on the cue sheet?
They were both so good, though.
It was a nip-and-tuck match.
Please announce the winner.
- I wonder who it is. - I'm scared.
CRAVITY.
ONEUS.
(Who's the winner of the Ace Battle?)
Gosh.
What?
(Startled)
(Gasping)
(To be continued shortly)
Please announce the winner.
- I wonder who it is. - I'm scared.
CRAVITY.
ONEUS.
(Who's the winner of the Ace Battle?)
Gosh.
(Team Ranking, Ace Ranking)
(Startled)
(CRAVITY's HYEONGJUN, lose)
(ONEUS's HWAN WOONG, win)
(HWAN WOONG wins Round 1's Ace Battle.)
- Hug me if you want. - No, thanks.
(His teammates congratulate him who felt immense pressure.)
That's fine.
He's still in first place.
He'll forever be their ace.
(CRAVITY's HYEONGJUN lost to HWAN WOONG.)
- Well done. - You did so well, though.
He won't step down from first place.
Congratulations.
By 6 to 24,
(The result of the Self-Evaluation, 6 to 24)
the right to decide on the cue sheet for Round Two...
- It was 6 to 24. - goes to ONEUS.
(ONEUS gets the right to draw the cue sheet in Round 2.)
- By 6 to 24, - Wait.
- the right to decide... - You're revealing the numbers too?
on the cue sheet for Round Two...
Even the number of votes.
It was 6 to 24.
Quadruple.
(The math genius analyses the result with a cold heart.)
Hey!
Don't be so direct.
My goal was to win first place,
so you could call it a bummer.
But I'm proud of myself...
for performing only with my body...
and going against HWAN WOONG.
We're also proud of you.
(Well done, our ace.)
HWAN WOONG, you won. How do you feel?
First, I'm exhilarated.
It made me happy to win first place...
in the name of ONEUS again.
Thank you!
(Powerful)
(Cheering)
That felt great.
(He relieves all his tension.)
(Ace Ranking 1st place, ONEUS, HWAN WOONG)
(ONEUS gets to decide on the cue sheet in Round 2.)
Road to Kingdom: Ace of Ace.
Round Two.
- Already? - Just like that?
Are you all wondering what the next mission is?
- Yes! - Yes!
It's our chance to climb up.
We can turn it around...
if we place first in the next mission.
I will reveal it right away.
That's fast.
What would the mission be?
We're blessed by announcements today.
The mission of Round Two is...
(What's the mission in Round 2?)
It is...
Identity.
- What? - Identity?
Identity?
What's Identity?
- It's like who we are, right? - Yes.
Well, we know what the word "identity" means.
Identity in Round Two is a mission...
in which you can show people your team's colour and identity...
through your songs.
Oh, we're using our songs.
The story of the team.
- A mission we're confident in. - Our colour.
Aren't we at a disadvantage...
if we have to portray our story?
What should we show them?
I believe it's going to be a fierce competition...
because every team is performing with what they're most confident in.
It'd be so embarrassing if you performed your own song poorly.
We're participating with our own songs,
so it's the main mission. We have to do better.
There's a notification regarding the ace in Round Two.
- What? - What is it?
- Is there a new rule? - I guess there is.
I don't feel so good about this.
The ace in Round Two...
The same person can't be the ace member?
- Five aces? - None.
- Two? - It's not just one.
- Two aces? - You must pick two ace members.
It never goes the way I expected.
It's good for us, though.
We have a lot of members.
- We have a lot to pick from. - Right.
Then, half of us are ace members.
(2 out of 5 members of ONEUS must perform as the ace members.)
- Half of us. - Half of us.
It'll be difficult for both the aces to stand out.
- Right. - Yes, that's the problem.
Both of them need to stand out.
Just like in Round 1, the points you'll get in Round 2...
are 10,000 points from the Team Ranking...
and 10,000 points from the Ace Ranking.
There will be a total of 20,000 points.
But there's a difference from Round One.
What is it?
I'm nervous.
I hope it's advantageous for the bottom four teams.
Please give us a chance to turn it around.
After your performance in Round Two...
No way.
(Nervous)
There will be a first elimination.
Oh, my gosh.
Already?
Oh, please.
- No! - Why does it feel so soon?
It's suffocating.
The elimination candidates will be determined...
by the accumulated points from Rounds 1 and 2.
The seventh-place team in the Team Ranking...
and the seventh-place team in the Ace Ranking...
according to the final outcome...
Oh, the final outcome.
Those two teams will be elimination candidates.
No way. Another Ace Battle?
Those two teams will compete.
The team to be eliminated will be determined by the Ace Battle.
It's literally an elimination battle.
Everything is determined by the ace members.
It must be a huge pressure for the ace members.
Imagine the pressure.
We should really grit our teeth. Elimination is on the line.
That's insane.
The Ace Battle in Round Two is...
- an elimination match. - Right.
- So, it's so significant. - Right.
You're responsible for the team's elimination.
We should pick one carefully.
If the same team placed seventh...
in the Ace Ranking and Team Ranking,
there will not be an Ace Battle.
(Surprised)
You will be eliminated immediately.
They're so cruel.
- They could be the same. - That was the case this time.
8TURN must be so scared of Round Two.
I bet they'll go all out.
- I can't even talk to 8TURN. - Seriously.
They might make it if they give it their all.
We need to cheer up!
We've got nowhere to go but up.
Let's take back our first place.
We placed seventh in not one but two rankings.
So, I couldn't stop thinking that we might be eliminated...
if we don't get into the top three.
We're going to bet our life and death this time.
The CrewOne's score isn't that different.
We're the same, though.
We're the most in danger.
(The CrewOne in 6th place is in danger of elimination.)
You're right. It's the accumulated point,
so it could be us.
If we don't belong in the top three next,
we'll be eliminated.
- We need to win this time. - We could be eliminated too.
Let's risk everything in Round Two.
It might as well be our last one.
Our goal in Round Two is definitely the top three.
I believe that we should go all out.
THE NEW SIX has a powerful identity.
We're actually confident this time.
We need to consider...
the chemistry between the members and the ace members.
We're going to need a good strategy.
We'll stand our ground and climb up with tenacity.
(A few days after Round 1)
(The CrewOne's practice room)
(The members are warming up before practice.)
- Pay attention, please. - Okay.
There's an important announcement regarding Round Two.
What's that?
Is there a change?
What is it about?
(The members of ONEUS are also curious.)
- It's pretty thick. - Is it an allowance?
We worked hard on the show,
so they finally paid us.
(Laughing)
- I'm so thankful. - Count the envelopes.
Six, right?
- Let's go! - Oh, gosh.
- What? - Let's see.
What is this?
- What is it? - It looks cool.
That's amazing.
We will reveal one of the two aces of other teams.
(One of the two aces of all the other teams will be revealed.)
(They were notified of the rules for Round 2's aces.)
(You must pick...)
(not one but two ace members.)
(Unlike in the previous round,)
(there will be 2 ace members in Round 2.)
(There are 2 ace members,)
(so there's likely to be a new ace.)
I did not see that coming.
Our aces must have been...
- revealed too. - No way.
I'm sure our ace members are the least known.
I can't figure out YOUNITE.
- I can't predict who they chose. - I have no clue.
It's a great opportunity to analyse their strategy.
You're right. We might be able to predict...
- which song they chose. - We might.
- I see. - Right.
Shouldn't we check out the number-one team, then?
- ONEUS? - Should we take a look?
- Let's see. - The number-one ace.
Whose team are you the most curious about?
- The number-one team. - Me too.
- ONEUS. - ONEUS.
The team we're most curious about.
Let's check out ONEUS,
the recent number-one ace's team.
- Yes. - All right.
Should we check out ONEUS first?
- Okay. - Yes, ONEUS.
Why would you reveal our strength without our permission?
(Who's one of the aces in ONEUS?)
My guess is HWAN WOONG again.
He's been winning Ace Battles.
They need to maintain their place.
(Will it be HWAN WOONG's 3rd time as the ace member?)
It also makes me think, "I doubt he'll do it again."
Right. Me too.
I wonder who else will be the ace.
I have a feeling it's SEO HO.
SEO HO.
My guess is SEO HO.
He's known to be a good singer,
- and he's very acrobatic. - Right.
That's true.
(Fancy acrobatics...)
(and great singing skills, SEO HO)
- Shall we take a look? - Okay.
- We knew it was him. - As we expected.
- Open it. - Okay.
- I knew it. - I knew it.
- Three times? That's tough. - Wouldn't he be tired by now?
Is it like, "I'll protect my team?"
- I bet. - He's too much, though.
How could he be the ace three times in a row?
(HWAN WOONG is constantly their ace...)
(from the Evaluation Match to Round 2.)
But he won first place every time he competed.
- It's a monopoly. - This is too much.
It shows how confident he is.
That makes me wonder...
- who the other one is. - Right.
The important thing is who will perform with him.
Exactly.
(ONEUS' aces in Round 2, HWAN WOONG...)
Next team, 8TURN.
- I'm so curious about this one too. - This is a tough one.
8TURN's rankings have been fluctuating.
They went from first place to last place.
It plummeted.
Should we check out The CrewOne,
who's right above us?
(Team Ranking and Ace Ranking)
(The CrewOne and 8TURN are the bottom 2 teams...)
(in Team Ranking and Ace Ranking.)
They're really going to grit their teeth this time.
They might be eliminated if they do poorly.
Their aces have a huge responsibility.
- It must be a lot of pressure. - More so than other aces.
8TURN's ace.
- I bet it's the leader. - JAE YUN.
That's a good guess.
When I look at 8TURN, I still remember...
MYUNG HO's performance in the Ace Battle.
It was impressive.
It certainly was.
- The CrewOne's... - It has to be Junseok.
It should be Junseok.
I bet it's him.
I can already hear it.
"Junseok!"
Then, Jimin will have to...
- compete again. - He'll compete once again.
(Lim Jimin, 2nd place in the Evaluation Match Ace Battle)
I think it actually is him.
Should I open it?
- Yes, open it. - Let's go.
- Shall we take a look, then? - Go.
If it's those two...
The members of 8TURN will grit their teeth this time.
I can't wait to find out.
(Oh Junseok, MYUNG HO)
- MYUNG HO is competing again. - The energy...
That's tough.
Are you worried about 8TURN?
(Are you worried about 8TURN's ace members?)
Not really.
(Great confidence)
We have to win this time.
- You're right. - We have to.
I believe that Round Two...
is a 1-on-1 match against 8TURN.
I agree.
Our scores are similar, so it has to be that way.
If we lose to 8TURN,
we're more likely to be eliminated.
(The CrewOne's aces in Round 2, Oh Junseok...)
(8TURN's aces in Round 2, MYUNG HO...)
The team that earned similar votes as us.
- YOUNITE. - YOUNITE.
They placed second in both.
It's a tough team to beat.
- I think it's EUNSANG again. - EUNSANG.
One of the bottom four in the Evaluation Match.
(They went from one of the bottom 4 teams to the top 3 teams.)
We went up in one mission.
He experienced the thrill from designing it like a play.
Right.
(Addicted to the thrill)
I think he'll do the same.
I do too.
- Should we check it out? - Let's go.
Come on out, EUNSANG!
As expected.
As soon as they see EUNSANG's name,
they may think, "Will it be another intense one?"
Right. Like, "They're at it again."
"They're up to something again."
"What is it this time?"
But we have a surprise for them.
(YOUNITE's aces in Round 2, EUNSANG...)
- CRAVITY. - CRAVITY, it is.
I wish that they would perform "Love or Die."
I'd like that.
(I want to see that too.)
TAEYOUNG's part in "Love or Die" by CRAVITY...
looks so cool.
(Is TAEYOUNG their ace if they're singing "Love or Die?")
THE NEW SIX.
- I think they'll do "Love or Die." - "Love or Die?"
They couldn't perform as a whole team for "Love or Die."
(They were a member short during "Love or Die.")
Because JUNHYEOK couldn't perform,
I assume they'll take this chance to do "Love or Die."
I hope CRAVITY battles...
- THE NEW SIX with "Love or Die." - Me too.
- With the same song? - It's my wish.
Honestly, I want to see both groups perform "Love or Die."
It'll be like do or die.
(Next week, THE NEW SIX versus CRAVITY)
(Who will win the "Love or Die" battle?)
Which group will know our ace first?
- Let's see. - I bet it's HYEONGJUN.
(CRAVITY's revealed ace, TAEYOUNG)
- I knew it. - Right?
His performance was amazing.
TAEYOUNG is predictable.
Let's teach him a lesson this time.
- Nice. - Yes.
Do they know our team's ace?
- Yes, they know it's JUNHYEOK. - Yes.
They must tense up.
- Right. - Totally.
(CRAVITY's aces in Round 2, TAEYOUNG...)
(THE NEW SIX's aces in Round 2, JUNHYEOK...)
- We've got one left. - The last one.
As for TEMPEST...
I predict it'll be HYUK.
- Same here. - Right?
(1st candidate, main vocalist HYUK)
HYUK is a great dancer.
- I think it'll be HANBIN again. - Me too.
HANBIN will be one of the aces.
The ace of TEMPEST is...
(TEMPEST's revealed ace)
- HYUK. - I knew it'd be him.
He's a new ace.
The main vocalist is the ace.
HYUK might kill us all with his singing.
TEMPEST needs to perform a refreshing stage.
Their intense performance was beaten to a pulp by us.
(The VS Mission winning team's confidence)
(TEMPEST performed a powerful stage for the Stray Kids Match.)
(But THE NEW SIX won.)
It'll be interesting.
(Let's wait and see.)
- You can do it, right? - Of course.
(TEMPEST's aces in Round 2, HYUK...)
(Round 2 Revealed Ace Lineup)
(HWAN WOONG, Junseok, MYUNG HO, EUNSANG)
(TAEYOUNG, JUNHYEOK, HYUK)
Everyone is a strong opponent.
It's like the teams are using their killer moves.
We'll do well.
- I agree. - I'm confident.
Having to battle against them will be scary.
I'm happy they're in our team.
Are they worthy as your opponent?
(I'm not too sure about that.)
What's important is who their partner will be.
It'll be someone who has proved himself to be talented.
They'll knock us all out.
Get eliminated, and Round Three...
Advancing to it is impossible.
We must perform.
(Who are the other 6 aces to help avoid the 1st elimination?)
(The bright morning of Round 2 has come.)
(The winner of Round 1, CRAVITY is here!)
(The air to work sure is nice.)
(8TURN, who didn't get any sleep, has come, too.)
(Sizzling)
(Round 2: Identity)
(Decided by ONEUS, the winner of the Ace Battle)
(Revealing Round 2's cue sheet)
(What?)
(For real?)
(Seriously?)
(It was set by ONEUS.)
(This is mean.)
(The cue sheet was up to the winner.)
(This is a competition!)
(8TURN in 7th place is going 1st?)
(To finish them once and for all.)
(It could be their last performance.)
(A team will be eliminated in Round 2.)
We never die.
(We will not budge...)
(from 1st place.)
(Look. This is the spirit of the 1st place.)
(We'll show you the one...)
(taking first place is scarier...)
(than the one protecting it!)
(Like we'll let you take it!)
(Stunned)
(8TURN who dropped from 1st to 7th place)
(CRAVITY who rose from 7th to 1st place)
(The prelude of Round 2 is unpredictable.)
(He came out of the casket.)
(From intense performance with their survival at stake...)
(to a refreshing stage)
(A more fierce performance battle)
(And)
(Battling with songs of the same title)
(THE NEW SIX versus CRAVITY)
(Shocked)
(It's a mirror battle.)
(Was ONEUS after this?)
(What I said has become a reality.)
(This match will also be entertaining.)
(For this joy)
I pat myself on the back for planning out this fun picture.
(What is the big picture of Round 2 ONEUS intended?)