(O Sol's Room)
(Kim Yoojung)
(Yoon Kyunsang)
(Song Jaerim)
(Yooseon)
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)
(Junior Track and Field Competition)
Until my first year in high school,
I was a track and field athlete.
Ready!
Keep going! Good!
Good!
My specialty was hurdling.
It's also known as obstacle racing.
Keep running!
O Sol, good! You can do it!
A little more. Keep running!
Yes! You're almost there!
O Sol came in first place!
First place!
Gold medalist of hurdling, Gil O Sol.
My dad always told me life was
just like obstacle racing.
Gil O Sol!
-The rules of life are so harsh
-Dad!
that once you pass through an obstacle,
another one always awaits you.
So he told me never to get exhausted,
and overcome anything, just like
jumping over those hurdles.
Back then, I didn't know
what life was about...
...or what he exactly meant by that.
I guess those harsh rules of life...
...are just like this ice cream
bar that split in two ways...
...in a way I never expected.
No matter how hard I try,
things don't go the way I want,
and life goes on
regardless of my own will.
It's like an invisible force
is controlling my life.
Let's go.
Hurdling is about jumping
over an obstacle...
...that's 76.2cm high and 120cm wide.
The two most important things you
need in order to win this match...
-...are power and speed.
-Ready.
Also, you have to estimate
the appropriate timing...
...to jump over the obstacles
in front of you.
Shoot.
Wait for me.
My knee.
What is this?
Your bad taste for men eventually
made you into a total fool.
"Am I your girlfriend now?"
Does that still work?
How embarrassing.
Excuse me. No, that's not true!
That's not true!
I said that's not true!
I told you, that's not true.
That's not true!
My goodness.
How much did you drink last night?
Watch out, this soup is hot.
Why? Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong at all.
This dried pollack soup
will help with your hangover.
What's wrong?
No! O Dol is taking a dump
in the bathroom right now!
Sorry. I didn't see anything.
Hold on.
Hey, Gil O Dol!
Get your butt over here.
-Come out.
-I didn't smoke it.
I just found Dad's
cigarette, and got curious.
I was really just looking at it.
-Take it off right now.
-What?
Pull your pants down on the
count of three. 1, 2, 3!
What on earth?
Why are you wearing this?
Wait...
-Then that box...
-O Sol, just listen to me.
Why are you wearing this!
-Stop that!
-Tell me why!
Why aren't you two eating breakfast?
What is that in your hand?
-It's the one I bought.
-No.
You little punk.
-Come here, you punk.
-It's all a misunderstanding!
I'm telling you!
Take off that underwear right now!
Come over here!
The weather is wonderful.
There's barely any fine dust
and the sky is so clear.
-Stop, you jerk!
-Get over here.
You better stop right now.
You little punk!
Come here.
Get over here. Take that off right now!
-O Sol, let me explain.
-You little punk.
You're still a little kid.
How could you smoke
when your dad is at home?
Dad, I really didn't smoke it.
I'm telling you.
I never smoke anyone's last cigarette.
Last cigarette?
Give me back my underwear!
Today is the last day you breathe.
-Dad, hold on.
-Come here.
-Please, stop.
-Let me take his underwear first.
-Take it off now.
-I'm sorry, Dad.
Come over here, you jerk!
I said, take off that underwear!
What is this?
-Stop right there!
-Stop!
Stop, you little punk!
Take off your underwear right now!
-Take it off!
-You guys...
...really seem like a happy
and harmonious family.
Good morning!
(Cleaning Fairy)
I e-mailed you the list of
cleaning tools and supplies.
Please confirm before noon.
In the afternoon, you have
to meet the investors...
A fingerprint here. Clean this part again.
And you'll have to do a presentation.
I sent you the details via e-mail.
I see soap scum in the sink.
-Clean it again.
-Yes, sir.
Another fingerprint here. Clean again.
-Clean behind the photocopier too.
-Yes, sir.
Organize the binders again.
-Jae Min.
-Yes, sir.
-Clean the toaster again.
-Got it.
-Dong Hyeon.
-Yes, sir.
-Reorganize the cushions.
All Cleaning Fairies.
Clean the whole office again!
-Yes, sir!
I'll send you a report regarding
recruitment in the first half.
Please review it and let me know.
About the open recruitment,
we'll do what we've always done.
I'll leave it in your hands.
Got it, sir.
Extra hand sanitizers and gloves...
...are in your desk drawer...
...and I left a change
of clothes at the usual spot.
-Okay, enough.
-If you need anything else,
please let me know anytime.
I will. Thank you.
(Horse Head)
You see, what happened was...
Gosh, you must've been surprised.
I left my brother's birthday
gift in that bag. My goodness.
You didn't open the box, did you?
Touching someone else's belonging
can be considered theft...
Hello, you're here.
Sorry to keep bothering you.
I know you're busy.
Gosh, why did I leave this in that bag?
Right?
-You didn't open this box, right?
-Well...
You should work on refining your taste.
You probably got dumped because
of your horrendous taste.
What did you just say? Gosh...
Who told you that you could open the box?
You're ridiculous.
Gosh, what is this?
So? When will you reimburse
me for the repair cost?
Well, that's...
I told you that I'll reimburse
you by the end of the month.
I already asked for your understanding.
Do I have to be understanding
just because you asked?
No, it's not that, but...
You don't seem to be struggling
financially, so don't be petty.
If you can give me a little
more time to help me out...
I am not a philanthropist.
I'm only here because you
found my robot vacuum,
so let's not bother each other anymore.
(Hanil Bank, Account
Holder: Jang Seon Gyeol)
If I don't receive the money
by the end of this week,
my lawyer will be in touch
to take legal action.
What? Legal action?
Does that mean you'll sue me?
How could you sue someone
over something like this?
Wait, sir.
-Sir.
-Oh, right.
Does that line still work?
"Today is our first day as a couple."
You're too easy.
He read it. He must've read the card too.
Gosh, what's happening?
Was that deja vu or a prophetic dream?
I wondered what that nightmare was about.
What? What now? What is it this time?
Another spam text from a casino?
(You've passed Jongwon Group's
initial resume screening.)
Oh, my. What a nice car.
Did you get a new car?
I don't think this is
the car I saw last time.
Gosh, you must be very rich.
Hey, what do you want?
I thought we were done.
Got something else to say?
I felt this the last time too,
but you have a tendency to just say
what you want to say and take off.
It's rude to cut someone
off in conversations.
-Aren't I right?
-So? What do you want to say?
I'm busy, so just go ahead and say it.
You read the card, but I'll let it slide
because it was my mistake.
But whether I have bad taste
or not, why do you even care?
It's none of your business.
Why do I care? Well, I never cared.
And I do not want to care.
It's wrong to look down on
others just because you're rich.
People come before money.
It's not the other way around.
Fine, I'll give you the money.
That darn 3,500 dollars.
No, after the reward,
I only owe you 2,500 dollars.
That's just my monthly salary...
I mean, it's a little more than that,
but don't look down on me like that, okay?
You got that?
Legal action, my foot.
Did you think that would scare me?
That little...
(Congratulations)
Congratulations, O Sol.
I knew you'd make it happen.
This is nothing.
It's just the initial screening.
Don't make such a fuss.
My gosh, Mr. Gil.
These days, even just passing
the resume screening isn't easy.
To be honest, it means that
she's halfway through getting hired.
Ju Yeon, you sure know
what you're talking about.
Hey, you just wait.
We're having pork belly now,
but if I do get a job this time,
I'll treat you all to rib eye steaks.
Gil O Sol.
Gil O Sol!
-Hey, come on. Rib eye steaks!
-All right.
Rib eye steaks! Gil O Sol!
-Gil O Sol!
-Rib eye steaks.
-Rib eye steaks!
-Choi.
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
Come join us.
Come and have a seat.
You're having pork belly.
Is today a special day or something?
Who is he?
That weasel who recently
moved into the rooftop room?
"Weasel"?
Is this not fully cooked yet?
It's nice to meet you. I'm O Sol's friend,
-Min Ju Yeon.
-Hi.
-My goodness.
-It's too hot.
It's not fully cooked yet.
Don't be so greedy.
Pork belly must be eaten rare.
Slow down. Eat slowly.
By the way, is today really a special day?
O Sol has a job interview tomorrow.
That's why all of us are
having dinner together.
-Stop it.
-A job interview?
It's so hard to get a job these days.
I'm impressed.
Your efforts never betray you, you know.
Make some efforts.
All right. Let's clink our
glasses to wish O Sol good luck.
-Okay, sounds good.
-Fill up your glasses.
I'd like one too.
Thank you.
Okay. You're all ready, right?
All right, here's to O Sol's
successful job interview.
-Nail that interview!
Drink up!
Look at you, Mr. Gil!
(Jongwon Group Interviewee Waiting Area)
(2018 Open Recruitment
for Interns and New Hires)
(2018 Open Recruitment for
Interns and New Hires)
Ms. Gil O Sol.
-Yes?
-Your specialty is running?
Yes. I was an athlete until 10th grade.
Then I guess you have quick
reflexes and good stamina.
There you go. I practiced this one.
Yes. Track and field is
the basis of all sports.
As you said, to be a good runner,
you need not only strength but
also quick reflexes and stamina.
But I think you need those
when you work at an office too.
Speaking of quick reflexes,
let me test how quick you are.
-Ready for an English interview?
-Yes.
Introducing yourself in
English would be too boring.
Can you tell us about any funny
incident that happened...
...while you were an athlete?
Instead of introducing myself?
-Can I start?
-Sure.
Hi.
When I was young...
Running...
And...
What should I say?
I'm doomed.
Running... Happy...
It's okay.
No one gets a job the first time.
What did I say? People these
days are so competent.
All you need to do is
lower your standards.
Also, never mention that
you have quick reflexes.
Here.
Get up.
Eat this.
Eat up.
Gil O Sol, you can do this!
Everything will work out for you.
You're an extraordinary girl.
Yes. I am extraordinary.
Here.
I am an extraordinary girl.
I love it.
I have a good feeling about you.
Do you make good coffee?
-Pardon?
-Your stockings...
Is the color Apricot Number Two?
From you to your friend, and then
from your friend to her friend...
Once you become Diamond Grade,
a six-figure salary...
...becomes yours.
(OK Loans, Leader Loans)
When are you going to pay back?
I can't believe you.
Let me teach you a lesson.
(We'll help you like a family.)
This? My daughter was born
in the Year of the Rabbit.
And my son in the Year of the Pig.
Gil O Dol, you're on fire.
Are there any others? I can still fight.
There's no one left.
Your phone is ringing.
-Just a second.
-Sure.
I found that jerk.
Come here right now.
Do you see that girl with
long hair at 10 o'clock?
I bet my hand that she'll
ask me out in five seconds.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Do you want to say something to me?
Excuse me.
Can I have your phone number?
No, you can't.
Gosh, he's so pretentious.
You're pretty, but you
don't have a good taste.
Do you want to have my number instead?
Stop right there, all of you!
Are you Lee Dong Hyeon?
Gosh, you look so sly.
Yeong Sik.
What do you like so much about this punk?
I'm not him.
Dong Hyeon, this guy wants to talk to you.
As a former athlete,
I don't want to hit a person.
We'll have a fight here,
and the winner can have Eun Hee.
I'm not interested.
What?
I'm not interested in her,
whatever her name is.
Are we done now?
You jerk.
Did you just make Eun Hee cry?
Hey. Shouldn't we head
back to the office?
I'm leaving.
You're just leaving like that?
I thought it was getting interesting.
Wait for me.
Stop right there!
-You punk!
-Dong Hyeon.
Stop getting on my nerves.
You're good.
I'm bleeding.
Why don't you stop now?
Yeong Sik.
What is it? Are you scared?
Jae Min, are you okay?
Yeong Sik, are you okay?
I think my nose is broken.
I'm okay. Bring it on.
Be a man and confront me.
Yeong Sik.
-Yeong Sik!
-This will be your last day.
Yeong Sik!
Please stop!
Are you out of your mind?
Come here!
Let's play together!
-Make a circle.
-Go round and round.
Gosh, my legs hurt.
Can I come tomorrow too?
You don't have to come here so often.
Even if you show up here
tomorrow, I won't see you.
You can't do this to me.
Now that the spirit is gone,
you're the only one I can rely on.
There they go again.
Straighten your shoulders
and be confident.
You can do this!
Whatever.
It's her.
Ma'am!
You're the fortune teller at
the intersection, aren't you?
Who are you?
I once asked you when I'd get a job,
and you said I'd be lucky this year.
You must be mistaken.
No, I'm not. I'm sure it's you. Ma'am!
Hey, the girl downstairs!
Did you have another interview?
You're busy these days.
So when can we have rib eye steaks?
Rib eye steaks, my foot.
Do you think it's that easy
to get a job these days?
Gosh, you startled me.
Why would you yell at me?
How do you know the lady...
...who just left?
The lady who just left?
Well... It's a secret. Why?
Secret?
What about the other woman?
Stop prying into my personal life.
Are you interested in me, by any chance?
What are you talking about?
It's just that strangers
keep coming to my house.
If that fortune teller
lady shows up here again,
you have to tell me.
She's a fraud.
I even bought talismans from her.
As if I'm going to be lucky this year!
Tell me when she comes to see you.
Why is it so hard to get a job?
Is it my bad year?
Nothing seems to be going right.
(Gihyeon Motors, NG Electronics,
Shimwon Display)
I thought everything would go well
once I got a job interview.
How could there be nothing
that's right for me?
Hello?
What are those pink idiots?
An idol group?
Come over here.
He's calling us pink idol
wannabes because of you.
Be quiet. This is already embarrassing.
-You be quiet.
-Stay out of it, you punk.
Hey, quiet down.
How could you get into a gang fight
in a children's playground?
It wasn't a gang fight.
These punks started it first.
Do you see my crooked nose?
-I'm really a victim.
-Shut it!
Seriously!
Look at this guy. He's a total scumbag.
Mister, you already
have a criminal record.
You have a criminal record?
It's not me!
It isn't me either.
Then what? Is it me? Or him?
-Can I help you?
-I received a phone call.
I'm here to see my employees.
It's dangerous to hire just
anyone in your cleaning agency.
You should run a background check
if you don't want to regret it later.
What? What do you mean?
That guy even has a criminal record.
Didn't you know?
A criminal record?
He doesn't even have a family
member who can verify his identity.
How could you be so reckless
when you hire people?
(Police Station)
Are you heading back to the office?
What?
Yes.
I knew it.
I hardly lose when it
comes to fist fights,
and it seemed strange.
That explains it.
Gil O Dol! You...
O Sol.
Hello, O Sol.
Fire them right away.
What do you mean?
Didn't you hear what that officer said?
They assaulted our employees first.
Why don't we just wrap this up
with disciplinary action?
They fought in their uniforms
in front of a client's house.
Isn't this more than enough to fire them?
Is this because of Dong Hyeon?
-If it's because of what...
-About his criminal record?
If I cared about something like that,
I wouldn't have hired
him in the first place.
-You knew?
-Do you think I hired him,
without knowing something
important like that?
Then why...
Dong Hyeon and Jae Min have been
with us since this company opened.
-Firing them so easily like this...
-So what?
You want me to cut them some slack...
...since I've grown friendly with them?
Ms. Kwon, that's not
the way to run a company.
At times like this, you're just like...
...your grandfather, Chairman Cha.
Cleaning Fairy has a reputation...
...for being responsible and sincere
compared to other companies.
It's all thanks to our welfare
and great working environment.
But do you know how many people
are left among the initial members?
It's just three.
Me, Dong Hyeon, and Jae Min.
Poor cleaning, poor attitude, being tardy.
You never listened to their stories...
...and just fired them
whenever they bothered you.
I can't even remember how many times...
...you changed your housekeeper
for these reasons.
Is it wrong to take care of things
according to company regulations?
It's not wrong.
But I don't think
you're doing it right either.
Anyone can make mistakes.
We can't be perfect.
It goes the same for cleanliness.
Hello?
Tomorrow is Grandpa's birthday.
You didn't forget, did you?
I know. Is this why you called?
Well, not exactly.
You sound irritated.
Is something wrong?
Let's talk later. I'm busy.
I'm trying to tell him
for his own benefit.
It feels like I'm talking
with my boss, not my son.
Ms. Cha.
What's wrong with your face
on a great day like this?
Who is it? Should I take care of him?
There is someone...
...whom I have no control
over in this entire world.
That one person.
What kind of punk is stressing you out?
That punk is none other than
Ms. Cha's son.
Ms. Cha's son?
Wait.
Ms. Cha was married?
-Is she a widow then?
-A single mother.
A single mother?
Ms. Cha!
-I'm sorry, O Sol.
-I don't know what to say.
You fought when you're supposed
to practice taekwondo?
Gil O Dol.
Do you want to give up
on becoming an athlete?
I said I didn't hit...
-I just tried to scare them a bit.
-I don't care.
Don't do anything stupid
before your entrance exam.
You're not going to tell Dad, are you?
Why? Are you afraid you might be scolded?
I don't want him to get worried.
Of course, I won't tell him.
It's nothing to brag about.
All you did was scare them?
You should've dragged them into
a corner and beat them up.
It makes me upset seeing
your faces like this.
I did hit him once.
I landed a straight right
on that idiot's face...
I'm sorry.
Eat up.
Let's eat.
(Stop)
Mr. Gil Gong Tae.
Due to the company's situation,
we can't extend your contract.
Thank you for your hard work.
200 dollars for the academy,
4,500 dollars for the student loan,
plus...
(Day to pay back 3,500 dollars!)
3,500 dollars to pay back
for the repair cost.
Goodness...
Why is there so much to pay?
O Sol.
Are you asleep, my daughter?
You came home just now?
I know it's hard looking for a job.
I'm sorry...
...for being a poor father.
Did you drink?
No, I didn't drink.
Go to sleep.
I'm sorry for waking you.
-Go to sleep, Dad.
-Okay.
(Entrepreneur of the Year)
(Excellence Award)
On my father's birthday,
with my happy family.
Flowers and Mae Hwa.
Mae Hwa is prettier than the flowers.
He's so silly.
Dinner is ready, ma'am.
Chairman Cha will come downstairs shortly.
Already?
Seon Gyeol, you must be hungry. Let's go.
I told them to make many delicious things.
Everything's been disinfected.
Shall I do it again for you?
No, it's okay.
You still haven't cured
yourself of that disorder.
Dad, you're here.
How have you been?
A little bit of dust can't kill you.
When I was in the military,
all of us slept together
in a hole in the ground,
and I even ate rice mixed with sand
when I was in Saudi Arabia.
But I'm still alive and
robust as you can see.
I find it hard to believe,
but you say you used to be covered
in dust at construction sites,
and couldn't even shower for days,
to meet deadlines for demolishing
and constructing buildings.
You say that's how you made it this far.
I've heard that story so many times...
...that I know it by heart now.
You two, again.
Why are you bickering
with each other already?
Let's not do that and eat.
Oh, right.
Ta-da.
Happy birthday.
Please stay healthy and live a long life.
Water, please.
Let's eat.
We're finally having dinner together
after so long. Isn't this nice?
Seon Gyeol, by the way, who is Geum Ja?
The other day,
you went crazy trying
to find Geum Ja at home.
Who is Geum Ja? Is it a person?
Or...
...do you have a pet now?
You don't need to know.
How dare you talk to your mother
in that manner?
Don't use a deceased person's name.
It'll bring bad luck.
A deceased person?
Who is Geum Ja? Tell me.
The person who raised me.
In your place, Mother.
That nanny?
I heard she passed away
from lung cancer five years ago.
I didn't know that
lady's name was Geum Ja.
But like Dad said,
you shouldn't use her name...
...because she's dead now.
That's creepy.
Oh, right. Did you see, Dad?
I think Seon Gyeol's
business is doing very well.
I see it everywhere these days,
from TV shows to magazines.
I thought he was just fooling
around with his cleaning business,
but I'm so proud now.
That being said,
how about you start
training him at AG now?
I'm not interested.
You have to learn the job.
Will you run that business forever?
It's not like there's another
heir that can inherit AG Group.
I cannot pass my company down
to someone with such a flaw.
No, I have no interest
in passing it down to him.
So, he can clean all he wants
for the rest of his life.
-Dad.
-Germaphobia?
What a fancy name. In reality,
it's nothing but a mental illness.
You developed that illness because
you're mentally unhealthy.
Why do you have to be like this, Dad?
How could you say that to
your one and only grandson?
I sent you to the States so that
you can treat the condition,
and you started a cleaning
business upon your return.
Why?
Did you want to clean the world
according to your standards?
How did you know?
I can't stand filth.
It looks like your place is
also full of bacteria, Grandpa.
I don't think I can stand
being in this space.
May I leave?
You rude brat!
What on earth are you doing, Dad?
Seon Gyeol, are you all right?
You're bleeding. Look, please...
Please go bring the first aid kit.
You still got that temper.
Just like when I was little.
Happy birthday.
I wish you a long life, Grandpa.
Seon Gyeol. Wait, Seon Gyeol!
Dad, why do you have
to treat him like that?
You know it's been so long
since we last gathered.
Seon Gyeol, Seon Gyeol!
We're sorry to disappoint you,
but you're not the candidate
that this company is looking for.
Darn it.
Gosh, what a mess!
Nothing is going my way.
(Interviewee Identification Slip)
Seon Gyeol!
Look at you. You look filthy!
What on earth happened to you?
Take your clothes off!
Go wipe the dirt off this instant!
Jang Seon Gyeol.
Didn't I tell you that you must
always look clean and well-kept?
Because your mom is not around,
you have to look spotlessly
clean at all times.
Grandpa, I'm sorry.
-Cleanliness comes first!
-I won't do it again.
Maintain cleanliness at all times.
Who do you take after?
Why won't you listen to me?
I'm sorry.
Chairman Cha doesn't hate you.
You know that, right?
He's just worried that other
people might judge you.
That's why he gets mad
at you over things like that,
so don't take it to heart.
Geum Ja.
Yes, Seon Gyeol.
When will my mom come
back from the States?
Ms. Cha will come home in 10 days.
You're lying.
You said the exact same thing last time.
10 days again?
Do you miss your mom a lot,
Young Master?
No.
It's just that, now that Mom is gone,
Grandpa seems to be angry at me.
He keeps scolding me...
...because Mom isn't here with me...
...and I don't have a dad.
92...
93...
94...
94.
95...
96...
3,500 Dollars.
We keep running into each other.
Do you live around here?
You live in that building
where only rich people live, right?
That super high and fancy-looking one.
Am I right?
What a coincidence.
Do you want to join me?
Have a seat.
It's my treat.
Hey.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can
pay you by next week.
I had a job interview today.
I was going to pay you...
...as soon as I land a job.
But I blew it.
To tell you the truth,
I've been failing...
...every single interview I've had so far.
I look stupid, right?
You seem very drunk.
You should go home.
Hold on.
You know what?
I...
...used to be an athlete...
...back in school.
You know what a hurdle race is, right?
I'd never fallen once.
I was amazing.
I'd jump over...
...all the hurdles in front of me.
So...
...my dad...
...used to be so proud of me.
But...
...I keep falling these days.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I keep falling even if I don't want to.
Oh, these.
You don't know what these are, do you?
There are...
...97 pens in total.
These are the pens and pencils I used...
...while applying for jobs.
This is my youth.
This is my effort.
This is my expectation.
This is my hope.
I took them out to throw them away.
But I can't seem to bring myself to do it.
Should I continue until 100?
Gosh, this is so funny.
Why do I keep making a fool of myself...
...in front of you?
I'm sorry.
I wasted your precious time again.
I apologize.
I should get going.
Gosh.
Wait.
Your shoes.
-What?
-Those...
Oh, right.
Are you okay?
Gosh.
These stupid shoes.
They're all broken.
They keep getting in my way.
Can you get up?
You got hurt too.
It must hurt.
Come on.
Gosh.
Wait...
Hey.
Wear these instead.
You shouldn't walk barefoot.
Thank you.
Aren't you the girl from downstairs?
Gosh, you reek of alcohol.
Get up.
You shouldn't sleep outside.
Put it down.
Times have changed.
You can't sleep outside anymore.
What are you doing right now? Who are you?
Gosh.
Hey.
Gosh, she's much heavier than I thought.
What's wrong with me?
I should've just kept running
like when I was in high school.
I thought if I gave up everything,
I would be able to live
normally like anyone else.
But why is it so difficult?
My life is a total mess.
Don't struggle on your own so much.
Don't try to live like others either.
If you try a bit less than others,
you'll receive less stress
than others as well.
That's how you should live.
That's how you win.
Good morning.
Are these yours?
They're not mine.
My slippers have three lines in them.
You came home in those last night.
What? I did?
You got hurt too.
It must hurt.
I have lost my mind!
Can I help you?
I've posted an announcement
for recruiting new employees.
Please confirm it.
Have Hwang Jae Min and
Lee Dong Hyeon's termination...
...been processed as I requested?
It will be taken care of within the day.
If I revoke my order...
...on firing those two...
...do I become a different
person from my grandpa?
No.
But you'll be able to
become a better owner.
Yes! Great!
Can we get some more beers?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay. Two more beers for table 1.
Miss, can we get some more nachos?
Okay.
Thank you.
(Balance: 1,480 dollars)
Dad, can you give me some...
Dad, do you have some
money you can lend me?
To tell you the truth,
when I filled in for you last time,
I got in an accident.
I'll pay you back once I get a job.
Let's do it.
(They promised me a permanent contract...)
(...but I was suddenly kicked out
on the streets for no reason)
(You can do this, Gil O Sol!)
(Cleaning Fairy)
Cleaning Fairy?
(Cleaning Fairy Fitness Test
For New Recruits)
Number 19.
Number 10.
Number 11. Please take
your identification slip.
What am I doing here?
O Sol.
What are you doing here?
Yeong Sik.
What are you... That's what I want to ask.
Me?
I've come...
...to a tiger den to catch a tiger.
A tiger? What do you mean?
I'll tell you later.
But why are you here?
No way...
Are you here to take the fitness test
for the cleaning company?
Hey! How could you...
How could you think that? You're so silly.
I was just enjoying the nice weather...
...and came here for a stroll
and do some exercise.
I think they're holding
some event over here.
Number 44, Gil O Sol.
-Yes!
-Yes?
I think it's your turn, O Sol.
It's my turn now, right?
-Ms. Gil O Sol?
-I'll be back.
-Number 45, Lee Ah Reum?
-Yes.
Get ready.
Let's go, Gil O Sol!
(Junior Track and Field Competition)
Ready.
Until my first year in high school,
I was a track and field athlete.
So far, I didn't think
my skills from back then...
...were helpful for me in any way.
Who knew they'd be so
useful at this very moment?
Hello, sir.
You're here, sir.
-What... What's going on?
-Thank you so much...
...for deciding not to fire me.
I'll work even harder from now on.
I love you, sir.
-I love you!
-No, stop it.
That's enough. I had no
choice but to put it off...
...as we're back up with orders,
so you don't need to thank me.
Gosh, that obnoxious stuck-up.
Sir.
I know I disappointed you.
I'm sorry.
That will never happen again.
The first time is a mistake,
but the second time is a choice.
It's your life, so don't make
a choice like that again.
I believe in you.
No matter what anyone says,
I trust you.
The fitness test has been completed.
Today, we'll proceed with the orientation.
Thank you for your hard work.
We discovered a real gem
during the fitness test.
You'll be happy to see her as well.
The other day...
Thank you for pushing
the payment deadline.
I'll return your slippers soon.
Also, about that day...
...I didn't make any mistakes, did I?
Don't worry about the slippers.
Just throw them out.
I hope we never cross paths again.
How obnoxious.
O Sol, isn't this office nicer
and cleaner than you expected?
Well, it's not bad.
Hey, you didn't tell O Dol...
...that we'll be working together, right?
Yes, not yet.
You absolutely cannot tell him
about me working here, okay?
If my family finds out,
I won't even ask you any questions
and beat you up to a pulp,
-so consider yourself informed.
-All right.
If that's what you want.
Your secret is safe with me.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting so long.
Please follow me.
I wonder if we'll have a
pretty new hire this year.
You know, someone who looks
like Seolhyun or Suzy.
What? Isn't he that guy?
That jerk who punched my nose.
Oh, my gosh!
What's that jerk doing here?
Sir.
These are our new hires.
-Hello, sir!
3,500 dollars?
You're the CEO?
Horse Head?
Someone once said...
...that serendipity turns a blind eye
to you when you want it to happen...
...but that it bestows its magic
upon you when you don't want it.
Just like such cruel rules of life,
another coincidence took place for us.
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)
So you're saying that guy, 3,500 dollars,
is the CEO of Cleaning Fairy?
-Sir, please.
-Gosh.
How about another round of a drink?
Gil O Sol!
Isn't it so odd?
He's a total germaphobe.
He's obviously got problems.
Let go of her hand. Don't you hear me?
-I told you to let go of her hand.
-There's no way you're dating him.
Did you ask him to act
as if he's your boyfriend?
He is my boyfriend.
Unlike you, who looks down on
those who do this kind of work,
he's a wonderful person.
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)