(O Sol's Room)
"Kim Yoojung"
"Yoon Kyunsang"
"Song Jaerim"
"Yooseon"
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)
You made this stupid mistake
because you were distracted.
You completely ruined the
company's reputation,
which my employees have
worked so hard to build.
Do you even realize it?
I'm sorry.
You're saying sorry again.
I can't even stand the sight of
you, so get out this instant.
Get out of my office and
my company right now!
(Jung Hye Won)
Mom.
How have you been?
Don't I look pretty today?
I chose the prettiest clothes...
in my closet to come see you today.
What do you think?
Do I look like a lady now?
You worried about me all the time...
because I didn't wash up
well and acted clumsy.
You're the same as always, Mom.
You look pretty.
You're so pretty, and it's
actually kind of annoying.
To tell you the truth,
I had a tough day today.
(Jung Hye Won)
If I...
didn't quit being an athlete back then...
and kept going on, what do
you think would've happened?
That darn medal.
Why were you so foolish?
Why did you go inside for that medal?
Gosh, seriously.
I really didn't want to cry today.
Look.
I'm not even wearing the sunglasses
I had on every time I came.
I would've brought them
if I knew I'd cry again.
Mom, I'll be right back.
Gosh.
That hurts.
Seriously, who could it be?
Is this the Shaolin Monastery or what?
I honestly can't get used
to climbing these steps.
Hey, you.
Is today a special day?
You look beautiful today.
Look who's talking. Is today
a special day for you?
You look like a different person.
Really? Do I look dashing?
I never said that. I just
said you look different.
What's that? That black plastic
bag doesn't suit your outfit.
Oh, this? It's nothing.
What's in it?
If it's something delicious, please share.
What is it? Let me see. Gosh, seriously.
I suffer from...
severe constipation.
Well, I heard that today...
is your mother's death anniversary.
- How did you know?
- Mr. Gil told me.
Goodness.
Why tell someone who has
nothing to do with our family?
Gosh, you're hurting my feelings here.
How could you say that I have
nothing to do with your family?
After all, we eat and sleep together.
My gosh, are you trying to
ruin my future or what?
Well, it's true that we sleep...
under the same roof.
You downstairs and me upstairs.
Do you want one?
I already have one.
What does this look like to you?
Yogurt.
- Is it not?
- It is yogurt.
But this is a very special one.
It gives me solace.
"Solace"?
When I was little, my mom gave me...
a bottle of yogurt every time I cried.
As soon as she gave me one, I
stopped crying immediately.
Someone comes by...
and leaves yogurt on my mother's
death anniversary every year.
Every year for the past six years.
I have no idea who it is,
but this tiny bottle of
yogurt brings me solace.
I feel as if my mom came
by and left it for me.
I felt that way so strongly today.
I wanted to burst into tears,
but this was so sweet and tangy...
that I couldn't even cry.
I managed to get the
exact same figure, sir.
But it's coming from overseas,
so it'll take at least a week.
Thank you. You should get going.
Sir, about Ms. Gil...
I'm pretty sure I told you not to
talk about her in front of me.
Today is her mother's death anniversary.
It's hot.
She told me that she had to go
somewhere in the afternoon.
I think she wanted to go visit
her mother at the columbarium.
What's going on this time?
That outfit and makeup
don't even suit you.
Do you have a blind date
after work or what?
Or were you going to hit on a client
who seems to be a good catch?
You're out of line.
What?
I didn't know. I had no idea.
Can I be criticized when I had no idea?
Okay, fine.
All right, Geum Ja. I'll go.
I should, right?
Did you hurt your foot?
You seem to have trouble walking.
No. My heels are hurting
my feet, that's all.
I never wear heels.
I don't think that's what it is.
From how you're walking, I can
tell it's not your shoes.
It looks like you pulled a ligament
in your ankle or something.
You sound like a doctor.
Here.
Hop on.
- What are you doing now?
- I'll give you a piggy back ride.
Neighbors should help each other.
Gosh, are you crazy? You pervert.
I'm trying to be nice. How
could you call me a pervert?
You don't have to be nice to me this way.
If you want to help me,
just pretend you never heard
what I told you earlier.
You know how some days can be.
You get all sentimental even
without a drop of alcohol.
Some people post something on
their social media late at night,
and they regret it so much
the next day morning.
How shall I put this?
After telling you those things,
I'm regretting doing so,
and I want you to forget what you heard.
Hey, my dear neighbor.
I have to say, you're very cute.
"My dear neighbor"?
Gosh, why are you calling me "dear"?
Well, because there's no one else here.
Ms. Gil.
Sir.
"Sir"?
Oh, you must be her boss.
We've been seeing each
other often, haven't we?
- Do I know you?
- Me?
The day you walked her home
because she was drunk,
her brother and I ran into you.
Oh, the pervert is here too. Hi.
Hey, what are you doing here?
That pervert.
Pervert?
Why does everyone call me a pervert?
Look, I am not a pervert.
This lady here and I live
together in the same house.
- We eat and sleep together...
- Gosh, seriously.
Just go on. Hurry up.
I'm off.
What's wrong with him? How
dare he call me a pervert?
Unbelievable.
Is that guy drunk?
What brings you here?
It's...
Well, we lucked out. There was
a vending machine nearby.
Oh, I'm okay.
Pardon?
All right, then. I'll drink both.
Well...
Why did you come all the way
here at this late hour?
Is there something you'd
like to say to me?
Well, it's nothing important.
It's about my figure.
How will you compensate me?
You probably can't even
afford to compensate me.
That's why you came here?
How much does that thing cost?
- How much did you pay for it?
- 5,700 dollars.
Come again? 5,000...
- How much?
- Forget it.
Just come to work on time tomorrow.
Pardon?
I was too harsh earlier. I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Well, how's your leg?
Sorry?
Yes, I'm all right.
If you got hurt because
the client pushed you,
you should've just told us.
Are you dumb? Why put up with it?
Well...
I mean...
I couldn't find the right
moment to tell you.
Also, it was my fault anyway.
No matter what happens,
I can't let anyone...
lay a finger on my employee.
Anyway, come to work as usual tomorrow.
To make up for the damage, you'll
have to work your bottom off...
I mean, you'll have to work hard.
- Go home now.
- Wait.
Hey, kitty.
Just a second.
I have a treat for you.
I bought it just for you.
Here.
Does it taste good?
Kitty, how do I look today?
Don't I look pretty?
I hope at least you think so.
You can find the registration
card and the serial number here.
It's the right product.
How did you get it?
Well then...
Now that you've received it,
it's your turn to show us.
- Show what?
- You have security cameras at home.
I think we should still make sure
my employee is responsible...
for breaking the figure.
Do you agree?
Do we have the diagnosis for
Ms. Gil's ankle injury yet?
It seemed pretty serious.
Yes.
The treatment will take
more than four weeks.
Our legal team is planning on filing...
assault and bodily harm charges.
My goodness.
Charges?
Mr. Jang, I got a bit
carried away that day.
I found out only afterwards.
I have no idea how it ended up there.
I'm sorry, Mr. Jang. Please
let it go this one time.
Please.
Well, fine.
But I'm not the one you
should apologize to.
You'll have to apologize
to my employee directly.
Okay?
That day,
I got a bit carried away.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry. It was my fault after all.
It's not true. I...
It was actually all my fault.
I dropped the figure there.
I'm really sorry.
Please forgive me.
You don't have to do this.
It's okay. Please stand up.
After making all the fuss and
kicking her out like that,
he went to apologize to her in person?
Does Mr. Jang have multiple
personality disorder?
You probably don't know yet.
Mr. Jang is actually...
quite soft-hearted.
Soft-hearted?
That's the funniest thing
I've heard this year.
Please come down now. Let me do it.
Hey, be quiet and go dispose
of the waste instead.
Gosh, you're so stubborn.
I'll be right back. You
have to be careful, okay?
You're distracting me. Go away.
Mr. Jang, you're here.
We're almost done here.
Thank you.
Ms. Gil, you're working so hard.
Is your leg okay now?
My leg?
Yes. I'm quite strong.
The symptoms of acute stress disorder...
usually disappear within four weeks,
so you don't have to worry too much.
But there's one exception.
Although it's not my field, it's a
condition in oriental medicine.
Lovesickness.
It occurs when you're deeply in love.
It causes you to think of someone
repeatedly and irregularly,
just like PTSD.
Although it's very rare,
if you turn out to be lovesick,
it might actually help...
treat your OCD.
Mr. Jang.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm all right.
Did you see that? Unbelievable.
I'm holding a girl covered
in dirt and sweat,
and why am I feeling all right?
Well, are you okay?
Yes.
Watch out!
What is...
Mr. Jang!
- Mysophobia?
- You didn't know?
Didn't I tell you at the team dinner?
Marvel Comics' new character,
Mr. Jang of Cleaning Fairy.
Well, I just thought...
he was a bit fussy.
He's not just a bit fussy.
He has a serious problem.
He panics every time he brushes
against someone in the street.
Have you heard of the
sticky note incident?
Sticky note incident?
You haven't?
It happened when Mr. Jang
was in middle school.
Grand Prize, Jang Seon Kyeol in Class 3-3.
The student achieved great results...
in the school math competition...
and deserves this prize.
Principal...
- Park Jeong Jae.
- He must have been pretty smart.
He'd win all kinds of prizes all the time.
- You know what happened every time?
- Congratulations.
Please send it by post.
Don't forget to pay the postage though.
No way.
I don't believe it.
How could he...
You're exaggerating a bit too much.
Why can't you believe it?
What's the first sound
babies make after birth?
Well...
I guess they cry.
Exactly.
But do you know what Mr. Jang said?
Have those scissors been disinfected?
That's enough.
Stop making Mr. Jang look
like a weird person.
What are you talking about?
He is a weird person.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You always seem to take his
side and ruin the mood.
Tell me the truth. Are you a spy?
A mole?
An informant?
You shouldn't side with those in power.
We should all team up and...
Did you buy that only for yourself?
Give me some.
Sorry. It's all gone.
Fine, enjoy.
By the way, I heard he went to US...
actually for treatment, not to study.
Was it Rochester?
They're known for OCD treatment,
but I guess it didn't work.
Who told you that?
It's actually well-known.
Come to think of it, I
feel a bit sorry for him.
He's handsome, he's tall,
and his family is rich. His personality...
can be a bit difficult at times,
but I'd say he's almost perfect.
But he has mysophobia?
I wonder how that kind of
person could catch O Sol.
With bare hands, at that.
I'm wondering about that too.
Well...
I was falling right before his eyes.
- It must have been instinctive.
- He would have dodged.
Normally.
In addition, you were in the
middle of cleaning work,
covered in germs and sweat.
You're wrong.
Could it be possible...
that Mr. Jang...
has feelings...
Feelings?
O Sol, did you wash your hair today?
No. Why?
Can you smell it? All the way over there?
Hey, come over here and smell my hair.
Oh, shoot!
I didn't mean to...
I've read too much scenarios
for romance movies lately...
and I guess my head is
full of silly romance.
Dong Hyeon, what should I do?
Are you awake? Ms. Kwon!
Ms. Kwon, I think Seon Kyeol is awake!
Don't get up and stay in bed.
Are you okay, Mr. Jang?
You can't even stand the
sight of dirty things.
Last time it was bird poop,
and this time it's a rag.
What's with all this misfortune
you're going through this year?
I knew you'd hate being in a
hospital, so I brought you home.
I'm glad you did.
This isn't even my first time.
Honestly, I was a bit surprised.
I didn't imagine that you
would catch O Sol...
in that short moment.
Is your obsessive-compulsive
disorder getting better now?
If it were better,
I wouldn't be lying here, would I?
Daniel, was it?
Did you talk with Dr. Fore's disciple?
What did he say?
- Total quack.
- Quack?
Didn't you say he was talented?
Since you've seen that I'm
fine, why don't you go now?
You'd prefer that, right?
I'll show you out, ma'am.
Let's go.
I brought your favorite fruit.
Don't skip your meals...
and if you need side dishes,
I'll send the housekeeper.
You know I throw them all out anyway.
Stop bringing stuff here.
They only mess up my house.
- Shall we go?
- Fine, I'm leaving.
By the way, what did you
mean by that just now?
O Sol, or whatever that weird name was.
Who did Seon Kyeol hold?
Well, that's...
I didn't know Mr. Jang's
mysophobia was so severe.
I even kissed him to get out of a pickle.
I practically committed murder, didn't I?
I know. But he still saved
you despite his condition.
He's just like Ghandi or Dalai Lama.
He treats violence with nonviolence.
- He needs to win the Nobel Prize.
- Oh gosh.
Why are you always like this
when someone talks seriously?
Whatever, forget it.
Goodness.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Excuse me.
Miss Neoguri? I'm sorry...
Miss O Sol?
Who are you?
I'm sorry, but who are you?
She says there's no need for you to know.
But you're the ones who brought me here.
I have to know at least...
- Mr. Jang's mother?
- Oh my gosh.
She's asking how you knew.
I saw you at our company last time.
I thought you looked very
pretty back then too.
Looking at you up close like
this, you look even prettier.
You're very stylish, and
look totally like a model.
- Liar.
- Sorry?
She heard her son got hurt because of you.
Yes.
How is Mr. Jang? Is he all right?
I was about to go see him...
as soon as I went to work today.
- She says there's no need.
- What?
She's telling you not to go near Mr. Jang.
Go near him?
But why do you keep
talking instead of her?
She and I can just talk face-to-face.
That's because she wants to show you...
that she is on a totally
different level from you...
and make you feel offended.
I'm sorry.
It may be uncomfortable,
but you need to keep your
arm fixed for two weeks.
Yes, Ms. Kwon.
I'm on my way to work right now.
I stopped by at the hospital.
No, it's nothing. It's just...
my arm hurts a bit.
Okay, I'll see you soon.
My goodness.
Mr. Kim. What are you doing
here so early in the morning?
I was wondering about the lady...
that my son, Seon Kyeol, saved.
I just wanted to see your face.
- Don't take it the wrong way.
- Okay.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
There's no need.
I was a little worried before I saw you,
but now that we've met,
I feel so relieved.
I'm a bit sensitive, and tend
to jump to conclusions often.
I hope you understand.
Jump to what kind of conclusion?
You know what I mean.
You know how parents get...
when they worry about their
young sons and daughters.
Gosh, no way!
That's totally absurd.
- Don't worry.
- I know.
I guess my imagination got
out of hand for a while.
I can't believe Seon Kyeol
grabbing or touching someone.
I was concerned, but of
course that's impossible.
I'm so relieved he will never
get intimate with you.
Why do you think something
like that will never happen?
You never know what might happen in life.
Who knows?
Look at this little brat talk.
You're pretty.
I like your honesty and boldness,
just like young kids these days.
I hope you keep working hard
with my son from now on.
Wait a minute.
Why are you thinking
that will never happen?
Is it against the rules for Mr. Jang
to like me or something?
What are you two doing here?
Oh, my. Seon Kyeol, what
is wrong with your hand?
Do not touch my body.
I don't know what business
you have with my employee.
You avoid your own mother like this,
and I was just curious about
the girl you saved. Why?
You touched a nobody
like her, but I can't?
What a messed-up disease.
I didn't mean to offend
you by saying messed up.
Cancel what you said about
calling her a nobody.
You need to watch your mouth.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
I didn't mean it.
That's fine, ma'am.
I didn't feel offended at all.
Don't worry about it.
Both of you should stop wasting
your time on pointless things,
and get to work.
The way I see it, there's absolutely
no reason you two should meet.
Ms. Gil, don't you have to go to work?
Yes. Of course I have to go.
I have to go, but...
Seon Kyeol.
That obnoxious little punk.
How could he call himself a son?
Miss, don't meet anyone like him.
Meet someone who's kind to you.
Okay. I will.
You came here to intimidate that lady,
but you seem to be more shaken up.
It was nice meeting you.
See you next time.
Goodbye.
Do you actually think I did
it because I like you?
No, not really.
I was just angry, so...
I guess you heard everything.
Gosh, you'll be late for work.
If you're late three times,
you're out.
Goodness gracious.
I left home early today.
Wait, sir.
I won't give you a ride.
You can take the bus or get a taxi.
Figure it out.
No, that's not what I was going to ask.
I'm running late because I
had to meet your mother.
Shouldn't you make an exception for...
I never told you to meet her.
You should've just said no.
We were all taught to be polite to elders.
How was I supposed to say
no to my boss' mother?
They say even your boss' dog is your boss.
What? Your boss' dog is what?
I'm just saying...
That...
Your hand...
Thank you very much for
everything yesterday.
If it weren't for you, I would've
ended up in a bad situation.
I don't know how I can thank you.
If you need help with anything,
please let me know.
I'll do everything in
my power to help you.
I do feel bad for some
things that have happened.
Ms. Gil.
Yes?
There's something I'd like to check.
- Could you give me your hand...
- No!
That's my bus!
Sir, I'm so sorry. I won't be
late if I get on this bus.
See you at work!
Hold on. Wait, Ms. Gil.
Gil...
So you ended up getting a cast?
Yes, it'll be uncomfortable,
but I decided...
to put up with it so that our
efficiency isn't compromised.
I'm impressed.
Of course. I am a competent CEO.
I'm not talking about that.
You helped someone, knowing
you might get injured.
Isn't this the first time?
Like I said,
I am...
a great CEO.
You helped someone, knowing
you might get injured.
Isn't this the first time?
I've been wondering for a while now.
Like Jae Min said,
are you...
an internal spy by any chance?
A spy?
Well, we're in the same boat, you know.
When we aren't at the
office, we can badmouth...
the company a little just
to let off some steam.
Are you the only one with integrity?
You make me feel embarrassed.
What's there to badmouth about?
There are many things. First off...
Oh, you were in the car.
What's wrong?
Please give me a call. Take care.
Oh, hello.
My gosh.
Good day.
It's a car wash service.
If you call me, I'll
come to you right away.
- Okay.
- Thank you. Take it easy.
Oh, leave all the
recyclable materials here.
I'll clean them all up after I'm done.
Have a great day.
Do you know him?
He's my dad.
Then why did you hide?
He doesn't know that this is my job.
What is it?
She was covered in sweat, but
you held her when she fell?
With your bare hands?
Was it the first time?
Touching someone other than yourself...
with your bare hands, after
your OCD symptoms began?
And you were still okay?
Your vision didn't become blurred,
and you didn't start panting either.
You didn't experience such extreme fear.
Is that what you're saying?
Well,
don't say it's lovesickness.
That's such nonsense.
Please give an explanation
that I can understand.
What I'm asking is, can my OCD symptoms...
suddenly improve out of nowhere?
Can the condition improve for no reason?
Any similar cases?
No. As far as I know, there
hasn't been such a case.
OCD symptoms arise from
psychological reasons,
so if your condition has improved,
there must be a reason behind it.
But what can the reason be?
I'm not sure.
You must have a better idea.
Then let's try this.
We'll do a simple test.
Let's find out if you're okay
with touching only that person...
or other people as well. It'll
help us determine the reason.
A test?
Try touching someone else's belonging.
If you can do it,
we should celebrate your recovery.
(Actor Hwang)
(Mr. Hopeless Romantic)
(The Love)
Guys, big news.
It gave me goosebumps.
What's he saying now?
That place in Sangwol-dong. It
has to be a prostitution house.
Oh, that house?
Did you see under the bed?
There were boxes of condoms.
I'm 100 percent sure.
Why did you explore every
nook and cranny of the house?
(Car Cleaning Service That Comes to You)
- O Sol.
- Yes?
- Do you want some coffee?
- Yes, that'd be great.
Hey, I'll do it. Get some rest.
Where did my cup go?
Did someone throw it away?
You should have washed it right away.
I remember putting it right here.
I'm sure someone threw it away.
Don't waste your time and
just use mine today.
Gosh, where did it go?
- Gosh!
- Mr. Jang!
Mr. Jang.
What are you doing there?
Were you hiding there?
What are you talking about?
Let me tell you...
why I'm here.
Well...
Those cookie crumbs!
Jae Min, look at those cookie crumbs.
If we start seeing insects in this office,
the whole staff will have
to clean up the place.
Isn't that scary?
Be careful. You all have to work harder.
Keep the office clean. You
can do better than this.
Does he look around the
place while we're not here?
I can't believe him.
- Mr. Jang, there you are.
- Yes.
When can you confirm the purchase request?
Oh, that.
Right now. I'll go to my office...
and confirm it right away.
He's been acting strangely lately.
What brings you here?
There you are.
If you have insomnia, why
do you drink coffee?
And it's fake coffee too.
- It's bad for your health.
- Forget it.
My whole life is fake anyway.
Can someone's life be fake too?
I deceive people. That's why it's fake.
When you finish your coffee,
you should go back.
- I don't need any more treatment.
- Why?
- Do you think I'm fake too?
- That's not it.
It's not like the treatment will
make the spirits come back.
- And...
- And?
I feel bad about being
treated for free every time.
It's not for free.
You serve me this amazing coffee.
I might not be able to help
the spirits come back,
but there might be something I can
do about the holes in your heart.
What do you say? Will you
give me another chance?
You should get over that accident too.
It's already been six years.
It's not like you caused
that accident or anything.
That accident?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
As if.
When my home collapsed,
it felt like my whole life fell apart.
To think I might end up in the streets,
it felt like a huge rock
was stuck in my heart.
I couldn't eat...
or even drink any water.
I was almost dying.
And you came to each of us...
to listen to our stories...
and give us the energy to live.
What you did was absolutely amazing.
Even after becoming such a great doctor,
you still haven't forgotten us.
Yes, I'm a doctor,
but I'm not sure if I'm a great one.
By the way, have you met that girl?
- Who?
- You know,
that girl who you said changed your life.
Come to think of it, she must
not be a little girl anymore.
Would she be a beautiful lady by now?
A beautiful lady, she is.
She seems to be stronger...
than I expected.
Get some chicken on your way home.
With extra sauce.
Gosh, why would he ask me to get it?
He's my little brother,
and he never does anything.
(Kwangpo Butcher's Shop)
(Beef leg bone for bone health)
- Where's my chicken?
- Here.
Yes!
What is this? Is this a chicken leg?
Is my girl home?
- Yes.
- So where's my chicken?
Chicken? You should watch your weight.
There are too many strong
ones in the 75kg class.
You should go down to 72kg.
Gosh! I wanted some chicken!
Why did you buy beef leg bone?
It looks like a front leg.
Yes. It's supposed to
be good for your bones.
Is it for O Dol?
That's a great idea. His
competition is coming up.
It's so nice of you.
It's not for O Dol.
What? No? Then who is it for?
Is it for me?
Dad, are you working again?
What?
Well...
I had a meeting outside the
office this afternoon.
Around there,
I found this.
It had your phone number on it,
so I took it.
It's just to kill some time.
It must be hard work.
It's not hard.
I'm still strong.
Do you see these muscles?
It might be a bit tough in the beginning,
but once you get some regular
customers, it can be quite nice.
You don't need any capital to start with,
and you can manage your time freely.
It's actually pretty nice.
The business cards came out amazing.
Yes! I finally have a job...
where I need business cards.
My girl, you can call me
whenever you're in trouble.
There are some kimchi
pancakes on the table.
You like them, right?
I put some meat in them too.
They taste amazing.
Look at that.
You should have told me earlier.
Then I would have bought some
makgeolli on my way home.
Why are you eating with your hands?
Use chopsticks.
Forget it.
Why didn't you make more?
It's too little, right?
- Before we finish everything,
- It tastes so good.
bring some to Choi.
- Me?
- Yes.
He helped me hand out my
business cards today.
He never complains once.
Isn't that so nice of him?
I'll get a plate.
Rooftop!
Is no one home?
Is he at the comic book cafe again?
They won't taste good when they're cold.
Why are you looking into
a guy's room at night?
Gosh, you startled me.
- When did you come?
- I've been watching you.
What? Are you really a
pervert or something?
Here. It's from my dad.
Oh, my. Kimchi pancakes?
Chef Gil is the best.
What about makgeolli? You don't have any?
When you eat kimchi pancakes,
you have to drink makgeolli.
Gosh. Why would you want makgeolli?
Sounds good!
Sounds good, right?
Cheers.
I heard you helped my dad out today.
Thank you.
No need to say thanks between us.
You're so lame.
By the way...
don't you...
have any family?
Family?
Why are you bringing that up suddenly?
I just thought...
it's time for you to receive
care from your family.
- That's why.
- I believe...
I'm old enough to live without
my family's caring now.
What does age have to do with it?
You should rely on them
whenever it's tough.
That's true.
You should rely on me when
it's tough for you too.
Aren't we practically a family now?
We eat together, sleep together...
There you go again.
You leave me speechless every time.
Living as an adult...
is tough for anyone.
Don't carry all that weight on your own...
and ask for a shoulder.
Shall we...
tell each other a secret?
A secret?
A secret just between the two of us.
Just us two?
That sounds good. Let's do it.
- Me first?
- Yes.
Fine.
To tell you the truth,
I work at a cleaning agency.
Is that...
a secret?
How could that be a secret?
What's wrong with a cleaning agency?
Seriously, don't you know
the meaning of a secret?
You're shouting it out
to all our neighbors.
Sorry. I just thought...
you were joking.
It's not a joke.
My dad will go hysteric if he finds out.
My dad has been doing cleaning
work for his entire life.
So he wished O Dol and I...
never did any work similar to that.
He told us to work...
at a warm and cool office,
no matter how small it was.
He told us to live an
ordinary life like others.
But that's not as easy as it seems.
Living like others is the most difficult.
But...
I think this line of work
suits me quite well.
At first, I was going to quit
as soon as I saved up money,
but it's pretty fun.
All I do is simply...
work hard and sweat.
I like it because it feels
like I'm exercising.
It's your turn now.
Tell me your secret.
My secret is...
that there is someone that I like.
I've been watching her
for quite a long time.
Gosh, is it some sort of crush?
Did you tell her how you feel?
No.
I'm being very cautious.
It's not time...
to show myself yet.
I understand.
It's always difficult to
catch the right timing.
It must be tough for you.
Having a crush on someone...
isn't a pleasant experience at all.
What kind of person is she?
That person you like.
Am I asking too much?
She's a very bright...
and pretty person.
That's why I want to protect her.
So she can...
always smile.
Hurry up.
(Stop Redevelopment This Instant!)
(AG Construction Does
Not Deserve To Be Here)
Here. Drink this.
You don't like yogurt?
This is really tasty.
Are you a college student?
Working part-time?
I saw you on the way to the supermarket.
You kept reading a book.
My mom told me...
the workers tearing down this area
were working against their will too.
She told me not to turn a blind
eye when I saw them working hard.
Am I being to nosy?
O Sol.
O Sol!
That's my mom.
Drink it when it's cold.
Mom!
Hello.
Where have you been?
How sweet.
Why did I bring this home?
(The Love)
Socrates said that love is
an irrational desire...
that paralyzes rational judgment.
Plato said that the lack
of judgment due to love...
is an act of a divine being,
and an area that cannot be
determined by human beings.
Nietzsche said that love always
results in mental derangement.
But the lack of judgment is optional,
and it's mostly only relevant to
the feelings for a loved one.
Love starts when you think a
particular person is special.
For example, this person may be
able to do something others can't.
Do something that others can't do?
(The Love)
Gosh, that's nonsense.
That's right.
What you thought nonsense
actually starts to occur.
Just like a miracle.
That scared me. Gosh.
You seem to be lacking
your sense of judgment.
What is this crappy program?
Lack of judgment my foot.
Why am I listening to this trash?
You are in love right now.
(The Love)
I better wash up.
Did you wake up now?
Is today a special day or something?
Why did you wash your hair?
I always wash my hair.
But what is this smell?
Are you cooking something?
Right! My beef bone soup!
Goodness me!
Good morning.
Wake up, Jang Seon Kyeol.
Snap out of it.
It's just a TV show.
It's no big deal, you know.
Pull yourself together.
Gosh, those jerks. What's
with that ridiculous show?
I couldn't even sleep because
I had too much on my mind.
I'm so annoyed. Those scums.
I hope that show fails big-time.
Karma will get them.
Did you watch the show yesterday?
It was amazing. It was a
documentary about love.
- Hello, sir.
- Sir, did you happen to watch...
- No, I didn't.
Why would I watch such garbage?
Why is it so messy here today?
If you don't clean food crumbs,
germs will multiply in no time.
All germs and bacteria, die.
Go away, viruses.
I told everyone to clean
thoroughly at all times.
Tomorrow, we'll deep-clean the office.
This must be covered with germs now.
No one knows how to clean properly.
Well...
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
You are in love.
No.
No! No way!
No! I'm not.
No way, I'm totally not in love.
I'm not. I'm not, okay?
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)
I knew that he could be a weirdo,
but he's really unpredictable these days.
This is beef bone soup. I thought
this would be good for Mr. Jang.
You should give it to him directly.
- That will be better.
- No!
- Can I help you?
- You booked our cleaning service.
The apartment complex in Sangwol-dong?
Gil O Sol!
So Gil O Sol is the only
person he can touch?
Sir, you've been acting so strange lately.
Give me your hand.
I have to check something.
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)