(O Sol's Room)
(Kim Yoojung)
(Yoon Kyunsang)
(Song Jaerim)
(Yooseon)
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)
-Go in. We're almost there.
-Give me...
Gosh, why is he so heavy?
That's real strong alcohol.
Goodness.
Just go up this step, please.
There, great.
You're doing well.
Gosh.
I'm sorry...
...for not knowing how you felt.
I mean,
for pretending not to know.
If you're sorry,
I hope you start knowing
how I feel from now on.
The time!
It's already so late.
Good night.
What should I do?
Looking for me?
Don't run away.
I left something in my room.
Your room?
I'm starving right now.
I'll go make breakfast.
Go make breakfast.
Enjoy.
Have a seat for a second.
Thanks for the food.
-About yesterday...
-You've fallen for me, right?
Pardon? I've...
-What did you say?
-So it's true.
You've fallen for me.
I think you got the wrong idea.
Be my girlfriend, Gil O Sol.
What?
Girlfriend?
Today is...
...our first day as a couple.
Our...
Our first day?
Why?
You don't want to?
No, it's not that.
I mean, that's not what I meant.
I've told you...
...that I don't have
any romantic feelings for you.
But it seems like you do.
No, I don't.
You do.
I don't.
Why are you being like this to me?
If you're joking,
please stop.
I'm not joking.
I'm dead serious.
Last night, didn't you say...
...you're sorry for pretending
not to know...
...about my feelings for you?
When did I say that?
You must've been...
...too drunk.
You caressed my face like this
as you were saying it.
I clearly remember.
Let's date.
For real.
I can't.
You can't?
No, I mean...
Let me know when you're done.
I'll clean up.
Wait, Ms. Gil. O Sol.
Ms. Gil.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Stop avoiding me and tell me.
It's not because of the doctor,
nor do you dislike me.
Why are you being like this?
Gosh, what do you mean?
At the moment...
...I'm not interested in dating anyone...
...whether it's you or someone else.
You're not interested in dating?
What do you mean by that?
You said the same thing to me a while ago.
-You said you had no interest.
-That was... Back then...
I feel the same way.
So I apologize for my reckless action...
...last night.
I'm sorry.
How much longer can I do this?
You shouldn't have moved
into that place to begin with.
What can you even do?
If it's too hard, just tell him the truth.
Who knows? He might be able to help you.
Tell him what?
"I promised your grandfather..."
"...that I'd never date you."
Are you talking about that?
Or shall I tell him that they promised...
...to help my brother
if I cured his mysophobia?
I can't say it.
I can't.
Me getting kicked out is one thing,
but what about O Dol?
Are you worried about O Dol?
Or are you afraid
that he might be disappointed?
Both.
Both?
I took on the job thinking
it'd be good for both of them,
but why do I feel like
everything's going astray now?
I already wiped that spot.
-Move. You filthy jerk.
-My gosh.
You even bought a key chain?
You have such a weird taste.
I...
...bought one too.
Let's go if we're done here.
Just a moment.
Is he seeing someone or what?
Something's fishy!
-Right? Something's up with him.
-Beluga.
Come here.
We cleaned all the glass panels
as well as the floors.
We're finishing up now.
Mr. Jang.
Mr. Jang?
Yes?
What are you pondering?
Me?
I wasn't. I wasn't
thinking about anything.
About Ms. Gil...
Have you heard anything?
What are you talking about?
Well, you know.
Anything about her being
in a difficult situation?
I don't recall hearing anything like that.
Why? Did something happen to her?
Oh, no. It's not that.
Oh, right. You said your friend
in Minnesota was planning...
...to tell the girl how he feels
about her. Did it go well?
No.
I mean...
Well, he said...
...he's not sure whether
it went well or not.
Tell him that I'm rooting for him.
I have to go to that meeting now.
Okay, I'll see you at the office.
Yes.
Why did you reject Kim Hye Won?
How could you humiliate her twice?
Is that why you called?
Do you really like men?
Do you? Is that what it is?
Stop talking complete...
...nonsense.
I'm busy. I have to go.
Seon Gyeol.
Gosh, this brat.
Feeling as if you're flying
freely in the sky...
...is certainly a privilege
only divers get to enjoy.
You can let everything go...
...and solely focus on your breathing.
-O Sol.
-Yes?
That thing's on. Your favorite scene.
-Water. The water scene.
-There are...
...many similarities.
-Oh, it's really that scene.
-It helps them realize...
...that they are the center
of their lives.
My gosh, that is really cool.
How would it feel to be underwater?
It's so romantic.
When they do not know where to go,
they move forward by
listening to themselves.
It gives them a sense of freedom.
An envelope?
Yes.
Okay. I'll bring it to you right now.
Why did he forget something so important?
Are you done cleaning?
Yes, we're done here.
We just have to check Hall B.
I can do that.
You guys can leave now.
You all worked so hard.
Get some good food on the way.
Beef, for example.
Well...
Thank you.
-No problem.
-Let's go.
Before he changes his mind.
Beluga.
Take care. I'll be back.
We'll meet again.
My goodness.
They must be lonely these days.
Mr. Jang, I'm here.
Where are you?
You're already here?
Come towards the main aquarium.
Okay.
See you there.
There is no one else here.
You can take off
those sunglasses and mask.
Okay.
This is the envelope you
were talking about, right?
I hope I didn't make any mistake.
Don't worry. This is nothing important.
Pardon?
What I needed was...
...you.
You wanted to be underwater.
I thought this might be the closest thing.
If you don't need anything else,
I'll get going.
Why? Stay with me just for an hour.
Just for an hour.
Well...
Come.
Where are we going?
The Beluga will be fine.
It sang to me with a beautiful voice.
Have you ever tried whale meat?
I know a famous restaurant.
You barbarian. You eat all you want.
My Beluga.
Have you seen my phone strap?
You lost it?
Good. It was so tacky.
I have to go back in.
Hey! You can't go in there alone.
Is that documentary fun?
You recommended it...
...to that quack.
It's not...
...exactly fun.
But it's cool.
There is a scene where they free-dive.
It amazes me every time I watch it.
Free-diving?
For a while, I seriously considered...
...learning how to do it.
Did you learn how to do it?
No.
You can't do everything
you want to do in life.
Sometimes, you're forced to do
something you don't want to do.
Sometimes...
You have to give up on something you want.
Is that a turtle?
I saw...
...this TV documentary once.
When sea turtles hatch,
they follow the stars
to go back to the sea.
On their way, most of them
fall prey to predators.
Only three percent make it...
...to the sea.
That's...
...a law of nature.
But...
...nowadays...
...baby sea turtles...
...are lured by artificial lights
on beaches.
They head to the city, not the sea.
In the end, they dry out.
Do you...
...ever wonder that?
"Am I..."
"...being guided by the stars..."
"...or..."
"...artificial lights?"
"If I am being guided
by artificial lights,"
"will I ever make it back to the sea?"
I swear I dropped it around here.
Nothing is here.
Let's just go.
No. It has to be around here.
Where is my Beluga?
Gosh, this is a waste of time.
I can't believe you.
What are you staring at?
Me?
Isn't that O Sol?
I found it.
What should we do?
I saw O Sol.
What would she be doing here at this hour?
You're being ridiculous.
I'm sure you're mistaken.
-Let's go.
-I swear.
I can't be mistaken.
Hold on.
You heard something?
Right?
I'm not sure. Let's just go.
Listen. I definitely hear something.
You don't hear that?
I think I hear something too.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
We're from a cleaning agency.
We're just finishing up.
If you're done, please leave.
Okay. Sorry.
Let's go.
Come on.
It was definitely O Sol.
Stop it.
I'm sorry. I was nervous.
Well...
Why did you hide? You could have
told them you were working.
That would have been fine for me...
...but you haven't told them...
...that you're working at my place.
I think it's been about an hour.
Shall we go?
It's already...
...been an hour?
All right.
Let's go.
Get up.
It's just like being underwater.
It's beautiful.
Whether they are stars or lights,
can't you go with me?
If we look for it together...
...we might be able to...
...make it to the sea more easily.
If that's not the case,
I'll just take you there.
Trust me.
If it's with you,
I feel like I can go anywhere.
-No, that's not true.
-You borrowed my money last time.
Don't you remember?
-O Sol!
-What's up?
-It's so good to see you.
Our food just came out.
-Cheers!
-You're dating, aren't you?
-Who?
Me? Date?
You can fool everyone else,
but you can't fool me.
Who is he?
Does he work at the aquarium?
Don't be ridiculous.
Look at your makeup and your lipstick.
You even washed your hair.
Tell me. Who is the guy
that made you like this?
Aren't you going to introduce us?
Why do you keep thinking that I'm dating?
My gosh.
I feel really happy for you.
Everyone around me is dating.
It's like it's dating season.
Why? Who else is dating?
Him.
-Really?
-He speaks so politely to her.
"Yes, I have time."
"Yes, I'm on my way."
Despite his cold looks,
he's so obedient to his girlfriend.
Look.
-Hey, don't.
-Come on.
No!
Hello? This is Lee Dong Hyeon's phone.
A guardian?
Your grandma is in critical condition.
Mr. Jang?
How did you come here?
Your grandmother is in the operating room.
She'll be out soon.
I can't thank you enough.
Who is Kang Deok Soon's guardian?
O Sol was with us.
It's been a while
since you've seen her, right?
Yes.
Unbelievable.
So the elder lady in here...
...is not Dong Hyeon's grandma...
...but the grandma of a friend
who died from an assault case?
-Yes.
-Furthermore,
he was falsely accused
for that assault case?
It's apparently a famous
story among the nurses here.
Dong Hyeon.
-Dong Hyeon.
Here's my credit card.
Thank you.
Mr. Jang paid for the hospital bills
all this time.
After I was released, I tried almost
everything you could think of.
It wasn't easy for me...
...to find a proper job
when I had a history of assault.
I did anything I could...
...and began to work
at a cleaning service company.
That's when I met Mr. Jang.
He heard my story and
still offered me a job.
Since then and until this day,
he treated me without any bias. And...
...he was the first person
who stood by my side.
Mr. Jang is like a savior to me.
Are you going home?
Get in.
Why are you looking at me like that?
What?
I thought you had already left.
I had something to take care of,
and didn't want to make you uncomfortable.
What about Dong Hyeon?
He's still at the hospital.
I heard the elder lady is okay.
The surgery went well.
I'm relieved.
You must've been surprised
to see me suddenly.
Well, a little.
I heard everything from Dong Hyeon.
That you helped him support
that lady all this time.
I wasn't the one who helped.
It's Dong Hyeon.
You look pretty with makeup on.
Sorry?
You look even prettier without it.
You're home.
Ms. Cha.
What brings you here so late?
Why are you so surprised?
Why are you two coming home together?
Why did you barge in here
again without even calling?
What is that?
Oh, come take a look.
I asked around and received pictures
of the finest ladies around here.
Why do you keep doing this?
I said I'm not interested.
Why aren't you interested?
You said you like women.
But that...
Look. I'll let you meet anyone
as long as you like her.
Please, can't you just stop?
Is there a woman you like?
Is that why?
Yes there is.
I like someone.
What? There is?
Oh my gosh.
Who is it? Who?
Hold on. Get me some juice
with a lot of ice in it.
Okay.
She is the woman I like.
So I hope you stop doing
things like this from now on.
What's he saying? What?
What's he talking about now?
Nothing. It's nothing,
so please don't worry about it.
The lady I like...
...is Ms. Gil O Sol right here.
Wait, hang on.
What's going on? So you're saying...
...this girl is the one you like?
This girl, O Sol?
-Yes.
-No.
Ma'am.
That is not true.
You said you didn't decide to move in
because you like Seon Gyeol.
You said you came here to work.
Yes, I did move in here to work.
What kind of work? Answer me.
Seducing him?
Mom.
Answer me. Since when?
Since when?
Well...
It's just...
Mr. Jang just...
...has a crush on me.
Goodness.
What? That is absurd.
Hey, why would Seon Gyeol
have a crush on you?
She's right.
It's a one-sided thing.
For now, at least.
So...
...she doesn't like you.
It's the other way around?
Why?
Why did you want
to see me out of the blue?
You see...
...no matter...
...how hard I try...
...to understand the situation...
...I just cannot understand
what is going on.
Why don't you like my son, Seon Gyeol?
Pardon?
I mean, is it even
possible not to like him?
He's handsome, rich, and successful.
He's the perfect catch, and
yet he has a crush on you.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
Is it because of his personality?
-Sorry?
-Right.
He is my son, but he can be...
...cantankerous at times. I admit it.
No, he's not cantankerous at all.
He's a wonderful person
once you get to know him.
You know him very well.
Then what is it?
Is it...
...because of his mysophobia?
Do you think it's too much?
No, it's not that.
I guess you're still clueless
because you're young.
Do you know how great it is
to date guys who are clean?
Guys who are fussy but clean...
...are much better than...
...men who never shower and stink.
It's so much better.
Absolutely.
At the moment, I can't even afford...
...to judge whether
someone is clean or not.
What's the problem, then?
What don't you like about Seon Gyeol?
Well, it's not that I dislike him.
I mean...
Shall I say it's because of...
...the difference between
our social statuses?
He's way out of my league.
I'm speechless. This is ridiculous.
You're young. Why must you think that way?
Pardon me?
To be honest with you,
I thought you were quite impudent...
...and outspoken. I liked that about you.
I'm not.
I'm very polite,
and I hold my tongue all the time.
I have no idea why Seon Gyeol likes you.
I know, right?
Why does he like me?
It's causing trouble for both of us.
By any chance...
Did my father say something to you?
-Sorry?
-Did he tell you not to date him?
Did he say there will be consequences?
Dad, we need to talk.
How dare you barge into my office?
When will you grow up?
You'll turn 50 soon.
Yes, I will turn 50 soon,
so I must say my piece.
Do not meddle...
...in Seon Gyeol's love life.
Don't do what?
I don't want him to live
a miserable life like I did.
He's miserable enough as it is.
You know that.
What are you talking about?
Seon Gyeol is seeing someone now?
O Sol.
He likes her.
When I was pregnant with Seon Gyeol,
you separated me from his dad.
Don't you dare split up those two.
If you do, I won't let it slide.
Promise me, Dad.
If O Sol cures his mysophobia,
you'll just let them be.
Okay?
Stop spewing nonsense and leave.
Now!
Dad, please.
Dr. Kim, what brings you here?
Oh, I'm here to see Chairman Cha.
He's in his office, right?
-Yes.
-Great.
Wait, Dr. Kim.
So you're saying the shock therapy...
...can produce visible results, right?
Yes.
But you need enough safety
measures in place...
Thank you, Dr. Kim.
For the fourth quarter...
I have to take this call.
Sure.
Please go on.
We conducted a survey among
our customers from the fourth quarter.
Yes, sir.
Gil O Sol?
I'd like you to find out...
...as much information
as you can about her.
Yes, anything you can find.
Anything and everything about her.
Sure. No problem, sir.
O Sol, I need you...
...to go home today.
Pardon me?
Go home?
Leave immediately.
And stay at home until I call you.
If Seon Gyeol calls you,
don't answer it. Got it?
But why all of a sudden...
I'll explain everything later.
For now, just do as I say. Okay?
Talk to you later.
Wait, hello?
Ma'am.
Hello?
Sir, it's not hard to do.
-Please check it just once.
-Gosh.
For goodness' sake.
Sir.
Check it for me just once.
Why is it, that only
that part is missing...
...among all the security camera footage?
Gosh, this young lady is so stubborn.
We don't have it because it doesn't exist!
You'll never find it even if
you keep coming, so leave!
Goodness gracious.
You're all colluding together, right?
You're helping those hoodlums, aren't you?
Those hoodlums' hit him first.
Why is only that footage missing?
Darn it.
It hurts.
Hey, O Dol.
O Dol. It's not like that.
I just fell on my own.
You're lying. I saw everything.
Move.
I said, move.
Hey!
What? Are you going to
beat him up or something?
You really want to quit sports?
Yes, I don't care.
Why would you beg
for security camera footage?
Why do you keep butting in?
I feel responsible.
If something happens to you,
how will I face O Sol?
-How will I face your dad?
-It's not your fault.
I'm the one who hit that person.
So why did you? Why?
I heard a disciplinary
committee will be held.
What are you going to do now?
What's on your mind?
Stop crying.
Are you done crying now?
This is embarrassing.
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
Here.
What?
Your skirt is way too short.
Cover yourself.
This kind of skirt is
supposed to be short.
It must be uncomfortable to walk in.
Come. I'm starving.
Wait for me.
It's so cold.
Japchae?
Is it a special day today?
Oh, my.
Here.
Try.
How does it taste?
Good.
O Sol is on vacation.
She only told me today.
Vacation?
Dad, I'm home.
Oh, my girl is here.
My girl.
How did you get here so fast?
You didn't have to bring anything.
KTX is really fast.
This is nothing.
Have you been doing well?
Yes. O Sol, it's been a while.
-You look a bit tanned.
-I do?
-I live near the sea.
-Right.
Where is O Dol?
He will be home soon.
You didn't eat, did you?
Have a seat. The food will be ready soon.
Take your time.
You're on vacation?
Kind of.
(Job Application)
(Cover Letter)
(My life turned upside down
when my mother passed away)
The quotation request has been
confirmed and sent to you.
Okay. I'll take a look.
Ye Joon must be waiting for you.
Shouldn't you head home?
Yes. I'll leave after checking the e-mail.
Thank you for today.
I'm on my way home.
Is there anything you want to eat?
So when will the Busan branch open?
What?
Oh, next week.
When it's open, I'll be pretty busy.
That's why I took a vacation now.
That was a good idea.
By the way, why is everything
that you bought from China?
You can get it even here.
Well, the thing is, things from Korea...
...are expensive in Busan too.
Right. It's hard to get fish
from Korea even near the sea.
I guess that's right.
How is it going with
the disciplinary committee...
...for O Dol?
Don't worry too much.
His coaches and colleagues
are helping him a lot.
It'll be fine.
My son, cheer up and eat.
All right.
How is it going?
Ms. Cha.
Everything is going as planned.
This will be a perfect shock therapy.
10 out of 10!
Yes!
Dr. Kim.
Is the medical team waiting outside?
Okay. Let's do this.
Ms. Gil?
Ms. Gil...
What is going on here?
Come.
(Mr. Jang)
(Missed call from Mr. Jang)
O Sol.
Why isn't she answering?
O Sol, answer the phone.
(Mr. Jang)
Go get some rest. I'll finish up here.
No, I'll do it. I'm almost done.
Then shall we do it together?
Aren't you going to answer that?
What?
It has been ringing for a while.
O Sol...
Gil...
(Mr. Jang)
Is...
...something wrong?
No, nothing is wrong.
Then leave this up to me,
and go talk to him.
It seems he's pretty desperate.
Okay, then.
Hello?
Mr. Jang?
O Sol...
Hello?
O Sol.
Mr. Jang?
Do you hear my voice?
O Sol...
-O Sol...
-Is something wrong?
Mr. Jang?
Mr. Jang!
What on earth is so urgent...
...that you have to go out this late?
I'm sorry, Dad. Something
came up at the company.
I'm sorry, O Dol.
I'll call you later!
I'll go with you.
Mr. Jang! Mr. Jang!
Mr. Jang!
Get out!
I said, get out! Get out!
Everyone, out.
Get out!
Don't you hear me?
Mr. Jang.
Mr. Jang!
Oh, gosh.
What happened?
Mr. Jang, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
You have to regain your senses.
Mr. Jang! Mr. Jang!
Mr. Jang...
Mr. Jang!
O Sol.
Gil...
...O Sol.
Are you okay?
He will be fine now.
Don't worry too much.
Did you look into what I asked?
An accidental death?
When?
The Jungang-dong incident?
Are you saying Ms. Gil's mother...
...was one of the victims
of the AG Group incident?
I understand.
(Applicant Form,
Gil O Sol)
You must've been so scared,
suffering on your own.
I didn't even know that.
I'm sorry...
...for coming too late.
Mr. Jang, Mr. Jang!
Gil O Sol.
O Sol.
O Sol!
Mr. Jang, you're awake.
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
I was so worried about you.
I thought something bad might've happened,
and I was terrified.
Mr. Jang.
From now on,
don't go anywhere without me.
You have to stay...
...right next to me 24 hours a day.
Okay, O Sol?
I will.
I won't go anywhere.
Let's be together 24 hours a day.
Don't go anywhere.
You promised me.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll stay right by your side.
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)
I can go by myself.
Yes, Mr. Gil. Please allow
me to date your daughter.
Isn't he so good-looking?
He's my boyfriend.
I really shouldn't be doing this
for O Dol's sake.
A disciplinary hearing
for O Sol's brother?
Your brother will be fine.
I plan to pass AG Group
down to Seon Gyeol.
They're certainly
not right for each other.
Find suitable people
to put in the disciplinary committee.
(Clean with Passion for Now!!)