[English subtitles are available]
[Dowon] [Yoon Dojin]
[With My Dear Bro]
We're probably going to take that.
Left, right.
Let's go, let's go.
It feels like we're really in El Nido.
What should we do
tomorrow morning?
Charge at home.
Give me a 1,000 Peso note.
Okay. Here.
I'll make you something simple.
It's more portable. Something you can eat quickly.
They sell strawberry jam here too.
-Strawberry jam?
-Yeah, they sell it here.
Do you like banana strawberry jam?
-I've never had it before.
-You've never had it before?
Tissues.
[Eat well, bro.
Come to Lio Beach at 1400]
Although I'm not good at drawing now,
recently, I've been preparing to draw.
I hope I can draw when I have time.
For example, when making a poster,
I can draw it with an iPad.
Like this,
add in the color.
I need to print my own clothes too.
Can I order a basil mojito. No alcohol.
-Basil mojito, no alcohol.
-Yes.
Sorry. Do you have scissors?
Okay, can I borrow it?
Thank you.
The view is beautiful.
Hello.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Thank you.
Before I came here,
Dowon and I made a promise to give each other a surprise.
I've prepared it. I prepared it in Korea.
Something that reminds me of that place.
I bought one in every place.
It's all done.
Like this. The bracelet, is done.
It suits the wrist.
Brother's wrist is thinner. This is definitely his size.
When I give him this present,
I'm going to give this to him secretly.
Yes. Now, mojito, basil mojito.
I can finally taste it.
The ice has already melted.
I'm going to give him a poster as a gift.
I'll put it up in his place with a small letter
and send it to him together.
This one.
[Dojin, this trip...]
This trip...
I chose this poster because
this image,
even so, are you able to get what you want
in your life
and to feel that you're loved?
Something that conveys that.
Because a lot of locals in El Nido love Dojin,
I hope you keep this memory, and become a better actor.
I hope you can trust yourself more and move forward.
I don't know if Dojin can find this.
Then I'll put it on the most obvious sofa in the living room.
Bye.
If I let you join together,
what kind of competition do you want to take part in?
I like basketball.
You can go play with them.
What?
Nice!
Net!
What?
One more point! One more point! Just wait a little.
Nice!
Just cross the net.
See you again, bro.
Thank you. Thank you. Bye bye.
Let's go. You saw that, right?
With the spirit of DODRAM.
DODRAM?
The name of the volleyball league is DODRAM.
-We have to go that way.
-Pick up the ball.
-When did you get here?
I... About 30 minutes ago.
Let's go. Where? Over there?
Here, this way.
Yoga.
Have you ever done yoga?
I did that, pilates.
Pilates. How was Pilates? Could you do it?
Of course, I'm flexible.
-I want to try.
I want to learn it.
Have you done yoga before? Can you do it?
I can do some pilates.
Oh, that's right.
I'll teach you.
I just have to stay still, right?
-Of course. Just follow me.
-Okay.
-Hello. -Hello.
Hello. Nice to meet you. I'm Dojin.
-You're back.
-I'm Dojin.
-I'm Beck.
-Beck.
-I'm Dowon.
Do-won. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
-You're a yoga class teacher, right?
-Yes.
Okay.
When will we start yoga class?
And then we're gonna do the yoga at the end of the bridge.
-Here?
-Yeah. During sunset.
It must be beautiful.
-That's good. -That's good.
I need to use the toilet. Prepare, and like change clothes.
-Okay. Toilet's over there.
-Thank you.
-Go ahead. -Okay.
The toast is good.
I spread some banana strawberry jam. How is it?
It's delicious.
The plane flew over.
I really like the sea.
-The sea?
-In travel destinations.
I like everything. Cause it's traveling.
If I don't have to do yoga today,
I would just rush in.
You can go ahead. I'll wait for you.
I'll talk to the teacher.
No, it's already scheduled.
What do you take a schedule for?
The teacher is here.
-Hi. -Hi.
Are you ready for the yoga class?
-Yeah, I'm ready. -Yeah.
-We're going to do yoga there. So let's...
-Over there?
-You can take one each.
-Okay.
-You got it? -Yeah.
Wait. I'm already getting tired already.
Give it to me.
-Give it to me.
-No.
-Do you need help? -No, no, no. I'm strong.
-He's pilates master.
-Yeah.
-Pilates master.
Yoga class... Is hard?
We can do hard
we can do easy, it's really up to you.
What do you want today?
-Very very easy.
-Okay, no problem.
Thank you.
How many minutes do you want?
-He's master.
-Yeah.
He's only hard, hard course. I'm easy.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Put your arms by your sides.
As you inhale, reach your arms up.
Look at your hands.
As you exhale, slowly fold forward.
And then step your feet back to a plank pose.
All right. Now look forward again. Inhale, to the tip of your toes.
Lift your chest up, open the front body, maybe look up.
And then exhale. Send your hip back. Tuck your toes.
Lift the hips, downward facing dog.
Last two breaths here.
And then inhale, start to walk or step your feet forward.
And exhale, release your ar,s.
This time, bend your knees into a squat.
And then inhale, find your chair pose.
Imagine you're sitting down on a chair.
Go ahead. Bend your knees.
Bend your knees, reach your arms up.
And then start to look up towards the sky.
Start to do the same thing you did on the other side.
Okay, look at one spot again.
Look at one spot again.
Focus there, take your hands to your chest.
Four.
Three.
Left foot steps back, plank pose.
Look forward, inhale, and then start to look up towards the sky.
But at the same time, you're stretching up higher.
This time we're going to step only the left footback.
-Two.
-One.
Left heel down.
Extend your arms out.
Rest your other ear, relax and breathe.
Okay, let's do round two.
Look forward, take your hands forward this time.
Okay. When you're ready, inhale, lift the chest.
Maybe lift the arms.
You can stay here if you want or lift your feet.
Five. Maybe look up.
Four.
Keep breathing. Three.
It should be the last step.
-And exhale back to where you came from.
-There should be another 10 minutes.
-I don't think so.
-From here, straighten your front leg.
Exhale there. How are you feeling?
Feel so good.
Keep going. Balancing pose. We're going to do three poses.
Start to walk your shoulders. Closer to the ground.
Make a bridge pose.
Look, isn't this a zombie?
Four, hold it up. Three.
Put your shoulders in. Put it in more.
Put what in?
I told you to put it inside.
What more?
That's it.
You can do it.
All the way back down.
Back down.
Oh, okay.
We'll do one more round.
-O-one more?
-One more?
Okay, one more.
Yeah, one round.
Exhale everything out. And when you're ready,
start to reach your right leg up to the sky.
Right leg up.
Two, three.
Hang in there.
Four.
My...
Two, three.
If I hadn't had surgery.
If I'm not this tall.
Let's slow down the breath.
We're here for five.
This is our final pose.
It's called the shavasana or corpse pose.
Where we allow the body to completely relax.
Good relax but
my body is dead.
I'm hungry.
-Hello. -Hello, guys.
Hello.
This is our food menu.
Good evening.
-Thank you. -I also have some drinks here.
-Really? -So many dishes.
Here also.
Thank you.
How are you? My name is Marcos.
-Marcos. -Marcos.
How are you?
I'm Dojin.
Welcome to the Philippines.
-Thank you. -First time here?
Yeah.
-My first time here.
-All right.
Should we ask him to recommend it?
-Can you recommend best menu?
-Yes, okay.
Since you're two,
I'd recommend our paella.
This is very good. Very famous in Spain.
We make it really good. You will try.
-Okay. And for two. -Okay.
Croquette and gambas.
Croquette and gambas. Yes.
Two sangrias.
One each?
-Yeah. -Okay.
Perfect.
Thank you.
-Thank you. -Thank you very much.
It's so pretty.
You said you liked this kind of bread.
This kind of bread is delicious.
It looks really delicious.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
Enjoy, thank you guys.
It's so beautiful.
Aren't you going to cheers?
I'm not drinking.
No, who would cheers for sangria?
You're Korean. What are you talking about?
-As long as you're Korean... -Okay.
I just pretended to drink.
-You didn't drink, did you?
-I didn't.
Is this a toast?
-I think I hit it hard. -Hold on.
You need to say a toast.
Go ahead.
An acrostic poem with El Nido?
-An acrostic poem with El Nido? -Yeah.
-El.
-In El Nido.
Ni.
Three, two.
In Nido.
Do.
With Dojin.
I'll give you 3.7 points.
-Okay. -3.7 points.
How was the yoga today?
I think it was great.
To be able to see the sea while practicing yoga.
How many more times can there be in my life?
That's right.
It's really nice. Like you said. Seeing the sea.
I pretended I couldn't do it.
Two.
Right? You said you did pilates.
I was a little flustered.
I've done pilates about five times now.
-Five times? -Five times.
You're a master at this level.
That's right.
It's here.
Here, the platter selection.
Thank you.
-It looks delicious. -It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
What's wrong?
Is it hot?
It's too hot, so I can't taste it.
I think so.
How is it?
Tasty?
It's really good.
I recommend this place. It's a good restaurant.
A good restaurant?
Trip advisor? 999 points?
Yeah.
It's really delicious.
Delicious.
Great.
But I won't forget today.
I had a tiring day today too. I had a good time.
I...
Say "Dojin, you worked hard."
-Today is really.
-It's so good.
No need to say anything.
I just want to enjoy today.
Let's enjoy the food now.
Okay, let's have a drink.
Cheers to the third night on El Nido.
El Nido!
Let's get it.
-Why didn't you finish it?
-It's really good.
Okay. It's really good.
Hurry up and eat.
Is this how you do it?
[Enjoy, brother.
Come to the Lio Beach at 1400]
Brother!
This is the best healing.
Cheers.
This is our last shopping day.
Let's do a mission.
Buy clothes and put them on within the time limit.
He's not here.
We can't buy anything at this rate, can we?
Oh no!