[English subtitles are available]
[Do Won] [Yoon Dojin]
[With My Dear Bro]
Today.
We are shooting morning vlog for Do wWon.
-Hello. -Hello.
What are you doing?
What brings you here?
I'm from the filming team.
I see.
Hold on.
Can I go to the bathroom?
You're pretty shy.
Hold on.
Are you a parrot?
Come in.
Okay, got it.
What are you spraying?
A mist.
A mist?
Thank you.
I'm going to pick my sunglasses.
This is a prop for someone shy.
Yes.
I want to choose one of these two.
Which one should I choose?
For me, not this one.
It's the same color as the shirt.
It looks good on you.
-I can't see.
-It's Korean style. Someone on the front.
I can't see anything.
Let me light up your road ahead.
-Which one is better? -Brown.
Brown.
I'll wear this then.
I'll pick this.
Do you want to check your luggage again?
Someone stole my phone.
Did you leave it downstairs?
-Ah... Mr. Cockroach -Mr. Cockroach.
Mr. Cockroah, where's the phone?
Mr. Cockroach?
Give me my phone.
Weren't you playing a song?
Oh, that's right.
Thank you, sir.
Let's get it
The weather is nice.
You said the weather is good?
Weather is good.
-Weather is good. -Yeah.
-We're have to go eat seafood. -Seafood.
You said you wanted seafood.
-I want seafood too. -I really want it.
Do Won said he wanted to eat seafood.
Seafood?
I found a restaurant he'll like.
A restaurant that specializes in seafood.
There's seafood here, right?
There is indeed seafood here.
Check the menu.
There are all kinds of prawns.
Prawn dishes.
Squid dishes.
Lobster.
Shall we eat here?
What should we eat?
-What a happy worry. -Yeah.
I'm drooling.
-Lobster. -Lobster?
-Grilled. -Let's get it grilled, shall we?
This one?
Okay.
Let's have a prawn, shall we?
Prawn.
Is this garlic pepper?
-Garlic? -Yes garlic pepper.
-This one. -Okay.
And for drinks, Coke Zero.
-Okay. -As usual.
One grilled lobster.
And then, one garlic pepper prawn.
And steamed oysters and baked clams.
One more dish of this.
And this soup.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
Okay.
It's our last shopping today, right?
-Almost. -That's right.
It's like a mission. Giving each other a fixed time.
And wear the clothes we bought for each other.
We need to finish in quickly an hour. Right?
I've never worn a Hawaii shirt before.
Choose a cold tone one for me.
Cool tone?
And flip flops that's very local.
Flip flops that's very local.
I'll leave it to you. Okay. Got it.
I trust your feeling.
You.
It's real.
Thank you.
This is soup. This is the grilled oysters we ordered.
-We don't need to dip this in sauce, right? -Cheers.
Cheers, oysters.
There's that seafood vibe.
It's fresh.
Delicious.
Prawn cheers.
Cheers, prawn.
Cheers.
It's really delicious.
I really ate a lot.
The prawns?
I've never missed a college festival--
Does it want it?
What should I give it?
We can't let it eat.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
-Steamed fish with lemongrass. -Thank you.
It's kind of...
-What? -It's really salty.
It feels like eating fish sauce.
It seems to be the problem.
We have to remove this and it'll be fine if we eat it like this.
Something like this.
Thank you.
Very tender.
Have you eaten lobsters?
I really had it a long time ago.
It's my first time.
Really?
I'll do a drone shoot.
A drone shot?
Try it.
Thank you.
How is it?
This is what lobsters taste like.
The forehead that shows the truth.
A new palette to my taste buds.
Lobster.
Thank you.
Is it good?
The Spanish restaurant was really good too.
This is really delicious too.
This is the best healing.
I'm eating a lot.
Let's go.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
Thank you, sir.
-Bye bye. -Thank you.
One hour. Shop for an hour.
Okay, one hour shopping.
Don't buy weird clothes.
-I'll work really hard. I will be serious. -That's good.
-Something taht we both will look good in. -A little.
Okay.
Let's do that.
-I'll go this way. -I was going to go this way.
-Then I'll go this way. -I'll think about it.
-I think I should go this way. I'm going. -Okay.
Extreme introvert starts again.
This is bad.
It's because Dojin isn't here.
So this is what it feels like.
Hi.
There are a lot of pants here.
Can I buy three? 20?
If I look for it, there should be other areas.
I think there's a performance there.
Lady.
Won't you leave me.
They're singing a song I know. How interesting.
-Hello. -Hello.
The doggy is taking the car like this.
It's amazing. The police cars here in El Nido
are like trucks.
They're so passionate. I-I
couldn't even lift my head.
Hello.
I'm going to sort out my schedule for today.
With this friend.
First...
Okay.
With Papago. Hello, I'm shooting right now.
Hello. If you don't mind, can I film?
Hello. If you don't mind, can I take a picture for a while?
Okay, let's go.
Let's go somewhere else.
-Hello. -Hi.
Hello.
Wait.
If I'm shy I have my sunglasses. I can just wear them.
Okay.
I'm confident now.
I'm going in for a bit.
Hello. If you don't mind, can I take a picture for a while?
-Hi. -Hello, sir.
Hello. Hello.
If you don't mind, can I take a picture for a while?
-Yeah, sure. -Sure.
Thank you.
How much is it? So this place is expensive.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
At this rate, I won't be able to buy anything, right?
I got here first.
I think, Do Won is probably still wandering around now.
What time is it?
This is bad.
I'm here, but he's not here yet. That's it!
Where was it?
Oh it's here. I'm here, I'm here.
What time is it?
-What time is it? -Did you buy something?
I arrived at 50, just now.
What do you take a promise for?
-Let's go. -Back home?
-Yes, let's go home. -Okay.
Buy some vegetables along the way, then go home.
-Okay. -Let's go.
What did you buy?
But it's much cooler inside.
I'll put it here.
Here?
Don't you need to take a shower?
I'm going to marinate the chicken first.
-I'm going to marinate the chicken first. -Okay.
Add some oil.
He really eats a lot.
I'm really confident now. In terms of eating,
-Now my weight... -Weight management.
What did you eat to lose weight?
Chicken breast, rice, kimchi.
-Really? -Yes.
Can I eat two whole fried chicken?
Two whole fried chicken. Two.
At least two.
-Are you going out? -Yes.
Go ahead.
What are you going to take?
Me? The motorbike.
Take care on your way. Safety first. Safety.
I'll be back.
Is there really nothing you want to buy?
Melona?
To get Melona when I return?
-Yes. -Okay.
Oh, right.
If a cockroach shows up, call me.
Don't say that.
Be careful. It might even appear on the ceiling.
I can smell the chicken already.
Let's cut it with a knife to make it marinate better.
Add some salt.
What is this?
Put some curry powder.
I need to get changed.
While Do Won makes the fried chicken,
I'm going to buy some fruits and food that he likes to eat.
And also Melona.
I'm at the market.
Hello, hello.
Do you remember me?
-Yeah. -Sure.
I remember you.
Do you want to get one for free?
Yes, because so many.
You want one free because you buy a lot.
Yeah, a lot.
-Yeah this is all really, really. -Yeah. Yeah.
Nice.
-All of? -All?
Yeah.
Let me try if it's the right flavour first.
Can I try this?
-Yeah. -Yeah?
It's right.
It's right. I'm going to cry cause it's so good.
This is it.
I found it.
Discount.
-So how much is it? -620 pesos.
-600 only. -600 only.
-600? -Yes.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
You have a cute smile.
-Me? -Yeah.
We, together.
Saying that we are both cute.
Put fried powder on the outside.
I think it'll work if we fry it for eight minutes.
Dojin will enjoy it anyway.
It's going well.
Dojin is here.
Do Won should be taking this with me.
The weather is nice.
The view is nice.
There's a feel to it.
It reminds me of the past.
Nice.
You bought a lot. Gosh.
It's really delicious.
It's really delicious. It's really delicious.
-It's sweet. -The staff should try this too.
-Right. -Really.
Shouldn't we buy some?
It's so sweet it's basically a fraud.
All of?
-All? -Yeah, yeah.
Four pineapples. Thank you.
This must be delicious.
Is the fried chicken successful?
The pineapple cutting was successful.
What?
You cut a lot.
Right? If I put my mind to it, I can do it really quickly.
It looks delicious.
Oh, no.
It dropped.
I will eat well.
It feels like you know,
when I go to my grandma's,
The vibe of the chicken sold in the countryside?
The size are similar.
The legs are really big.
It's not bad.
It doesn't really stick on your teeth.
It's good.
But I don't really like fried chicken.
But I like this kind.
It smells nice too.
I have to try the pineapple.
The plate you're using.
It's like minimalism.
It's like the chicken from the countryside.
Why is it so cooling?
The pineapple will probably appear in my dreams.
It's the clothes that you want to see the most.
Okay.
First of all, this hat is the first one.
What do you think?
It's kind of like during the Rehabilitation period...
How should I put it?
Like what Nietzsche wore.
Give it to me. I'll try them on one by one.
It's really good.
Okay, next.
Next.
And these shoes.
Sun... Sunny shoes.
Sunny... Sunny shoes.
What's this? Aquashoes?
Aquashoes? Yeah, aquashoes.
There has to be a highlight in fashion.
It'd be perfect if I wear this in the water.
You have to wear it in summer or in the water.
Okay, next.
Next.
Next is...
Shirt.
Get me a cool tone one.
I've never worn a Hawaii shirt.
How should I put it? Traditional Hawaiian vibe?
Shit.
It feels like traditional Hawaii.
But isn't it nice?
Well...
It's very comfortable,
-the shirt -Yeah, very comfortable.
They said it's 100% pure cotton.
-The silky smooth touch to it is nice, right? -That's right. This is good.
Okay, next.
But the pants...
-There were really no pants. -There weren't pants.
There weren't any, but even among those,
I chose the best one.
I'll pretend I didn't see it.
This pyramid vibe, El Nido vibe.
El Nido pants. Do Won, aren't you an elephant?
But I like them.
I actually like this kind of pants.
This is pretty.
I found it.
But I like them.
I actually like pants like this.
It's like ice pants.
I bought them given I don't have other choice.
Fine, I agree with this pair of pants.
Thank you anyway.
But for me, I tend to like
wearing clothes according to the atmosphere and the mood.
But this mood is a bit hard for me.
-I'm an introvert after all. -Okay.
This is really loud.
I don't know what there is.
First of all, because you said your feet is not feeling comfortable.
First, sandals.
I do want to buy slippers.
Okay. They said they don't have my size.
I'm touched.
Try it on.
Your feet are 280. I bought 280.
No, Do Won, if this is 270,
my feet will change automatically when it goes in.
It really suits you.
Right?
But it's really good, isn't it?
It's nice. I really like it.
Next.
Hawaii shirt.
This is a stretch.
Plastic. Is real plastic.
It's not bad.
And, wait, wait, wait.
What else?
These is real sunglass.
-Real sunglass. -Yup.
You don't have sunglasses, do you?
It's a nice day, but it's really sunny.
Holy!
Sunglasses. I really don't have sunglasses.
Thank you. I will wear it thankfully.
Okay, I'll take a shower first.
Okay, go ahead.
Go take a shower.
The sunglasses are really good. I'm going to wear them tomorrow.
I'll keep wearing them when I get back to Korea.
Of course. I'll wear them when I get back to Korea.
I'm turning the lights off.
Okay.
I'm already sleepy.
I'm sleeping with my shoes on.
When I bought that shirt,
I said it was for my friend.
I said you are a big man.
My friend, gift.
Not me.
He... He is big man.
Big man?
Yeah. big man.
The last large size was on the mannequin.
So I bought it and they took it off.
I walked around with my instinct.
I need to see how to match it.
Like this design and this color.
There were places that seem branded too.
It was too expensive, so I just left.
It looks like a brand store in El Nido.
This shop is an expensive place.
Thank you.
Even if it's expensive, since it's a gift for you,
so I didn't...
So you didn't feel like it's a waste of money.
Yeah, I didn't. I just felt like you have to wear this.
Whoa. I will become someone who can live up to these presents.
Dojin said his feet hurt. I think I should buy him this.
I mean it.
If someone asks me for it, I won't give it to them.
This is really good.
Thank you, friend.
Hello.
Let's go.
I had so much fun.
I had fun with no regrets.
Until I miss it again.
When I miss this air, this relationship, this closeness,
I would want to come back again.