♪See how the clouds drift♪
♪Chasing after the glow of the setting sun♪
♪But they end up lost♪
♪In the dark of the night♪
♪Had I never touched♪
♪The moon's reflection in the water♪
♪Never shattered♪
♪That beautiful lie♪
♪Perhaps I'd never have understood♪
♪That despair is but an illusion♪
♪Love is like a blade♪
♪The thinner, the sharper♪
♪The wound I made♪
♪Just inches from my heart♪
♪Yet still, it couldn't♪
♪Stop my longing♪
=Love & Bid Farewell=
=Episode 16=
Zhao Li?
Sister Yao?
Slow down, don't fall down!
Catch me if you can!
Slow down. I can't keep up with you!
I told you to slow down!
Sister Yao,
you're so kind.
When we grow up,
it would be wonderful
if you could marry my brother.
What are you saying, silly girl?
Your Highness, I've told you
that you cannot enter without permission!
Chief Gu, are you alright?
I'm fine.
- You may leave now.
- Yes.
Come inside quickly.
Sister Yao,
where have you been all these years?
My brother has been so worried about you.
Chief Gu?
Sister Yao,
were they calling you?
Yes.
Sister Yao is indeed Chief Gu.
I'm truly happy to see you again
after all these years.
But there's something
I need to ask you.
What is it?
Feel free to ask.
Now that you've given me permission,
I'll speak plainly.
Now
I'm engaged to the Crown Prince.
But I've heard
that there's a palace maid
who is very close to him.
I want to know,
if you are the maid
who is always by his side?
Yes…
I see.
My brother and I thought you were dead.
For years,
on every Ghost Festival, Qingming Festival,
or your birthday,
my brother couldn't sleep,
tormented by thoughts of you.
I was heartbroken too.
But I never imagined
that not only were you alive,
you had entered the Eastern Palace
and become a close confidante
of the Crown Prince.
Or rather,
his favored guest.
Zhao Li,
you've misunderstood me.
Misunderstood what?
Misunderstood that you
and the Crown Prince are innocent
and nothing more,
or you're not his favored guest?
Zhao Li,
listen to me.
My relationship with Yue Jinchen
is too complicated
to explain in a short time.
Yue Jinchen is not a good person.
If you marry him,
it might not be a good thing!
If I don't marry the Crown Prince,
does that mean you want
to marry him instead?
I would never marry him!
Sister, that's absurd.
You don't want to marry the Crown Prince,
yet you don't want to leave him either.
After all these years,
I thought you
were still the same sister I knew.
But I see
you've changed.
Staying here
is not my choice.
It's Yue Jinchen who really...
Enough! I don't want to hear any more!
Sister Yao,
we used to do everything
together as children.
I only ever wanted to confide in you.
I always thought
you would marry into my family
and become my sister-in-law.
But now
I see you had grander ambitions,
looking down on my brother.
My relationship with Zhao Ming
was never possible.
But things are not as you think.
Zhao Li,
Yue Jinchen is not a good person.
He's deep and scheming,
He's not what he appears to be
on the surface!
I told you,
I don't want to hear you
slandering the Crown Prince anymore.
Your Highness?
Who gave you permission t
o act so recklessly in the Eastern Palace?
Your Highness, I...
- Get out.
- Your Highness, I...
This is the Eastern Palace,
not your mansion.
Zhao Li, leave now.
- Yao...
- Yue Jinchen.
So you've been deceiving Zhao Li
while keeping me imprisoned?
I'm only doing this...
Everyone who cares about you
ends up being used by you,
turned into nothing
but pawns in your game.
(Yao)
(What should I do?)
Poison Mandarin Ducks and Forgotten Love Water
(The Secret Poisons of Yueying)
are two legendary secret poisons.
(- Forgotten Love Water)
It's said they can control one's mind.
Those who are poisoned
will only listen to the one
who poisoned them,
obeying all commands without resistance.
However,
the one whose blood is used
to bind the Poison Mandarin Ducks
will have their life shortened.
No one who's experienced it
has lived past the age of forty.
Poison Mandarin Ducks and
Forgotten Love Water are not ordinary.
Poison Mandarin Ducks
shares emotions,
joy, and sorrow.
Forgotten Love Water
erases past memories,
forgetting everything.
Poison Mandarin Ducks only works
with my blood as the binder.
Once she forgets everything,
she'll love me only.
Your Highness, you must not!
Are you willing to risk your life?
Back then, my mother wanted
to use this on my father,
but she only wanted him
to feel her happiness,
not her sorrow.
So she hesitated and never used it.
In the end, the Empress found out,
accused her of practicing witchcraft,
and she was sentenced to death.
So I mustn't be soft-hearted.
I need Yao to forget everything,
so that
we can be together forever.
Your Highness, if you use the poison,
it will backfire on you.
As long as I can be with her,
what does it matter if I only live to forty?
That's enough.
Your Highness...
Leave.
Yes.
(Poison Mandarin Ducks)
(Forgotten Love Water)
(Yao)
(We can start over)
My lady,
please have some.
Or I'll be punished again today.
Has she eaten?
Replying to Your Highness,
Chief Gu ate everything.
I watched her finish it.
Yao,
after tonight,
we can start over.
Yao.
Yao, you're awake.
Who are you?
You don't remember me?
That's wonderful.
You...
You're hurting me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Yao.
Yao?
Who is Yao?
This place...
Where am I?
I am Yue Jinchen,
the Crown Prince.
You are my betrothed.
We've known each other since childhood,
and were engaged long ago.
But because I made enemies at court,
you were kidnapped
by villains
and fell off a cliff.
You've been unconscious ever since.
The physician said
you might lose your memory.
I didn't expect...
I'm sorry, Yao,
for the suffering you've endured.
From now on,
I will never let you be wronged again.
We're getting... married?
Yes,
we're getting married.
Now that you're awake,
we should proceed with our wedding.
Once we're married,
everything will be in its proper place,
and I'll feel secure.
But who am I?
Am I only your betrothed?
That's it?
♪But I only see a lone rider galloping away♪
Yao,
your past
was too painful.
Those unhappy memories
are better left forgotten.
♪Thousands of thoughts, don't ask♪
You only need to remember
that from now on,
we are each other's only one.
♪The silver lamp extinguished,
candle smoke blows away with the wind,♪
♪dispelling the hatred♪
With me here,
♪Dreaming of the morning,
waking up to deep love♪
♪Red lips stained with vermilion♪
you have nothing to fear.
♪A farewell letter is difficult to write,
eternal longing♪
♪The heart grows cold, losing direction,
for whom does it fall?♪
♪Still waiting,
unrequited love dies on a lonely pillow♪
♪Vermilion stains red lips♪
♪Only sorrow remains, no smile can be seen♪
♪Through the night, a few rounds of warm wine♪
Yao, look.
This pear tree,
I planted it myself for you long ago.
It's in full bloom now.
I like this pear tree.
It smells so nice.
Like home.
Because this is our home.
Soon,
I'll use its blossoms
to make pear flower candy.
In the past, during our leisure time,
we would sit here
playing chess and drinking tea.
You would cook soup for me,
and I would tell you stories from books.
Then
I'll continue making soup for you.
And
I'll slowly tell you all about our past,
so you can remember everything.
Yao,
it's so good to have you.
By the way,
you've just recovered,
and you need to be more cautious.
Stay in the mansion today
and prepare for the wedding.
Just don't go out.
You can send the servants
to buy whatever you need.
I can't imagine
what I'd do
if anything happened to you again.
Alright.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
are you alright?
So this is the suffering
of the Poison Mandarin Ducks.
(Doesn't matter)
(Sharing feelings with Yao)
(This pain is nothing)
Your Highness,
why put yourself through this?
Your marriage
with Princess Zhao Li is imminent.
The Empress, who has been under house arrest,
has returned from the temple
to oversee the wedding.
All eyes are on your every move.
And here you are,
not only avoiding the preparations
for your marriage to Princess Zhao Li,
but also hiding someone here.
If the Empress found out
that Gu Junyao is in the Eastern Palace,
it would be difficult to manage the situation.
The Eastern Palace is now
filled with the Dark Blades.
No one will know that Yao is here,
and no one can take her away.
But Your Highness,
your marriage with Princess Zhao Li…
Or do you want both?
Zhao Li's situation requires the right timing.
For now,
nothing can interfere with my time with Yao.
♪In the mire of deceit♪
♪Lies trap our fate♪
♪Love and hate entwined♪
♪Shattered by your sword, the knot unbinds♪
♪Pear blossoms fall, leaving a tale of pain♪
♪Thoughts grow stronger, like a hidden flame♪
♪If all memories were to fade♪
♪But longing remains♪
♪Let's bind our hearts together♪
♪Even in pain, let me draw near♪
♪Can this fleeting sweetness linger♪
♪Just a bit longer?♪
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
(All rights reserved)
(by Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Company Limited)