♪See how the clouds drift♪
♪Chasing after the glow of the setting sun♪
♪But they end up lost♪
♪In the dark of the night♪
♪Had I never touched♪
♪The moon's reflection in the water♪
♪Never shattered♪
♪That beautiful lie♪
♪Perhaps I'd never have understood♪
♪That despair is but an illusion♪
♪Love is like a blade♪
♪The thinner, the sharper♪
♪The wound I made♪
♪Just inches from my heart♪
♪Yet still, it couldn't♪
♪Stop my longing♪
=Love & Bid Farewell=
=Episode 11=
(Defender Duke's Mansion)
Lady,
a letter from the Crown Prince for you.
Meet me at Wangxian Tower
at nine tonight.
It seems the Crown Prince
has genuine feelings for you.
Quickly, help me get ready.
Yes, my lady.
Dad.
Nice toys.
I…
Princess?
What is it, Your Highness?
Didn't you write to me
to meet me here tonight?
(All I can do)
(is help you achieve your goal)
(and take the throne.)
♪In the mire of deceit♪
♪Lies trap our fate♪
♪Love and hate entwined♪
♪Shattered by your sword, the knot unbinds♪
Your Highness.
♪Thoughts grow stronger, like a hidden flame♪
♪If all memories were to fade♪
♪But longing remains♪
♪Let's bind our hearts together♪
♪Even in pain, let me draw near♪
Let go of me, Your Highness.
You pushed Zhao Li and me together,
yet here you are, drinking alone.
I know you have feelings for me.
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
Let go, Your Highness.
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
Since you address me that way,
it indicates
that you are my subordinate.
You should be obligated
to follow my commands.
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
Yes, Your Highness.
I command you
to stay.
Turn around.
♪Falling into the abyss♪
♪Fates entwine♪
♪Weaving a tale of parting♪
♪The candle flickers as I fall again♪
You said we got caught up in the moment
on the cliff
and should not be taken seriously.
Would you dare to try it again?
♪Dreams unfulfilled, forever out of reach♪
Are you afraid?
♪Even in pain, let me draw near♪
♪Can this fleeting sweetness linger♪
♪Just a bit longer?♪
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
♪Your blade is stained with the blood♪
♪Piercing through all dreams♪
♪You are the obsession I can't let go♪
♪An unsolvable puzzle in this life♪
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
(Yao,)
(even if you can fool others,)
(can you fool yourself?)
Lady.
Lady Zhao doesn't seem naive.
What exactly is the prince planning?
Chief Gu,
may I have a word?
Your Highness, the Duke
is known for being decisive.
He wouldn't kill her in a fit of anger,
would he?
Silence.
General,
Chief Gu has been taken by the Duke.
What?
My father took her away?
(Defender Duke's Mansion)
It is a blessing to be able
to meet the daughter of an old friend
and play chess together today.
But I wonder,
am I playing
against the little girl I once knew
or the palace official she has become?
I serve my ruler faithfully.
It's been years since we last met,
so we're just old acquaintances now.
Duke,
please speak plainly.
Very well.
I'll be straightforward.
As the daughter of an old friend,
I should look after you.
But as a father, I'm worried.
I've heard rumors
about you
and the Seventh Prince.
My daughter Zhao Li
is soon to marry him.
So,
as her father,
I shall resolve all unpleasant matters
before she takes her place
in the Eastern Palace.
Junyao,
for my daughter's sake,
drink this
and leave the Seventh Prince.
I understand your concern.
Duke,
I'm the Chief Steward
at the Seventh Prince's palace.
Whether I stay or leave
is his decision.
Are you
rejecting my offer?
I appreciate it, Duke.
But I can't handle ﻿alcohol
and must respectfully refuse.
You dare refuse my offer?
I shall end you with my own hands.
Chief Gu,
I'm giving you one last chance.
Don't force me to be ruthless.
Father!
Zhao Ming,
- what are you doing?
- Father,
you're trying to kill an innocent person
just to secure my sister's marriage.
Isn't that too extreme?
Move aside.
I can't.
I said move!
You ungrateful son.
Zhao Ming, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Yao,
are you all right?
Well,
how are you feeling?
I'm all right.
If that's the case,
it's getting late now.
General, you should head back and rest.
Your Highness,
I wish to stay a little longer.
I'd like to talk to her.
General, you're an outsider.
It would be inappropriate for you
to talk privately with my official.
Please, Your Highness.
Allow us to speak privately.
Fine.
I shall leave you to your reunion.
Yao, you finally admit your identity.
Zhao Ming, I…
Yao,
I'm so glad.
The Gu's injustice has been cleared.
Yao,
I may not have been much help,
but I'm truly happy for you.
Now, you can finally
live as your true self.
♪In the mire of deceit♪
♪Lies trap our fate♪
♪Love and hate entwined♪
♪Shattered by your sword, the knot unbinds♪
♪Pear blossoms fall, leaving a tale of pain♪
♪Thoughts grow stronger, like a hidden flame♪
♪If all memories were to fade♪
♪But longing remains♪
♪Let's bind our hearts together♪
♪Even in pain, let me draw near♪
♪Can this fleeting sweetness linger♪
♪Just a bit longer?♪
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
(All rights reserved)
(by Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Company Limited)