♪See how the clouds drift♪
♪Chasing after the glow of the setting sun♪
♪But they end up lost♪
♪In the dark of the night♪
♪Had I never touched♪
♪The moon's reflection in the water♪
♪Never shattered♪
♪That beautiful lie♪
♪Perhaps I'd never have understood♪
♪That despair is but an illusion♪
♪Love is like a blade♪
♪The thinner, the sharper♪
♪The wound I made♪
♪Just inches from my heart♪
♪Yet still, it couldn't♪
♪Stop my longing♪
=Love & Bid Farewell=
=Episode 22=
Your Highness.
How is she?
Your Highness!
What time is it now?
In reply,
it's already the afternoon.
Afternoon?
(It's already afternoon?)
(Have I really slept
through an entire day and night?)
You shouldn't get up.
The physician repeatedly warned us
that your body is weak right now,
And you need to rest.
It's best if you don't leave the bed.
The child...
Please accept my condolences, Miss.
Gone...
It's good that it's gone.
I'm free.
I'm completely free now.
Miss,
please don't be like this.
The physician warned us
that you shouldn't get too emotional right now.
If you do,
it could
cause long-term health issues.
Long-term health issues...
For someone like me,
it would be better to die than to live.
Your Highness.
Leave us.
Yes.
- Yao.
- Get out!
I came to ask you,
what exactly happened?
What happened?
You came to ask me what happened?
Fine,
let me tell you.
Zhao Li is dead too.
Zhao Li's death was an accident.
What you need to do now
is take care of yourself.
Take care of myself?
Zhao Li, Zhao Ming-
What did they do wrong?
How innocent they were!
Just because they were close to me,
you wouldn't spare a single one of them.
One by one,
everyone around me is gone.
All because of you!
Yue Jinchen!
You're nothing but a bloodthirsty demon.
Yes,
a demon like you
doesn't deserve to have children.
Let me tell you!
We don't deserve
to have children in this life.
So you deliberately
killed our child, didn't you?
What if I did?
Yao,
weren't we supposed
to live out this life together?
♪See how the clouds drift♪
Get out!
Oh, right.
You've always despised me,
♪But they end up lost♪
even refusing to have my child.
♪Had I never touched♪
Everyone else can make you sad,
♪Never shattered♪
but not me.
Why is your heart so cold?
♪That despair is but an illusion♪
♪Love is like a blade♪
♪The thinner, the sharper♪
So salty.
Even someone as heartless as you
can shed tears
that are salty.
You look
so pitiful
and fragile.
But I don't feel anything anymore.
♪The wounds of love pierce deep into the heart♪
Your tears,
your weakness,
your delicate, and fragile appearance-
It's all just a facade.
The real you
is heartless, ruthless, selfish,
and you never loved me.
♪See how the clouds drift♪
I was a fool to believe you once.
I won't indulge you anymore,
♪In the dark of the night♪
nor will I soften my heart.
♪Never shattered♪
♪That beautiful lie♪
From now on,
I'll take good care of you.
If you have the guts, just kill me.
After all, I'm the one
carrying the weight of all their deaths.
♪The wound I made♪
♪Just inches from my heart♪
♪Yet still, it couldn't♪
♪Stop my longing♪
♪How to forget what once was♪
♪The wounds of love pierce deep into the heart♪
It smells nice...
Like home.
Because this is our home.
In two days,
it will be the day
of Princess Zhao Li's funeral, right?
That's right.
She must want to go.
She was like a sister to Zhao Li.
She would want to say a final goodbye.
Forgive me
for speaking out of turn, Your Highness.
Gu Junyao clearly
harbors ill intentions towards you.
She's tried to kill you multiple times,
and even though she was carrying your child,
she cruelly chose to end its life.
It's clear she's ruthless
and will stop at nothing.
Keeping her around
is like nurturing a tiger
that will turn on you.
Shiba,
you're getting bolder.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
But these words
have been stuck in my throat.
Even if it costs me my life,
I had to say them!
Stand up.
Your Highness...
I said, stand up.
If you're going to bare your heart,
you must be ready to be stabbed.
If I hadn't said what I did that day,
she wouldn't have survived.
Sometimes I want to ask you,
how can I win back Yao's heart?
But what would you know about that?
I'm just at my wit's end,
trying anything out of desperation.
Sister Cuiju,
have you been taking care
of that lady in the main hall again?
Yes,
our Crown Prince
treats her so well,
hiding her here
and having you watch over her
day and night.
I've heard His Highness's fiancée is gone.
With how much His Highness favors that lady,
he might make her the Crown Princess.
If that happens,
you'll be the greatest hero among us.
We'll all rely on you then.
Crown Princess?
That's just wishful thinking.
You're so naive.
What do you mean?
Sure, the Crown Prince favors her now,
but he keeps her locked away
in the Eastern Palace,
never letting her step outside.
Who knows
there's even such a favored lady?
It's clear that her status can't be told.
The Crown Prince keeps her
like a caged bird,
something to toy with, nothing more.
If she dreams of becoming Crown Princess,
that's absolutely impossible.
Your Highness!
- Your Highness!
Are you Cuiju?
Yes, Your Highness.
You've been in the palace for years.
Do you know the punishment
for gossiping about your superiors?
I know my mistake!
Please forgive me, Your Highness!
Shiba,
take her away
and give her fifty lashes.
Yes.
I know my mistake!
Please forgive me!
Your Highness, have mercy!
Your Highness!
They were right.
I should give Yao a proper status.
Your Highness.
Please have mercy on me.
Please stop crying.
What's wrong?
Where's Cuiju?
Cuiju neglected her duties yesterday,
so she was given fifty lashes
and expelled from the Eastern Palace.
She won't be taking care of you anymore.
If anything happens to you today,
I'm afraid I'll be the next
to get fifty lashes.
(Yue Jinchen...)
(You're so two-faced.)
(This is your true nature.)
(I should have known.)
Miss.
Alright,
I won't cry anymore.
(Praying that I can repay
what I owe Zhao Ming in the next life.)
(Guilty friend Gu Junyao in tears.)
Now that I'm trapped in this Eastern Palace,
I might never leave.
But these things,
they don't belong here.
If I burn them here,
they won't carry my thoughts
to those I've lost.
So I want to ask you,
please take them outside the palace,
find a quiet place and burn them,
as a final tribute to my lost friends.
Miss, I...
I know it's a lot to ask.
But I have nothing else to offer.
This is all I have left.
Can you help me?
Miss, you ask too much.
Your Highness.
I heard Yao is willing to eat now.
Yao really listens.
If I didn't eat,
you'd take it out
on the people around me again.
If this goes on,
I'll be carrying the weight of all these lives.
What do you mean?
You know exactly what I mean, so why ask?
I really don't understand.
Fine.
If you really don't understand,
let me remind you.
Where is Cuiju?
So that's what this is about.
Cuiju spoke ill of you,
so I gave her a minor punishment.
Enough!
I'm sick of this.
I can't bear it anymore.
I know you're now the Crown Prince,
you hold all the power,
and no one dares defy you.
But I'm asking you,
please don't use me as an excuse
to hurt others.
I've had enough of this guilt.
(Praying that I can repay
what I owe Zhao Ming in the next life.)
(Guilty friend Gu Junyao in tears.)
You just can't forget him, can you?
I just can't.
♪My heart is like a city♪
(I can feel your resolve, Yao.)
(You're serious.)
(You'll never forgive me.)
(I thought there was still a chance for us.)
(But I was wrong.)
(You're Yao.)
(Yao...)
(I will hold on with you.)
(We...)
(Will fight to the bitter end.)
♪Our paths diverge♪
♪Lamp extinguished, candle smoke blows away
with the wind, dispelling the hatred♪
♪Dreaming of the morning,
waking up to deep love♪
♪Red lips stained with vermilion♪
♪How to keep a touch of warmth?♪
♪A farewell letter is difficult to write,
eternal longing♪
♪The heart grows cold, losing direction,
for whom does it fall?♪
♪Still waiting, unrequited love dies
on a lonely pillow♪
♪Vermilion stains red lips♪
♪Only sorrow remains, no smile can be seen♪
♪Through the night, a few rounds of warm wine♪
♪Love is two people♪
♪Falling into the mortal world♪
♪Thousands of thoughts, don't ask♪
♪Parting ways, our paths diverge♪
♪Lamp extinguished, candle smoke blows away
with the wind, dispelling the hatred♪
(All rights reserved)
(by Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Company Limited)