♪See how the clouds drift♪
♪Chasing after the glow of the setting sun♪
♪But they end up lost♪
♪In the dark of the night♪
♪Had I never touched♪
♪The moon's reflection in the water♪
♪Never shattered♪
♪That beautiful lie♪
♪Perhaps I'd never have understood♪
♪That despair is but an illusion♪
♪Love is like a blade♪
♪The thinner, the sharper♪
♪The wound I made♪
♪Just inches from my heart♪
♪Yet still, it couldn't♪
♪Stop my longing♪
=Love & Bid Farewell=
=Episode 17=
Yao,
do you like what I prepared?
I like anything you prepare.
Is it beautiful?
It's very beautiful.
Yao,
I have to attend court in a bit.
I'll bring you a gift when I return.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Alright.
You're back.
When we used to go to the temple fairs,
I promised to give you a lantern.
I made it myself.
Do you like it?
It's so cute.
♪In the mire of deceit♪
♪Lies trap our fate♪
♪Love and hate entwined♪
Do you like it?
I like it!
Chen, your wedding robe
will be ready soon.
Let me take your measurements.
Looks like I'll soon be wearing a robe
that Yao made with her own hands.
I've never made clothes for you before?
The wedding robe will be the first.
You always know how to tease me!
The measuring tools are in the study.
I'll go get them.
Let's talk in the study, then.
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
Wait for me a moment.
♪Rain slips through my fingers♪
♪Falling into the abyss♪
♪Fates entwine♪
♪Weaving a tale of parting♪
♪The candle flickers as I fall again♪
♪Gently holding your face closer♪
Yao,
this all feels too good to be true,
like a dream.
But Chen,
if it's a dream,
we must eventually wake up.
♪Even in pain, let me draw near♪
♪Can this fleeting sweetness linger♪
♪Just a bit longer?♪
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
Yao, promise me
that you'll stay by my side forever,
okay?
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
We're about to get married.
Of course, I'll always be with you.
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
Your Highness,
your heart pains
are becoming more frequent.
Could she be remembering something?
As long as Yao
stays by my side like this,
that's all I need.
(The Eastern Palace)
I'm Princess Zhao Li's personal maid,
sent by Her Excellency
to invite the Crown Prince
to discuss the wedding.
How dare you stop me!
By order of His Highness,
no one is allowed in or out
of the Eastern Palace.
Please return.
Step aside!
Miss, let's go.
Chen.
Yao.
Why are you here?
Chen, you gave me a lantern,
so I made you a sachet
in return.
It smells so nice.
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
Since Yao gave it to me,
I'll wear it every day from now on.
Then let me put it on for you.
Alright.
Chen,
the weather has been so nice
these past few days.
I'd like to go out for a walk,
and maybe visit the market.
Is that alright?
Yao, be good.
Our wedding is approaching,
and those who've hurt you
are surely watching from the shadows.
The Eastern Palace
is the safest place right now.
After we're married,
I'll take you out
to ride horses and admire flowers.
Okay?
Your Highness!
Your Highness,
I know you're still upset with me,
But today, the Empress sent someone
to take our measurements for the wedding robes.
You must be present.
I'm sorry, Your Excellency.
I'm swamped with official duties today.
After court, I have
more important matters to attend to.
I must trouble you and my mother
to handle the wedding preparations.
But...
Isn't this our wedding?
Your Highness!
Your Excellency.
You said
the Eastern Palace
is also preparing for a wedding?
Yes, Your Excellency.
The people we sent
couldn't get close to the Eastern Palace,
but they kept watching them.
It seems those in charge of purchases
bought many festive items.
There's something suspicious going on.
Since it's my wedding,
I must find a way to see for myself.
(The Eastern Palace)
- Raise it a little higher over here.
- Alright.
Keep an eye on it.
I'll take this inside.
(Joy)
Is there something you need?
What is it?
Gu Junyao, what do you think I need?
Do you know me?
Do I know you?
Gu Junyao, do you know what you're talking?
No,
I haven't recognized you.
I thought you and my brother
were childhood sweethearts,
that you had feelings for him.
He was willing to sacrifice
the entire Defender Duke's Mansion for you.
But you?
You're here,
preparing for a wedding
with Yue Jinchen.
He's my fiancé!
And we, My brother and I,
are nothing but fools.
Zhao Ming...
You don't remember anything?
Chen said
I was injured by villains
and lost my memory.
Lost your memory?
Then,
do you remember the Gu family?
Gu Xunan,
your father?
You were just a pawn to him.
And your entire Gu family
was nothing more than a stepping stone
for Yue Jinchen to become Crown Prince.
The one who orchestrated all of this
is Yue Jinchen.
Your Highness!
Sister Yao!
Yue Jinchen,
you've deceived me so cruelly!
Miss! Miss! What's wrong?
- Zhao Li, leave now!
- Hurry, hurry!
- Miss!
- Get out of here, hurry!
Hurry, hurry!
- Miss!
- Miss,
- are you alright?
- Are you alright, Miss?
- What happened?
- What's going on?
- Miss.
- Are you alright, Miss?
Call the Imperial Physician!
(The Eastern Palace)
Your Highness.
Where is Yao?
I deserve to die.
Princess Zhao Li
disguised herself and got in.
She spoke a few words to the lady,
and the lady fainted.
The physician has already seen her.
She's not in serious condition,
just resting early.
Yao.
Chen,
I had a dream.
In the dream, you deceived me.
Everything was fake.
You and I were actually mortal enemies.
Dreams are always the opposite.
Yao is the one I care about most
in this life.
Even if I betray the entire world,
I will never betray you.
But every time I wake up,
my heart feels so uneasy.
You really won't lie to me, right?
If you lie to me,
I'll never forgive you in this lifetime.
♪In the mire of deceit♪
♪Lies trap our fate♪
♪Love and hate entwined♪
♪Shattered by your sword, the knot unbinds♪
♪Pear blossoms fall, leaving a tale of pain♪
♪Thoughts grow stronger, like a hidden flame♪
♪If all memories were to fade♪
♪But longing remains♪
♪Let's bind our hearts together♪
♪Even in pain, let me draw near♪
♪Can this fleeting sweetness linger♪
♪Just a bit longer?♪
♪Cast our dreams into the fire's embrace♪
♪Let them end with a final grace♪
♪Burn away my memories of snow♪
♪And the deceit♪
♪Let me cherish one last look♪
♪In your gentle gaze♪
♪Our last kiss is so tender♪
♪In the next life, may we never meet♪
(All rights reserved)
(by Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Company Limited)