Sometimes we wake with anxiety.
An edgy energy.
What will happen today?
What is in store for me?
So many questions.
We want resolution,
solid earth under our feet.
So, we take life
into our own hands.
We take action, yeah?
Our solutions are temporary.
They are quick fix.
They create more anxiety,
more suffering.
There is no resolution
to life's questions.
It is easier to be patient
once we finally accept
there is no resolution.
No, it's right here.
Yeah.
Three minutes!
Dead! Carotid artery!
- Dead! Chest cavity!
- Frank!
- Have you heard of the black mamba?
You heard of the black-- Hey, man!
What are you doing?
You want-- Hey, look, I'm just
showing off my moves, man.
- What are you doing?
- I gotta go.
We didn't even get into the ice yet.
I gotta catch a plane.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
- Wait.
- Ah, come on.
Hey, man, you gonna make me
chase you over here?
Come on.
Wait. Listen.
Come on, man, what's happening?
Where you going?
You know what's happening, you know?
I gotta go.
I gotta go, man.
I told you, I have to go.
- You gotta go?
- Yeah.
We got-- But the ladies
are here, man.
What's the matter?
Stay, okay? I need you to--
Don't you like me anymore?
- I just have to go. I have to go.
- You're my guy.
- Look.
- And you started it.
- I can't finish it without you.
- You finish it.
- Sawatdee kha!
- That's not part of the deal.
- Hey, there they are.
- Hi!
- Look at this. Ladies. Come on.
- Come on, come on!
- He's saying no. Rick! Rick!
- Rick!
- Rick! Rick!
Hi.
Oh, morning.
How'd you sleep?
I slept okay.
Have you seen Laurie?
Not yet.
Should we see if she wants
to get some breakfast?
Yeah, I'll go ask her.
No. I'll do it.
Kate and I
are gonna go get breakfast.
You wanna come?
No. I think I'm gonna
keep sleeping, if that's okay.
Listen, I'm sorry about Valentin.
Honestly, I had no idea
you'd even care.
Jac, please. I...
I want to be your friend.
We can talk about it later
when you're not sleeping.
You want us
to bring you back something?
No, thanks.
Okay.
I think I should wait
till we're home,
you know, before I tell Mom. Like...
maybe wait
till she's back on her meds.
Tell Mom what?
That I'm coming with you.
What?
Lochlan, I don't want
to be responsible
for fucking up your life, okay?
Just let me fuck up
my own life, all right?
They're back!
Hello! Hi!
How was it?
How did it go?
It was, uh...
You know what, can we actually
talk about it later?
I just... I want to shower and...
Yeah, we'll talk about it
at breakfast.
Okay.
Lochlan?
What?
Tell us.
I don't fucking know anything, okay?
Belinda.
Hey!
- Sawatdee khrap.
- Sawatdee kha.
This is my son, Zion.
- Sawatdee khrap, Zion.
- Sawatdee khrap.
Yeah. Yeah. We met, Mom.
Right. Oh, that's right.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yes. Yes, yes.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Um. Do you want to join us?
It's okay. I just saw you
and just wanted to say... hello.
Hello.
- Bye.
- Shut up.
- Wow! You like this guy.
I don't know.
Well, he likes you.
You know, he wants to go
into business together.
Really?
What? The spa
you always talked about.
Where would we even do it, right?
Wherever you want. Hawaii. Here?
He ain't got no money,
and neither do I.
I don't even know
where I would get it.
I don't know investors like that.
Hello? Do I have to say it?
- Z.
- What?
I already told you.
I'm not taking
that blood money, okay?
Mom...
Listen, 100,000 dollars
isn't enough anyway.
We would need more than that,
so drop it.
What if it were a million dollars?
- But it's not.
- Okay, no, you told him
you would get back to him.
Why don't you just see
- how much you can get?
- Z.
You don't have to go through with it.
Just see.
See how much you can get.
I mean, you're always gonna wonder.
If I go up there
and negotiate with him,
then I don't do it?
It'll piss him off,
and then he'll fuck me up.
No, no. He won't do anything to you.
He's done it before.
'Cause I'll be there.
I mean, plus,
you'll need a professional
to help you negotiate
this deal anyway, so...
So, you liked it, the center?
Yeah, it's a really cool place.
Great.
Yeah. It's not a cult.
Well, I think it's great
that you've proved to yourself
that you can live
a simple life like that.
We'd all be fine
with a lot less, right?
Yeah.
What?
Like, the food.
I mean, it was vegetarian, but it...
You know, you could tell it,
like, wasn't organic, and...
it was just kind of bland and...
I don't know, it was kind of like,
"Could I, like, really eat this
for a whole year?"
And then-- Oh my God.
And then I went back to my room
and it was this, like,
tiny little box with, like,
a mattress with stains on it
and no air conditioning, and...
I know... I know...
I know I'm not supposed
to be attached
to this kind of stuff,
and I don't want to think
that I am, but, like...
I don't know, I think I am.
I know I am.
Like, the idea that I'm, like...
that I'm, like, this princess
who needs things to be a certain way,
it's just so pathetic.
It's not pathetic.
No, Mom, it is. It is pathetic.
And, like...
I don't know, like, I guess
I am spoiled, 'cause, like...
'cause, like, I can't live like that.
Oh, sweetie.
You don't have to prove anything.
There's so much suffering
in the world,
and we have it so easy,
and, like,
other people have it so hard,
and I just--
I feel like it's really unfair.
And I just feel really bad.
We're lucky. It's true.
No one in the history of the world
has lived better than we have.
Even the old kings and queens.
The least we can do is enjoy it.
If we don't, it's offensive.
It's an offense
to all the billions of people
who can only dream
that one day they could live
like we do.
- Yeah.
- Oh, baby, come here.
I'm really sorry
- I brought you guys here.
- Oh, baby. Oh, baby.
I love you so much.
- Hey.
If you made one of your shakes,
I'd drink it.
Nah, I already had one earlier.
Stuff's on the counter
if you want to make one, though.
No one's gonna make you a man.
Okay? You gotta do it yourself.
All right, I'll see you later.
Where are you going?
Just down to the beach.
You want me to come?
I'm just gonna go read
for a little bit.
All right, see ya.
Are you mad or something?
Okay. Look, Loch,
it's okay for you
to, like, worship me,
but don't like...
"worship" me.
You know what I mean?
Look, all you care about
is getting off, and...
I saw you lying there
and I thought you looked
a little left out,
and I'm, you know, a pleaser.
I just wanna give everyone
what they want,
and I'm in a family
full of narcissists--
Okay, dude.
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Let's just drop this,
like, forever, please.
Okay?
I don't know how to do this.
Come on, let's do it.
- Okay.
- Ready?
How are you, my friend?
Did you like the fights?
I looked for you after.
I was on a date.
And you were busy with two men?
They your friends?
Maybe some guys I know
from the gym?
What their names?
Why do you want to know
their names?
I think I've seen them before.
I don't know.
Some good fights, though, huh?
I'll see you soon.
Hey.
You brought my book.
Yep.
Read it. It'll change your life.
I'm almost finished.
You've read
the whole thing already?
I went to Duke.
Okay, genius. What do you think?
Yeah, I mean,
I thought that the sex stuff
was pretty interesting.
You should read the other ones
I gave you as well.
She's amazing.
They're not about sex,
but the laws of the universe,
how we're all connected.
She has this theory
that there are different groups,
and we're in these groups
with people we know
and people we don't know.
And these groups are working together
to fulfill this divine plan.
And sometimes you don't even know
you're in the same group
as someone else.
So, you and I,
we could be in the same group
and not even know it.
- Hi!
- Hi.
Hey. Hey.
How did it go?
Well, I didn't kill anyone.
- Oh, that's good.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I said what I had to say.
Got the monkey off my back.
I missed you.
Yeah.
Hey.
Sorry I couldn't help you out
last night.
It's fine. I'll find someone else.
It won't be hard.
Well, if it makes you happy,
get 'em.
You know what you should get?
Highlights. Just right here...
- Hey, Dad.
- Oh, hi.
Hey, Lochy.
Yeah?
Do you think you could live
with no money?
I mean, no money,
no house, nothing.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I could.
Yeah. I think you could.
Hey, uh, it's your last day.
Don't just sit in here.
Go do something.
All right? Go swim or...
Go.
All right.
- Later, Dad.
- Yeah.
I know you know.
Please don't say anything.
If you do, I'm dead.
They will deport me.
I go back to my country, I'm dead.
My friends, all of us, are dead.
They can't work. They have no way
to make money here.
If you say something,
you're killing me.
- You're killing me--
- Valentin.
Um. Not sure if you've heard,
but the Hollingers
are coming back
tomorrow morning.
They are hoping to say hello
to Ms. Lemon
and take a photo with her
before she leaves.
I'll let them know.
Can you find out
if she's okay with a photo?
We might post it
on the hotel's website.
It's very important to Khun Sritala.
- Ah! Sawatdee kha!
- Fuck.
- Good morning. Um...
- Hey.
I was just gonna put these
on the table.
They're your phones and things.
- Saxon asked for his back.
- No, don't.
- Don't do that, please.
- So I just-- No?
Yeah, we don't want them.
- We don't need them.
- Okay.
Are you enjoying having a break
from your phone?
Yeah.
Do you know what I could do?
I could put these
on the hotel boat that takes you
to the airport tomorrow,
and that way you can detox
till the very last minute.
- Yeah, sure. Let's do that.
- Okay.
Yeah. Pam, uh, when we got here,
you said something
about this fruit.
Remind me what you said
about it.
Uh, yes. Uh, the seeds
of the fruit are poison.
- Oh, right. Yeah.
- Yeah, the locals
actually call it
the suicide tree
because people grind up
the seeds and eat them
when they want
to kill themselves, so...
Don't eat it.
I don't think you'd want to anyway.
It doesn't taste very nice.
Have a wonderful last day.
Thanks.
Sawatdee kha.
Can I get you any drinks?
- No, we're okay--
- Uh, two whiskeys.
- Rocks, please.
- Certainly, sir.
Yeah. Thank you.
Trust me. We're gonna need it.
Mom, you know how you always say
you always gotta be prepared
because you never know
when you're gonna get your moment?
This could be it, Mom.
Don't miss your moment.
- He killed the bitch.
- I know.
Look, maybe this
is the one good thing
that's meant
to come out of all of it.
I mean, think about it.
This place is killer, man.
You're, uh... You are balling.
Thank you.
I thought we'd be talking privately.
Sorry. Zion.
Yeah.
Uh. I'm her only son.
We're a team.
It's just how it's always been.
But don't trip.
You know, cone of silence.
Uh, business major, U of H.
I don't care about what you did,
what you're gonna do.
All I care about is business
and the bottom line.
MBA, baby. Hey.
My mom brought me up to speed
on your initial offer.
Unfortunately,
it's gonna be a pass.
Oh, is that right?
She's just caught up
in the ethics of it all.
She just doesn't think the guilt
and the emotional stress
would be worth it, so...
And she wants to focus
on starting her own business,
'cause that's her dream.
That was the point of the money.
Yeah, but... that amount of money
isn't gonna get it done,
you know?
I mean, for her to take on
this kind of risk with you,
you know, she would need to feel
like her dream is coming true,
like, full on.
I mean, you got your dream here.
She's gotta get hers, right?
I mean, what happens
to a dream deferred?
You know? Does it dry up
like a raisin in the sun?
Hers has been deferred
a long time.
Might explode.
My point is...
is there enough money here
for everyone to get
their happy ending?
I think so.
So, how much would it take
for her to get her happy ending?
Well, we crunched
the numbers, Greg,
and if we're being realistic,
all in, soup to nuts...
five million.
That's not happening.
Look, I know that's a big ask,
but I did do a little research,
and according to the internet,
your wife...
late wife-- ex-wife...
uh, former wife,
rest in peace, was worth
at least half a billion dollars.
Don't believe everything
you read.
Oh, I know.
I found some very public records
where that number
pretty much checks out.
So what we're asking for
is a mere one percent
of your total haul.
We get that,
and we are ride or die
till the day we die.
We are Team Gary.
I mean, peace of mind
is worth one percent.
Don't you think?
I mean, and you won't miss it.
I mean, what? You're gonna...
You're gonna spend
through all 500 mil here?
Come on, man, how many years
you got left anyway? Right?
I'm not doing this.
He's not giving us any money,
and this is a waste of time.
Okay? Now let's go.
- Zion!
- Look, Mom,
why don't you just give
us businessmen a minute alone?
No. I mean it.
Hey! Hey! Hey, hey! What...
What are you doing?
I was just making my big pitch.
You go back in there
and you tell him your mother
takes things very personal.
She doesn't trust him, okay?
And if we don't make a deal
and we don't get the money,
who knows what I'll do?
Look at you playing hardball.
Yes, Mom!
Just tell him
that your mother's
a very honest lady, okay?
But he better come through.
He wants us to be scared,
but we gotta make him scared. Okay?
Now go close it.
Yeah.
Boys!
It's time to go to dinner!
Let's go!
Hey, uh, miss, excuse me.
Uh, it's our last night,
and I thought it might be, uh,
fun if we made cocktails
in the room later.
Um. Piña coladas?
Uh, if you could bring some rum
and mixers to the villa,
get them sent there.
- We have a blender.
- Yes, I'll let them know.
Great.
Piña coladas?
Yeah. It's our last night, so...
I've never had a piña colada.
Are they good?
You're not gonna have one
tonight either. You're not 21.
Sucks.
- Hi!
- Aw!
- Hi.
- You made it.
- Yeah.
- So pretty.
Aw.
I thought you were gonna miss
our last dinner.
I just had a late night.
How was it? Was it fun?
What'd you do?
I went to the fight thing,
which was whatever.
And then I went back
with Aleksei to his apartment.
Ah. Okay, Aleksei.
Ladies.
How was your last day?
- It was nice.
- Yeah.
- Relaxing.
I wanted to remind you
about your morning massages,
and tell you, um,
the owners are arriving tomorrow,
Khun Sritala and her husband,
and they were hoping
to take a photo with you.
- Would that be all right?
- Yeah, of course.
Yes, ladies, um,
enjoy your dinner.
Okay.
Too nervous to eat.
You were supposed to close it.
Well, he said he was gonna
think about it.
But I gave him your account number
and the routing number, and...
Look, he could wire
the money tonight.
There's a line
between positive thinking
and delusional.
You're crossing the line, babe.
Go big or go home, right?
In a goddamn body bag.
Okay, that's enough.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- What do you think I'm doing?
I'm checking my account
is what I'm doing.
- Over there getting my hopes up.
- All right.
You're free.
It's a new day.
Told you you have nothing
to worry about.
Of course I was worried.
I love you.
But you know,
I was never too worried.
Because amor fati.
Do you know what that means?
I don't know what that means.
It means you have to embrace
your fate, good or bad.
Whatever will be will be.
Yeah. And at this point,
we're linked,
so if a bad thing happens
to you, it happens to me.
I think we're gonna be
together forever, don't you?
That's the plan.
Is it?
Yeah.
I'm so glad we did this.
Me too.
Thank you for organizing, Jac,
and paying for the villa.
Are you sure we can't help pay?
No, no.
It was my total pleasure.
Um, well,
our pastor at our church
talks about how
there's a time in life
after years of, you know,
watering and weeding
and nurturing your soil,
and then one day,
you look around...
and your garden is in bloom.
And that's how I feel right now.
Everything is in bloom.
All our flowers are in bloom.
I've just been in the best mood
all week. I really have.
I mean,
I can do yoga and meditate
and whatever, but nothing,
you know, for me, makes me feel
more grounded than...
you know, being with friends,
real friends.
It's a lonely world.
It can be, you know?
People judge you
for your superficial defects.
You guys judge me
for my profound defects.
- No!
- You know what I mean.
- Yeah.
- And, uh,
I've just been
on cloud nine all week,
and I really needed it, so thank you.
That's funny,
'cause if I'm being honest,
all week, I've just been so sad.
What?
I just feel like my expectations
were too high, or...
I just feel like,
as you get older,
you have to justify your life,
you know?
And your choices. And...
when I'm with you guys,
it's just so, like...
like, transparent
what my choices were,
and my mistakes.
I have no belief system.
And I...
Well, I mean,
I've had a lot of them, but...
I mean, work was my religion
for forever,
but I definitely lost
my belief there.
And then--
And then I tried love,
and that was just a painful religion,
just made everything worse.
And then, even for me,
just, like, being a mother,
that didn't save me either.
But I had this epiphany today.
I don't need religion or God
to give my life meaning
because time gives it meaning.
We... We started this life together.
I mean, we're going through it apart,
but we're still together, and I...
I look at you guys,
and it feels meaningful.
And I can't explain it,
but even when we're just sitting
around the pool
talking about whatever inane shit,
it still feels very fucking deep.
I'm glad you have a beautiful face.
And I'm glad that you have
a beautiful life.
And I'm just happy
to be at the table.
I love you.
I can't even just have,
like, one glass?
You... You need to get a Coke.
Come on.
Okay. Lochy, come on.
- Yeah, I'm coming.
- Come on.
I couldn't ask for
a more perfect family.
We've had a perfect life,
haven't we?
No privations, no suffering,
no trauma.
And my job is
to keep all that from you,
to keep you safe.
'Cause I love you.
- I love you so much.
- We love you too.
- I do.
- Yeah.
- Love you, Dad.
- So...
- Love you too.
I'd like to make
a toast to Thailand.
And I just can't wait
to get back home.
But to Thailand, thank you.
- Yeah.
- "Kop ku ka."
Khop khun kha.
"Kam ku-- Kap-- Ka Bun Ka."
Okay.
Piña colada?
- Smells weird.
- No. It's... No. Mm.
It's strong. It's fine. It's fine.
Drink it, drink it.
It's good. Drink it.
No! No.
- Dad!
- Dude! Dude!
No, it's, uh... the...
- No, the coconut milk's off.
- What?
- Tim! Take a nap!
- The coconut milk's off!
- The coconut milk is off!
- Relax! Okay.
- Not good. No. No, no. No. No.
- Don't drink it. Here.
- It's all good.
- Come on!
- Come on.
Okay.
I'll see you...
I'll see you in the morning.
Is that it, Tim?
Have you ever heard of wine?
- What?
- There are several bottles
of wine in the cabinet
right behind you.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You know?
Lochlan,
why don't you get an opener
- and get some glasses out?
- Get some towels.
A few glasses of wine.
Who wants to try some chardonnay?
- Piper, can you get the glasses?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Holy shit, Ma.
- I called the bank. It's real.
- Are you kidding?
- And then Greg called...
- Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What did he say?
He said he gave it to Tanya
as much as he gave it to me.
It's what she would have wanted.
And he said he wanted
to make sure I lived up
to my end of the bargain.
And then what'd you say?
- I said that I would!
- Yes, Mom! Yes!
- Yes!
- Wait, wait, wait. I'm nervous.
But I just gotta wrap up
some things today,
and then we're gonna be outta here.
- Get outta where?
- Thailand!
I don't wanna be
down the road from him
when he changes his mind!
No, the money's already
in the bank, bruh!
But still!
I wanna be hard to find.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Um, um...
What about your man?
You two were gonna start
a business together?
Don't you wanna start
your own spa?
Can't I just be rich
for five fucking minutes?
Yes. Yes, you can.
- I can?
- Yes, you can.
- Yeah?
- Yes, we can! Yeah!
- Oh my God. Yeah.
- Okay, look, listen.
Why don't you go get ready, okay?
- All right.
- I booked a treatment for you,
stress management,
and you're gonna need it.
What? No, no, no, no, no!
I don't need that, Ma.
We're too blessed to be stressed!
Look, it's too late to cancel,
and if I'm paying,
you're going, so...
- Okay.
- ...go get ready.
Mom?
She's a Cancer Venus,
so it's very intense,
and he's an Aquarius Moon.
It's like, "Babe,
- it's never gonna happen."
- Right. No.
He's never gonna give you
what you need.
- He's gonna withhold forever.
- No. Hey.
Can we pick up this story
in just a second?
I'm still really hungry.
- Ooh, can you get me a donut?
- You got it. Donut.
Well, look who it is.
You come into my house,
lie to my wife.
Get the fuck outta here.
We're on the first boat.
I don't want anything to do with you.
I remember your mother.
Yeah.
I knew she was a drunk
and a slut.
Didn't know she was a liar too.
Wanted you to think your father
was some kind of great man.
She told you a fairy tale, kid.
Your father was no saint.
You didn't miss out on much.
And that's the fucking truth.
What?
You're gonna try to kill me now?
I don't think so.
- What is it?
- He's here.
- Who?
- Just insulted my fucking mother.
Forget about him. Okay?
You're free. Remember?
- You're over it.
- How can...
How can I get over
everything he's taken from me?
He took my whole fucking life.
Stop worrying about the love
you didn't get.
Think about the love you have.
I love you.
I'm right here.
I couldn't even get
a goddamn breakfast up there.
Are you all blind or what?
Please don't do something stupid.
I'm fine. I gotta go.
- You're really freaking me out.
- I'm just gonna go see my lady.
- What lady?
- The Indian lady.
It's...
I'm gonna be okay.
Shit.
Hey.
Yo.
- What book are you reading?
- What book?
The one in your hand.
I don't know. Here, it's like a...
- Morning.
- It's a book, whatever.
Okay.
I'm gonna let your father sleep.
He needs it. Okay, let's go.
Lochlan, sweetheart, breakfast!
Lochy, come on.
All right,
just meet us up there!
The treatment center room
is over there
- by the big Buddha--
- All right, Mom. Breathe.
Okay? We did that shit.
- Yeah.
- We did that shit!
Yeah, we did.
And you worked so hard, Ma.
Good things happen
to good people.
You're right. I love you.
I love you too.
Now, go on,
find your center or some shit.
Sawatdee kha!
Zion?
Yes, ma'am.
I will be sitting
with you this morning.
- Sawatdee kha.
- Sawatdee khrap.
Right this way.
- How are you?
- I'm very well, thank you.
How are you doing?
Hey. Hey.
Hi.
I will be right with you.
- Hey.
I really-- I need to talk to you.
- I have a session.
- This is urgent. Okay, please?
I just need
a few minutes of your time.
- I--
- I can meet you after.
- No, no.
- Look, just sit on this bench.
I'll have them bring you a key, and--
I need to talk to you now.
Please.
Look. You'll be all right. Okay?
I'll come find you.
I promise.
Just give me one hour.
One hour. Sorry.
I'll come find you.
Lochy?
Lochy!
Son! Wake up! Hey!
Wake up! Son! Son!
Come on, come on!
Come on! Come on now!
Come on! Help!
Come on, baby.
Come on. Help! Help! Somebody help!
How were the massages?
Oh, fantastic.
We had to sneak one last in
before we leave.
Thank you for agreeing
to a photo.
Khun Sritala.
Sawatdee kha.
May I introduce you
to my husband, Khun Jim?
- We love your show.
- Aw!
Well, we love your hotel!
We hope you had a nice stay.
Oh my gosh.
We had the best time.
Oh, Belinda.
- Sawatdee khrap.
- Sawatdee kha.
How are you today?
Good, yeah. Um. How are you?
I'm good, as usual.
Pornchai...
I've really loved getting
to know you.
But...
some things have changed
for me, and...
I'm gonna be
leaving Thailand tomorrow.
Leaving tomorrow?
What about...
starting a business?
You, me.
Maybe. But...
circumstances have changed
for me,
and I just can't commit
to anything right now.
I'm so sorry.
Uh. Would you mind very much
- if we took a picture together?
- No, of course!
- Great.
- Okay!
- Jim, you stay here.
- I'll go over here.
- Okay.
- Yes. Come, come. Come.
Beautiful!
Wow. Such beautiful ladies!
Okay, maybe one more. One more.
- Okay.
Maybe one with just...
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah?
Wow. Beautiful.
Khun Jim, in the camera.
Yeah. Thank you so much.
- Surprise!
- Cheese!
Oh, yeah. That's good!
That's good, Khun Jim. Yeah.
Rick?
Get outta here.
Why? What are you doing?
Get the fuck out of here.
Smile!
Oh my God!
Fuck you.
Jim!
- Pornchai!
- You okay? You okay?
Go, go, go! Go!
- Why?
- He killed my father.
He's your father.
He's your father! He told me.
He's your father!
Rick, what the fuck?
- Wait!
- Go, go, go, go!
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no! No, no.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, no.
Hey, you're okay, all right?
You're gonna be okay.
You hear me? You hear me?
You can't die on me, okay?
Chelsea.
No.
No. No!
Hey! Hey!
Help me, please!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
We're gonna be
together forever, okay?
Just like you said.
Hey! Stop!
Hey.
I think I just saw God.
Come on.
Oh, God.
Kids! Look what I have!
Hey, guys. Wait.
Things are about to change.
We'll get through it as a family.
'Cause we're...
we're a strong family, and... and...
you know, nothing's
more important than family,
right?