[English subtitles are available]
The daughter of the Shen family is willing to rest in the same tomb with His Highness Prince Jin.
She is now bestowed with a length of white silk fabric.
Stop!
Your Highness!
Ghost!
Your Highness.
[The Substitute Princess's Love]
[Episode 2]
Your Highness, I've checked Her Highness's pulse.
She's not the princess.
How is she?
Nothing serious. She should be fine after sleep.
Thank you.
-Sir.
Nan Bo and I just came back from Xigong Alley.
They learned that I came back
and destroyed all the evidence, did they?
They did.
When we went there,
the restaurant in Xigong Alley where the spy worked
was already empty.
We arrived late.
It's good.
I don't have to hide anymore.
Let's investigate it openly.
Your Highness, we have not
gained nothing.
The provisions that were transported to Zhenxi Pass
[Virtue and Benevolence]
were escorted by Li Bing,
the Minister of Revenue.
In that restaurant,
we found Li Bing's carriage.
He ran away too quickly.
We don't know where he is now.
There must be evidence on him
that can accuse the mastermind.
You must find him.
Yes.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
Even the underworld is so beautiful?
This is not the underworld. It's Prince Jin's mansion.
You...
Who are you?
I'm a maid of Madam Shen.
Her Ladyship asked me to take care of you.
What are you doing?
Your nanny is in the Prime Minister’s Mansion.
As long as you obey us, she will be fine.
You...
I have already married as a substitute as per your request.
What else do you want?
How dare you say that so loudly?
How many lives do you have?
If you don't let my nanny go,
I'll reveal the fact that I was a substitute bride.
I'll just die with you.
Even if you tell anyone,
the Prime Minister will only have to drink three cups as punishment.
By then,
you little liar will be beheaded on the street.
Why should you die if you can live?
As long as you do one thing for the Shen Mansion,
the Shen Mansion will release your nanny
and let her come here
to live a good life with you.
What is it?
This is the jade pendant His Highness carries with him.
If you can steal it,
[Night]
the Prime Minister will let your nanny go.
Is this valuable?
Are you trying to harm His Highness?
His Highness is a famous God of War.
It won't affect him if he loses a jade pendant.
Then why would you send me to do so?
You are his wife.
You'll have a chance to get close to him.
Miss Shen,
His Highness has arranged a carriage
for you to go back home.
If you are fine,
you can go home.
His Highness wants me to leave.
Maybe I should go back.
I can't really
stay here to be the princess.
Let someone else steal this jade pendant.
Nanny and I will leave quietly.
I promise we won't talk about this.
Listen.
There's no turning back for this matter.
Your nanny's life
is in your hands.
No matter what you do,
you must stay here.
Let me think about it.
Get out of the way!
Your Highness, this is Li Bing's carriage.
Li Bing.
Li Bing, who did this?
Your Highness.
It's not that I didn't want to send the provisions
to Zhenxi Pass,
but that whole batch of provisions
had long been embezzled by Prime Minister Shen.
I...
Am sorry to the thousands of soldiers in Zhenxi Pass.
Give me the evidence of Prime Minister Shen's embezzlement of provisions.
I will clear your name.
It's useless.
You've been out fighting for years.
I'm afraid you don't know
the power of Prime Minister Shen in the capital.
Li Bing.
Shen Yurong.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
After this war,
half of the soldiers died. He must feel pain as a general.
But the battlefield is cruel.
When young men go to war,
they must be determined to sacrifice themselves for the country.
Now that we've won the war,
it's their honor.
Prince Jin sacrificed himself for the country.
Your Majesty, I humbly request that you posthumously bestow an honorary title upon His Highness Prince Jin.
He is worthy of being enshrined in the ancestral temple.
Shen. You don't know yet, do you?
I have good news for you.
What is it?
The battle report is wrong.
Prince Jin didn't die.
He's back.
He will come to the court today.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
[Chaoqian Hall]
Brother.
Your Highness, we are colleagues in the court.
My daughter is married to you.
We are related by marriage.
Related by marriage?
Brother, stop!
Put down your sword!
I said put down the sword!
Your Majesty.
Sorry for disturbing you today.
You brought your sword to the palace, which is a disregard for royal law.
Do you still respect me?
I'm sorry. I'm willing to accept the punishment.
You may leave.
Did my wife send someone to Prince Jin's mansion?
Your Excellency. Don’t worry.
Her Ladyship sent Aunt Xin there early in the morning.
She will certainly convey every detail
to Princess Jin.
One mountain cannot accommodate two tigers.
The war at the front line is over.
But the war at the court has just begun.
Let go of me!
Miss Shen, His Highness is back.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
Your marriage may be rearranged.
Why don't you go back to Shen Mansion first?
Yes, you can go back first.
There must be a mistake.
I'll wait for His Highness here
and make it clear to him.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
Why are you still here?
[Night]
Your Highness, I'm sorry.
For what?
That day,
I shouldn't have hit your butt. I was wrong.
But you shouldn't hate me
and drive me away.
At worst,
I'll let you hit mine.
Where do you think you are?
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
This is where
we held our wedding ceremony.
I wasn't present that day. The wedding didn't count.
Why?
How can the prince's mansion not acknowledge things that happened?
Besides, I slept with you
in a shabby temple the night before.
Don't talk nonsense.
It's fine if you don't dare to admit it.
I'll pretend it never happened.
I won't mention it again.
Why can't I admit it?
I was injured that day. It was because I was injured.
You were indeed injured.
But you were quite strong when you forced me.
I asked her to get some water.
Just to get some water.
Yes, get some water.
Get some water.
Forget it.
Ask someone to send her back to the Prime Minister’s Mansion.
I don't want to see her anymore.
Yes.
No, Your Highness. I'm married to you.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
If you want to kick me out,
you might as well kill me.
Whatever.
Get some water.
Your Highness, wait for me.
Did she really go get water?
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
What else?
Nanny, the prince's mansion is so cold.
I'll bring you here once I finish my mission.
We'll have a home then.
Your Highness, it's spring now,
but it's still cold.
It's snowing heavily tonight.
I've made a charcoal fire for you.
It'll warm you up at night.
Steward Yi.
No need.
In the future, there's no need
to kindle a fire in my tent.
Your Highness.
That would freeze your body.
Although I'm back,
I feel like I'm still in Zhenxi Pass.
It was snowing day and night there
endlessly.
We lacked clothes and food.
Many of our fellows
never made it through the nights.
Your Highness, the war is over.
Don't...
Punish yourself anymore.
But they entrusted their lives to me.
I failed to protect them.
General.
Each of us in our battalion
took a piece of our own sword tassel
and asked the military doctor
to assemble them into a new one.
This battle will be dangerous.
If we can't come back,
please take this sword tassel back to the capital.
Consider it as returning to the court for us.
Report!
General.
The entire scouting camp died in Shanyin Valley.
We can definitely go back.
We'll return to the capital in triumph together.
By the way,
prepare a carriage for the girl from the Shen family at the door.
Send her back when she's ready.
Yes, Your Highness.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
Bodhisattva has shown his presence.
His Highness has returned safely.
This is...
Are you Miss Shen?
My name is Shen Keyi.
You are...
Prince Jin's legitimate wife?
What are you talking about?
This is His Highness's elder sister.
His Majesty granted her the title of Lady Yunying.
Miss Shen, you misunderstood.
A few days ago, the news of His Highness's death came.
I went to the Dazhao Temple to pray.
I came back as soon as I got the news today.
Your Ladyship, she is a member of the Shen family.
Why are you telling her so much?
Miss Shen, why are you sitting at the door?
His Highness wants me to leave, but I want to stay.
Aren't you afraid of him?
I am.
His Highness is always pulling a long face. He's fierce.
His Highness
is very stubborn.
It's hard to change his decision.
It's okay. I can change it.
My name is Shen Keyi.
Keyi means "can." I can do things that other people can't.
Here.
Take it.
What a silly girl.
[Jin]
Thank you, Guard Wan.
His Highness still refuses to sleep in the room?
He has been outside for so many years.
Now he's finally back to the capital.
He doesn't even want to sleep in his room
but to set up a tent in the yard.
This house doesn't look like home anymore.
His Highness is carrying too much burden.
He doesn't dare to slack off for a moment.
But the war is over.
The living must move forward eventually.
Your Ladyship.
Allow me to say one word.
His Highness won't tolerate the daughter of the Shen family.
He will chase her away in a few days.
You don't have to
waste your energy on someone from the Shen family.
There's always a way to subdue one thing.
I think this princess is a wonderful person.
Guard Wan, it's late. Let's go back.
Thank you for your umbrella. I'll send someone to return it to you tomorrow.
You Ladyship, you can keep it.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you haven't had breakfast, have you?
Have some warm porridge.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, it's my fault.
Miss Shen didn't leave.
Give her the porridge.
Thank you, Your Highness.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
After having your food,
we'll be a family.
Don't drink it.
Your Highness.
I've never had such delicious porridge.
I won't eat for free.
I will repay you.
Honey.
What are you talking about?
What honey?
According to seniority, you should call me Uncle.
Uncle?
Then we are relatives.
Can't I live in your house?
Nonsense.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
[Prince Jin's Mansion]
His Highness ignored me.
I will try to get him to talk to me.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
It's just a door.
Once I cross it,
I will be able to save Nanny.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
Sir, calm down.
The Shen family is really good at playing these little tricks.
You don't have to be angry about it.
Has she left?
She's still sitting at the gate.
It's troublesome to be back in the capital.
If she's in the military camp,
I won't care about her gender and background.
I'll just throw her out.
Sir, why did you try so hard to save her?
Although she's a member of the Shen family,
I can't let her die for me.
Besides, she saved me.
I don't want to owe anyone anything.
But this marriage is bestowed by His Majesty.
What if we can't drive her away?
Having one more person from the Shen family in the mansion
means having one more spy.
In the future, we will be restricted in everything
we do in the mansion.
The mansion is not like the barracks.
Besides, Her Highness is delicate.
You can't beat her or scold her.
You can only hide and practice swordsmanship.
Is this my mansion or the backyard of the Shen family?
Miss Shen, stop sweeping.
There are many servants in the mansion.
It's not appropriate.
It's okay, Uncle Fu.
Miss Shen, My Lady, please stop sweeping.
How many days has it been snowing?
If His Highness sees this...
Your Highness.
Uncle.
Good morning.
Call me Your Highness. Don't try to get intimate with me as a relative.
Your Highness, I said I would repay you.
I can really do a lot of work.
I swept the snow.
What?
Don't we have servants, Yi Fu?
Your Highness, I'm guilty.
It was Miss Shen who insisted on sweeping the snow in front of the door.
I couldn't... stop her.
Good.
Your Highness, Miss Shen always lives at the door.
It's not appropriate.
How about I prepare a guest room for her?
I think she likes to live in front of other people's doors.
Let her be.
When she doesn't feel comfortable,
she'll go back.
Your Highness,
I feel comfortable staying here.
Can I continue sweeping the snow?
Shen Keyi.
Steward Yi, His Highness just said yes.
Good morning, Your Highness. Good noon, Your Highness.
Your Highness, I've watered the flowers.
Your Highness, I've swept the floor.
Your Highness, I've cleaned the doors.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, do you think this stone lion
looks even more imposing after being cleaned?
Is this His Highness's?
Your Highness.
Miss Shen, His Highness has ordered you not to enter the mansion.
Here comes the imperial edict.
Brother, the imperial edict is here. Come out and receive the edict.
Where is Her Highness?
Yi Fu, did she go back?
Miss Shen seems to have left.
[Prince Jin’s Mansion]
No way.
The imperial edict can only be announced when Her Highness is here.
Then don't announce it.
Brother, don't embarrass His Majesty.
So many people are here, huh?