[English subtitles are available]
[Running Like A Shooting Star]
Do you know
what the most challenging thing is for an athlete
when he steps onto the field?
It's not technical movements
or the determination to win.
It's not money, the status, or fame either.
The most challenging thing
is to think about nothing.
-Go!
[Episode 13: Who wants to be your friend?]
[Men's 100 meters preliminaries of the Spring Track and Field Tournament]
Qi Tian.
Shixing.
What is the secret you want to tell me?
I achieved this result
through many years of training.
But he did it
as he stumbled,
vomited,
and had gastrointestinal discomfort.
It can't even be considered systematic training.
Sir,
thank you for what you've done.
Shixing.
You're not in a good state today.
Are you not feeling well?
You didn't lean forward
at the finish line.
Besides, I've never seen you run like that.
I had a slow start.
I saw it.
Are you absent-minded today?
You didn't perform well just once. It's fine.
-When the finals...
-Stop talking.
I can lose
and perform badly.
But I can't do that in front of you.
The next race is
Heat Two of men's 100 meters preliminaries.
Luo Bing,
I'm going to let you know Qi Tian you like
is nothing special.
Set!
On your marks!
Set.
Go, Tianfu!
Isn't that Tianfu?
Yeah.
He's running so fast.
Wu Tianfu, go!
Come on!
Xinghe, go!
-Go!
Surpass him!
-Go, Tianfu!
-Go!
He has completely
become a sprinter.
He is faster than when he had a competition with you.
Great!
[Men's 100 meters preliminaries of the Spring Track and Field Tournament]
Not bad.
Impressive, Ming.
Not bad, Tianfu.
Not bad. 11.0 seconds.
Your personal record.
I swear I'll set a new record of less than 11 seconds next time.
Look who's there.
Hey, Bro.
-Let's go.
Tianfu,
you performed well just now.
Really?
Why are you here?
Hi, Ziji.
We came to cheer for you
after class.
Captain,
don't you have training today?
Anyway,
you were... an important member
in the basketball team.
Of course I should come here to see my former teammate.
That's right.
Shasha and I are in a relationship now.
What?
You two are in a relationship?
So
you came here to watch the game with your girlfriend.
Tianfu,
he's not here for you.
Could it be...
our get-together last time
worked?
Considering your appearance,
why can you find a girlfriend
right after you broke up?
Qi Tian, watch your mouth.
What do you mean by that?
Ziji,
you look very handsome in your sports uniform.
Yes, Ziji is very handsome.
Is he more handsome than me?
You're... a little more handsome.
-Come on.
-So disgusting.
The next event
is today's final event:
-The preliminary round of men's 4 x 100 m relay race...
-Fatty.
-Get ready and warm up.
-Okay.
A total of 18 university teams
will participate.
Sir.
-There will be three heats.
-Should I warm up my hands
-or feet?
-The top 8 teams will take part in the finals tomorrow.
We've finally gathered everyone.
Fei Zhe would be happy
if he could see this.
I bought this pair of shoes
with him.
He didn't wear them for long.
After that,
as long as there is a competition,
I'd bring them with me.
I always think
I can show him around
and let him see more in this way.
I think
I can run faster later.
It's the preliminary round.
We should save our strength.
Don't break the rules.
Qi Tian is right.
I can't wait anymore.
Let's go.
Let's defeat them all.
Yiran,
the coach said
you don't need to participate in the preliminary round later.
Well...
Then who will be the first runner?
Wu Tianfu will be the first runner.
I'll be the second runner.
Ai Ziji will be the third runner.
Qi Tian will be the fourth runner.
With our strength,
we can definitely make it to the top 8 teams.
R-Really?
But why?
There is nothing wrong with Yiran
participating in the preliminary round, right?
Maybe the coach wants to save our strength.
Everyone knows
Xue Yiran's strength.
What's there to hide?
Let's obey the coach's order.
Qi Tian,
I'm counting on you to make it to the finals.
Let's go.
Why doesn't Xue Yiran participate at this critical moment?
I also want to know why.
What happened?
Did Fatty
come to the wrong race?
Could it be that he's an all-rounder?
Could it be that Xinghe's coach has noticed it too?
Shengling's Zeng Shixing is not on the track either.
Could it be...
both coaches are saving their strength?
You're leaving?
You don't want to participate in the 4 x 100 m relay race?
If I can't even win in the 100 m race,
what's the point of participating in the 4 x 100 m relay race?
I thought Xing would participate
to compete with Xinghe.
You performed well in the past
even without me and Xing.
So don't panic
just because Xing won't participate this time.
Our opponent this time
is not Shenglin,
but ourselves.
So
don't make any mistake.
Leave the final part to me.
Shenglin is the best!
-Go!
Today's final event is about to begin.
Track One: North China University.
Track Two: Huainan University.
Track Three: Xinghe University.
Track Four: Agriculture and Forestry University.
Track Five: Shenglin University.
On your marks!
Set!
-Go!
Come on, boys!
Go, Wu Tianfu!
Go!
Hurry!
This is the first time I see such a fat guy
in a track event.
Fatty is still fast
on the football field.
Fatty, run faster!
-Huainan, go!
-Huainan!
Forget what I said.
Sorry, Fatty.
I've rested for long.
It's finally my turn to run.
Ziji!
-Ziji, come on!
Cool, Ziji!
Is he Ziji?
His hair is too ethereal.
He's definitely the neatest among stinky men
and the manliest among all the neat men.
When the race is over,
I'll ask him what shampoo he uses.
I'll go with you later.
Come on, Ai Ziji!
Be worthy of the title I gave you.
What a wonderful game!
Frizzle.
Hold tight!
Come on!
[Men's 100 meters preliminaries of the Spring Track and Field Tournament]
We made it to the finals.
Do our best in the finals, guys!
-Go!
I knew we could definitely make it to the finals.
But I didn't expect you to perform so well.
Today is a perfect day.
Qi Tian won the first place in the preliminary round.
Besides, I set my personal record.
We also made it to the finals
of the 4 x 100 m relay race.
I can't wait
to watch the game tomorrow.
Who would have thought I could participate?
Sir, you are amazing.
I made the best of a loser.
Sorry. It was a slip of the tongue.
I made the most of everyone.
Everyone,
our coach said
in future competitions,
as long as I'm qualified,
he'll let me participate.
So, thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I might have
given up fighting for a chance today.
You are the best sprinter
in your team.
No need to belittle yourself.
After I go back later, I'll continue to practice
to prepare for the relay finals tomorrow.
Enough.
Stop practicing.
The competition is tomorrow.
Today,
go relax yourselves.
Yes.
I suggest
we should have a bath tonight
in my family's bathhouse.
I'll treat you to a massage.
I think it's a good idea.
Last time,
Tianfu didn't give us many bath coupons.
He only gave one to each of us.
I...
I didn't have many.
It's my fault.
I'll tell my family
to ask the best massage therapists to wait for us.
Sometimes,
don't shoulder everything by yourself.
Thank you, Sir.
Xue Yiran,
is the institution offering laser treatment for scar removal
I recommended to you useless?
Why are there still so many scars on your back?
They
don't matter
to me anymore.
You have a pretty face,
but you
don't care about details.
Speaking of a pretty face,
no one is more handsome
than Ai Ziji, who has tight muscles.
That's right.
I didn't expect
that I could be so passionate.
After graduation,
don't ask me to run again.
The training is really tiring, and I have to be exposed to the sun.
But you will
remember this forever, right?
Yes.
Maybe I'll never
be more focused or hard-working than now in this life.
Tianfu,
what do you plan to do after graduation?
I'm just a freshman.
Don't you think it's too early
to talk about graduation now?
Look at you.
We're just having a bath,
relaxing ourselves,
and chatting.
Right? Don't be so nervous.
Just say whatever you want.
It depends.
If I can make some achievements
in college,
I'll find a job
related to running in the future.
If I can't,
I'll just find an ordinary job.
I'll cheer for Qi Tian and Yiran
in front of the TV.
How do you know
Yiran and I
can persist in running?
I don't know.
He
just thinks
it will be a pity
if either of you
gives up.
Why are you worried?
Xue Yiran even refused
Canyu's agent.
Why would he give up running?
It's just that
I don't have a free cosmetics endorser anymore.
It makes me angry.
Why do you think
I'll endorse your products free of charge?
I'll give you a 20% discount at most.
You are so mean.
Who begged me
to establish this relay team back then?
What are you doing?
Miao.
We're off work. We're leaving first.
Can you send your friends back?
Okay, I have a key.
Thank you, Uncle Liu.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
You can stay here for as long as you want.
There...
are sauna and steam rooms over there.
Let's go back to school
after taking another bath, okay?
Tomorrow's competition
is a hard nut to crack.
I don't understand you.
You can live in your dorm.
Why do you want to rent a house outside?
Do you have much more money than you need?
It's inconvenient for a mature man
to live in a dorm.
You?
A mature man?
What?
You're not convinced?
Your abdominal external oblique muscle
and serratus anterior are quite ordinary.
You're showing off your muscles in front of me.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Why did you come?
Xinghe made it to the finals of the 4 x 100 m relay race.
So?
What does it have to do with me?
Well,
I don't know
why you are angry.
You lost to Qi Tian in the preliminary round. So what?
What?
Do you think I would like you
if you won?
You think if Qi Tian lost,
I would be with you right away, right?
You don't know women at all.
Even if I'm with you,
can you guarantee you won't lose forever?
You think if you lose, I'll run away with someone else right away?
Shixing,
we can't judge a person
according to the result of a competition.
Besides, I won't change my feelings for you
just because of your performance.
You'll always
be my most important friend and family.
Xue Yiran will participate
in the finals tomorrow.
The juniors in the team really hope
you can lead them to compete with Xinghe.
Xinghe's team is really strong this year.
Defeat them with your strength.
Who wants to be your friend?
♫Can we go back to the past?♫
Don't go too far.
♫Sometimes I want to hide the courage that I pretend to have♫
You should be happy that I came to see you.
You don't want to be friends with me, right?
♫Not saying anything against my will♫
Fine, I'm leaving.
Don't.
♫I want to continue♫
Have you had dinner?
Recently, I learned
to cook fried rice with chicken. It's very delicious.
♫Can I reverse the time?♫
I'll cook for you.
You know how to cook fried rice?
♫Who gets hurt because of my temper?♫
Is it edible?
I'll take a rain check.
♫Bystanders are indifferent♫
♫I don't want to hear what they say♫
Why is it not edible?
♫They talked about their destinations♫
♫They said they had unparalleled adventures♫
♫They said I should give up♫
♫I don't want to care♫
♫They said where my face should turn to♫
That little brat has really grown up.
♫They said where I should look at♫
♫They have many principles♫
Calm down.
♫Ignoring how far the dreams are♫
It won't be a problem
to handle Zeng Shixing.
♫They said where I should put my hand♫
♫They said no secret should be in my heart♫
You have a key, right?
I have a gate key.
It's in my bag.
What should we do now?
We need a cellphone to ask someone to open the gate.
The cellphones are in the locker.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
Getting close to me
would always bring bad luck.
Don't think like that.
It's okay.
Back then, when I went
to study medical cosmetology,
in order to save money,
I specially spent one night in the bathhouse.
I slept very well.
Just sleep.
I think
you're becoming more like a monk.