[English subtitles are available]
[Running Like A Shooting Star]
I'm fine.
There's no need to surround me.
[Episode 9: Enter Your Own Peak State]
It's an old problem.
What's wrong with you?
Old problem.
What old problem?
Ms. Luo,
take a look at him.
There are many types of doctors.
I specialize in Sports Medicine.
Given his current condition,
it's difficult for me to make a judgment.
How long have you
been experiencing this?
Answer him.
How long has it been?
Actually,
it started in my second year of high school.
At first,
my coach thought
it was just vomiting due to excessive training.
But the situation worsened over time.
When my talent for running was discovered,
I began high-intensity training.
Honestly,
I enjoy training.
I also understand that people around me
have very high expectations for me.
But the higher the expectations,
the greater the disappointment.
During a city-level Youth Track and Field Championship,
everyone thought I could win,
but unexpectedly,
Liu Haoyu emerged.
You'll have to try harder
if you want to surpass me, a genius.
Qi Tian is nothing special.
What genius?
I think he's just not up to it.
Later on,
my coach always used Liu Haoyu to motivate me.
What's funny is,
nowadays when I see Liu Haoyu,
he doesn't even remember me.
Maybe I'm just lame.
You can't even bear this little suffering.
You think having a bit of talent
makes you extraordinary, huh?
Look at Liu Haoyu.
I was training
while vomiting.
I swore that I'll beat Liu Haoyu
at the next High School Games.
During this time, the thing with Shen Ming happened.
In a fit of pique,
he left and kept training with his father.
So he didn't know about my training condition.
Why is it that I work so hard,
yet you can breeze through effortlessly?
You've always been the supporting character in my life,
the one who always lagged behind.
But now, you've become the school's superstar.
My parents also boasted to everyone,
saying that a running genius had emerged in our family
and that they would organize a group to watch me in the Olympics in the future.
They had no idea
that I was light-years away from the Olympics.
All of this added immense pressure on me.
Eventually,
my weight dropped to 55 kilogram.
How can you call yourself a man if you can't even bear this little suffering?
Why are you kneeling there?
What a loser.
Weak-kneed.
Meaningless.
So meaningless.
It's so boring.
My body seemed to have reached its limit.
For a while,
just the thought of running
made me nauseous,
and seeing training
made me physically uncomfortable.
God gave me ankles suited for running,
but didn't give me
a matching body.
I'm probably just a joke.
No,
you're not a joke.
I will help you get better.
Sir.
It's just that you have too much empathy,
competitiveness,
and sense of responsibility.
Trust me. You will get better.
Running and food don't make you vomit.
The real reason for your vomiting
is the mental stress
that has disrupted
your digestive system.
Mental stress can cause sympathetic nervous system imbalance,
autonomic nervous system disorder,
gastric acid secretion imbalance,
and insufficient blood supply to the gastric mucosa.
This has long been confirmed in medicine.
Actually,
I've noticed for a while that you might have
mental stress issues.
You always think about
how to train harder.
But you never think about stopping yourself.
In the disdain of others,
in self-denial,
you keep pushing yourself.
Eventually,
both physically and mentally,
you fall into endless exhaustion.
But once the exhaustion accumulates,
one...
loses their radiance.
If it weren't your own experience,
how could nineteen-year-old you
speak such words?
Xue Yiran,
help Qi Tian back to rest.
As for tomorrow's final...
Fatty.
You go.
Me？
Fatty.
I'm sorry.
I held everyone back.
I disappointed you all.
Qi Tian,
stop being overly responsible.
Originally, we didn't count on you
to compete in this match.
Didn't you hear what Wang said?
Hurry up and become an irresponsible jerk.
[Changing Room]
You're such a jinx.
You even dropped the baton.
It's said that during the second leg baton exchange of Huainan,
the runner went out of the exchange zone.
As a result, Huainan's result was declared invalid
and canceled.
♫Don't want to be afraid. I hurt to hesitate♫
♫But we can't wait to feel this change♫
♫It's not too late, free from hate♫
♫Think of the future that we can crate. Face the facts today♫
♫There's a better way♫
The weather has been getting cold.
♫Like a tree♫
Why can you always find me
no matter where I am?
Aren't you curious
about what place we came in yesterday
with Fatty's help?
What place?
The fifth place.
Impressive, right?
We, and Fatty,
came fifth in the whole city.
Yesterday,
Liu Haoyu didn't get to see you.
He said we at Xinghe looked down on him,
making him race with a fat guy.
Is that so?
Obviously,
Liu Haoyu
has set his sights on you, the Golden Hound.
Your passive,
non-rejecting,
non-responsible state
is starting to resemble that of a jerk.
Coach told me to think less
and daydream more.
Speaking of Coach,
Wang said he arranged a training camp in the mountains.
It'll be at the end of October.
It's quite cold in the mountains.
Would you like me to accompany you, Mr. Rustic,
to buy some warm clothes?
Do you think...
Wang can really cure me?
I don't know.
He said so.
Let's just believe it.
Anyway, things won't get any worse for you.
I want to believe in Wang.
If it weren't for you,
I don't think I could come back to running.
Maybe
I'd never be able to experience
the heat of the sun reflecting off the track,
smell the fragrance of the grass,
or hear the cheers around me again.
Every element of the track-and-field ground
fills my heart with something.
I want to come back.
I want to run again
with full vigor.
Thank you, Xue Yiran.
Actually,
I just want to comfort
the you from the past, full of wounds.
How great it would be
if I could return to the arena.
I'm exhausted.
In this Track and Field Club,
there's one with a hand injury,
one frequently feels nauseous,
and an old man about to retire.
It's simply a team of the elderly and infirm.
Ai Ziji,
what's with your sarcasm
every day?
The booked room isn't very professional.
It's just an ordinary guesthouse.
So, we need to bring more equipment with us
in case there isn't enough.
Where's Wu Tianfu at a time like this?
It's just me and Xue Yiran, two handsome guys,
doing all the work.
Is this reasonable?
I'm not very pleased
with being on the same level as you in terms of looks.
As the saying goes,
"One should not be arrogant.
Xue Yiran,
who exactly
do you think highly of?
Go ahead and keep being arrogant.
One day, you'll end up like Amumu.
You even have the face to say that to me?
Who,
back in freshman year, had no friends,
and was always moping in the corner with a sullen face,
and blaming others for bullying you?
Xue Yiran, are you asking for a beating?
Alright. Stop it, you two.
Wu Tianfu said he went to Huainan University
to have a meal with a friend.
He'll be back soon.
Look at Wu Tianfu.
He made friends all the way to Huainan.
Which friend of Wu Tianfu is in Huainan?
Here.
Actually, I saw you that day.
It's just that Qi Tian wasn't feeling well,
so I didn't come to you.
I didn't expect you to still remember it.
It's fine.
I'm used to it.
As a jinx,
I can't do anything well
except
handle pressure.
So what happened later?
Did they give you a hard time?
What else could they do to give me a hard time?
They just won't let me run in the future.
Handing over the baton
is something that requires two people.
Why did they only target you?
Tianfu,
there isn't always a reason for everything in the world.
We can only accept our fate.
Who can I blame for the fact
that I always seem to have bad luck?
No.
No, I don't agree with it.
In my values,
as long as you are willing to work hard,
there will definitely be results and rewards.
That's because you're lucky.
All the people in the world who work hard and get rewarded
are lucky.
Sometimes I wonder
if I should become an online writer.
Then I can stay at home every day
without having to deal with people
or
hurt anyone.
Don't always be so pessimistic.
Look,
the shoelaces you gave me
are tied nicely, aren't they?
♫A fleeting beam of light♫
♫The youth wants to catch up to the sun♫
♫My dream makes me♫
♫Willing to be crazy♫
♫Breaking through fear, racing against destiny♫
♫Not being nervous anymore, not being content with the status quo♫
Don't rush.
The first thing you need to do is rehabilitation.
♫Never again♫
♫Feel lost♫
What are you looking at?
Is it better looking than me?
♫Once promises are made, I never thought of leaving♫
Don't flatter yourself.
Haven't you already been looking at Tadao Ando's works?
♫Even facing the hardships of reality♫
Why haven't you made any progress in aesthetics?
What do Tadao Ando's works
have to do with your face?
♫The wish made in summer will eventually come true♫
Voilà!
Look!
Let's go.
This place is nice.
Not bad.
I remember the house I rented is self-service
with no staff.
We were arranged by You Qian's mother.
I'm a nutritionist
and also a chef at a five-star hotel.
In these days,
if you want to eat anything, just tell me.
That's great.
I am specifically responsible for your daily life.
I am in charge of rehabilitation.
I used to be
a team doctor for a sports team.
If you need relaxation, massage,
I can help.
Just call me Dr. Liu.
Keep it low-key.
Mom, hello.
Hi, Mrs. You.
Hello.
Thank you for taking care of our Qian before.
These are my gifts to you.
Feel free to enjoy them.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you, Mrs. You.
Stupid.
Don't call her Mrs. You.
Call her sister.
Thank you, sister.
Alright.
Call me whatever you want.
Qian,
You must focus on your rehabilitation
and listen to the doctor,
got it?
I got it, mom.
-I'm going to hang up now. Bye.
-Bye, Mrs. You.
-Bye.
Let’s go.
There are three rooms in total.
You can assign them yourselves.
Okay.
Sir, I want to share a room with you.
Well, Qi Tian,
would you like to share a room with me?
No.
I don't want to share a room with Xue Yiran.
I'm neat.
I feel sick just seeing him.
I don't want to live with you either.
You are so stupid.
You...
Enough.
You can live with me.
I'll live with the best.
Let's go. Let's share a room.
The air in the mountains is really good.
I feel like my skin looks better.
Tianfu.
There are a lot of trees in the mountains.
You can use this.
What's this?
What is it for?
What are you planning to do later?
I heard there's a hot spring nearby.
I want to go for a soak.
A hot spring?
Don't you have any other options?
Why do I feel like
you've never taken a bath with me before?
Is that so?
We're both men.
What's there to hide?
I have everything you have.
Maybe we just never had the chance.
Why don't you take a bath with us?
What secrets do you have on your body?
What?
Do you really want to take a bath with me?
Plus, you always wear these
long-sleeved undershirts.
The weather was hot before.
You got a WeChat message.
Tomorrow morning at 5:30,
Qi Tian will go to the meditation room.
I'll wait for you there.
The others will start morning exercises promptly at 6:00.
Everyone, have some dinner today
and rest early.
Copy that.
I'm going to take a shower now.
Do you want to join me?
Well, I don't really mind.
That's gross.
Qi Tian.
Let's get started.
Sit.
Today, what I want to tell you
might be a bit complex,
difficult to understand,
or even a bit mystical.
But these are some of the results of my research
on athlete psychology over the years.
You can try
to follow my thoughts.
If you don't understand,
we can always stop.
Do you remember Lolo Jones,
the American athlete who competed
in the women's 100-meter hurdles
at the 2008 Beijing Olympics?
She was leading the race
after the start
but stumbled over the second-to-last hurdle,
losing the gold medal.
Do you know what she was thinking at that moment?
She said
that at the moment she stepped out, she was thinking,
"I need to extend my legs as far as I can."
You see,
in the world's highest level of competition,
just such a small thought
caused the disappearance of her ZONE state.
ZONE state?
Yeah.
ZONE state.
The ZONE state is a concept
proposed by psychologist
Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi,
which means
being completely immersed
in one's goals,
relaxing,
and allowing the body
to achieve a state
of extreme focus.
That's the ZONE state.
It's also called the peak state.
The peak state?
Every athlete,
when they step onto the field,
is actually pursuing
this peak state.
In other words,
it's about disregarding oneself
and disregarding others.
I'm so tired.
I miss the braised pork ribs at school.
Do you know
what's the hardest thing for an athlete the moment
they step onto the field?
It's not the technical moves,
nor the determination to win,
nor the money, status, or fame.
The hardest thing
is to think of nothing.
Especially in short-distance sports,
most of it relies on our muscle memory.
This requires us to enter this ZONE state
so that our bodies
can exert 100% of their energy.
Wanting to win
makes you anxious.
Fear of losing makes you a coward.
The more distractions you have,
the worse your physical condition will be.
Now,
let's go back to you problem.
Why do you fear running,
and avoid it?
Because...
I feel like I can't lose friends,
health,
or even the whole world
just for running.
Because...
as long as I stop running,
I won't vomit anymore.
In fact,
there are many athletes who have the same problem as you.
Most of the time,
it has nothing to do with the intensity of the exercise.
Because some esports players
also vomit
during competitions.
Some can even vomit
for a minute and a half.
Although Coach looks like this,
he is actually
very professional.
I can tell.
When Wang was training me,
he told me a lot about his past.
He actually had
a promising student
named Zhuang Xizhe.
They achieved a result
almost approaching the national record.
But that year,
only one person could participate in the competition.
For him, Wang fought
with his leader.
Finally,
the leader agreed to let Zhuang Xizhe participate in the competition.
Get up!
Perhaps due to immense pressure,
Wang's training of Zhuang Xizhe
became stricter.
However, Zhuang Xizhe was too hot-tempered.
Who did you fight with?
In the end,
Zhuang Xizhe didn't get to participate
in that important competition
and ended his sports career early.
Years later,
the news about him
was about another fight.
He injured someone
and ended up in prison.
After he came out,
his work and life were very miserable.
You can't go on like this anymore.
Let's go.
Go home.
Let's go home.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Wang was very sad.
Perhaps he had put
too much pressure on the child,
leading to his psychological issues.
Later, he started reading various books
about psychology,
trying to make up for his guilt.
In training,
he no longer rushed for results.
It's no wonder
he's like this now.
Actually, he could be considered
a frustrated person.
In his youth,
he once had lofty aspirations.
But I've never seen him
unhappy.
He's always cheerful.
Some people
are like shells.
Time gives them sand,
but what they give back
is pearls.
The causes of these diseases
lie in stress and depression,
not in the exercise itself.
Qi Tian,
you've targeted the wrong object of dislike.
Studies show
that stress and depression
can lead to various illnesses,
such as ulcers, high blood pressure,
irregular heartbeat, headaches,
and more.
The majority of human stress and depression
stem from emotions
such as resentment, regret,
anxiety, disappointment,
expectations, fear, sadness,
and various other feelings.
Removing them
is indeed challenging.
Therefore,
you must learn
how to calmly deal with them.
Of course,
for a nineteen-year-old like you,
this is indeed difficult.
Even for someone like me in their fifties,
it's impossible to remain undisturbed in every situation.
But this is a mandatory lesson for every athlete
until retirement.
So,
Qi Tian,
in the upcoming period,
your goal
is to learn
how to peacefully coexist with the distractions
in your mind,
and truly enter
your own peak state.
Qi Tian,
keep up the good work.
Why am I saying these words to you?
Because in you, I see potential,
the potential to reach greater heights.
Don't ever
give up.