[English subtitles are available]
[Running Like A Shooting Star]
People
tend to believe
that their thoughts have made them who they are.
If so,
a person is nothing but a collection of thoughts.
You should try thinking about
[Episode 10 Seize Every Day]
the thoughts that bother you from a bystander's perspective.
Once your head is full of thoughts that bother you,
much of your energy will be consumed,
and you'll become less and less concentrated.
You'll have poor judgment and become less creative.
As a result, you'll be stopped from entering the ZONE.
Coach makes Qi Tian
stay with him in the meditation room every day.
Will it get Qi Tian to improve his speed?
What the coach is doing is so weird.
Qi Tian
kept silent
after he came back to his room every night.
I have no idea what he was thinking.
The coach looked happy every night.
After he came back every night, he would sing in the shower.
Wang sang every night?
When you calm down,
label every thought that bothers you.
Then you will find
those thoughts in your head
are quite similar.
How come I worked so hard,
but it was you who got the first place easily?
I used to be way better than you,
but you are one of the most popular people at the school now.
Come on.
You have to work harder.
Otherwise, you won't beat a genius like me.
When you know what those thoughts that bother you are,
try labeling them.
I tend to number them.
Bad Thought No.1.
You can easily get the first place.
Bad Thought No.2.
You have to work harder
to beat a genius like me.
Bad Thought No.3.
Most people
will have no more than ten thoughts
that keep bothering them in their life.
But they would feel the number of those thoughts is far greater than ten.
And they're tired of dealing with them.
The next time Bad Thought No.1 comes to you,
you'll say,
"Oh, it's you again."
Try to talk to them
as a bystander.
Try to keep calm and think critically
when you're dealing with the thoughts that bother you.
Gradually, you will find
those thoughts will come to you
less and less frequently.
You don't have to think hard about them.
Just let those thoughts be there.
Try to get familiar with those thoughts.
Many of them
will be like the friends that will be with you forever.
Your goal is
to focus on breathing.
Think about nothing.
Clear your mind.
Should we get one for Qi Tian?
He should be here soon.
Get him one.
Qi Tian.
How are you feeling?
I'm so hungry.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm starving.
Qi Tian.
I remember you haven't eaten much at every meal
since you began to run again.
You couldn't even finish the food I bought for you.
Why is your appetite so great today?
Coach.
Though I can't
be in the state you talked to me about for now,
I'm much calmer now.
And I don't feel sick anymore.
That's because your sympathetic nerves
are not in disorder anymore.
The secretion of your gastric fluid is also normal now.
Sympathetic nerves in disorder?
Qi Tian.
You had a mental disorder?
Don't talk nonsense.
Qi Tian just got better.
Don't make fun of him.
Coach.
The theory you used is really good.
Although I don't quite understand
the cutting-edge brain science theories
or psychology.
But at least,
your methods worked well for me.
Thank you, Coach.
Don't mention it.
Actually,
I should thank you
for giving me the opportunity
to teach you what I have learnt
and to watch you grow day by day
and become stronger and stronger.
I'm really happy for you.
Coach.
Will your methods work for me?
I want to become stronger too.
You...
In terms of mental strength,
you're way better than Qi Tian.
You don't need those methods.
I'm better than Qi Tian in that aspect?
Okay.
I agree with you.
No wonder you've been so happy these days.
Thank you.
Actually,
to evaluate
how good a coach is
is to see how well they can train their athletes.
Athletes like you are like firewood.
A good coach is like one who will
ignite the firewood.
Let's drink a toast to Coach.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
-Thank you, Coach.
I'm so full.
I haven't eaten so much in a meal for a long time.
Dr. Liu just came to help us get relaxed.
He said there was a thermal spring here
and advised all of us to take a bath in the thermal spring.
He said it would help get our muscles relaxed.
I've just taken a shower.
But your hair is dry.
And you're not wearing slippers.
He lied to you.
He hasn't taken a shower yet.
He has mysophobia.
He wants to keep it a secret.
When he used to live with us,
he complained we were too untidy.
And he has never bathed with us.
Right, Tianfu?
It seems that
Yiran has never bathed with us.
Ai Ziji has mysophobia. So do I.
The idea of sharing a bathtub with you guys
makes me feel uncomfortable.
How could you say that?
Fine, you just stay here.
Qi Tian, would you like to go with us?
I ate too much.
I'm afraid I'll feel uncomfortable later if I take a thermal spring bath.
I'll go next time.
Okay.
Bye.
Thank you.
You're such a terrible liar.
That's because
I'm an honest person.
An honest person
doesn't hide things from their best friends.
What on earth...
There is a new girl group.
The lead dancer is so pretty.
Really.
I bet you'll like her a lot.
Xing, I missed you so much.
Why didn't you come back to the team for training after the match?
Xing, you're amazing.
You finished the race within 10.19 seconds.
No college students
in the past two years have been faster.
My fish!
You scared my fish away.
We're here.
How come you're still fishing?
Didn't you miss
your cute juniors?
Yeah.
Fine.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
Anything will be good.
I heard you had competed in the city-level contest for autumn.
Why did you do that?
If I didn't participate,
the winners of the 4 x 100 m relay race
would become another school's team.
Xue Yiran also competed in the contest this year.
How come he would compete in a contest of that level?
I don't know.
There is something very strange about Xinghe this year.
That's not important.
The important thing is that they have recruited a new member. His name is...
He used to be Shen Ming's schoolmate.
He's only a freshman.
But he almost beat me.
Almost beat you?
A freshman?
He has been seen as a gifted runner
since high school.
And I'm sure
he wasn't at his best in that race against me.
He fell on the ground after the race.
Xue Yiran carried him away.
Really?
Was Ms. Luo there that day?
Ms. Luo?
You won't believe this.
She's a huge fan of his now.
She said he was art
all the time.
What's his name?
He's called Golden Hound.
His name is Qi Tian.
Are you ready to go running with us?
Yes.
Let's go.
The coach said
I only needed to meditate for an hour every day.
For the rest of the day,
I would be in training with you.
Good for you.
Looks like
it's going to rain, right?
Let's do the training indoors.
No.
I just came out from seclusion.
Let me run freely.
So you're fully recovered now.
Don't be a jerk.
Cut the crap.
Are you running or not?
I don't feel like running.
The caged hound has been set free.
♫Talking like a child♫
Wait for us.
I believe in those long nights
there will be someone
♫I will love you more♫
who can bring the passion out of you.
The person is like a shooting star flying through the night sky.
He will help you know yourself
and get you to love your life.
♫Talking like a child♫
And he's also like a torch,
making you feel
your own warmth.
♫Take a little time to think things over♫
♫We're just one song away from heaven♫
It's so cold.
Are you alright? Xue Yiran was running so slow.
Hey.
It's so cold outside.
Why were you running in the rain?
Go get changed now.
I feel so good.
I didn't run for ten days.
Today,
I feel incredibly good after running.
What are you hiding us from?
You got a big green dragon tattooed on your back?
I don't mind letting you see it.
I don't want to scare you.
How did you get those scars?
I got burnt by cigarette butts.
Who did this to you?
Someone from my family. It's a story about child abuse.
My stepmother did it to me.
What was your dad doing?
My dad fooled around all day.
He paid little attention to me.
What about your birth mother?
She
remarried.
You don't have to feel sorry for me.
It's all over.
At that time,
you were still a child, right?
Of course.
I grew stronger and stronger.
My stepmother had to avoid me.
I want to tell you a joke
to make you feel better.
But I'm unable to do that.
You must have felt hopeless.
It's all over.
Really?
I now have you by my side.
In
less than a year,
we'll have to
go our separate ways.
I feel a little sad when I think about it.
In the meditation room,
Wang said some words to me.
Let me say them to you now.
Don't regret what happened in the past.
Don't worry about the future.
Seize every day.
What happened in the past
won't bother you anymore
if you don't care about it.
Now,
we are completely honest with each other.
You now know
all my secrets.
You must feel sorry for me because of my unhappy childhood.
Then tell me a joke.
No, I won't.
Hurry up.
I'm hungry.
I used to tell you jokes.
You're so cold-hearted.
What are you going to eat?
Gu said he would make us Sweet and Sour Mandarin Fish today.
Wait for me.
Yiran.
I think
you look different today.
But I can't tell
what's different about you today.
Yes.
He's not wearing
that...
He's not wearing his long johns today.
Don't talk nonsense.
That is compression clothing.
It can accelerate the process of blood going to the heart
and improve the efficiency of exercising.
Come on.
Your compression clothing is nothing good.
It can only be worn in winter.
In summer, you must feel very hot in that clothing.
How did you get these scars?
You really care little about your appearance.
Now the medical beauty technology is highly developed.
I'll recommend you a clinic where you can have the scars removed through a laser surgery.
How could you say
you have mysophobia?
I do have mysophobia.
What's wrong about it?
We can see so many stars in the sky in the mountains.
Yes.
There're too many lights in cities so we can't see many stars there.
We're going back tomorrow.
I feel a little sad about it.
The tea here is good.
The air is also fresh here.
If you like it here so much,
let's come here often.
Did you notice that
after these days' training,
Ziji and Tianfu made much progress.
Tianfu has improved a lot.
Yes.
But
we didn't improve.
That's not true.
We all made a great stride.
You must have had
a happy childhood.
Very much so.
My parents
own a small business.
It's easy to tell
that you grew up in a happy family.
That's why you were always naive.
That's not fair. I wasn't naive.
I was just innocent and carefree.
I never
experienced pain or failure.
What I'm going through
is something I should go through in my childhood.
In my experience,
if you had many unhappy experiences in your childhood,
it doesn't mean you'll have fewer happy experiences when you grow up.
So,
try to be happy
every day.
Not to be bothered by the past.
Just to embrace the future and always wear a smile.
This is your style.
We're finally back.
I want to eat braised pork ribs.
Wasn't the food Gu cooked good?
Yes, it was.
Of course, it was.
But
people can feel nostalgic.
I felt nostalgic for braised pork ribs,
the lively campus,
and the youth of our schoolmates and the days spent with them.
You're making me want to have a braised pork rib
and get back my youth now.
I stayed in the meditation room for so many days.
I did nothing but sit in meditation and drink tea.
I feel like I were almost ten years older.
Do you want me to take you to the canteen
and ask the lady working there to give us more braised pork ribs?
I need three more braised pork ribs.
Listen.
I've just
received a notice.
On November 25,
the school will hold
the Hanfu Exhibition.
Every club
needs to
present a show
about Hanfu, the traditional Chinese clothing.
The training makes me exhausted.
And I have to learn the lessons I skipped during the training in the mountain.
I don't have time.
Right.
I haven't sent
the face masks the girls ordered to them.
I don't want to spend time rehearsing for the Hanfu show.
Let those who want to do it do it.
If I don't begin to study hard from now on,
I'll fail my tests again.
If Qi Tian doesn't participate in the show,
I won't either.
Wait.
Let me tell you.
In my childhood, apart from watching my grandpa do shot put,
I also enjoyed watching TV shows and movies.
So my second biggest dream
is to be a director.
So,
you can take this opportunity
to help me fulfill my dream of being a director.
No.
I'll pay you.
Hello, Director.
Hello, Director. Hello, Director.
Look, it’s Xue Yiran.