What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm playing the game.
Think about it.
If no one else gets across,
it'll just be the two of us left.
We'll both press X in the next vote
and get out of here with the money.
With 22.7 billion each!
You motherfucker!
Player 276, eliminated.
No one can cross the bridge now!
It's game over, shitheads!
- Stop.
Stop what?
Come help me keep them off!
Bring it!
Come over here if you want to die!
Come on, you fuckers!
Player 209, eliminated.
Player 163, eliminated.
This just keeps getting
more and more interesting.
I can't jump anymore.
You have to move forward.
How? He's blocking the way!
What are you waiting for?
Just push him out of the way!
Keep going or we're all going to die!
Try me!
Just let me through!
I'll give you half of my winnings!
And I'll help you keep the rest off!
You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you.
Let go!
Player 192,
Player 442, eliminated.
Turn around.
Turn around?
Yes, go back!
I… I can't.
We'll die if you don't. Go back now!
Go back!
Player 377, eliminated.
Are you okay?
Player 349, eliminated.
What are you staring at?
I did you all a favor.
Spare me!
I can't jump anymore!
Just die, then.
Get out of the way.
Don't you fucking get it?
You and I would get all the money!
But if I pushed you from behind,
I wouldn't even have to share it.
Move.
The rope is speeding up. Hurry up!
Player 100, pass.
Player 336, pass.
Come on, move it!
Jun-hee.
Let's go.
We've got to move before it's too late.
What are you going to do then?
Just sit here and die?
I know you're angry with me.
Why did you do it?
For the money?
That person saved me and the baby.
And you killed her
with the knife that I gave you.
I didn't know, okay?
I didn't know that
you were there with her!
Jun-hee.
I was trying to find you.
I wanted to protect you and the baby.
I wasn't just thinking about myself.
I did it so we could get out of here
and start a new life together.
A happier life. That's why I did it.
So let's just go.
We have to get out and live, Jun-hee.
We have to get out of here with the baby.
I'll help you.
What will you do, carry me?
Can you do that?
That baby is mine.
The baby has nothing to do
with trash like you.
We never want to see you again,
not even in our dreams.
Hurry up!
Yo, what the fuck?
You goddamn idiot.
We could've ended it here.
I can't jump anymore.
Get out of the way, please!
Player 435, eliminated.
Player 448, eliminated.
Player 260, eliminated.
Player 096, eliminated.
Come on!
Quick!
Player 353,
Player 039, pass.
Player 203, pass.
♪ Knock, knock ♪
♪ Who is there? ♪
- ♪ Your little friend ♪
♪ Come on in ♪
♪ Little friend, little friend
Turn around ♪
Touch the ground ♪
- ♪ Little friend, little friend… ♪
-
♪ Little friend, little friend
Touch the ground ♪
Now away you go ♪
♪ Little friend, little friend
Turn around ♪
Touch the ground ♪
♪ Little friend, little friend ♪
Player 125, pass.
Jun-hee, stay there!
I'll be right there!
Don't be scared. Jump! You've got this.
- Come on!
- Go, move it.
I said go.
I'm going.
Help me.
Help me!
Please.
Help me! Please!
Please help…
Player 306, eliminated.
Player 333, pass.
Jun-hee, stay there! I'm coming for you!
Mr. Seong, no!
No, don't come back.
No, Jun-hee.
I'm coming now!
Don't give up!
Please stay where you are, Mr. Seong.
If you don't make it,
my baby won't survive either.
You told me…
to protect my baby no matter what.
That's what I'm trying to do right now.
Please help me.
Jun-hee.
Player 222, eliminated.
The game is over.
SQUID GAME 3
EPISODE 4
Soldier 018,
outer perimeter.
NO. 11 KANG NO-EUL
Soldier 011, outer perimeter.
DUTY OF THE DAY
OUTER PERIMETER
Soldier 016, outer perimeter.
Get the pursuit team ready.
Follow me.
Well, putting the baby
in the game was genius.
Made it twice as fun and dramatic.
Glad you enjoyed it.
I had no idea
the game would turn out like that.
Yes, but what do we do with this baby now?
Well, now that the mother's eliminated,
maybe…
we should just eliminate it too.
Eliminate it?
Wait, one way or another,
we all saw that baby
cross the finish line. Right?
That's true.
It's not fair to eliminate
someone who crossed the finish line.
You know,
that's the first time
you looked attractive with
your mouth open.
Look,
the baby is not
an independent participant.
It's dependent on 222.
And if 222 is eliminated,
the baby must be eliminated.
If that's the case,
we should've made the baby move
with its mother in the previous game.
If the baby crossed the finish line
separately from its mother,
then it should be considered
an independent participant.
Okay.
If we all can't agree,
why don't we just ask the host?
How about having the baby play
as Player 222 in the next game?
Isn't that the mother's number?
Yes.
And what's your reasoning?
Soon, the players will vote
whether to continue the game.
So what changes if the baby participates?
If that baby competes
in place of her mother,
both the voting and the game
will be more interesting.
I promise you.
If our host is so sure of himself,
let's do that.
Okay. Agreed.
Same here.
Player 222 is back from the dead,
thanks to her baby.
This is a bigger twist than
the resurrection of Jesus.
Awesome!
222 is invincible!
And I knew it!
I knew you could do it!
I knew it! I knew it!
Listen.
Are you good with numbers?
There are only eight of us left now.
Then the prize?
That's 44.8 billion divided by 8 people,
which makes 5.6 billion.
5.6 billion?
5.6 billion.
I think that's good enough for me.
How about you?
Good enough for me too.
Apart from that guy, who owes ten billion,
I bet it's more than enough
for everyone to settle their debts.
In that case, at the next vote, we should…
Congratulations to all of
you for making it through the fifth game.
Here are the results of the fifth game.
In the fifth game,
16 players were eliminated.
We now have nine players remaining.
The prize money accumulated
to this point is 44.7 billion won,
and each person's share
is 4.96 billion won.
Why are there nine players left?
It's eight.
He's right.
There are definitely eight of us.
Players 039, 100, 125, 203,
222, 333,
336, 353,
and 456.
Nine players have survived.
Hold on.
Player 222?
That girl?
She died earlier!
You all saw it, didn't you?
Player 222 jumped off the bridge!
Player 222
is right over there.
What?
Are you saying that baby is Player 222?
That is correct.
Wait.
That doesn't make sense.
That newborn baby is a player
all of a sudden?
That is correct.
The baby is Player 222.
So that baby
inherits its dead mother's number
and her money?
It's 4.9 billion!
- That is correct.
- Screw you!
What kind of bullshit is this?
That bitch is dead.
If she's dead, the money should be ours!
That damn baby's
done nothing to deserve it!
That's right!
We've earned that money
by risking our lives in the games.
That damn baby shows up out of nowhere,
becomes a player,
and gets to share the prize money with us?
Are you kidding me?
This is outrageous!
So if I die here,
are you going to give my prize money
to my damn kids?
My prize money is down by 700 million
because of that baby?
You can't be serious!
It's unacceptable!
That's right!
Since the mother is dead,
the baby should also be eliminated!
Am I right?
Yes, the baby must be eliminated.
Damn right!
The kid must be eliminated too.
We have to kill it!
Right.
I can't let this happen!
The baby must die too!
It's got to be eliminated!
- Yes, it must be eliminated!
- The baby must die!
- No! That's nonsense!
- No way in hell!
- The baby is not qualified.
- Eliminate it!
- It can't even take the money.
- Take the baby!
- Hand it over!
- This is bullshit!
456, hand over the kid.
Give me that damn kid.
Hand it over or I'll kill you too!
Physical violence
between players will no longer be allowed.
It is our intention
to give every player a fair chance.
Please cooperate.
To congratulate you
for reaching the final game,
we have prepared a special gift.
Name?
Kim Mu-dong.
"Kim Mu-dong"?
Resident registration number?
Mr. Choi Woo-seok.
Yes?
Stop looking at him
and answer my questions.
Do you really know the house owner?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I know him well.
Captain Park is a member of a crime group!
You have the evidence right here.
These are the uniforms
and masks they wear!
Hey.
I've been dealing with gangsters
and drug cartels for 20 years now.
What kind of crime group
wears a pink uniform like this
and puts stupid toy masks
over their faces?
I'm telling you the truth!
Those bastards wear these masks,
take people to an island,
make them play kids' games, and kill them!
Have you seen this happen?
Well…
I didn't see it myself.
We've been looking for that island.
Once my team finds it, they'll call me.
What about the money then?
The money he buried!
That's clearly dirty money!
A lot of people in this area,
especially the elderly,
prefer not to keep their money
in the bank.
They hide it in a jar
or under the floorboards.
There's nothing suspicious about it.
- What the…
- No, wait.
Look at this, okay?
This is Captain Park,
and the guy next to him is one of them.
He'd play ddakji at subway stations
to lure victims.
He may look like a normal guy,
but he's cruel.
This bastard…
made me play
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Minus One
and shot the man
who was like a brother to me.
So, who is this guy?
I just told you.
He'd play ddakji at subway stations…
No!
Not that.
His name, age, address, job.
Stuff like that.
What are you asking me for?
Isn't that your job as a police officer
who gets paid with our tax money?
Sure.
That's why I did
a background check on you,
to make sure your tax money's working.
Man, you've got quite a rap sheet.
Kidnapping, false imprisonment,
assault, threats, extortion.
Nine criminal convictions in total.
Now with the burglary
and the animal protection law violation,
you've hit double digits.
No, it's not me you should dig into.
Look up Captain Park.
That guy is fishy as hell.
Did you run his ID?
Captain Park Yeong-gil
was fined once for illegal gambling
ten years ago, and that's it.
Since then, he's been completely clean,
without so much as a parking ticket.
This is the island
where I was shot.
I used up an entire tank of air
getting there from the site of the games
through an underwater cave.
An air tank lasts about 40 minutes.
Even taking into account
the propulsion device you used,
I'm sure the island
is within a 13-mile radius…
somewhere on this map.
It's been five days
since they took Mr. Seong Gi-hun.
We only have one day left
before the games end.
It's impossible to search
all these islands in one day.
Let's start with the most likely options.
What do you think, Captain?
If you ask me…
it's not in this area.
The currents are strong here,
and the coast guard often patrols the area
for Chinese fishing boats.
They wouldn't have picked
somewhere like that for the games.
Let's search
these islands as soon as it gets light.
We'll cover the south
and have Boat Two take the north.
Okay.
All right.
Let's do it.
- Hey, Detective Song.
- Yes, sir?
Do we have
Park Yeong-gil's location?
It looks like he's out at sea, working.
You'll have to call him.
His property has been damaged.
It's late, so I was going to call
in the morning.
Fishermen don't sleep at night.
His dog just died.
You should call him and let him know.
Yes, sir.
Detective, I need to make a call as well.
Who do you need to call?
My lawyer.
Here.
No, not this. Give me my phone, please.
Your phone has been seized
as criminal evidence.
If you need to call someone,
use this.
My friend is a lawyer,
and his number is in my phone.
Give me my phone.
I said no.
Hello?
Is this Captain Park Yeong-gil?
Yes.
Hi, I'm calling
from Moojin Police Station.
I'm calling to inform you that
there's been a burglary at your residence.
Someone broke into my house?
We got a call
from your neighbor,
and we caught the intruder at the scene.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
So what did they try to steal?
He tried to steal
the cash and clothes
you buried in your front yard.
Ah…
Could you tell me the burglar's name?
Yes,
his name is Choi Woo-seok.
A man in his forties.
Do you know him, by any chance?
No, I've never heard of him.
I see.
The thing is,
this guy has been saying
some crazy things.
Crazy things?
He says you're a member of a crime group
that takes people to some island
and makes them play murderous games.
He also says the cash you buried
in the yard is dirty money,
and the pink clothes--
Give me my phone right now!
My lawyer's number is in my phone!
You're violating my rights
by not letting me have it!
Is this how you small-town cops work?
Screw the rules and do whatever you want?
Fine! I want to talk to your chief then!
One of my closest friends
is a big deal here in Moojin!
I can get you all fired!
All right, fine.
Calm down, okay?
I'll let you use your phone.
Okay. Come on, quickly!
Hi,
sorry about that.
It's a bit noisy over here.
Listen, Captain Park.
As soon as you get back to port,
we'll need you to come to the station
to see if there's any other damage.
- Also,
I'm really sorry to tell you this,
but your dog has died.
It looks like Mr. Choi Woo-seok killed it.
Right, thank you.
Who called you this late?
Oh, just someone I used to work with.
He had a bad dream
and warned me to be careful.
What was his dream about?
His dog died.
In his dream.
What's your passcode?
I can't tell you that.
I can unlock it with face recognition.
Hold it up for me.
Here. Put your face up to it.
- Hey! Get him!
- Hey!
Siri, call Hwang!
Hey! You little…
Go back inside.
I'll radio Captain Ko on Boat Two
and come back.
All right.
MR. CHOI
Hi, Mr. Choi.
This is Boat One.
Boat Two, do you read me?
This is Boat Two. Go ahead.
We've been exposed.
Kill everyone on the boat now.
Copy that.
Hwang! Captain Park is one of them!
What?
He's one of the masked men!
I found his uniform and mask at his house!
I also found a picture of him
with the ddakji guy! Shit!
Be careful, okay?
He knows I broke into his house!
Hwang, be careful!
Hwang!
Captain, would you like some ramyeon?
Get another one ready for him.
Where's Hwang?
Behind you.
Who are you?
What are you after?
Why did you save my life before?
I was…
just following orders.
Who gave you that order?
He told me to do whatever it took
to keep you alive.
You know where that island is, don't you?
Even if you get there now,
what do you actually think you can do?
Look around you.
There's no one to help you now.
Where is the island?
I was supposed to die
a long time ago anyway.
But the captain gave me a second chance.
Where is it? Answer me!
Thanks.
It's been fun.
Everyone, please take your seats.
We have prepared
as much food and drink as you need.
If you need more,
please don't hesitate to ask.
I'm a little worried.
About what?
Well, the baby may have lowered
each player's share of the cash,
but won't the majority still want to stop
the game for that much prize money?
No need to worry.
The final game will definitely take place.
How can you be so sure?
They have no reason to vote no
if they know for sure they'll survive.
Sounds like you have a plan.
Our host always has a plan.
You will now
take a vote to decide
whether to continue the games or not.
But before we begin,
you will be given a hint
about the final game.
In the final game,
you will each get to choose
which players to eliminate.
What?
We get to decide who will be eliminated?
That is correct.
If you can all agree on
which three players should be eliminated,
everyone else
will make it through the game.
So we just need to
eliminate three people,
and we get to decide who?
That is correct.
In the final game, you only need
to eliminate a minimum of three players.
You said,
"A minimum of three players."
Doesn't that mean
more than three can be eliminated?
That is correct.
However, the choice will be yours.
So we can also decide
how many will be eliminated?
- That is correct.
- Damn it.
Explain it better.
What the hell are you saying?
Let me get this straight.
All we need to do is
eliminate at least three people,
and we get to decide who they will be?
That is correct.
It's entirely up to you to decide
who will be eliminated in the final game.
If you eliminate three players,
the rest will be able to leave this place
as the final winners.
Now, let's begin the vote.
The vote will be held
in reverse order of your player numbers.
Player 456, please cast your vote.
Player 353, please cast your vote.
Player 336.
Player 333.
Player 222.
Player 222 will be considered
to have abstained
due to their inability to make decisions.
Does anyone have any objections?
I have…
no objections.
Can I have some more rice?
Do we all agree then?
- Yes.
- I agree.
Let's finish the vote quickly
and enjoy the food.
Player 125.
Hey!
Go cast your vote.
Player 100.
Lastly, Player 039.
Can we just call it now?
We've already got 5 out of 9 votes,
so that's a majority.
Do you need to cast your vote?
No, I'm good.
I was going to vote O anyway.
A majority of 5 out of 9
have voted in favor,
so we will proceed to the final game.
Thank you.
Since we have made it this far,
let's toast to giving it our best shot
until the end.
Everyone, raise your glasses!
Cheers!
- Cheers.
Now, let us feast!
Enjoy, everyone.
Hey,
bring me more galbi and japchae!
Booze. I want more booze.
And our host was right again.
Mmm. I wonder
how they'll decide who to eliminate.
I suppose it all depends on
what the next game is.
Sorry,
but we will have to keep it a secret
until tomorrow for your entertainment.
I can't wait for tomorrow.
We'll just have to stay up
all night and drink, then.
And then the sun will come up,
and the games will start.
Where are you off to?
- I'm gonna call it a night.
- Already?
Come on. Have a drink with me.
Ooh.
That sounds sexy.
What does that mean?
I'd rather drink
with my footstool than with you.
I think they got Team 2 too.
The bleeding has stopped.
It's a perforating wound,
so you should be okay for now.
- Once we find that island--
- We should give up now.
We've still got time.
I'm sure
there are still some people alive.
Is that really the reason
you want to find it?
My brother is on that island.
If I don't find it now,
I may never get another chance.
Please help me.
We can't search the entire area
by ourselves without the other boat.
It's not in this area.
The currents are strong here,
and the coast guard often patrols the area
for Chinese fishing boats.
They wouldn't have picked
somewhere like that for the games.
The island must be here.
This is Boat Two.
They've been dealt with.
And Boat One?
It looks like they got Captain Park.
- Number 011, answer me.
I have nothing to say.
How far do you think you can get
in that tiny boat?
It's not too late.
Bring him back.
If you turn him over without a fight,
I'll let you off the hook.
From now on, stop looking for us.
It's better for you too.
Player 246, Park Gyeong-seok.
I don't know how you know him.
But I think I might know
where he's headed.
Seohyeon University Hospital,
pediatric cancer ward, Room 4104.
How about it?
Do you want to come back now?
If it's three people,
the solution is simple.
It's a no-brainer.
Player 456 over there.
222, that damn kid.
And 125, the junkie.
We can eliminate those three.
Once we eliminate those three,
the six of us will play nice,
divide up the money and get the hell out.
Then how much would each of us get?
Huh?
It's 7.6 billion.
So let's make a pact here.
The six of us will stick together,
only take out those three,
and then go our separate ways
with 7.6 billion each.
But we still don't know
exactly what the game will be.
They also said more than three
could be eliminated.
That's true,
but they said
we'd get to choose who to eliminate.
So whatever it is, we'll definitely
have the upper hand as a team.
All right, that's enough talking.
If you want to do this as a team,
put your hands together.
Come on, man. Are you in or out?
I guess having the baby in the game
was a good thing for us after all.
Why are you going back?
Drive north at full speed.
As soon as you reach land,
call the police.
Your daughter is in danger.
You know my daughter, Na-yeon?
You should go now.
Get as far away as you can
before the fog lifts.
Officer,
he boat is getting away again.
Kill them both.
Player 456.
He wants to see you.
Take a seat.
This could take a while.
I have a proposition for you.
It's about your future. And the baby's.
Did we ever…
have a future to begin with?
As you have probably guessed,
the others will target you and the baby
in the next game.
Isn't that what you
and the people above you want?
That's why
you put a newborn baby in the game.
You want to see those money-crazed men
kill the baby with your own eyes.
I'm trying to help
you and the baby here.
You're trying to help us?
Take this knife
back to your quarters
and kill the trash
who wants to kill you and the baby.
They're fast asleep
after all the food and drink.
Slit their throats one by one,
no one will notice.
Why are you suggesting this?
Mr. Seong Gi-hun.
I'm sorry about Jung-bae.
Do you want to kill me?
Then go ahead.
It's just you and me here.
There's no one here to stop you.
But killing me won't change anything.
Someone else will take my place,
and tomorrow's game will still go ahead.
And in that game,
you'll have to fight the trash
trying to kill you and the baby.
Once you kill all of them,
you and the baby will be
the only players left.
The next game can't be played
with only two people.
Then, according to the rules,
the game
will end there.
You and the baby
will get out of here alive.
You have my word.
They will try to kill you
and the baby tomorrow.
Kill them first.
That is
the best choice you can make right now.
Player 456.
Do you still have faith in people?
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song