제가
th
Donaldomic
ho
o
states
and
or you don't want me to come back?
I heard that you were ill.
You didn't go back to the palace.
You should go back to the palace.
Who would have thought that you would be so close to my husband?
You are so quiet.
Your child?
Is he worthy of me?
What are you doing?
Sister Tang, I was the one who made the decision
to give birth to a child for you.
I am also thinking for you.
If you want to fight,
then fight me.
Okay.
Your Highness!
If you can't make him cry, then you should take care of him.
Lu Shao, are you crazy?
Yes, I am crazy!
Since I came to the palace,
I have been living in peace.
I even buried all my family's assets in the ground.
But you...
I have been living in peace since I was born.
My sister Tang was born in the same year as me.
Now she has a child.
You are the one who is heartless and heartless.
You are a bastard!
Lu Shao,
you have been married for many years.
You are a bastard!
You forced your father to die because of you.
You are not worthy of your husband.
You are a bastard!
You are not worthy of your wife.
You committed four crimes.
I did not punish you.
You are already a man of conscience.
You dare to humiliate me?
Then I will
have a good meal
and fight with you.
How about that?
Are you crazy?
Enough!
You are so ridiculous.
What is the dignity of the royal family?
During the period of the imperial edict,
you were already a man of conscience.
Even if Lu Zhao made a mistake,
his parents were dead.
You have no right to divorce your wife.
Lu Zhao,
Chu Wang has his own reasons.
But you have no choice.
You even want to kill your father.
You cannot bear the position of the princess.
You are a couple.
You should not be afraid of your father.
You are a man of conscience.
You are a couple.
I do not want to see you become enemies
and disgrace the royal family.
I order you to divorce now.
You will be married and will not be together.
Thank you for your help.
The imperial edict is urgent.
I will write a divorce letter
and have a good talk with Zhao.
I beg you to let me
and Zhao
have a private talk.
Lu Zhao, are you willing to do it?
Yes.
I will.
I have never written a letter
to send to the Pilan Palace.
How did you know that I was there?
You do not deserve to know.
The divorce letter is here.
If you want it, come and get it.
Uncle Jiu Huang is outside.
How dare you make a noise?
What?
Are you afraid?
You know kung fu.
You are not Lu Zhao.
Who are you?
I am Lu Zhao.
I am also a shadow of your destiny.
By the way,
if I did not stop in time,
I am afraid that I have to prepare for your funeral.
Do you think you can hook up with Xiao Ren?
I am not afraid of you.
I am afraid that you will not be able to do it.
Xiao Ren,
you are just a little smart.
You can move me.
Do you know that
in a short time,
Xiao Ren will personally send you to my bed?
You will come to me like a dog.
You better pray that you live a few more days.
Otherwise, you will not have the chance to dream if you die.
Lu Zhao,
wait and see
how arrogant you can be.
I will not let you die here.
You will not be allowed to enter the palace.
I beg you to leave.
I will not let you die here.
I will not let you leave.
You will not be allowed to enter the palace.
Lu Zhao,
from now on,
you are no longer the Princess Consort of Chu.
You do not need to follow me
back to the Pilan Palace's order.
You have achieved your purpose
of taking advantage of my chef.
Uncle Jiu, you...
The reason I didn't expose you
is because you have some deep thoughts with Miao He.
But you must remember,
those who try to get into the deep abyss
will be the ones who are caught in it.
I hope you will be polite and considerate in the future.
Take care.
Princess Miao He,
Uncle Jiu,
the sister of Tong Ba of the New Garden,
no wonder she is willing to help me.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Good. Good, my dear.
After all, you caught the King of Nanzhao
and solved my big problem.
This is a life-long journey.
I will reward you with a lot of rewards.
Whatever you want,
I will give it to you.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Go ahead.
The guilty minister, Liu Mingfu, committed suicide.
His residence is already in the palace.
But the daughter of Liu Mingfu, Lu Zhao,
just left the Palace of the King of Chu.
I beg Your Majesty to return his residence to Lu Zhao.
Just for this?
Just for this.
Good.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Come.
I...
It's my last request.
Let's go.
I'd love to.
Let's find a hotel.
No.
Be a good wife.
Not in.
Look around.
I'll show you right away.
What are you doing?
I really looked for a friend ATM.
I can then call you called beloved colleague.
Can you talk?
Yes!
Is this house sold?
From today,
This is your home part.
You don't have to keepenergetic anybody's house.
And the servant you were in the Liu family before.
From now on, you have your elders, friends by your side, and...
And... what?
Ah Zhao, I didn't build this house to put you in this place.
If there's a place you want to go,
do what you want to do, and do it boldly.
Only I will watch over you. If you want to come back, I'll be there anytime.
Thank you.
Go and take a look.
You're not coming in?
I'm not coming in.
Our Xuntian Gate has too many killings.
We can't even get a name or power.
Usually, people in Xun's house are on the side door.
If we go to the main door, it's a big deal.
You're going to the house today. I'll just go to the side door.
Go.
It's no use.
Xuntian Gate is the emperor's sword.
The emperor's sword is a sword.
In order to make the people of the world be blessed,
how can we not enjoy it?
Today, you helped me.
There will be many people who will rely on you.
This is the meaning of Xuntian Gate.
Xiao Ren, if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't even think about when I can return to this sunny place.
Ah Zhao, I know better than anyone what you're carrying in your heart.
You can come back now.
I just don't want you to be a part of the evil.
Have you decided to stay?
I've decided.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Xuntian Gate still has some official business. I'll go back first.
Yes, official business is important.
So he did so much for me.
I'm sorry.
He did so much for me.
Shaoyao,
is he injured?
He's been injured for three days.
Don't worry.
The Ling Manor was confiscated.
His Majesty is the one who's willing to take it back.
I heard that the report of King of Nanzhao's arrest
must be to take back the house
so he's in a hurry to catch King of Nanzhao, right?
I understand what he's doing,
what he's thinking.
Miss,
you don't have to worry about it.
A few years ago, you picked up a wounded pigeon
and took good care of it.
One day, the pigeon flew away.
You just went there.
The pigeon spent the most difficult time with you.
You told it to stay.
But the master said
he was too sleepy to see it.
So he let it go in the good weather.
But do you know?
The pigeon came back that night.
Because it thought
the master was at home.
I think for a pigeon,
flying to the sky and returning to the court
are not conflicted.
Miss,
the one who truly loves you
will choose the path you choose.
A'Zhao,
I didn't take this house
to put you in this place.
If you have any place you want to go,
do what you want to do.
I'll be here
if you want to come back.
Do not be afraid.
He never my enemy.
Neither once he taught me to be embarrassed.
We are the same kind of people.
Something's wrong, Miss Lu.
The Chief Xiao is seriously injured.
Commander Ling asked you to go and have a look.
What?
I...
I haven't had the time to tell you how I feel.
Please don't send anything!