We've got the evidence.
Why bother planning any further?
Let's just go straight to the police.
Well…
this involves the Uathepa family.
If we go to the police,
we could get into trouble.
Your family is influential.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for.
But he's your boyfriend.
Can we really make a difference?
Well, the evidence from Pam
leaves no room for doubt,
and we owe Bee our thanks
for her sacrifice.
We must do whatever it takes
to condemn the Uathepas.
- But…
- Bee, don't be afraid.
I'll protect you.
DALAH: DEATH AND THE FLOWERS
We're moving forward
with the investigation
based on all of the available evidence
to hand,
and we're very close
to finding the perpetrator.
At this opportunity,
I'd like to urge Dr. Narisa Tangsinsup
to turn yourself into the authorities.
In this way, you can prove your innocence.
If anyone is harboring her
or detaining her against her will,
then I am advising that person
that you are breaking the law.
So if you are watching,
you must release her immediately.
- Sir?
- Go ahead.
You're saying Dr. Narisa
is another victim?
That she's been kidnapped?
We're unable to confirm that just yet.
Pardon me, sir.
Sir, someone wants
to identify the offender.
This way, sir.
Take it from here.
Sir, wait!
Excuse me, sir,
can you tell us what's happening?
I've known from the start.
That woman hates Uncle Ohm.
They had a big fight once,
and she almost called off the wedding,
but he wouldn't let her.
What fight?
Uncle Ohm was using Narisa.
I can tell you, truthfully, he's a fake.
Our family propped him up
as some sort of respectable figure,
but he's actually a cad.
He did shitty things to countless women,
and Narisa found out.
- Off the record.
- What?
You said you wanted the truth.
This is the truth.
Keep typing.
So you think Ohm died
because of a jealous act?
I'm sure of it.
And revenge, very likely.
He just used Narisa
to polish up his image.
To polish his image?
Yes, to seem respectable and so cool.
His feminist campaign,
all the punchlines and so on.
There's one last thing
I'd like you all to think about.
If you want something said, ask a man.
If you want something done, ask a woman.
His fans screamed for him without knowing
he didn't invent any of that.
It was Narisa.
She was his brain and his wallet.
But in reality, she did it for herself.
She backed Ohm to push through a law
so he could build a shopping mall
over Uathepa Square,
raking in billions
without anyone daring to stop her.
All because she wanted
to prove herself to her father.
She thought helping him
would put her in the limelight.
But that didn't happen.
We've talked about this!
You can't run this campaign
unless the party accepts me,
and I want credit for my contribution.
You can't claim it as your own!
And what's this?
You said it once on stage,
then again in an interview.
You know what?
I didn't even come up with that quote.
I took it from Margaret Thatcher.
Risa, when a man
speaks the word feminism,
it's seen as cool.
But when a woman says it…
it's hysterical.
Shit.
Lately,
she's been living with him in hatred.
She stuck through with the engagement
because she wanted Uathepa Square.
Guess she couldn't take it anymore.
That night…
it must have been her last straw.
Uncle Ohm started insulting Narisa,
accusing her of trying her best
to ruin his political career
and the reputation of his family.
What?
He pushed her around.
What the hell, Pam?! Hey!
Why did you mess with my girlfriend?
Fuck your fake feminism!
I did respect her.
I let her ride me because she was weak.
Fuck you!
Ow!
Why don't you ask her
if she prefers your cold finger
or my warm rod?
I tried to stop them.
That's how I got these cuts.
Narisa did it.
Kris told me a different story.
And you believed what he said?
Kris might have something going on
with Narisa.
Something?
Pam, do you know where Narisa is hiding?
Useful information.
Pam.
Pam!
Well?
She said Risa did it.
So if we find her, Pam could be a witness.
Maybe, but I'm not convinced.
Pam seems suspicious.
Why would she lie?
Beats me.
But I'm confident
we'll find Risa pretty soon.
Hey, Pop.
From the clip I got from the hotel,
and from what Pam told me,
there may be other suspects.
This could be especially so
if Pam's claim about Ohm's history
with various women turn out to be true.
You shouldn't listen to that girl.
She's a troublemaker.
The family's black sheep.
Just before,
you said Pam had no reason to lie.
Damn it, Montree.
You're a man of the world.
You know how men are.
Ohm wasn't any worse
than the rest of them.
You better focus on finding Risa.
Have you got that?
Okay?
Back to the murder now
of Mr. Anusorn "Ohm" Uathepa.
It looks like "Big Montree"
is trying his best
to track down the perpetrator.
From a political standpoint…
Hey, have you been following
the Anusorn murder story?
- …likely to deprive society…
- Hey!
…of new generation choices.
Yes?
Anusorn was still so young,
don't you think?
Here.
It's all here.
FLORAL DESIGNER CONFESSES
TO BEING AT CRIME SCENE
Believe me,
now that Montree's in charge,
he'll catch the killer real quick smart.
You know Chief Montree?
Of course. He's handled
all kinds of high-profile cases.
Like that Madam X case.
Have you heard of it?
That was almost 30 years ago.
A Western woman died, and there was
an X-shaped cut on her face.
Once Montree got involved,
he found the killer right away.
MADAM X
Madam X.
Uathepa Street.
"Ikebana" derives
from the Japanese "ike" or "ikeru,"
meaning "to keep alive" or "arrange."
And "hana" meaning flowers.
Together, it means arranging flowers
or giving life to them.
- Originally…
- Psst!
Hey.
Japanese monks arranged flowers
for religious purposes.
- And then later--
- Come quick! Now!
And then later…
Miss, you shouldn't let
your boyfriend interrupt.
Otherwise, we won't get anywhere
with the lesson.
Delivery boy, not boyfriend.
Please excuse me.
Please start your arrangements.
Delivery boy?
Hasn't your six-star hotel
taught you any manners?
But this is important.
Nothing is important
when you're arranging flowers.
- But… What?
- Come.
What? No, I'd rather not sit.
Hi.
And centuries later,
flowers took on a more significant role
in various rituals,
and to many individuals,
became a symbol of faith.
- Miss Dalah, excuse me.
- They became a part of people's lives
in ceremonies and traditional practices.
I told you this is very important.
You have a death wish?
It is the mere essence of Ikebana's way,
which reflects the profound interplay
between mighty nature and humans,
mere cogs in its expansive machinery.
You might well wonder how such a concept
is conveyed through flower-arranging.
We do this by creating a dialogue
between various elements in the vase.
Try to angle them towards one another,
or set them apart.
Hm.
Explore different heights.
Leave some spaces empty.
You're not just arranging flowers,
you're imitating nature itself.
Try to remember
the things that I told you.
The essence of flower-arranging
is to give life to flowers.
It's a very noble pursuit,
but what does that mean?
It means we're giving life
to what is dying or already dead
through our various arrangements.
In other words,
we're prolonging the beauty
of what has passed
for as long as we can.
For you, miss.
This Sarath guy is cute.
He kind of suits you.
You think "cute" suits me?
Well, he is useful.
- At this opportunity…
- Useful for your work or for your heart?
…to turn yourself into the authorities.
If anyone is harboring her
or detaining her against her will,
then I am advising that person
that you are breaking the law.
So if you are watching,
you must release her imme--
Your friend is really good at hiding.
My neighbors are excellent busybodies,
but no one's caught wind of anything.
Narisa's trying to figure out what to do.
She won't need your room much longer.
Oh, it's not really any bother.
It's hard to find
high-quality tenants anyway.
Well, for now, I'll just continue
keeping an eye out for her.
An eye out?
Ta-da!
My dear Jerd proudly presents…
There's still so much
I don't know about you and Jerd.
Well, Jerd's a bit of a tech geek,
to put it mildly.
Ah, here comes our protagonist.
Sooner than I expected.
Miss Risa.
It's me.
MISS DALAH
Noomnim, what's wrong?
Well, Miss Risa is--
Is what?
Hang up.
There's no need to make them worry.
Misunderstanding, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Miss Risa,
you almost gave me a heart attack!
Why did you go out?
Nobody saw me.
Where did you
get that cigarette from?
What are you now, my prison warden? Hm?
I'm sorry. I'm just worried.
I found it in this room.
Miss Risa, you must take care of yourself.
Everyone's worried about you.
Not everyone.
Believe me.
That bitch used us.
When will you get it, Xinxin?
But Pam, it's you who started all this.
I was just angry, okay?
She used our trauma
as leverage against Uncle Ohm.
She didn't even care
about who'd get hurt the most.
That bitch
might have actually killed Uncle Ohm.
But Kris told me Aunt Risa's hiding
because she thinks you did it
and wants to talk to us first.
What nerve!
Dumping the blame on me.
Can't you see it?
This all happened
because of her selfishness.
Lek!
Lek?
Where the hell are you?
I had to carry these all myself.
So, you don't want
to expose Uncle Ohm anymore?
For what, Xinxin?
We thought speaking out could help,
and look what's happened.
Is it supposed to be like this?
Do we all need to implode to save her?
If we don't speak out,
then what about the other women--
He's fucking dead now.
He can't hurt anyone anymore.
So… you're going to pin it all
on Aunt Risa?
Yes!
Ask Kris where she is, and corner her
until she confesses
that she's the murderer.
What if she didn't do it?
Your mother's right about you.
Stop being so dumb, Xinxin!
We have to do something.
Dalah…
…you know what to do.
When a design doesn't click,
you know what's the best thing to do then.
Keep the best part, and discard the rest.
Even when you're arranging
just one flower…
It's still an arrangement.
This time…
I'm not leaving anything behind.
That's good, if you're sure of that.
Miss Dalah.
Oh!
- Is it beautiful?
- Mmm.
Not bad at all for a rookie, hey!
Thank you.
Do you like it?
Let's register you for the workshop, hey!
I enjoyed it.
I got lost in it, and I forgot why I came.
Ah!
All right, call me when you remember.
Welcome to the voicemail service.
Please leave your message--
Risa can't stay there anymore.
She'll give herself up?
I won't bother you anymore.
Thank you very much for the clip.
Do you think it was Kris who did it?
I know Mr. Anusorn
had more enemies than friends.
It's my job
to give condolences to Mr. Ekapop,
but after seeing the clip,
it's hard for me.
I'll go with you.
Good evening.
On behalf of the hotel,
I would like to express our condolences
for your loss, sir.
More likely you're here
to bill us for the cancellation.
No, sir.
Apart from the fees
of the wedding planner,
there are no charges.
Hm. I thank you.
You don't have to pay me
the design fees either.
Since the wedding didn't happen,
and since Mr. Ohm was found dead
on my property,
it's only right
that I refund my fees to you, Mr. Ekapop.
I didn't ask her for that.
You can be my witness.
Yes, sir.
Oh, we ordered these flowers
from Miss Dalah's studio for you as well.
Thank you.
You didn't have to come all this way.
Not at all, sir.
Our hotel is privileged to have served
the Uathepa family for a long time.
- Sweep up. What are you doing here?
- These flowers are nothing, sir.
- I'll give you instructions…
- Regardless, very thoughtful.
It's our pleasure, sir.
It's the least we could do for you.
If you'll excuse me,
I have an urgent matter to attend to.
Sorry for any rudeness.
Oh, Miss Florist.
You seem deeply saddened
by the passing of Mr. Anusorn.
He must have been very good to you.
Um… yes.
You'd have known him well.
Been here a long time?
Since I was in college.
My grandma brought me here.
Even though
I only met Mr. Anusorn recently,
I could tell
that he was a really good person.
It's unbelievable that somebody
could do that to such a nice guy.
You know,
some people think that it's Narisa.
Don't you think that's impossible?
They were deeply in love.
You can't be sure.
What makes you think so?
You're not family.
That's why you think that.
It's the family
that benefits from Risa's money.
Mr. Ohm wasn't in love with her.
What do you mean?
She wasn't his type.
And what's his type?
Very young.
Young? Like you, maybe?
Equity and equality.
These two words sound similar,
but there's a big difference between them.
In politics,
when we talk about equal distribution,
we're talking about equity.
Equity is when you give Mr. B more
than you give Mr. A
because Mr. A has a more solid…
I'm trying to listen. Focus.
Xinxin.
How was it?
Do you think I'm a decent teacher?
Yeah.
I'll let you get back to it.
We can talk more at home.
At home?
- Ooh, Xinxin!
- Xinxin, at home!
READY FOR THE EXAM?
DID YOU ENJOY MY CLASS?
LOVED IT. I'M REVISING NOW.
OH. JUST ASK IF YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND ANYTHING.
SO MANY QUESTIONS.
COME TO MY OFFICE THEN.
I'LL SEND THE LOCATION.
NOT FAR FROM YOUR HOUSE.
UNCLE OHM
I'M HERE
BUT NOT SURE IT'S THE RIGHT PLACE.
IT IS. IT'S MY PARTY'S SAFE HOUSE.
Hi. Come in.
Make yourself at home.
My secretary just stepped out for a bit.
Something to drink?
Uncle Ohm, are you really free?
Of course.
Have a seat.
Here, drink something.
So, what do you
want to ask me about, Xinxin?
Well, I'm a little confused
about this here.
Let's see.
Right here.
Right here?
Ah, okay, I see now.
This passage is a little confusing.
Pay attention now.
The vocabulary here is rather vague,
so you need to look at structure.
When you…
pay attention to someone,
it's important to look them in the eye.
- You smell nice.
- Uh…
I think I'm going to go home now.
Xinxin! Xinxin!
Xinxin!
What's this?
You have a boyfriend?
Speak! Tell me!
I don't even know what happened.
- Who is it?
- What's going on, Prapha?
Ask your daughter
who it is she slept with!
Xinxin, what happened?
Pa, I was raped.
Raped?!
Who raped you, Xinxin?
Who was it?
Who the fuck was it?!
If this becomes public,
how could I ever face anyone again?
Tell me now!
I'll kill that bastard!
What happened already happened.
We can't go back and fix it,
but it's not your fault, Xinxin.
You're not the first,
and you're not the only victim.
Don't be afraid
of what people will think of you.
Other women chose to stay silent,
but I think you should speak out.
Risa!
What are you planning with my daughter?
Hasn't she suffered enough already?
Xinxin, you're not doing this
for yourself, okay?
Xinxin, remember…
no mothers want people to know
their daughters have been raped.
If your dad finds Risa first,
what do you think he'll do?
How would I know?
No one even knows what he's up to.
Hm.
But he'll protect his sons
more than his daughter, right?
I guess so.
Then we must find her soon
so your father can turn her in.
What makes you think that?
I have to say it?
Say what?
You killed Ohm, didn't you?
I let her ride me,
because she was weak.
Fuck you!
That night, I had had enough.
I could no longer pretend
that I didn't know
what he did to our daughter.
I wanted revenge.
I wanted to kill him.
I wanted to bash his head in.
But in reality…
I couldn't do it.
I was too weak.
Pa won't have to protect us.
We didn't do anything wrong.
But we have to find Risa anyway.
Our daughter must not get mixed up
in their scandal.
Bee.
What's wrong?
Pam, please don't blame Risa.
Why are you protecting her?
She's the one
that put you through all this.
It was you, Pam.
You're the one who actually
sent the clip to people
when I begged you not to.
But you never listen to me.
Bee.
It's the only evidence
that would incriminate him.
You care more about revenge than me.
Not true.
Pam…
because of you, I took the pills.
Not because of that asshole or Risa.
Bee…
Please, Pam.
Let's help Risa.
Bee is right.
I told the police your aunt did it.
Pam, why did you do that?
I just wanted to end
all of this crazy shit.
The clip, Bee's humiliation…
But you were right.
What happened to Bee was my fault.
It's still not too late to tell the truth.
It's Kris.
Okay.
What? Why didn't you say anything?
Kris told me to take you to Dalah.
What for?
There'll be more dead bodies.
Kris also wanted you
to bring someone along.
THIS IS WHAT I MEANT TO TELL YOU EARLIER
MADAM X CASE CLOSED
What's going on here?
Mr. Vibul,
your party is presently involved
in a tight political race.
I believe the party's image is important,
so I trust you'll tell me
everything that might be useful
in Mr. Anusorn's case.
Otherwise, if the shit
happens to hit the fan later…
Sorry for wasting your time,
and thank you for coming.
You told me before…
you knew Mr. Anusorn well.
Of course I do.
I've been living and working there.
Since you graduated college?
Yes.
I don't know anything at all
about Ohm's issues.
But before the wedding,
there was an attempt to blackmail him
by our rival party.
Mr. Ekapop was informed about it,
and he told me that
he would handle the matter himself.
Blackmailed how?
Sex clips?
Mr. Anusorn had a thing
for college students.
Right?
As in not just you?
You knew because you saw him
with many other college students…
who were in the same videos that Pam saw.
You're in one of them, right?
I'm unable to confirm that it's Ohm.
Where are those clips now?
You know where those clips are.
- Spit it out.
- Please relax, Pam.
Jaa is on your side.
Are you, Jaa?
Please tell us… where those videos are.
We've got something, sir.
Here.
Huh. Send a team.
Yes, sir.
- Hello? Anyone there?
- Miss Dalah?
- Open the door!
- Miss Dalah!
Miss Dalah!
- Break it down. Go!
- Yes, sir.
Give it to me.
Go!
Arranging flowers…
is like extending beauty.
Prolonging the life of flowers
that might have wilted sooner,
if left on the plant.
Lamduan!
Throw this away.
Humans are selfish.
We want to preserve beauty
for as long as possible.
Seeking different methods
to prolong the life of what we love.
You have secrets.
And you don't?
Sometimes, we could even
revive something that's already dead,
or someone who's already passed,
through methods that defy nature,
but bring us satisfaction.
All in pursuit of our own happiness.
Hello, Mother.
Hello, Dalah.