The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 16
Consort Jing, how is this pill?
How is it?
I'm not good at medicine.
I dare not say much.
Please call the imperial physician
to check it.
It's okay if Consort Jing has something to say.
Your Majesty,
I think this pill
is a forbidden pill in the palace.
Forbidden pill?
I just need to replenish my blood.
Isn't it too late?
I don't know, Your Highness.
I only know that you need this pill,
so I learned to give it to you.
How dare you!
When did I need this forbidden pill?
How dare you slander me!
I dare not!
I dare not, Your Highness.
This pill is Ling Yun's, not mine.
Ling Yun took this pill to please Your Highness.
I also want to ask for a favor.
So I stole his pill
and came to give it to Your Highness.
I really dare not harm Your Highness.
It's Ling Yun again.
Men, bring Ling Yun here to ask questions.
Yes.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
May Your Highness be blessed with good health.
Get up.
Did you get the pill
that the maid gave to Consort Wan?
Your Majesty,
I don't know about this pill.
I only know that
Cuiwei
was with Aunt Sun
in the herbal medicine bureau.
Then I exposed Aunt Sun.
Cuiwei was also punished to go to the new department.
Since then,
she has been hating me.
She wants revenge.
Ling Yun,
you're not telling the truth in front of His Majesty.
You said Consort Wan was looking for this pill.
This is obviously a gift
that you prepared for Consort Wan.
For Consort Wan?
Where does this come from?
What does Consort Wan need?
This forbidden pill.
Cuiwei,
Consort Wan is a noble consort.
How could you violate the palace rules
and use this to nourish the palace?
You can frame me.
But you still want to slander Her Highness
and ruin Her Highness's reputation.
Please forgive me.
I've always been loyal to you.
I didn't want to slander you.
How dare you!
His Majesty is slandering his colleague.
What crime should you be guilty of?
Chief Steward Wu,
do you think this scoundrel
is slandering me?
Please calm down, Your Highness.
If he really slanders Consort Wan,
His Majesty will be punished for his death.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
I have something to report.
Consort Wan...
Consort Wan only sent
Eunuch Shuiqi
to order me to kill Mingyu.
After the promise was made,
she took me out of the clinic.
Before I poisoned her,
I was discovered by the criminal Ruyi.
Consort Wan ordered me
to kill Ruyi and silence her.
I've confessed all my crimes.
But this forbidden pill
really has nothing to do with me, Your Majesty.
Please forgive me.
I was also forced to do so.
Your Majesty!
I'm a bloodthirsty person, Your Majesty.
I've never seen her in private.
I'm not good at killing people.
Please investigate this carefully.
Your Majesty,
I'm a high-ranking consort.
How could I be involved in this kind of
slanderous servant?
I'm innocent.
I'm a maid.
Although my status is low,
I'm still a noble woman.
The order of the harem
prohibits the murder of maids.
You're killing maids.
How could you
do this to the people?
Your Majesty,
this bitch slanders me.
She's trying to frame me up.
If there's a real evidence,
I'm willing to fight with her with my life.
Please clear my name.
Please give me a good reward.
Your Majesty,
I've already pointed out the murderer.
Please help me
to uphold justice for the dead maid.
Your Majesty,
I remember
that a few days ago,
Consort Wan took the maids
of Chengxi Palace to the new maid's room.
She was so angry that
she wanted to cut Lingyun's tongue.
I think
Consort Wan hates
this maid.
Consort Wan,
what do you mean?
Enough.
Consort Wan,
I'll trust you
since I allow you to assist the harem.
These maids
should be taught well.
You should handle this.
Yes.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'll take good care of
these maids.
This maid
is narrow-minded
and sharp-tongued.
She's a playboy.
Let her come to the imperial study.
I'll teach her a lesson for you.
Your Majesty.
Lingyun,
I have to admit
that you're better.
I didn't expect you to leave the new maid's room first.
Cuiwei,
I've sent you
the last batch of maids a few days ago.
You're good at teaching.
Why don't you prepare
your future career?
You...
You need to prepare your future career.
Don't think
you can do anything
if you're not in the imperial study.
You're a half-man, half-wolf.
Haven't you heard of it?
Cuiwei,
Ruyi is my friend.
You killed her.
Do you think I'll let you go?
The murder scene has been here since ancient times.
This is the heaven's gift.
I've reminded you
that if I send the medicine out,
it can help me get out of the new maid's room.
But if it's you,
you'll lose your life.
Do you think I'm kidding?
You knew
that I killed Ruyi.
Ruyi.
Eunuch Shunxi.
I'll give you
all my money.
I'll follow you from now on.
Please ask for my help
in front of Her Highness.
I promise
that in the future,
you'll be alone.
Whatever you ask me to do,
I'll do it.
I won't break my promise.
Miss Cuiwei.
Your life is
Her Highness' life.
I can't afford it.
I've brought you
some gifts for Her Highness.
Here.
Take a look.
Get on the road.
Your Majesty.
I'm guilty.
What crime?
I bullied Your Majesty.
I hate him very much.
You're a little self-conscious.
You know you hate him.
I got that forbidden medicine
from Her Highness' palace.
Her Highness
probably knew that
I found her stealing the forbidden medicine
to get favor.
So she wanted to kill me.
She tried to make me suffer.
She used the forbidden medicine to get favor.
I know that.
But you designed the little maid
to steal the forbidden medicine
from the imperial garden.
You made the palace restless.
You're so bold.
Your Majesty is wise.
So Your Majesty already knew
that Her Highness planned to steal the forbidden medicine.
You also know that
I used a trick.
At the Spring Banquet,
you almost lost your life
by stealing the sword of the five evil spirits.
I saw you were deaf and dumb.
I saved your life.
I took you out
and sent you to the new storehouse.
I thought you would be calm.
I didn't expect that you didn't know the truth
and dared to plot against me.
I think you're really sick of living.
I deserve to die.
But Your Majesty,
I'm thinking
if I die because
Her Highness used the forbidden medicine,
it would be a disgrace to the imperial family.
So my death
can't be related to Her Highness.
It can't be related to the forbidden medicine.
Please give me
a good death
that is fresh and decent.
Are you using the reputation of the imperial family
to make fun of me?
I dare not.
Then kneel here and think about it.
Think about a new death
that I haven't seen before.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You've been kneeling for a day.
How's the new death plan?
Your Majesty,
I dare not say.
You're not afraid of death.
You dare not say.
Soldiers fight to protect the country.
I'm here to
benefit the people.
The doctor's forbidden herbs
are to save the dead and heal the wounds.
These people let me admire them.
Although I'm just a little maid,
I want to do something useful
so that I can die.
Lingyun,
you dare to compare yourself
with soldiers to protect the country
and the officials to protect the people.
You've never seen a shameless person
as shameless as you.
Your Majesty,
I know
I'm not worthy of comparing myself
with those loyal officials and doctors.
But Your Majesty,
some officials
are too proud
to remember
the grace that you gave them.
Of course,
I should
punish them.
How dare you,
Lingyun,
defame the country
and the officials.
It's a death penalty.
If my death
can help you,
I'll be able to die.
Thank you, Your Majesty,
for giving me
such a good death plan.
Do you think
this death plan is fresh?
Fresh?
It's really fresh
to say that
your life is so important.
His Majesty
Aiya,
you're really getting onwards.
You can't even
deal with a palace maid.
I heard that
you almost got caught
by Jin Yao's Ilsar yesterday.
I see
that you've not been
the indicators of Her Majesty
for a long time,
you've forgotten
what we came into the palace to do.
My Lord,
of course,
Can you keep your position?
How dare you!
Even if that scoundrel Lin Yun goes to jail,
he won't be a threat to us.
Didn't I return to the court as a teacher?
His Majesty is holding a celebration banquet.
You can watch it.
I will make that scoundrel Lin Yun
die a terrible death.
Don't say it so early.
The whole harem
is waiting to see your joke.