(Memory is the only tool
one has against time. - Joseph Brodsky)
♪Morning light♪
♪Dew turns to frost♪
♪Please don't wake♪
♪Her dreamland♪
♪Hopes held close♪
♪Safe and sound♪
♪Free from despair♪
♪The mark on the door♪
♪Stays from a day gone by♪
=The Other Me=
=Episode 2=
Miss Song.
Are you feeling unwell?
I just feel a bit dizzy.
And I have no energy.
That's normal.
You've been in a coma for two months.
Your waking up is already a miracle.
Yuxian.
The doctor said you woke up.
I thought it was a joke.
You're really awake.
Does this hurt?
Hello?
Who are you?
You said Yuxian lost her memory.
Yes.
Her body functions are fine.
She just needs some simple rehab exercises.
But she's lost
her memory.
How much is gone?
Sorry about that.
This isn't my area of expertise.
Regarding this matter,
Miss Song's previous therapist
might have more insight.
Mr. Xia.
Let me explain
the rest to Mr. Xia.
Okay.
Yuxian.
This is Dr. Tian Miao.
You've been seeing her for counseling.
Hello, Miss Song.
Listen to me.
Keep pulling me, and I'll hit you.
Mr. Zhang.
Come here.
Yuxian.
I'm Uncle Zhang.
Do you remember me?
I don't think so.
It's okay if you don't.
You'll remember eventually.
This...
Doctor, thank you for your care.
You don't have to.
Our hospital is part of Song's Group.
We'll do our best to treat Miss Song.
Take this.
Use the best medicine available.
Don't worry about the cost.
Really, no need. You're too kind.
Mr. Zhang, you said
you'd just take a look.
Alright, alright.
Yuxian, I have a meeting to attend.
Let me know what you'd like to eat.
I'll go buy it for you.
I'll bring it next time.
Mr. Zhang is just like that.
Did he scare you?
Mr. Xia.
I forgot Miss Song's evaluation form.
I need to head back.
Okay.
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
Move up a bit more.
Hee.
Coming.
Hee is your assistant.
She's been with you
for two or three years.
Yuxian, I'm Chen Hee.
I need to take my assistant's call.
Hello?
Yuxian, you're finally awake.
You have no idea how worried I've been.
Are you feeling better now?
Hee.
Leave us alone.
Okay.
The doctor said
you should do more rehab exercises.
Come on.
Can't Hee do it?
You're my wife, not Hee's.
We've been married
for three years.
Yet you're still so shy.
But I don't remember.
It's okay.
I'll help you remember,
piece by piece.
(I wonder how Yuxian
and Lu Yuan are doing.)
(Notification: Xiaoxue)
I'm awake.
(Xiaoxue)
How is Yuxian?
(Lu Yuan)
Not awake.
How about you? Any trouble?
(Xiaoxue)
No trouble at all.
I'm doing well.
But with a lot of people around,
it's hard to stay in touch.
(Lu Yuan)
You must be cautious with Xia Qingyang.
Miss Song's memory is still recovering.
If she remembers anything,
you must let me know.
Yes, sir.
I hope Yuxian
recover soon.
She is blessed by fate.
She'll get better in no time.
♪I opened the morning window wide♪
♪And a sunbeam gently streamed inside♪
♪I traced the curve
of your face so tenderly♪
♪With a whisper of flowers in the breeze♪
♪The wind flows freely♪
♪Love takes flight surrounding it♪
♪That's Schubert's Rhapsody♪
♪We'll leave the turbulent past behind♪
♪And forget the lost time♪
♪When we missed the start
of the fairy tale♪
♪We'll leave the turbulent past behind♪
♪Erase the scars♪
♪And rewrite the start of our fairy tale♪
♪Unfold the love, unfold the love♪
♪No more hiding♪
♪As the curtain falls, I'll go with you♪
♪Because love's encore
will always ring true♪