- Hey, what the hell?
- Noom Nim-san, we need to talk.
I will only kiss the person I want to kiss.
P'In, do you want me to bring these documents for Khun Mark to sign?
If the person who brings these documents to him is not you, he won't sign them.
Here's your coffee.
- It's bitter.
- Still? I added quite a bit of sugar.
This is sweeter.
Ting? Did you see Nim-san?
Why are you avoiding my eyes?
What's your answer?
Khun Nim, let me tell you this.
Akitsuki-san is a womanizer.
If you aren't signing them, please excuse me.
Hold on! I told you, I haven't finished talking.
Let go of me!
You don't have any right to do this to any woman!
I truly worry about you,
Nezumi-san. Will you be my girlfriend?
Please kindly take care of me from now on.
‎[Boss, Please Don't Flirt | Oh My Boss]
‎‎♫ Do you think you're the only one who feels this way ♫
‎‎♫ What you feel in your heart ♫
‎‎♫ Do you think that I don't feel the same ♫
‎‎♫ Is it okay to only think like that ♫
‎‎♫ Why are you keeping it to yourself ♫
‎‎♫ Tell me what you're thinking, no need to wait ♫
‎‎♫ I can't see clearly if you love me or if you're just lonely ♫
Everything has turned pink.
Will you be my girlfriend?
What?
Why are you shocked?
I just asked if Boss had already arrived.
Can you ask him to sign this?
Sure.
Will you be my girlfriend?
- What?
- Ah!
Why are you shocked?
I just asked why you did your makeup and dressed up today.
You startled me.
Oh my goodness.
What's going on? Am I distracted?
No, I can't do that. I must keep calm and focus on my work.
Please ask In-san to come to the conference room.
Okay.
Why did Nim-san have to be the person to bring the documents for Khun Mark to sign?
Oh, it was Khun Mark's request.
I didn't know how to refuse.
I was afraid he'd cancel our project if we didn't do what he asked.
But it is not Nim-san's responsibility.
I understand you want work to go smoothly.
And everything you do is for our company,
but it's important to care about your colleague's feelings too.
Nim-san...
helped you even though it wasn't her job,
and you still forced her to do what she didn't want to do?
You two will be working together for a very long time.
I want you to care more about each other's feelings.
I understand.
As for Khun Mark's matter, I will handle it myself.
Yes, Boss. I'm sorry.
Nong Nim, can we talk?
Sure.
Did you tell Boss
that I was the one who asked you to bring the contract to Khun Mark?
I thought we made an agreement yesterday.
But I didn't tell him that you asked me to do it.
Even though you didn't say it, Boss would have known anyway.
I felt really uncomfortable yesterday.
Uncomfortable?
Nong Nim,
do you want to ruin our company's project?
If Khun Mark cancels the project, what will you do?
I don't think not attending dinner with a client will hurt the company.
Nong Nim,
I even trusted you,
but you're extremely terrible and irresponsible.
Am I irresponsible?
Are you saying that to me?
I'm never irresponsible. I always care about my work.
But if there are any conditions outside the scope of work, I'm telling you I'm doing it.
Do you know what I went through?
I was sexually harassed.
What?
And you still want me to go see that man?
You don't even know what he's like!
I didn't know... that something like this would happen.
I'm sorry, Nong Nim.
It's fine.
I didn't want it to happen, either.
I just want you to understand me a bit.
Hey... I-I had no idea what you went through.
If I had known, I wouldn't have blamed you.
Nong Nim, I'm sorry.
I heard that you called out your employee in the middle of the meeting.
You sure are protecting that girl.
She's not an ordinary secretary, is she?
This matter involves the employees in my company.
Are you saying I'm meddling?
You're more serious about her than I thought.
Did you forget about us?
Don't do this.
I've said it before. I don't want to say it again.
Gosh. I'm just kidding.
I'm not that forgetful.
I never forgot about us.
And about that thing you don't want anyone else to find out,
especially that girl,
I also never forgot.
I made you rice balls.
You're better.
Excuse me?
You know how to protect yourself now.
What you said to In-san was very good.
Did you hear that?
I've got savory food.
Do you have any desserts for me?
I don't. I didn't prepare any.
I will go prepare some for you.
You have it.
Here it is.
Have you signed the documents?
Aren't your lips too pale?
You should freshen up your makeup.
And don't you have any manners?
What?
Shouldn't you knock first?
I normally don't knock, though.
And you, don't let me see your lips and face pale again.
I don't like it.
You may leave now. I need to teach my secretary a lesson.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't want Hazobe to know about us.
He has a big mouth.
It won't be good for you.
I'm sorry.
All right.
You should get back to work.
I'll see you in the evening.
What's going on?
You will find out soon enough.
So you asked me if I was free because you wanted to take me to a supermarket?
You make lunch boxes for me every day.
I should get to choose what I want to eat.
Fair enough, but...
Boss!
You should have told me.
Not this one. The other one is better.
- It's the version with fat.
- This is high in fat.
Koji-san.
I don't want pumpkins.
No.
Hello, Akitsuki-san!
Oh, hello Oba-san!
I haven't seen you in so long.
Are you here to shop for groceries?
Oh, yes, I came here to buy dinner for my wife.
What about you? Did you come with your wife?
Oh, no, no. This is Noom Nim-san. She's my secretary.
We ran into each other here.
Oh, really?
- I'm sorry. My wife needs me.
- Okay.
- Talk to you later
- Of course. Bye.
- Nice to meet you.
He's a former client.
Thank you for sending me home.
I took you around until late at night. Your mom wouldn't say anything, would she?
She won't. It's not even midnight yet.
Give me that. I'll help you carry it.
It's okay.
It's no problem, I can carry it.
It's fine. Just give it to me.
It's totally fine.
Give it to me.
Like this?
- Are you sure?
- Give it to me.
It's okay. We can carry it like this.
Boss.
Where have you been? You're home late.
I went to the supermarket to buy some fresh groceries.
Who drove you home?
My boss.
Your boss? Why did he have to drive you home?
I was carrying a lot of stuff. He drove past and gave me a ride home.
He was driving past Ladprao all the way from Asoke?
There were a few of us. He sent my friends home too.
Noom Nim,
those Japanese bosses can't be trusted.
Some of them have family back in Japan and trick Thai women into being their mistresses.
Don't let them disrespect you.
You're exaggerating.
I'm not exaggerating. Look at Aunt Nid's daughter, who lives a street over from us.
Her daughter was so happy she found herself a Japanese husband,
but when she flew to Japan,
she found out he already had a family. She unknowingly became his mistress.
Not everyone is like that, though, Mom.
Don't generalize.
All in all, it's like that, Noom Nim. If the majority are like that,
you should be careful and behave yourself.
Don't get too close to your boss.
Other people may misunderstand you.
[ViperX]
Wow, you're such a good secretary, Noom Nim-san.
You remember your boss likes his coffee sweet.
She's my secretary. It's her job to remember every little detail.
What are the reasons some people keep their relationship a secret?
I saw what you shared on Facebook. What were you rambling about?
Don't tell me you have a boyfriend.
I don't know. He's so good to me when we're alone,
but when there's someone else around, he acts like he doesn't want anyone to know about us.
Don't tell me you're dating your handsome Japanese boss.
- Yes.
- Oh my god!
My dear, Noom Nim! You're contributing to the peace between Thailand and Japan.
Hold on. I'm still not sure how he feels about me.
Why is that?
How about this? Bring him to meet us.
We'll check him for you.
If he's playing you, I'll make him pay.
Should I do that?
How's work? Are you able to adapt yet?
It's going good.
I still have many things to learn, but it's been fun and challenging.
You sound like you're interviewing for a job.
Tell me what you really think.
Well...
You seem a bit tense whenever you're with me, Nim-san.
Are you afraid of me?
What did I do to make you afraid of me?
That's not it.
Thai people always say "no" and "nothing" when asked a question.
It's annoying.
Trying to change this kind of habit is a fool's errand.
Is there anything you want to say, Khun Rena? You can be direct.
Fine. Then I will ask you directly.
You and Koji are dating now, aren't you?
Forget it. You don't have to answer me. It's your private matter after all.
I would answer that,
but... I...
- I...
- It's okay. I can tell from your reaction.
On the one hand, you're so happy to date a perfect man like Koji.
But on the other hand, you're not confident about him, right?
Oh, Child,
do you know him well enough?
There are so many things you don't know about him.
Koji is more dangerous than you think.
Oh, Child,
do you know him well enough?
There are so many things you don't know about him.
Koji is more dangerous than you think.
Boss.
Yes?
Are you free this evening?
Yes, I'm free.
What do you want me to do?
I'm going to see my friends.
Will you come with me?
Sure.
I would go anywhere if I got to go with my Nezumi-san.
Okay.
- Hello. Dubai Luxury is pleased to welcome you. You may enter.
- Thank you.
Where are your friends?
Over there.
I'll take the bald guy. I want to lick his head.
- They're not here yet!
- Oh, there they are.
You finally got here.
Hello, Akitsuki-san.
- Hi.
- Hi. Please have a seat.
Excuse me, can we have another plate? Thanks.
- I'm Poppy.
- I'm Meow.
- I'm Pinn.
- I'm Poppy.
- I'm Meow.
- That's enough.
Last time I was wasted, I didn't see your face clearly until now.
You're so perfectly, stunningly, and painfully handsome.
He's so handsome that I'm jealous of you, Nim!
Stop. Don't hit on your friend's man, Poppy.
Please make yourself comfortable.
By the way, Khun Koji, you speak and understand Thai, right?
Yes, I do.
Oh, he does! So smart. That means you've been living in Thailand for a while, right?
- So smart!
- It's been several years.
- Oh!
So are you living here permanently?
- I go back sometimes.
- Right.
Who do you go back to?
Your wife and children?
What are you guys talking about?
I'm sorry. My friends are just talking nonsense.
Sure.
Excuse me while I go to the bathroom.
You fool! What were you saying? He ran away. Look.
I was helping you as a friend. Why are you scolding me?
He's right. We should ask him directly.
This reaction of going to the bathroom means he went to get ahold of his bearings.
He's acting suspiciously.
I'll tell him you guys are teasing him.
Hey!
- What the heck?
- I wasn't teasing him, though.
Boss.
I'm sorry about my friends.
They like to mess with other people like that.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I think they just want to get to know me.
I already told them not to tease you again.
It's totally fine. I'm okay. Don't think too much.
Excuse me while I quickly take this call.
You can go back to your friends first.
It's possible that he already has a wife and children. Don't you think so?
Having a wife and kids isn't as scary as him having a husband.
That's too much. Aren't you two going over the top?
It's true. I think it's the truth.
It's possible.
You guys can stop teasing him now.
You're being soft-hearted.
Don't you want to know what secret he's keeping anymore?
That's right. Nim, we've already discussed it.
There's something suspicious about him.
I'm so sorry. A work emergency came up.
Tonight was so much fun, but I must go.
I'll see you next time.
- Okay, Boss.
- Okay.
I told you. As soon as we questioned him, he found a way to escape.
Right!
What did he mean by fun? He didn't eat or laugh at all.
- What the heck was fun?
- Right. I didn't hear him laughing.
He has to go take care of his work. It's urgent.
What work is that? You're his secretary. Do you know what it is?
Yes, tell us.
- What work is that?
- So?
Complete silence.
See? You're his secretary, but you don't even know.
- It's so late already. What work is he doing? Isn't it suspicious?
- For sure.
He has... a wife.
- He has a husband!
- A wife!
Yes.
Can you come to your senses?
You're loud. It's embarrassing.
Why? We've been loud since we arrived.
I know they're listening to us.
I want them to know what we're talking about.
[Osaka, Japan]
You came back early.
Isn't it unusual for you to come back so soon?
There's no reason for me to stay.
Didn't you say you would check out Akitsuki's new girl?
You said that, right?
Oh, you're here, too.
I'll get the usual, please.
Yes, Sir.
I met Akitsuki's woman already.
What do you think? Was she like what I told you?
She's more ordinary than I thought,
but there's something unexpected about her.
What's more unexpected is Akitsuki-san.
What? Does that mean the rumor is true?
Yes.
Will you not do anything about it?
An innocent girl like her
won't be able to do anything if Koji is not there to protect her.
She can't beat me.
Relax.
I know you're worried,
but she's just an ordinary girl.
Am I worried?
The one who should be worried is you.
You can't even handle a simple girl.
I tried my best.
I did it for you, Rena-san.
Is that so?
Then from now on, you don't have to try to do anything for me anymore
because I don't need your useless attempts at trying.
He came all the way here.
Shouldn't you be nicer to him?
It's not necessary.
I no longer want to give him any false hope.
Well, these documents you sent me, can I give them to the president?
Yes. Please do.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Is something the matter, Nezumi-san?
It's nothing.
Your mouth says no,
but your eyes say yes.
I've told you before
that if you're curious about something, you should ask me.
I'm curious.
About what?
Are we really lovers?
Why are you asking that?
Because I can't guess your emotions.
Sometimes you're good to me, sometimes you act like you don't care about me at all.
I feel like I'm just your secretary.
I honestly don't know what to do.
Did I make you overthink that much?
I'm sorry, but I feel really uncomfortable.
Like last night when you left saying you had work,
was there any work at that time of night?
Also, I'm your secretary. Why didn't I know anything about it?
I really left for work.
It was urgent work that came in.
I saw you were having fun with your friends so I didn't want to bother you.
Besides, it's outside working hours.
I see.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Making someone who's worried, not worry.
But we're in the office. Someone could come in.
We will be fine. I told them not to come in.
I'm sorry.
Are you still angry?
Yes.
Lately,
there have been many things I've had to worry about. I'm tired.
Are you tired?
Yes.
Can you hug me? So I can relieve my tiredness.
Those Japanese bosses can't be trusted.
Some of them have family back in Japan and trick Thai women into being their mistresses.
Don't let them disrespect you.
Did your tiredness go away now?
Almost.
What can I do to relieve your tiredness?
I can't do that. We're in the office.
Please. I just want to be close to you.
Please?
Just a little, okay?
- Who's there?
- Good morning.
Nim-chan, are you all right?
Oh, I'm thirsty. Excuse me.
Oh, Nim-chan?
Nim-chan?
Where is she hurrying off to?
Boss, did you bully her?
Wow, you're getting scarier every day.
Why do you hate me so much?
I only asked you a question.
Why did you come in?
If there's nothing, you can leave.
I just wanted to warn you about Rena.
What is it?
She went back to Japan.
It looks like she's planning something.
I don't care what she's doing.
Boss, it will be good to be careful.
He hasn't replied for two days already.
I should send him a complaining message.
[What time is it in Korea right now?]
Oh, I knew it. There's no smoke without fire.
There must be something between Boss and Rena-san.
See? It feels so good holding hands like this.
What kind of first date is this?
Are you bringing me here to buy a mobile phone?
Our first date begins after this.
The souvenir I've prepared for you is still in my room.
This was your plan to trick me into going to your place.
Boss, what are you doing?!
Koji-san, there's a mark!
Noom Nim, are you home already?
What's wrong with your neck?
♫ Even though I love you more than anyone else ♫
♫ I don't know why I didn't dare say it ♫
♫ Although you're the only one who loves me the most ♫
♫ I didn't let you know or assure you ♫
♫ To someone who isn't good enough ♫
♫ Someone who disappointed you ♫
♫ Would you be able to forgive them? ♫
♫ One thing that I just realized ♫