(E Ji Ah)
(Kang Ki Young)
(Oh Min Suk)
(Queen of Divorce)
(Seongwoong General Hospital)
Gosh.
Are you awake?
Are you okay?
How could I be?
Gosh, the pillow here is nice.
I found you passed out in my house.
I see.
- Gosh. Wait.
- What is it?
What's wrong?
- Prosecutor Park Jin Woo?
- Yes.
Both of our houses were ransacked.
I bet it has to do with restoring
the data from the phone...
or the video of Pastor Cheonji.
Prosecutor Park won't answer your call.
What?
Prosecutor Park got a
job at Chayul Law Firm.
What?
Noh Yul Seong must have
raided our houses...
in case we had any copies of the data.
I see.
I'm sorry. I trusted my friend too much.
Look what happened to me. I'm
here because I trusted my husband.
Gosh.
I'm the one who was trapped
in the prison of trust.
This is awful. You hurt your right hand.
I want to watch an action movie.
(Action)
Wait. No. I want to watch a comedy movie.
Romance. Romance sounds good.
(Ro)
Are you sure you can't use your right hand?
Let me.
Right. What was the title of that movie?
In the movie, Jesse and
Celine meet in Paris.
We watched that movie together.
You mean...
"Before Sunset?"
Yes. That's the one.
They also met after nine years. Right?
I want to watch that movie.
Watch this drama instead.
People say it's good.
- I'm leaving now.
- Wait.
What should I do when I finish the drama?
Close the laptop like this.
So I closed the laptop like this.
Let's go out.
Forget it. I can go alone.
No. I want to get some fresh air.
Can you get my shoes?
(Episode 8)
We won't be able to investigate
Professor Seo's further, right?
I'll start at square one.
I'll look for evidence that
Na Yu Mi's death was homicide,
not suicide.
- What if you find it?
- I'll demand for a reinvestigation.
I can use Na Yu Mi's case to
investigate Noh Yul Seong.
Then it might lead me to
Professor Seo's case too.
Right. Before I do that, I will have to...
watch a movie first.
- Get back inside.
- Okay.
Right.
You should sleep at a hotel tonight.
- What?
- I doubt you can sleep at home.
You easily get scared.
Who says I easily get scared?
Says you. You get scared easily.
Don't act like you don't.
(Park Jin Woo)
Did you throw that away?
You were too lazy to
throw this away, right?
I didn't find anything...
on the security footage from both houses.
The police officer who was
investigating dropped the case too.
Nice. I knew you were good. Why
couldn't you be like this before?
- Focus on Kim Young A. What's this?
- Yes, sir.
You can go now.
What's this?
My gosh. The chairwoman
went on and on about...
how you had to be the next
party representative...
no matter what. She
avidly advocated for you.
I'm grateful for the support.
That's why I prepared that for you.
This pastor is known as
Kim Young A's mentor.
Was this true?
Can you look at the next photo?
It gets more interesting.
This man, Pastor Cheonji, is
a cult leader, straight up.
He says he heals people with
superpower or something.
Oh, my.
Is Kim Young A a believer of this cult?
Even if she isn't, I doubt that...
she can neither accept
nor deny her connection.
Her husband is an actual
believer of this cult.
(Cheonji Dongsan)
Gosh. You know, I have a
hunch about you these days.
You've been going on blind dates, right?
So you're not blind today.
- What?
- You know,
you ought to discuss stuff
like that with the expert here.
I'll go and get some coffee.
Iced Americano, right?
No. I want chamomile.
A certain someone is
making my heart flutter.
Did you read Kim Young A's news article?
What?
(Kim Young A)
("Pastor Cheonji Was Indeed
Kim Young A's Mentor?")
There's even a controversy about
Kim Young A's faith in a cult.
Did you leak the photo?
Why would I do that?
I had no idea he was a cult
leader when I took the photo.
This all worked out.
You must announce your divorce now.
As long as we get a divorce,
no one will care if I'm a believer...
of his religion or not.
What about the children?
They are mine, anyway.
They don't concern you.
You should tell the truth.
"I'm not the believer. My husband is."
"He's asking me for a divorce."
"But I'll do my best to overcome it."
How will my children face the consequences?
They already know, don't they?
But exposing this to the world
will be a different story.
I will avoid doing anything
that might affect my children.
Can you please make this
divorce thing go away at least?
Hey, Ms. Lee. What's wrong?
Ms. Kim. I mean, Lawyer Kim. I...
How dare you communicate
with her behind my back?
Why are you coveting my precious grandson?
She's done nothing wrong. I asked her...
Bring Seo Yun.
- Listen to me, Seo Yun.
- Seo Yun.
Do you know why your parents got a divorce?
Your mother abandoned you
because she's with another man.
Ms. Cha!
Remember what I said.
You'll understand it when you grow up.
Seo Yun. That's not true.
Mom.
Why are you crying?
Take him with you.
Do you get it now?
The more you get in our ways,
the more I will provoke Seo Yun.
This is my warning.
(For customers only)
(Mom)
The number you dialled does not exist.
Please check and dial again.
Mom.
How am I going to protect Seo Yun?
(General Ward A)
I thought I was going to starve
to death while waiting for you.
Thank you.
- Gosh. You must be his wife!
- Pardon?
You guys don't look so young.
You must hurry up and make a baby.
Yes. I'm trying.
That's not going to cut it.
- You must try harder.
- Harder.
- Yes.
What just happened?
Well, she kept saying I should
hire her as my caregiver.
I told her my wife was taking care of me.
Why is that me?
I never specified who she was.
Did we look like a married couple?
- I'm hungry.
- Gosh.
All right.
I at least make you laugh, don't I?
What?
It says so on your face. "I'm troubled."
As for Ms. Kim Young A,
she won't budge because she
doesn't want to hurt her kids.
I bet you two saw eye to eye.
That must be the reason
behind your trouble.
What else could it be than the children?
Let's keep trying and find the
perfect solution for Ms. Kim.
We must try harder.
(Incoming call)
- Hello.
- It's about Pastor Cheonji.
Talk to my secretary, please.
Wait. I know that your
husband is a believer there.
Because a successful businessman
was a believer of the faith,
my wife believed in the
pastor and went there.
But it was a total cult.
She's neglecting our
laundromat and our children.
Who is this?
(Dry Cleaning)
- Is that the place?
- Yes.
(Dry Cleaning)
Give me back my wife!
Honey!
(We specialize in clothing repairs.)
They forced me out.
They used physical force to kick me out.
(Hanjoo Party)
(Party Representative Kim Young A)
(Member of the Supreme Council, Ha Hyun Ho)
Keep going.
Well,
the husband of Representative
Kim also goes to that church.
It was a cult.
I lost all of my money
and wife to the church.
My family was ruined.
This is so unfair. It's so wrong.
What is this?
That's what I would like to ask you.
What have you been up to these days?
Given the recent events,
take responsibility as
the party representative.
Hand them out.
- What's this?
- What?
- Right.
- What is this?
- Oh, my.
- I can't believe this.
Take responsibility instead of
trying to cover this up with money.
- How will she face the consequence?
- How could she do that?
This is a big problem.
How will she fix this?
("Why Did Kim Young A Hand
Him the Shopping Bag?")
The husband of the laundromat closed
down the shop and disappeared.
- What?
- Talk about an odd coincidence.
Yes.
What was in the shopping bag?
She bought a Swiss roll for his children.
Let me see the photo.
Okay. Can you hold it up?
Can you see it?
Something is off.
Right? It's as if they were
waiting to take this photo.
I'm sure someone is
behind this whole thing.
- Did you hear that?
- Yes.
How are you feeling?
I can use chopsticks with my
left hand pretty well now.
I'll get discharged soon.
- Don't exert yourself.
- Okay. Have a good day.
What's the hurry?
- Pardon?
- What?
Let's find this person.
The one who leaked the photo of Ms.
Kim and Pastor Cheonji.
And the one who leaked the photo
of her with the laundromat owner.
In my opinion, it was
done by the same person.
I'm craving caffeine.
- Open the glove box.
- What?
Did you put some in here
because I said I liked this?
No way.
It's tastier because you got this for me.
He's out.
Go.
The first-term assemblymen of
Hanjoo Party declared today...
that they opposed Kim Young A
running for party representative.
Sir.
How did he find me here?
How did you find me here?
- What? You startled me.
- You jerk.
You. You're dead meat today.
You jerk. I gave you the pictures.
How dare you use them like that?
The photo at the restaurant
and the promotional photo.
Exactly. Why did you say that
Kim Young A wasn't a believer?
Why did you jabber that
nonsense, you old man?
- I can go inside, right?
- You piece of trash.
Gosh, that hurts. Darn it.
It hurts.
That jerk.
You jerk. I gave you the pictures.
How dare you use them like that?
You used the restaurant and
promotion pictures like that?
They were best buddies,
but they're fighting now.
I thought he would be
using Kim Young A instead.
Noh Yul Seong is playing it smart.
You piece of trash!
Stop! It hurts.
Just a moment. Gosh.
Yes?
How are things moving there?
Things moving?
Aren't you supposed to
be curious about me...
who you left out on the road?
I get it. But...
providing information
is part of our contract.
Okay? Hello?
Is there anything new to share?
There's nothing new as for now. But...
can you really believe...
I'm keeping my contract duties?
I'm starting to get confused about who's...
on my team.
Gosh.
Kim Young A must resign!
- Resign!
A cult is nonsense!
- Nonsense!
Kim Young A must resign!
- Resign!
A cult is nonsense!
- Nonsense!
Kim Young A must resign!
- Resign!
A cult is nonsense!
- Nonsense!
- Kim Young A must resign!
- Ms. Kim Sa Ra.
- Resign!
- A cult is nonsense!
- Let's talk as we head inside.
- Nonsense!
(Ambulance only)
You can't be like this.
Once the results come out...
I will discharge the patient!
Discharge?
We will not discharge him. I apologize.
- What's wrong with you? Move away.
- I heard he had a bloody stool...
- and got here in an ambulance.
- Move!
- Gosh.
- It hurts so much.
- It hurts.
Let's get on the bed, Sang Hoon.
I'm right here.
Be careful. Just a moment.
Take it slow. That's it.
Goodness.
Why are you being like this again?
Have you been skipping out on your pills?
Dad took the pills from me.
Again?
Why are you stopping our sick
child from getting treated?
The pills are getting in the
way from the pastor's prayers.
That's why he isn't getting better.
Sang Hoon can't get better
without any medication.
Don't just be saying things
because this isn't your business.
Honey.
Don't stick that in him.
(Emergency Medical Center)
- Hello?
- It's me.
In the law of child welfare,
isn't there something
related to religious beliefs?
Oh, was it Article 17?
There's an article that
states that if a minority...
is stopped from being treated
due to religious beliefs,
it can be seen as child abuse.
Right. That one.
Is CEO Yoo Min Chul guilty of that?
Then even termination of
parental rights is possible.
That means Kim Young A...
can legally adopt the kids, right?
Mom.
Get a divorce with Dad.
Then...
I won't be able to live with you.
You know that.
It's just so embarrassing...
that my dad is someone like that.
You don't have to feel
that way in front of me.
Aren't we in the same family?
Don't you know what I'm saying?
You should leave our family!
I...
was always worried if
you two would get hurt.
But you're always worrying
about me, Sang Hee.
We can't leave each other.
We're always so worried about each other.
How is that possible?
Dad and the two us...
are of no help for you.
I will take good care of Sang Hoon.
(Seoha Medical Center Seoul Hospital)
Dad.
Is the pastor more important to you...
or are we more important to you?
We are nothing compared to him.
The pastor is someone who is way above us.
Taxi!
(Vacant)
Someone who has a bigger
ambition than their competence...
(The generation-changing
Hanjoo Party of the nation)
is bound to cause trouble.
That's why I distanced
myself from Noh Yul Seong.
But I'm going through all the trouble.
- Ms. Kim.
- Yes?
Please take a look at this.
- I will discharge the patient!
- Discharge?
We will not discharge him. I apologize.
What's wrong with you?
- Move away.
- Gosh.
There's no place to hide anymore.
You must address your stance.
Let's change the ending...
to your divorce solution.
You want me to get a divorce?
Even if you get a divorce,
I think I can find a way to
let you live the children.
Will that make you get a divorce?
If that's possible,
Sang Hee and Sang Hoon's
thoughts matter the most.
I think the children have
already made up their minds.
(Together with the people)
- Mom.
- Sang Hee.
Mom.
I can't do it.
I can't live without you.
Of course.
What kind of daughter
parts from her own mom?
Sang Hee came to me.
If the two of you were to get a divorce,
she wanted me to help find a
way to live with her mother.
- You went to her?
- Sang Hoon agreed to it too.
Don't hesitate about getting
a divorce because of us.
Not all families must have
a dad and mom to be happy.
Right.
(Cheonji Dongsan)
Is Kim Young A a member
here with her husband?
Have they received treatment
with supernatural powers?
I'll reveal a surprising truth.
The CEO of Chayul came to me recently.
He wanted us to bring Kim Young A down.
Why would he want to do that?
Don't you remember the
previous nominations?
The party representative
did not favour him.
That's why he holds a
big grudge against her.
But since I'm not helping
him with bringing her down,
he's making her a member of a cult...
and trying to bring me down as well.
- Please tell us more!
- Just a moment!
- Tell us more!
- Please!
- Pastor!
Why can't you finish things off neatly?
There's an article sent out
about the false information.
There won't be any favourable arrangements.
It will die down soon.
Do you think Kim Young A will stay still?
What can she do at this point?
The newly-elected members
are greatly against...
her being the party representative.
The party members are
holding protests against...
the family of cult members.
Well, it was a smart move...
to bring out Ha Hyun Ho.
If all of the members of the party
are turning their backs against her,
she has already received a
political death sentence.
What can she do at this
point to bring out a miracle?
(Hanjoo Party)
The candidate Noh Yul Seong
is backing is Ha Hyun Ho.
Let's teach Noh Yul Seong a lesson.
But first, let's teach my husband a lesson.
- Hello.
Thank you for making time
while you're all busy.
I do not believe in that religion.
However, my husband...
Yes. He has fallen into it deeply.
(Press Conference Based on
False Religion Speculation)
Additionally, he has been
asking for a divorce with me...
who has been against that religion.
For a while,
I have been making an effort to
get my husband out of there...
and to stop a divorce. However,
it wasn't enough.
That is why I am here today...
to announce a big decision...
(The generation-changing
Hanjoo Party of the nation)
I am here to announce a big decision.
I will accept my husband's
request for a divorce.
I do not have the parental
rights of my children.
However, I cannot leave them
in the hands of my husband...
who is a big cult member.
To be responsible for my loving children,
I am looking for ways...
to be able to raise them.
(Press Conference Based on
False Religion Speculation)
Thank you.
(Press Conference Based on
False Religion Speculation)
When did you get here?
I got really surprised.
- You were amazing.
- I felt nervous.
(Han Ji In)
Sa Ra, you don't know
Seo Yun's number, right?
Trying calling the number below.
Hello?
Seo Yun.
- It's Mom.
- Mom!
You've grown so much, my son.
I'm sorry. I will call you a lot more now.
Did you like another man?
What?
Is that why you're not seeing me?
No way! That's not true!
Your grandmother wasn't
being true about that.
Really? You're being honest, right?
Of course. You're all I have.
James? Seo Yun?
Seo Yun. Let's keep our call...
a secret between us. Okay?
Okay.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
I miss you!
I get can discharged on my own.
You'll feel miserable on your own.
And you went through
all this because of me.
Nice one, Ms. Kim. You did a great job.
I really envied the support
she got from her children.
All right. Let's go.
It must be nice to head back
to the house of newlyweds.
Oh, right.
It has been a while.
We'll be off.
Don't forget what I told you.
- Newly-weds need the effort!
- Effort!
Besides, the wife isn't young.
What's wrong with how old...
What's wrong?
Don't mind her. Get in.
Get in. No!
Are you still staying in the hotel?
Yes. I can't seem to find a decent place.
Do you want to stay at my place?
What about you?
I'll go somewhere else.
It'll still be scary to be alone.
Right.
- Then should we be together?
- What?
No. I'm just saying... Come on!
Just until you find a place.
You said it's hard staying in a hotel.
So it's Lawyer Dong and me...
staying in Lawyer Dong's house together?
Yes. Lawyer Dong and you in the same place.
Let's not cross the line, Lawyer Dong.
Come on. You're the expert at crossing...
What? I thought you were getting
some clothes from your place.
Head to your place first.
No. I can drop you off first.
That place is a mess.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
You don't have to.
Right.
You just got discharged.
What are you doing?
I can go inside, right?
I'm moving out soon. Why bother?
You have to come in here on
your own until you move out.
Removing the traces will
make you feel better.
Here. Your shoes.
Oh, right. I thought you got rid of this.
I was also too lazy to get rid of it.
I didn't keep it because I was being lazy.
- Well...
- It's the same for you.
I wasn't able to...
get rid of Kim Sa Ra.
Did you like another man?
Is that why you're not seeing me?
The movie we were going to watch again.
It was an open ending.
What do you think happened to the two...
who got back together after nine years?
They both must have returned
to their own places.
Nine years ago, their hearts were burning.
But now, they're at an age
where their minds are burning.
At an age filled with thoughts.
Just like us.
My heart which has met
Kim Sa Ra once again...
is still burning.
Nothing can stop it.
When you're able to free up your mind,
come back whenever you want.
I'll be right here.
I thought there weren't going to
be any miracles for Kim Young A.
Looks like we're the ones
to get the death sentence.
She's a girl the chief
secretary's wife loves.
(Profile)
Come on.
Did you really have to,
in the middle of this?
Did you not hear?
The party members of Hanjoo Party...
must get a call from the
wife to be considered close.
This is the only way to shake up the party.
Were you able to free up your mind?
What?
You must still need more time.
You wanted to have a meeting.
(Pastor Cheonji, Real Name: Cheon Ji San)
This solution...
is based on winning parental
rights and destroying Cheonji.
Shall we have headbands on this time?
I guess not.
To win parental rights,
we must prove that the
husband's religion is a cult.
There are only rumours
and claims about this.
Can't we use the footage
Lawyer Dong got us?
They will just call it
malicious editing again.
That's why we'll go with no
editing and reveal everything.
No editing and everything revealed?
How do we do that?
Let's cast the heroine first.
Me again? What's up?
Ms. Son, try these on.
These?
My sister.
- Take them off.
- Take them off?
Ms. Son.
- Put them on again.
- Again?
- The sister from earlier.
- Take them off?
- What is it?
- Ms. Son.
So you're saying Pastor Cheonji...
won't be able to recognize
her without the sunglasses.
That's right.
You want me to go back there? I'm scared.
It'll be fine.
You'll come with me, right?
Good luck.
Me? For what?
- My goodness.
- Oh, my.
You just need to sit next to Ms. Son.
Sit stylishly as usual.
Now, we need Dae Gi and Bom...
to cast the male protagonist.
Who is it?
Cheers!
- Come out.
- Move, please.
Come out.
Who are you two?
Hello.
Do you think buildings are like noodles?
You were trying to sneakily eat it all up.
That's why you shouldn't
have a second-in-command.
(Certificate of all
registered matters: Building)
Did the pastor send you?
If you want to keep the
building, work with us.
If you want to go to jail
for embezzlement and fraud,
decline our offer.
Which one do you prefer?
As soon as he gets in the car,
make him drink a vitamin drink.
That's the pastor's routine.
(Hwang Vitamin)
If you're not going to pay
for accommodation, wake up.
Gosh, my head hurts.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Prosecutor Son Jang Mi.
Why am I here?
Well,
you became unconscious after drinking this.
- Have this tested for ingredients.
- Yes.
I think he's on drugs.
- Let's see.
Name, Cheon Ji San.
Occupation, Pastor of Cheonji Dongsan.
Your specialty is therapy
utilizing psychic abilities.
- Gosh. Your charge is...
- Prosecutor. Later, please.
I have a bad headache.
My goodness.
Someone has died.
You are now being urgently arrested...
for involuntary manslaughter.
Who are you?
It's a man who has done this many times.
First,
- look at this photo.
- Who is he?
He passed away while you were trying
to remove the cancerous growth.
Your psychic power was too strong.
I guess you can't control it.
Let's do that.
That thing.
Yes. Interrogation.
Prosecutor, it's confrontation.
Yes, that's right. Confrontation.
Let's do that. Let's do the confrontation.
It hurts.
Testing.
- Your earplugs are in, right?
- Yes.
Are you good at acting?
Bom, how's everything?
- Do it well.
- Outside is done with preparation.
Okay. Let's go.
Come in.
My goodness.
- Have a seat.
- Oh, gosh.
Why are you here?
Did a church member who was being
treated by Pastor Cheonji...
pass away?
Yes, I heard about it.
Hey! When did I?
When he removed the cancerous growth,
the heart stopped.
This never happened.
Are you joking?
Seriously, my hand hurts so bad!
Do you think this is a joke?
Stop the fraud. Tell us the truth.
Hurry!
Prosecutor, let's take a break.
Shall we?
I'll take a break.
My blood pressure is soaring.
What's going on?
What are you talking about?
The people who received
treatment from you...
have collectively filed complaints.
The psychic power was so strong
that their ribs were broken,
their back was broken, and
they lost their eyesight.
For goodness' sake.
I don't have any psychic powers.
Others might overhear.
Only you and I know that it's fake.
Others might overhear!
Only you and I know that it's fake!
If I had psychic powers,
my mother won't have passed away of cancer.
Never mind that.
Anyway, the prosecutor...
saw the video where you took
out the cancerous growth.
She truly believed that
you had psychic powers.
Hey!
- Blood from a slaughtered animal.
- Yes.
Where did you put it?
Let's tell them that the cancerous
growth was from that blood.
Then, we can get out of here.
Bring it here.
Yes, I'll tell them to bring it.
Crazy bastards.
There's no such thing as
psychic powers in this world.
What did you say?
You are...
That's not important.
What did you say?
Well, it...
doesn't matter what I said.
Why not?
It matters a lot.
- My goodness.
- Oh, my.
- What is...
- My goodness.
- Why are we in a revival meeting?
Everyone!
What should I do?
Arrange a revival meeting
inviting all the members in Korea.
Don't let the pastor know.
If it doesn't go well,
your building will be done.
A revival meeting. Okay.
Do you think this is a revival meeting?
Pastor Cheonji is a swindler.
Wasn't it your scene of confession?
Crazy bastards.
There's no such thing as
psychic powers in this world.
You should know this. The
police are probably here by now.
No way.
You swindlers!
How dare you try to deceive me?
- Oh, my!
- My goodness!
- Let go! Let go of me!
- Hey!
- Oh, my!
- My goodness!
- It hurts!
- Where do you think you're going?
- I'm not going anywhere.
- You little...
- Don't do this!
- Hey!
Don't we need to help them?
Let it be.
Oh, my.
(Cheonji Dongsan)
- Hurry. Let's go.
- Oh, gosh.
- Come this way.
- This way.
Oh, no. What should we do?
How many members withdrew?
Maybe about 30 percent.
The husband is still one of the 70 percent.
It would be easier for Kim
Young A to win the custody.
Family is something you're born into.
It's about blood relations.
That's what I thought.
But it's not after looking
at Kim Young A's case, right?
It's something you can create
even if you're not born into it.
Creating a family is easier than I thought.
It's nice.
- Oh, my. I dropped it.
- Why?
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
What's wrong?
When we were driving,
where did the coffee cup fall?
Front or back?
It fell backward.
It flew until here.
No.
Something falling out of a
running car can't move backward.
Newton's laws of motion.
Something that was moving forward
will maintain that motion.
The car was moving fast.
So we believe it fell backward.
But actually it didn't.
Right.
So it's correct to fall in front...
of that speed bump I dropped.
But why?
But at the time of the incident,
they said Na Yu Mi opened the
taxi door while it was moving...
and that the driver
immediately hit the brakes.
According to the taxi driver's testimony,
Na Yu Mi should have been found in
front of where he hit the brakes.
But in fact,
she was found about six meters
behind where he hit the breaks.
It doesn't make sense.
The position of the body is...
a bit strange to call it a suicide.
Then, is it a murder?
Who?
The police should find it out.
Reinvestigation.
The brake marks start here,
so Na Yu Mi shouldn't have fallen here...
but here.
Physics give me headaches.
But this makes sense.
Right? Let's reinvestigate.
- First, call the taxi driver.
- Leave after registering the case.
I'll contact you after checking.
That little...
When?
I'll contact you when the time comes.
Were you able to meet them?
A mystery of the mistress of
Chayul Law Firm's CEO's death.
The reporters are interested.
Yes, so?
They can't write if there's no
proof that she was his mistress.
There is a proof.
What?
(Photos)
I didn't want you to see these.
I'm sorry.
They'll be able to write
articles immediately.
Once the articles are written,
the police will be pushed to reinvestigate.
They should be.
I wish the reinvestigation happens.
This is something to celebrate.
- Here.
- My goodness.
Did you only drink here instead of working?
Why is there so much alcohol?
I kept it for a day like today.
I'm proud of myself.
Here.
Congratulations. Finally,
reinvestigation will happen.
Noh Yul Seong is getting
closer to the prison.
I hope your head temperature...
gets at least one degree lower.
I'll get going. Take
this taxi to your house.
I don't think I can.
I told you not to linger around Sa Ra.
You're doubting me and
reporting me to the police.
When are you going to stop this nonsense?
Look.
Hello.
(September 25, 2022, the
day of Na Yu Mi's death)
Hello. You came.
- Congratulations.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
- You're very beautiful.
Na Yu Mi got into an accident.
She committed suicide in the taxi.
- The food is great too.
- Oh, really?
Thank you.
- Give me a minute.
- Sure.
Did she commit suicide?
In the taxi?
I heard she jumped out from
the taxi while it was moving.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Where?
(On her way home. She committed suicide.)
(I'm investigating further.)
(Keep me posted.)
Now you understand the situation, right?
Who would send messages like
that if I knew she was dead?
I'm not the culprit in
your eyes too, right?
If rumours spread, and someone
writes an article about it,
do you know how much you would
need to pay for compensation?
It could be fake messages for an alibi.
Okay. Then, let's do this.
Compensate with money for its cause.
I'll claim damages from you...
enough to ruin you. Okay?
Noh Yul Seong isn't lying.
Noh Yul Seong isn't related...
to Na Yu Mi's death?
(Prime suspect)
(Who murdered Na Yu Mi?)
The divorce papers will
be ready by next week.
It's all thanks to team SOLUTION.
I have a personal desire
for someone like you...
to succeed.
Would you like to expand
your personal desire?
Would you like to work with me?
For the campaign?
If I have three people like you,
I won't need a campaign to win.
Work with me.
I've never thought about it.
Consider it. We can talk about it again.
CEO Noh Yul Seong is waiting.
Let him in.
He contacted me so frequently
to let him meet me in person.
I purposely asked him to come at this time.
I want to repay you.
(Together with the people)
Did we have anything to discuss?
I didn't know you had a visitor.
It's fine. She's close
enough with me to be here.
You can leave if you feel uncomfortable.
I apologize.
I've made a mistake worthy of death.
Why did you when you can't even die?
Please give me a chance.
If you give me the opportunity
to assist your campaign...
in this election, I will
support you from all angles.
You're too late.
I asked for Sa Ra's help...
to join our campaign.
If she agrees,
I'll appoint her as the Chairperson
of the Election Committee.
It's a great promotion.
It's not just me.
I'm worried about you two.
Sa Ra, are you all right?
(Hanjoo Party)
No, I'm not.
(The generation-changing
Hanjoo Party of the nation)
Yes.
Keep your schedule empty for this weekend.
I got an appointment with the
lady I told you about earlier.
Mother, please cancel.
Do you know how much trouble I went
through to get this appointment?
I've got a brilliant idea.
(Hanjoo Party)
You're in my way.
Kim Young A likes you so much.
- It's not your business.
- Are you joining her camp?
Why are you curious?
Seo Yun is coming back soon.
Can I meet him?
Of course.
But we should be a family first.
Let's...
get married again.
(Queen of Divorce)
What's the meaning behind these flowers?
Why would you use Kim Sa
Ra to reach Kim Young A?
You need someone to put pressure on her.
I'm not doing this only for Kim Young A.
Kim Sa Ra and Dong Gi Jun are...
investigating Na Yu Mi's case again.
The mother saw something!
She was a witness for Na Yu Mi's case.
You're not related to
Na Yu Mi's case anyway.
Do you really think so?
Was there a part-timer here?
We found the key man.
Let's catch him now. Noh Yul Seong.
Are you still saying that the
part-timer isn't related to us?
What is this about?
Something you didn't
want to get involved in.
The incident that the mother
knew about when she was alive.
You know, right?