Yes, Dad?
Oh, not yet.
They say we'll have to wait.
No.
No!
You…
can see me?
Yes.
I can see you.
The patient's blood pressure is falling.
Dr. Koh, we're waiting.
All right. Let's get started
with the surgery.
Who permitted him to do this procedure?
Dr. Ahn is crazy.
His blood pressure is dropping!
Dr. Koh, start operating!
The patient will go into cardiac arrest
if he doesn't act fast.
We can't let that happen at this hospital.
Seung-tak, move aside.
You move aside.
Sun-ho. You're my first assistant.
What do you think you're doing?
Dr. Ahn, you're lucky
we're in an operating room.
Get out of my sight.
I'm not letting you operate
on this patient.
Sun-ho, I gave you an order!
Why you, punk…
Dr. Ahn Tae-hyun.
Do you believe you have the right
to treat patients?
Can't you see the patient is critical?
-Get out.
-What are you two doing?
Are you going to let the patient die?
We don't have time.
Let's do this quickly. Scalpel.
Bovie.
Why aren't you holding it back?
Army navy retractor.
Sternal saw.
Tweezers.
-Suction.
-Sun-ho.
-I said suction.
Suction.
Why are you lying in this bed
when you should be operating on patients?
How long are you going to be in a coma?
Dr. Koh is operating
on a tamponade patient right now.
Dr. Koh?
Tamponade is…
Yes. That's the same injury Dr. Cha had.
And Dr. Cha is
still in a coma because of that.
I don't know why Dr. Koh
is handling the same case again
when he's only a first-year resident
and other doctors are here.
It's baffling.
Do something, Dr. Koh!
Cut.
Dr. Lee, you can finish it from here.
I saved the patient as you asked.
Dr. Lee will take it from here.
Follow me outside.
Hey, stop right there.
Seung-tak, come back!
Seung-tak.
You punk.
Can a first-year resident
do that?
No, it's not possible.
It's impossible.
A first-year resident
can do a cannulation at best.
If they're good,
they can barely perform that.
Has anyone ever done this before?
Yes, there was one instance.
When Dr. Cha was an intern.
-Yes, that's right, there was.
-Yes, everyone talked about it.
But how could he?
Seung-tak!
You can see me, right?
Why are you pretending that you can't?
You see my hand, right? You can see it!
Talk to me, you punk.
You can see my hand, right?
Look up at the ceiling.
So what?
Why do you care about that?
You can see me, right?
Remember this place?
You entered my body
and scared Dr. Ahn pretty good.
You…
Since when could you see me? When was it?
I don't know. Ever since that day…
It was just my luck.
Since the day I became a ghost?
Then why didn't you tell me?
Why did you pretend you couldn't?
You never asked whether I could see you.
-Why would I tell you?
-Is it just me then?
Do you also see the other ghosts?
Hope Dr. Cha pays attention to me today.
-Excuse…
-He's ignoring us again.
Like he always does.
Why did I get my hopes up?
I wonder why they're
holding on so desperately
as if they have
a great life ahead of them?
One should know to let go when it's time.
Don't you agree?
-Why you!
-Hey.
That piece of…
-Don't.
-Let go. I'll kill him.
Don't do it.
Because of you,
I almost got possessed by others.
It makes me mad just thinking about it.
Have they stopped bullying you?
You should have been nicer to them.
You were able to see ghosts all along?
From the very beginning…
Since when?
Let's just say you're the 250th spirit
I've seen so far.
Hey, don't label me as a spirit.
Just call me a ghost.
No. That's my prerogative.
I can call you whatever I like.
You're a spirit.
Why can't I call you that?
Fine. Let's move on.
How did you end up seeing ghosts?
I mean, ghosts, not spirits.
That's a private matter.
Hold it right there.
I don't like the tone
you're taking with me.
Hey, punk. I'm a senior doctor.
Does that really matter right now?
Okay. So why did you reveal
your secret now?
-You were pretending until now.
-To save the patient.
I don't like seeing people die.
So that's why you've been using me?
You could see me all along. Why?
You didn't have
anything better to do anyway.
-I did it for your sake.
-I'm so grateful for that.
You wanted to keep me busy?
Did you think I'd be touched
by your kind consideration?
I know how you think, you punk.
You don't know me.
Wait a minute.
Did you go to my place on your own?
That?
I went to see if anyone was there
since you kept calling for "your baby."
Is it refreshing?
There's no one at home
to give water to my baby.
Mandu, I'll come get you soon.
Instead of my baby, I'll take you.
Come here, Seung-tak.
Come here.
I didn't want to see you mope,
so I nudged you a bit.
But you were out to get me.
Do you know Dr. Cha's home address?
So that's why I haven't seen him around.
You're his colleague, right?
Take what he needs.
Make sure you lock the door behind you.
So this is where he spends
the money he makes as a surgeon.
It's a modest apartment.
This is "his baby"? This thing?
Was he dead?
Your baby is a hardy survivor.
Somehow, I saved your life
and also your pet's.
I'm so relieved. So where is he?
Where did you put him?
I rescued your pet
and I don't even get a thank-you?
Then Doctor, where did you
take my baby? Tell me.
Are you asking me right now?
What are we, friends?
You've been asking me questions too.
I don't like your tone.
Now look here, you punk.
I don't like being called "punk."
I was going to bring that up.
You don't know me.
Just call me by my name.
Speak for yourself.
You said the accident was my fault
and being in a coma was my fate, too.
I'd like to punch you in the throat!
You're yelling at me?
I should be the one yelling.
You possess my body whenever you please.
Do you think I wanted to?
I sacrificed my pure soul
when I entered your body!
An arrogant prick like you!
You think I liked it then?
I almost struck my own body.
Your body isn't even that great.
You can't even use your fingers properly.
You're all talk.
At least I can talk like a doctor.
You can't even open your eyes.
How could you say such a thing to me?
I'll never possess you again.
I don't need you, you punk.
I'll let any other ghosts enter my body
except you.
Don't even try entering my body.
I'll smash your soul into pieces.
You keep taking that tone with me!
You bastard. How could you talk like that
to a senior doctor?
People never change.
Even when they're a ghost.
Your husband is no longer
in critical condition.
The operation was a success.
Doctor, my husband will live, right?
Thank you so much. Thank you, Doctor.
-Chae-hee, Dad is going to live.
-Really?
Yes.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
That bastard.
He pretended he couldn't see me.
He talks back to me.
Wait a minute.
He made me do the intubation for him.
How could he?
I don't have the time
to be saving other people's lives.
Hello.
I think that's the patient
Dr. Koh operated on.
I heard he did the procedure perfectly.
-How was that possible?
-He's just a first-year resident.
Unbelievable.
He did the surgery?
Yes, he did.
He did it.
I knew Seung-tak
was a brilliant student in med school.
But he's no armchair expert anymore.
Where did he learn to do that?
Blood pressure looks normal.
Pulse is okay.
-Amount of drained fluid?
It's 200cc.
Did you get the ABGA results?
Did he receive one-on-one training?
That's right. He studied in America.
That's where he learned it.
How's the ABGA result, you punks?
-Did we get the ABGA results back?
-Okay.
In Bourne Identity, Matt Damon's character
is a trained assassin.
And he has expert fighting skills.
Nice. The prognosis looks good.
Looks good. Check on him once every hour.
So Seung-tak must have received training
from the best surgeon
while he was studying in America.
That's how he became so good.
But why did he fumble Dr. Cha's operation?
Hey, Dr. Koh.
Don't give me that angry look.
I came to check the patient.
Patient's blood pressure, pulse,
and drained fluid are normal.
The ABGA results were good too.
I'm waiting. You were the lead surgeon.
So give the order.
Don't look at me.
I'm not going to help you with this.
Are we friends now?
I talked to the patient's family
so could you write up the OP record?
OPERATION RECORD
The operation record?
You don't know how to write one?
How would he know that?
He probably hasn't even seen one.
Dr. Ban says you have to stay
by the patient's side until he wakes up.
You know the reason for that.
Dr. Ahn, you're lucky
we're in an operating room.
Get out of my sight.
I'm not letting you operate
on this patient.
Dr. Ahn Tae-hyun.
Do you believe you have the right
to treat patients?
Dr. Ahn, are you out of your mind?
Why did you let Seung-tak
perform the operation?
-I'm sorry.
-It already happened.
Skip the explaining.
You better handle this.
-What?
-You're lucky the patient lived.
There were other surgeons available
in the hospital.
If anyone finds out
a first-year resident did surgery,
then we're in trouble.
There's already bad press
about surgeons switching places.
You won't be the only one.
This could damage our reputation.
Okay, Doctor.
Did you sense anything strange
about Seung-tak?
What? I don't follow…
What? Never mind.
The fact that Seung-tak performed
that surgery is strange in itself.
Hold on. Does that mean
Seung-tak is a genius?
A brilliant mind?
How does he become a genius overnight?
He was unremarkable during his internship.
An overnight genius?
Out of the blue?
This is the administrative director.
Cameras recorded
the No. 7 operating room, right?
Send me a copy of the footage. Right now.
Excuse me. If you're still around,
let's try to save her.
Since when could you see me?
When was it?
I don't know. Ever since that day…
It was just my luck.
It's uncomfortable being around you.
Could you leave?
That's my patient. I'm not going anywhere.
-If you don't like it, you can go.
-I was the lead surgeon.
-I did the surgery.
-Using my hands.
You can't even hold a scalpel.
You can't brag about that.
You can't treat a patient
in the physical world.
That was below the belt.
I'll pull out your tonsils
and pickle them in salt.
Sir, are you coming to?
Start with obeying commands. Say his name.
Mr. Moon Suk-joo?
-Blink eyes if that's correct.
-Blink your eyes if that's your name.
Mental okay.
Next, check his motor functions.
-Start with his left hand.
-Move your left hand.
Move your right hand.
-Good. Next…
-Do you remember your daughter's name?
Nod your head if you remember.
Your family is okay.
You don’t have to worry about them.
Chae-hee takes after you a lot.
Are you feeling okay?
Can you think clearly?
Dad.
Are you okay, Dad?
Dad says he's feeling okay.
Since when did he
care about patients so much?
He didn't perform the procedure. I did.
I'm sorry.
I had a situation.
I'll be more careful.
Young-min.
Dr. Koh operated on a tamponade patient.
The nurses tell me he did a good job.
He's quite a doctor, isn't he?
Why couldn't he do the same
when he operated on you?
I know.
But what kind of relationship
did you two have?
Dr. Koh says you hated each other.
But his behavior says otherwise.
You think so?
Anyway…
he's peculiar.
He's very peculiar.
I'll be joining your department
as a new resident.
My name is Koh Seung-tak.
Let's save the patient first.
Dr. Cha Young-min.
How did you end up seeing ghosts?
I mean, ghosts, not spirits.
That's a private matter.
How did he turn out like that?
Seung-tak.
You're home?
Did you take a cab?
-What about your car?
-What? Well…
I parked it at the hospital.
I was too tired to drive.
Why? Did something happen at work?
No. You look so pretty today, Mom.
Seung-tak!
Dad!
The patient has a daughter?
Yes, sir. The girl is seven years old.
Fortunately, she was unharmed
in the car crash.
I'm happy to hear
that her dad regained consciousness.
Seung-tak performed the surgery perfectly
and the patient is doing well.
I clean this spot all the time.
I didn't intend to possess
his body yesterday.
But the patient's condition
became critical.
I couldn't allow Dr. Ahn to operate
on the patient.
Tess.
Oh my.
This mosquito.
I'm going to get you.
What are they thinking?
Wonderful, ain't it?
What? What are you doing here?
Dr. Koh. What is it?
I received this yesterday.
Illegal parking?
Someone parked my cars
next to a fire hydrant.
That comes with a hefty fine.
Sorry. I didn't notice the fire hydrant.
You can see the blue car parked nicely
next to the white car.
Now I have to pay a fine.
-Hold on a sec. What's your point?
-My point is that
Cha Young-min is self-centered,
arrogant, and lacks spatial awareness.
On top of that,
he has little regard for the laws.
Luckily, nothing serious happened.
If there was a fire, think about
how serious it would've been?
-A fire?
-Hey!
Let's talk about that later.
-Just you and me.
-You need to reassess your decision.
Would you want to invest
your incredible skills and time
on someone like this?
Bye.
Come back here!
You disrespectful punk.
I said come back here.
Seung-tak! What was that about?
Seung-tak!
-Seung-tak.
-What is that?
He's really weird.
You punk.
How could you talk about me
behind my back?
I said it in your presence.
It wasn't behind your back.
I have little regard for morals?
Because I’m in this state you mock me?
Even when you were in your body,
I didn't have high regard for you.
Look, people make mistakes.
I didn't know I parked
next to the fire hydrant.
And there was no fire.
You recovered your car.
Can't you look at it positively?
Anyway, you found your babies,
so bring my baby to me.
Because you parked my cars
next to a hydrant,
the fine is one million won.
All right. Just bring back my baby.
Pay up first if you want to see your pet.
You're taking my pet hostage?
How can I possibly pay you?
Excuse me. Are you Dr. Koh?
Let me call you back.
What is this about?
I write medical articles
for the Jaemin Daily.
I'd like to learn more
about the operation you did yesterday.
Is it true
that you single-handedly saved a trauma
patient's life in an impossible situation?
"Young heart surgeon at Eunsang Hospital
performs remarkable
open-heart surgery alone
to save a trauma patient."
Even the senior surgeon
can't do that alone. But Dr. Koh did?
"When the lead surgeon
could not carry out the surgery
due to a sprained wrist,
Dr. Koh stepped in
and showed tremendous skill
in saving the patient's life."
Which doctor was it?
They shouldn't have been there
if they were injured.
"A personal tragedy Dr. Koh
experienced in childhood
was the reason why he courageously
operated on the patient."
Do you know anything about that?
What?
No, I don't.
"He deserves praise
for his passion and skill."
"He's a hero and an amazing doctor.
I support him."
I told the staff not to
leak the incident to the press.
What is going on?
This solved the incident in one swoop.
Was this your idea, Doctor?
Did you call the press?
We have to spread news like this.
That's why I'm here.
Geez. You tried to sabotage his career,
but now you're promoting him?
I don't think that would do any good.
There's been a scandal about surgeons
switching places to save costs.
That was about uncertified doctors.
But you're certified.
You're surprising me
with your God-given talent.
Where do I report an invasion of privacy?
"Privacy"?
What? That personal tragedy?
I've done nothing wrong.
No details were divulged.
You can't keep it under wraps either.
So it was a preemptive leak.
And it was a glowing piece about you.
With Dr. Cha out of commission,
we need to groom a new star doctor.
I'm going to blow my top. Calm down.
Three times one is three.
Three times two is six.
Wait, is that correct?
-Three…
-I'm not a specialist yet.
Just a first-year resident.
Then why did you perform the procedure?
-You told Dr. Ahn you would take over.
-I wish I could punch your face!
What did he do wrong?
They were going to transfer the patient.
Which means the patient could die
during transit.
He can't even hold a scalpel right
but he wanted to save the man.
Let me ask you something.
Have you received training from someone?
No way your MBA program
teaches you how to operate.
You got an MBA? For real?
I know grandfather
pulled you out of school
because you were skipping your classes.
You must have learned so much.
The women in our lives…
Yes, Mom?
Yes, Director Koh.
He slammed the door.
That article?
It's part of the plan.
We'll build him up as a hero first.
Seung-tak, is the article true?
You saved the patient
in that critical moment?
Oh my gosh. It's him.
-That's the doctor.
-I guess so.
Oh my. You're so modest about it.
You did the entire operation
and the patient also recovered.
Are you a genius?
I don't think I'm a genius or anything.
Mom,
I'm a little busy.
Can we talk later?
Of course.
When will you be home today?
So what's the plan?
Why are you raising his profile?
The higher you are, the harder you fall.
And that'll cause more damage
when he's the center of attention.
Don't worry.
He'll never
get a seat at the board.
Good morning.
Seung-tak is quite a talent.
He gets attention wherever he goes.
The administrative director
is so good at his job.
Seung-tak was merely helping out,
but he made him into a star.
It's the least he could do.
Besides, Seung-tak is next in line
to be the chair.
I'm so grateful for what he does.
I'm so glad Seung-tak has a cousin
who has his back.
Grandfather must be so happy.
The hospital is in good hands
with both grandsons working hard.
Seung-tak has a hard life just like me.
Enemies coming from all sides.
What do you want?
Let's go somewhere and talk.
We…
are not trying to mug you or anything.
Right, guys?
Just come with us quietly.
Go where?
Hey, young patient.
What? What are you doing?
I'm playing hide-and-seek.
-Hiding from who?
-From my mom.
Go away.
You can't hide like that.
And you shouldn't be
walking around unattended.
You need to go to your room.
Go away.
I'd like to hide too.
Just stick my head somewhere.
Hey there, Mr. Hero.
I've got something to ask.
-About yesterday…
-That wasn't me.
What? Then who was it?
Didn't you read the article?
They said it was as if I was possessed.
For real?
It won't happen again so let's just
carry on like we normally do.
How can you be so sure?
It could happen again.
I made a deal with the spirit.
Really?
Doctor, Seung-jo needs the operation.
Please.
He'll die if he doesn't get it.
That's Seung-jo's mother.
We're discharging her son tomorrow.
Why do we have to?
We don't have a doctor
who can do the operation.
He just needs an artery conduit
replacement in his right ventricle.
Is that hard?
Yes, it's complicated.
It requires CABG.
It's a complicated operation.
And if another doctor
takes on Dr. Cha's patient
and doesn't succeed,
-then it's all on them.
-Doctor, please.
We have nobody else to turn to.
Are all doctors like that?
At times, yes.
She'll have trouble finding a doctor
or hospital that will take her son.
Why?
The medical bill.
Our hospital promised to fully cover
the cost of the operation.
Dr. Cha's rich patients
made donations to the hospital.
That was supposed
to cover her medical bill.
I didn't know about this.
It's a special project. Only Dr. Cha
can dip into the donation funds.
Dr. Cha might be an abrasive person,
but there are times he surprises you.
-He'll reject people…
-Please.
…who use their influence
to get him to do an operation.
He's such a cool doctor.
A special request?
What kind of request do you want?
It's not that difficult.
There's a walnut snack
they sell at Yeongdeungpo Station.
Could you buy one bag for me?
Could you get a DVD for me?
There's this book I want to read.
Only one library has it.
How could I possibly do those things?
Don't you know?
We're in the same situation.
I knew it.
Come on. You have a way to do it, Doctor.
You can enter his body.
So you're asking me to possess his body?
We're in the same situation?
See? I knew he'd turn us down.
What did you expect?
He's an arrogant prick.
Did you wag your finger at me?
How old are you? You're so disrespectful.
-He's…
-Come on. Dr. Cha.
You even saved a life that way yesterday.
So please consider our requests.
Otherwise…
life will be tough around here.
If there's any snack
or dish you want, tell us.
It's not just that patient.
All of Dr. Cha's patients
won't be able to get surgery.
We lose one doctor
and the whole department is in crisis.
The tamponade patient is doing well.
He's out of the ICU.
What's the next order?
You want me to take care of it?
Why did Dr. Cha make Sun-ho
his first assistant that day?
He should've known better.
I found you.
How did you find me?
-Because I have big eyes.
-That's amazing.
What are we doing next?
What do you want to do?
Seung-jo isn't her biological son.
He was adopted when he was a baby.
He had ailments since he was little.
She couldn't afford the medical bills.
Her husband wanted to return the boy
to the orphanage. But she refused.
They got divorced
and she's raising him alone.
Let's play finger wrestling.
All right.
Doctor.
Thank you.
What?
Yes, sure.
Thank you, Doctor.
We found out yesterday
that you operated on my husband.
Thank you so much
for saving his life.
Thank you, Doctor.
Yes, sure.
I'll never forget what you did for us.
I'm so grateful.
So the next order?
Doctor, it's time
for the chest tube squeezing.
The squeezing.
So we'll remove the hematoma
from his thoracic chamber?
What? A walnut snack?
He needs a DVD? That jerk.
What kind of request is that?
What is he doing?
That imbecile. He doesn't know anything.
Now you're making me
do a squeezing procedure?
He can't even do a simple thing like that?
How did he become a doctor?
You told me not to enter your body again.
I did as you said.
Where are you going? Seung-tak!
I've got something to talk about.
What are you doing in my room?
What are you doing?
No, you wouldn't…
Put that back.
I only wore that suit once. It's new!
Hey, you.
Why take it out on the suit?
Put it back when I'm still being nice.
Gently.
You punk! You only have yourself to blame!
Okay!
Okay.
Take it easy.
Calm down.
Seung-tak, I'll do whatever you ask.
What will it be? Tell me.
Shall we go do the squeezing together?
No!
You told me to do it gently.
I just did as you said.
Are you crazy?
How could you be so petty like this?
-I'll punch you in the throat!
-Revenge is petty.
Did you expect it to be classy then?
Dr. Koh.
What is this?
What?
What…
Did someone throw it away?
It's my size.
These are all new.
I bought this at the flagship store.
Damn it. I charged this on my credit card.
In 6-month installments.
That bastard.
He's got big dark circles around his eyes.
OUT
This is my office. Why?
Se-jin.
What are you looking for?
I found it.
Must have come from somewhere else.
What's that for?
To see your dad's chart?
You don't know my password.
Even if you knew,
the device is probably locked out.
Now look here. You can't keep coming here.
The patient needs his meals.
Let go of her!
Okay. Let go of me.
Just take this to him.
You're making it difficult for me…
to give a meal to my dad.
We'll take it to him. Just leave it here.
Did he eat all of the marinated crabs
last time?
It's my dad's favorite.
Of course, he did.
The chairman finished it all.
He relished it.
All of it?
We'll take this to him.
So don't come here again.
You're making our job difficult
by coming here.
Thank you.
If he asks for me, let me know.
Okay.
Sir.
I am not trying to suppress news
about your current state.
Do you have any savings?
Not a lot.
Do you own a house?
-I rent.
-What about your family?
Do you have a single mother
or lots of brothers
and sisters to support?
No, I'm alone.
I'm sorry for asking that.
Do you love my daughter?
You can't answer that question?
Then why are trying to date her?
Sir, I think there's a misunderstanding.
If you're
interested in her because of
her future inheritance, then give up.
She says she won't receive a dime from me.
I see.
If that's okay with you, then marry her.
What?
Se-jin knows the truth.
I'm allergic to crustaceans.
So how could I eat marinated crabs
and be okay?
I won't ask you to uncover the truth.
Instead…
I ask you
to prevent her from coming here.
Why add to her burden
when her hands are full
just caring for you?
What right do I have?
As her dad,
I've only caused her pain.
While you're in a coma,
she's at your side every day.
Good morning.
And she handles patients
in her spare time.
You're not feeling nausea or dizziness?
She realized what condition I'm in.
Which means she'll do something about it.
If those bastards find out
that she knows then…
You know what I'm saying, right?
That doctor is very diligent.
He always does a routine check
four times a day.
I knew it.
That's keeping me from dying.
I don't know whether
to be grateful or angry.
Why add to her burden
when her hands are full
just caring for you?
What right do I have?
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay? Excuse me.
Wait.
It's not your fault.
Both the Chairman and I.
So don't try too hard.
Administrative Director. It's me, Se-jin.
I’d like to discuss
the Chairman's condition with you.
Do you have time to talk?
If those bastards find out
that she knows then…
You know what I'm saying, right?
No, Se-jin…
Your Iced Americano is ready.
Just five minutes.
Let me borrow your body for five minutes.
Hey, Seung-tak.
Is that your answer?
What will you do
if I enter your body right now?
Seung-tak.
Come here.
Hey Seung-tak.
Hey!
This damn boundary.
Seung-tak, come over here.
Let's just talk.
You have time to talk, right?
Just a minute.
I also needed you for just five minutes.
But you ignored me.
That was what you wanted?
When you raised your hand,
I thought you were telling me to go away.
Let's keep it that way then.
This talk is over.
I'm sorry. Seung-tak. I'm sorry.
Seung-tak. Just once.
I'm begging you.
Just for five minutes! Please!
Just once, Seung-tak!
If this wasn't here, you'd be dead.
Come back here! Hey Seung-tak!
Why did you call me? I'm busy.
You're acting weird. That's unlike you.
Is this about the news article?
I don't care about stuff like that.
But why aren't you asking me?
-Ask you what?
-About the tamponade surgery.
You were there.
You would've told me if I needed to know.
You'd say it first.
To a friend.
The doctors in ER are puzzled.
You can't treat a trauma patient properly
but it turns out
you're a brilliant surgeon.
What about you?
Which would you prefer?
Nobody likes a dummy.
Especially, when our work
involves saving lives.
But I don't like
seeing you getting stressed.
Don't overreach.
Don't suffer from cognitive dissonance.
Thanks for the advice.
Yes, Brother?
What is it?
He didn't touch his coffee.
You can have it if you want.
Thanks.
I was a little thirsty. What luck.
You two seemed to be having
a good time together.
Before, you were always beating him.
Sorry?
It's a habit I picked up in med school.
But why?
Did the young doctor do something to you?
Well…
He's indebted to me.
A big debt.
It's just that when I look at him,
I get so bothered and annoyed.
Enjoy your coffee.
Sure.
Well, the young doctor does annoy people
with his attitude.
But he's not a pathetic guy.
I'm a good judge of character.
Trust this old lady.
She's not that old.
What…
What is this?
Neurology department. Building 37.
Code blue.
He's so disloyal. What a mean bastard.
A doctor is coming soon.
It's a cardiac arrest.
Announce a code blue.
Okay.
Well…
how can I take on a patient like that?
Just do things the normal way.
Didn't you see it earlier?
The spirit left my body.
Don't page me anymore.
Okay?
Soo-jung says I shouldn't overreach.
I'm a partying type of guy.
Did they change the bunk beds?
Yesterday, he was a brilliant surgeon.
Today, he's not.
I can't find Seung-jo.
What?
You scared me.
Hey, young patient.
Are you playing hide-and-seek?
I told you,
just hiding your head isn't hiding.
Your mom won't be able to find you
if you hide here.
Get up already. Your mom will be worried.
Doctor.
-What's wrong?
-He's suffering a cardiac arrest.
Administer 1 ml of EPI. Now.
Charge.
Will I die?
Doctor.
What?
Will I die as punishment
for what I did to you?
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey.
Mr. Doctor.
Can't you save me?
It's a V-fib. Get the defibrillator ready.
V-FIB: VENTRICULAR FIBRILLATION
DE-FIB: DEFIBRILLATOR
We're charging.
Charge. 200 joules.
Everybody, stand back.
Your grandfather
hasn't changed his mind yet?
He wouldn't want to
waste a talent like me.
Your succession doesn't look easy.
Family feuds are always the bloodiest.
I wonder why
I'm clinging onto such a jerk.
I'm a doctor. I'll eventually die
whether or not I enter your body.
It's better to be a hidden genius
than a useless moron, isn't it?
But…
I'm not going to die like this.
It's infuriating.
I can't watch people die.
It's not my style.
-We have a deal?
-Okay.
You can only possess me
when it's necessary and I agree to it.
-I'll wave like this.
-I'm not a pet.
Ma'am, you can't do that.
Are you the quack
who saved that bastard's life?
You broke your promise first.
How could you handle the operation
when the other doctors can't?
So you open the chest at once.
You're walking too close to me.
Are you afraid that they'll find out
you can see ghosts?
Why aren't you revealing
what you know, Dr. Koh?
Where is he right now?
Can you hear me? Seung-tak!