Over there.
Slow down.
Aim at that.
Miss, are you scared?
We didn't mean to.
But you two seem to have quite a connection.
Nanny, over here.
Young master, take it easy.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Miss,
are you alone?
I came here with my father.
He said he had something to do
and needed to step away.
So what do you do for a living?
You're hunters from the mountains, aren't you?
How did you know?
You have animal pelts in your bamboo basket.
How do you know we didn't buy them?
There are some scraps in your basket.
Nobody buys those,
but sellers wouldn't throw them away.
Want to try?
Here you go.
Look.
Keep your arm straight.
Relax your shoulders.
Relax.
Ready?
Shoot.
Hurry.
Run!
Hold this for me.
Smell it.
Isn't it fragrant?
It'll be ready to eat soon.
Qin, use this to wash.
What's this?
Soapberry powder.
It removes grease.
This is quite expensive.
We usually just use wood ash.
Give it a try.
Okay.
This works really well.
I secretly took it from my mother.
I'll bring you more in 10 days.
In 10 days.
How did you know?
We've played together for so long.
I noticed that every 10 days,
you come with oil on your hands.
What kind of oil is this anyway?
It's tree sap.
My family collects it.
We make a groove in the tree,
then place a bowl underneath,
and the sap slowly drips into the bowl.
What do you collect the sap for?
To water flowers.
You water flowers with tree sap?
What kind of flowers?
My father says
only our family can know about it.
Why do you go there every 10 days?
After 10 days, the bowl is full.
I need to pour the sap onto the flowers.
So the tree and flowers must be close to each other?
Why don't you make a groove in a bamboo stick
so the sap flows directly to the flowers?
My father says
we must fill a complete bowl
before pouring it on the flowers.
Take me there to see it.
I'll make you a mechanism.
So it can pour itself when the bowl is full.
Then you won't need to go there so often.
It'll save you a lot of trouble.
No way.
My father doesn't allow me to bring others there.
Then how about this?
I'll teach you how to make it.
Awesome!
If it rains,
we can add a bamboo curtain on top to block the rain.
Chong, you're amazing!
Thanks so much for your help today.
I'll bring you meat rolls tomorrow.
Great! See you then.
Young Master.
You've been sitting here all night.
It's almost dawn.
Why don't you get some rest?
I'm not the only one
who can't sleep tonight.
That's great, sis!
Now I'll never get lost again.
And you'll always be able to find me.
Everyone has returned now.
But Zeng Xin is nowhere to be found.
Zeng Qian must be worried sick.
But now the mirage has completely disappeared.
It's not in the sky.
Not in Mirror Lake either.
Even if we want to search, we don't know where to start.
What's wrong with you now?
That one-eyed little beggar of yours may have run away,
but at least he came back.
He shouldn't be hard to find.
What are you so worried about?
What am I worried about?
All the missing people have returned.
Yes.
But he doesn't remember anything.
Even if I find that one-eyed beggar,
would he remember what happened that night?
Could he still prove my innocence?
Can this amnesia be cured?
I've heard of people with this condition before.
Apparently after experiencing some kind of trigger,
they suddenly remember what happened before.
I studied medicine.
About this condition,
I know more than you do.
That's not what I'm afraid of.
What I fear is
these people aren't sick at all.
They've been put under a spell.
Think about it.
This armored creature captured them first,
so why would it release them afterward?
Why?
They must have learned some secret,
and then this armored creature put a curse on them
to make them forget what happened,
fearing they might reveal it.
That still doesn't explain why they were released.
There are too many unexplained things here.
Who is this armored person?
Why capture these people?
Where did that city disappear to?
Where is Zeng Xin?
Why is he the exception?
Among all of us,
only Liu Guanying is fortunate.
He's the only one who found his daughter.
He's a Night Demon.
Why would Zeng Qian think that?
He's such an ordinary, simple person.
Just a bread seller.
How could he be a Night Demon?
Tongtong.
Do you remember what I just told you?
Tell me again.
My name is Liu Tong.
You're my father.
Your name is Liu Guanying.
Grandma has poor eyesight.
Everyone calls her Aunt Ji.
Good.
That's enough for now.
We'll talk about the rest later.
The most important thing now
is not to worry Grandma.
How did you get that scar on your face?
I served in the military before.
During the war,
I was injured in a fire attack
and ended up looking like this.
Is that Tongtong coming back?
Mother.
Why are you awake?
Without Tongtong here,
I couldn't sleep well.
Tongtong!
You're finally back.
Your father said you were staying at a new friend's place.
I was so worried about you.
Without you here, Grandma,
I couldn't sleep well either,
so I came back.
You're such a sweet talker.
Grandma's love for you isn't wasted.
- Let's go.
- Back to the room quickly.
Didn't you say you couldn't remember anything?
But I remember what you told me.
Don't make your mother-in-law worry.
Where are you going?
Those people in black prevented us from digging the tunnel.
They must be connected to that city.
Even related to the disappearances.
Maybe if we find them,
we can discover Axin's whereabouts.
Those people in black appear and disappear like ghosts.
How are we supposed to find them?
Jinghu Lake.
Zeng Qian.
We'll go with you.
They're long gone from there.
They've been there before.
Don't you think she's acting like
a dog?
She's in a bad mood.
Watch what you say.
Incense.
How does this rag smell like incense?
It's just like how we smell of cooking oil after making food.
I've been sniffing for ages and couldn't smell anything.
Zeng Qian.
Even if you're a hunter,
isn't that a bit exaggerated?
What kind of person would carry the scent of incense?
There are plenty of people who burn incense regularly.
Such everyday incense scent dissipates quickly.
Even the keenest nose couldn't detect it.
But the place where this person stays
must have constant, abundant burning of incense.
Taoist temple.
Buddhist temple.
Dengzhou has two Buddhist temples and one Taoist temple.
Just three places.
That makes our search much easier.
I think we only need to check one place.
Wuji Temple.
This place was closed recently,
supposedly for internal renovations.
They're not letting anyone in.
I thought it was strange at the time.
Now that I think about it...
We don't know what's going on inside.
If we force our way in,
we might alert them to our presence.
Could we get in by pretending to be worshippers?
If the men in black are really in the Taoist temple,
and we go there rashly to investigate,
we could easily be recognized.
Who cares if we're recognized?
With Young Master Xie's influence in Dengzhou,
we could have officers escort us in,
and those men in black wouldn't dare touch us.
Well, thank you
for thinking so highly of me.
Let me tell you something.
This Taoist temple has powerful connections.
Master Zhang inside is the prefect's cousin.
Never mind about me.
Even my father has no influence there.
If we go, we'll be recognized.
Then we can find someone they haven't seen before.
Well, if you put it that way,
this becomes much simpler.
What's with those faces?
It's too soon.
Put those expressions away
for now. You'll need them later.
Come in.
Alright, stop looking.
You can show those expressions now.
No need to hold back anymore.
You can even change your voice.
Boss.
Why don't we just ask that knife guy to come directly?
Young Master Xie
probably wants to show off in front of us.
Taoist Master,
what brings you here?
Last year I made a wish at your temple for a son,
and a few days ago my wife indeed gave birth to a boy.
Today I've come to fulfill my promise.
That's very thoughtful of you.
However, our temple is under renovation these days
and we cannot receive visitors.
Please don't worry, Master.
I'll just go in to light some incense and leave.
Besides,
I've come here
with sincere intentions.
It truly is inconvenient these days.
Please understand.
Master,
I've already come all this way.
If I go back without fulfilling my vow, I'll be scolded.
Sir,
please don't put me in a difficult position.
Aren't you the one making things difficult for me?
I just want to go in and light some incense.
How could that possibly disturb you?
I'm going in.
I just want to go in and light some incense.
I need to offer incense.
Did you all see that?
This Taoist temple definitely has something suspicious going on.
This wall looks easy to climb over.
Why don't we sneak in tonight and take a look?
Those men in black aren't ordinary people.
There are only about a dozen of them.
Such a large temple.
How can they guard it all?
The dozen we saw might not be all of them.
This is the spot.
The wind direction is perfect.
We randomly selected the location to release the sky lantern.
But they responded so quickly inside.
This means there are guards stationed inside all four walls of the Taoist temple.
This temple is so large,
divided into inner and outer courtyards.
There must be at least a hundred guards,
plus those on rotation,
making it at least 300 to 400 people.
That's incredible.
Who are they exactly?
Bandits?
Officials?
Military?
My brother must be in there.
How do you know?
Just a feeling.
Assuming Zeng Xin is really in the temple,
with the current level of security,
even if we manage to get in,
it would be difficult to safely bring him out.
I know you're anxious,
but the more anxious you are, the more likely you'll make mistakes.
We will definitely enter the temple.
I already have a plan.
Ma'am,
let me help you.
Go help your father serve the dishes.
Why do you always appear and disappear like a ghost?
Here, take this.
Number 18, Tazhong Hutong.
The commander of Qianji Guard's Han Division is there.
No need to open it.
It contains the same information.
If you already knew what to tell me,
why bother writing it down?
You must love what you do.
That's what being professional means.
Brother Bao, when you come to see me at night,
you can just knock and come in.
You don't have to meow like a cat.
Be professional.
Oh, right.
Don't forget to burn the note.
Okay.
If you don't come in soon,
the wine will get cold.
Finally no longer a Night Demon.
That beggar friend of yours
has first-class tracking skills.
But you didn't seem to tell him
that I used to be a Tabai.
You have no backup today.
And you won't have any in the future either.
You'll have plenty of chances.
But right now I have something important to do.
I don't have time to deal with you.
I hope you won't bother me anytime soon.
Don't worry.
After today,
I won't need to look for you anymore.
But your death alone isn't enough.
I know someone is behind you.
You were following someone's orders.
I want the truth.
The truth?
I happen to know the truth about something.
What if someone told Mrs. Ji
that her son died 4 years ago?
How many years has it been since anyone called you by your real name,
Feng Buhai?
If you insist on killing me today,
then someone will tell this secret to Mrs. Ji.
After I finish my own business,
I'll give you an explanation for Liu Guanying's death.
The wine is cold,
but it's still drinkable.
Since it's cold,
drink it yourself.
Tongtong,
come out here.
Mother-in-law isn't here.
I have something to tell you.
I thought you had already told me
almost everything from the past.
There's one more thing,
very important.
So you're not my father.
Your father was on a mission
when he was attacked by enemies.
With his last breath,
he asked me to take care of you and your grandmother.
I promised him.
Because your father wasn't just my comrade,
he was also the man who saved my life.
But when I actually arrived in Dengzhou,
I realized
I simply couldn't bring this tragic news
to an innocent child
and a poor old lady.
So...
To spare grandmother and me from grief,
you simply appeared as my father.
Your father and I were like brothers,
I knew everything about his life, big and small.
And...
When your father left home, you were too young
to remember what he looked like.
And grandmother has poor eyesight.
Originally, I only needed to disguise my voice
to get away with it.
But the neighbors all knew your father.
So I disguised myself as someone with a disfigured face,
covering my face with a thin veil daily
to prevent others from seeing my true appearance.
You could have kept this secret forever.
So why did you tell me?
Because you already knew.
Although I tried my best to hide my true face from you,
you're very clever.
In less than six months,
you saw through my disguise.
It started with little things,
you became suspicious of me.
For example,
I didn't know you disliked candied haws,
I didn't know you were afraid of rabbits,
I didn't know you were a decent swimmer, and so on.
But these were manageable,
I found reasonable explanations for everything.
Until one day,
you found a condolence letter in my room
about your father.
This letter came directly from the Ministry of War.
Under normal circumstances,
ordinary soldiers would never receive such treatment.
But your father was a Tabai soldier,
and had achieved merits.
So the Ministry not only provided compensation
but also sent a condolence letter about your father.
I knew about this beforehand,
to keep you and grandmother from learning the truth,
I intercepted the letter.
I thought that when you grew up,
I would explain everything to you.
That's why I didn't destroy the letter.
But you found out anyway.
So my pretending to be your father
couldn't be hidden anymore.
But...
I didn't tell grandmother,
did I?
That's why I say you're clever.
You kept questioning me back then.
After I told you the truth,
you cried your heart out.
You didn't speak to me for three days.
And then you decided
to help me keep this secret from grandmother.
All these years we've spent together
rather than being father and daughter
we're actually more like friends.
Good thing I'm still growing.
Let me ask you something.
Can I beat up those kids?
I'm telling you all this today
because I'm afraid
if you discover this again
you might lose control
and let grandmother know the truth.
Sister, look.
These are your favorite flowers.
Sister.
Why don't you take the bed?
I'll sleep on the floor.
Sister.
You must be tired.
I'll get you some hot water
to wash your face.
Young Master, are you up?
I'll bring you some porridge.
Okay.
You are
from Qianji Guard.
I remember you.
I'm looking for Cao Sheng.
Then wait a moment.
Didn't I tell you to wait?
I told you to wait.
Commander Lin asked me to give this to you.
What's in the box?
I don't know.
But she said I must deliver it to you personally.
Where is she now?
The item has been delivered.
Farewell.
Waiter!
Check, please!
Sir?
Sir,
our noodles cost 10 wen,
you're still short 2 wen.
Last time I ate noodles here,
there were two eggs in it,
but today there's only one.
That's impossible.
We always use just one egg.
Then last time it was a double-yolk egg.
Today's isn't.
Did you shortchange me an egg?
No, sir.
Double-yolk eggs are a matter of luck.
That's just how it works.
You're short one egg.
I'll give you two coins less.
Sir.
Then say no more.
Young Master.
Liu Guanying's water pouch,
the drawing on that pouch
is almost identical to this one.
Especially these mountains and that river.
So this is Sunset Valley by the Huo River.
This is my father's handwriting.
The 38th year of Jingyun reign,
which was four years ago.
Something significant happened that year.
The Battle of Wusuling.
That painting on Liu Guanying's kettle
has the words 'rebel camp' written on it.
I heard that
when the rebels were defeated,
their remnants fled to the Huo River area.
Baili Yuan was ordered to pursue them,
but the rebels hid in the mountains.
Baili Yuan and his men searched for months without success.
It wasn't until the Prince of Jingnan came to help
that they finally located the rebels
and eliminated them.
Could these events be related to the mirage too?
How many more secrets does Liu Guanying have?
We know he's Ye Yao,
and that his real identity is Feng Buhai.
Liu Guanying was actually his deceased comrade.
Now it seems this Liu Guanying, or rather Feng Buhai,
is involved in far more than we know.
Right now I'm more concerned about my father's secrets.
Feng Buhai was once a scout in Baili Yuan's camp.
It's no surprise that he saw the mirage.
But my father drew the exact same mirage,
which means he was there too.
Was it coincidence,
or was it...
Are you in there, Master Cao?
Wait.
What are you waiting for so long?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
You two in the room
being all secretive.
You!
Don't you have any manners?
Did I invite you in?
You just pushed your way in.
In broad daylight,
a man and woman alone behind closed doors.
It wouldn't sound good if people found out.
This is Master Xie's place.
And he's not charging us rent.
Come in if you want.
See?
Now that's someone who knows how to talk.
That sounds so nice to hear.
I came to tell you
that the person you asked me to find
has been located.
Let's go then.
Go where?
Where are you planning to go?
Didn't you tell Zeng Qian you had a way to get into Wuji Temple?
Do you have a plan?
It's already in motion.
By the way, Yunniang.
Did you take the porridge to Zeng Qian?
Did you both have some?
You need to eat something too, Cao.
Come in.
Have something to eat.
Why are you alone?
The young master went out with Xie Jingtang.
This is Chen Qi's home.
He should be back soon.
Why are you looking for a night soil collector?
Does it have something to do with the plan to infiltrate Wuji Temple?
I've been quite curious.
Aren't you the criminal Zeng Qian captured?
Why are you so eager to help her find her brother?
Perhaps it's my chivalrous nature.
You've got some nerve.
Wait a minute.
I should be looking for that one-eyed little beggar.
Why am I getting involved in your business?
Perhaps it's because you're not only chivalrous, Master Xie,
but also kind-hearted.
Seems you understand my personal qualities
quite thoroughly.
Alright.
No more joking around.
I really need to attend to my own business now.
This chivalrous act
ends here.
Don't worry, Master Xie.
We won't let you be chivalrous to us forever.
When the time comes,
we'll come to your aid as well.
You help us find Zeng Xin,
I'll help you find the little beggar.
And help me steal something.
No,
someone stole something from me.
Help me get it back.
I can do that.
And help me kill someone.
That depends on who it is.
The person who stole from me.
What did they steal from you?
Is it worth killing over?
He took my...
Chen Qi is back.
This night soil collector job
isn't something just anyone can do.
That smell on him
I can smell it from this far away.
When you disguise yourself as someone else,
how do you deal with height differences?
If I want to be taller,
I put something in my shoes.
If I want to be shorter,
I just hunch over.
A difference of three inches isn't a big deal.
But if it's too much,
there's no way.
So you've gotten a good look at Chen Qi now, right?
Yes, I have.
I'm excellent at remembering faces.
Once I've seen someone, I never forget.
However,
what are you suggesting?
No way, brother.
No, no.
This thing,
I absolutely cannot do it.
Have some confidence.
You can do it.
Didn't you say you could become anyone?
I just can't become that night soil collector.
I can't get on that waste cart.
I'm afraid before I even get on,
I'll vomit until there's nothing left.
Sesame oil on your nose,
ginger in your mouth,
can remove the odor.
You're treating me like a coroner.
Think about it.
We're helping each other now.
Can I just not have your help?
I have plenty of people.
Plenty of people to help me.
Is that so?
Then why haven't you been able to find that little beggar?
This has nothing to do with money.
Sometimes having more people doesn't help.
You need to find the right person.
You're here.
I was just about to look for you.
What are you really up to?
The most important thing now
is to confirm whether Zeng Xin is actually in the temple.
Forcing our way in won't work.
We need to be clever about it.
The entire temple is now heavily guarded.
It's no exaggeration to call it an impenetrable fortress.
But it can't be isolated from the world.
Where there are people, there are needs.
Where there are needs,
there will be supplies.
With so many people living inside,
they must need food, right?
So they'll definitely need to purchase supplies.
When that happens,
we'll hide near the Taoist temple
and knock them out secretly.
Let's have Xie Jingtang
disguise himself as one of them and sneak in.
Wouldn't that work?
First of all,
we don't know what they're up to in there.
Judging from the closure of the temple,
they must have planned this in advance.
And for things like food supplies,
they can prepare them beforehand.
They can arrange specific vendors to deliver at scheduled times.
Their people don't even need to come out.
They just need to collect the deliveries at the door.
I had thought about using knockout drugs before,
but if they're even slightly cautious,
they'll definitely inspect all food supplies carefully.
So drugging won't work either.
But then I realized something.
Their people can stay inside the Taoist temple indefinitely.
But some things can't stay inside.
First, food waste.
Second, human waste.
Food waste is easy to handle.
It can be fed to horses.
But human waste...
So you thought about the night soil collectors, didn't you?
The waste carriers.
Ordinary households only need night soil collectors every 8 to 10 days.
Wealthy families every 3 to 5 days.
But with hundreds of people in the temple,
they'd need collection at least once a day.
Even if I could disguise myself as that night soil collector...
Even if I could overcome the smell,
what if I'm discovered once inside the Taoist temple?
That sky lantern there,
that would be my fate.
You'll be in disguise.
How would anyone recognize you?
I'm using disguise techniques,
not transformation magic.
People who know me well could easily see through it.
Sewage workers wear face coverings
to block the smell, covering half their face.
You shouldn't be easily recognized.
I'll go.
This is my own business.
There's no need for others to risk themselves for me.
Master Xie,
please disguise me as a sewage worker.
Is there any problem?
This isn't difficult at all.
Actually, I've thought about this before,
but there's one issue we need to resolve.
The sound.
Can you teach me this?
Do you know how long it took me
to learn this?
A whole year.
Even if you're 10 times smarter than me,
it would still take at least a month.
If you put it that way,
she might learn it in no time.
Let Zeng Qian give it a try.
You're the best candidate to enter the Taoist temple.
And your height is similar to Chen Qi,
differing by no more than 3 inches.
So when you went to find Chen Qi,
you were considering both of us.
If we can successfully enter the temple
and find Axin,
how do we rescue him?
This is the most crucial step.