Mr. Xie
That's too formal,
bringing all these treats.
Now that's being formal, Daniu.
How long has it been since we've seen each other?
Isn't it normal for me to come visit you?
I'll arrange for all of us brothers to have a good drink later, alright?
Good.
Sounds good.
But right now,
My stomach...
I'm having some trouble.
Do you have a toilet here?
I'll take you there.
Come.
Wait here.
This way.
Miss,
you bought so much pine resin oil.
You need to be careful with it.
This stuff catches fire easily.
Here.
Thank you, miss.
Let's go.
Nice weather today.
Yes, it is.
What's that sound?
Let's hurry and leave.
Zeng Qian!
What is that noise?
Didn't you follow the method I taught you?
I
It's been half a day already
and you haven't made any progress at all.
People who don't know better might think
my Qingfeng House has added pig slaughtering to its business.
Maybe it's because you're such a good teacher.
So I'm your teacher now, huh?
Then I'd better show you what I can do.
How
did you do that?
The reason everyone's voice sounds different
is because when we speak,
besides our throat,
our chest, pharynx, mouth, nose, and head
all play a part.
You need to learn to control them first.
But anyway,
expecting you to learn
to sound exactly like Chen Qi
in such a short time is impossible.
Let's do this.
Sixty percent similarity will do.
For the remaining forty percent, blame it on a cold.
Just say you've caught a cold these days
and your throat is uncomfortable.
How close do you think it sounds now?
You can't just rely on the cold excuse.
Here,
now,
take a deep breath,
together,
pull in.
Come, look this way.
Chen Qi is back.
Young Master,
is this really necessary?
It's just about meeting her.
There can be no mistakes in this plan.
Falling asleep during it would cause trouble.
Alright.
I'll help you then.
No need.
I'll do it myself.
I'm quite experienced now.
Let me offer you another bowl, young master.
No, no, no.
I'll drink this bowl first.
Brothers from Qianhuo have suffered following Brother Daniu.
I'll take this one first. Come on.
Then let's all drink together!
Come on!
Bottoms up!
Drink up!
What's that noise outside?
Niu, what noise could there be?
Have a seat.
It's just the booze worms in our brothers' bellies crying out.
Come on.
Here.
Drink up.
Drink it now.
Come on, eat some food.
Fill it up.
Come here.
What for?
I haven't bathed for days.
Afraid I might smell.
And I caught a cold.
Don't want to infect you.
It doesn't matter. Come here.
Isn't it too tight?
It's fine.
It can be tighter.
To get through a body search,
this alone might not be enough.
I have a plan.
I'm driving
a manure cart.
How many days since you bathed?
Let's go.
Open the gate!
The usual rules.
Everyone handles their own area.
Hya!
Clean the bucket thoroughly!
Got it!
Before you leave, I want to talk to you again.
If you successfully enter the Taoist temple,
don't rush things.
You might think the simplest and most direct approach
is to capture one or two people,
extract Axin's location from them,
or force them to take you to Axin.
But they are well-trained.
If you encounter fanatics willing to die,
you'll be exposed.
Then forget about rescuing Axin.
Even your own escape would be questionable.
Even if you manage to escape,
we won't get another chance.
A direct attack is burning our bridges.
Only cunning gives us room to maneuver.
You are a hunter,
skilled at hiding and lurking.
Plus we're operating at night.
So the temple
becomes your forest.
As long as you stay calm and controlled,
they won't discover you.
Won't find you.
We'll have time,
and with time,
we'll have opportunity.
Young Taoist,
your whistle is really pretty.
Look,
I have one too.
Yours isn't as nice as mine,
nor as loud.
That's because you blow it well.
Young Taoist,
who gave you that whistle?
Nobody gave it to me.
I found it myself.
You're lying to me.
I'm not lying.
I really did find it.
Where did you find it?
Yichen!
Master, I'm here.
Yichen,
what are you doing here?
It's almost dawn.
Time for morning prayers.
Hurry up.
There was a lady just now.
What lady?
Being late for morning prayers is one thing,
but now you're lying too.
I'm not.
Where did you get this whistle?
I found it at the entrance of the Sanqing Hall.
Didn't I tell you not to go to Sanqing Hall?
There are peach blossoms there.
I wanted to collect some.
There aren't any elsewhere.
Alright.
Remember,
don't go there again.
Let's go.
There are peach blossoms there,
and nowhere else.
Why hasn't Chen Qi returned yet?
Indeed.
Why is he so slow this time?
He used to be quite efficient.
Brother Wang.
Has something happened to Chen Qi?
Should we go look for him?
You can't wander around here.
There are patrols.
If nothing else works, let's ask him
what we should do.
If we can successfully enter the Taoist temple
and find Axin.
How can we rescue him?
Now we're at the crucial step.
If Zeng Xin is definitely in the Taoist temple,
then his current situation
must be one of two possibilities.
First, he could be under house arrest.
Second, he could be imprisoned.
But regardless of which one it is,
there will certainly be guards watching at the door.
I'm very confident that you can locate
Zeng Xin's exact position.
But rather than alarming the guards
and putting yourself at a disadvantage,
why don't we actively create chaos
to divert their attention?
Fishing in troubled waters.
How's it going, Mr. Wang?
Chen Qi has disappeared.
Should we tell them or not?
If we keep wasting time like this,
if something really happens,
what if we get dragged into it?
Say something, will you?
Where's Sun?
Sun?
He was just here.
Where did he go?
Sun!
Now we've lost two people.
That's it.
I have to tell them.
Chen Qi is back.
Where is everyone?
Let's get out of here.
Alright then.
I'll have one with you.
Why are you still drinking?
Wuji Temple is on fire!
Master Xie, I must go.
Brothers!
Go!
Hurry, please!
Everyone be careful!
Hurry!
Keep up!
Follow me!
Why is nobody here?
I don't know.
What's going on?
Open the door!
You can't come in.
We're from
the fire brigade.
Isn't there a fire inside?
We can handle it ourselves.
Hurry!
Pour the water!
More water!
Quickly!
Coming!
More!
Over here!
Hurry up!
Who are you people anyway?
Why won't you let us in?
Let me tell you.
If this Taoist temple burns down,
you'll all be held responsible.
Why haven't the firefighters arrived yet?
Aren't they already here?
Why aren't they going in?
Open the door!
Come with me quickly.
Can't we handle this ourselves?
Now they're letting us in,
but I don't even want to anymore.
Boss,
let's not just be stubborn.
If this temple burns down,
we'll all be in trouble.
Let's go. Follow me.
Hurry up!
Water!
Hurry!
This way!
Keep up!
Axin.
Come with me.
Who are you?
Let me go!
For a young lady,
you're quite capable.
Who are you people?
And who are you?
It doesn't matter.
You'll find out soon enough.
Take her away.
Yes.
You thief!
We have plenty of ways to make you tell the truth.
That voice...
Thank goodness I recognized your voice.
Why are you here?
Let's talk outside.
Axin.
Wake up.
Don't worry.
It's just a sleeping drug.
Let's go.
Stop right there!
We're out of water bags.
I need to bring some back quickly.
Open the gate!
Wait.
You're moving water bags
by yourself?
I'll send two men to help you.
You two.
Open the gate!
Young Master,
what about this stealth vehicle?
Burn it.
That Qianji Guard commander went to Wuji Temple.
Who's there?
Just a moment.
Come in.
Cao Sheng, what are you doing?
Young Master.
Zeng Xin hasn't woken up yet.
Will he be alright?
You'll have to ask Dr. Xie about that.
After all, the knockout drug
was provided by him.
Don't worry. It's fine.
That medicine is my special formula.
He'll wake up after 5 or 6 hours of sleep at most.
Aren't you a doctor?
Why are you studying this kind of thing?
I originally intended to deal with Gu Tingmei.
Who?
The one who stole my things.
Cao Sheng.
I helped you rescue Zeng Xin.
Now
it's your turn to help me.
I'll give you the one-eyed little beggar first.
What?
You found him?
He's been back from his disappearance for two days.
Those bounty hunters still haven't found him.
How did you find him?
The question is,
with so many bounty hunters looking for him,
why couldn't they find him?
If the little beggar, like others,
also suffered from amnesia,
not remembering who he is,
or what happened before,
then he wouldn't be hiding out of fear
from seeing the armored man kill someone.
If he's not hiding,
he still needs to fill his stomach.
Either begging
or working for others.
If he were begging,
he would have been found early on.
So that leaves only working for others.
The work he's doing now
must involve minimal contact with people.
It can't be at teahouses or taverns where he'd be visible.
Otherwise, he would have been found already.
After eliminating possibilities,
we're left with
dock laborers,
coffin shop assistants,
stable hands and such jobs.
The options are few.
I had Yunniang make some inquiries.
Sure enough,
she found him at the coffin shop.
To prevent other hitmen from finding him and causing trouble,
I had Yunniang put him in that old shack
with plenty of food and drink.
Indeed.
Having many people isn't always effective.
You need the right person.
But you said it yourself.
He doesn't remember anything.
Even if you've found him,
he can't prove your innocence.
Don't worry about that.
I'm a doctor.
Soul loss is a difficult condition,
but it's not completely incurable.
I'll bring this troublemaker back now.
These records
I brought them back from the Taoist temple.
What's depicted here?
A ritual ceremony.
Look at the image below.
The 19th year of Jingyun reign,
23 years ago.
The mirage had already appeared back then.
Until now,
the mirage has appeared at least three times.
The first time was at Gaomeng Lake over 20 years ago.
The second time was at Huohe River four years ago.
The third time is now in Dengzhou.
The three appearances of the mirage
all have one thing in common.
Look.
This is the one at Huohe River.
Although the mirage appeared in Luori Valley,
it wasn't far from Huohe River.
Gaomeng Lake itself is a shallow water area.
Dengzhou has Mirror Lake.
All three mirages appeared near water.
Yes.
Why is that?
Also,
who are those people at the Taoist temple?
How do they know so much about the mirages?
I'm not sure.
But every time a mirage appears,
there's another common factor -
people disappear.
For the one at Luori Valley,
we don't know the details.
But from what we've seen in Dengzhou and Gaomeng Lake,
nearly 200 people disappeared each time.
This document records
the list of people who disappeared during the Gaomeng Lake mirage.
These people all disappeared on the sixth day of May
and returned two days later on the eighth.
Just like what happened in Dengzhou this time.
Except all these people...
They're all dead.
Protector Ding
Everyone on this list died within a year.
If the situation in Dengzhou
is the same as in Gaomeng Lake,
then everyone who returned
will also
die.
Li Hongchou, Che Zhigang, Xing Dongdong
Wang Feihu, Yang Yuchen, Zhou Yangfan
Jia Yan, Fu Yuxinshu
Starring
Cast
Also starring
Feng Yanhang, Liu Jinliang, Guo Ming, Ge Zhangxin, Yang Shifu, Liu Run, Luo Hao, Chen Maying, Shao Yiming, Li Haohao
Zhang Jian, Yu Lili, Dong Yan, Zhang Yunle, Liu Zhiheng, Wang Xiyou, Tu Yuanshuai, Li Qing, Zhong Xuanke, Pu Shisong
Dong Xiaoxiao, Jiang Chengze, Chen Hongwei, Zhang Weiwei, Long Peiying, Ren Yuan, Wang Xincheng, Li Huiqi, Jing Zongjie, Chen Shangwei
Luo Hao, Li Qing, Pan Miaomiao, Lin Zhiyin, Guo Zhi, Zhou Jie, Zhuo Weijie, Shi Zhiyang, Zhang Weihui, Liu Run
Yang Yulin, Han Bin, Peng Wencan, Guo Chengjia, Zhang Binghui, Liang Lili, Ma Xiaoyue, Gong Haiming, Lu Kaiqin, Yang Hao
Tian Ye, Zhang Leiming, Zhang Guangchao, Chen Xue'er, Yuan Liqin, Chen Miaoying, Duan Jiazhuo, Zhou Hongyu, Wang Xiaoying, Zhang Dengkai
Liu Bo, Huang Xiaolin, Zhi Jian, Yao Ke, Zhu Shoubi, Zhu Yangbing, Yang Gaofeng, Liu Chengyu, Zhao Yuanbin, Cao Shengjian
Chen Xiaoniu, Song Peng, Li Xiumei, Zeng Chao, Zhou Mingliang, Zhou Xinhua, Liu Xueli, Cao Weibing, Chen Qianyao, Ge Shuchang
Gao Feng, Shen Xun, Zheng Cong, Wang Qing, Shao Shen, Cheng Wenbo, Zhao Wenyu, Liu Kai, Dang Ziyu, Xu Guang
Wei Jianxing, Lu Yonghong, Xue Lingfei, Du Miaomiao, Chen Lijuan, He Fali, Wang Zhen, Chen Lijuan, Hu Yang, Chen Miaoying
Duan Jiazhuo, Zhou Hongyu, Zhu Xiao, Lin Hezhong, Tang Yongxin, Wang Yiming, Zhang Buyuan, Wang Liping, Yan Lijun, Shi Laiqiang
Gu Guanglin, Niu Jiangang, Yu Tao, Zhang Ping, Liao Tingkai, Jin Kang, Chen Wei, Chen Zhixiang, Zhu Ningxuan, Wang Xiaodong
Pan Wendong, Zeng Qian, Dou Yunfei, Lin Daoping, Chen Hui, Fu Chongbing, Sun Dingguo, Zheng Linling, Han Ying, Fang Ganmin
Xiao Xianghua, Hu Zhaoxiu, Zhu Lin, Shi Liangjian, Liu Ailin, Han Xiuhong, Bi Xing, Zhang Ting, Guan Jixue, Xu Caixiang
Huang Yanyan, Liang Qingqing, Liu Peiqiang, Li Junxian, Shi Huaicheng, Yang Chunling, Xi Miaomiao, Yang Jiale, He Ting, Ma Yunxian
Ni Jingui, Xia Chenlong, Fang Jiawang, Wang Mengfan, Zheng Hao, Sun Yanlong, Li Long, Han Shuai, Mei Qingyuan, Ling Feihong
Liu Yuan, Hu Liangnei, Wang Shuai, Zhou Zhenjian, Kong Xin, Song Liangjie, Niu Pinfeng, Lu Shunhui, Zhang Kun, Li Fei
Li Hengbo, Li Zuju, Chen Kun, Chen Zhihui, Lin Mei, Li Zhiyong, Meng Chao, Nur Ahmat Tunyaz
Feng Bingbing, Xiao Qi, Lu Yan, Liu Xingyun, Hong Baowei, Zhou Qilong, Zhang Chuangao, Luo Xianfa, Dong Danmeng, Zuo Guojun
Liu Cheng, Pan Zhengyang, Zhang Dongsheng, Li Zhidong, Jing Chao, Liu Daqing, Zhang Zhenfei, Fu Yifen, Hu Gui, Wang Xinyu
Directors
Photography Team
Lighting Team
Sound Team
Set Design Team
Editing Team
Voice Actors
Featured Song
'Snow in the Palm'
Visual Effects Team
Beijing Aikan Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Bimuyu (Beijing) Digital Technology Co., Ltd.
Stage Crew
Drivers
Special Thanks
Product Support
Hebei Youying Cultural Communication Co., Ltd.
Hainan Youxi Film Industry Co., Ltd.