♫ The wind blew across the crowded street ♫
♫ Lemon goes with coffee ♫
♫ We have a rapport, flustered ♫
♫ In the pouring rain ♫
♫ I start to refresh my memory ♫
♫ Your eyes are as clear ♫
♫ As the sky ♫
♫ As time goes by ♫
♫ For you, for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms ♫
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched ♫
♫ For you, for you ♫
♫ As I see your beautiful face ♫
♫ I'll realize all your dreams ♫
♫ You are the one for me ♫
♫ Whether in the clouds
or the bottom of the sea ♫
♫ I will only run towards you ♫
♫ In a changing world ♫
♫ All I want is you ♫
♫ Tides surge toward the island ♫
♫ I firmly walk towards you ♫
♫ Even if the moon sets and the stars move ♫
♫ You are my only one, my love ♫
♫ Life is inlaid with a rainbow of happiness ♫
♫ Staging the most beautiful reunion ♫
[Episode 13]
Tu, are you okay?
I've taken the medicine.
Thank you for your concern, Mr. Ji. I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm really okay.
Didn't expect Mr. Ji
to be quite concerned about Tu.
Caring for subordinates is part of
a department manager's duties.
I hope Xiaoning becomes a regular worker soon,
so she could help reduce
some of our performance pressure.
Good, you are so positive.
You and Tu seem to be
the only ones in our department
who are about the age of Mr. Ji, right?
Not everyone can match my senior.
Just kidding.
You are being jealous.
Mom, don't worry.
Xiaoning might have caught a cold
and a sore throat.
I wanted to consult you.
When she was sick,
what medicine she took that worked quickly?
Steamed oranges.
Eating it and she'll get better.
Just wait. I'll make it
and bring it over to you.
It's okay, don't bother. I'll do it.
That works too, I'll send you the recipe.
Just follow the recipe.
Okay, thanks, Mom.
Sir, you're picking oranges?
Yes.
We are having a discount on them. Half price.
Buy three jin and get three jin free,
would you like some?
Do you have any of better quality?
The better ones might have no discount.
That's okay.
Those over there
are directly supplied from the place of origin,
especially fresh and sweet.
Alright, please pick out some for me.
Okay.
Mom has gone to sleep?
She went to sleep after taking the medicine.
[Time's up]
The timing is perfect.
Mom said you ate this to get over
a cold faster when you were little.
It's hot.
I forgot.
But it's my first time making it,
seems like I added too much salt.
It's okay, having more salt
is what makes it effective.
Really?
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm fine. Mom took my temperature
as soon as I came home.
I have no fever.
Then my hands are too cold.
I'm really fine.
There's no need to make such a fuss.
Even if you are fine, don't study today.
Go back and rest early.
Okay.
Does it taste a bit sour and salty?
No.
- I'll make it for you again.
- No.
I finish this today,
and will surely get better by tomorrow.
I'm going to take another one
tomorrow morning to enhance the effect.
No problem, I'll make it for you.
Well,
could you put a little less salt?
- Of course, I can.
- Okay.
Sunrise, sunset, and the starry sky
are the most beautiful scenes I think.
It's really nice
to have you enjoy them with me.
What does it feel like?
Isn't that the feeling of being in love?
When you went back to your hometown,
I thought you would never
come back to Star City anymore.
I just thought that in the future,
there might be no one
to do such romantic yet boring things with me.
Now I am here.
From now on, I will stay with you
and do such things. I won't leave anymore.
Tomorrow night is the New Year's Eve.
In the new year, I can once again not be alone.
Tomorrow, I'll give you a New Year's present.
Really? What is it?
You're not telling me? Fine.
How are you?
You're not coughing much anymore.
Did you take your medicine?
I did.
Three times a day, not a single dose missed.
Let me talk to her.
Xiaoning, you have an exam tomorrow, right?
I have a good idea.
How about I go to the entrance
of your bank and put up a banner
to cheer you on?
I'll let your mom go too.
Have your mom wear a qipao tomorrow.
To cheer you up. What do you think?
I'm not going, it's embarrassing. You'd go.
Mom, why don't you get
some medicine for dad to take?
You're right. Let me tell you,
your dad feels uneasy
if he doesn't play fool for a day.
Listen,
how about I wear a hooded outfit tomorrow?
I'll dress up
as that thing that girls like nowadays.
- Like this.
- What's that thing again?
- That…
- Fox.
That fox.
Don't do it.
I know you want to soothe me.
I'm not nervous at all. Don't worry about me.
That's good then.
Okay, keep it up!
Go for it!
Bye.
I have used the power of metaphysics.
So you can definitely pass the exam.
Love you.
You're at the top of my list
right now alone.
Come on. The top of your list
is Ji Yuheng
whom you kiss in the bedroom closet.
Now that you're living under the same roof,
you can speed up the progress now.
No matter how pretty that face is,
you still need to test him on the field.
Why is your face blushing?
Are you running a fever again?
No. I think the cold
hasn't completely cleared up.
Let me check.
Your face isn't hot.
It doesn't seem like a fever.
I'm not having a fever. Just the cold
hasn't completely cleared up.
I know my body pretty well.
It's fine if you don't need
to speed up the progress.
Why did you eavesdrop on me?
What?
I came in and chatted with you.
But you chatted with Ling Weiyi
and doubted my…
No, no. You heard it wrong.
I'm going to sleep now. You can go.
That sudden?
- Come out.
- No.
Come out.
You have an exam tomorrow.
If you get sick from it
and perform poorly tomorrow, you'll blame me.
Rest well.
I didn't hear you cough all the way just now.
You should be getting better.
Remember to drink some water later.
Got it.
I'll pick you up after the exam.
I've booked a restaurant to dine together.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Good luck.
[Adhere to examination rules
and maintain integrity and regulations]
[Dairui Bank, Development Department
Division One, Tu Xiaoning]
[Dairui Bank Employee Promotion Exam Questions]
[Answer Sheet]
♫ I can always see the faint glimmer of light ♫
♫ Flowing through the gaps between my fingers ♫
♫ As the wind along the way ♫
♫ Accompanying me through yesterday ♫
♫ Rushing towards
all the destinations of the future ♫
♫ Sweat poured down every step ♫
♫ Chasing happiness with all my heart ♫
♫ Every scene passed by ♫
♫ We know there's a new beginning in life ♫
♫ Refreshing all the unknowns ♫
♫ Gathering the fulfillment of desires ♫
♫ Every moment counts ♫
♫ You know there's a new beginning in life ♫
Get off work. Let's enjoy the vacation.
Wish you all a happy New Year's holiday.
Let's get excited.
Mr. Zhao, getting so excited?
Instead of staying at home,
going out and spending your bit of money?
This lady,
I am now seriously informing you as a creditor,
before the midnight on January 1st.
please settle the interest you promised me.
Otherwise, I will add
the interest onto the principal.
You understand the power
of compound interest, right?
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhao.
I was a bit arrogant just now.
No problem. If I'm right,
you don't have a penny on you, right?
Ms. Rao, do you have any plans
for New Year's Day?
Yes, if you happen to pass away,
then I'll have an activity.
I could go attend your funeral.
It's the New Year, don't say such things.
If you don't have any plans,
I could ask you out,
considering it as a kind gesture.
Don't bother doing so.
I'll send you the QR code later.
Just transfer the money to me.
Don't bother buying a gift for me.
I don't need it.
Why do you talk so mean?
So what?
I didn't just ask you out alone.
Tu just finished her exams.
Let's all have a meal together
and help her decompress.
Wait, Zhao. Did you ask Mr. Ji about it?
I did, but I was rejected.
He said he has to have dinner with his family.
Well, Mr. Zhao, I'm really sorry.
It looks like Tu has to refuse you as well.
She also has to have dinner with her family.
What a coincidence.
Seems like they are a family.
Well, let's dismiss?
Well, what else?
Let's dismiss. Go home.
Sorry.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Driving while wearing high heels.
I'll go report you to the traffic police.
I have flats in my car.
Thank you, goodbye.
- Bye, Jing.
Bye, Jing.
Bye, Zhao.
Your shoes got crushed.
Get lost.
The vibe of this restaurant is quite nice.
Why doesn't Mom come along?
She is a bit tired and wants to rest tonight.
You've had a tough day.
Let's see what you want to order.
This restaurant is a bit expensive.
I heard that the food of this place is nice.
But I've never been here myself.
But it's just the two of us.
I think it's a bit expensive.
How about we go somewhere else?
Take a look at the menu first.
It's already this late.
The slightly better restaurants
are probably all booked by now.
If we must leave,
we might just have to go to the noodle shop
near our community.
Spending the New Year's Eve
at the noodle shop near our community
is really a bit shabby.
Indeed. Shall we give it a go?
Alright then, it's been a tough year.
Just take it as a little treat for us.
Exactly.
Hello, the food you ordered is here.
Thank you.
Please enjoy your meal.
Okay.
I haven't ordered,
yet the food is already served.
You had already ordered it.
After all, this is our first
New Year's Eve together.
I must treat it seriously.
Rest assured, I can still afford
such a candlelit dinner.
Then why did you mention the noodle shop?
You treat me to dinner.
Let me share some good news with you.
Okay.
I think I did quite well in the exam.
I reviewed the case analysis
several times after the exam.
I think I could pass it.
Next, I will have to work on
independently acquiring clients.
After the vacation,
I will start looking for clients.
This seems pretty nice.
Then this is worth to celebrate.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
Ji is so thoughtful.
Look, he's ordered so much delicious food
and even brought us here.
He really made it formally.
He is considerate.
It's all about the hustle and bustle
to celebrate the New Year's Eve.
After Yuheng got together with Xiaoning,
he's truly become much happier.
Due to my poor health,
we seldom celebrated the New Year seriously,
so our home was always desolate.
In the future, if you don't mind,
let's spend the festivals together.
That's great. It's been so long
since the home was this lively.
Why don't you move to our place?
Sure. If you move to our place,
then she'd have company.
With you, I can go out for walks or strolls
whenever I want.
What do you mean?
If you don't go out for walks
or strolls with me,
you'd go dancing with someone else?
- I…
- This man…
I'll do something else.
I can play chess or go fishing.
Alright then.
I'm serious, in-law.
Ever since Xiaoning moved out,
our home has been quite desolate too.
If you go to our place,
it would liven up our place.
I would bother you so much.
Not at all.
Just prepare meals for one more person.
Think about it,
the two of us can talk and chat.
We can also go shopping together.
Anyway, if you are okay with it,
we will come pick you up right away.
Right, there's plenty of space at home.
Thank you.
Think about it.
This song is quite nice.
Look, he's not as handsome as Ji.
If I do well on my exam this time,
then I would have almost completed
about 20% of the KPIs in our agreement.
20%? That's quite a lot.
How about you?
Talk about it. The two of us
are friendly competitors.
Why do you keep it a secret? Share with me.
Are you halfway there already?
Of course not.
There are few clients in our department.
Could I possibly keep a few hidden from you?
But you're the leader.
If you keep some hidden,
I wouldn't know either.
I don't.
Good then.
Ji, you need to work harder.
Okay, leader.
Xiaoning, actually, I have something
to tell you here.
[Ling Weiyi]
You go first.
It's okay, you take the call first.
- I'm going to the restroom.
- Okay.
Hello, Weiyi, what's wrong?
Where are you?
I don't know either.
Qi Yu asked me to a place
I've never been before
and he hasn't arrived yet.
What about you? What are you doing?
Do you want to spend
New Year's Eve with me tonight?
I heard there are fireworks
at the Bell Tower tonight.
No.
I'm dining with Ji Yuheng
at a Western restaurant on Wutong Road.
So, I won't watch the fireworks
with you tonight.
I heard that restaurant is quite expensive.
He booked it?
I think he planned it long ago.
What a coincidence.
He was about to tell me something,
and you happened to call.
Is he going to confess to you?
I have to go now.
I'm back.
Was the call an emergency?
No, nothing special.
Okay, let's eat.
What do you want to tell me?
Nothing.
Is the food enough? Should we order some more?
Come on, let's cut the cake.
Do you really have nothing to say to me?
Why do you ask so suddenly?
Come on, cut it.
There really isn't a ring.
How is it? Is the taste good?
Delicious.
This is a new store.
And this is their signature flavor.
Weiyi.
No flowers, no cake, no presents.
So, what is my New Year's surprise?
It's happening now.
Look.
It's the sunset.
Sunrise, sunset, and starry sky.
The most beautiful things
in the world belong to you.
Sunrise, sunset, and the starry sky
are the most beautiful scenes I think.
He still remembers that.
I wish this moment could last forever.
♫ Your eyes are as clear as the sky ♫
♫ As time goes by, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched, I fall for you ♫
Look.
There it is.
♫ And making it into an everlasting song ♫
Come on.
♫ It's been a long time ♫
♫ The whole world is happy for us ♫
♫ In the pouring rain ♫
♫ I start to refresh my memory ♫
♫ Your eyes are as clear as the sky ♫
♫ As time goes by, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ I'll realize all your dreams ♫
♫ You are the one for me ♫
How many sunsets have we watched today?
Five.
This is the first time in my life
that I've said goodbye to the sun so earnestly.
♫ I firmly walk towards you ♫
♫ Even if the moon sets and the stars move ♫
Thank you, Qi Yu.
This is the best present I've ever received.
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Capturing all happiness for you ♫
♫ And making it into an everlasting song ♫
♫ You are my only one, my love ♫
♫ Feel the beat of the heart frequency ♫
♫ Hold you tight ♫
♫ You are my only one, my love ♫
♫ Life is inlaid with a rainbow of happiness ♫
Be careful.
Xiaoning, I have something to tell you.
No way. Right now? On the street?
Go ahead.
I want to talk about my mom.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
My dad is buried back in our hometown.
I haven't visited his grave
since I came back from abroad.
After the New Year,
I want to go visit his grave with my mom.
You can come with us if you don't mind.
It's okay if you don't want to.
Of course, I want to.
I accompany mom to visit dad's grave.
Isn't that normal?
I just didn't expect you would tell me that.
I thought you…
What did you think?
Nothing. I-I'm a bit hungry.
Me too.
Don't go to such an expensive restaurant again.
It's expensive, and the servings are small.
Come on, No.100 to 120 can start ordering now.
What's your number?
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
- Here's the menu.
- Thank you.
Hello, excuse me, I would like to ask
[Four-person meal for friends]
if all these are set meals?
Sorry, madam.
There are too many people coming today.
And our food preparation
is also based on set meals.
We might take more time to cook
if you go a la carte.
Take more time?
Yes.
All right, thank you.
They've only just called No.98.
We are No.231.
How long do we have to wait?
Wait a bit longer. You've been
wanting to try this restaurant.
Usually, we don't have the time.
Alright.
[Seafood Gathering A111]
I have a number here.
If you two don't mind, you can use it.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
- What number is it?
- No.111.
Jin, eat your fill today.
I got this place's 50% off coupon
half a month in advance.
Thanks, Zhao.
Don't mention it. Come on.
Even without a date, she wouldn't
spend New Year's Eve alone.
It is our first New Year's Eve together
since we got together.
Nice, it's really nice.
It seems
that you were with Ling Weiyi
for the previous New Year's Eves.
Yes, how did you know?
Just a guess.
Right, that was easy to guess.
Who else would I spend New Year's Eve
with if not with her?
But every year, the two of us
just spend New Year's Eve
feeling the festive vibe, nothing else really.
Back when we were in college,
we had to turn off the dorm lights at ten.
One time we came back after twelve,
and we had to climb through
the window to get into the dorm.
Luckily we were on the second floor.
Otherwise, we couldn't climb back in.
What about you? How do you
usually spend New Year's Eves?
I don't seem to have much idea
about New Year's Eves.
I remember when I was in college,
every New Year's Day
I seemed to be busy with the paper.
Then, after going abroad,
housemates would often throw house parties,
but I rarely participated.
- I was pretty much all by myself.
- You were always by yourself?
So, I'm the first one to spend
New Year's Eve with you, right?
Make a guess.
Looks like I'm pretty special.
What about me?
Am I a bit more special to you now?
It's almost twelve.
Why don't you get up? Come on.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
Ji, Happy New Year!
I'm the first one to wish you
Happy New Year, right?
Me too.
♫ Lemon goes with coffee.
We have a rapport, flustered ♫
♫ We continue the warm moments of the past ♫
Tu Xiaoning, I like you.
What did you say?
I said I like you.
What did you say? I didn't hear it clearly.
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Capturing all happiness for you ♫
I said I like you.
Have you heard me this time?
♫ It's been a long time ♫
♫ The whole world is happy for us ♫
♫ In the pouring rain ♫
♫ I start to refresh my memory ♫
♫ Your eyes are as clear as the sky ♫
♫ As time goes by, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ I'll realize all your dreams ♫
♫ You are the one for me ♫
♫ No matter up in the clouds
or under the sea, I run to you ♫
♫ In a world where everything change,
I long for you ♫
[Iron Giant]
♫ Tides surge toward the island ♫
♫ I firmly walk towards you ♫
Happy New Year! Wish you
your bonus to double and your debts to clear.
♫ As time goes by, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Parallel kite strings take a turn ♫
♫ Shining brightly ♫
♫ As I'm touched, I fall for you ♫
♫ As I feel the warmth in your palms,
I fall for you ♫
♫ Capturing all happiness for you ♫
When did you start liking me?
When do you want me to start?
What?
I even wanted you to fall in love
with me at first sight.
But if so, it's only happened four months ago.
Who said that? We've met since high school.
Forget it.
If you had liked me since high school
and didn't confess to me until now,
that would be quite scary.
Were you nervous
when you confessed to me back then?
That obvious?
You would never
get nervous even in the most important exams,
and no matter
what happens at work,
you could think of a solution right away.
Why were you so nervous about confessing to me?
Just do as we said just now.
You take a rest first. I don't need it for now.
Don't want to hide a ring
in a cake.
What era is it now? That's too cliche.
Go ahead.
I think confessing now is too casual.
I want to talk about my mom.
But don't forget,
I have many things I'm not good at.
I'd be clumsy in front of the person he likes.
When I want to confess,
even if I have prepared many lines,
but can only say I like you.
Just this simple line.
Actually, I'm not good at everything.
Those polished resume
and calmness in front of people
are all achieved through my hard work.
Actually, I have many flaws.
I hope in the future, if you see the ordinary
or even mediocre me,
don't be so disappointed in me
and don't despise me.
Why would I? You are Ji Yuheng.
I am Ji Yuheng only if you like me.
If you don't like me, I am just a nobody.
Ji Yuheng will always be Ji Yuheng.
In my heart, you are the best
in the whole world.
[Ling's Building]
Hey, how is it going?
You haven't contacted me in two days,
must be in crazy love.
It's early in the morning,
can you talk about something normal?
[Exam Results Inquiry: Pending.]
I am talking about something normal.
What are you talking about?
Forget it. I haven't had
the chance to tell you yet.
I plan to take Qi Yu back home
before the Chinese New Year,
to speed up the progress.
What do you mean?
Want to get married next year?
That soon?
Very likely.
We'll get married together then,
directly entering the next stage of life.
You want to get married, go ahead,
why get me involved in it?
Are you in such a hurry to get me married off?
Tu, I heard from the security
that the results are out.
You should check it now.
I just logged in.
[Tu Xiaoning, Development Department
Division One of Star City Branch, Passed]
I passed! Ling Weiyi, I have passed.
You've passed, that's great!
Hard work pays off.
That's great.
Okay, Mr. Zheng. Whenever you have time,
I will discuss the loan matters
with you in person. Okay.
Tang, another new client again?
You are making it fast.
That's really impressive.
In the Development Department,
performance matters the most.
I've just arrived,
so I must work harder for sure.
Tang, in that case,
I have to say something.
If I were a girl,
I would choose to be in the lobby.
It's more stable.
Of course. If you did it for Mr. Ji,
then I understand.
Li Xiang, you really don't understand us girls.
I definitely want to get promotion.
And the Development Department
fits my career plan better,
with a smoother pathway upwards.
But for other aspects you mentioned,
I'm looking forward to them as well.
Tu Xiaoning, you are amazing!
Thank you.
Congratulations, Xiaoning.
Didn't expect you
to pass the written exam so quickly.
What's so unexpected about that?
I knew that Tu would pass in one go.
The Development Department will
surely have a place for you in the future.
- Thank you, Zhao.
- You're welcome.
The journey ahead is still long.
There's still a lot to go through.
Tu, don't just think so, right?
There's no time to lose.
There are very few positions
for temp workers to become regular.
Passing the written exam
is just a basic requirement,
but we need to meet all the requirements.
You need to improve your performance
in the shortest possible time,
to prove that you deserve this position.
It's just about developing clients.
You are right.
Xiaoning, you need to hurry up.
There is a way to go
from customer development to making loans.
[Happy New Year Across a Decade]
Everyone, hurry up. It's almost midnight.
If we go to the playground now,
we can catch the New Year countdown.
Yuheng, let's go together.
A lot of girls from the school next door
are coming over for the New Year countdown.
I won't go. You guys go.
Just take a day off.
Today is also a big day.
Right.
You guys go ahead.
Alright, we'll go first. We're running late.
Hurry up.
[Little Lemon Any Luck Today]
Who is the first person
to say happy New Year to you?
Happy New Year, Tu Xiaoning.
♫ The night swallows the dusk ♫
♫ Only shadows follow closely ♫
♫ You're the streetlight waiting for me ♫
♫ The beam of light behind you ♫
♫ Warms the flowing air ♫
♫ Time seems to pause ♫
♫ I'm privately cherishing this moment ♫
♫ My feel is for you, just like the rain ♫
♫ Falling wetly and passionately ♫
♫ Oh, baby, my heart belongs ♫
♫ To you and no one else ♫
♫ The fireworks over my heart never cease ♫
♫ Maybe it is you ♫
♫ No one knows ♫
♫ Baby, it is you ♫
♫ I hope you know ♫
♫ You ripple through my quiet memories ♫
♫ Feeling each other's warmth ♫
♫ My feel is for you, just like the rain ♫
♫ Falling wetly and passionately ♫
♫ Oh, baby, my heart belongs ♫
♫ To you and no one else ♫
♫ The fireworks over my heart never cease ♫
♫ Maybe it is you ♫
♫ No one knows ♫
♫ Baby, it is you ♫
♫ I hope you know ♫