This drama series is fictional
and is not related in any way
to actual places, persons,
organizations, settings, and events.
What's going on?
Are you all right?
Ms. Oh.
Ms. Oh!
Oh Wansoo!
Ms. Oh.
Red Swan
Episode 6
Come this way! Hurry!
- Let's go!
- Hurry it up!
Do you know what happened?
Sir. Can you hear me?
We're at the scene
of the accident that occurred on Route 77,
the highway between Seoul
and Paju, Gyeonggi-do.
It is said that there was
an attempt on Ms. Oh Wansoo's life
as she was on her way back
from visiting NOW Foundation.
The police suspect
that her vehicle was attacked
by drones that carried explosives
as seen in terror attacks
around the world as of late.
Pull it out.
If the debris had lodged
a little deeper inside him,
it could have damaged his lungs badly.
How is he, doctor?
The operation was successful.
We'll transfer him to the recovery room
to see how he does
then perform a detailed checkup again.
Thank you.
I'll head down to the emergency center.
I was there just now.
Director Oh gained consciousness
and is now in a regular ward.
Q2 has only suffered fractures
to the arms, legs, and shoulders
and has no critical injuries.
He'll go into surgery in an hour's time.
Report this
to the chairwoman over the phone
and let me know how Doyoon is
once he's moved to a ward.
I'll go visit the vice-chairman
-and drop by the National Police Agency.
-Yes, sir.
Abrance Hospital
Sir.
Luckily, no one seems to be
in critical condition.
I see. I'm glad everyone is alive.
There are many reporters at the hospital.
The PR team is on its way here.
I said I get it.
What about him?
I mean the bodyguards.
They're both alive.
One of them had a successful surgery
and the other is about to have one now.
What?
What about the press?
Were there any articles?
Don't get up.
You're all over the news and the reporters
are lined up outside the hospital.
Mr. Oh will be here soon,
so I'll head back home.
The doctor tells me
that it was a miracle
that you weren't hurt.
Rest up.
I'll go take a look outside before I go.
Abrance Hospital
- How's Ms. Oh doing now?
- Please tell us.
- How is her condition?
- Please give a word.
The photo from the attack
and the press release
have been sent
to your respective company emails.
Director Oh won't be able
to answer your questions
as she needs
absolute rest for her recovery.
They say NOW Foundation has been receiving
more and more donations.
Is this true?
-How much have you received so far?
-Did you hear that, Mom?
Gosh.
She must have been born lucky with money.
We are unable to confirm.
We will send you the press release
at a later date.
- Can you tell us more?
- How is Ms. Oh doing?
Did her husband visit the hospital?
Please tell us more.
Excuse me, Mr. Reporter.
What are you doing?
Mom.
Mom!
The mission failed.
I'm sorry.
Who did you say you were again?
Let's just go, Mom.
So what I was saying
is that she's my daughter.
And as for my daughter,
she is Hwain Group's Chairwoman Park's…
sister-in-law.
- Do you get what I mean?
- Ah.
-Would it be okay for me to record this?
-No, you can't.
We're not here to give you an interview.
What I'm saying is that she's here
to visit her daughter-in-law.
Then could I take a photo of you?
No. What do you mean, a photo?
You sure are bad at your job.
This isn't some photoshoot.
Make it look candid.
Right. I see.
Do you have a business card?
Hold on.
Here.
CBM Reporter
Hwang Sejun
Thank you.
This is my big break.
Are you sure we're going to be all right?
He's just doing his job as a paparazzi.
You need to keep being seen
so that they won't look down on you.
Go on. Smile.
Wait. You shouldn't smile. That won't do.
Pretend to be sad.
-How can I help you?
-I'm here with the commissioner general.
The commissioner general is here.
The Grand Palace
Mr. Han.
-Come in, sir.
-Thank you.
NOW Foundation's Oh Wansoo
attacked by drones
It's an honor
to be here, Chairwoman Park.
-Please sit.
-Yes, ma'am.
I thought the arrest rate for murder
in Korea was 99%.
I'll find the perpetrator
no matter what, ma'am.
But who could it be
for them to shoot guns and use explosives?
On top of that,
she was also attacked in Manila.
It's very concerning.
I'll find whoever did it.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
No need for such formalities.
-Sit down.
-Yes, ma'am.
The National Forensic Service
is working as quickly as it can.
Since it happened in Korea--
You're making my head ache!
I don't put up with excuses.
Just find out who did it…
and give them the death sentence.
Yes, ma'am.
There's no need for you to worry.
Why do you keep doing that?
Yes, ma'am.
This way, sir.
Sure.
Goodbye, ma'am.
I think ISIS could be behind this.
We'll need to investigate this thoroughly
since the attack took place in Korea.
Commissioner General.
Yes?
Failure to catch the culprit
is incompetence.
I'm sorry?
But choosing not to catch them
is resourcefulness.
I beg your pardon?
Every time she is attacked,
people pay Director Oh more attention
while our company's stock prices
go down by 5 to 10%.
Right.
Yes, yes, I see.
I understand what you mean.
So you're saying…
you want this dealt with quickly
so that there won't be any rumors.
Stock prices dropping
would negatively affect the economy.
You're right indeed.
But the National Intelligence Service
requested the intel we've gathered
since the attacks could lead to
-diplomatic tensions.
-Commissioner General.
Do I need to spell it out for you?
I'll be sure to deal with it.
Of course. You can count on me.
Abrance Hospital
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Do you need anything, ma'am?
Where are my bodyguards staying?
Hold on. Excuse me, Kim.
Seo Doyoon
Here, Doyoon.
It's from Mr. Kim.
It's footage from all the CCTV cameras
near the site.
Thank you. I'll treat you to a meal later.
Take care of yourself.
I'll contact you if we get any updates.
National Police Agency
What did the police say?
They suspect ISIS to be behind the attack
but are yet to find any evidence.
A suspicious motorcycle was spotted nearby
during the time of the attack,
so they had 50 officers look over
all the nearby CCTV footage over the week,
but they lost track of it.
Here.
Just like the last time,
it's 70 bundles in US dollars.
It's for Eight Star Fortune
in Incheon, right?
Yes.
Understood, sir.
Should I look further into
the police's investigation?
If there are any updates,
report them to me right away.
Yes, sir.
Can you be sure
that the money you delivered
wasn't to hire a contract killer?
That's why Juhyuk died!
The vice-chairman
seems to be creating his own slush funds.
How much?
It's not much.
I think he's created around 100 accounts
that hold a billion won each.
Let him.
He must be in need of money
without me knowing.
But he seems to be dealing
with some dangerous people.
I can't tell if the money is being kept
as a slush fund or for something else.
Hold on.
Is 100 billion won chump change to you?
I'm sorry?
You can keep your mind off that for now.
What did Yongmin say?
Is he still being stubborn?
I'll go and talk to him.
He doesn't want the foundation
even after I said I'd give him
our duty-free business as well.
I just don't get it.
What more could he want?
Who does he take after to be so greedy?
Cosmo's Vice-President Kim Yongmin
still won't answer my calls.
Leave him be.
I asked Mr. Han if we could split off
our duty-free business
to give to him as convertible bonds,
but I don't think he's given up
on having Cosmo join us yet.
That Mr. Han…
Keep a close eye on him.
Yes, sir. I'll report back
if there are any updates.
That idiot keeps trying
to look the gift horse in the mouth.
- Damn it.
- Sit down.
Just tell me!
It's none of your business
whether we suffer a loss or not.
This involves
more than just Cosmo Cosmetics.
We're investing in the duty-free shop
so you can have it bequeathed.
Look, Mr. Han.
Either the vice-chairman or Wansoo
should come here
and beg us for forgiveness.
That's not important.
It might not be to you, but it is to me.
This is why one's lineage matters.
She's the daughter of some measly caddie.
How dare she interfere
in our new product launch?
And how many generations are required
to validate one's lineage?
Your grandfather also started out
as a peddler who used to sell
all-in-one cosmetics, Jiyeon.
You… Have you lost your mind?
Who do you think
you're speaking to right now?
Vice-President Kim
and President Seo.
This investment will be beneficial
to both of you.
And Director Oh will never listen
even if we tell her to apologize.
What has my dead father
or my mother done for me?
All they offered me
was that foundation run by Wansoo,
not even one of our subsidiaries.
You're practically telling me
to suck it up
and launder money
for Yongkook's inheritance.
I told you
that I'd explain everything later.
Shut it!
Who I hate more than my mom
is you who planned all of this.
I don't intend to involve myself
with you or Mom anymore,
so stop crossing the line to lecture me
and just leave.
You were so quick to dump him on us.
Why are you ordering him around now?
Have Wansoo have the Chinese FDA
approve of our cosmetics line.
Then I'll give it a second thought.
Yes, sir.
I beg you.
Please think carefully
about what I told you today.
Who does he think he is?
He's just the family lawyer.
I won't allow it.
I agree. I'm with you on that.
He was the one
who arranged for me to marry you
after my marriage with Yongkook
fell through.
He convinced my mom.
Yes, honey.
I'll be right down.
Can't you answer the phone outside?
You startled me. Have you lost it?
Why would you scream like that?
I'll turn a blind eye,
so help me keep doing that.
A blind eye to what?
Damn it.
Abrance Hospital
Your discharge procedure
has been completed.
We should go.
The chairwoman sent me here
to keep you safe.
You can wait in the car, Ms. Yoon.
I'll be there
after I visit the injured bodyguards.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait here.
I'll be quick.
Yes, ma'am.
Q2 is receiving his checkup.
Please come in.
You almost died.
Just another inch
and your lung
could have been seriously injured.
But you're safe.
Why do you keep
putting yourself in danger?
My mom told me once
that there's nothing more honest
than one's money and one's body…
since one's money and one's body
follow one's heart.
Our family used to be poor.
My mom kept putting money aside
to give me pocket money
and buy me new sneakers.
She also worked part-time
behind my father's back
to pack a hearty lunch for me and Juhyuk.
I yelled at her to stop doing that,
but she told me
that she was following her heart.
Why would you ever
let your heart follow me?
There's nothing we can do.
That's not true.
I saved you, didn't I?
It happened before I even knew it.
I'm just glad that you weren't hurt.
But I can't do anything for you in return.
A friend of mine in the police
sent me CCTV footage.
You don't need to show me.
-It's from the scene of the attack.
-I don't need to see it.
I trust you now.
I trust you.
There are bodyguards
waiting for me outside.
We'll talk more once you're discharged.
Get well soon.
Don't put yourself in danger for my sake.
Please.
Stem cells are useless.
And colostrum doesn't taste good.
But time flies by
so mercilessly.
I heard your car was totaled
and set ablaze.
You haven't got a scratch on you.
I was lucky.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
And the bodyguard?
He was seriously wounded,
but he's in recovery.
Did he…
put his arms around you like this
to protect you?
They only do that…
because we're paying them well enough.
Can you buy a person's life with money?
Of course. How could you not know that?
Then have you ever…
bought someone's life with money?
That's a trade secret.
Your life is your own to lead.
Don't ask me for advice.
Anyway…
you must have bad luck this year.
How many times has your life
come under threat already?
So why don't you
try to be a nicer person from now on?
Then good things will happen.
And solve that business with China.
Taera said she wanted to make
an investment in our duty-free business.
Your husband's mistress.
Or is she my husband's mistress?
Anyway,
her father is Jang Heungsoo,
the former justice of the Supreme Court.
-I know.
-Her mother isn't on the family register,
but Taera is.
Her half-brother is a famous fund manager
in Hong Kong.
She says she'll invest
in our duty-free business
if Yongmin's family pulls out
because of what you did.
-And you'll let her?
-That depends on you.
Mom. Hold on, Mom. Hold on.
I'll let you in. See you.
The lady of the house said
she'd be here to greet me.
Mom.
-Gosh, Taera. Hello.
-Mom.
Good grief.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
I can't let you do that.
Ms. Byeon, this is my mom.
-I know.
-So what do you think you're doing?
I'm afraid I can't let her in.
Wait. But why?
I could drop by
to say hello to the chairwoman.
You cannot enter
without the chairwoman's permission.
If you want to visit your daughter,
you can do so outside.
I'll do no such thing.
Follow me with those gifts my mom brought.
-Let's go, Mom.
-You can't do that.
Ms. Byeon, it's me.
- Let's go in, Mom.
- What's going on?
It's you, Wansoo!
You see, this woman here…
She doesn't realize who I am
and refuses to let me through.
Do you know who her father is?
Ms. Byeon. I'll talk to them.
I'll show you to the annex. Follow me.
Hey, you.
You should take these inside.
I've brought truffles and abalones
as big as my fist.
We can't let in food from the outside
that we don't know the origin of.
Follow me.
-Gosh, Mom.
-This is unbelievable.
Wait here.
A hedge fund manager in Hong Kong?
Yes, that's right.
Her brother is quite famous in Hong Kong.
And?
I heard that Yongmin's family
refused to make an investment…
ma'am.
Let me warn you.
Don't overstep your boundaries.
If you want anything, tell me.
What do you mean?
For staying out of our business.
Divorce him.
Try again with something that's possible.
Why are you doing this…
ma'am? My gosh.
Listen.
Do you want to be kicked out of the house
without your son?
Do you think I can't do that?
Regarding the terrorist attack,
we'll give you the details
after we've looked into it further.
-Yes, please do that.
-We're still checking.
We can't go into the details right now.
Why are you back already?
It was nothing serious.
I didn't need the rest.
But still…
are you sure you're all right?
What is it?
The original copies
of the foundation's ledgers
I mentioned before.
Give them to me.
Actually…
there are two of them.
The ledgers I have have been altered
for taxation purposes.
Then does Mr. Han have the real ledgers?
I thought you didn't want
to know about this.
Give them to me.
I'm a senior managing director at Hwain
despite not having a college degree.
Do you know what that means?
I take the fall should any problems arise.
I know.
And?
I'll think of something.
-Wansoo.
-Hyunsoo.
I hated our mother,
but I can't forget what I saw
when I visited her.
I did that. You had no part in it.
She paid too heavy a price.
And with the recent attack--
Is it revenge you want?
Do you want us
to dive headfirst into danger?
I'm not saying I'm going
to do something right away.
There's nothing people like us can do.
Chairwoman Park and Mr. Han
made sure of that already.
-Hyunsoo.
-What do you need the ledgers for?
You expose their slush fund, I go to jail,
and then what about you?
You're the director of NOW Foundation.
You'll go to jail too.
We'll both go to jail and that will be it.
-Is that what you call revenge?
-I'll think of something.
We need something
to be able to fight back against them.
Hyunsoo.
How long have you been standing there?
Not for long.
Go to bed.
But what if…
Father finds out?
He already knows.
Now go to bed.
Yes?
How are you feeling?
Why did you leave the hospital already?
I can receive outpatient treatment.
I'll get back to work
first thing tomorrow.
Was the video that Juhyuk left you
the footage of
the late chairman's body being moved?
Yes, sir.
Then you must already know
that I'm in that footage.
Yes, sir.
Why do you think he left it to you?
To let me know
that Chairman Kim Duo was murdered.
That's what he must have meant.
You said that you were there
on the day he died, didn't you?
-Yes, sir.
-Did you see the perpetrator?
It was the same person
who attacked Director Oh in Manila.
Did you see their face?
No, sir.
I found out
while staking out at Eight Star Fortune.
I noticed that the person had
a peculiar habit when using a knife.
And what's that?
You must still suspect me.
I ran another errand for the vice-chairman
to Eight Star Fortune.
Sir.
Go on.
Of all the people in Hwain,
who do you think wanted Chairman Kim Duo
and Director Oh gone the most?
I don't know.
How much do you think
the vice-chairman fits that profile?
The vice-chairman was loved
by the late chairman.
They had a great relationship.
He had no reason to do that to his father.
You went on an errand to deliver money
to Eight Star Fortune again.
I'm sure someone there
planned the recent attack as well.
Do you think the vice-chairman
could have had a part in this?
The vice-chairman? That's nonsense.
Doesn't the vice-chairman also need
NOW Foundation's slush funds to survive?
You should go back to the force.
If you want to find who killed Juhyuk,
you can do that as a policeman.
There won't be any trouble your way
if you had no part in Juhyuk's death.
You've given me plenty of trouble already.
I swear that I'll find…
the person who murdered Juhyuk.
I don't want to lose you as well.
Who had the most to gain
from Chairman Kim Duo's death?
-How should I know?
-What about the inheritance?
-How would I know that?
-Sir!
Please…
Please help me.
I'm begging you.
Eight Star Fortune…
The money you deliver there…
What is it for?
What the perpetrator is after
is NOW Foundation
where Hwain's slush fund is stored.
But why did they murder Chairman Kim Duo
who had nothing to do with the slush fund?
What are you doing here?
What about the CCTV?
Butler Byeon is the only one
who monitors the CCTVs here,
and she just left the house.
I'll get right to the point.
Go ahead.
The original copies
of NOW Foundation's ledgers
should be somewhere
in Mr. Han's study at the annex.
Please get that for me.
Be careful.
I'll leave now.
I'll take care of it,
so don't do anything.
You should go after
your friend's murderer.
I'll go after Hwain Group.
It's dangerous,
so please don't do anything.
I'm sure that the attacker is anxious
after failing again.
There's no telling what they'll do.
That's why…
we need something
that we can hold against them
in order to fight back.
Thank you
for coming back.
Two bags of onions
and two bags of cabbages.
- The same as last time?
- Yes, ma'am.
They're from the same grocer.
Grocery list
There are no CCTVs at the annex.
It's so that they can hide
whoever comes and goes.
This is where illegal meetings take place
and bribes are exchanged.
What are you doing there, K1?
It's nothing, sir.
What was she looking at?
I don't see anything.
Come here. Come here.
Good boy. Good dog.
Please scan your fingerprint again.
Ms. Byeon is looking for you.
You should head over.
The chairwoman asked me
to bring her some more water
since the meeting was dragging on.
Is that so? I'll do it.
Who's in there with her?
The chairwoman,
the vice-chairman, and Mr. Han.
Okay. You go ahead.
Okay.
You're the new head of the RF Team
who guards Director Oh, right?
Your fingerprint has been recognized.
What will you do about Cosmo Cosmetics?
I'll try to convince Vice-President Kim.
We'll split off our duty-free business
to leave to him as inheritance.
I don't see why not.
Then leave that to Mr. Han.
Pay no mind to Yongmin's antics.
Please enter the passcode.
Who? Seo Doyoon?
Yes, sir.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, sir.
Head to NOW Foundation immediately.
-Keep a close eye and report to me.
-Yes, sir.
Ledger
Year 2022
NOW Foundation
Senior Managing Director Baek
Your fingerprint has been recognized.
The Grand Palace
The safe has been unlocked.
Hwain Group slush fund management ledger
Year 2022
Is the director in?
Mr. Oh told me to deliver this bag
to Director Oh.
But Mr. Oh is already here.
He just arrived.
Yes.
I know.
I've brought the bag
that you asked for, Mr. Oh.
What? I did?
Give it to me.
You can go now.
No.
Let me hold on to it.
What is it?
Give me a moment, Hyunsoo.
It's dangerous. I'll hold onto it.
Hyunsoo.
What is it?
I'll see you later.
- We're from the prosecution.
- Hey.
- You can't go in!
- Hold on!
We're from the Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office.
What's going on?
This is a search and seizure warrant
for NOW Foundation.
We ask for your cooperation.
- Start searching.
- Yes, sir.
And…
this is an arrest warrant.
Mr. Oh. You're under arrest
for embezzling funds from NOW Foundation.
- Take him in.
- Yes, sir.
Come with us.
Translated by Sony Hong