This drama series is fictional
and is not related in any way
to actual places, persons,
organizations, settings, and events.
Do you know why I called you here?
-No, sir.
You will take note of the people
the president meets privately.
Senior Inspector Shin will secretly
investigate the slush funds
kept by those
who met the president in private
and report your findings
to me and no one else.
Yes, sir.
Restricted area
Why did you want to see me?
Before his death, Senior Inspector Shin
was looking into Hwain's slush funds.
And?
Do you still despise me for what happened?
You covered up his death.
That was because Senior Inspector Shin
failed to find any evidence.
How was I supposed to arrest those behind
Eight Star Fortune without evidence
when they were based in Manila?
Back then,
I wrongly suspected you.
Just come out and ask me
if I was in cahoots with Hwain Group.
I can't say
that I still don't suspect you.
It's all in the past now.
So why did you want to see me?
I'm here to report to you
about Hwain's slush funds and the suspect
behind the recent terror attacks.
But first,
there's intel I've obtained
about Hwain through the NIS.
It is said the former president
has hidden away
a large amount of his slush fund abroad
through his son, Chairman Kim Duo.
I'm sorry?
They must plan to use it
to make Hwain's first son the successor.
Find out how they plan
to bring the money back from Switzerland.
That's what you should do first.
Senior Inspector Shin's attacker
must be related to
Chairman Kim Duo's slush funds somehow.
Red Swan
Episode 9
Do you want something, sir?
- I'm okay.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Could I get some water, please?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Peter.
I'm going to Switzerland right now.
There's an important matter
I'd like to discuss,
so please let me know
when we can talk privately over the phone.
Are you left-handed?
No, I'm not.
How tall are you?
I'm 5 ft 8 in.
Why?
The flower shop delivery is complete.
It's nothing.
It's just that you look taller than that.
Wait.
Can you speak Chinese by any chance?
Not at all.
Why do you ask?
Never mind. It's nothing.
You should get back to work.
How could I have not thought
that Mr. L could be a woman?
Why do you ask?
Evidence…
I need evidence.
Zürich, Switzerland
My slush fund of 16 trillion won
is being kept at Celli Bank in Switzerland
and can only be retrieved
if Ms. Oh Wansoo visits in person
and signs for its withdrawal.
This way.
It's a great pleasure to meet both of you.
Ms. Oh.
Before we begin,
we do need to check some information.
Thank you very much.
Your biometric information
is a perfect match
with the data we have
from the late Mr. Kim.
However, we do need
to proceed with caution
as the amount of money involved here
is quite substantial.
Of course.
A few days ago
Oh, my fucking lord!
Can you believe this?
It's 18 trillion won!
- Can you?
- Be quiet for a second.
Both of you sit down.
Even if we split it
between the three of us,
we'll be getting over five trillion each.
Right?
Between the three of us?
Didn't you listen to what the will said?
So you're going to keep it
all for yourself?
Can't you punks shut up?
We've got a problem on our hands
that we might not be able to solve
even if we were to put our heads together.
That senile fool is giving me trouble
even from beyond the grave.
Don't stress yourself too much, Mom.
Listen. There's 18 trillion won,
and 16 trillion of it
is from an illegal slush fund.
Even the remaining 2 trillion is stored in
illegal borrowed-name accounts.
That's not a small amount.
It won't be easy to launder all of it.
We won't ever get it done
with the launderer that we have.
Without help from the launderers
in Hong Kong or New York,
there's no way it can happen.
He donated the money.
You don't have a share.
You can't do that to me.
So you'll keep everything for yourself?
Whoever ends up getting it,
we'll need to launder it first.
We should split it three ways
to keep things fair.
We can't split it three ways.
Yongkook's succession
needs to go smoothly,
so most of that money
will be spent on that.
You can't be serious!
I don't intend to let anyone
have more than an exact three-way split.
Father donated the entire amount
to NOW Foundation
so that Wansoo could use it
for a good cause.
Are you nuts?
This isn't some chump change.
You're going to give it all to Wansoo
so she can waste all of it?
What can we do
when that's what Father wanted?
That's not what he wanted at all!
It's a slush fund
that was illegally acquired.
There's no way for us to retrieve it.
He only said he was donating it
because he had no way of giving it to us.
So he donated it to the foundation
so we can launder it little by little
to use in your succession
and also make good use of
the money he left us.
He just had it siphoned
through the foundation.
Stop getting ahead of yourselves
and stay out of it.
Let Wansoo do what she wants with it.
I said I would never let that happen.
How dare you try
to con me out of my share?
You must have lost it.
-How dare you touch me?
-It's not a small amount.
You're not even a member of the family.
-What was that?
-Both of you.
Be quiet!
If you understand what I meant,
just keep living quietly like a mouse.
Why don't I just report you?
I'll tell everyone
that the former president's son
had been keeping a slush fund
worth 16 trillion won in Switzerland.
Do you want the entire world
to know about that?
Don't you dare threaten me!
Fine.
We'll split it in half.
Forget about Mom.
We'll split the money in half.
Hey. You're not getting any.
Why would you need
all that money at your age?
You really must have gone nuts.
That's right. I'm completely nuts.
There's no telling what I'd do
unless you give me half of that money!
Keep that in mind.
Do you think that's the only thing
I have on you two?
I'm warning both you and Mom.
Unless you want to spend
the rest of your life in prison,
you better give me my fair share.
I was told that Father
could have been murdered.
Do you know who killed him?
How the fuck should I know that?
You…
What did you just say?
Are you saying I killed him?
What are you talking about?
That's strange.
I said he could have been murdered.
Shouldn't you be surprised to hear that?
Do you know who did it by any chance?
How would I know who killed him?
What about Mr. Han?
Does he know who did it?
Hey. Have you gone insane?
Prison?
You're the one
who should be worried about that.
Fucking hell! Seriously!
You're the one who's trying
to keep the money for yourself!
"Fucking hell"?
It doesn't matter how much.
I will never let you get your hands
on my father's money.
Not a single penny.
Get lost.
Damn it.
He's a complete thief.
What are you going to do?
What are you staring at me for?
Why did you do it?
What?
To Chairman Kim Duo.
You're asking me that now?
Why didn't you say anything then?
I was so shocked…
that I couldn't ask you then.
Who are you to ask me why I did that now?
Forget about it.
If I kill Oh Wansoo,
NOW Foundation will become mine.
And after you kill her?
It will be easy to siphon the money
from the foundation and have it laundered
although it will take long.
Fine.
Should I have Oh Wansoo killed?
Why would those terrorists
stop in the middle of their attack?
It would have been great
if she quietly died in Manila.
If that happened, we would have never
found the money in Switzerland.
Is that so?
I'm sure he made it so the money could be
accessed even after her death.
It's complicated.
She was to withdraw the money,
not inherit it.
Enough of that nonsense.
Once Oh Wansoo retrieves
the money from Switzerland,
wouldn't it be okay to kill her then?
You've been the lawyer of this household
for over 30 years.
So how did you not know
that the old man had that much money
and that he planned to give it all
to the foundation?
Let's give it some thought.
Be quiet for a second.
Don't order me around.
Please leave, sir.
I have a lot on my mind.
Get it done, okay?
I'll look into the places
where we can launder the money.
Now that I think about it,
that was out of the blue.
Did you see me kill the old man?
He just dropped dead.
You pretended to believe me then.
Why are you accusing me now?
You've ruined my mood.
Sir.
Sir…
He… He just fell.
He was talking to me then he just…
He suddenly collapsed.
What are you doing here?
You should have told me.
I'm telling you, he just collapsed.
He really did!
You should
take Jiyeon with you
to the vacation home in Yongpyeong.
Why would she go on a trip with me?
Just take her
and buy her a gift
like a necklace or something.
Just get out of here!
You were never here today.
Mr. Park. Where are you?
Come to Nonhyeon-dong.
Let me take that for you.
- You're so pretty, Wansoo.
- Hello.
I'm such a fan.
Did you have a nice trip?
Yes.
The car is parked over there.
All right. Take a seat over there.
I gave it some thought
and I think I have a great idea.
Please go on.
We'll use Oh Hyunsoo.
Oh Wansoo's brother.
How so?
We'll have him launder all the money
that Wansoo brought back from Switzerland.
What is she going to do
when her brother is involved in it?
And?
We'll launder the money
and use it to purchase Hwain Bio stocks
under Yongkook's name.
It's a holding company.
With simple legwork,
his succession will become very easy.
What about Mr. Oh then?
He will decide to take his own life
out of guilt for embezzlement.
Perfect, right?
What's this?
Are you trying to negotiate with me
so that I'll share the money with Yongmin
in return for your help?
I'll think about it.
I come to you with a helpful idea
and this is what I get.
Yongmin is sure to receive
a small share of the money.
That damn mooch.
Both father and son are so greedy.
Why would he want what's mine?
What right does he have?
He should be grateful
that I'm willing to give him even scraps.
How dare he try to get in my son's way?
He's nothing but a lowly servant.
How dare he?
I'll make a deal with them
using the ledgers.
That's too dangerous.
These ledgers…
How about we just hand them over
to the prosecution right away?
Just leave it to me.
This is too big for us
to take on ourselves.
There's no talking to you, is there?
We'll hand over the ledgers
to the prosecution
and tell the world about the donation
that the former chairman made.
We can't do that
without any solid proof.
They'll destroy what they can't have.
And the money from Switzerland
is from an illegal slush fund,
so it won't be easy
for the prosecution to trace it.
They'll just accuse her of lying
because she wants a divorce,
kill her, and make it look
like an accident.
But it's too dangerous for us
to contact them now.
We could end up losing the ledgers.
I'll make a deal with Mr. Han.
Listen closely.
Your sister's life was in danger
all this time because of that money.
The ledgers are the only way
that we can find whoever is behind this.
The person behind this? Who?
Mr. Han?
Yongmin?
They're all innocent
according to the ledgers, so how?
They already know we have the ledgers
so they're useless.
We need to get our hands on new evidence.
About Kim Yongmin…
It's true that he was born out of wedlock,
but he bears no relation
to the late chairman.
-I'm sorry?
-What?
I found this in Mr. Han's safe.
His entire fortune
was put into a trust.
And the trustee is Kim Yongmin.
Are you saying that Yongmin was born
between the chairwoman and Mr. Han?
They're after NOW Foundation
for the slush fund
since it didn't seem likely
that he'd become Hwain's successor.
That's why they've been after your life.
So that's why Yongmin
reported the embezzlement.
Revenue of trust certificate
Then the person
who tried to kill me was Yongmin?
It could have been him
or it could have been Mr. Han
who wanted his son to receive that money.
Lee Jin the bodyguard…
Is she a Chinese emigrant?
I don't know.
All I know is that she graduated
from the Police University.
Why do you ask?
Watch out for her.
Don't ever let yourself be alone with her.
I'm trying to find evidence against her.
But she's loyal to the chairwoman.
She doesn't work for Mr. Han or Yongmin.
Her loyalty to the chairwoman
could be a cover.
Are you saying that K1 was behind
all the attacks ever since Manila?
She can handle all those weapons?
I'm looking into it.
First of all,
I'll give you the ledgers.
Remember what I said.
You have to be careful
of Mr. Han.
Both of you too.
Stay safe.
Let me know when you go to see Mr. Han.
Okay.
I hear what you're saying.
So it's difficult to bring
everything into Korea at once?
Yes. We'll need to make some arrangements.
And there will be a hefty commission
that you can't avoid to pay.
Let's keep in touch.
Bye.
Vice-Chairman Kim Yongkook
Where did you go?
Now you ask me where I am?
Where are you?
Okay. I understand.
What did he say? Is he coming here?
He is,
but he's going to take
Junhee out for a moment.
Junhee? Is he going to kidnap Junhee?
He's Junhee's father.
Why would he do that?
Officially speaking,
he's Junhee's brother.
Whatever.
But think about it.
The late Chairman Kim Duo
left them an enormous fortune,
and you're his supposed second wife.
And as for Junhee,
he's Chairman Kim's son
officially speaking.
I guess he has a claim to the inheritance.
Get over here.
Vice-President Kim Yongmin
-Now!
-Managing Director Jin.
I'll talk to you later.
What's with you?
Where are your manners?
Did you embezzle the company's funds
to buy Hwain Bio stocks?
-Who told you that?
-Did you buy them or not?
I just thought I should buy them
while the prices were down
after Wansoo's brother was arrested.
My company's money isn't yours.
How is this your company?
This is your dad's company.
You must be dying to go to prison.
Prison? Did you say prison?
You better return
the money you took right away.
Buying their stocks
would only do them good.
I didn't buy them to help them.
Wake up.
You can never win against Yongkook.
Why do you think you were
married into our family?
Your family was taking the trash out
and dumping it on us.
Why you…
I'm going to report it to Dad if you don't
return the money in three days.
Snap out of it.
Report it.
Go ahead.
I'm not the same Yongmin
you used to know yesterday.
Don't you know how much my father
has saved up in his slush fund?
-I see.
-Didn't you tell your father yet?
And they'll share it with you?
To you? Your mom is going to do that?
I won't be asking for handouts
like some beggar.
I don't think you know me that well.
Bring me the money then.
You don't think I can do it.
When your family dumped you on us,
she didn't even bother to give you
a single subsidiary.
I know that she's afraid
to split up the group,
but how could she send you
to us empty-handed?
I'm going to take over Hwain!
Bring back the money you took!
Do you still not understand?
You fucking deaf?
Hello.
Are you here alone?
You told me to come alone
so the driver brought me here.
Right. How about we go for a walk?
Okay.
Why did you want to see me?
I have something to tell you.
I also wanted to ask you some questions.
Go on and tell me.
Do you know who I am?
You're the vice-chairman.
Dad…
You knew?
Hey, duck! Get down, come on!
Mom. We're too beautiful.
Hiding won't do anything for us.
I guess we're not in the wrong
since we came here worried about Junhee.
I wonder what they're talking about.
You see…
I'm going to…
break up with your mom.
I understand.
I wanted to ask you something.
Who I want to live with?
I see
that you take after me.
You're quick-witted and brave.
And you don't let anyone know
when you're hurting inside.
I'll live with Mom.
You have a big family at the Grand Palace.
If I go to live there,
Mom won't have anyone else.
We'll live with Grandma.
I'll live with Mom and Grandma.
I might…
never be able to visit you or your mom
ever again.
Would that
still be okay?
We can meet later
when I grow up, right?
Of course.
Then it's fine.
Goodbye.
Wait. Why are you leaving already?
I'll be meeting him
at ten tonight
under Haengju Bridge at the Han River.
Are you going somewhere?
It's late.
Yes. I was going out
to see a friend of mine.
Sure. Have fun.
Yes. I'll see you later.
There aren't any CCTVs
in that area by the Han River.
I'll be watching nearby
but please be careful.
Calls
Calling
Seo Doyoon
Mr. Oh Hyunsoo
Recording call
The money was moved
to the Canadian account safely.
I saw the deposit.
Are you planning never to come back?
I don't know.
Does your sister know
that her brother is taking money
and leaving for Canada to hide?
I should tell her now.
Give me the ledgers.
Let me ask you one thing before I do that.
Was Chairman Kim Duo murdered?
What?
Cut the nonsense.
Who was it that tried to kill Wansoo?
What is it that you want to know?
Can you promise Wansoo's safety
if she gets a divorce and gives up
all her rights over NOW Foundation?
What are you planning to do
with Chairman Kim Duo's slush fund?
It's none of your business
since you'll be leaving.
What price must Wansoo or I pay…
for you to assure
that Wansoo will be safe?
Why are you asking me that?
I can convince her to get a divorce,
but I won't be able to talk her into
giving up the foundation completely,
even more so now.
Director Oh has always valued
the foundation even more so than her life.
You should just keep
looking out for yourself.
Mr. Oh Hyunsoo
Stop recording
Emergency Medical Service.
I'm on the bank of the Han River.
Can you track my location
and send an ambulance?
His main artery has been cut.
-Hey…
-You shouldn't talk.
Is this the Central District
Prosecutors' Office?
I wanted to make a report
regarding Hwain Group and NOW Foundation.
The Grand Palace
Good evening.
I'm Prosecutor Seo Jinsoo from Seoul
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
What is the meaning of this at this hour?
Do you have a warrant
for search and seizure?
We're not actually here to do that.
I'm here because there's something
I need to tell the chairwoman in person.
Don't you think it's rude
to visit without letting us know first?
I'll tell Mr. Han.
Wait. He's not in right now.
I saw him go out earlier.
Should I call him?
I'll do it.
Please wait.
We'll discuss it with our lawyer first.
Sure thing. I'll allow that much.
Goodbye.
- Please wait.
- Take your time.
He's not answering.
Stay there for a moment.
Please wait a little longer.
We did our best not to look conspicuous.
We won't take long.
I told you to wait.
Why isn't he answering his phone?
I've called him over 20 times now
but he's not answering.
Twenty? Keep calling him.
Vice-Chairman Kim.
Where are you right now?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
There she is.
What's going on here?
Where's Mr. Han?
Are prosecutors allowed to
do things like this at such a late hour?
We thought it'd be best
to tell her in person,
since she's such an important figure.
What's he on about?
Hello, ma'am.
I'm Prosecutor Seo Jinsoo of Seoul
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
And?
We have your summons.
I came here
to hand it to you personally.
- Summons?
- Yes, ma'am.
Should I wait for your lawyer
and speak to him before I go?
It's fine. Give the summons to me.
Here you go.
Leave if you're done here.
Our lawyer will contact you soon.
Well, then…
Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
The killer…
is K1.
Whose order could she be following?
That's who we're after.
I'm sorry.
We did our best,
but the patient has passed.
What's going on?
Hey.
Still no word from Mr. Han?
His phone still seems to be switched off.
That nutjob.
Where could he be
and what could he be up to?
Keep calling him.
We've been calling him nonstop overnight.
He must be clueless about the state
this family is in right now.
He's supposed to be our lawyer.
Jeez.
I'll step inside.
First, you should sit down.
I'm sorry.
Two hours ago…
No…
I thought
I should tell you this in person.
Two hours ago…
Mr. Oh…
passed away.
Where?
On a bank near the Han River.
He was taken straight to the hospital…
but he had lost too much blood.
-Where is the morgue?
-The reporters have gathered outside.
Ms. Yoon told me
that the chairwoman
is going to the prosecution soon.
That's why the reporters must be here.
You should leave after she does.
I'm sorry.
This is hell.
I think I might go insane.
I feel so suffocated
that I might lose my mind.
My poor brother…
What do I do now?
I've lost my brother as well.
What am I to do now?
12 missed calls from Ms. Yoon
7 missed calls from Ms. Byeon
16 missed calls from Mr. Park
14 missed calls from Ms. Yoon
One new unread message
Look at you.
What took you so long to get here?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I took some cold medication and…
So you were sleeping soundly
while this house was turned upside down?
We should go.
I've made the preparations.
The prosecution will just ask you
a few simple questions.
You don't need to do anything.
I'll take care of everything for you.
What's gotten into them?
Why would they summon me?
Don't tell me they're going to arrest me.
Mr. Oh
seems to have handed over
the ledgers to the prosecution.
He did?
It's not a big deal. I'll take care of it.
Wait.
I thought you said Wansoo's lover handed
the ledgers over to the prosecution.
I managed to sweep it under the rug
but Mr. Oh went ahead
and exposed the ledgers.
Keep your head clear
and follow me to the prosecutors' office.
All you need to do is sit there.
Are you sure
that the ledgers don't include
anything incriminating?
Of course. We should go.
The reporters have gathered outside.
I'm going to end up photographed.
There's no telling
how the public will react to this.
I've also taken measures against that.
It's time. Hold on.
Oh Wansoo's affair
The news about
the slush fund was covered up
with news of Oh Wansoo's affair.
The car is ready outside the gates.
You must now walk out the front gate
and deal with the reporters.
All you have to say to them is,
"I don't know anything about that."
Just what is going to happen to me?
We should head out for now.
Don't forget to keep looking confident.
You want me to leave like this?
Hey. There's been breaking news.
-What is it?
-Let me see.
-What's that?
-There was breaking news.
Let's check.
- What's this?
- Was this uploaded just now?
Oh Wansoo's affair?
Siphoned off slush funds with lover
It was uploaded just now.
It must be true.
No way.
-There she comes.
-There she is.
-She's here.
-She's coming.
- There she comes.
- There she is.
Move… Please.
I am sorry
for the inconvenience I've caused.
I will fully cooperate
with the prosecution's investigation
so that this misunderstanding
can be resolved.
Is the news
about Ms. Oh true?
Is her affair related to the slush funds?
The rumors spread by tabloids
have now been plastered all over the news.
Is it true?
Remain dignified. They're taking photos.
Then was the slush fund
at NOW Foundation
created by Director Oh,
who was planning to divorce her husband?
Is the news of Ms. Oh's affair true?
Who is the man she's with?
Why would you ask me that?
Is Ms. Oh in the house right now?
Will she be divorcing her husband?
Well, I really don't know
anything about that.
- We should go.
- Wait.
- Please give us a word.
- Talk to us.
- Chairwoman.
- Please answer us.
- Can you give us some answers?
- Please tell us.
Will Ms. Oh be coming out?
There still are
a lot of reporters outside.
Should I tell the chairwoman
about Mr. Oh's passing?
No. That won't be necessary.
She won't attend his funeral anyway.
But shouldn't you at least tell
the vice-chairman about this?
That won't be necessary.
I don't think you should
head out right now.
That's right. The news sites have
been plastered with articles about you.
You should wait upstairs for now.
-Please take her upstairs.
-All right.
Hyunsoo's wife should be
arriving at the airport.
I'll go to meet her.
You should head upstairs.
Vice-president's office
I got the news. Wansoo's brother died.
We're getting divorced.
You've put up all of my stocks as well
as my father's stocks as collateral
to buy even more Hwain Bio stocks.
You're a complete con man!
I told you already.
Before I divorce you,
I should report you to the police first.
Give me a break!
Your father gave me his permission.
What?
Father allowed me to do that.
What did you say?
What's all this?
Photos of you cheating on me.
I showed Father every last one of them.
You backstabbing punk.
You blackmailed him?
You punk. You bastard.
You jerk. You deceitful prick!
Did you film me having sex as well?
Yes.
I'm not getting a divorce.
I won't let you divorce me.
-Yongmin.
-And I'm putting everything into Hwain.
I won't let you off
if you ever get in my way.
You've messed with the wrong person.
Those photos?
Send them over to the press
and not just my dad.
Spread it worldwide for everyone to see!
I'm rich enough.
Cheating isn't reserved for men.
I'm going to be just fine.
As for you,
I'll make sure that you end up
crawling in the gutters.
You've messed with the wrong person.
I'm going to make you
lose everything you've got!
I won't ever forgive you.
We offer our condolences
The late Oh Hyunsoo
Here she comes!
PROSECUTION SERVICE
Will Hwain Group
be investigated as well?
-This is unbelievable.
-Were you aware of Ms. Oh's affair?
- How is Ms. Oh involved?
- Is it true?
-Please give us a word.
-What will happen to Hwain Group?
Just one comment, please.
Is Ms. Oh involved
with the slush funds?
- Tell us about the foundation's funds.
- How much is there?
- Answer us, please.
- Can you please tell us?
-Give us a word.
-Please wait.
About those reporters…
There weren't as many as I expected.
Did they all go
to report on Oh Wansoo's affair?
That would be for the best.
Let's stop by for some dumpling soup.
Yes, ma'am.
You should stay
at a hotel for the time being.
There's work to be done
with the reporters and everything else.
Work?
Why did you kill
Oh Wansoo's brother?
He embezzled money
and he was a gambling addict.
I guess a loan shark killed him.
Will everything be over then?
I'm doing my best.
You're sure
that I'll be safe, right?
We've even
had a son together.
I know I can trust you.
I felt bad that I couldn't give
something big to Yongmin.
I can see
how you might find that upsetting.
But you see,
I've built this company up
by entering a loveless marriage.
I need to protect Hwain.
Who succeeds the company
to protect it in the future
is what's really important.
Don't tell me
that you wanted Yongmin
to succeed the company
instead of Yongkook.
Is there a reason why he shouldn't?
Who in the world would have
the son they had with their concubine
succeed the company?
Does that make me a concubine?
Of course you are one.
My gosh.
Yongmin's in-laws have plenty of money.
That's more than enough for him.
So you're saying he has enough
for the son of a concubine?
Please enter the passcode.
The safe has been unlocked.
He told me to give it to Mr. Seo Doyoon
should something happen to him.
Well…
I actually have another favor to ask you.
Please tell the prosecution
that the evidence your husband prepared
is inside Mr. Han Sangil's safe at Hwain.
Translated by Sony Hong