♪I have seen the mountains
and the ocean in your eyes♪
♪Passing through virtual dreams♪
♪I share with you some of my luck♪
♪Writing you into
all four of my seasons♪
♪A gentle wind in the summer♪
♪Shooting stars in the night sky♪
♪You're my little stroke of luck♪
=Misfortune Miss and Lucky Mr=
=Episode 14=
Ms. Shen, you're a good actress.
Gu Yichen,
what's wrong?
The gentleman left.
Does the bet still count?
Let's meet him now
and get him to honor his promise
to invest in the company.
Why would he invest in the company?
Because we're getting engaged.
You know quite a lot, Ms. Shen.
Is there anything else
you'd like to remind me of?
(I messed it up tonight.)
(Gu Yichen is really angry now.)
I know my absence
has affected the funding.
But it was the driver
who took me out
to the outskirts of the town.
I barely managed
to escape and come back.
Gu Yichen,
let's meet the gentleman right now
and get him to invest in the company,
okay?
Ms. Shen,
there's no need
to humble yourself so much.
Gu Yichen,
why are you saying that?
I ran three hours
across half the town
just to fulfill your wish.
Are you giving up
over a little setback?
My wish?
What about yours, Ms. Shen?
My wish
is to be with you.
Why did you look into my wardrobe?
Didn't we talk about this?
How long are you going
to keep fooling me?
Where are you from?
Why did you approach me?
What do you want?
Who sent you?
Did you do all this for the luck stat?
Holding hands adds 30,
a hug add 50,
a kiss adds 500,
and double the stat if I fall for you.
Ms. Shen,
you've calculated everything so well.
Gu Yichen,
I admit
that I approached you
with an intention in the beginning.
I thought you were an obnoxious,
overbearing president.
But the closer I got to you,
the more I...
You had this bag
to get close to me, didn't you?
Ms. Shen,
you've planned every step
so meticulously
and made me fall for it.
Calm down, Gu Yichen.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Ah!
We'll talk this out,
or you're not leaving.
Gu Yichen,
I hate it so much
when you act like an overbearing boss.
A childish boss like a high schooler,
right?
Do you think you're so smart
that you'd know the entire truth
with a few words?
Tell me everything, then.
Do you think
they'll break up this time?
I don't see this happening, though.
Shen Qingge,
♪Sorting out vague memories,
following you♪
tell me
who you are.
♪Slowly, the distance
between the two shadows grows♪
This bag.
♪No longer like you♪
I don't need it anymore.
You don't need it?
Is it because you've gained
enough luck stat from me? Right?
♪The luggage is packed. I can♪
You approach me,
get close to me,
and move into my house
all because of the luck stat.
Gu Yichen,
you're an entitled,
full of flaws,
and completely oblivious fool!
Right.
♪Tick-tock-tick-tock,
whispering to time♪
I'm just a stupid fictional character.
♪The first dream remains
with you by my side♪
I'm so stupid
that I fell in love with you.
♪We are too forgetful♪
♪Back to back, we left in a hurry♪
♪A love across an endless journey♪
Chen left.
Seems like they're completely through.
Hurry.
Let's go and comfort him.
♪When I turn back, I can't see♪
Why bother doing that?
♪The street where we met♪
He finds out everything.
♪You vanished in the crowd
and never returned♪
♪My finger curls up in helplessness♪
(If this is a novel,)
(is all my effort
to make the company go public)
(arranged by the author?)
(Why would I even do that?)
(To escape Grandma's control?)
(But why would Grandma control me?)
(To protect Grandfather's
and Father's life's work?)
(And who are my grandfather and father?)
(What kind of people are they?)
(Why am I not concerned about all this?)
(What exactly do I care about?)
♪Our world ends with a period♪
♪Being pulled apart,
surpassing light-years♪
♪But I forgot to say goodbye♪
How come you always hit a red light?
All the lights are green for Chen.
You should just ride in his car.
I...
Chen pulled over.
He must've seen me.
Go to him.
Hurry.
Red light.
You were driving slower and slower,
that's why we couldn't catch up.
I told you to speed up.
What's wrong with you?
I don't want you to go to him.
What else could it be?
Why not?
Because I just don't want you to.
(If this is really the world
of a novel,)
(there must be boundaries.)
Chen,
Zhao Moran told me
that woman fooled you.
Let's ignore her, okay?
I won't do that to you.
I'm willing to do anything for you.
Ms. Wei,
I'm very tired now.
Can you leave me alone?
Chen.
Hey.
Send Ms. Wei home.
All right, Mr. Gu.
Even so,
he still won't choose me.
When you finally get something
you've dreamed of,
you can't help but smile.
I never needed
to dream about anything I want.
Seems like being too lucky
isn't something
to feel happy about either.
Suddenly, you look so pitiful to me.
(Do I?)
♪That person who often
appears in your dreams♪
♪Is the one you love deeply
and can never forget
♪You always believed
they would be with you for life♪
♪But missing them
taught you what fate is♪
♪Holding them in your heart
without speaking of it♪
♪Pretending to be strong♪
♪Always thinking the world
won't go on without them♪
♪Being alone,
you never learn how to let go♪
♪The one you love the most♪
♪The one you miss the most♪
This should be the boundaries
of the novel's world.
♪How many remain?♪
So I'm a fictional character.
♪The scars you soothed for them
in the night♪
♪The one you miss the most♪
♪Leaving no regrets in your youth♪
Gu Yichen,
you're an entitled,
full of flaws, and oblivious fool!
I'm indeed foolish and absurd.
I'm always full of myself,
but in fact, I'm nothing.
The high and mighty
president of Gu Group
is nothing but a joke.
You're so lucky,
but why are you so angry every day?
You're showing a cold face
to your clients.
Can't you just smile a bit?
Not only can I not smile,
♪Always thinking the world
won't go on without them♪
but I also don't have
the basic emotions of a human.
♪Always thinking the world
won't go on without them♪
I have no idea what familial love is.
♪Being alone,
you never learn how to let go♪
I have no friends
♪The one you love the most♪
or love.
♪The one you miss the most♪
The girl I think loves me
♪How many remain?♪
is actually using me.
♪The scars you soothed for them
in the night♪
Gu Yichen,
♪The one you miss the most♪
you think you're smart, don't you?
♪Leaving no regrets in your youth♪
But you can't even notice
Shen Qingge's tricks.
♪Accompanying you to complete
every journey♪
How pathetic you are.
Lily,
have you heard any news about Gu Yichen?
Not yet.
I've sent out more people
to look for Mr. Gu.
How about you?
I've searched all the places
we went together,
but still...
Good day, audience.
Breaking news.
A male corpse was found by the river
in the city.
It's suspected to be a case of drowning.
The police have sealed off the area
for an investigation.
♪The spring breeze
carries a floral rain♪
♪There are you and me in the scenery♪
♪The clouds are low, the mountains
are green, and the sunlight is peaceful♪
♪I happen to encounter you♪
♪I have seen the mountains
and the ocean in your eyes♪
♪Passing through virtual dreams♪
♪I share with you some of my luck♪
♪And you uncover my little secrets♪
♪A gentle wind in the summer♪
♪Shooting stars in the night sky♪
♪You are my little stroke of luck♪
♪Too afraid to believe
our love chances upon each other♪
♪I hold you tightly♪
♪The clear skies after a downpour♪
♪A sweet moment in loneliness♪
♪You always bring warmth to my life♪
♪Walking slowly with you,
anticipating the future♪
♪How lucky I was
to have met you long ago♪