♪I have seen the mountains
and the ocean in your eyes♪
♪Passing through virtual dreams♪
♪I share with you some of my luck♪
♪Writing you into
all four of my seasons♪
♪A gentle wind in the summer♪
♪Shooting stars in the night sky♪
♪You're my little stroke of luck♪
=Misfortune Miss and Lucky Mr=
=Episode 13=
Sir, sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Chen, you've changed a lot.
Why?
Do you have good news for me this time?
Right.
I'd like to invite you
to my engagement ceremony.
That's great.
Looks like I'm going to lose the bet
we made before.
Right.
Bet?
The Gu Group plans to go public,
and we need your cooperation.
Gu Yichen's engagement
will help the company go public?
What kind of girl is she?
Upright,
kind,
brave,
and she knows me.
She knows you?
Looks like she loves you very much.
We're in love with each other.
Where's she?
Bring Ms. Qingge here.
Should we serve the dishes now?
All right.
The subscriber you've dialed
is unreachable.
Please try again.
Seems like this isn't your true love.
I'm sorry.
There's something urgent
I need to take care of right now.
It's all right.
We'll meet again after that.
I must do this.
Mr. Gu,
I found out something.
I think
you need to know the truth.
I need to find Shen Qingge now.
Let's talk on the way.
(Today's very important to Gu Yichen.)
(I can't mess this up.)
(Let me rehearse what I'm going to say
to the gentleman.)
Hello, sir.
I'm Shen Qingge,
Gu Yichen's fiancee.
Since the Gu Group
acquired the Shen Group
and helped them overcome difficulties,
I've become luckier.
No.
I've become happier.
We're going the wrong way, sir.
Sir.
Isn't the Huaqiao Hotel downtown?
Where is this place?
Stop the car, sir.
Drop me off here.
Stop, sir.
I want to get out here.
There's a signal blocker in the car.
You won't be able to make calls.
Ms. Shen,
please sit tight.
I won't hurt you.
But if the car goes out of control,
the consequence isn't what we want.
Please, sir.
Today's very important to Mr. Gu.
I need to be there.
Please send me back.
What do you want?
I'll give you anything you ask for
after today.
I'm begging you, sir.
Let me go back.
Where is this place?
Where am I going?
Qingge should've left home by now.
Why did you bring me here?
Mr. Gu,
aren't you going to invite me in?
Qingge,
are you home?
Sir,
please open the door.
Hey.
Sir,
please open the door.
Sir.
Hey.
The president of Gu Group
is actually living here.
I feel bad for you.
What are you trying to get at?
What are you doing?
Do you know what's inside this, Mr. Gu?
According to Ms. Shen's custom,
men shouldn't open women's wardrobes.
What are you trying to do?
Ms. Shen has been using you.
(Luck stat to go home: 10,000,
Hold hands +30, Hug+50, Travel, Mrs. Gu)
Hey.
That ruddy novel has been
torturing me for the past week.
I was transferred to the front desk
because of it.
Can you stop talking like Gu Yichen?
So,
we can pretend to be close
to cover your ambition
to acquire the Wei Group.
How did you know my plan?
How did you know that the company
was going public?
I read the novel.
I've noticed
that when I get close to you,
everything goes smoother for you.
This is my first aid kit
during my tough time.
Now that I have you,
I don't need it anymore.
Have you ever made a bet?
About marriage and investment?
(Turns out)
(she gets close to me)
(not because she loves me.)
Hey.
I beg of you, sir.
Sir.
All right.
(Gu Yichen,)
(wait for me.)
(I'm coming for you.)
Gu Yichen,
I thought I'd never see you again.
You have no idea
where the driver tried to take me.
Ms. Shen, you're a good actress.
♪The spring breeze
carries a floral rain♪
♪There are you and me in the scenery♪
♪The clouds are low, the mountains
are green, and the sunlight is peaceful♪
♪I happen to encounter you♪
♪I have seen the mountains
and the ocean in your eyes♪
♪Passing through virtual dreams♪
♪I share with you some of my luck♪
♪And you uncover my little secrets♪
♪A gentle wind in the summer♪
♪Shooting stars in the night sky♪
♪You are my little stroke of luck♪
♪Too afraid to believe
our love chances upon each other♪
♪I hold you tightly♪
♪The clear skies after a downpour♪
♪A sweet moment in loneliness♪
♪You always bring warmth to my life♪
♪Walking slowly with you,
anticipating the future♪
♪How lucky I was
to have met you long ago♪