A Little Thing Called First Love
♫ I can't find a way ♫
♫ To prove that love is biased  ♫
♫ I want to give it up ♫
♫ I keep fighting with myself ♫
♫  Pretending that I don't care ♫
♫  Pretending to be busy every day ♫
♫  But in the end, I could not endure it ♫
♫ I want to know what you're now up to ♫
♫ You're all that I can see ♫
♫ You're in my heart every minute, every second ♫
♫ I must control myself and forget you ♫
♫ Not willing to fall into the trap of
a love like this ♫
♫ You're all that I can see ♫
♫ You're in my heart every minute, every second ♫
♫  I must control myself and forget you ♫
♫ But I unknowingly wrote about you in my diary ♫
♫ If this is love ♫
♫ Why does it feel strange? ♫
♫ Don't know how it came so suddenly ♫
♫ Maybe time will slowly bring the answer ♫
♫ Stretch out your hand ♫
♫ And drive away my uneasy dreams ♫
♫ According to you, our encounter ♫
♫ Is the result of Heaven's favor ♫
Episode 35
Ten Months Later
Have you reached a consensus with Frank yet?
Not yet.
I argued with him all night yesterday just for him to allow me to come up with another design.
Then let's come up with a few more.
There's no disadvantage from coming up with extra options.
You're already deep in participating in this project.
Take advantage of this, okay?
I understand.
Wu Fangxu, are you done painting the section view yet?
It's done.
- Are you heading to the airport now?
- Yes.
Good luck!
Let's take a look at this
Ground Transportation Center
I've arrived at the airport.
I've also arrived.
Wait a second for me.
How long do I have to wait for?
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Where exactly are you?
How did you know I was coming back today?
- I...
- Hey, how come your phone suddenly went silent?
Is this how you pick people up from the airport?
I'm sorry.
I'm Liang Younian.
It's okay.
- Hello? Miaomiao?
- Yes, Mom.
Then do I have to come out to pick you up or not?
It's okay, Mom. I'll just take a cab back.
Let me send you.
It's okay. I can take a cab.
Let's go together. Younian's friend is my friend, too.
Let's go.
Wait for it to stop fully.
- Yaoyao!
- Sis!
- Mom!
- You're back!
- Did you miss me?
- I missed...
...my Barbie doll.
You think about your doll but not me?
It's in my luggage.
I'll get it for you.
- My baby.
- Mom.
- I've missed you so much.
- I missed you, too.
Look at you, you're all grown up now.
Did he drive you here?
We ran into each other.
Thank you both so much. I remembered the wrong time to pick up Miaomiao.
Next time, I'll treat you guys to a meal.
It's okay, Auntie.
Okay, when?
When you guys have time.
I have time right now.
Let's go.
Here, suggest something to our guest.
He insists on having a free meal when I'm so busy.
Do what you need to do.
This is yours.
This menu is so interesting.
Little friend, did you draw this?
How could it be? It's so ugly, it could only be drawn by my sister.
Here, take this for me, get to work.
I just got back and you're putting me to work?
What? Do you have to take a rest for forty-nine whole days?
Hurry up.
Sis! Is your luggage full of rocks? It's so heavy!
I'll help you.
Thank you, Brother.
You can leave it here.
Brother, help me open it.
If you open your sister's luggage, she'll get mad.
Aren't you her boyfriend?
How could she get mad?
How did you know?
My sister told me.
- I...
- Stop stalling, help me open it.
But if you open her luggage like this, she'll definitely get mad.
Then, if you help me open it,
I'll let you see a magical drawer.
Magical? How magical?
You'll know once you see it.
Drawing Sketch Book
My sister has a lot of drawings of you.
But they don't look like you at all.
Look at it.
After you're done, immediately come over and help me open the luggage.
The drawing's not bad.
It's just that He Xin's proportion is a little off.
H-He Xin?
Aren't you drawing He Xin watching Kaituo play basketball?
Yes! He Xin. Her proportion is off?
Who allowed you to look at my things?!
Your sister, she—
Don't blame a good person! When did I tell you to look?
We already broke up! Please leave.
Hurry and go. You shouldn't look through other people's things.
Your sister has such a big temper?
You broke up with my sister?
But I still—
What are you doing?
Who told you to bully my sister.
Who is it?
It's me.
I have something that I want to tell you.
I...
I don't have time.
Haicheng University
Let go of me.
Why do I have to let go?
I was here first.
Is there any evidence that can prove that you were here first?
Senior, you saw that I came first, didn't you?
There are still so many empty seats. You don't have to fight like that.
It's not me who is fighting.
It's him being all crazy. I was clearly here first.
Recently, why do you guys fight whenever you meet?
It's like you guys have a blood feud.
Senior! Haven't you realized?
Recently, he kept on picking on me.
Who is picking on you?
- Don't think too highly of yourself.
-You—
Okay.
You guys can fight next time.
Didn't you say that you wanted to discuss the candidates for the head of the school broadcasting station?
Let's hurry. I still need to go register at the graduate school.
Lin Kaitou, I brought you some things from my hometown.
I don't want it.
- Senior, I'll go add some water.
- Okay.
Jin Mou, wait a minute.
Why do you drop things and then run away every time?
I brought that for everyone.
I have said that I don't want it.
Even if you brought it for everyone, I don't want it.
Then you can throw it away.
Jin Mou, I have someone in my heart already.
So stop giving things to me from now on.
I'm afraid that if she sees it, she will be unhappy.
After all... she is very bad-tempered.
Okay. I know.
He Xin!
Were you eavesdropping on us just now?
As a reporter, where are your job ethics ?
That... That's because you said that I'm bad-tempered.
I never thought that you would say bad things about me in front of other people!
I said that the person I like is bad-tempered.
Does it have anything to do with you?
Don't think too highly of yourself.
Think it through. Are you really not talking about me?
He Xin!
Didn't you hear me talking to you?
I take back what I have just said.
The person that I like is you.
Why do you look at me this way?
It's not the first time that I have confessed my love to you.
So?
S-So... so what?
Aren't you going to give me an answer?
Then... let me think about it.
Don't think. Tell me the answer right now.
I'm afraid that we will have another fight tomorrow, and you won't talk to me again.
But...
So do you want to be with me or not?
Yes.
Mrs. Xia's Private Kitchen
Xia Miaomiao! Come downstairs and help me clean the dishes!
Oh, Mom. I'll be downstairs right away.
Your food is so delicious!
Delicious? Come back next time, I'll give you a discount.
Younian, what does "da zhe" mean?
- Discount.
- Oh, I see.
Okay! Thanks! I'll get going then.
I'll come back next time.
Are you leaving now?
Miaomiao, your classmate is leaving!
Why don't you come downstairs and sent them out!
I'm busy.
I'll walk you guys out then.
Thank you for sending my daughter home today.
You are welcome.
Take care!
Okay, okay.
Weren't you busy?
I'm done washing.
Then clean these up and go upstairs.
Santu has come a few times asking how to open the luggage.
Wow!
Thanks, Sister!
Don't thank me for now.
I have your favorite here.
Thank you, Sister!
Do you like it?
Wow!
Yes!
Little fool.
Sister, are all these mine?
This one is not. This one is for Sister A Xia.
Sister!
You have so many! Aren't they enough?
Are you coming downstairs to help me or not?
The night market is about to start.
We are coming!
Liu Shui, you can throw away the garbage.
I'll clean the table.
Didn't you leave a while ago?
I was waiting for you here.
I-I'm very busy.
I'm going to throw away the garbage.
Then I'll go with you.
There is no need.
Then you... can you give me five minutes?
I have something to tell you.
I... I don't have time now.
I'll wait for you at the lighthouse.
Come when you have time.
I...
Don't feel any pressure.
It's okay even if you don't come.
Do you have something to tell me why you asked me to come here?
I promised you that the second you come out of the airplane, I'll tell you why I didn't go abroad.
What do you think is the point in saying all these right now?
- Miaomiao—
- Just say it. I'm listening.
Do you know why I always like to be in the lighthouse?
Because the wasted factory that you can see from the lighthouse,
is where my mom had her accident.
Since the accident happened to my mom,
Fang Shi had put this project aside.
My mom was the designer of this project at that time.
It was her first project without the help of my dad.
My mom always joked that
if she was not busy getting married and having kids,
and not having time to do what she liked,
with what she could do, my dad wasn't qualified even to dig for her.
My mom liked to brag, didn't she?
So your mom was just like you. Very interesting.
Last year, when we were about to go abroad,
Fang Shi restarted this project.
And I had a chance to join them.
That's why I didn't go abroad.
I wanted to stay here to finish this project for my mom.
Actually, you could have just told me.
I hesitated for a long time on whether to tell you or not.
But I was afraid that you might give up going abroad for me.
It shouldn't be like that.
You should do what you want.
Not be like my mom.
Because of me and my dad, she held up her own dream.
In the end, there was only regret left.
Senior, I believe that this wasn't what your mom thought.
She chose the life that she thought was happy.
And you, shouldn't speculate her decision like this.
It's like at that time,
you should have told me to let me make my own decision,
instead of habitually thinking for me
to make the decision for me based on what you thought would be good for me.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
Give me some time.
I know.
I'm in school having class.
Just work and don't worry about me.
Don't keep running out to call me.
Aren't you afraid of being criticized?
All right, I know.
I will wait for you to get off work and go to movies together.
Stop saying it. I'll be really mad if you keep saying it.
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Then let me take a look.
Snacks. I was afraid that you would criticize me.
Really?
See?
What's there to hide?
I'm afraid.
It's good that you know it.
You're the one that asked me to supervise you to lose weight.
Worst case scenario, you can be a happy chubby girl.
That wouldn't work! Losing weight is important, okay?
Even if I don't succeed, at least it means I have a heart that wants to succeed.
I'm going to suffocate to death!
How long are you two going to talk?
Miaomiao!
When did you come back?
Weren't we just voice chatting last night?
We didn't tell you intentionally.
You were scaring us like that last time you came back.
We are sisters! Do you have to revenge on me like this?
Miaomiao!
We miss you so much!
You have been eating burgers and fries for a year.
Why are you still so skinny?
Don't mention it.
There was one midnight that I suddenly craved for dumplings with pickled vegetable fillings.
I was craving for them so much that I cried.
That is nothing. I'll buy you ten plates in a minute.
- We'll all go to the cafeteria together, okay?
- Okay.
I wouldn't go then.
I have promised Senior Da Chao to have dinner and watch a movie together.
You have been together for a year, and you guys are still so sickeningly sweet with each other.
Can you care about our single ants?
You are not even worrying for us.
I am!
Okay, it's all up to you!
"Okay, it's all up to you!"
Chubby Xia!
Be a lady.
Tang Mengfei! Long time no see.
It has not been that long.
Do you want some cookies?
Do you know how many calories a butter cookie has?
I'm already a popular model.
Who would use her as a model?
Okay.
- You eat then.
- I'll eat.
But I didn't say that I wouldn't eat it.
Then eat more.
Get fat!
These are all yours.
I'm not trying to make you fat!
Make her fat!
What the hell is this?!
It's no use even if you throw it away.
I don't agree with what you do.
I'm your leader. You need to listen to me!
Because you know that I'm right.
Retract the overhead floor and use more glass
is the way to make the light go deeper into the building.
Don't talk to me now. Let me think.
Frank!
Younian, can you not fight with him?
You have been fighting about lighting for three hours.
Our design project is an apartment building for senior people.
What? Shouldn't we start from the daily needs of senior people?
Large area lighting will benefit the mental and body health of senior people.
I insist on my design.
Younian.
The design that you have...
Based on the situation right now,
needs too much work in modifications.
I would suggest changing as well.
See, your teacher also says this.
How about this?
You carry on based on the original plan.
I will change based on the new design.
Younian.
You will exhaust yourself to death.
I agree.
All these are what I have to share.
Thank you, everybody.
Thank you, Student Xia for sharing with us.
Miaomiao had really good scores when she was in Britain.
She was praised by all the professors in Birmingham University.
You can take a look at her work.
If you have more questions or other things that you want to communicate about,
you can ask your senior, Miaomiao.
Self-study time.
I want to ask you about...
Ask one by one. I can't even hear it.
Senior, your sharing was very inspiring to me.
I want to apply for the exchange student in Britain as well.
You...
Wang Yutian?
Teacher Wang, I'm on my way to deliver the materials to you.
Thank you.
Teacher Jia!
Teacher Jia.
I need to deliver the materials.
Teacher Jia, wait for me.
Wrong way. It should be this way. I forgot.
- There is no time.
-Teacher Jia! Jia Yi!
Can we have a talk?
But I really need to deliver the materials. I really have no time.
It will just take a little while.
We can sit there and have a talk.
I have been pretty busy recently.
But I'm trying to make myself better.
Teacher Jia, your major is designing.
Have a look. How is my new shirt?
It fits well, right?
That's the thing.
I have been always trying to talk and communicate with you.
But I think that you have been evading me.
Today,
let's solve this problem in an adult way.
Teacher Jia, if you think that we are not suitable,
just tell me clearly. I won't keep persisting.
I'm not evading you intentionally.
It's just that before, we really didn't fit well.
I really didn't think of us that way.
Th-Then think about it now.
Actually, I did think of it.
But I don't know how to tell you about it.
Give it to me straight.
Looking at how you treated Lu Peng, you are not the kind that would hesitate.
Straight? It would make people sad.
What? What did you say?
What are you doing?
Did you pick this yourself?
I-I don't know anything about clothes.
The staff picked it for me.
What?
This is what's different between us.
If I like this shirt, I'll buy it right away.
If I don't, I won't even look at it.
Because you know if it's something that you would like or not by one look at it.
Teacher Jia, I think that there are some clothes, only by wearing them
can you tell if they are suitable or not. Right?
Teacher Li.
I'm just a teacher assistant.
I'm on my way to promotion, and I don't know if I will succeed.
But I'm a teacher from the designing department.
I have a certain level of requests for the taste of clothes.
Of course. That's necessary.
Also Teacher Jia is so outstanding and cute.
In my eyes, you are the most perfect in this school.
- I think—
- Teacher Li.
Just... don't you understand that I'm rejecting you?
Rejecting?
It's okay if you reject me.
You don't dislike me, do you?
Not really.
It's good that you don't dislike me.
- But—
- I still have a chance if you don't dislike me.
That way! Be careful!
Shooting my Kaituo's long legs with super-wide angle is perfect.
Three cameras are surely different.
- Take a break
- Okay.
Wait for a bit. I'm almost done.
Okay.
Are you tired? I bought you water.
Never mind. Why so hot-tempered?
I'm not. You're hot-tempered.
Peng Fei, who's that girl?
What's her connection to Lin Kaituo?
At first, I thought she was Lin Kaituo's girlfriend.
I later found out that she is Liang Younian's younger sister.
As you know, Younian is Lin Kaituo's brother.
As a conclusion, she is probably Kaituo's younger or older sister.
Younger or older sister?
Hey, Peng Fei.
Get someone to replace me.
I need to go to the toilet.
I'll get back to the game. Wait for me.
Student!
- Were you calling me?
.- Yes.
Hi, Student. I'm Lin Kaituo's friend.
I am fourth year, Business Management student, Ye Nan.
Hi, is there something you need?
Can I add you on WeChat?
You can't.
Lin Kaituo, why not?
Because she is my girlfriend.
Sorry for disturbing you.
What are you looking at?
I'm done. Let's go.
Calling me the hot-tempered one?
Kaituo, can you slow down?
Get Ye Nan to wait for you.
You seemed so happy talking to him.
I can't walk anymore.
Okay.
You're getting more and more spoiled.
Kaituo.
What?
We're holding hands.
Why? Are we not supposed to?
We can.
But...
But what?
But I don't feel anything special.
Is it because we know each other too well?
I didn't mean anything else.
I saw on TV when two people hold hands, it was as if their hearts stopped beating.
How come we hold hands,
there weren't any special feelings?
Do you feel anything now?
Lin Kai—
A Little Thing Called First Love
♫ Can you see my heart? ♫
♫ Can you read my mind? ♫
♫ Live inside my eyes, tell me words of love tenderly ♫
♫ I want you by my side, always watching over ♫
♫ My heart... ♫
♫ My heart restlessly beats whenever I see you  ♫
♫ I'm afraid to look up, I'm scared you might catch me blushing ♫
♫ Regarding what love feels like ♫
♫ I've only heard about it from friends ♫
♫ I never thought about when it would be my turn ♫
♫ You are so dazzling and outstanding ♫
♫ I'm just a faint breeze blowing ♫
♫ But fortunately, I ended up in your hands ♫
♫ Can you see my heart? ♫
♫ Can you read my mind? ♫
♫ Live inside my eyes, tell me words of love tenderly ♫
♫ I want you by my side, always watching over ♫
♫ My heart... ♫
[A Little Thing Called First Love]