A Little Thing Called First Love
♫ I can't find a way ♫
♫ To prove that love is biased  ♫
♫ I want to give it up ♫
♫ But I keep fighting with myself ♫
♫  Pretending that I don't care ♫
♫  Pretending to be busy every day ♫
♫  But in the end, I could not endure it ♫
♫ I want to know what you're up to right now ♫
♫ At every moment, you're all that I see ♫
♫ My heart misses you every minute, every second ♫
♫ I must control myself and forget you ♫
♫ Not willing to fall into the trap of love just like this ♫
♫ At every moment, you're all that I see ♫
♫ My heart misses you every minute, every second ♫
♫  I want to control myself and forget you ♫
♫ But I unknowingly wrote about you in my diary ♫
♫ If this is love ♫
♫ Why does it feel strange? ♫
♫ Don't know how it came so suddenly ♫
♫ Maybe time will slowly bring the answer ♫
♫ Reach out your hand ♫
♫ And drive away my uneasy dreams ♫
♫ According to you, our encounter ♫
A Little Thing Called First Love
♫ Is the result of heaven's favor ♫
Episode 13
I was so scared earlier.
You didn't expose me, right?
No. I said that I picked it up and forgot to return it to him.
That's good then. Did he believe it?
He believed it.
It's too bad that I have to reprint the pictures again.
I'm hanging up.
We should be done by the afternoon, right?
You are so tired. How about you rest a little?
The architecture major midterm is such an abyss of suffering.
You finally suffered through it and you're even helping me with this now.
It's fine.
Making clothes is like resting and de-stressing for me.
Some people just can't stay in their own dorms and keep going to other people's dorms.
Some people just don't like staying in their own dorms so why can't they go to other people's dorms?
Guess what I bought.
Food. Clothes.
Look here, I now have the same motorbike as Kaituo.
Where did you get so much money?
I borrowed it from Liang Younian.
Senior Younian has that much money?
Yes, the Architecture majors scholarships amount is very high, and he gets it every semester.
Shouldn't every major's scholarships be the same? Why do they get more?
Our department has a special scholarship from the Fang Family's Enterprise Group.
Yes, and this special scholarship is awarded very quickly.
It's not like our school's scholarships
where you have to wait for the approval and distribution of funds.
How do you know more than me?
I am Haicheng University's front line reporter, He Xin reporting in.
All of you are here. Are you all done with your exams?
I am done Senior Sister. What about you?
I came back to pick up some books to study. I have one more exam tomorrow.
Senior Sister, have you ever won the Fang Family's scholarship?
I have. But most of the top-class scholarships are taken by Liang Younian.
See? Liang Younian's allowances are more than he could spend.
I only borrowed some and I'll return it once I get a scholarship, too.
You say it as if you'll get it for sure.
Xinxin can definitely get it.
Oh, right. Lin Kaituo says that he wants to get the scholarship, too.
- Really?
- Yes.
You can get it for sure but I can't say the same for Lin Kaituo.
You talk first. I'm going to go study.
- Bye, Senior Sister.
- Good luck, Senior Sister.
Bye-bye.
Hey, when do you guys plan on going home?
I will go back home whenever Kaituo decides to go back. When the time comes, we'll be wearing couple clothes,
driving our couple motorbike,
and going back home together.
Do you know how to drive?
No, but I can learn.
You can say it's romantic if he's driving you back, but you two are driving together separately.
At most, you can call it road mates.
It's not like he would be willing to drive me back home.
I also want to go home with Senior.
Why are both of you so pathetic.
Useless!
Ah Xia, should we really be doing this?
What's wrong with it? I looked into it earlier.
Your Senior has to pass this route to go take the bus.
We'll wait right here. We'll definitely run into him.
Hey! Senior.
Senior.
Are you guys going home, too?
Uh. Yeah.
Senior, I'm not going the same way as you, but Miaomiao is.
From here on, I will formally leave Miaomiao to you.
Remember, she likes to sit at the back row on the bus
but she will get carsick if she looks outside the window for too long. Take good care of her.
I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
Let's go.
Thank you.
You must sit together with Liang Younian on the bus, it's ideal if you can sit at the back part of the bus.
Student. Sorry.
I'm with her.
Kaituo! Drive slower.
I can't keep up with you.
Hey! Kaituo! This is running out of battery!
I can't catch up to you!
Don't charge the motorbike to full battery because he will have to drive you back if you run out of battery.
What crappy idea did Ah Xia come up with? This really ran out of battery.
Senior, do you want to listen to music?
Senior.
Yes, I got it.
The motorbike is on the roadside. When you're off work, come and get it.
Okay, I will take the subway back home.
Oh, right. Don't tell my mom.
Or else she'll scold me again.
Okay. Bye-bye.
What are you going to do with your motorbike?
My dad will come get it once he gets off work.
Are you going or not?
Let's go!
What are you doing?
Can you sit still?
Grab my bag not me.
Friendly reminder, if you fake sleep do it more naturally.
How do I be more natural?
No. Not natural.
Why don't I really fall asleep?
How do I sleep for real?
Can't sleep.
You can do it.
Count sheep.
One sheep.
Two sheep.
Three sheep.
One hundred thirty-two sheep.
One hundred thirty-three sheep.
One hundred thirty-four sheep.
♫ Can you see my heart? ♫
♫ Can you read my mind? ♫
♫ Live inside my eyes, tell me words of love tenderly ♫
♫ I want you by my side, always watching over ♫
♫ My heart... ♫
♫ My heart restlessly beats whenever I see you  ♫
The 19 year old Xiao Xie has been feeling low.
It turns out that he has gotten into online campus loans.
Xiao Xie is a second year student at Haicheng University.
He started dating a girl and through that girl's recommendation,
Xiao Xie was introduced to the loan sharks and wouldn't stop.
In half a year, he'd owed fourteen thousand yuan (~ $20000 USD) through borrowing loans.
Younian, you're back.
Kaituo also came back. He just finished his dumplings and went back to his room.
What do you want to eat? I'll make it.
No worries. I'll just wait for dinner.
Okay.
Dad!
Honey, let's go to Harbin for New Years.
Didn't you say that you've never seen snow before and yet your name is Yang Xue (first name means snow).
You always think about traveling whenever you have a break.
Harbin's winter is very beautiful.
Look.
Younian is back.
Dad.
You came back. Perfect.
Take a look, too. How about we go to Harbin for the New Year?
What do you think?
I'm okay with whatever. You guys decide.
Why don't you sponsor us a bit.
You only know to say nonsense.
How can you say something like have Younian sponsor?
He sponsored He Xin to buy a motorbike.
So what if he chipped in for a family vacation?
Younian, don't listen to your father's nonsense. Go unpack your bags.
Help me put away the wine.
[Ctrip: Rest Assured Service, Rest Assured Price]
Why did you soak so much jujube?
Don't worry so much. It will come in handy.
Mom. I'm back.
Miaomiao, you're back.
Dad?
When did you come back?
He got home ten seconds before you.
I came back to celebrate the New Years with you all.
Are you hungry? Mom is making dumplings.
I'm so hungry.
Mom, I want to eat the pork and cabbage filling ones.
You will eat what I make.
So picky.
Let Dad have a look.
How is university life? Is it tiring?
It's okay.
I'm tired.
You're tired. Why are you tired?
Tired from doing homework.
Tired from doing homework?
Would you be able to go to the university without doing your homework?
You won't be tired once you get into a university.
Okay?
Why did you just come?
Now, my dad has forced me to look after the store.
Do you still want to go play?
I can't. Let's wait until my dad comes back.
Oh, right.
Do you know why Kaituo isn't working part-time this winter break?
He's just sleeping at home everyday.
In order to review for this semester's midterm,
he stayed up late for 2-3 weeks. It must've taken a toll on him.
He's now recuperating.
Grandpa, you can't set up stalls here.
What? I can't set it up here?
Am I in your way,
or disrupting your business?
Seriously.
I'll go inside first.
Grandpa, did you make this through processed coconut?
Of course.
Have you seen any coconut that grows like this on a tree?
This craftsmanship is so so.
So so?
Youngster, that's because you don't know how to appreciate it.
Why don't you let me add some work to it?
I'll definitely be able to sell more than you.
You want to add to it?
Sell it better than me?
Okay!
I'll let you try it.
Let's see if you can do a better job at selling them than I can.
Okay, you go and try it.
Okay, I'll go get a pen.
No way.
[Open]
Lin Kaituo really got first place?
I don't like that attitude.
Why can't our Kaituo get first place?
It's not that, I am just envious.
I always just merely pass.
Did you check what place Senior got?
Why would you need to check Liang Younian's?
Of course, he would be first again.
Talking to you guys is so boring.
All you two talk about is Liang Younian and Lin Kaituo.
It's almost the New Year and I miss Kaituo so much.
He's better off making deliveries.
At least that way, I can follow him from behind.
Now, he's at home every day and Aunt is worried that something's wrong with him.
If you have so much free time to worry about Lin Kaituo, why don't you worry about yourself first instead?
Have you thought of the topic for the broadcasting station?
I know.
Who would've thought that the devil himself, Lin Kaituo,
due to studying too excessively for the midterm,
has been lying at home for the entire month.
Lin Kaituo. Lin Kaituo. Liang Younian. Liang Younian.
Liang Younian, Liang Younian and then Lin Kaitou
Miaomiao, has it been a while since you've seen Liang Younian?
Yeah.
The last time I saw him was when he rode his bike past my house.
How about I go to the Liang family's house for New Year's dinner?
No.
They're going to Harbin during that time for a vacation.
Miaomiao.
I'm hanging up. My parents are back.
I'll going to go see if they need my help.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Sis. Look. Are my clothes pretty?
Pretty. Turn around.
You didn't even cut the tag.
Miaomiao, you have some, too.
- I also have some, too?
- Yes.
I knew it, Dad is the best.
Your father only knows to pretend to be the good one.
When I was shopping earlier, I ran into your high school teacher, Teacher Liang.
He was with his wife to buy winter coats.
They said they're spending the New Year in Harbin, is that right?
Yeah.
Senior is really going to Harbin.
- Go put on the couplets.
- Sure
Where's the glue?
Shoot. I forgot to buy it.
Miaomaio, go buy a bottle of glue from the bookstore.
I just got an order, so I need to start cooking now.
Okay.
Yaoyao, stop playing. Come here.
Help Dad clean this up.
Okay.
Xiao Tuo, come here and try out this coat.
Your card ending in 2314 has deposited 12,000.($17,000 USD)
Account balance is now 12,300. ($17,050 USD)
Look at this. Look at this.
What are you drawing?
I'm telling you. When you leave, you better buy all the ones you drew on.
You can't even leave one behind.
Okay.
She ignored you, young man.
Don't embarrass yourself.
The color's a bit dark, can you change it?
Why did Senior Dachao insist on selling me the most expensive one?
Xia Miaomiao.
Senior?
Wh-What are you doing here?
Painting.
I'll give this one to you.
Me?
This must have taken a long time.
You're giving this to me? You even drew our lighthouse.
N-No, I mean, you drew a lighthouse.
The lighthouse is not ours. It belongs to everyone.
No.
It's just...
Thank you, Senior. I'll definitely cherish it well.
Little Miss, look over here.
You don't have to cherish it too much.
I have all that you could want over here.
Look. Lighthouse.
You should go home first.
It seems like you are in a rush.
Yes. Right.
I'm leaving first, Senior.
Mom, you don't need to tidy it.
I still need to sleep.
Kaituo.
You got a message just now and I accidentally saw it.
Why do you all of a sudden have so much money?
You didn't borrow money from anyone, right?
If you need money, you can tell me.
Moreover, the rent you paid before is still here. No one touched it.
You can use it if needed.
There is no need to be stubborn with us.
It's from a scholarship.
How could a scholarship be so much?
I didn't hear Younian receive so much—
If it was Liang Younian who received this amount of money today, would you doubt him?
Xiao Tuo!
After the New Year, it'll be a while before you head out, right?
The closed season for fishing is extended this year. I'll set sail later.
Look at her.
Who are those kids that are singing?
How would I know? They're child stars.
TFBoys!
(Very popular boy band in China)
All the girls in our class like them.
Son, wait until your mom grows up. My son~
Son?
Who's son is this?
My son.
She's crazy. It's time for her medicine, just ignore her.
Xia Yaoyao, you're crazy.
Little crazy person.
Throwing a tantrum so he doesn't need to go to Harbin. Now, I can't go, either.
I know.
But my mom...
No buts, give your phone to your mom, I'll talk to her.
Okay.
Mom.
Xinxin wants to talk to you.
Okay.
Hey, Xinxin.
Bring this into the kitchen.
Thank you, thank you. Happy New Year to you, too.
You two, turn the volume down.
Okay.
Go ahead, I'm listening.
Okay, okay.
Oh, really?
Then you guys sleep early. Don't play too late.
Okay.
I will give the phone to her.
Hurry and go. Don't let her be scared alone.
It's the New Year soon. Where are you letting her go off to?
Her classmate, He Xin.
Says that her mom and dad went on vacation and left her alone at home.
She's scared so she wanted Miaomiao to accompany her.
Be cautious when you head out.
Okay. I'm leaving.
Wait!
Bring Xinxin some dumplings.
Right.
I want to go, too.
I'm not bringing you along.
Then I'll cling onto you!
This child.
Hurry and get off.
Who's knocking at this hour? Kaituo, did you order delivery?
Are you surprised?
Brother Chao came to celebrate the New Year with you guys!
Go back.
I came all this way. You want me to go back?
Liang Younian. Liang Younian will welcome me.
Go back.
They want us to go back.
Happy New Year!
Hey! Don't leave.
It's really heavy.
Come on in.
Three of a kind and a single.
Your turn.
Three Queens and a pair of fives.
One five.
Pass.
What should I play?
Put this one, it's the strongest card.
Look what I found.
What is it?
Jujube liquor.
Be honest with me. After you guys entered the university,
did you ever drink wine?
Nope.
You?
You must have had some.
You.
You haven't had any?
Oh, my.
Y-You're more well behaved than you look.
Kaituo was very well behaved to begin with.
I'll go get the cups.
Got angry?
That's enough!
Okay, I'll pour it for you.
Continue.
It's your turn.
Here.
Bottoms up. Who's scared of you?
You two just drink according to your limits. Be careful.
Should we do a toast? Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
Don't burn yourself. Did it burn you? If anything happens...
5, 4, 3, 2,1! Happy New Year!
Lin Kaituo.
Xia Miaomiao.
- I feel like I'm going to throw up.
- Right now?
Hold it!
I can't hold it!
You're so fierce.
I can't tell if she's actually drunk or faking it.
Sleep then.
Senior.
I want to ask you something.
Go ahead.
Where are my glasses?
I don't know. I'll help you look for it afterward.
Okay.
Xia Miaomiao, are you awake?
HDFZ, 6, Liang Younian
Senior's room?
Why were my glasses with Senior Dachao?
You must be hungry.
Are we not going to tell them to come eat together?
The others... they can't be woken up.
You eat first.
Be careful. It's hot.
Thank you, Senior.
Senior, your dumplings are really good.
These are your dumplings.
You brought them over last night.
Oh, I see.
This also tastes really good.
Thank you.
So you guys celebrated the New Year together and didn't even invite me?
That's going too far!
We decided at the last minute.
It would've been the New Year by the time you got there.
But you're really overboard.
You left empty-handed.
How come you brought so much coming back?
Hold this for if you think it's too much.
Did you manage to find a topic for the campus broadcast?
No. It's been an entire winter break.
I can't think of anything.
Don't worry. We'll help you think.
I saw this over winter break.
Why don't you just do a topic on confessing.
You two can take the opportunity to confess, too.
Then I won't have to analyze your problems every day, I'm so tired of it.
There's this new love confession wall plugin on the site.
Type in the name of the person you like and it will generate a link.
Isn't it cool?
Yeah.
Where are you going?
Broadcasting station!
What's up? You asked me to come over in such a rush.
Senior Sister, come and take a look at the topic I came up with.
I want to do a Confession Special Event with the school newspaper.
It won't be limited to love, family, or friendship.
I want to encourage everyone to live while they're young and to loudly express their love.
Not bad, but what means will you use to make this event happen?
I want to go through the school newspaper and the school social media platform to collect confessions.
Every day, we'll read out ten confessions from the broadcasting station.
For a week, we can also coordinate with other offline events.
What do you think?
It's good.
Then why don't you see if you can coordinate with other majors to do an offline event together.
No problem.
[A Little Thing Called First Love]
♫  Can you see my heart? ♫
♫  Can you read my mind? ♫
♫ Live inside my eyes  ♫
♫  Tell me words of love tenderly ♫
♫  I want you by my side  ♫
♫  Always watching over ♫
♫ My heart... ♫
♫ My heart restlessly beats whenever I see you  ♫
♫ I'm afraid to look up, I'm scared you might catch me blushing ♫
♫ Regarding what love feels like ♫
♫ I've only heard about it from friends ♫
♫ I never thought about when it would be my turn ♫
♫ You are so dazzling and outstanding ♫
♫ I'm just a faint breeze blowing ♫
♫ But fortunately, I ended up in your hands ♫
♫ Can you see my heart? ♫
♫ Can you read my mind? ♫
♫ Live inside my eyes, tell me words of love tenderly ♫
♫ I want you by my side, always watching over ♫
♫ My heart... ♫
A Little Thing Called First Love