("Light of Firefly" Unit)
♪The night is long
and the moon glows in my heart♪
♪As I watch the passers-by
wander around the metropolis♪
♪Even black coffee becomes sweet♪
♪Because you're with me♪
♪Look, our youthful years
spoke of destiny♪
♪Hold our hands tight,
and we'll stand by each other♪
♪Wait for the red beans to sprout♪
♪Snowflakes fall gently
and rest on my shoulders♪
♪Piece by piece♪
♪Loaded with vows♪
♪I hope the flowers
will bloom next spring again♪
=Angels Fall Sometimes=
Okay, this should be enough.
- Thank you.
- Alright, take care.
How much is this?
Eight yuan.
=Episode 19=
(The Greatest Love Is Found in Togetherness)
(Hospital Mall, Neurology Department)
Grandpa called me today,
asking when we would go back
for the Spring Festival.
This is exactly what I'm worried about.
What should we do about it?
If we don't even go back
for the festival,
Grandpa will definitely overthink.
But with the current situation,
how can we get back?
Should we just tell Grandpa the truth?
After all, we can avoid
seeing him forever.
I've tried to persuade your brother,
but he just doesn't agree
and says Grandpa mustn't know about it.
So what do we do?
Your brother
lied to us before too, didn't he?
He said he had broken his arm,
and I didn't suspect him.
I really thought he had broken it.
He and Chen Guangpu had broken
their arms and legs
when playing football before.
Are you suggesting
we tell Grandpa
my brother has broken his leg?
We have no other choice.
Okay.
Then let's just tell Grandpa
my brother and I fell off bikes.
I'll pretend to be injured as well.
That way, Grandpa won't doubt it.
Okay.
Will this work?
I've helped you put on
the gauze and the splint already.
There shouldn't be any problems.
Later on, I'll put this on my arm too.
Anyway, if it's a motorcycle fall,
it's normal to see serious injuries.
I'll also fake some injuries on my face
to make it more true.
You've put it on backwards.
How can you not give it away?
No worries. No rush to put it on now.
I've informed
your parents.
I said you fell and broke both your leg
and arm when riding a motorcycle.
Okay.
As long as Grandpa
can't tell, it's okay.
Just leave it like this.
Que,
Spring Festival is coming.
Go home and have a look.
Still angry?
Why would I be angry?
Whom would I be mad at?
I couldn't even see you.
W-W-What would I be angry about?
Well, wasn't I busy?
Then why are you back?
I hurried back as soon as I was done.
I need to mend our relationship.
Is a relationship so easily mended?
You left the home so decisively.
H-H-How can it be mended?
I was waiting for you
to calm down, okay?
So I could come back
and apologize to you.
You...
What did you do wrong?
I made you sad.
You know you made me sad.
An Zhique,
I never thought
you could be so heartless.
I raised you with so much effort.
You fell in love and then left me.
Isn't it true that you don't have
your dad in your heart at all?
How could it be possible?
You are my father,
and I am your daughter.
No matter what,
I should be filial to you.
Besides,
I knew a long time ago
that you weren't mad at me.
You had He Xindi send
things to me many times
without telling me they were from you,
but I could tell right away.
Isn't that so?
How can I be mad at you?
You're my daughter and my son-in-law.
How could I be angry with you?
Dad,
from my childhood to now,
I haven't really done
anything too crazy.
This matter
might be the biggest thing in my life.
I hope
you will still support me
when I want to do something,
just like before.
I promise
I will not let myself be mistreated.
When I need you,
could you still stay by my side?
Haven't I always been by your side?
Actually, when I first
learned about Tuo's illness,
I was stunned.
I'm quite regretful now.
Haven't I added to your burden
by arguing with you?
Taking care of a patient
is quite exhausting.
I-I-I made you
have to take it alone.
Don't worry, Que.
From now on, I will be with you.
I won't ever let you suffer alone, okay?
I won't let you get tired.
I can manage on my own now.
You're my dad.
Don't worry.
When I need you,
I will go to you directly.
Well,
h-h-how is Tuo now?
He is not
in a very good condition.
The doctor says it can be
actually considered optimistic,
and that the time period is not short.
His left arm...
His left arm is still quite functional.
His legs aren't very nimble.
But his feet can still exert strength.
We plan to visit his grandpa
this Spring Festival.
I-I-If the old man sees him
like this now...
We will deceive him,
saying he got injured
riding a motorcycle.
Alright then.
So you mean to say,
you'll all celebrate
at Tuo's home this year, right?
Am I not discussing it with you?
What's there to discuss?
If you want to go, just go.
Besides, if I didn't let you go,
could I stop you?
If you don't want me to go, I won't.
No.
Just go.
While Tuo's health is still okay,
have a good Chinese New Year.
Don't worry about me.
I have many friends.
I will
play poker
and Fight the Landlord.
I-I-I'm telling you, without you,
I can still have fun
during the Spring Festival.
Thank you, Dad.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, we're back.
You got hurt so badly on a motorcycle?
What happened?
Do you want me to make a dish?
No need. Go take a rest.
Dad, don't busy yourself with it.
We'll cook today's meal.
You guys go ahead.
I was saying
I'd been feeling uneasy all along.
You can ask Ye
how many calls I had him make.
Why was there no news from you?
I made a video call,
and you didn't respond to me.
See, there was an accident, right?
I figured something was up.
I told you all about it,
but you didn't believe me.
W-W-Well, you see it now, don't you?
Riding a motorcycle in the winter?
You're dressed so warmly with a hat.
Your vision isn't clear, is it?
For sure, you were wearing earphones.
How dangerous that is.
No, Grandpa.
It's just that I wasn't careful
when turning and took a fall.
You took a fall.
And you, Ye!
I've told you so many times.
Don't walk with headphones.
What if you
bump into things?
How dangerous that is.
Such a grown person,
still making me worry.
Grandpa, we just got back.
Scold them later. Don't be angry.
Que, I'm quite happy that you've come.
I wanted them to invite you here
for Spring Festival.
But I felt it was inappropriate
to let your dad be left alone
at home.
No, my dad will spend
the festival with his colleagues.
It's not easy for him
to get a break this year.
He doesn't want me to be at home
so that he can enjoy his drinks.
He should come here to drink.
I've got plenty of good wine.
Any day during the holiday works.
We have rooms for him.
Alright.
Then, okay.
Your arm is injured like this,
and so is your leg.
Ye,
how come you injured your left face
while he hurt
his right arm and right leg?
How did you fall?
Come on, show me.
You were sitting behind your brother.
He was in front and saw an obstacle.
It fell to the right, right?
You hurt your right arm and leg.
H-H-How did your left face get injured?
Grandpa,
it happened so suddenly.
Who would care about
how we fell at that moment?
Yeah, I got panicked and I jumped off.
I fell on that side when I jumped off.
No, no, when you jumped off, you see,
the inertia would take you to the right.
But you scraped your left face.
Was it a magic motorcycle?
Grandpa, you're reconstructing
a crime scene now.
You've been watching
too many crime dramas.
I...
Grandpa,
have you ever guessed
the murderer correctly?
You forgot the reason why you
switched to watching idol dramas?
Right, exactly.
There was a TV show.
Grandpa didn't know
who the killer was even at last.
I told him,
but he kept insisting
that there would be a twist.
I've never really guessed
who the murderer was.
Grandpa, you see?
They look down on us, don't they?
Let's watch a mystery film today
and take a guess.
No, I'm not going to watch.
I'll never be able
to guess who the murderer is.
You're so badly injured.
Don't ride a motorcycle anymore.
Got it.
Sell it. Don't ride that thing.
Alright, I won't ride it anymore.
Worrying.
What?
What is it?
You've been in trouble again?
How is that possible? I haven't.
What's wrong?
The warehouse manager said
you'd been unloading goods
every day these past few days.
Some are missing?
I only unloaded the goods
into the warehouse.
I never touched them.
Who said you touched the goods?
Do you need money?
I don't need money. I've earned money.
Mom, this is for you.
For me?
It's even a gold necklace.
Is it really gold?
It's copper. Take it or leave it.
Who talks like that?
It was bought by our son.
It must be real.
And it's a golden ox.
Why is it an ox?
My mom was born in the Year of Ox.
No, the Rabbit.
My dad was.
I was born in the Year of Pig.
I'm going to take a bath.
You were born
in the Year of Ox. You take it.
No, the Pig.
♪Don't break my heart♪
♪Be gentle once again♪
♪I don't want to see♪
Bao.
Mr. An, you're here.
What's up?
You're not going home?
My home is too far away.
No direct flights,
and I couldn't snag a train ticket.
So I'm going back later.
You're here alone?
Yeah, Xindi and Guangpu
have to do a live streaming.
It's Spring Festival. Few customers.
I can manage by myself.
I want to earn as much
as possible for Que.
No wonder people say
you have a good heart.
Bao,
Que has gone to Tuo's home
to celebrate Spring Festival.
I am also alone.
If you don't mind,
let's spend the festival together.
Alright.
Come to my place
to eat my dumplings then.
I can make the wrappers.
I'm pretty good at making the filling.
What are you doing? I can help you.
N-N-No need.
I'm just about to get
the cake I just baked.
Try it and see
if it's different from Que's.
Alright. Just give me a little.
Okay!
Just some of it will do.
Tuo.
Que.
Can you take some pictures
of me with Grandpa?
How about we go out for a walk with him?
Alright.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, let's go out
for a walk, shall we?
Good.
I have a gateball match coming up.
It's the last match of the year.
We'll go with you.
To cheer you on.
Where are you going? I want to go too.
OK. Let's change
our clothes and go together.
I'll go change my clothes.
No. 9.
Gate 1.
I can't understand
this little ball game.
Me neither.
I know nothing related to ball games.
My little grandson.
So handsome.
My grandson.
The beautiful girl in the back
is my granddaughter-in-law.
- She's so pretty.
- There are three gates on the field.
One ball per person.
Each goal scored is worth one point.
Hitting the middle pole
scores two points.
Five points per round.
At the end of the game, the one
with the higher score wins.
How do you know it?
I often played with them as a kid.
Do you know?
My brother used to join Grandpa
in dancing at the square.
It was not dancing.
That was a senior choir.
You were dancing there with a fan.
Have you forgotten?
You were dancing
with a fan while singing?
Yeah, in the center position.
It was the Phoenix Dance.
Really impressive.
Don't laugh at me.
Didn't I do that to make him happy?
Hit No. 6.
Had I known it back then,
I would have danced with him more.
Ye,
spend more time with him in the future.
He likes playing gateball,
singing,
watching idol dramas
and grocery shopping.
He always says
it's quite comfortable to be alone.
But look how happy he is
when we're back.
He talks on and on,
having endless words to say.
No. 1.
It's them.
Okay.
It's my time.
It's Grandpa's turn.
Grandpa, come on, Grandpa!
Grandpa, you're cool!
No. 1.
Three points.
Come on.
- Grandpa.
- Come one, Grandpa.
Well,
people spend
their whole lives growing up,
getting married
and having kids.
After their children grow up
and start their own families,
they toil to raise their grandchildren.
Then their grandchildren go to school
and fall in love.
And in the end,
they're all alone again.
After I fell ill,
I just couldn't stop
worrying about my grandpa.
Every time I think
I might not see him again in the future,
I really can't get him off my mind.
Don't worry.
Ye and I will take good care of Grandpa.
Come on, Grandpa!
Go for it, Grandpa!
Grandpa, you're amazing!
Grandpa, you're great!
- So cool.
- Grandpa, you're awesome.
- Good!
- Bravo.
Xu, fantastic!
♪About what I love♪
♪What exactly is happiness♪
♪What's worth a lifetime to pursue♪
♪I once gazed at the rainbow,
wishing for happiness♪
♪Wishing for us to be together
and live a simple life♪
♪Except that we're in love
with each other♪
♪Even the plain innocence
at the beginning♪
♪Who will tell our story♪
♪Through singing and each lyric♪
♪So many eager attempts,
all encourage me not to shrink back♪
♪My heart is responding, and it's me♪
Grandpa,
if you are tired, let's take a break.
You ran too fast just now.
If it weren't for my regular exercise,
I couldn't have kept up with Ye.
Let's take a break.
Take a break.
Actually,
I'm actually fine.
I'm in high spirits.
Now,
I often drink my homemade health tea.
It works.
My blood pressure has stabilized.
I also made some
for your dad to cool down his temper.
He should drink more of it.
Haven't you noticed?
It works.
These past few days,
your dad hasn't been angry.
He has a smile on his face.
And he even does chores.
He gave me a big surprise this morning.
He was sweeping the yard.
You should have had
him drink your tea earlier
so that I'd have got less scolding.
Yes.
Your dad has gotten old.
Now he's too old to scold you guys
and hit you.
After one gets old,
they get less picky
and less courageous.
They say when one gets old,
there's not much time left.
Time is numbered.
Actually, I feel
once a person gets old,
time seems
to stretch on especially long.
Guess what I'm thinking.
I keep thinking about
when Spring Festival will come,
when you get holidays
and when you will come to see me.
Once a person gets old,
they feel
time just goes by slower and slower.
But
don't worry about me.
I've lived a worthwhile life.
I married your grandmother,
the woman I loved.
I also worked
as a carpenter, a job I enjoyed.
I raised a daughter,
who has never caused me
any worry in my lifetime.
She's filial.
So are my grandsons.
And my granddaughter-in-law
is filial too.
I've gotten old,
but I have my house,
live a comfortable life
and have a big family.
See?
Others get old and suffer from dementia,
but my mind isn't muddled at all.
Now,
I often think of
your grandmother when she was alive,
she would fill the yard
with vegetables and flowers
and such.
You were riding a little wooden horse
around the whole yard.
"Grandpa,
when I grow up,
I will take you to some grasslands
to ride a big horse."
You even said
that you'd buy me the grasslands.
In a flash,
you've grown up.
Child,
I...
I don't need you to buy some grasslands,
nor do I need you to visit me every day.
I just want you to be healthy,
safe and sound.
Let me know
you are well every day.
That's enough.
I'm fine.
Grandpa.
G-G-Good.
I've been doing fine.
That's good.
Good.
How come you're back?
Where should I go?
Didn't you go back to your home?
I went back to fulfill my filial duties.
I didn't hit the mark.
Isn't it not the Year of Ox?
I think at least one of them
should be born in the Year of Ox.
When I was a kid,
we had a bronze ox statue.
Why did they buy it
if it was not the Year of Ox?
What can you remember?
You don't even remember
your parents' age.
You messed it up, right?
At least it's gold.
Oxen are seen
as a good omen.
Why did you buy these things?
Isn't it Spring Festival?
I need to get
some festive things for our place.
What does this mean?
H-H-Hang this over there.
What is this?
Do you plan to get married
during Spring Festival?
The wedding decorations?
The seller must have sent
the wrong item.
He Xindi, let me tell you.
You have to cut this thing yourself.
Find a piece of red paper
and a pair of scissors.
Sit by the window, looking outside,
and cut out the sorrow
of not getting married piece by piece.
This seller is crazy. I don't want it.
Don't do this. It's unlucky.
Keep it for now.
You'll get married eventually.
Hang it up later.
Aren't you going home this year?
Going home? I have no home.
I'll stay here.
Where should I stick this?
On the door?
This large "Fu" character.
Hang it there, on that wall.
- There?
- Yes.
Move it to the center, to the right.
Yes.
- Is it okay?
- A little higher.
Coming.
Try this.
Add a little to it.
I can't beat him.
I can't.
How can they still run away?
Use less salt.
You're such a noob.
Stop playing games. Eat something.
Wait. I'll finish this round soon.
Get him some food.
Have some water.
Coming!
Hello, your delivery.
Wish you a pleasant meal.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, thank you.
- Why are you back?
- Give me.
Go change your clothes.
Change your shoes.
I just mopped the floor.
Change your clothes.
Why should I do it?
Go to my home.
Why?
To have dinner.
I've just ordered some food.
Come on.
Eating takeout today?
Hurry up. Change your clothes.
No need for that, right?
Well, it's okay,
but at least change your shoes.
- Your family...
- Cut the small talk.
How could I leave you alone
at home to eat takeout for real?
Hurry up. My parents are waiting.
Go.
I need to put on some makeup.
Why? It's not a blind date.
Hurry up.
Wait a moment.
I'll bring your mom cosmetics.
Hurry up.
Change your shoes!
I just mopped the floor.
What are they singing?
Why can't I hear it clearly?
It's a live band.
All about the atmosphere.
C-C-Can they be called a band?
Without a touch of rock at all.
Mr. An, you even listen to rock?
What do you mean by "even"?
I'm an old rocker, you know?
Rock.
Like...
Like this...
Good.
Irritable.
Wait.
What's wrong, Mr. An?
I-I-I'm a bit confused.
Want some water?
I got excited. It's nothing.
Do your thing.
Come on.
This Spring Festival
is meaningful
because we have
a new family member, Que.
And next year,
there'll be one more,
my great-grandchild.
Cheers. Let's wish everyone good health.
Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year.
You seem uncomfortable.
Who's uncomfortable?
Guangpu says you're a Northeasterner
and eat dumplings
during Spring Festival.
Mr. Chen, you made this?
Thank you.
Where's your mom?
Call her out for dinner.
Mom!
I'm coming!
Move aside.
He,
Guangpu didn't even give a heads-up.
We didn't prepare anything.
Consider this a meeting gift.
Look, it has a diamond.
A real diamond.
Mom, isn't it too valuable?
Mrs. Chen, this is too expensive.
I can't accept it.
What's so expensive about it?
It's his first time
bringing a girlfriend home.
No, Mom.
Mrs. Chen,
Guangpu and I are not...
Just keep it for now.
As long as you don't find it ugly.
Her taste
has always been not so great.
What good taste is needed?
Diamonds
just need to look good.
Guangpu,
put it on for her.
No, Mrs. Chen,
this is too expensive.
I can't accept it.
I really can't take it.
Just put it on as she said.
It's pretty good.
Try it on.
It looks good.
It's like it was
specially bought for you.
Thank you, Mr. and Mrs. Chen.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
We are a family.
Let's not talk about money.
Chen Guangpu is unreliable.
If he argues with you,
you teach him a lesson.
If you can't handle him, just tell me.
I'll make him behave with beatings.
Okay, Mr. Chen.
Let's eat.
Have a drink?
Yes.
Dad, you can't outdrink her.
- Hey.
- What?
I said you can't outdrink her.
I'll drink with you today.
Mr. and Mrs. Chen, I toast to you.
Cheers.
I'll finish this glass.
- Look.
- Happy New Year.
Look.
Dumplings are here.
Hurry, eat while it's hot.
Here you go, Mr. An.
Drink.
Okay.
Okay, let's eat.
L-L-Let's have a drink first.
It's Spring Festival.
Bao, Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Wishing you good health,
good luck and happiness.
May you make a fortune.
Make a fortune.
Right, let's...
let's first
give Que a video call on WeChat
to say "Happy New Year".
My dad is calling.
Come on.
Say "Happy New Year".
Dad, Happy New Year.
Que, Happy New Year.
Lin Tuo, Happy New Year.
Drinking?
Mr. and Mrs. Lin, Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, Mr. Lin.
Happy New Year.
Don't drink too much. Bao, make sure
he doesn't drink much.
Que's dad,
I've saved some good wine for you here.
Come to my place
during the festival to drink with me.
Sure, I'll come over and drink with you.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
- Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Don't drink too much, Mr. An.
♪Look, our youthful years
spoke of destiny♪
♪Hold our hands tight,
and we'll stand by each other♪
♪Wait for the red beans to sprout♪
♪Complete the unfinished words♪
♪Don't lament the fact
that time is endless♪
♪Send the eternal wishes
to the ends of the earth♪
♪Wait for the red beans to sprout♪
♪Snowflakes fall gently
and rest on my shoulders♪
♪Piece by piece, loaded with poems♪
♪I hope the flowers
will bloom next spring again♪
♪Wait for the red beans to sprout♪
♪Snowflakes have fallen gently
and rested on my shoulders♪
It looks nice?
Yes.
So amazing.
♪I hope the flowers
will bloom next spring again♪
♪Piece by piece, loaded with poems♪
♪I hope the flowers
will bloom next spring again♪
- Happy New Year.
Look at my hand. Follow it.
Look up.
Puff your cheeks.
Alright.
You don't choke on food, right?
This hand. Hold tight.
Use some strength.
You know about this disease.
It goes from one part to another part.
It develops gradually
over time,
from the upper limbs
and then slowly to the lower limbs.
Slowly from the right side to the left.
His strength will worsen.
His muscles will atrophy more and more.
Eventually, it may affect
like speaking,
swallowing,
breathing, and so on.
Even now,
it's still difficult to fully control
and reverse it.
We can only try to delay
its progression as much as possible.
So in terms of nutritional support,
respiratory management
as well as mindset control,
one must do their best
to potentially slow down the progression
of this disease.
(Ji Jia Design)
How is it? Is it strenuous?
Am I heavy?
No.
Do you need help?
No, thank you.
Tuo.
Don't come over.
Turn off the light.
Tuo,
are you alright?
It's okay. Don't be scared.
I'll help you up.
All right.
With this, you won't
have to worry anymore.
You won't need to get up
to go to the bathroom.
Let's go to sleep.
Que,
send me to a nursing home.
♪The moment we meet♪
♪It feels like I'm electrified♪
♪Your face, oh, my God♪
♪That's what my Mr. Right looks like♪
♪What do I do? I fall for you♪
♪Happiness comes unexpectedly♪
♪Cupid's arrow♪
♪Makes everything
indescribably wonderful♪
♪The stars blink as if confessing love♪
♪You seem to walk
right out of the light♪
♪My heart beats so wildly♪
♪I'm secretly rewinding my memories♪
♪Oh my♪
♪My heart beats so wildly♪
♪I'm secretly rewinding my memories♪
♪It's love, love♪
♪Why do I feel I'm on cloud nine♪
♪So happy that even insomnia is alright♪
♪Walk with you
all night long in my mind♪
♪So this is what love feels like♪