[English subtitles are available]
[Decreed by Fate]
[Episode 8]
[Boqing Hall]
Constable Zhang.
So you're from Chonglou.
Tell your master.
Watch his son.
Waiter.
Yes, sir.
Three people?
Check out.
Yes, sir.
We've pretty much bought everything the princess likes.
Let's go back.
The General's Palace must not be as comfortable as home.
-Besides, she may not be used to the stuff here. -Top one desserts.
This is her favorite.
-There you go. -This one.
Take care of the princess when you're with her.
Especially don't let her drink plum wine.
Otherwise,
she...
She's going to get drunk again.
This is good.
Take this one.
I'll beat you to death.
Stop!
Brat.
How dare you help this dog from the North Kingdom?
So what?
Don't you feel ashamed as adults
to bully such a child?
Come on.
Take it.
Thank you.
Aren't you in Pingyang?
Why are you here?
Yan Wu.
You are from the North Kingdom?
So what?
I didn't say anything.
Why do we divide the North Kingdom
from the South Kingdom?
Since you're from the North Kingdom,
why do you follow Director Lu?
Is he also from the North Kingdom?
During the war between the South and the North,
my parents
were both dead.
He saw that I was lonely,
so he kept me with him.
Well,
I have something to do.
Goodbye, Miss Ling.
Director Liu seems to have changed his attitude towards Boqing Hall recently.
Do you feel sympathy for Wenren Jing?
Who cares about that tumor Wenren Jing?
Then it must be the other one.
You…
There are even more reasons to kick Boqing Hall out of Pingyang.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
If Boqing Hall is gone,
Wenren Ling will have nowhere to go.
By then...
Wonderful.
Then I'll save her
and invite her over to my Yinshu Pavilion.
That's killing two birds with one stone.
Director Liu is really smart.
Okay.
The first step of the plan,
catch adultery in Boqing Hall.
Master,
have we been too idle recently?
Is there anything serious?
Yes.
Don't forget to attend the matchmaker party tomorrow night, Master.
Director Zheng has reminded me several times.
Well.
Who will hold it this year?
It's the newly opened Boqing Hall.
Master.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
My heart ached
when hearing the words of Boqing Hall.
Is there anything else?
Master will return to the capital in one month.
I'm really worried by that time people will...
I'll return to the capital in one month.
I hope everything goes smoothly.
Lord Song.
Yes?
Your hands...
That's not the point.
Please help us find a widow named Zhu Xiuchun.
She lived in Pingyang ten years ago.
Now she is missing.
Who is Zhu Xiuchun?
She is Lan Que's biological mother.
I'm a matchmaker,
same as you guys.
I'm really not good at these things.
Call the police.
This is a strange thing.
It's not appropriate to report it to the police.
So you mean...
We want you to check the household register
to see if she is still in Pingyang.
Lord Song has been in a good relationship with the county government.
It makes things easier if you ask them.
Since you're so determined,
do you have something on me?
We don't know that Lord Song has helped someone forge his identity.
We also don't know that you hid information for others.
Then you should enjoy your twilight years in peace.
Are you threatening me?
Yes.
Don't touch me.
Lord Song.
I want a divorce!
What nonsense are you talking about?
It's obviously I am divorcing you.
Lord Song has something urgent to do.
We're more professional for divorce.
Lord Song.
Come back soon.
Alas.
See you.
Didn't Chairman Fang say
"Seven Out" doesn't apply to me.
I'm divorcing peacefully,
not only from the husband's side.
You just want to get more property.
I'll never agree.
Let's go to Boqing Hall to hold a divorce ceremony.
No way!
They finally left.
Love
is too tiring.
Director Lu, they've left.
Stop pretending.
Behave yourself.
It doesn't look appropriate.
Sit down.
Get me a grape.
Wipe it.
Tea.
I never thought
it would be this hard
to be served by handsome men.
I can't even go to the toilet.
It's hard for us, too.
Though we still have one hand free,
we can't go either.
I found what you wanted.
[Zhu Xiuchun]
This is hard to find.
If I hadn't invited the magistrate for tea,
well, I wouldn't have...
We should all thank the magistrate, right?
Yes.
Ouch.
Master.
My heart ached again.
Alas.
Sit down.
What's going on?
Are you entangled by my earth vine?
How can we untie this earth vine?
It will be untied when it should be.
Where is the person I asked you to find?
She's dead.
You lied to me.
Why would we lie to you?
It's written clearly on the paper
that she hung himself.
[Coroner's Report. Suicide by Hanging.]
They said as long as I stayed in the North Kingdom,
they would guarantee my mother's safety.
I could come back to visit her after I succeeded.
I'm finally back.
Have they been
lying to me?
Let me ask you.
Is Chonglou a spy agency of the North Kingdom?
Who else do you have in Pingyang?
I am gonna kill them!
Hey!
Untie the earth vine!
Go after her.
Go to Pingyang.
We have to untie this quickly.
When we were walking on the street,
everyone was looking at us as if we were monsters.
I just want to know
when I can go to the toilet.
My disciple,
look at me.
Look at Director Lu then.
How come we can endure this
but you can't?
Hey.
Jing.
Can you stay still?
We knew it!
We caught you.
Chairman Fang,
Excuse us.
A chairman, a director,
and a matchmaker.
What an eyesore.
The three of you are doing the strapping again.
How shameless you are.
Shameless!
What's wrong with you two?
Boring.
Get out!
What a pity!
Let's drag them to the street.
Let the people in Pingyang see how promiscuous Boqing Hall is.
Don't come forward!
What are you doing?
-Stay back! -How can we get out?
Take off your hands.
-Take off your hands! -Get out!
I want it.
No.
Why is it untied?
What?
This...
Earth vine...
The Twelve Earthly Branches
refer to 24 hours.
It will be untied in 24 hours.
Who said we were promiscuous?
No.
You misunderstood.
You said you would drag us to the street
and let people watch us.
Did you say that?
No.
I didn't say anything.
Shall we let them see this?
OK.
Come and look!
-Here are the two directors from Yinshu Pavilion and Tongxin Pavilion. -It's all your fault. You wanted to catch the adultery.
-Come and play a new game!
-We caught them committing adultery.
You got me into trouble!
Bah! You fool!
Bah! It's all your fault!
Bah! Idiot!
Come on, move faster.
Move faster.
[Yinshu Pavilion]
Come and play.
Is Qin Yiyi crazy?
She's entangled in a mess with a poor scholar.
Yiyi loves talents.
I heard that the scholar is knowledgeable.
Maybe he'll pass the official examination someday.
That's something to fool those poor scholars.
How many of them can pass the official examination?
It's better to be a concubine for someone who's rich and powerful.
Yiyi said those rich and powerful people only treat prostitutes as toys.
They won't treat them seriously.
Yiyi. Yiyi.
You sound like you are close to her.
Why didn't she introduce you to more clients?
This is what Yiyi's clients gave me.
Try it.
It smells so good.
Do you want to try it?
Try it?
All you know is eating.
When you're as fat as a pig, no client will come to you.
You never plan for yourself.
I don't have to work if no client comes to me.
Isn't it good?
It smells good.
Drink as much as you want tonight. My treat.
Yiyi.
Miss.
You can't go up there.
Who are you?
Yiyi, leave now.
Yiyi.
Miss.
Don't be scared.
Yiyi.
-Don't touch me! -Go!
Stop!
Mr. Hong.
This way.
The room on the second floor, please.
She...
Yiyi.
I want her.
Bastard!
Take him out.
Don't stain this place.
Yiyi.
Go.
-Go. -Let go of me.
-Look.
Yiyi.
Is my makeup okay?
What?
What are you doing?
You're really a pig.
That's Mr. Hong.
What do you mean?
Although his father, Master Hong, kept a low profile,
everyone knows that the Hongs is very rich in Pingyang.
Wow.
Then their cook must be as good as the royal chef.
You idiot.
Why did you suddenly get angry?
Let me tell you. Bring in a bottle of wine later.
Mr. Hong.
Please come in.
I want Yiyi.
She has been chosen by an officer.
He wants to marry her as a concubine.
Who is the officer?
I don't care.
All I want is Qin Yiyi.
Aren't you engaged?
What?
Didn't your father teach you well?
I knew you sent Wang Zhen to my house to tell on me.
My father is a good man.
Even if he listens to you,
I won't.
How dare you!
Who let you in?
I let her in.
Let me pour you some wine.
Have a seat.
What's your name?
You can call me Qingqing, Mr. Hong.
What's so good about Qin Yiyi?
She's always like a piece of wood.
She only knows how to piss off people.
You're right.
Send the gorgeous girl to my house.
What's wrong?
We'll talk about
Qin Yiyi later.
I want her.
Let's go now.
Let's go.
Master Wang.
I'll take good care of Mr. Hong.
-I'm going to live a good life. -Qingqing, where are you going?
You should have cared more about me.
Take off your hands.
-What's going on? -Let's go.
Qingqing.
Another reckless guy.
[Boqing Hall]
Yan Wu.
Sir,
you're back.
Did you bring back the stuff?
Yes.
I put them in the woodshed for now.
Okay.
I heard some news when I went back this time.
I heard that the Governor of Lin State was punished because he was connected to the North Kingdom.
His whole family was executed.
But strangely,
the concubine he just married to a few months ago
disappeared mysteriously.
The richest man of the capital, He Wansan, seems to get involved, too.
His whole family was exiled.
Similarly,
one of his concubines disappeared mysteriously.
I heard
these two concubines seem to know martial arts.
It's confirmed that
they all came from Chonglou.
By the way,
find out who Fang Xianxun is.
Something is wrong with him.
Yes.
The people I sent to follow
lost the target
when they came nearby.
Send more men
to search this area carefully.
Yes.
Be careful.
Excuse me,
have you seen a girl in blue clothes
with a scar on her face?
No.
Miss,
have you seen someone...
-No. -Sir.
A bowl of sugar water.
Okay.
My disciple.
You said you wanted to find Lan Que.
Now you're sitting here drinking sugar water.
What do you mean?
Well,
We've been busy all day.
This is for you.
This is good.
Find him quickly.
We still need to prepare the matchmaker party in two days.
We'll find him.
But how long are you going to keep searching like this?
We need to find someone who's well-informed
and hangs around on the street all day long.
For example...
Oh.
The news will be explosive if I write it out today.
Hi, you two nosey parkers,
how have you been?
How's everything going?
Oh.
It's you, Miss Jing.
Well,
last time, we wrote about you like that.
We didn't mean it.
We didn't want to write anything about Miss Jing.
Director Liu forced us to write like that.
That's right.
Take off your hands.
Are you asking about the corpse found in this morning?
No.
A female body was found by the riverside this morning.
There were wounds all over her body.
She got strangled on her neck.
But then again...
Wringing the neck from the back
is a usual trick that assassins from the North Kingdom would use.
The body was found naked.
The government has blocked the passage of the message.
They just put a portrait on the city gate and called on her family to identify her.
Well...
Hey.
You want to leave?
No, no, no. Look.
Guys,
I've told you the news.
Can we leave now?
Of course...
No.
We're not asking about the body.
You just talked about it voluntarily.
You...
I want to ask
whether you've heard of a girl named Lan Que.
Miss Lan?
Yes, I know her.
Master Hong.
What's wrong?
As Wang Yizhi said,
we've been targeted recently.
Tell them to be careful.
Don't let anyone catch us.
It's a servant from the Eastern City.
But he's very skilled at martial arts.
I'm no match for him.
I was...
Wang Yizhi is targeting at Young Master.
I'm afraid he'll harm Young Master.
Wang Yizhi is cunning.
What about the girl who was brought back from the Baihua Brothel?
We've handled it.
She was thrown to the riverside outside the city.
Alas.
Sorry.
Sister, I'm back.
Butler Lv asked me to bring you a lot of things.
Where is he?
This is the place the nosey parkers mentioned.
Master.
Be careful.
No wonder it's hard to find her
since she hides in such a remote place.
Miss Lan Que.
Stop hiding.
We're here to help you.
Watch out for the trap.
Master.
Are you alright?
Help!
Master, don't move.
Hold the cage.
Keep breathing.
No.
If I were outside the cage,
-I might be able to open this iron cage. -I can't swim.
But now I'm inside.
-I can't use my full power. -The water is rising too fast.
What are you doing?
Give me a hug.
At this time,
you still have the mood to joke?
Master, listen to me.
My feet got stuck.
If the water keeps going up, we'll all be dead.
I'll hold you up.
You hold on to the cage.
Hang in there. You might be able to wait until someone comes to save you.
Where do you get stuck? I'll untie it.
Left foot or right foot?
Are you hurt?
You can't swim.
Don't go down there.
Besides,
it might be okay.
No.
-I have to go down there and untie you. -Master!
-Let go of me! -Master!
-Wenren Jing! -Let go of me!
Look at me.
I've been alone for more than ten years.
I thought I was free.
After I met you, I found these years were so boring.
After today,
I'll take a position in your heart.
You won't forget me even when you get married.
I'm such a selfish person.
Shut up!
Get up!
Get up.
It's a deal.
Don't forget me.
My disciple.
Get up.
Fang Xianxun.
Fang Xianxun!
Help!
Help us!