[English subtitles are available]
[Decreed by Fate]
[Episode 03]
Get out of Pingyang!
Who asked my Matchmaker Hall to leave Pingyang?
So handsome.
It's him.
Do you know him?
Sort of.
Stones are like jade.
Pine trees are green like emeralds.
You're so pretty that
no one can compare with you.
It's good to be educated.
All I know is that he's handsome.
[Pingyang Top-class Matchmaker]
Who are you?
So handsome.
[Top-class Matchmaker]
It's bestowed by His Majesty.
[Lu Tingxiao of the Capital]
A golden folding fan.
Wow, a gold folding fan.
Oh no.
Li Gui met Li Kui.
Ling.
Come in.
It's not him.
You two should come, too.
Sis, what are you doing?
And what are you doing?
I...
Why did you prepare fruits for Lu Tingxiao?
Let's run away.
Do you really think he is Lu Tingxiao?
As a top-class matchmaker,
why is he so young?
He's not a matchmaker.
I met him in Jiaofang in the capital.
With his appearance,
he might be a courtesan.
Jiaofang?
Yes.
That means
he could be a musician
or a guest.
But he might be Lu Tingxiao, too.
It's possible that he has a special talent.
But if he is Lu Tingxiao,
we're doomed.
After all, we opened the hall in disguise.
If he wasn't Lu Tingxiao,
but he had pretended to be Lu Tingxiao,
there must be a deeper conspiracy.
If we get involved,
we might be doomed, too.
I regret it.
I should have stopped him and talked to him,
whether he's fake or not.
First, seduce him with money. Try both tough and soft tactics.
I don't mind sacrificing my beauty.
Sister.
You don't have to
sacrifice your beauty.
Forget it.
Let's run for now.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
We're going to throw out the trash, director.
Let's fight if it's not okay.
Jing.
I’ve explained to the two directors
about your opening the hall in Pingyang.
Today,
It's my pleasure to meet you two today.
In the next evaluation,
I'll put in a good word for you.
Thank you, Director Lu.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Stop!
Director,
someone didn't trust us today.
He said someone in the imperial court
wanted to report us for opening the hall in disguise.
It really scared me.
Director,
this is also disrespectful to you.
We can't just let it go.
Right.
I'm sorry for offending you.
Please forgive me, Miss.
It's easy to say sorry.
Ling.
Yes.
Cut his face.
Director Lu.
Someone dared to scare me today.
I want to scare him, too.
See you.
Go!
[Boqing Hall]
Bah!
She's just a maid.
A dog counting on its master's power.
This is great.
He's here and the seal is real.
Don't come to me for for something offensive
like this next time.
What a bastard!
I'm not convinced.
The new chairman of the Matchmaker Society
will assume office soon.
Let me see if your Boqing Hall
can be that free by then.
[Baihua Brothel]
Have a seat.
Bai Jia,
what's going on?
What do you think of this?
She's from a rich family.
She's also pretty.
Is it enough to pay my debt?
Clear his debt.
Yes.
Thank you.
I love you sincerely.
I eloped with you to Pingyang behind my parents.
How could you do this to me?
Let go of me!
Shut up!
What did you feed her?
Don't worry.
I don't want her to die.
You're a gambler.
You should know removing your hands after making a bet.
After drinking this,
if she go on missing her lover,
she will feel cold all over,
and then her eyebrows will get frosted.
Eventually, she will die of heartache.
The death
looks the same as freezing to death.
Fine.
Get out!
You don't deserve to be my lover.
That's good.
Get out!
Well...
You said it yourself.
Bai Jia,
come back!
Later,
send her to the same place.
No.
Jing, you want to see me?
Ling.
Director Lu, have some desserts.
They're all signature dishes of Jufu Restaurant.
The desserts are too dry.
Have some tea and they won't be dry.
Jing, do you want to ask me something?
What are you talking about?
I just want to thank you for saving my life.
But I'm afraid the tea is poisonous.
That's impossible.
It's impossible I only poisoned the tea and desserts.
You're really inexperienced.
This is called triple guarantee.
His kit is quite complete.
Is Lu Tingxiao, the first-class matchmaker,
pretending to be a Jiaofang musician in the capital,
or is the Jiaofang musician pretending to be Lu Tingxiao?
It gives me such a headache.
But you look so handsome.
With bright teeth,
your skin is white as snow.
It looks more delicate in a close distance.
I really want to stay by your side.
Be good.
I will take good care of you.
In what way?
Why are you awake?
I wasn't unconscious at all.
I wanted to hear what you said,
but it turned out to be nonsense.
You don't even know how to hold your breath.
You're really inexperienced.
I'm inexperienced?
Look who's tied up now.
Let me ask you.
Are you Lu Tingxiao or a Jiaofang musician?
Why did you lie?
Why did you help me?
What's your plot to infiltrate into my Boqing Hall?
You have too many questions.
I suggest
we ask each other three questions.
What do you think?
You want to bargain with me?
It looks like you haven't suffered enough.
Time to eat.
Buddy.
Keep an eye on her.
I have to go to toilet.
Okay.
Time to eat.
Come quickly!
She ran away.
Stop!
-Help!
-Be quick! Catch her!
Catch her!
-Mr. Hong, it's you.
-Stop!
-Please!
Save me.
What's wrong?
I was sold to here.
Greetings, Master Hong.
What are you doing?
She's our girl.
She was disobedient and ran out.
I'll redeem this girl.
To be honest,
she just arrived today.
The price...
What price can't I afford?
Come to my mansion later to get the money.
You may leave.
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you, Mr. Hong.
I don't know how to repay you for saving my life.
I will reward you with a large sum of money.
No need.
Mr. Hong,
I'm worried
they will still take me away later.
Please help me to the end.
I have no one to rely on in Pingyang.
Please.
Please help me.
I have some prestige
in Pingyang.
If you don't mind,
you can hide in my mansion.
Okay.
Please come with me.
[Baihua Brothel]
If you don't ask now, don't ask.
Give me your hand.
First question.
Are you Lu Tingxiao?
No.
Liar.
How come your pulse is racing?
If I say I am, you won't believe me.
Of course I said no.
Why did you open a matchmaker hall in Pingyang in my name?
To solve the divorce case for myself.
Lord Song said
no one could handle my divorce case in the world.
I can only become a top-class matchmaker
and do it for myself.
I'm asking
why you used my name.
Because it requires the name of a top-class matchmaker to open the hall.
Because you are famous.
Because you're mysterious at your whereabouts.
If I had used Liu Zhan's name,
he would have exposed me the next day.
It's my turn.
Why did you help me?
Lord Song said you opened the hall in my name
and caused a mess in Pingyang.
The other matchmakers were going to make it shut down.
This old man is really good at saying nice things.
You came to Pingyang just to help me?
Of course I have other purposes.
Tell me in details.
But I can't tell you the details.
Why do you only accept divorce cases?
To become a top-class matchmaker,
all matchmakers' cases can be calculated.
There are so few divorce cases.
It's not good for you.
Because I married a heartless man who has two faces.
So I hope to save the world,
and those who have married a heartless man.
Okay.
What kind of heartless man is he?
But I can't tell you in details.
One last question.
Your other purpose has nothing to do with me, right?
Right.
Good.
Let's stay out of each other's business.
You do your business,
and I handle my divorce cases.
I'll thank you once I become a top-class matchmaker.
I'm going to bed.
Wait.
Stay out of each other's business.
That's impossible.
You almost ruined my reputation.
You want to continue?
From now on,
you must listen to me.
Or you have to leave.
Otherwise...
What?
No one has ever threatened me.
I'm leaving now.
Liu Zhan said someone in the imperial court might be framing you.
I really have someone in the imperial court.
Otherwise, at my age,
how could I be a top-class matchmaker?
[Top-class Matchmaker]
Director,
the tea is cold.
Let me refill it for you.
Good.
But I'm curious.
If you're not a musician,
why were you in Jiaofang that day?
Jiaofang is full of male musicians.
You...
Don't tell me...
What a pity.
You have such a good appearance and figure.
After this exhausting day,
I feel so tired.
I'm going to bed.
Director Lu.
This is my room.
[Lu Tingxiao of the Capital]
Good night, Director.
Sweet dreams, Director.
Young master.
Hush.
The informant reported that
Bai Jia had showed up.
Play chess with me.
How much have we earned in the past three months?
Not a penny,
and we've nearly spent all the money taken with us from the mansion.
How come?
We took so many divorce cases.
We should at least make some money.
For the Zhou family's divorce case last time,
you broke so many antique jewelries.
You can't even compensate all of them.
And the rent and daily expenses of the Boqing Hall.
If this continues,
we won't have enough money to eat.
I will pay attention to this.
I'll try not to let this happen again.
You still have doubts?
I tried the lie test method my father had taught me.
He must be Lu Tingxiao.
Although he answered the questions fluently,
I'm always worried that he's up to something.
I'm going to keep an eye on him all night,
to see what he's up to.
You should go and rest.
I'll keep an eye on him.
I don't have time to clean other rooms today.
You stay here for the night.
Let's go.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Okay.
Interesting.
Someone seems to be watching the same thing as us.
They're hiding movements.
I can't tell if they're friends or enemies.
There's only one reason for hiding movements.
It's easy to recognize them.
We both hided our movements in the fight.
Can't tell who was the winner.
If we had not hided it,
I'm afraid it wouldn't be that simple.
So you think they are friends,
not enemies.
Not enemies.
If they were enemies,
they didn't need to hide it, and could have used the finishing move.
But whether they're friends
remains question.
That was close.
How did you know there was an ambush in Bai Jia's house?
Something is wrong with the dust in the room.
Someone must be on the beam,
and must have been in ambush for a long time.
Yes.
Then why did we pretend to leave before going in?
How could you know how many people were on the beam?
If you don't know the strength of your enemies,
don't alert them.
You are wise.
But the clue is broken.
Where should we find him next?
What does Bai Jia usually do?
Well,
I've looked into it.
He's just a gambler.
Where would a gambler go?
I see.
Of course gamblers go to the gambling house
And pawnshops, too.
Yes.
Go to sleep.
Thanks for your hard work today.
It's not hard work
as long as I'm with you.
One day,
I will become someone as powerful as you.
Go to sleep.
Yes.
Is Wenren Jing here?
Not necessarily.
It depends on what you want to see her for.
Mrs. Ma.
You look different today.
After I've got rid of that bastard,
I surely feel different.
Then why are you here today?
Of course I'm here to return the reward.
I've heard your director is back.
Rumor has it that he is a handsome and talented man.
He's kind of pretty and talented,
but his character is not very good.
Jing.
Do we have a guest?
Director Lu.
I've heard that the director of the Boqing Hall is both pretty and talented.
You are indeed extraordinary as I saw you today.
I'm flattered.
Thank you for helping me with the divorce.
It's just a small reward.
Mrs. Ma,
I helped you, right?
Yan Wu.
You're welcome.
I hope in the future, Mrs. Ma...
Oh, no.
I can't call you Mrs. Ma anymore.
What should we call her?
My maiden name is Gao.
Nickname,
Yuanyuan.
Gao...
After the divorce, we should call the woman by her original name.
I hope you can choose another person, Miss Yuanyuan.
Our Boqing Hall will do our best to serve you.
Thank you, Director Lu.
Let's talk in details.
Please.
Jing.
Make some tea.
Yes, Director.
You're welcome.
A top-class matchmaker is really different.
My cousin's
and nieces' birth dates will be all given to you.
Director Lu got three orders just by a few words.
If he lets you handle them,
you'll be one step closer to be a top-class matchmaker.
Don't you know one should refuse to eat the food handed out in contempt?
Even if I should starve to death,
I wouldn't beg Lu Tingxiao for help.
That's my sister.
You have guts.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I just think Director Lu
looks very kind today.
Just get to the point.
Nothing.
Well,
could you let me handle
the three orders from Mrs. Ma?
I promise I will complete the task.
Don't you
only want divorce cases?
How about
making me happy?
And I'll let you do it.
What do you think?
What do you want?
[Yinshu Pavilion]
I'm one step closer
to be a top-class matchmaker again.
Young master.
[Zheng]
Why are you panicking?
I'm not.
What?
The new chairman will arrive tomorrow noon.
Great.
We have to prepare in advance
and take the opportunity.
Don't let those of the Boqing Hall know about this.
Are you stupid?
The reason why Boqing Hall could be opened
must have something to do with that Lord Song.
How could I not know?
If they come,
we'll suffer.
Don't say anything discouraging.
Alright.
I like cleanliness.
I'm happy when it's clean.
Why should I do this?
I was fooled by Lu.
This is my room and my bed.
On what ground could he ask me to leave as soon as he came?
And he ordered me around.
Just leave if you've finished cleaning.
I'm going to take a nap.
You should go out.
This is my bed.
It's mine now.
Get out.
I...
just...
don't.
Get down.
Get down!
Don't think you can do whatever you want as the director.
I'm not scared of you at all.
What are you doing?
You...
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
Go.
No.