Chinese TV Series Exclusive YouTube
Why is it fighting?
I don't know.
But...
This is a good chance for the 5th Prince to show off his charm to Xiao Yan Zi.
5th Prince!
Show us your skills! We're all watching!
Jing Yuan! Jing Yuan!
You've been practicing martial arts since you were little. Don't let us down!
5th Prince!
Come on! Come on!
Jing Yuan! Jing Yuan!
Jing Yuan!
This is a good move.
Zi Wei, which one do you think they're fighting? Xiao Yan Zi?
Xiao Yan Zi has been restless since early morning. I'm not sure either.
These kids are always making trouble.
They're really not like Zi Wei.
Young people should be wild.
Let them compete with each other. It's not good to be in a fight.
Yes.
Miss Zi Wei, help the old master prepare the cultural relics.
Yes, old master.
Good.
You have a gift for each other?
Here, I'll go get some more grass.
Okay.
You've been so close.
5th Prince, help me get it.
5th Prince!
This is a competition, not a dance!
So it's him you want?
What are they talking about?
They're talking about...
I don't know.
What are they talking about?
They're talking about...
I don't know.
Boring. Let's go.
Xiao Yan Zi, wait for me!
Although Xiao Yan Zi isn't Yong Qi's sister,
they're so different.
How could Yong Qi like her?
Love is...
It's really hard to understand.
Xiao Yan Zi, wait for me.
I'll go get the grass.
Yes.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
The family is so close.
Xiao Yan Zi!
Come and see!
If I knew they were so close,
I wouldn't have met them.
The difficulty of life is in love.
What?
You regret meeting me?
How could you say that?
I'm talking about them.
I'm not a puppy.
If I can't get her,
I can't get the relationship between Xiao Yan Zi and the Fifth Prince.
Lord Jing,
you're obviously not related to Xiao Yan Zi.
Why are you upset with the Fifth Prince?
You really think you can get along with the Fifth Prince?
This...
I was afraid that the fire would burn.
So I kept it for the Fifth Prince.
You can even doubt that?
Lord Jing,
you're too petty.
Then you...
If you're right,
why should I be petty?
Okay, okay, okay.
You've made up a line with me several times.
Now you want me to do it?
Fine.
I...
won't be angry with you.
You're just a prince.
I, Xiao Yan Zi, have never been so mean.
I'm not a bad girl.
I, a prince,
have never been so low-key to talk to a girl.
Watch out!
Jing Yuan!
The sky is clear
The world is different
This time you say
I've been
The color of the flowers is different
The flowers are?
The flowers are red
The fire is burning
I cooked you some wine
and drank some cold water.
Drink it.
Hurry up and drink it.
It's only good if you drink it while it's hot.
You sound experienced.
When I was filming,
the rain and water were common.
If I got sick and missed the work,
the whole team would be waiting for me.
But, Mr. Jin,
you're good at writing and dancing.
Why can't you swim?
When I was in the Royal Garden,
I was thrown into the water and almost drowned.
How could he have the right to be drowned?
He's a bad guy.
I'll kill you.
The queen has turned into a dog and left.
Don't be afraid of water.
I'm sorry.
I mentioned your past.
The queen must have punished them severely.
The ones who can enter the Royal Garden are the nobles.
Although my family is from Ula-Nara,
I'm a bastard.
So, for the rest of my life,
I'll do my best
to not let the queen down.
Just do it.
I didn't expect
that my casual words
would make his life so harsh.
Mr. Jin, I'll toast you.
Cheers.
I've missed you.
Let's drink and have a good time.
I'll play the most romantic movie for you.
I'll play it in my memory.
You're the one who hit me.
My life is destined.
The time you gave me is not enough.
I'm the one who told you.
Let the longing become a river.
The night sky is so beautiful.
I'll wait for you to see the beautiful scenery.
The flowers are so beautiful.
The moon is so beautiful.
Love is enough.
After the end,
we'll go back to our own time and space.
This time, you said
you missed me.