The Long Ballad
Greetings, Your Highness.
I'm sorry for my rudeness.
Please kneel.
Thank you, Your Highness.
How's the progress of the case?
The mastermind has been investigated.
It's time to change the head of the Bureau, Song Meng.
Bring her here.
She is the maid who bought the fake identity.
I don't know what this identity used to do.
I have to think of a reasonable explanation.
Otherwise, I will die.
I will die.
Your Highness.
I said it.
I said everything.
I came to the palace...
actually...
actually for...
I can only rely on you.
Officer Jing.
Officer Jing?
How could it be Officer Jing?
How dare you speak nonsense in front of Her Highness?
How dare you speak nonsense?
I'm sorry.
You are my life-saving prop.
Right now,
my hands hurt.
My heart...
hurts even more.
When we first met,
we fell in love at first sight.
I thought you were just a commoner's son.
But I didn't expect that...
our identities are so unreachable.
But true love...
is not about the feeling of love.
What is love in this world?
It's the love that...
we give each other in our life.
Officer Jing.
I tried my best to get to the bottom of this.
I just want to ask you a question.
Right now,
there is only one thing left.
It's him.
You should be like the Pan family.
I should be like the Pu family.
The Pu family is like a thread.
The Pan family...
is like a thread.
Let go of me.
Jing Yue.
If you really have something to do with this woman...
I have nothing to do with her.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, please don't make things difficult for Officer Jing.
It's all my fault.
I'm just afraid...
that after I die,
the palace will be in a state of shock.
I'm afraid...
that they will say that Officer Jing...
is a coward,
that he is a man of no value,
that he kills people,
that he eats people,
that he is a man of no value.
I thought of this.
I was so heartbroken.
I'm so shocked.
I should be fine now.
It's not difficult.
You are so obsessed with her.
You can't bear to drag Officer Jing into this.
Fine.
I'll help you.
I've passed the test.
You've improved.
What?
No.
It's unreasonable.
What should I do?
Who can save me?
Pearl Princess.
Wait.
Your Highness.
I'm a member of Pearl Princess.
What are you talking about?
When did there ever be a Pearl Princess in the palace?
There was no Pearl Princess.
In Pearl Princess's world,
how could there be no Pearl Princess?
Did I kill her?
Xiao Yanzi, where are you?
Your Highness.
This case is well done.
Get the matter of the gold back to the emperor.
He is in a hurry to be prepared.
Yes.
No wonder Xiao Yanzi hasn't entered the palace yet.
Your Highness.
Pearl Princess is the illegitimate daughter of the emperor.
On the day of the hunt, she will be the father.
Then she will enter the palace.
She will be the new wife of the empress.
The devil's eyes are on fire.
Take her away.
What I said is true.
Wait.
I'm not going to believe what I said.
On the day of the hunt, we'll share it.
The empress is suspicious.
I said the new wife is in a big trouble.
She will kill me.
Xiao Yanzi.
You are in a big trouble.
I'm sorry.
Where are we going?
Shenqing Temple.
No.
The empress has forgiven me.
What else do you want?
I warn you.
In the palace...
How dare you run away?
I'm too weak.
Please forgive me.
This little maid is clumsy.
She broke something.
I'm teaching her.
Just this little word?
Yes.
Go.
I'm scared.
Isn't it just a broken thing?
Do you have to hit me?
You bitch.
Today I'll teach you a lesson.
If you hit the prince,
you'll have ten heads.
It's not enough.
You're wrong.
Do as the rules.
Yes.
You'll be killed by the hunter.
Ten times more.
No.
She will die.
You low-class maids.
When you come into the palace,
you have to know your fate.
Stop.
Ten times more.
Lord Jing.
It's only three...
Yes.
You want to save her.
Why did you let her suffer for nothing?
In this palace,
the rules are the rules.
If you make a mistake, you'll be punished.
Rules?
Can rules be bigger than human lives?
How can you be so cold-blooded?
Did you see the steel from afar?
Last year, a man promised to help the maid.
But they both died.
The palace has a life.
Keep your mouth shut.
But...
I have to keep my mouth shut.
Only six princes left.
Once the prince is dead,
the character will die.
No.
How many more princes?
Why don't you have numbers?
What numbers?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
The numbers haven't changed.
So I'm not short of numbers when I talk to him.
He must be my official CP.
Go.
My lord.
You and Miss Lin are talking in secret.
I'll open the door for you.
It's all your fault for talking nonsense
and ruining my reputation.
Ruin?
You mean...
You're Tong Zishan?
Are you in love with her or are you two sisters?
I like her.
Shut up.
Let's talk.
Don't be so mean.
I'm a night-watching fairy.
We're a couple.
We can't be separated.
If you don't believe me,
I can prove it to you.
How?
Do you remember my prophecy?
On the day of hunting,
Princess Pearl will be pregnant.
If this really happens,
it's the best proof.
What's your conspiracy?
Your props are so heavy.
So scary.
So creepy.
It's true.
The criminal department is the criminal department.
Look at these props.
The criminal department is the key.
Don't die early.
Say it.
I...
I just want to make a bet with you.
What do you want to bet with me?
Be bold.
I bet this.
If Princess Pearl really appears,
even if I win,
the jade pendant belongs to me.
If you lose,
I'll make you die.
Deal.
My man,
Nan Nian.
Where is Xiao Yan Zi?
Such a big field.
Jiu Yan,
help me keep an eye on this Lin girl.
If there's any movement,
you help me solve it.
I told you to smoke incense and smoke insects.
But you
have been smoking in the field for a long time.
Jing Yan,
thank you for your job today.
Prince Wu,
Lord Fu,
Jing Yan,
we grew up together.
You always ignored all the famous girls.
But today you bring a maid to the field.
Er Kang,
Er Kang and I are very curious.
It's just a work.
Nothing else.
How dare you steal?
Do your job well.
And you...
You're so cruel.
I'm just a maid.
I don't know the rules.
If you steal again,
I'll throw you into the woods to feed the wolves.
Do your job well.
I have to find a way to escape.
Otherwise, I can't catch up with the key plot.
Why are you still standing there?
Do your job.
Er Kang said
you were cruel
and heartless to us.
You took away the best bow in the field
and stole two maids.
Why didn't I see it?
It seems that I
can only use you.
How dare you steal again?
It hurts.
This is...
This is Lord Jing's jade pendant.
He never leaves his body.
Could it be that
Lord Jing and you
are telling the truth?
What do you think?
Miss Lian Er, you must be tired.
Come on.
Go to the sound system and take a rest.
I'll do this.
Miss Lian Er, slow down.
Be careful of your feet.
Brother Huan Zhu, I'm back.
I'm back.
Miss Lian Er,