♫  Happily tossing and turning in the spring and autumn  ♫
♫  Nothing but love and freedom  ♫
♫  Over thorny roads, across treacherous heights  ♫
♫  After a thousand sails have passed, who will swim with you  ♫
♫  I'm willing to go through the ups and downs of the world for the sake of the people  ♫
♫  Still embracing the original innocence  ♫
♫  The sound of vows falling to the ground,
this heart can be proved by Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  The darker it is the more dazzling like stars there are  ♫
♫  I wish to stride through the ups and downs of fate, and live towards the sun  ♫
♫  Moments turn into eternity, fleeting years become forever  ♫
♫  The road ahead is long,
and there is an unquenchable light in my heart  ♫
♫  Because someone is waiting for me  ♫
♫  There is one person who will complete the dream  ♫
Did I make a mistake?
I promised Yunqian that I would protect his family.
But who would've known?
I could not even protect him.
You're upset with me.
I just think that...
if it weren't for me,
he wouldn't have died.
The Sun family deserved it.
Sun Ru colluded with Zhuang Wenfeng and embezzled the disaster relief fund.
This caused widespread starvation and millions of people were left without a home.
Did he not deserve to die?
As for your friend, I gave him the opportunity to live.
But he chose to die.
Am I wrong?
Life is cruel.
Who doesn't suffer?
He was luckier than most, yet he did not appreciate it.
It's good that he's dead.
A weak man does not deserve to live in this world.
Your Highness,
do you still remember your initial goals?
Of course.
To become an empress,
bring change to the corrupted government of Southern Chen,
and make this country a better place.
Then, is everything that you do now...
for the sake of that goal?
I know what you mean.
Let me ask you.
The life of one man and one family.
Which matters more?
The life of a family and a country.
What is wrong with giving up on a man and a family for the sake of a country's people?
Everything comes... at a price
Both were black sheep,
but why must Sun Ru die
yet Zhou Cishan can live?
It's only temporary.
When the timing is right,
he will receive the penalty he deserves.
Fine.
Such a temper.
Uncle?
I was not expecting you, sorry for my rudeness.
I hope you can forgive me.
I came uninvited.
Sorry for intruding, Your Highness.
Do you need something from me, Uncle?
It's nothing.
I just wanted to speak with you.
Please feel free. I'm all ears.
Don't go too far.
What do you mean, Uncle?
The one thing your father hated most
was to see sibling rivalry between you all.
He wished for his children to live in peace.
He wished to see you live in harmony
and care for each other.
Unfortunately,
not everything goes according to what you wish for.
It seems...
that you don't plan to turn away from the wrong path.
The wrong path?
Uncle, what do you think is the right path?
The right path is your father's will.
Since he willed for Chen'er to inherit the throne,
I will protect him at all costs.
If anyone with ill intentions dares shake up the foundation of Southern Chen,
I will not hold back.
If so,
I shall look forward to it.
Back in the day,
you and I, along with Brother Sun,
ranked on the honor roll together
and toured the streets on horseback.
We were so high-spirited.
But in such a short time...
But in such a short time,
he left us eternally.
Brother Sun had a big heart
and held no prejudice.
He always took extra care of me
and I'm very grateful.
Did you know?
Brother Sun once told me this.
Though he is in the ancestral hall,
his heart is with the world.
His biggest wish was to see the world like a wild free crane.
And during his free time,
to exchange drinks with close friends...
would have been paradise.
Indeed, he lived a solitary life.
But...
he mistrusted one man.
I wasn't sure before,
but seeing how sad you are,
I am certain that you did not...
intentionally cause Brother Sun's death,
but it was the one who supported you that led it to happen.
Brother Shen,
do you really know Princess Roujia?
Did you know?
My tutor...
also had an unnatural death.
And the cause was your endorsement.
I know.
You did not intend for him to die.
It was Princess Roujia who used you to lure me in,
then sent men to kill my tutor then later, blamed it on the Sun family.
But, Brother Shen, I know you may not have wanted to be part of it.
Since you know everything so clearly,
are you sure...
that you will still enable such deeds for your own agenda?
Zhuohua?
Why are you here?
I'm so sorry for disturbing you, Your Highness.
My uncle said something similar, too.
You must know why I'm here, then.
Why are you so polite with me, Zhuohua?
I believe that you understand why, Your Highness.
You and I are like-minded with similar circumstances.
We have poor relationships with our families, and are both aware...
of how challenging our paths are as women.
Since that is the case,
we should be of one mind and help each other to finish this race.
In my opinion, you're not quite right, Your Highness.
Which part of it?
In the beginning, I really thought that we could walk together.
Later on,
I thought that we just worked differently toward the same goal.
But now, I realize...
that we are no longer going in the same direction...
and have parted ways.
Our relationship...
is just like this hairpin.
Since she does not appreciate my kindness,
then I will not hold back.
♫  The love that opened my eyes  ♫
Your Highness, what kind of person are you?
♫  A dream of a goose and a phoenix crossing together  ♫
♫  Tenderness is like parting and complaints  ♫
♫  Going around for a lifetime, constantly cut and scattered,
the world is day and night  ♫
♫  The fireworks of the world are like quicksand
of the world after all  ♫
- Your Highness.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Thank you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I'm not worthy of your thanks.
The world owes it to you.
Nobody is less worthy than others.
♫  Again, someone on the precipice of fate  ♫
Which is the real you?
♫  The heartache is caused by the painful loneliness  ♫
Brother Yunqian,
are you willing...
to get drunk with a sinner like me?
♫   The setting sun cannot clear the morning fog  ♫
♫  The fleeting years burst into pieces,
the memories of them cause me pain  ♫
♫  I can't hold onto my lover's heart, turning back,
I realize there is nowhere to go  ♫
♫  The fireworks of the world are like quicksand
of the world after all  ♫
♫  In that moment of confusion,
I want to know what your answer will be  ♫
♫  Again, someone on the precipice of fate
leaves tear stains behind while bidding farewell  ♫
Shen Jinghong!
♫  The world of mortals is lonely and painful  ♫
Shen Jinghong, you're burning up.
Wake up.
Don't move.
Do you want some medicine?
My head hurts.
It hurts?
Do you want a massage?
Take it slow.
You're awake.
Have some medicine.
Why are you here?
I walked right in.
Your door was open.
Also, if I didn't save you,
you would have gotten brain damage from the fever.
But why don't you have any servants at home?
You were in the yard all night and nobody noticed.
I wanted to be alone so I gave them a day off.
Since you don't have servants now,
all the more reason I should stay and look after you.
Thank you for helping, Princess Jing'an.
I'm fine now.
Please return, Princess Jing'an.
But...
Don't move.
Do you really want to get brain damage?
It's none of your business. Right?
You...
Fine.
Finish the medicine and I will leave.
I will watch you finish it.
Are you happy now?
I'm a foreign princess,so I can be excused for my manners.
Princess Roujia, shouldn't you be a precious and pure being?
How can you come to a man's home in the morning?
You've misunderstood, Jing'an.
I'm here to meet Official Shen to discuss matters regarding Jishan Hall.
Stop pretending.
I'm not a fool who would believe you.
Never mind.
You're young and unfiltered, so I will not find fault with you.
But don't go too far.
Don't forget, your brother is concerned about you.
Are you unwell?
Why are you here, Your Highness?
Please return.
Why?
My humble abode is unworthy of your presence.
What are you doing?
Lowering your temperature with alcohol.
Don't worry about me, Your Highness.
I'm much better now.
Is that so?
I see that your ears are still red
so I thought you still had a fever.
I know you're angry at me.
I was a little harsh that day,
but Sun Yunqian's death was a surprise to me.
Of course, I knew you were friends.
Even if I did not care about him, I cared about your feelings.
After recovering,
you should replenish your nutrients.
Your Highness is precious,
so you don't have to waste time here.
Since you know Her Highness is precious,
then you should know that Her Highness has never taken care of others like so.
She even scalded her fingers to make soup for you.
♫  The moon in the water asked the flowers
in the mirror why lovesickness hurt?  ♫
♫   The setting sun cannot clear the morning fog  ♫
♫  The fleeting years burst into pieces,
the memories of them cause me pain  ♫
♫  I can't hold onto my lover's heart, turning back,
I realize there is nowhere to go  ♫
♫  The fireworks of the world are like quicksand
of the world after all  ♫
♫  In that moment of confusion,
I want to know what your answer will be  ♫
♫  Again, someone on the precipice of fate
leaves tear stains behind while bidding farewell  ♫
♫  The heartache is caused by the painful loneliness  ♫
♫  The fireworks of the world are like quicksand
of the world after all  ♫
♫  I cared about you with all my heart,
but how are you going to accept it?  ♫
♫  The sound of the wind is like
the desperate cries from the jackdaw  ♫
♫  This regret sprouts from the joys and sorrows  ♫
♫  The city in my heart collapsed from the loneliness and pain  ♫
♫  In the years of deep love, I am willing to shield you from the wind and sand  ♫
Official Mu,
what do you think?
Official Mu.
Were you listening to me?
Your Majesty, my apologies for my manners before the throne.
No need to kneel.
I was just asking.
What is wrong with you today?
You have been so restless.
Your Majesty,
my...
my back is slightly aching.
I don't feel quite well.
I'm sure it's because you are worn out from working on the Talent Appreciation System.
Summon an imperial physician.
Your Majesty, I am afraid...
that it's just a minor discomfort.
I will get better in a few days.
There is no need to summon an imperial physician.
- It's just...
- Your Majesty.
I'm fine, really.
But...
Your Majesty, in my opinion, I don't think Official Mu is unwell.
If not, then what?
Perhaps it's menstruation.
Well, it's like that.
I...
I misunderstood.
Well, why don't I give you half a day off?
You may go home and rest.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I shall complete my work at the Ministry of Revenue before I return home.
Sure.
You should take care.
Don't overwork yourself.
Yes.
I shall take my leave, then.
Your Majesty, please excuse me for being honest.
My greetings to you, Lord Ding.
Thank you, My Lord.
This is the palace carriage.
His Majesty knew that I was unwell
and fetched the palace carriage to send me home.
His Majesty is so kind to you.
His Majesty is kind to you, My Lord.
I'm nothing compared to you.
Is somebody being jealous?
Oh, it's my man!
Grandaunt,
can't you just stay in the capital?
You should allow me to show my filialty to you.
That's right. It's so far and distant.
Once you depart from here, we won't know when we can meet again.
I've lived in Jiangnan for too long.
I'm not used to the capital's climate.
Your Majesty is the emperor and has many responsibilities.
I'm honored that you are here to bid me farewell.
What do you mean?
I am a junior.
Juniors typically bid their elders farewell.
I'm just doing what I should be.
Ordinary people at your age
would have already gotten married and had children.
That's right.
But nothing I say will work.
His Majesty always gives excuses.
Why are we talking about this?
Your Majesty.
Be honest with me.
Do you have someone you like?
How is that possible?
It seems Liu Chen has feelings for Zhuohua.
I noticed it when we were in Jiangnan.
Will he lose focus on this
and fall out with Liu Yan for her sake?
You're so sharp, Your Highness.
Speaking of which, a few days ago, I saw the female Tanhua of Southern Chen.
She is very witty.
That's right.
Zhuohua is talented and not inferior to men.
You're a young lady now.
Why are you acting cute
like when you were younger?
Grandaunt,
I would like to ask for something from you.
What's mine is yours.
Even if you want the stars of the sky, I will try to get them for you.
Grandaunt, can you give me the Evil-erasing Sword?
The Evil-erasing Sword is a national weapon.
It can only appear when the country is in danger.
Noble families are in power.
Is this not a sign of a dying country?
Jiaojiao,
since when have you been interested in political matters?
I am also of royal blood.
It is only normal for me to be concerned
about the national matters of Southern Chen.
Normal?
Jiaojiao,
could it be that you wish to take that seat?
Grandaunt.
Did you not teach me all this knowledge on governance for national stability?
You should know very well that I am more capable than Liu Chen.
If I become the empress, it will bless the people.
I taught you such things
so that you would have a sense of discernment.
I did not expect to encourage such ideas.
What is wrong with having these ideas?
Jiaojiao,
that is a road of no return.
While it seems noble and glorified,
it is actually like walking on thin ice.
You cannot lower your guard for even an instance.
Only an incapable ruler would walk on thin ice.
I will definitely be a wise ruler who is loved by the country.
Jiaojiao,
you've had a rough childhood.
I cannot bear to see you take such risks.
I just hope to see you live happily as the First Princess of Southern Chen.
Grandaunt,
but I only want that seat.
If you really care about me,
give me the Evil-erasing Sword.
Impossible.
Jiaojiao,
why would you have such ideas?
Just forget about it. This is impossible!
Grandaunt, calm down.
It's my fault,
don't be angry anymore.
Jiaojiao,
return to Jiangzuo with me.
We will live a peaceful life.
Okay?
- Listen to me.
- Grandaunt.
I will not return to Jiangzuo with you.
I just want to tend to you in the capital.
Why am I feeling dizzy?
Jiaojiao.
You drugged me?
Grandaunt,
this drug is harmless.
It will only make you weak.
I would never hurt you.
Qi.
Look at you.
Those who know what happened would know that you requested Qi to do the Mu family a favor.
But those who don't would think you're unwilling to part with her.
Why are you pointing it out?
Mother. Old Master Mu.
Since His Majesty has made the judgment, it's time to wrap it up.
In the future, if we just do as we're told,
there will be nothing to worry about.
Don't worry. I will keep an eye on him.
Even if I can't do it myself, I have 18 sisters to help me out.
Qi, I don't mean to lecture you.
Though I'm quite the playboy, I gave every concubine the acknowledgment they deserved.
They are all part of the Mu family.
But you are even worse than I am.
Can't you even acknowledge him?
Such behavior is really unfair.
So, you're fair?
But our home is running out of space.
Do you think Qi cannot see what kind of player you are?
You want to be the Prince Regent's father-in-law, don't you?
Stop calling me out.
Enough, let's go or we won't reach the lodging in time.
We'll get going, then.
Qi, you are meant to do great things.
The Mu family is unable to support you,
but don't worry, you have me.
They will not cause you more trouble.
Just walk forward fearlessly.
Thank you, Mother.
♫  The flowing water bends and reflects the round moon  ♫
♫  Gently sprinkling your eyebrows and eyes  ♫
Let me do it myself.
- Delicious, right?
- Delicious.
♫  The night rain hitting the sycamore tree disturbs a sparrow  ♫
♫  The young maiden become acquainted with
the green robes in that moment  ♫
What's wrong?
Would you like a steamed bun?
♫  ...stretching while not breaking my time and drifting away  ♫
♫  Thousands of words are not enough
to accompany the long journey  ♫
Since it is your treat, we should at least go to Yipin Bakery.
When I have ever starved you?
♫  Accompanying you, calmly waiting
for the clouds to fade away  ♫
I was thinking of getting a free meal
but I didn't expect it to be sold out.
My Lord, shall we go to Shixiang House?
I heard from Juli that they hired a good chef who's skilled in pastries.
Sure.
♫  Toiling away long hours together with the candle's light  ♫
♫  Not caring about the high mountains, deep waters, and long roads  ♫
♫  Fortunately, you are here, not afraid of the repeated trips
and hanging around with me  ♫
♫  You are like the flowers and moon, stretching while unbroken my time and drifting away  ♫
♫  Thousands of words are not enough
to accompany the long journey  ♫
♫  You are like the flowers and moon,
more graceful than a palace in the sky  ♫
Should I acknowledge him?
This hairpin is luxurious.
If other women wear it, it would outshine them.
Only you can match up to it, Yunyun.
As expected of a most outstanding noble lady.
I'm sorry. That was rude of me.
You shouldn't say that, Your Highness.
You are my savior.
I am so grateful to you, Your Highness.
Every injustice has its perpetrator.
I will make sure Mu Zhuohua pays for it.
Zhuohua may have her reasons.
Never mind. If you have any troubles,
just let me know and I will help you as much as I can.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Jing'an, you're back?
You look very happy.
I presume you enjoyed yourself.
I'd be happy doing anything as long as I'm with Official Shen.
Princess Jing'an has been in Southern Chen for a while now,
yet your manners are still lacking.
I'm afraid you're overly focused on romance
and overlooked your priorities.
I wonder who has been crushing on the Prince Regent for years
and eventually became a maiden.
You fight every time you meet.
We are family. We should live in harmony together.
Who are you calling family?
You have skin as smooth as porcelain.
I'm sure these pearls will make you even more dazzling.
Yunyun is not completely wrong.
The Mid-Autumn Palace Banquet is tomorrow.
You must be careful to guard your dignity.
After all, you didn't come to Southern Chen just for sightseeing and leisure.
All right. I shall excuse myself.
Grandaunt,
I know you're awake.
Do you dislike seeing me so much?
Grandaunt.
I'm your beloved Jiaojiao.
Did you not say that you would even give me the stars of the sky?
Now, I am only asking for the Evil-erasing Sword.
Why won't you give it to me?
"Only"?
When civil unrest begins, poverty will strike.
The ones who suffer are the country's people.
Jiaojiao, don't be so unrepentant.
"Unrepentant"?
Grandaunt,
I never understood that about you.
You had the capabilities,
yet you had no courage to ascend the throne.
Back then, you were only one step away from the throne.
But I am not like you.
I will not remain in a small place like Jiangnan, wasting my life away.
Let me do what you never did.
You can remain in the capital
and watch how I resurrect the Liu Clan's glory.
♫  I can't forget the love that is still is nipping at my ears and temples  ♫
♫  Memories keep slamming into rocks and have nowhere to berth  ♫
♫  Both sides gaze at each other in the drizzling rain, but one has turned into clouds and mist  ♫
♫  Leaving the isolated heart's island, like waves without a shore  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously love is locked and entwined in our eyes  ♫
♫  For a hug, we burn for a lifetime  ♫
♫  Thousands of sails have been used to search for you  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously willing to swear life and death
to be entangled for a lifetime  ♫
♫  For a moment of heartbeat, paying homage to Heaven  ♫
♫  Never parting ways, we made this promise long ago  ♫
♫  I can't forget the turmoil of love and hate,
even if the next day is far away  ♫
♫  Two souls embrace in chaos, how can it be written off?  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously love is locked and entwined in our eyes  ♫
♫  For a hug, we burn for a lifetime  ♫
♫  Thousands of sails have been used to search for you  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously can't be erased, and haunted by lingering dreams  ♫
♫  For a moment of heartbeat, paying homage to Heaven  ♫
♫  Want to have one more glimpse of you,
even just for a second more  ♫