Subtitles and Timing brought to you by the ❦Team of A Dazzling Love❀ Team @viki.com
♫  Happily tossing and turning in the spring and autumn  ♫
♫  Nothing but love and freedom  ♫
♫  Over thorny roads, across treacherous heights  ♫
♫  After a thousand sails have passed, who will swim with you  ♫
♫  I'm willing to go through the ups and downs of the world for the sake of the people  ♫
♫  Still embracing the original innocence  ♫
♫  The sound of vows falling to the ground,
this heart can be proved by Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  The darker it is the more dazzling like stars there are  ♫
♫  I wish to stride through the ups and downs of fate, and live towards the sun  ♫
♫  Moments turn into eternity, fleeting years become forever  ♫
♫  The road ahead is long,
and there is an unquenchable light in my heart  ♫
♫  Because someone is waiting for me  ♫
♫  There is one person who will complete the dream  ♫
Yun Xiangyue?
So, after rescuing his wife and daughter, he led the pursuers away.
It seems the person using the hawk-claw-like weapon had tried to capture him alive.
The one using needles wanted to kill him.
They are not from the same group.
Logically speaking, the human skull is quite tough.
Only a few weapons are capable of piercing through the skull.
I heard that the Tang Sect, known as the masters of hidden weapons in Shu, has a similar weapon.
It's called...
It's called Stormy Pear Blossom Needles.
The needles are as fine as cow's hair, too thin to be seen.
And it can pierce through bones.
But I've only read about all these things in books.
I don't know if it's true or not.
I've seen them before.
It's Wandering Needle, the Imperial Shadow Guards' unique and powerful weapon.
Don't speak recklessly.
Emperor Brother.
Emperor Brother?
Emperor Brother, stop writing.
Let's go and play.
Just go without me.
- What's this? Let me play with it.
- Your Highness, this isn't a toy.
- Let me play with it. Just a little while.
- You can't play with this.
- Just let me pay with it.
- Yan. Yan.
Emperor Brother, I want to play with it.
Little Brother Yan, that's the Imperial Shadow Guards' Wandering Needle.
It's a lethal weapon. You can't play with it.
But if you like it, I'll make one set for you when you grow up.
It can be kept as a self-defense weapon.
Fine, all right.
Help!
- Little Brother, hang in there!
- Help! Emperor Brother!
Your Majesty, the Crown Prince has been in poor health.
I'm afraid it has damaged his fundamental well-being this time.
In the future, he'll need to take extra care of himself.
Any carelessness can lead to illness.
We will make every effort to maintain his health.
It's just that His Highness has to suffer a lot.
Mother, forgive me.
It was all my fault.
No, it wasn't
Little Brother Yan.
Emperor Brother.
Little Brother Yan, didn't you promise not to be a crybaby anymore?
I didn't expect even the invincible Lord Ding to be in this state.
Put the body away.
We'll return to the capital.
Protect His Lordship.
My Lord, leave first.
My Lord, make way!
It's so high up.
Why do you have poison with you?
Poison?
Oh, you mean the one I threw at the man just now?
That's not poison. It's lime powder.
Lime powder?
What's wrong?
I think I caught a cold.
What should I do now?
The metropolitan examination is around the corner.
Where are you going?
Find His Lordship and Miss Mu.
His Lordship said not only does this operation aim to expose the mastermind,
but it's also to test Miss Mu.
We can't be present.
Thank you, My Lord.
My Lord, I... You have to be responsible for this.
Despite anything, you're the chief examiner.
You see. It won't be too much to help me secure a place
through the back door. Right?
I don't need a high rank.
Just as long as I can take the palace examination.
You should learn how to treat your subordinate from First Prince.
I can't do that.
My Lord, are you in a better mood now?
Were you trying to please me?
Well, I dare not try to please you.
But I noticed you were in a bad mood.
The ones who tried to kill you
didn't seem like Shadow Guards. Right?
If they were not Shadow Guards, who do you think they were?
How... How would I know?
My Lord, are you suspecting me?
Your memory is really poor.
I just saved your life.
I just think that this Wandering Needle is like a silent killer.
If they were really Shadow Guards, we would have been dead by now.
If Shadow Guards were really here, what would you do?
Mu Zhuohua.
My Lord, didn't you want to lure the enemy into the trap?
So I'm doing you a favor here.
Five years ago, 30,000 soldiers of the Cangwu Army perished at Juma River.
That included our father.
His Lordship has always believed that he carelessly lives alone in this world.
That's why he does everything himself, never relying on others.
I'm also a survivor.
The Falcon Squad consists of former Cangwu Army members.
You would never disobey His Lordship's orders.
But we're different.
My father traded his life to save His Lordship.
So I won't allow anything to happen to him.
I shall entrust His Lordship's safety to you two.
Let's go.
What...
I thought he didn't have any urges because he was injured.
I thought the rumor was true.
After all, Father said all men have urges.
Unless he's not a man.
What's happening now?
What... What is he planning to do?
No, no, no.
I need to stay away from him.
It was a repeating crossbow?
What was I thinking?
You didn't even release the arrows.
How did they die?
- This is...?
- Wandering Needle.
Wandering Needle?
Where are we going?
This thing is indeed powerful.
My Lord.
We were late. Please leave first.
Let's go.
Who's there?
You don't need to be too restrained.
Based on seniority, you should call me Great-Grandaunt.
Your Majesty, it's very nice of you.
I know my place.
I'm just an orphan of the Zhou clan's collateral line.
It's all thanks to Your Majesty's care that I'm where I am today.
I dare not overstep my bounds.
Well, well.
All of you can be excused.
Mother, you promised me before.
Why did you eat your words?
Do you think I'm willing to do this?
To harm your dear little brother?
Ju'er, everything I've done is for you.
Liu Yan holds great power and influence.
If he were to rebel one day, who could control him?
He would never do such a thing.
We've been brothers for many years. I trust him.
Then, what if he finds out the truth behind the war at Juma River five years ago?
What if he discovers that I wanted him gone forever?
You plotted the war at Juma River all by yourself back then.
I only learned about it afterward.
I helped you handle the aftermath to protect you.
Deceiving Yan like this made me feel deep remorse.
But why do you still have to take his life now?
- He's the one who doesn't want to let me go.
- You—
That's why he discovered Yun Xiangyue and Yuan Chengming.
Ju'er,
only when he's dead can you truly feel at ease.
Mother!
Yan has always considered you his birth mother.
You protect him time and time again.
If he were to learn the truth behind these events,
would he still remember the sibling bond he shares with you?
Yes.
I believe he would.
Mother, a mother's debt is repaid by her child.
Back then, when you wanted Yan to drown, I risked my life to save him.
And I ended up with a lifelong ailment.
Now, if you still want his life,
I can only follow suit as I did back then.
Are you trying to threaten me?
I dare not.
My Lord, I lost your cloak.
It's all right.
What is it again this time?
My Lord, I've finally figured it out.
The clues pointed to the Shadow Guards,
so you deliberately took this risk
to see if His Majesty would show up to save you.
Now that the Shadow Guards have appeared,
do you...
Do you now believe that it wasn't His Majesty?
The ones who can mobilize the Shadow Guards can only be His Majesty or...
Mu Zhuohua.
Are you truly that bold or timid?
Forgive me for speaking out of turn.
Chen'er is honest and impulsive.
Roujia doesn't care about worldly disputes.
The one who can mobilize the Shadow Guards and knows my health condition
could only be Dowager Empress.
Yet we have a strong bond even if we're not biologically related.
Our mother-and-son bond has lasted for thirty years.
My Lord, you can only drink it after boiling it.
You'll get sick if you drink it like this.
We're on the run now.
So just make do with this.
What should I do now?
I won't be able to make it for the examination now.
If so, sit for the next one.
I can't wait until then.
I've been preparing for so many years.
Let's hurry on with our journey, then.
I...
Get on.
I'll carry you.
But... But it's not appropriate, My Lord.
I...
I'll just rest here for a while.
I'll be able to walk after resting.
Just let me rest for a while.
Then, prepare to sit for the exam next time.
But I still feel it's inappropriate, My Lord.
Get on.
Why are you so light?
My birth mother passed away when I was young.
No one cared about me.
They often bullied me for being an illegitimate daughter.
They didn't give me enough food.
That's why I've grown so thin and petite.
I don't think the Mu family would go to the extent of being stingy with food.
My Lord, you have no idea servants in prominent households like this
tend to treat those who are powerless with disdain.
It was because I never had enough to eat as a child that I made a vow.
When I grow up, I must succeed in the metropolitan examination and make sure I get to eat my fill.
Eat more from now on.
His Lordship has a well-shaped head.
Don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Stay away from me.
Don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
Please don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
- Don't be scared.
- My Lord!
My Lord, are you all right?
Don't kill me.
Looks like you're safe and sound.
We don't have to worry anymore.
Let's go.
No, don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
Go and decoct some medicine.
Yes, Your Lordship.
No...
The decoction is ready.
Why don't you deliver it?
Me?
I lost my temper the other day and scared Miss Mu.
I didn't know His Lordship still needed her.
I'm afraid I may mess it up for him.
Just go and do this favor for me.
Hurry. Go quickly.
She has a fever.
Metropolitan examination.
I'm going to be late.
I can't make it for the exam.
Here's the medicine.
Are you expecting me to feed her?
"The benevolent do not doubt;
the wise do not worry, the virtuous do not fear."
What... What does that mean?
"The virtuous do not fear."
She's reciting scriptures to prepare for the metropolitan examination.
"The benevolent do not doubt."
Don't...
Don't you know how to feed someone?
Zhijian does.
Then, tell him to come inside now.
He...
He's upset.
Zhijian seems seems lively and cheerful.
In fact, his knot is heavier than yours.
Let me do it, then.
You can go and comfort him.
Just say it if you have something to say.
Stop flipping through your notes. Or I'll ignore you.
I'm looking for a phrase to comfort you.
His Lordship refuses to believe that His Majesty is behind all this.
He's even willing to put his life at risk as a stake.
Fortunately, it ended well.
His Majesty really sent his men to protect His Lordship.
But this time,
our investigation is in vain again.
We'll get to the bottom eventually.
After news that our father and brothers had died on the battlefield reached us,
our relatives were too busy fighting over the family wealth to care about our lives.
It was His Lordship who stormed into the residence on a rainy night
and took us both away,
giving us a chance to survive.
From that night on, you could no longer speak,
and I lost my heart.
Yes.
But I never thought about...
what His Lordship had lost.
Everything.
My Lord, let me feed her the medicine.
Which of you two can come and feed her?
Come here.
"It is said..."
"It is said in history, a wise person should speak and act with caution."
But you're far from cautious in your words.
Your talk is full of nonsense.
"It is said...
to trust the capable without doubt."
"T-Trust the capable without doubt."
How can you still think of currying favor when having a fever?
This phrase has a well-known meaning.
It indicates that one should trust and utilize capable individuals without hesitation.
But, My Lord, she sounds like she's ironically criticizing.
It sounds like she's saying that you are...
Enough.
Can you stop talking nonsense and focus on feeding her the medicine?
"It is said..."
"It is said, a wise person should speak and act with caution.
The benevolent do not doubt, the wise do not worry, the virtuous do not fear."
All right, I get it.
Just drink your medicine.
Are you sure you want
to use the rewards granted to you in exchange for allowing females to attend the imperial exam?
Yes.
When I was among the common people,
I witnessed women with extraordinary talents, strong character, and determination.
They're no less knowledgeable than men.
But due to outdated beliefs,
they can't take the exam and contribute to the country.
Their lives are not easy.
I believe if knowledgeable women
can stand in the court based on their abilities,
they will be like a flag for the world to see and remember.
Over time, their mindset will gradually change.
I ask that you give women all over the nation a chance
to prove themselves by allowing them to attend the imperial exam.
The path of the imperial exams is like the rivers and seas with undercurrents.
You think that passing the exams might change your destiny.
Yet none of these paths will be like a stroll.
Mother?
Mother.
Mother!
Mother,
I miss you so much.
Mother, you were right.
You told me that I must study.
After studying, I would gain knowledge, and my understanding will expand.
You also said that medical knowledge was beneficial.
Even if we can't save anyone's life, we can still save ourselves at a critical moment.
Mother.
Mother!
I failed to save you.
But you saved me.
I'm your mother.
I can even trade my life for you.
I was incompetent that you have to strive for your future on your own.
Every parent would plan everything for their children.
Mother.
Mother!
Mother, I will grow up someday.
And I will be a parent someday.
So I must strive for my future myself.
Look at me now.
Am I not in the capital now?
I'll sit for the metropolitan examination soon.
The metropolitan examination...
The metropolitan examination.
I'm going to miss it. I'm going to miss it.
Metropolitan examination! The metropolitan examination.
We're already on our way back to the capital.
We are, My Lord?
That's great. That's great.
My Lord,
thank you.
Thank you very much.
Could it be that His Lordship looked after me for the past two days?
That's impossible.
What virtues or abilities do I even possess to deserve that?
The dignified, prestigious,
and approachable Lord Ding
isn't as arrogant and cruel as rumored.
What are you going to do now, Mu Xiaoqi?
You even told Mother in your dream that you'd strive for your own future.
How can you think about relying on him now?
I used to consider First Prince to be the perfect candidate for the throne.
Lord Ding and First Prince have a good relationship.
Then, Lord Ding must be a stable support for me.
But I've overheard shocking secrets
and run into powerful individuals who want to take Lord Ding's life.
Even if it weren't His Majesty, it must be someone prominent.
So should I rely on him or not?
If he abandoned me in the woods back there, I would betray him without hesitation.
But Lord Ding never abandoned me.
He even carried me on his back and took care of me in person.
Wake up!
Come on, don't be soft-hearted.
It looks like you've almost recovered.
My Lord, we can arrive at the examination hall on time. Right?
My Lord, you're the examiner.
So, you'll definitely be there on time. Right?
I am the examiner,
but if I have another engagement, I can find someone else to replace me.
So you're not going?
That won't do.
Then, I must get off the carriage and ride a horse back.
Calm down.
- My Lord...
- We have one day left. We'll make it.
Wait, My Lord. If I don't make it in time for the examination, what should I do?
You can sit for the next one.
The next one?
My Lord, have you ever heard of a folk tale...
about Cao Cao and Hua Tuo?
Yes, I've heard of it.
Do you know the lesson from that story?
Helping others doesn't always lead to a good outcome.
Enough.
Stop trying to feel me out.
If you fail the examination, I'll support you for three years.
But what if I can never make it?
Then, I might as well support you for a lifetime.
What if I do well in the exam?
Then, I'll reward you with a gift.
I get a gift for doing well?
What gift do you want?
I...
Can I have this jade pendant?
Sure.
We shall see how well you do, then.
What should I do?
Why is Young Lady not back yet?
This is bad. This is really bad.
Young Master Shen.
Is there anything I can help you with, Your Highness?
It's an important day for the imperial exam.
I can't ask you to do anything for me.
I'm giving you the Four Treasures of the Study from Qingzhou for your exam.
May everything go smoothly.
Your Highness, please rest assured.
For this examination, I shall not disappoint you.
Subtitles and Timing brought to you by the ❦Team of A Dazzling Love❀ Team @viki.com
♫  I can't forget the love that is still is nipping at my ears and temples  ♫
♫  Memories keep slamming into rocks and have nowhere to berth  ♫
♫  Both sides gaze at each other in the drizzling rain, but one has turned into clouds and mist  ♫
♫  Leaving the isolated heart's island, like waves without a shore  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously love is locked and entwined in our eyes  ♫
♫  For a hug, we burn for a lifetime  ♫
♫  Thousands of sails have been used to search for you  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously willing to swear life and death
to be entangled for a lifetime  ♫
♫  For a moment of heartbeat, paying homage to Heaven  ♫
♫  Never parting ways, we made this promise long ago  ♫
♫  I can't forget the turmoil of love and hate,
even if the next day is far away  ♫
♫  Two souls embrace in chaos, how can it be written off?  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously love is locked and entwined in our eyes  ♫
♫  For a hug, we burn for a lifetime  ♫
♫  Thousands of sails have been used to search for you  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously can't be erased, and haunted by lingering dreams  ♫
♫  For a moment of heartbeat, paying homage to Heaven  ♫
♫  Want to have one more glimpse of you,
even just for a second more  ♫