♫  Happily tossing and turning in the spring and autumn  ♫
♫  Nothing but love and freedom  ♫
♫  Over thorny roads, across treacherous heights  ♫
♫  After a thousand sails have passed, who will swim with you  ♫
♫  I'm willing to go through the ups and downs of the world for the sake of the people  ♫
♫  Still embracing the original innocence  ♫
♫  The sound of vows falling to the ground,
this heart can be proved by Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  The darker it is the more dazzling like stars there are  ♫
♫  I wish to stride through the ups and downs of fate, and live towards the sun  ♫
♫  Moments turn into eternity, fleeting years become forever  ♫
♫  The road ahead is long,
and there is an unquenchable light in my heart  ♫
♫  Because someone is waiting for me  ♫
♫  There is one person who will complete the dream  ♫
Do you really like him?
Yes, I've fallen for him.
But...
I can't do that.
Why not?
Sir, you already know this.
My journey has been full of twists and turns, ups and downs.
I've endured countless hardships and overcame many obstacles to accomplish what I have today.
I'm afraid that if I allow myself to fall for Lord Ding,
I'll undo all my previous efforts...
and burn my bridges.
I've watched you grow up.
Naturally, I understand the hardships you've faced better than anyone.
But you need to understand one thing.
If you lose yourself for the sake of love,
then it's the fault of the world, not yours.
Sir, your words make sense.
But I'm still not capable of changing the current situation.
I'll bury my feelings for him deep in my heart
because I must continue moving forward.
Sir, I must take my leave now.
Do you have anything else to say to me?
I've said everything that needs to be said.
Go on.
After I leave this time,
I don't know when I'll be able to return and visit you again.
If you're having a bad time, come and visit me in the capital.
I will take good care of you.
Just focus on being a good official, that's how you'll show your care and piety to me.
Zhuohua, I have something to talk to Tutor Shang about.
Then I'll take my leave.
Off you go.
Go.
Coincidentally, I also have a couple of things to say to Your Lordship.
Please go ahead.
I can tell your relationship with Qi is not ordinary.
You should know that she changed her identity. Right?
She didn't hide it from me.
Qi changed her identity out of necessity.
When a woman holds an official position, she encounters constraints and limitations at every turn.
Her unique background makes her journey even more challenging.
You should understand this better than I do.
Forgive my drunken ramblings.
You treat Qi differently.
This kind of treatment might be a form of blessing for others.
But for Qi, it's perhaps more like a shackle.
Do you understand what I'm trying to imply here?
Thank you for your reminder, Tutor Shang.
I know she has her ambitions.
And I will clear the path for her.
I won't let her be held back because of me.
I'm nearing the end of my life.
It's my greatest fortune to have met her in this lifetime.
I won't ask for more.
Very well, then. Your words put my mind at ease.
It's also Qi's blessing to have met you.
You should leave, too.
My Lord, what did Tutor Shang tell you?
What did Tutor Shang tell you?
I asked you first.
Well... I won't tell you...
if you don't tell me.
♫  The flowing water bends and reflects the round moon  ♫
♫  Gently sprinkling your eyebrows and eyes  ♫
♫  The galaxy is like the sea,
the eyes are like the eaves covered with snow  ♫
♫  The night rain hitting the sycamore tree disturbs a sparrow  ♫
♫  The young maiden become acquainted with
the green robes in that moment  ♫
♫  Afraid that the number of twists and turns will increase  ♫
♫  You are like the flowers and moon, stretching while not breaking my time and drifting away  ♫
♫  Thousands of words are not enough
to accompany the long journey  ♫
♫  You are like the flowers and moon,
more graceful than a palace in the sky  ♫
♫  Accompanying you, calmly waiting
for the clouds to fade away  ♫
♫  Standing on heights looking clearly into the horizon with a shared aspiration  ♫
♫  It is much farther than just two consensual hearts  ♫
♫  Look at this world again after thousands of sails have passed  ♫
My Lord, you're back!
What is it?
Nothing.
Please continue your stroll with Official Mu, My Lord.
It's getting late.
Get an early rest, My Lord.
Isn't that the scum?
Beat him! Hit him!
Your Highness! Over here, Your Highness!
Your Highness, we prepared these gifts for you. Please accept them.
That's right, Your Highness.
It's a token of our appreciation. Please accept them.
Sister, just accept them.
They're giving your gifts out of their kind intention.
That's right. Please accept these gifts.
Brother, don't take this to heart.
They're only...
Sister, you gave out congee to the hungry.
It's only natural that they're grateful.
I just provided some rice and grains.
You and Zhuohua were the ones who tirelessly worked for disaster relief.
I truly feel undeserving.
Sister, I beg to differ.
We've both done it for the country and the people.
Official Mu.
You must be elated to see the people being this happy. Right?
The people of Yongding County have successfully overcome the disaster.
The greedy and corrupt Zhuang Wenfeng has been caught.
What could be more gratifying than this?
It is indeed a joyful occasion that Yongding County is back on track.
But...
What is it, Brother Shen?
Earlier, the First Prince instructed me to investigate Zhuang Wenfeng's background.
Care to guess how he obtained his official position?
Brother Shen, stop the suspense.
He's the assistant of Imperial Censor, Zhuang Zixian's nephew.
His father was a high-ranking official.
After his father's death, he was granted this position through connections.
Despite his mediocrity, he secured a good job position.
I'm afraid apprehending Zhuang Wenfeng may not be an end,
but a beginning.
It doesn't matter.
We'll face whatever comes our way.
After all, anything and everything that begins has to come to an end.
Official Mu, you're right.
My son has been taken to the capital.
You useless fool! What do I need you for?
If anything happens to my son,
you can just be prepared to be buried with him!
Mother-in-law, please calm down.
Mu Zhuohua may have Lord Ding as her support,
but I know her secret.
You?
Mother-in-law, Mu Zhuohua is the Zhuang family's runaway concubine.
We even exchanged an engagement letter before.
How can she deserve an official position after she's done such an improper thing?
Why? Why does she get her way?
How could she throw her weight around and make me utterly miserable?
I... I'm going to make her pay.
What are you planning to do?
I will go to the capital and strike the Dengwen Drum.
I'm going to sue Mu Zhuohua!
Juli!
Young Lady! Young Lady!
Young Lady, you're finally back. I missed you so much.
I missed you too. It's my fault.
Next time, I'll never leave you alone at home for so long again.
Young Lady, this is...
It's my mother's ashes.
I brought them back.
Third Madam, Young Lady has finally brought you back.
This place will be our home from now on.
Our days will get better and better.
That's for sure. Our days must get better and better.
Young Lady, you must be exhausted. Hurry inside and get some rest.
- I'll go and carry the luggage.
- Okay, go ahead.
Mother, can you see this?
You're home now.
I've brought you home.
Qi, this is my home.
Look at this apricot tree.
Isn't it beautiful?
In spring, it's full of apricot blossoms on its branches.
In summer, red apricots adorn its tips.
Earlier, I had someone choose an auspicious time for her burial.
I also picked a burial site with excellent feng shui.
Tomorrow, I'll accompany you to put your mother to rest in peace.
Thank you, My Lord.
My mother was trapped in the Mu Residence
for most of her life.
She always wanted to break free from destiny.
But in the end,
she couldn't escape it even after she traded her life.
Now, it was you who helped her overcome her fate.
Mother, you were right.
You said that if a woman studies, there will be a way out for her.
Zhimo? It's really you.
I'm back.
You're finally back.
Why didn't you tell me before you left?
By the way, where did you go?
Have you eaten?
You... You're not injured. Right?
I didn't have time to tell you.
We went to Jiangnan.
I haven't eaten.
I'm not injured.
Luckily, you came back safe and sound.
You have delicious snacks.
By the way, why don't you have one?
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Hey?
I thought you didn't like sweet things.
It's fortunate that you've reconciled with Lord Ding.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to enjoy such delicious pig's trotters again.
Try the chicken wings.
Look at you.
A few mouthfuls of food and you're taking his side.
Young Lady, why are you judging me when you're the same?
A few mouthfuls of food and you're staying next door for the meal.
I even made so much delicious food waiting for you here.
Lord Ding saved my life.
I couldn't bring myself to reject him when he invited me for dinner.
Young Lady, are you injured? Are your injuries serious?
I'm fine, no need to worry.
It was Lord Ding who got seriously injured while trying to save me.
You scared me half to death.
Eat slowly.
By the way, Young Lady, Lord Ding sure has a streak of bad luck.
First, he got injured in Jiangnan while saving you.
Now, someone filed a complaint against him in the capital.
A complaint? What do you mean?
I'm not too sure.
Zhimo told me.
It seems Lord Ding left the capital without permission.
Many people went to His Majesty to complain about him.
He was impeached because he left the capital without permission?
Yes, that's the word Zhimo used.
These gossipmongers. They sure have nothing better to do.
Are they the only ones who can complain?
Tomorrow morning, I'll seek an audience with His Majesty
and put this false accusation to an end.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Official Mu, what brings you here today?
Your Majesty, I know you're busy,
and I shouldn't trouble you.
But something has been bothering me.
Thus, I felt compelled to see you.
What's bothering you?
I've heard...
about the recent accusations against Lord Ding for leaving the capital.
Some even claim he's arrogant and disrespectful due to his accomplishments.
It's just as you've said.
Almost accurate.
So what are your thoughts on this matter, Official Mu?
I believe these memorials are full of nonsense.
Oh?
Why do you say that?
Your Majesty, you and Lord Ding are biological brothers.
Who could understand Lord Ding's character better than you?
To Your Majesty, his loyalty and sincerity are unmatched.
To his nephew, his care and guidance are wholehearted.
Even toward his subordinates, he's fair and understanding, setting a positive example.
You've always shown great approval toward Lord Ding.
Yet, these individuals are spreading malicious words,
trying to incite discord between Your Majesty and His Lordship's brotherly affection.
So do you have any idea why they would dare to slander him?
They criticize and defame him only because they fear and envy him.
It's exactly as you said.
I know Lord Ding's character and personality very well.
That's why I've already rejected all these impeachments made against him.
Your Majesty is indeed wise.
If I knew, I...
I would...
Your willingness to do so is truly rare and admirable.
If Lord Ding knew, he would be very pleased.
Your Majesty, I shall take my leave, then.
Someone has struck the Dengwen Drum?
Dengwen Drum?
How many grievances did one endure to willingly bear 30 floggings to strike the drum?
Hurry up and see who's striking the drum and what grievance to address.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Do you know you have to receive 30 floggings before meeting His Majesty after you strike this drum?
I know.
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
- Thirteen!
&lt;- What?
She would rather endure 30 floggings just to accuse me?
What is she up to?
Official Mu, you just returned from Jiangnan and can't even rest peacefully.
But now, His Majesty has summoned you.
Official Mu,  please come with me.
Miss Eighth... She... How could she accuse us when she's the evildoer?
Young Lady, what should we do now?
What should we do?
Just change into the court attire. I will go to the Xuanzheng Palace and confront her head-on.
I respectfully greet Your Majesty.
Who is kneeling?
What grievance do you wish to report?
I'm Madam Mu, wife of Zhuang Wenfeng, Yongding County's county magistrate.
I want to accuse someone.
This person is guilty of embezzlement, abusing power,
condoning acts of violence, oppressing innocent people, and committing all kinds of evil deeds!
Zhuang Wenfeng?
Zhuang Zixian.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Who is this Zhuang Wenfeng to you?
Your Majesty, Zhuang Wenfeng is my nephew.
Your Majesty, as Madam Mu stated, my nephew is innocent.
Now, Madam Mu struck the Dengwen Drum
to seek justice for her husband.
Madam Mu, you're now at Xuanzheng Palace.
Please speak sensibly before me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'm risking my life today to seek justice!
The people I want to accuse today...
are County Magistrate Zhuang Wenfeng and Imperial Censor Zhuang Zixian!
You!
What nonsense are you spouting?
Insolence!
How dare you behave insolently in the presence of His Majesty?
Madam Mu, Zhuang Wenfeng and Zhuang Zixian are appointed officials of the court.
Do you have evidence to accuse them?
I do!
This ledger contains records of Zhuang Wenfeng's bribery and corruption in Yongding County.
Other than this, he colluded with wealthy merchants, released counterfeited currency,
destroyed families, seized land, committed murder and arson.
No, no, no! Your Majesty, Zhuang Wenfeng is just my nephew.
I did not know of this matter.
I'm innocent!
This ledger also records Zhuang Wenfeng's accumulation of wealth in Yongding County for Zhuang Zixian.
If it weren't for Lord Ding and Official Mu handling it impartially,
I couldn't have brought this ledger here.
Your Majesty, please investigate this thoroughly.
Your... Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Take Madam Mu to the Imperial Academy of Medicine for treatment.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Guards!
Your Majesty, I...
I'm innocent, Your Majesty.
Zhuang Wenfeng and Zhuang Zixian are guilty of embezzlement and corruption.
From this day on, imprison him and the Ministry of Justice shall take over this case.
He shall be executed on an appointed day!
Those who assisted his wrongdoing shall be executed.
The others shall be sent into exile.
Madam Mu, wife of Zhuang Wenfeng, who stood up for justice by accusing him shall be pardoned.
She shall be rewarded thousands of taels of silver and erect a monument of loyalty and righteousness.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, I'm innocent!
What are you doing?
Your Majesty! Your Majesty! I'm innocent!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty is wise.
Your Majesty is wise!
Official Shen.
The First Prince told me that Mu Zhuohua, the administrator of the Ministry of Rites,
and Shen Jinghong, the Director of the Ministry of Revenue,
have selflessly served the people and shared the country's worries.
It was sure a painstaking effort.
Mu Zhuohua, the administrator of the Ministry of Rites, who has shown loyalty to the ruler and compassion for the people
and thoroughly investigated corruption, is hereby promoted to the Director of the Ministry of Revenue.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
As for Shen Jinghong,
you will go to the Ministry of Personnel and be promoted to the director there.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Also, Princess Roujia has contributed to disaster relief and aided the afflicted.
I shall reward her generously.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
I shall take my leave now.
Man'er, convert these rewards into rice and supplies
for those in need at Jishan Hall.
Yes, Your Highness.
Is there anything, Father?
Everyone received rewards, except you.
You must be displeased.
Well...
I am indeed slightly disappointed.
Chen'er,
you didn't receive any rewards because those were your duties.
What you should see aren't those rewards
but the people of the country.
I shall remember your guidance in my heart.
My Lord, thank you for what you did at Xuanzheng Palace.
Consider it as your repayment for defending me in front of His Majesty.
So you found out what I told His Majesty.
But you earned your promotion.
It was not because of me.
But I'm thanking you not just because you helped me get promoted.
But also for not letting my eighth sister be flogged again.
My Lord, my eighth sister is currently recovering.
Can I go and visit her?
There's nothing you can't do as long as I'm in charge.
But...
did you and your sister plot this together beforehand?
You sure have deep familial affection.
My eighth sister is smart.
You want me to risk my life for merely one thousand guan?
No way.
What if you could obtain something worth more than 3,000 guan?
What do you mean?
Free of worries for the rest of your life.
And you're capable of that?
I'm not.
But His Majesty is.
Are you saying...
All right.
I'll do what you say.
My Lord, will you blame me for not telling you about this?
You don't need to tell me everything.
You have your freedom.
Thank you for your guidance, My Lord.
I will fulfill my duties and not disappoint His Majesty.
You're an official of the Department of State Affairs,
so I naturally must advise you.
If you ever have doubts in the future, you can always come to me for guidance.
Yes, I understand.
This medicine can relieve pain.
So,
why did you help me?
Did I help you?
If you didn't accuse me, I wouldn't be at Xuanzheng Palace.
If I didn't go there, how would I receive His Majesty's rewards?
You're silly.
You could have handed the ledger to the Ministry of Justice.
Why did you have to strike the Dengwen Drum?
If I didn't do that, how could I see His Majesty?
Fair enough.
His Majesty rewarded you with thousands of taels of silver,
a mansion in Jiangnan,
and a monument
With this monument protecting you,
no one will dare...
to mistreat you again in the future.
Really?
That's great.
Great.
It's great.
Eighth Sister.
In the future, you won't need to rely on others for a living anymore.
After we bid farewell today,
I wish you well.
What's wrong?
I have something...
I didn't tell you all this while.
What is it?
When I was a child,
I had a Chausie cat.
It was white and fluffy,
and quite adorable.
I liked it a lot.
But as you know,
whenever Father encounters a cat, his tears will flow profusely.
So no one in the Mu Residence ever kept a cat.
Later, someone told him about the cat.
Father was furious.
And I was terrified.
What happened after that?
After that,
Madam said to kill the cat.
I didn't let them.
After that, she said I must get rid of the cat.
I held it and cried for a long time.
In the end,
I left it in your courtyard.
So it was really you who left the cat there.
You knew?
The cat was clean and white.
It must have been someone's pet.
It was clearly not a stray.
But because of that, Father almost threw you out of the house.
You didn't deny it either.
But it's as expected.
I took a bet that you wouldn't deny it.
That's why I chose to leave the cat in your courtyard.
I hope you don't think that I think you were kind.
I think you were silly.
A complete fool.
I didn't bother because I knew you wanted to keep the cat alive.
It's not because I'm a pushover.
What happened to the cat after that?
I didn't see you raising it.
I gave it to my teacher.
Taking care of it was too troublesome. I'm not so fond of cats anyway.
As long as it's alive.
You're the foolish one.
That cat has long since passed away peacefully.
I'm not a fool.
You're the fool.
Seventh Sister...
Thank you.
♫  I can't forget the love that is still is nipping at my ears and temples  ♫
♫  Memories keep slamming into rocks and have nowhere to berth  ♫
♫  Both sides gaze at each other in the drizzling rain, but one has turned into clouds and mist  ♫
♫  Leaving the isolated heart's island, like waves without a shore  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously love is locked and entwined in our eyes  ♫
♫  For a hug, we burn for a lifetime  ♫
♫  Thousands of sails have been used to search for you  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously willing to swear life and death
to be entangled for a lifetime  ♫
♫  For a moment of heartbeat, paying homage to Heaven  ♫
♫  Never parting ways, we made this promise long ago  ♫
♫  I can't forget the turmoil of love and hate,
even if the next day is far away  ♫
♫  Two souls embrace in chaos, how can it be written off?  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously love is locked and entwined in our eyes  ♫
♫  For a hug, we burn for a lifetime  ♫
♫  Thousands of sails have been used to search for you  ♫
♫  Obviously you know, obviously I understand  ♫
♫  Obviously can't be erased, and haunted by lingering dreams  ♫
♫  For a moment of heartbeat, paying homage to Heaven  ♫
♫  Want to have one more glimpse of you,
even just for a second more  ♫