[Life is a Choice]
You kindly saved him.
Why did he hit you?
Well, in the service industry,
the customer is always right.
Besides, he was drunk.
It was understandable.
Huanan, can you quit this job?
How could I?
With just the salary from my day job,
it'll take ages before I can marry you.
It's fine.
I'm already exhausted from work during the day.
When I get home, I just want to lie down.
And yet you still have to do designated driving.
No, that's too tiring.
It's not tiring. I'm a man, after all.
Isn't it normal for me to work hard?
Besides, a lot of men nowadays
work a full-time job during the day
and take on side jobs at night to make extra money.
[Episode 18]
As long as my wife is happy,
a little hardship is worth it.
[I'm Going to Marry You]
How about this?
I'll make money with you.
I'll do designated driving too.
No, that won't do.
If your mom finds out
her precious daughter is going through such a hardship,
she'll definitely look down on me even more.
Isn't she just looking down on you
because of your job and low income?
I'll be just like you.
Let's see what she'll say then.
Don't go against your mom.
This was my fault.
I was too impulsive.
I shouldn't have let my love for you
and my desire to protect you
make me overlook the reality,
right?
You're always speaking up for her.
She's never said a single nice word about you.
Well, it was the first time your mom met me.
It's normal that she doesn't know me well.
And not everyone
is as lucky as us.
We've managed to get back together
and love each other without caring about material conditions.
How many people would envy us?
Let me tell you, Nian,
there are so many people who hold the belief
that poor couples are miserable.
But I'm determined to prove them wrong.
You've worked hard today.
Here, this is for you.
Boost some dopamine that makes people happy.
You bought me a cake?
It's so cute.
[The Gu Family's Important Day]
It must taste great.
I'm glad you like it.
Why did you waste money on this cake?
Well, I work so hard to earn money
just to make you happy.
You must be tired, Huanan.
I'm not that tired.
It's just that sometimes,
when I'm tired,
missing you so much makes it really hard to bear.
Nian,
trust me.
The hardship now is only temporary.
I will definitely find a suitable job.
But you, don't overwork yourself.
We're not in the same company anymore,
so I can't always take care of you.
You'll probably have to take care of yourself.
And, in the coming period,
I might be quite busy.
We won't be able to see each other like we do now.
Don't worry, I'll work twice as hard.
I believe that one day,
I'll make your mom approve of me.
I'm afraid that I'm destined
not to see that day come.
Even if that's the case,
I'll crawl my way through
to marry you.
Anyway, I won't let you suffer like this.
What are you planning to do?
Don't worry about it, okay?
Godmother.
Su, why are you here?
I'm here to accompany you to visit Godfather.
How did you know
today is Gu's death anniversary?
Gu Nian told me.
We're really busy today,
and she couldn't leave, so she sent me instead.
Godmother.
I'll ride in your car later.
I came here on my motorcycle today.
Then let's take your motorcycle.
You want to go there by motorcycle?
Let me tell you,
Gu Nian's classmates and friends
have all ridden on her motorcycle.
She's never let me ride with her.
What I want is for us
both to have our own motorcycles
and ride together.
Alright.
Then you should get a motorcycle driver's license. I'll teach you.
[Yin]
Mr. Liu,
please have some water to calm down.
Su Yin, why are you so late?
I'm waiting for your explanation.
I'm sorry, Mr. Liu.
This is indeed my fault.
I'll take responsibility for all the consequences.
You'll take responsibility?
How are you going to take responsibility?
Mr. Li has always been a very punctual person.
Don't you know that?
You were late for nearly an hour.
Do you think he would wait for you?
Who do you think you are?
Today is the first test of the Revisit Project.
Such an important matter,
and you were actually late?
I trusted you so much before.
I even entrusted the whole project team to you.
And what did you do?
You were late at a critical moment.
You've really disappointed me.
Mr. Liu, please be careful.
Jiang,
why didn't you give the speech on my behalf first?
You could've at least bought me some time.
I did.
I've been slowing the speech down.
The problem is I couldn't hold on anymore.
Mr. Li was watching his watch,
sighing,
and listening to me.
He wanted to hear it from you,
not from me.
Come on, where did you go?
Today...
is my dad's death anniversary.
Anyway, you need to think about how to make up for it.
Mom, where is the household registration book?
It's in the drawer.
I've been looking for it in there, but I couldn't find it.
Where else could it be?
It's always been there.
You didn't hide it, did you?
Why would I hide it?
Well, only you and I know
where the household registration book is.
If it's not you,
could it be me?
What do you need the household registration book for?
I need it for something.
Are you looking for the household registration book
to register your marriage with Feng?
Yes.
Nian,
do you know what today is?
Today is your dad's death anniversary.
And you're actually thinking of getting married?
What? Didn't I set a reminder
on my phone of my dad's death anniversary?
Why didn't it remind me?
Do you need a phone reminder of your dad's death anniversary?
Your head is full of Feng Huanan.
Do you even have room for your father in your heart anymore?
Mom, don't say that.
I know it's my fault about Dad.
I'll go apologize to him tomorrow.
But, can you please give me the household registration book first?
I'm telling you, the household registration book isn't with me.
Even if it were,
I wouldn't give it to you.
Why wouldn't you give it to me?
Even the law states marriage is a free choice.
Why wouldn't I give it to you?
Because I'm your mother.
I don't want to stand by and watch you make a mistake!
Yes.
You are my mother.
But I'm not your puppet.
Since I was a child,
whenever I skateboarded or rode motorcycles,
you said I was irresponsible.
When I grew up and started looking for a job,
you wanted to arrange one for me.
When I have someone I like,
you want to stop me from being with him.
Only when I live the way you want me to,
am I considered the good
and obedient child.
I know it.
I know these years have been tough for you.
I've been compromising myself to please you,
just so you wouldn't be upset.
But you can't just think about yourself
and not care about my life, right?
What did you say?
All these years, you've been pretending to be happy
just to please me?
Yes.
I've been pretending to be happy.
But now, I don't want to pretend anymore.
And I can't keep pretending any longer.
Nian, do you know what you just said?
I know exactly what I said.
Because you've never understood the real me.
Why do I like Feng Huanan?
Because in front of him, I don't have to pretend,
and I don't have to be so perfect.
The love he gives me is equal.
Mom,
I've never felt unconditional love
from you,
nor have I ever been my true self!
No matter what you say,
even if you don't give me the household registration book,
I will still get married.
I want you to know
that we won't be defeated by reality,
and that my life
will no longer be controlled by anyone.
Gu Nian!
Gu Nian.
Mom? Mom!
Mom, hang in there.
I'll call Gu Nian and ask her to come back.
Don't call her.
I don't want to see her.
Okay.
Get up first.
Come on.
Let's go to the hospital first.
Ambulance!
Lin Xi.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
I've already asked the attending doctor.
It's a mild cerebrovascular blockage.
They've already done thrombolysis treatment.
She's temporarily out of danger now.
Aunt Dai has woken up.
The treatment was timely,
so there shouldn't be any serious long-term effects.
But the MRI shows that
there are still several areas in her blood vessels that are narrowed.
Lin Xi, you must help me
find the most authoritative doctor in this field.
Money is no object.
We must cure my mother.
You don't need to tell me that.
She's not only your mother;
she's also my Aunt Dai.
Don't worry, I'll do my best.
Come on, let's sit down and talk.
Try to relax a bit.
What about that Gu Nian?
Why didn't I see her?
My mom said she didn't want to see her
and told me not to contact her.
Wait, what exactly did she do
to make Aunt Dai so angry?
When I see her, I'll slap her.
Back then, I made my mom this angry too.
Xi,
why don't you slap me as well?
Consider it waking up my past self.
I'm really going to do it.
I'm gonna slap your face.
Mom.
Godmother.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
Su,
thank you.
You saved my life.
No need to thank me.
You're my godmother.
A godmother is just like a mother.
The doctor said
it's a mild cerebrovascular blockage.
As long as you stay in a good mood
and cooperate with the treatment,
you'll recover soon.
You're more worried about me than Nian.
You didn't tell her, did you?
No.
You said you didn't want to see her,
so I didn't contact her.
I'm afraid she'll upset you again.
You
are a good child.
If only Nian
were half as sensible
as you.
I used to make mistakes too
and often argued with my mom.
I'm not a good child.
Su,
was it you who helped me with the admission?
Nian wasn't here,
and you didn't have my personal information.
How did you handle the admission procedures?
It was... it was Lin Xi.
Gu Nian introduced me to Lin Xi before.
Lin Xi has been helping you
schedule your physical exams.
She has your personal information.
Su,
you didn't tell me the truth.
Nian even forgot her dad's death anniversary.
She wouldn't have asked you to pick me up.
Tell me the truth.
How did you know about
Nian's dad's death anniversary?
And how did you know
the exact location of the cemetery?
Gu Nian, you're really disappointing.
Su,
help me sit up a bit.
Sure.
Su,
why do I feel like
you're so familiar?
Nian said...
you came from somewhere else.
What exactly does that mean?
Godmother, how should I explain this to you?
Do you believe there might be
multiple dimensions in this world?
That people who have disappeared
might return through some sort of medium,
from another space?
They could come back as a tree,
a cat,
a speck of dust...
or even a person—
someone you wouldn't expect.
Gu, is that you?
I'm not him. I'm not Gu.
I am...
I must be out of my mind from being upset with Nian.
How could you possibly be Gu?
You can't be Gu.
Gu couldn't possibly be as young as you.
I'm not Gu.
It could be someone else.
Someone...
who's also very close to you.
The person closest to me,
besides Gu, is Nian.
It couldn't be Nian.
There's no way there could be two Nians to make me mad.
You can't be Gu.
Gu would never come back
and disappear again.
He wouldn't bear to make me suffer again.
No matter who you are,
you're like my child.
Oh, right.
Godmother,
the doctor told me to take off this bracelet
during the emergency treatment earlier.
I'm returning it to you.
It was a gift from Nian
on my birthday.
At that time,
it was her first competition,
and she won first place.
With the prize money,
she bought this for me.
I've been wearing it for two years,
and never had the heart to take it off.
You call me godmother,
but I've never bought you a gift.
Here.
I'm giving it to you.
Consider this my welcoming gift to you,
and also a token of the bond between us
as mother and son.
Godmother, I'm going to the restroom.
Su Yin!
Come here.
You came at just the right time.
I was about to catch you.
Give me the household registration book.
What are you talking about?
You're still playing dumb with me, huh?
Only my mom and I know where it is.
If it's not you, who else could it be?
But I still won't give it to you.
I can't stand by and watch you make a mistake.
Su Yin, don't you think you're being ridiculous?
You think that if you take the household registration book,
you can stop me?
Let me tell you,
no matter how many times you come back,
as long as Feng Huanan is still Feng Huanan,
I'll still like him.
You can't change that,
and you can't stop it.
Because you're not the current me.
You can't change how I feel.
Seeing you now,
I realize how awful I must have been back then.
I really want to slap you.
Come on, go ahead. Slap me.
There's something I didn't tell you.
Mom's in the hospital.
It was all because of you.
What are you talking about?
Mom is in good health.
Take a look for yourself.
Nian,
you finally want to see me.
Godmother, you're so weak.
Why don't we just not record?
Let's record it.
I don't want to see her right now,
but I don't want her to worry either.
What if, when she comes to her senses,
she wants to see me
and finds out I'm still in the hospital?
She'll just worry.
Let's just record this video.
When she remembers to video call me,
just tell her I'm busy
and send her this video.
Aren't I quite clever?
Yes, quite clever.
Well,
are you ready?
Godmother, let's do it. Come on.
Wait a moment.
Alright, let's do it.
Let's start recording.
Nian,
you finally want to see Mom.
I'm quite busy right now
and don't have time to take your video call.
You
can just do whatever you want.
I can't always keep an eye on you.
As long as you
don't do anything out of line, that's fine.
That's it.
I'm going to get back to work.
Alright.
How was it?
Why are you crying?
I already told you
that I'm making this up for Nian.
Maybe by the time she comes looking for me,
I'll have been discharged,
and this video
will be useless then.
It's just a backup.
When you have time,
help me edit it.
And add a little
beauty filter for me.
Don't let her see how haggard I look.
When did this happen?
Just last night.
Then why didn't you call me right away?
You blocked me.
How was I supposed to call you?
Let's go and find Mom now.
Hurry up.
The room on the left.
Mom.
Godmother.
Why are you here?
Have a seat first.
Su,
didn't I tell you
not to tell Nian?
I'm sorry, Godmother.
I didn't keep my promise to you.
Sit down.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were sick.
And I made you angry like that.
It's alright, it's alright.
Why are you crying?
I'm fine, aren't I?
You should scold me.
Or you can hit me.
Why should I scold you?
You didn't make any big mistakes.
Isn't it all because
I made you so angry last night that you got sick?
That's not a big mistake.
Alright, alright.
Life's long.
There will be plenty of days for you to make me angry in the future.
Stop crying.
Godmother, I went back and taught her a good lesson for you.
I got back at her for you.
You
are becoming more and more like an older brother now.
And you're starting to be
more like one of our Gu family's children.
Mom, I really didn't mean to upset you.
I just lost my temper for a moment.
Alright, alright.
I know.
I know what my own kid
is like.
Mom,
about me marrying Huanan,
let's put that aside for now.
Let's focus on your health first
and get you better, okay?
Why should we put it aside?
Just because I'm sick?
Doesn't that feel like emotional blackmail?
I'm not that kind of person.
Nian, tell me the truth.
Whether I'm sick or not,
even if I become a vegetable,
would you still like him
and want to be with him?
You must be honest with me.
Don't lie to me.
Mom,
I really like Huanan,
but I'm afraid of making you angry.
Then do what you want.
I won't stop you.
Mom.
I'm not saying this out of anger.
I'm being honest.
Since you like him no matter what,
what's the point of me stopping you?
I almost
didn't make it.
Some things,
I've come to terms with.
If at that time,
I hadn't made it,
maybe you two would still end up together anyway.
So, since that's the case,
you should do what you want.
I won't be the bad guy here.
Godmother.
Mom, why did you say things like that?
However, let me be clear upfront.
No matter what kind of ceremony
you two have in the future,
don't ask me to take charge of it.
I'm already too busy with my own affairs.
As for your own affairs,
you'll have to figure them out yourselves.
Once everything is ready, just let me know.
Su,
you've always
been so good to me and Nian.
I really appreciate it.
As for Nian's matters,
I won't trouble you with them anymore.
Let her decide for herself.
Mom,
are you saying this
because you still haven't truly accepted us being together?
Nian,
I've already made the biggest concession I can.
You can't ask me to try harder, can you?
Got it.
Alright, I've said everything
I needed to say.
You should be going now, shouldn't you?
Don't let this interfere with your work.
Mom, I'm not leaving.
I want to stay here with you.
Director Su,
I'd like to take a few days off.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you afraid of getting fired?
Hurry up and leave. Otherwise, I'll chase you out.
I'm not leaving, Mom.
I'll see you two off to the door.
No, no, no.
Godmother.
Be careful, Mom.
I'm fine.
Be careful.
I'll let you see.
Get in the car.
I'll take care of Aunt Dai.
Just go.
Mom, I'm leaving then.
I'm really leaving.
Go.
Just go.
Go now.
Godmother, I'm leaving.
Mom, I'm really leaving.
Get in the car.
Go.
Mom, remember to call me.
Su.
Aunt Dai, let's go back.
Su,
give the household registration book to Nian.
Thank you for everything you've done for us.
Here.
Mom asked me to give it to you.
I'm following Mom's instructions.
This is the biggest concession I can make.
Gu Nian,
from now on, we won't interfere with you and Feng Huanan anymore.
But there are some things you must keep in mind.
What things?
The Revisit Project.
We made a mistake, so we should fix it as soon as possible.
What should we do?
I heard that Mr. Li is very angry.
Being upfront and honest
is the best way to show sincerity.
Mr. Li is someone who values relationships.
He will understand.
But I'm warning you,
before you see Feng Huanan,
make sure to handle this matter first.
I see.
Feng Huanan!
Come on, Nian.
Why are you here?
Was it fun?
Invisible?
Are you a ninja?
Quick, pull me out.
Alright, I'll get you out.
Come on.
Let me take a look.
Let me give it a try.
How is it?
You haven't even gotten in.
I feel like my chest
still hasn't gotten in.
That's right.
I... I can't move now.
I can't move at all.
You're just too cute.
Nian.
Why did you call me over
so urgently?
I'm still running orders.
I placed your next order.
Stop kidding.
You don't even have a car. Why did you place an order?
It's our order.
Huanan,
my mom agreed.
Let's get married!
Really?
I...
Is it true, Nian?
It's true.
You must reschedule the wedding date.
Mom has already agreed.
Do you have a problem with that?