[English subtitles are available]
What are you going to do now?
You know me. An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
Hey, what are you doing?
[Hello?]
Hello, my name is Type.
I'm Tharn's boyfriend.
I have something to tell you.
You jerk!
That coward hung up on me.
Don't tell me you called him.
Yes, Tharn's ex-boyfriend.
He made me look like a bad guy that wanted to kill him.
No.
What?
You said
that he goes to the same school as Nic, right?
Don't tell me you're...
Yes, I'm going to find him.
Gosh.
Is there no other way, Type?
No.
Just wait and see.
[TharnType]
Calm down.
He's here.
You're fast.
Any news?
Calm down, Brother No.
You only give me one night.
It's not like we only have one or two students in my class.
So you didn't find anything?
I did.
But what are you going to give me in exchange?
I...
Are these all the students from your class?
Yes, brother.
You were going to negotiate with me,
but you just gave it to him the next second?
It depends.
I know who I can negotiate with and who I can't.
-I'd give up
-What is it?
if it's Brother Type.
Are you saying that I'm stupid?
Oh, so you knew it?
I found him.
Where?
This kid.
He's my classmate in French class.
I met him several times.
He's famous because he's handsome.
You're done now, right?
I'm going to school, then.
Wait.
Do me another favor.
Is it him?
Yes.
He's so tall.
Hey.
Isn't this bullying?
What bullying? When did I bully him?
Yeah, you didn't.
But there are three of us.
We're outnumbered.
Look at you now. You look like you would kill.
Speaking of look, I've been wanting to tell you this long ago.
What?
Your brother is so good-looking.
And?
-How come the older brother is so ugly?
-You jerk.
You ask me to relax, don't you?
Please keep being nervous, then.
Brother Type, that's Tar.
Bring him here.
Are you Tar?
Calm down.
Type.
Didn't you say my brother is here?
You're Tar, right?
-Yes.
-I'm Type.
Where are you going in a hurry?
Don't you want to talk to me first?
Or you only talk to Brother Tharn?
Aren't you going to say anything?
I'll make you break up with Brother Tharn.
What did you say?
Calm down, Type.
Kiddo, your face is pretty,
but not your mouth.
How can you steal someone else's boyfriend?
You're going to break up anyway.
-You jerk.
-Calm down, Type.
-Calm down, please.
-Calm down.
We're in a cafe. It's crowded.
People are going to say that you're bullying the kid.
You too, kid.
Weren't you broke up with Tharn a long time ago?
Why are you ruining others' relationship?
No matter what you say, you will break up in the end.
No matter what,
I will make you break up.
You're finally back.
Where did you go to date your ex-boyfriend again?
I had training today.
Ask Lhong if you don't believe me.
No need, I trust you.
Because I went to your ex-boyfriend just now.
Are you scared?
All I did was meet your Tar.
He doesn't belong to me.
But you belong to him.
Don't you know?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
He told me that you belong to him.
No matter what,
he'll take you away from me.
-Type, you know that...
-I'm not done yet.
Don't interrupt.
That kid...
He said that you still love him.
And he loves you very much too.
He loves you so much that he's willing to be the other man.
Because he didn't want to lose you.
He said
that he has never forgotten you.
He couldn't wait to come back to you.
His cheeks streamed with tears when he said these to me.
I feel so bad for him.
Type.
-I love you.
-Shut up.
When did I ask you to talk?
You know what?
Your ex-boyfriend is very pretentious.
He cried like the world was ending in front of me,
saying that he would take you back.
Does he think he's the heroine of a novel?
He thought I'd give you back just because he cried and begged me.
I won't give up my thing so easily.
I gave him a punch, but it didn't diminish my anger.
Did you hit him?
Why?
Are you worried about him?
Are you blind?
He's a man too.
He won't die just because he was punched.
Calm down, Type.
I'm worried about you.
I don't want you to get into trouble.
You're also a hypocrite.
Just be honest if you're worried about him.
Yes.
That's who I am.
Bad-tempered,
and bad-mouthed.
I never think before I speak.
I'm a jerk who bullies kids.
Is there anyone who would think for me?
Who's going to understand me?
I understand you, Type.
But listen to me first.
I want to explain what happened last night.
Let go of me!
Type.
I love you.
Let go of me!
I love you, Type.
I don't want to hear anything.
It's over.
I told him that you don't belong to him.
But you belong to me.
Don't ever see him again.
You promise?
I promise,
I won't see him again.
Look into my eyes and say it again.
I promise, I only have you.
Trust me, Type.
Okay?
Remember what you said.
Where are you going?
Anywhere. As long as I don't have to see you.
Screw it!
[Bar]
Type.
Don't drink too much.
You've been drunk since evening.
You don't have to stop me.
The reason I'm like this
is because of your damn friend.
Don't be like this.
Just trust Tharn since he says it's nothing, okay?
You want me to trust someone who lied to me?
He probably doesn't want you to feel uncomfortable.
You know him.
He might be thinking from your perspective.
If you knew it, weren't you going to overthink?
Besides, he just went to see Tar.
He didn't make out with him.
No said the same thing as you did.
Why am I so unfortunate that no one is on my side?
That's not what I meant.
What should I do?
If what you said is true,
then it was actually Tar who was in the wrong.
Now only you know it was his fault?
Gosh.
You should understand
that you're totally different from him.
People who don't know you would think that it's your fault for sure.
Who would do that?
Who would beat up an 11th grade kid like this?
Luckily, there was no teacher who saw it,
and no one took a video either.
Otherwise, you're doomed.
Calm down.
The more you act as he planned,
the more you lose.
That's who I am.
I'm a bad person.
At first, he said he could accept all of me.
But in the end, he told me to control my temper.
As Tharn's closest friend,
I know he can accept you as who you are.
Otherwise, he won't give in to you all the time.
But you have to stay calm.
Tar is very cunning.
And I just found it out too.
He looks innocent,
but he's vicious on the inside.
He even said he's going to take his Tharn back.
Have I been deceived?
Tum said his brother was very obedient.
Both you and Tharn were deceived.
But no matter how bad Tar is
or how he cries at Tharn,
as long as my friend ignores him,
things won't go his way.
If Tharn responds to him, I'll break up with him for sure.
Don't worry, he won't do that to you.
He loves you so much.
I hope so.
Take your man back.
Why is he with you?
Because you had a fight.
That's why I tried to advise him.
Type.
Why is he so drunk?
-Type.
-I told you, you two had a fight.
Can't you two talk it out?
Okay, thank you for sending him home.
Type.
You're welcome.
This handsome Lhong is glad to be at your service.
Talk nicely, okay?
I'm leaving.
Lhong.
Well...
Did he say anything to you?
What are you doing?
My boyfriend.
You belong to me, Tharn.
Take care of him first.
He's so cute when he's drunk.
I belong to you, Type.
Thank you for sending him back.
Let's go in.
You're welcome. I'm leaving.
I
belonged to you long ago, Type.
Don't move. I'll make you feel better.
You're so mean. No matter when it is,
you can always make me go crazy for you.
When I saw Lhong holding you,
I was jealous.
You rarely drink. Why would you go with another man?
Even though Lhong is my friend,
I would still be possessive of you.
As for Tar,
you don't have to worry.
Because that child
means nothing to me now.
You're the only one I have, Type.
What are you talking about? You woke me up.
I'm sorry.
Well,
how do you feel?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I yelled at you.
Really?
Yes.
After talking to Lhong, I figured it out.
I have never listened to you.
I was always angry at you in the past.
I don't know why, but I feel wronged.
I feel terrible.
I don't know how to explain my feelings.
You don't have to apologize to me.
I should be the one to apologize.
I won't see Tar again.
Please forgive me.
Tharn.
Hug me.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I think it's true
that people who get drunk always say they're not drunk.
You jerk.
So...
You've forgiven me?
No, not until you give me a hug.
You really love to act cute, don't you?
Please forgive me.
Okay.
Your friend cleared your name.
You have a good friend
Lhong
is my best friend.
If this happens again, I won't let you off.
Okay.
I promise.
You promised me.
You promised.
Tharn, Tharn.
What's wrong, Lhong?
Why are you yelling?
Look at this.
What is this?
At first, I was wondering what this was, like you are.
-Last week.
-Yes?
I uploaded the video you practiced in the band,
and also the video you practiced at Brother Khong's shop.
Someone reached out to us after watching it.
But the message he sent is a little strange.
You don't know unless you try.
Yes.
Let's try and talk to him first.
I'll tell Tae and Song, then.
I think we shouldn't tell them for now.
We should talk to that person first.
I don't want them to have their hopes too high.
Come on. Let's share the joy
and split the disappointment together.
Here.
Well,
do you want me to handle it, or you?
I'll do it.
Send me the number.
Okay.
If I make an appointment with him, we'll go together.
[I'll be home late tonight.]
[I'm going to practice. I'll be late too.]
[What do you want to eat? I'll buy it for you.]
[It's okay, I'll eat with No.]
["Dinner with No" is different from "eat with No".]
Hello?
Where are you?
My car has a flat tyre.
I'm going crazy. I'm running out of time.
I don't know how to change tyres, so I called a mechanic.
But I don't know when the mechanic will be here.
Should I go find you first?
No need.
It's almost time to meet the record label.
Talk to them and buy some time.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Come here asap.
Let go of me!
Brother Tum isn't here.
I said let go!
Let go of me!
Brother Tum isn't here.
I said let go!
What are you doing?
Mind your own business.
Step back.
I bought this kid. He's mine.
Brother Tharn, I didn't sell myself.
What is it? Should I call the security?
What a waste of money.
Are you okay?
He's fine. It's just a misunderstanding.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Brother, I didn't sell myself.
I really didn't.
Get up first.
[Come and see for yourself.]
You want to play it like this, huh?
Type.
Why are you here
at the hotel?
Did Tharn ask you to come?
Yes, he invited me too.
Let's go find him. Let's go.
Are you okay now?
Much better.
I'll call Tum.
Do you hate me that much?
What are you doing?
Tar, didn't you get beaten?
Why did you lie to me?
I was so worried about you, you know?
At least you would still worry about me.
Tar, stop!
Tar, let go of me!
No!
I won't!
I won't let you go again.
I said let go of me!
No!
I'm not letting go!
Tar, if you don't stop,
I'll never see you as my brother anymore.
No!
I won't let go!
Tar.
I have an appointment. Let go of me.
Your date is not going to show up.
What do you mean?
Did you lie to me?
Listen to me first.
I didn't want to lie to you.
But I have no choice.
You have a choice.
But you chose to lie to me.
-Let go of me!
-No.
No.
Brother Tharn.
Listen to me.
This is my only chance to be with you again.
I don't want to lie to you.
Just this once, please.
Tar.
You have no more chance, Tar.
Please let this be the last time. After that, I won't bother you anymore.
Tar!
Don't do this! You're degrading yourself!
I have no choice.
I had no choice a long time ago.
I'm just a playboy now.
I can have sex with anyone.
I'm cheap.
But I love you.
I love you.
I really love you.
Tar, I'm seeing someone.
Then break up. You have to break up no matter what.
You have no choice.
Just like me.
Come out, you jerk!
It's not what you think, Type.
I don't want to believe it.
You misunderstood.
There's nothing between us.
You win. Are you satisfied?
I'm an idiot
to think that Tharn would never cheat on me.
I was stupid.
I thought a man's nature could be changed.
I should have known
that
you'll end up having sex with him.
Let's break up, Tharn.
No, Type.
I won't break up with you.
Please don't say that. I won't break up with you.
I can't stand it anymore, Tharn.
How do you think I feel
to be jealous of my husband all the time?
I'm also tired of this game with your ex.
I've had enough!
Calm down, both of you.
Type!
Anyone could tell that this was the brat's plan.
Don't just blame it on Tharn.
What do you mean?
What plan?
Don't be fooled so easily.
Type.
He's in a fit of anger.
Let him calm down first.
Calm down.
How do you want me to calm down?
He said he wanted to break up with me.
Tell me everything you know.
I only know
that after I got here,
Type was about to take the elevator coming up for you.
He said Tar sent him a message
saying that you still loved him.
If he doesn't believe it, come here to check.
He will prove it.
Tar.
Don't let me see you again.
Tharn.
Brother Tharn.
What are you doing?
I'm moving out of this room.
We've broken up.
Do you want me to be the third wheel
when you bring someone home?
I won't break up with you no matter what.
But I want to.
Type.
I have nothing to do with Tar.
Trust me.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Didn't you know
that it was Tar who asked you out?
Why do you still believe him?
I knew
he set this up.
Then why?
I don't want to hold it in anymore, Tharn.
This time, it was a set-up.
But who knows which of your exes will come
crying to get your sympathy again next time?
It was San before.
Now, your ex is pestering me.
Then who's next?
Do you want me to die of madness?
I didn't do anything, Type.
That's why I'm telling you
that I can't stand it anymore, Tharn.
I don't want to be a clown anymore.
Look at me.
I'm a man.
Is this what you wish me to be like?
I follow you around, get jealous all the time,
and tell everyone that you belong to me.
I'm tired.
Now, I hate myself more and more.
If we're going to break up,
wouldn't it be better if we broke up now?
Let's not get any deeper.
Don't make me lose myself anymore.
Let me go.
Type.
I love you.
Please give me another chance.
Give me another chance.
I promise
that I won't break your heart again.
I won't let you cry again.
Don't leave me.
Don't break up with me.
Don't do this.
Don't make me give up everything.
Type.
I'll eat spicy food.
I'll eat raw food.
I won't be picky anymore.
I'll wake up early and wake you up.
I'll learn to cook.
I'll cook for you.
Can you not leave me behind?
Can you not break up with me?
Everything I've done,
I did it for you, Tharn.
♫I've now made the decision♫
♫Now I'll make you♫
♫My last lover♫
♫The person who stays with me all the time♫
♫I will not make you sad♫
♫Can you hear my words, baby?♫
♫If the world collapses, please remember♫
♫My love for you will never change, you can rest assured♫
♫We will walk side by side♫
♫As long as you always love me♫
♫Please don't let go of my hand♫
Type.
What happened?
Why did you come out with your bag?
I broke up with him.
How can I stay here any longer?
Hey, calm down.
You're in a fit of anger right now.
If you give it a thought,
you might forgive him.
No.
Sooner or later,
I'm going to break up with him.
So, maybe it is better
to break up with him now.
In case I don't want to let go of his hand later.
What happened to Tharn?
I don't know.
Please take care of him.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
If you've made up your mind,
I'll take care of him.
You idiots!
[I did as you said.]
[Give those videos back to me.]
Okay.
I'll send you the original file.
Thank you for your hard work.
[Brother Tharn will never be interested in you.]
What are you talking about?
[I know who you are.]
[You've been silent for a year.]
[But I know it was you.]
[Lhong.]
[No matter how hard you try,]
[Brother Tharn won't like you.]
Do you think you have a chance, then?
Will he fall for someone
who causes him to break up with the person he loves the most?
Not to mention
that 'someone'
was having sex with 3 men at the same time.
[You sent them to rape me.]
[Go to hell, you jerk!]
I won't die so easily,
unlike you.
Even if you cry to death,
Tharn won't come back to you.
Keep that in mind.
Brother Tum.
Brother Tharn.
I'm sorry.
Tar!
Tar, what happened?
Are you okay?
What happened, Tar?
What's going on inside?
Tar.
Open the door!
Tell me if you need anything.
Why don't you tell me anything?
Can't I help you?
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who never left him behind.
I'm the one who never betrayed him.
[Photos]