=Return of Fated Love=
=Episode 19=
Add another one percent of mine.
Then we can dispose of you at will.
Zhou Chuming.
Mr. Zhou, Mrs. Yu,
if neither of you have any objections,
then from today onwards,
the Group will relieve you of your duties.
The New President will take office soon.
After you hand it over,
you can leave the Group.
Grandfather left me with the share
so that I can have some money
and wouldn't be driven away.
I didn't expect it to be so useful.
Zhou Chuming,
are you also surprised?
Zhou Yang,
let's have a chat.
It feels good.
No wonder someone
strived to reach this position
regardless of his brother's life.
Zhou Yang, what do you mean?
What do I mean?
Zhou Chuming, do you think this position
should be yours?
Don't forget that
grandfather has more than one son.
My Dad is also one of the Heirs.
Moreover, he is the eldest son.
He should be more qualified
to inherit than your Dad.
What happened over a decade ago was secretive.
Not many people knew about it.
Most of the people involved
have passed away.
We are even less likely to know.
Secretive?
If you want to keep it secret,
you must not do it yourself.
Even as time passes,
it can't erase what they did
to my parents,
nor can it cover up the truth.
I don't know how Lin Qingqing
described it
in the information she gave you.
But I hope you remain sane
and tell right from wrong.
Don't become a pawn used by others.
Of course, I won't
completely believe it.
In order not to let a single enemy go,
I followed the information
and investigated further.
Guess what I found out.
After Zhang Sufang got married here,
she was not capable of interfering
with the Group's business.
All the actions taken
against my parents were
done by Zhou Zheng,
your father,
my dear Second Uncle.
- You!
- Chuming.
Business is like a battlefield.
It's all about fighting for
power and profit.
I've seen many cases like this.
I understand.
But Zhou Zheng shouldn't
be so despicable,
slandering my parents,
forcing them to leave the Group
and give up their inheritance rights.
He even wanted to send them to prison.
They were so forced
that they had to abandon me
and commit suicide.
Zhou Chuming.
This is the debt Zhou Zheng owes me.
Since he is gone, father's debt
should be repaid by the son.
I have to collect it from you.
As for Zhang Sufang,
since she wasn't involved
and she's your stepmother,
I can let her off the hook.
Zhou Yang,
there will be a fair judgment on that.
It's not for you to judge
whether my Dad is right or wrong.
But since you want to play,
go ahead.
I'll take it on.
Alright,
you said it.
Zhou Zheng schemed
to take over the Group
and pass it on to you.
Then I'll shatter your dreams
and you will get nothing.
No one should think about
taking this position.
At worst, we'll both be ruined.
Anyway, I have nothing to lose.
But you better think it through.
Can you risk everything
to play the game with me?
Do you dare?
I just installed a small surveillance.
You must have seen
such tricks before, right?
You told me on the phone
that you had a surprise for me.
It is a surprise.
But I don't understand
why you want to work with me.
I was immature before.
And I was resentful of my parents.
I didn't know the whole story.
So I even held a grudge against you.
Luckily, I uncovered the truth.
It was done by Zhou Zheng.
It has nothing to do with you.
So, I apologize to you.
As for the cooperation with you,
I've thought it through carefully.
Tell me, what are your thoughts?
Madam,
I've been observing you all these years.
Please don't be upset yet.
Listen to me.
I discovered
something interesting.
I think
you want to make Zhou Chuming a puppet.
After all, you're still young
and have ideals.
No need to flatter me.
Just say I'm ambitious.
I guess
you want to use Zhou Chuming
to completely control Zhou Group
and even turn it into yours
shortly.
I wonder if my guess is correct.
Grandfather was biased.
He gave everything to
Zhou Zheng and Zhou Chuming.
I don't want to accept this.
So I've competed with him
for everything since childhood,
including Yu Chuxin.
I don't really like her.
I just didn't want
Zhou Chuming to have her.
As for working with you,
it's because you can
make Zhou Chuming lose everything.
He won't get it,
but neither should you think you will.
I'm a person close to death.
Authority, wealth, love.
Why would I need them?
Although I don't agree with
your assumptions about me,
there is something
we can work together.
Mr. Zhou Chuming and Ms. Yu Chuxin
are temporarily
leaving their positions
due to personal reasons.
Effective immediately,
the position of President
will be assumed by Zhou Yang.
The Group will make
an internal announcement shortly.
However, the Board of Directors decided
not to make it public for the time being
to avoid speculation.
In short, I hope everyone will work with
President Zhou Yang
to achieve new heights of success.
(President Zhou Chuming)
President Zhou.
No.
Not President now.
Let me call you brother.
If you're upset, you can show it.
It can harm your health.
Do you think you can
to turn things around?
Let me give you some advice.
Don't be naive.
Today it's just your position.
Tomorrow, you might not even be able to
keep your shares.
How about
you kneel and call me brother?
I'll leave you 1% of the shares
like grandfather did.
It can cover the rest of your life.
Zhou Yang,
do you know
you look like a petty person now?
You're upset?
Bite me.
Come on.
Hit here.
Chuming.
It's time to go.