=Return of Fated Love=
=Episode 2=
Chuming.
Ye,
it's been half a year
since I was confined
in Lin's private sanatorium.
During this time,
my parents have been in a coma.
Zhou Chuming thought
eloped with Zhou Yang,
so no one would report me missing.
The sanatorium is under
the absolute control of Lin Qingqing.
Everyone believed her
and Director Zheng's words.
They thought I was
a mentally broken lunatic.
From an outsider's perspective,
everything happened to me
seemed accidental.
But I know,
all of this is related to Lin Qingqing.
But six months have passed.
Lin Qingqing had enough time
to erase the clues of
her persecution against me
during this period.
So we can't
report her to the police
without evidence.
We'd only alert her.
Even if we uncover some minor details,
it won't subject her to legal sanction.
So what do you plan to do?
Lin's company and Zhou's company
are about to merge.
Lin's Company
is much smaller than Zhou's.
And Zhou Chuming holds the largest share
of Zhou's company.
He is like the future lion king
in a pride of lions.
Although he hasn't taken power,
he's the focal point of
many people's competition.
In this situation,
Lin Qingqing and Zhang Sufang
will naturally get nervous.
If I join in
and find reliable partners
to support Zhou Chuming,
they'll tend to mess things up.
We can find more clues
as long as they reveal flaws.
You mean
to cling to Zhou Chuming.
You'll openly compete with them.
But when they are in chaos,
you'll follow the clues
and seize their flaws.
Yes, feint one way
and attack another.
I think it's feasible.
Since
they have schemes against Zhou Chuming,
I'll return to him
and leverage his influence
to find a way to deal with them.
Chuxin.
During the five months you were away,
he's been covering your parents'
medical expenses.
And he secretly sent
quite a few people to find you.
It seems
that he still cares about you.
Does he truly care about me,
or is he just unwilling to
accept my betrayal?
This still needs to be confirmed.
Chuming,
we recited our vows together
to share both hardships and joys.
If we can't stay together until old age,
then…
Chuming.
Chuming,
I've tried on the wedding dress
and I've also picked out your outfit.
Tomorrow,
you'll be the most handsome groom
at the wedding.
(Message alert from Director Zheng)
Miss Lin.
That woman ran away.
It seems someone's dreams
are about to be shattered.
Chuchu,
I just killed a fish.
Stay for dinner.
Yu Chuxin,
how dare you come back?
You must be Qingqing.
I heard from Mom
that you are Chuming's best friend and
you've been managing
a branch company out of town.
Today, you made a special trip back
to attend my wedding with Chuming.
Thank you.
Chuxin, where
have you been for the past six months?
Six months?
I've been working at the company.
Yu Chuxin, I thought
you eloped with Zhou Yang
after you ran away from home
six months ago.
What are you doing back now?
Run away from home?
How could I possibly run away from home?
Zhou Yang?
The patient seems to have suffered
a mental stimulation,
selectively forgetting memories
from the past six months.
And her mental state
is currently precarious.
She should rest in a good environment.
She can't suffer any more stress.
Alright, I understand.
I'll leave first.
Amnesia?
She might be dumped by Zhou Yang
and was affected.
Then let's find Zhou Yang
and have him take her away.
Qingqing,
they haven't divorced yet.
How can you have Zhou Yang
come and take her away?
If she gets affected again,
she'll blame Chuming for it.
What should we do then?
The court was supposed to
announce the divorce next week.
But she suddenly showed up now
and claimed she had amnesia.
Can they really get a divorce?
How about we lock her up somewhere
and deal with it after the divorce?
Qingqing, no one knows
how many people saw her return home.
Lock her up?
Where?
What kind of society
do you think this is?
Do you think this would work?
We'll keep an eye on her
and won't let her leave here.
We'll discuss it after the divorce.
Ms. Su is on her day off today.
I'll have her come back now
and watch her 24 hours a day.
Madam.
What about Chuming?
I'll talk to him about it.
Chuming.
The Doctor said I have amnesia.
But it shouldn't be like this.
We agreed
to protect each other for a lifetime
and wouldn't let each other
suffer sadness.
I believe in myself.
And I believe in you.
So these six months
should be very sweet.
How could I possibly forget?
A lot has happened during this time.
Let's talk after your recovery.
Get some rest.
Where will you sleep then?
The study room.
Ms. Su, take care of her.
Troublemaker.
Let's see how Miss Lin deals with you.
My baby.
Give me back my baby.
Yu Chuxin.
Miss Lin, here is the key.