=Return of Fated Love=
=Episode 17=
Do you still remember this?
You loser.
How dare you help outsiders
to deal with me?
You want me dead.
But I refuse.
Chuxin,
I'll continue to act by her side
until I'm sure to bring her to justice.
You should also beware of
her acting out of desperation.
(CEO's Office Mr. Zhou)
Monitor her.
Keep track of her.
Alright.
So,
you are also pretending.
Miss Lin,
our people are ready.
Lin Qingqing,
what kind of place did you arrange?
It smells terrible.
These are from Dad for you.
Passport, visa, plane ticket.
And a card that's enough
to cover the rest of your life.
He still cares about you.
But if you ask me,
even if you run away,
you'll live a restless life.
It'd be better to
surrender and get better.
Live well after you come out of jail.
By that time,
I won't deny you as my sister.
Go get her!
What do you want to do?
Chuchu,
Dad said
I didn't know how to share.
I'm correcting my mistakes.
I want to take you
to live a happy life abroad.
How about it?
Aren't you touched?
Does this mean I can
qualify for the Heir of Lin Group?
What's gotten into you?
Lin Chuchu.
Don't leave yet.
Your good friends
will be here soon.
Mrs. Yu, you'd better not play tricks.
Since everyone is here,
let's settle accounts
one by one.
You ungrateful traitor.
If it weren't for me,
you'd have been kicked out of company.
I spend money to support you.
What's wrong with using you
as a punching bag?
You secretly collected evidence
and teamed up with outsiders to get me.
Don't forget.
You helped me with these things.
If I go down, you won't
get away with it either.
You stupid woman.
Was I wrong about it?
Chuchu.
I didn't want to do this to you.
But why did you say
Lin Dong
never considered making me the heir?
Don't say
that I can't share.
Okay?
As long as you tell me the truth,
I will let you go.
Then go ask Dad.
I don't know.
You're crazy.
Lin Chuchu, I gave you a chance.
You know what?
I feel disgusted
when I hear you say these.
You won't say it, right?
Then take these secrets
as the Heir in the other world.
Yu Chuxin,
before you came,
I thought of many things
I wanted to say to you.
But now seeing you like this,
I'm no longer interested.
You pretend to have amnesia,
and conspire with
Zhou Chuming to deceive me,
taking down the people
around me one by one,
trying to collect evidence
to take revenge on me,
but what happened?
You're still crawling by my side
as half a year ago.
You can't beat me.
You will never win.
Lin Qingqing,
do you think you can win?
You plotted to harm me,
try to get Chuming
and win your father's approval
and Lin Group.
But what was the result?
I'm still Chuming's most beloved wife.
And you were abandoned by your father.
He didn't even consider you
as a daughter.
You committed numerous crimes.
In the end, you were left with betrayal
from everyone.
That's not true!
No one can take away what belongs to me.
What is mine, if I can't have it,
you shouldn't think about it.
It's all your fault.
If it weren't for
you clinging to Chuming,
I wouldn't have done these things,
and things wouldn't have developed
to this point today.
I don't want this anymore.
It's all your fault.
When I received the call from Tang,
I felt something was off.
So I was extra cautious.
As for how the rope broke,
I have to thank you.
I learned quite a lot when you kept me
in the sanatorium.
Get her!
Please let me go.
Help me.
Now I regret it.
It's too late.
We had called the police
when we arrived.
(Lin, Zheng and others: intentional homicide,)
(intentional injury, illegal detention, etc.)
(They have been taken according to law.)
(Ye gave herself up to the police)
(and confessed to her illegal acts.)
The doctor said Mom is recovering well.
She will wake up soon.
I believe Dad will be fine too.
The evidence of Lin Qingqing's
crime is conclusive.
The trial can be held soon.
After Director Zheng learned of this news,
he didn't surrender,
and wanted to flee.
He was also caught.
Finally, we saw the sunlight.
What are your plans next?
Take care of my sister.
Her IQ is that of a few years old.
She doesn't even recognize me.
I still want to cure her.
I believe she'll recover
soon with your help.
Ye.
Come and play with me.
Come on.
Ye.
Lin Qingqing won't influence you, right?
How can it be?
I've never used any of
the Group's resources for her.
I have no idea
about her actions.
No matter what,
she's your daughter.
Now you're distancing from her.
Aren't you afraid that people will say
you're a cold-blooded father?
I only have one daughter, Chuchu.
Wrong.
She's our daughter.