Who is it?
Is this Choi Chun Hee's...
Choi Chun Hee is you?
You're the one who made me like this,
the God of Music on a roll, Jang Joon Hyeon, you're the one who made me like this.
What?
If only you didn't make a big deal with that medal!
If you didn't chase me to the hotel and make all that trouble.
So the reason I, who am innocent, got mixed with this current scandal,
that I am facing  your dirty, cheap face,
that the Net is full of false accusations,
and that the world is full of lies and distrust
driven by an evil force
is every bit, all, all  because of you!
You, troublemaking medal girl!!!
Who are you, Ajusshi?
Byul, go inside.
Go inside and lock the door. Scoot.
But, they want me to train you?
I  can't  do it!
I  won't  do it!
Who's training whom?
What is he saying after showing up out of the blue?
Anyone else except her is fine.
I can never do it.
Hello?
You're the owner of 1006 right? Please move your stuff this instant!
You're probably here to get your stuff?
President
I would have thought you'll be busy these days, but here you are.
President, how can you do this?
I was going to do it if possible.
So, you mean it's not possible?
It's both her exterior appearance and not having to listen to her singing.
So, you're going to give up?
So, your talent reaches only up to there?
Excuse me?
No, what I mean is, I can do it if I wanted to,
but when I think about what I had to go through because of her,
I  still can't even sleep comfortably now.
You must have some bad relationship with that kid.
It's not even your average bad relationship.
No matter how much you pay me, I won't do it.
No, I can't do it.
Then, it can't be helped.
Well, if you can't do it, then you can't do it.
President Jo, perhaps you could say something in the same language.
Then, President, taking this opportunity...
Get out.
Where are we?
Drag him out!
Ahh! All right! All right!
Oh! Not this!
Ahh really...
Isn't this the court?
Why are we at the court?
I invested one billion won for your next album!
And for the lawsuit regarding to the drink and the department store you were an advertising model for, 2 billion won.
And most of all,
the fallen image of my Shine Star
because of you, 3 billion won!
And you can read the rest yourself.
President!
Why are you like this? You're joking right?
You said you can't do it.
Then our contract is automatically breached.
President!
You still think the world, no,
the entire universe is still revolving around you?
Then continue to live like that, and see how your life will turn out.
-President!
-Let go of me!!
Please...
Please give me another chance.
I already gave you a chance.
Choi Byul ☆
Dad, I love you.
Who are you?
- Who are you to come into someone else's house?
- Where's your dad?
Excuse me?
Choi Myeong Sik, your dad, where is he?
If a person borrowed some money, then he should repay it!
No. I can't do it. I won't do it!
Lady, I'm telling you now.
I'm not going to go easy because you're a girl.
So hurry up and tell me.
I don't know either. I'm just waiting for my dad to call.
Waiting for him?
There's nothing worth any money
in this house either.
This evil fate can't get eviler.
You and I must be really fated.
Please work hard.
Hey hey hey hey!
Where do you think you're going?
I have no relationship with this house.
You walked in here saying it's fate.
No... It's...
Hello, please quickly tell them that we don't know each other.
This person has no relationship to me.
He walked in here with all his stuff just now, prepared to live here, and you're saying you guys have no relationship?
I feel like I've seen you many times somewhere.
Oh? Oh?
Did you borrow money from me?
Your face looks familiar.
Excuse me?!
So why did you have come again?
Now even you're  here, seriously...
So what are you going to do now?
Do what?
We can't  "plant"  a girl ...
(implying "bury")
"Plant"  what?
You said it's fate.
Were you going somewhere to plant something?
If you can't keep your promise, then you should die!
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't.  Please don't do this!
I will pay back the money no matter what,
so if you give me a little time...
We have no time. We are very busy people!
Well there's no way I can pay you back right away,
so I'll work somewhere part-time and slowly...
Hey, are you crazy?!
Slowly my butt! That girl can make money right now.
If you get to know her, you'll see she is like an ATM machine!
That girl is a singer. You know Shine Star right?
She's going to sign a contract with Shine Star tomorrow.
Hey! What are you saying right now?
Miss, is this true?
What?
- Are you really a singer?
-Me?
Then, go sing.
It's not true. He's saying something untrue.
Go and sing.
She's saying it's not true!
Aihoo!
Hello?
What?
You lost him again?!
Catch him for now.
Catch him and break his legs right there.
No, you can't! You can't!
By any chance, is this my dad?
Dad or whatever, anyone who doesn't pay back the money needs to die!
Hey, what do you mean by they need to die?
Why do you say things so violently?
Just  plant  him somewhere nearby in the mountains.
Hey, just  plant  him in a nearby mountain.
Hey, up to his head,
just  plant  him up to his head.
Hey, just  plant  him fully!
Up to... Up to his head?
And him, too. Hurry up and  plant  him!
Plant  all of them!
Yes.
No, no, you can't!
You should know that I really have no relationship with her!
Stop! I will sing!
I will sing!
You told me to sing!
So I'll sing...aish
♬ On a green meadow, ♬
♬ In a house we build as pretty as a picture, ♬
♬ I want us loving and living for a hundred years. ♬
♬ When it's spring, plant the seeds ♬
plant the seeds!
♬ When it's summer, the flowers bloom ♬
Flowers bloom!
♬ In the fall, we harvest. ♬
♬ In the winter we are happy ♬
♬ Although one brags about a trendy high-rise, ♬
♬ although following the trend in living too may be one's style ♬
♬ I like it. I like it. If you and I will live together. ♬
♬ If you and I live together, woah, woah ♬
Hey!
You're pretty good. You have a nice voice.
No, him there making sounds
with that paper bag over his head.
They're pretty funny aren't they?
I know, right, Hyungnim?
Unnie,
are you really going to sign the contract tomorrow?
Of course! I'll guarantee it!
Please!
Really?
We just made an eye contract right now.
We're going to go to Shine Star together in our car.
Let's go, Hyungnim.
Hey, did they leave?
Be quiet!
Did they leave?
What are you doing?! Move this thing away quickly!
Ah that's it. Rascal.
Tell me. What do you want me to do?
At the next New Year's do you want me to play yunnori (korean traditional board game) twice
or do you want me to act as a driver for one year?
I don't need any of that.
Just take the company for a year.
What?
Nothing more.
Just one year.
After a year, I will hand it over
to a professional manager.
Why wait a year? Just hand it over right now.
If you can just do it, that's even better.
These days when adults retire, they age so quickly.
Why do you talk so much?
You know I lost to you on purpose.
I've been eating and sleeping off of your money,
so I put an effort to lose to pay you back.
Oh yeah?
Yes, I know it's 5:30 today.
Let's see each other at the hospital.
You go to the meeting with Director Yang today
instead of me.
I really don't have high expectations of you.
At least do work worth 1/10,000 of what was spent teaching you.
Hey ... your music style was trot?
I'm really going crazy. How could it fit you so perfectly?
As tacky as you look.
Hey, that shovel really suits you.
Hey, isn't this a worm?!
I hate worms the most! Move this away!
What's so scary about this, huh?
You really act the way you look.
It  is cute to me.
Hey, this one here is even bigger! Move it away!
Hey!
Hello?
Hey, I told you to move this away.
Excuse me?
My father's identification came out?
Hey!
All right.
Hey, where are you going?! Where are you going? Hey!
You're joking around right now, right?
Hey back number 17!
It's not him.
It's not my dad.
Thank you.
Is anyone there?
Excuse me!
There's a person here!
Is it a ghost?
Don't come! Don't come!
Have you done warming-up properly?
Coach!
When I went to go check the body,
I was praying that it wasn't my dad.
I was praying for just that.
Now that I know it wasn't my dad,
it's fortunate but,
I suddenly felt angry.
Honestly, I really hate my dad.
How could he not call even once,
to me,
to Byul, how could he do this to us?
You,
that time,
when you fainted on the track,
your father came to the school.
My dad?
Teacher,
please save my kid.
A marathon runner needs to know
how to give up as well.
That's a skill as well.
My kid is so stubborn,
once she starts running,
she doesn't know how to give up.
You've already seen it, right?
She's going to die if she keeps that up.
Teacher,
please rein my kid in.
If your dad disappeared,
there's probably a reason.
More than anyone in this world,
he loved his kids to death.
You know this as well.
Yes.
Unni!
Unni told me not to open the door to suspicious people.
Suspicious?
I'm not a suspicious person.
I'm a well known celebrity.
Little kid, you really don't know me?
Are you sure you're a celebrity?
Then why are you so dirty?
It just happened that way.
I'm not suspicious anymore, right?
Little kid,
do you have anything to eat?
Follow me.
I need to eat.
Look here.
Oh?
Not that, the one underneath it.
Eat that one, it's the older one.
Unni told me to eat the newer ones,
but we shouldn't do that.
We have to eat the older ones first.
So this one is the older one and this one is the newer one...
April 2014?
Are you sure this is the newer one?
You guys live off these?
Just hurry and close the freezer door.
Mom, why did you suddenly schedule a dinner meeting?
I can't even stop by the salon.
Then what? It's the first dinner
with the new president,
do you want him to be taken by others?
You just have to follow what I say.
All right.
The car you sent is here. Bye.
We're going to the hotel right?
Yes.
Yeah.
What do you want me to do to the  parachute  president?
(parachute : implying nepotism)
So I can act the way I usually act right?
Just sit down and eat a little,
And when he asks me something, I just smile.
Ok.
But Mom, the driver is a little weird.
He keeps on looking at me.
Why are you following me?
It's not like that.
Here you go.
Take it.
You've worked hard.
Do you still have unfinished business with me? What are you?
How did you guys come together?
Mom, what's with this guy? Why does he keep on following me?
Hello.
Welcome, President. I've only seen you in pictures.
Please sit.
Why are you not sitting, Soo In?
Yes.
I heard President Jo is on vacation right now.
For him to have such a great and successful son,
President Jo can now relax.
Well, I'm only here for a year.
Just while my father is resting, like a substitute.
First, please exchange greetings. This is my daughter, a trainee at Shine Star Entertainment.
She is pretty busy preparing for auditions lately.
Like your mother, you are very pretty.
Oh yeah, you are aware of the auditions for the Shine Star trainees?
I was wondering if that plan is still continuing without President Jo here.
Nothing will be changing while I'm here.
Everything will be continuing just as it is.
Your father was originally the judge,
but now you will be doing it instead?
Well, can't you use a different person? I think you can.
I think it is better for you to do it personally.
Because, in your position,
many people must keep an eye on you.
Oh yes... If that's what you think.
- Unnie!
- Oh Byul.
You're hungry right? I'll quickly make you food.
Unnie, I think it's a good idea for you to become a singer.
I like it when you sing, so if you sing to other people besides me,
other people will feel happy like me.
Who said those kinds of things?
Whether it's the shower or sink,
each drop of water is precious.
What are you? What are you to shower in someone else's house?
Hey.  Did you forget because of whom did  I get buried in the ground?
Then do you want me, Jang Joon Hyeon, to walk around outside looking such a sight!
Exactly why is President Jo attracted to her?
Exactly who is President Jo? Who is he to tell me to become a singer? Does he know me?
That's what I want to ask!
- What's going on?
- What  do you mean what's going on?
Then do you have another plan? Do you think those guys from earlier can't find your dad?
You should pay back the money before they find your dad.
Then are you really becoming a singer tomorrow, Unnie?
That's right! Thanks to my total talent  you'll succeed.
Hey, do you have a dryer?
Go dry it outside!
Hey hey.
- Hurry and go.
- Hey.
I don't like your small, dirty house as well. I'm going to go to a hotel.
So hurry up and go. Go safely and don't ever come back. Bye.
That girl. Really...
The song you gave me. You're the one who gave me my debut song.
Unnie, that Ajusshi is lying down outside.
Don't mind him and come here. Let's sleep Byul.
Tadaa!
Here you go.
But Unnie, if you become a singer, will you be wearing sparkly dresses and taking pictures?
Mom wore a dress too.
- Well, that's...
- You're going to be on TV as well, right?
If I can see you on TV, that'll be really great.
Then that means Dad will be listening to your song somewhere as well?
That means he might come home faster because he misses us? Right, Unnie?
Should we sleep now?
Good night!
Do you have 40 million won?
If I had the money for the penalty,
I would close down this store right away.
I can't even sleep with my back stretched out.
What is this? Ah, seriously?
Seriously, what kind of suffering is this?
Ajusshi!
Shh! Unnie will wake up.
Ajusshi, good night!
You too!
Ajusshi, eat with us.
How can you eat fried rice in the morning?
Then don't eat.
Wow, there's even seaweed in this fried rice.
Then would there be no seaweed for the triangle kimbap?
Why are you making fried rice with triangle kimbap?
If you don't fry it, it'll be cold.
Is this, by any chance, the old food?
Are you guys trying to kill me?!
You better eat it again.
Yoo Sik, didn't I tell you to escort the Unnie and Oppa well?
Of course, Hyungnim.
- They have a big future ahead of them.
-Yes.
Careful, careful.
Oh, our precious people. Do you want me to escort you to the president's office?
No, it's ok!
Out of the three judges, two of them are
me and Yoon Gun, K-pop critic.
There's nothing the new president can do on his own.
That judge, you're sure he's on our side?
Of course. He's my high school friend.
Whether they look at skill or whatever, Soo In will definitely win.
Just trust me.
Oppa, when you studied in New York, you had a classmate name Jo Geun Woo right?
What kind of person is he?
Not those kind of things. Like his personality or hobbies?
Or his ideal type?
Hello.
Why did you hang up so abruptly?
It's nothing.
You came early.
To prepare for the audition.
Yesterday, I made a mistake.
About what? It's true that I'm a parachute president.
Why didn't you say that you weren't a driver?
Why would I when you didn't even ask?
Why did you give a ride to a woman you don't even know?
I was going to the same hotel anyway,
and instead of going alone, it's nice to go with a pretty lady.
I really want to win this audition.
If I win, treat me to a meal. That much is fine, right?
I don't want to.
If you win, you should be the one treating.
Ah, that's fine too.
Then you're going to buy.
Oh, and the money you gave yesterday.
Ah, yes.
I'll use it well.
Why isn't he picking up the phone?
Hey, you wait here.
Okay.
Hello?
This is the child care center, right?
Teacher, I'm sorry, but can you drop off Byeol at home today?
Yes, thank you.
You have entered incorrectly.
Here.
Ah, you're the weird member-nim from before, right?
- You know me?
-  You have entered incorrectly.
Ah. Um.
Wang Dong Kyu
Shine Star Entertainment
Ah,  that...
Not that. That!
Omo, excuse me?
Give me my phone!
Aish, give me that!
Why do you just take someone else's phone like that?
You're such a weird person, seriously. You must be a kleptomaniac.
Take this.
It must lock automatically from the outside.
The security in this building is very outstanding.
Do you always act any way you want?
Why did you take my phone and...
You're the one who closed the door.
That's true, but...
Should we go down one floor? It may be unlocked there.
Okay.
Ah, look. It will be tiresome for two people to go down.
You try go down and come back.
What?
I'm joking.
Joke.
Really, he's such a weird person.
Excuse me! Anyone out there?
Excuse me! There are people in here!
Try calling security.
How do I know their phone number? It's my first time here.
If it's your first time here, why were you in front of the president's office?
I came to see him.
Why would you see the president?
I don't want to tell you!
Look here!
- Excuse me, where is the president?
- I don't know.
Excuse me...
Oppa! What brings you here?
Oh... President Jo asked me to help him with something.
President Jo?
Ah, this. I carried it around so I can give it to you when I see you.
What is this?
You just left last time.
It's okay, Oppa. This is just my heart.
I'll be thankful if you just thought of it like that.
No. I don't know about anyone else, but I can't be indebted to you.
I understand. If that's how you feel.
But don't you have to pick up the phone?
Huh? Yeah.
Hello?
What? Locked in somewhere?
You don't have anywhere else to call?
It doesn't look like he's coming.
But, what in the world do you do?
Who are you to recklessly press
whatever passcode for the president's room?
At the sports center too, you tried to open the lock with any key.
And am I your secretary? Huh?
You did that last time too. Why do you make me hold that drink for you? Seriously, huh?
You just took my phone too!
You're such a strange person, really!
Wow, you talk really fast.
You got yourself in trouble already?
Who is that person?
Let's go.
So...You're the president's son?
So he's saying he is the president's son,
and now he became the president.
That's why... Yeah.
So you're saying my father gave you a mission?
To raise this lady? So you came to sign the contract?
That's right. Should I try call the president directly?
The phone is turned off...
Ah, why did he turn off his phone?
This. Documents given personally by the president.
This.
Shine Star Audition Application
Next Shine Star Audition
What is this?
So, it's not about a contract.
He's telling you to participate in the audition.
Will you participate in the Next Shine Star Audition, Ms. Choi Chun Hee?
What? Me?
Although it's cable, it's still broadcast nationwide. There's even prize money.
Winner Prize Money: $100,000
The audition preliminaries are tomorrow.
What, tomorr...? Just a day before the audition, how can she...?
Does that even make sense?
You two make the decision.
We'll have to do as much as we can. We can't just back out. Do you have any ideas?
You want me to go on stage tomorrow? Do you think I'll be able to do that?
I don't know what I'm talking about either.
Ah, it's driving me crazy.
Hey. I've never even dreamed about being a singer.
Right now, finding a part time job is my priority, and I need to eat and survive with Byul.
I need to repay my dad's debt too.
I must've been crazy. What contract?
I'm sorry for being buried because of me. So you just go your way.
I'll take care of my business.
Hey, look...
So the window on this side won't open all the way down...
- Oh! Hyungnim.
- Huh?
- She's coming. She's here.
What happened? Did you sign the contract?
What is this? You couldn't?
I'm sorry. I'll work part time and make sure I repay the money.
Hey, are you now just going to leave doing whatever? Are you going to bite me?
But what happened to that oppa?
He left.
What?!
- But he has nothing to do with me. Really...
- What is that you're holding?
Next Shine Star Audition
Winner Prize Money: $100,000
$100,000? Hyungnim, the winner of the audition gets $100,000.
From the second preliminary round, it will be broadcast on national cable TV.
To all the participants who pass the preliminaries, a fixed appearance fee will be provided.
There's even an appearance fee.
First, get in.
Why?
Just get in first.
When the preliminaries start tomorrow,
adding more participants... How will that be received by the public?
Plus, we've already advertised that this was an audition targeted towards trainees.
As for me, I approve a new member coming in.
What is the goal of the Shine Star Audition?
Isn't it to bring out good talents to the world under our company's name?
If President Jo Hee Mun personally recommended this person, there must be a good reason.
Yes.
I want to meet that person as soon as possible.
Can I ask you what you're thinking?
You told me not to worry because the judges are you, Manager Wang, and a critic on our side.
Well, that's true.
The winner will be our Soo In anyway.
In an event where our Soo In is the heroine, it's good to have many bridesmaids.
Well, that's true.
Hello.
Oh, hey!
Choose one.
You should go to that audition.
You should be wearing at least these kinds of clothes for the audition.
Don't be too burdened,
this is our sincere offer.
You heard Hyungnim right?
Pick as much as you want.
Our hyungnim picked the best fashion, so pick one without burden,
Here, yeah, things like this.
These kinds of things are good.
Why? What do you think of this?
I don't think it's that one.
Things like this, how about this?
Why?
Let's see.
This is not a usable card.
Is it President Jo?
What should I do?
What do I do?
Aish!
I have something to say as well.
Honestly you didn't even sign a contract with her, so what do you want me to  do?
Hello?
You're preparing for the audition well, right?
Ah... The thing is... The audition preparation...
We have to do it, right?
- What?
- So what I'm saying is,
we went there thinking to sign a contract but they told us to prepare for an audition so...
When did I say that I was going to contract? I never said that.
Excuse me?
Are you trying to feed off me?
Did you think training a person was that easy?
Wait, hold on a minute. You're not starting to have different thoughts, are you?
How could I?
Don't forget I'm always watching you with my two eyes.
President, we are doing our best to prepare for the audition.
So don't worry about anything.
Don't worry about anything.
All right.
Then I'll trust you.
I can't even run away.
Did they say nothing at Midas?
You said you wanted to be a singer.
Yes.
But, do I have to lower my nose?
Then that means I have to shave my bone.
Why?
Ah, these days, Jang Dong Gun doesn't work.
We have to go with that younger trend.
Yeah, that's right. Not only should we fix your nose,
we should also stretch your eyes and raise your lips.
You know the Joker surgery?
It's pretty sexy.
I already made an appointment at this hospital,
so you just need to make a deposit in here.
Ok?
Aigoo!
Oh, patient Seol Tae Song?
Yes?
Let's take a look.
Let's see.
Open widely.
Okay. Nurse Kim! Please prepare for teeth extraction.
Top two, bottom two.
Wow...
Hello?
Hyung. Where are you?
Who is this?
Ah, it's me Hyo Yeol.
Shin Hyo Yeol.
I heard that you're my manager starting from today.
- What? Me?
- Whatever.
I'm at the Cheongpyeong villa right now,
hurry up and come.
Hey, do you know how far that is from here?
Hello?
Hey!
You were leaving a young kid at home?
Huh!
What, what, did I say something wrong?
But, have you decided to do the audition?
Are you going to wear this?
I didn't bring it home because I wanted to wear it either!
Aish.
But, why are we doing this audition?
What?
If you're not going to do it, what are you going to do?
Can you tell those guys tomorrow that you're not doing the audition?
Not me, you. You, you, you.
- Why are you doing it?
- That's me!
Stop asking and let's start. Now,
you know we have to finish what others prepared for ten years, in one day, right?
Forget about respiration or phonation,
let's decide a song first.
♪ Kkungttari syabara ppappappa...ppappappa ♪
♪ When you feel gloomy and frustrated ♪
It's so frustrating.
♪ Your appearance ♪
♪ Like a violet light ♪
♪ You softly came to me ♪
♪ A-B-C-D-E-F-G-H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P God will protect! ♪
♪ Hills over hills I climb, but there's another hill left ♪
In the end, you can only sing trot.
♪ I climb over and climb over ♪
Stop!
- The rhythm and the beat don't match.
- That's because I'm nervous!
Just imagine as if in this universe there is this string attached to your head,
and you raise this string.
Sing in this position.
Stop!
What's wrong with your pronunciation?
Bite that and practice. I'm tired.
I'm not sleeping.
♪ I climb over and climb over ♪
What are you doing and not getting on?
Mom, you go up first.
Why?
- I have something to get from the car.
Here you go!
Unnie!
Fighting!
Jeez.
Choi Chun Hee,
you have to pass in order to live.
- Please go.
- Fighting!
Please!
Looking at your outfit,
it must be the audition day today.
Is that a compliment?
Oh, of course. It suits you.
Thank you.
It must really be the audition day.
Sorry.
I see you again, Oppa.
Why are you here, Soo In?
I'm here for the audition.
Why?
Your album is coming out,
so why are you auditioning?
I'm still a trainee.
So you're going to participate as well?
We're really screwed.
Aren't you getting off?
The waiting room is off limits to people other
than the contestants and audition staff.
Why am I not a staff?
Oppa, I'll see you later.
This is the person that President Jo recommended, right?
Yes, that's right.
- Hello.
All the trainees are curious.
What kind of person you are.
♬ You are my Mr. Lee Lee  ♬
♬  You are my Mr. Kang Kang  ♬
♬  You are my Mr. Kim Kim  ♬
♬  My love is shake shake shaking  ♬
♬  My lips are eloquent with sorry sorry   ♬
♬  My heart is shaking worry worry  ♬
♬  Hey Mr. Don't Be Late hurry hurry hurry   ♬
♬  You are my love Mister oh!  ♬
Hey.
Yes? Me?
Yes, you. Can't you see the water bottle is empty?
She's pretty good.
Oh, you're strong.
Hey.
Water.
- Excuse me?
- Why?
Do you have any complaints when I'm asking you for water?
Unnie, I'll get it for you.
Here.
Wow, look at what she's wearing.
This is trending in what era?
Do you sing trot or something? What was it?
I hope you receive a special compliment.
Thank you.
She's the big sister around here, so you should understand.
Everyone seems to be sensitive because of the audition.
No wonder, it looked that way.
There are many voices of concern regarding our Geun Woo?
Do you think that way, too?
President, why would I?
Don't worry too much.
I know my son best.
♪ You saying that I don't seem the same, those words aren't completely false ♪
♪ I am also not used to how I changed ♪
♪ You were so... ♪
♪ Oh, I don't know ♪
♪ Under the lonely moonlight ♪
♪ If my shadow casts ♪
Welcome.
Hello, I am #46, Park Soo In.
Ms. Park Soo In, your mother is
the legendary Yang Joo Hee.
Yes.
That fact alone makes me look forward to this.
Start the song right away.
♪ There is now one person ♪
♪ A person I shouldn't love ♪
♪ I can't, I can't ♪
That lady can sing pretty well.
It doesn't sound enchanting though.
♪ I made him cry ♪
♪ With my wicked obsession ♪
♪ If the tears would steal the heart and disappear ♪
♪ It seems like it would come closer ♪
Straighten your back!
The audition is all about the 'energy battle' with the judges.
Don't lose in the eye fight with the judges.
Charisma.
- Chun Hee!
- Yes?
- Please give me your phone and follow me.
Okay.
♪ Afraid that you'll hide ♪
♪ Even if I'm dying in pain ♪
Oh, we're already on our last?
Hyungnim, she came out.
Hello, I am #47, Choi Chun Hee. Please take good care of me.
Ms. Choi Chun Hee. Interestingly, you picked a trot song.
By chance, is there a special reason behind choosing this song?
Ah, I...
When I was young, I grew up listening to my mother sing, who worked at the marketplace.
This is a remake song that my mom sang.
Your mother sang?
Yes. She released one album.
That was the story.
Have you been a trainee at another agency,
uploaded videos on Youtube,
or have any stage experience?
I don't.
None at all?
Yes, none at all.
How did a person like that think about coming to this audition?
Ah...
Let's listen to the song.
What's with her?
Aiyoo, that...That.
♪ I climb over and climb over, but the hilly path is endless ♪
♪ Living in this world, living this life ♪
♪ It's hotter than pepper ♪
- Let's keep watching. It's fun for me.
♪ If the two of us are loving and being loved ♪
♪ For hundred years, for thousand years ♪
♪ Fleetly flee, fleetly flee, we will live ♪
♪ Living in this world, living this life ♪
♪ It's hotter than pepper ♪
♪ Hills over hills I climb, but there's another hill left ♪
She should've been like this from the beginning!
♪ I climb over and climb over ♪
♪ but the hilly path is endless ♪
♪ Living in this world, living this life ♪
♪ It's hotter than pepper ♪
♪ If it is just the two of us loving and being loved, ♪
♪ For a hundred years, for thousand of years ♪
♪ Fleetly flee, fleetly flee, we will live ♪
♪ Living in this world, living this life ♪
♪ It's hotter than pepper ♪
♬  You are my Mr. Lee Lee  ♬
♬  You are my Mr. Kang Kang  ♬
♬  You are my Mr. Kim Kim  ♬
♬  My love is shake shake shaking  ♬
♬  My lips are eloquent with sorry sorry   ♬
- This friend, I want to take her.
- It will be 10 times the contract payment.
- I'll repay the principal.
What?
There are too many flaws. Decisively, she's not even sexy.
Listening to you, I'll just..!
I really hate eating alone.
Omo, President, we run into each other like this.
A second ago, we had eye contact.
Why did Jang Joon Hyeon fall to this extent?
Hyung, you're the one who made it like that!
You're forever ousted from this field