♫ Suddenly you said you wanted to break up completely ♫
♫ But last night, you still kissed me goodbye ♫
♫ And then you'd spent all night planning the future for the two of us ♫
♫  I said, "Okay, we'll return to our parents and not speak nonsense"  ♫
♫  You've dumped me, and it's not easy to be single again  ♫
♫  My love life has infinite possibilities once again  ♫
♫  Everything is moving too fast, it's hard to accept  ♫
♫  I hid my inexplicable excitement with a wry smile  ♫
♫ It's hard to become single once again ♫
♫ Once again, my love life has infinite opportunities ♫
♫ Our love has been engraved deep in my heart ♫
♫ In the end, we're no longer together ♫
♫ In the end, we've become a pair of strangers ♫
[Fall In Love]
[Episode 2]
So regarding the follow-up, I hope you can keep up the good work, General Manager Chen.
Please don't worry about that. Miss Jing is constantly looking for her ex, who has abandoned her.
She isn't in the mood to manage the hotel.
She'll make an appointment with me after reading the documents.
Miss Jing is quite pitiful.
- She just returned to the country a year ago...
- All right. Then I'll wait for your good news.
I'm uninterested in anything else.
Then I'll leave first. No need to see me out.
Come, Subei.
Hello.
- Yay!
- How did you do that?
Drink it!
Drink it properly. Can you even do it?
It's your turn.
Another two rounds.
Boss, get me another glass of whiskey!
I didn't order this.
It's a gift from the gentleman over there.
He said this drink matches your temperament perfectly.
What beverage is this?
It's a refreshing sparkling cocktail.
It's called "Raspberry."
Billy?
Hey, Miss!
I don't like Billy.
All guys named Billy are scum.
Give me another glass of whiskey. Hurry up.
Say, that girl has quite a strong personality.
Maybe you'll return empty-handed tonight.
She doesn't look like she can hold her liquor well.
Just watch and learn.
The drinks here are very good, right?
If you want more, I can buy you a drink.
I'm not drunk.
You'd better not try anything funny.
Since you're apologizing, you should drink this to show your sincerity.
Fine.
Who are you?
I'm her friend. She can no longer drink. I'll drink on her behalf.
Fu Zeyi?
What are you doing here?
I think I'm drunk for real this time.
You're indeed drunk. Come on, I'll send you back.
Let's go.
We can sit over there.
Are you sure you can walk?
Sit quietly.
Fu Zeyi...
I'm sure I'm still drunk.
Huh?
Is he actually real?
Why did you bring me to a hotel? You pervert!
Fu Zeyi?
It feels terrible, right?
Who told you to drink when you can't even hold your liquor?
Whose blood is this?
I'm not wounded.
You must be Lin, right?
That's why you saved me.
You should hurry and wake up.
I have plenty of questions for you.
Can you get me a first-aid kit?
- Miss, here's your first-aid kit.
- Thank you.
Do you need assistance?
It's fine. Thank you.
This might hurt a little.
Bear with it, okay?
You're a man! Can't you even endure the pain?
If you keep screaming like this, people in other rooms might think that I'm doing something to you.
Not bad at all.
It'll be too obvious when he leaves the hotel.
No. I should change it.
Isn't this too feminine?
I think a simple bandage works best for you.
So you said you didn't know me this morning at the Aizhe Hotel
because you didn't want to make things difficult for me, right?
How much did he drink to get this drunk?
You!
Don't mess around.
Don't take off your shirt!
Hey! You can't take it off below!
Hey, don't misunderstand my intention.
It's because you saved me before. That's why I...
I-I'm taking care of you.
What are you trying to do?
You...
What are you doing? You're crushing me.
Something is off.
How much did you drink to get this drunk?
You don't smell like alcohol.
Since you're apologizing, you should drink this to show your sincerity.
Could it be that it was fake alcohol?
S-Since
you saved me, I won't hit you this time.
I'll count to three. You should get up by then.
Three,
two,
one.
Listen, you're the one who's lying on my arm and preventing me from leaving.
You better don't try anything funny.
If not, I'll show you no mercy.
Are you already awake?
Take a look at this paragraph.
- Morning, Director Fu.
Morning, Director Fu.
- Morning, Director. Fu.
- Morning, Director Fu.
Why did I get myself involved with that woman again?
Director Fu has never been late to work. We couldn't get in touch with him for the entire night.
I'm sure he was kidnapped.
Look.
What are you guys doing?
The kidnappers will call us anytime.
- Kidnappers?
- We told you to be quiet.
Director Fu has been kidnapped. Later, the kidnappers might call us to demand a ransom.
- Go, go!
- You pick it.
I can't.
Hello?
You dialed the wrong number.
- Director Fu.
- Whose signature do you need?
- Junior Director Fu's.
- Come here.
- What's wrong, Senior?
Be careful.
Junior Director Fu has already returned safely. What are you worried about?
You're new to Fu Group. I've been working here for eight years.
He has never skipped our weekly Monday meeting before.
I'm sure something happened to him.
Anyway, we should be cautious.
Senior, can you accompany me?
Just go alone.
Senior...
Junior Director Fu.
I need your signature for this document.
Please sign here.
What are you doing? You're crushing me.
I'll head out if there's nothing else.
That was scary. Senior was right.
Fu Zeyi?
Why did he pay me?
Is he doing it again?
- Hello?
- Fu Zeyi,
what do you mean by leaving your card behind?
I don't mean anything in particular.
You can see it... as your compensation.
Compensation? Why are you compensating me?
Nothing happened between us.
That's right.
So you're deliberately trying to humiliate me again?
You can think whatever you like. This is how I treat strangers.
[Jian Bufan]
Hello?
Older Sister, hurry and come back! Dad is going to kneel and apologize to Fu Zeyi!
What?
Director Jing, you're finally back! Your cousin can't take it anymore.
- Where are they?
- Upstairs. Let's hurry.
All right.
Jian Bufan! Open the door for me!
Dad, just wait a little longer!
Older sister will be here soon!
- Open the door!
- Older sister will be here soon!
I don't believe that I can't make him cancel the debt.
- Older Sister, you're finally back.
- You brat!
How dare you sell me out?
- I-I'll teach you a lesson today!
- Uncle!
- I...
Uncle, please calm down.
There is no secret between us in our family.
Let's talk inside.
Let's go. Let's talk inside. Let's talk inside.
Come.
Have a seat.
Uncle. Say, should we use
Simmental cow leather from the high plateaus in Europe or Shinki-Hikaku shell cordovan from Japan
for the boss's new chair?
I think Shinki-Hikaku shell cordovan from Japan.
Cow leather is too ordinary.
This Shell cordovan is special.
As the saying goes, we lick one's boots.
Boots made from shell cordovan are superior and easy to lick.
Have you guys ever heard that licking one's boots is a bad thing?
Uncle, you see,
when you sit on this chair,
you do look and behave like a president.
Even if I were to leave the hotel
and leave it to you one day,
I could be at ease.
Really?
That's enough. I already answered your question.
I'll look for Fu Zeyi right now.
Fu Zeyi?
Uncle, didn't you say that you wouldn't compensate him?
I did a background check on this Fu Zeyi.
He is totally ruthless.
He's a true profiteer.
I do think he's devious enough to send me to prison.
However, during the investigation process,
I discovered... a shocking secret.
- A secret?
- What is it?
He was missing for three months
from August to October last year.
- I intend to use this fact...
- Three months?
to blackmail him and ask him to let me off.
What have you found then?
Nothing.
Why were you so excited if you found nothing?
It's precisely because of that fact that I know he's hiding something.
Think about it.
What was he doing and who was he with
during those three months?
Fu Zeyi went missing for three months
during the time he got to know me.
When did you get an Amex Centurion Card?
Don't tell me Fu Zeyi gave you that?
Wait,
you didn't even change your clothes.
This means you didn't return home last night.
And Fu Zeyi gave you an Amex Centurion Card this morning.
What did you two do last night?
You shouldn't meddle with an adult's affair.
He just seems like a troublesome character.
I just don't want you to be bullied.
Tell me.
How can a person change so drastically in just one year?
Maybe...
he was possessed?
Come on, be serious.
Maybe he lost his memories?
Right?
That's what I thought, too.
I must get to the bottom of this.
No problem. Just leave this to me.
Do you know how to solve this?
I'll interrogate him by force.
You mustn't hit him.
It's wrong to resort to violence.
Don't worry. I'll vent out your anger on your behalf.
Just wait here, Older Sister.
Fu Zeyi.
Fu Zeyi, come out. I know you're inside.
Were you looking for me?
Stop!
Ai Xin, happy graduation.
♫  I have confessed to you twice  ♫
♫  Keeping my bottom line intact  ♫
Thank you.
- Ai Xin! Come here!
- Coming!
Senior Sister!
I...
I like you.
♫  Were you expecting it to be like a scene in a movie?  ♫
I'm sorry.
I don't date a boy who's 150 cm (59 inches) tall.
Senior Sister, I've been playing basketball.
I'll grow to 180 cm (71 inch) soon.
Will you then go out with me?
We can talk about it once you're 180 cm tall.
Senior Sister, I will do my best! You must wait for me!
I'm 185 cm (73 inch) tall now.
Who are you?
She actually forgot about me!
Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
I won't drink.
Adulterated liquor is really dangerous.
I swore that I'd never drink again.
So did something happen between you two
because you got drunk last night?
What could happen between us?
He said he didn't know me.
You're right.
What could happen between you two?
He already said he didn't know you.
Don't tell me you still want to embarrass yourself in public?
Was it that embarrassing?
It was so embarrassing!
If only I could dig a hole and hide in it.
No matter what, we're considered old flames.
How could he forget about me?
Could it be
that his brain was damaged because of an accident?
That's right. I'm sure his brain was damaged.
♫  There's not a day that I'm afraid to be alone  ♫
♫  I’m afraid of seeing you again after we said our goodbyes  ♫
♫  I'm slowly getting used to missing you  ♫
♫  It seems like I've locked my heart away as the memory lingers  ♫
♫  If I decide to be brave this time,  ♫
♫  Then I'll hold your hands till eternity  ♫
♫  The moment we found the emotions we'd lost,  ♫
♫  it will overcome those lonely moments little by little  ♫
♫  If you were by my side,  ♫
♫  no matter how many promises we've broken  ♫
♫  There's nothing I'm not willing to do  ♫
♫  Just to have a simple and ordinary life with you  ♫
♫  If you were by my side,  ♫
♫  all my regrets will be blown away by the wind  ♫
♫  I only want you to be with me every second, every minute  ♫