Project Loki starts with Lorelei
Rios transferring to Pampanga,
where she meets the cold
and eccentric Loki Mendez,
who also happens to be her roommate.
She later joins the QED Club,
and the two eventually
become a crime-solving duo.
Later in the story, Jamie Santiago
and Alistair Ravena join them,
and together they hunt the elusive
mastermind known only as “M.”
When I was writing Project Loki,
I was heavily inspired by Sherlock
Holmes and Detective Conan.
These two works inspired me
to write detective stories
and come up with cases that
the characters would solve.
One of my dreams as a writer is
to see my story adapted for the screen,
whether as a series or a movie.
I’m also happy that
VivaOne became our partner
because they show great respect,
not just for me as a writer
but also for the source material.
It feels very overwhelming.
Until now, I’m still surprised that
I got the role in Project Loki.
But I’m very happy, very blessed,
and very determined to
give justice to the role of Loki.
I’m very excited to show it to everyone.
I know this role is challenging.
The character is very different,
and the genre is different from
the usual series people watch.
It’s very interesting,
and I’m really looking forward to
learning a lot from the director,
my co-actors, and the producers—
everyone involved in Project Loki.
Loki plays a big role, and despite
being mysterious, nonchalant and cold,
he still brings purpose
to everything he does,
with his investigations and
cases together with co-actors
Of course, I feel extremely honored
to be able to take on this role.
I consider really a big
responsibility for me because
as an original Wattpad fan myself,
I know how much this means to readers.
I’m really excited to bring her character
to life in the best way that I can.
Like I said earlier,
I’m really, really excited.
From the moment the project
was pitched to me,
my excitement immediately peaked.
I immediately read the book,
and one thing I’m most excited about
is staying faithful to the series.
and really do what I can do.
You know, bring or give glory, justice,
in terms of fleshing out her character
in having people to get to know her more.
It’s exciting for me, especially now that
I’m also a fan of Project Loki.
After reading the book,
I truly understood why
readers love this series so much.
It’s really different from
any project I’ve ever done.
It’s a great challenge as an actress
and pushes me outside my comfort zone.
Things I never thought I could actually do.
Things I never imagined I’d be
able to pull off, especially here.
It’s really cool that we’re exploring
different genres here in the Philippines.
It’s really exciting.
I already know this will be one of
my favorite projects I’ll ever work on.
They asked me if I was
interested in Project Loki
I looked up Project Loki online
when I was asked about it.
And I’m happy if I can be
completely honest,
I liked that it wasn’t a
typical love-team story.
It was more mysterious.
It was an edge to the show.
I’m really happy they thought of
casting me in this Project Loki.
When I read the book,
I noticed that my character
is the oldest among the cast
I play the older brother to
Dylan Menor in the story.
So when I found out I was the brother,
I noticed during the shoot that
I was a bit older than the others.
Not that I really thought of it that way,
but since it was a new cast,
I guess I was just used
to doing university series.
They’re my friends,
I’m already comfortable.
And now it’s a new whole cast,
and I felt that I was the one who
is extracted in University Series,
and put here in Project Loki.
So of course, I was still adjusting
to being around new people.
I’m still careful around them, which
fits the “distant older brother” vibe.
Of course, I was super excited.
Another character, another project,
another blessing.
I’m grateful because I never expected
to be accepted here, as Jamie
I prepared mentally, physically,
and emotionally for the role.
I also study Jamie’s mannerisms,
her character description.
I read it, I repeat it.
I do research because I want
to understand her personality.
I’m super happy, and at the same time,
I can’t believe it.
At first, I didn’t really
read Project Loki,
but I heard from my friends
that the story is really good.
While I was auditioning, I thought,
“What if I get into this series?
My friends would be so happy.”
It’s also a blessing for me because
Project Loki is well-known.
Super blessed and excited for this role.
Well, this is where my range
as an actor will really be tested.
Pretty exciting,
but at the same time nervous.
First of all, I want to greet
all the Project Loki fans.
because I know they’ve
been expecting this and,
they’re looking forward to this project.
So the expectation that I have is,
for the actors to do their homework,
because AkoSiIbarra did the four chapters,
like I really, really expect them to
really know the character inside and out.
and how they’re gonna
make it into a real person.
Because imagination is one thing,
reading it is another, and portraying it
on screen is completely different.
Well, Director Xian is an actor,
so I expect to learn more
about acting in general.
To him because he is a veteran,
seasoned actor.
and with him being the director,
for sure he will give me some tips,
some advices on how
I would portray Loki.
For sure gesture and nuances,
how will I deliver lines or expressions,
for sure, he will guide me.
with the help also of
my co-stars/co-actors.
I’m expecting a lot to him.
I’m really, really excited
to learn from him,
well someone who dwells in directing,
as well in music videos.
But for one day,
I would love to become a director
in the field of film and TV.
I’m excited to learn from his vision.
Also, I consider that
we are blessed as a cast
to have not only a director like him,
but also an actor for the director.
He is such a brilliant actor
in his own rights.
So, I’m very excited
to learn his techniques,
and tricks that he learned along
the way throughout his career.
Also, I’m excited besides his wisdom,
to be able to bond with him
through our shared experience,
being in this craft,
I really do believe that this
give us a huge advantage.
Our director knows exactly
what we’re going through,
and what it’s like to be in our shoes.
We’re all working close together.
We’re playing around different emotions.
We’re playing around a different
character background.
So, it’s real something
to look forward to,
to all the Project Loki fans
because of characters’ richness.
so expect the best
from the actors
who will be portraying
the QED 4
even
even all the
all the special characters involved.
I don't want to say too much,
but yeah,
expect
their 100%
And Dylan is our Loki.
Everybody!
Jayda!
Room or apartment 302.
Our apartment.
That’s when he says… [inaudible]
Hello… a little bit of
presence of mind, right?
Extend your patience.
Was it better?
1, 2, 3…
Yeah! Thank you guys!
Guys, this is Jayda. She sang “Babala.”
Please stream “Babala.”
Right! That’s right!
That’s my soundtrip.
Nice!
And this, we’ll only do it…
Alright!
Okay, let’s smile.
Go over there!
Just act if you want!
Act if you want or mouth the lyrics
if that’s your thing. Up to you.
He was surprised!
He was surprised,
you suddenly started singing.
Pack up!
Next one! Next one!
I was extremely happy
and the first thing I
did was thank the Lord
because this is a new role for me
I like challenging roles.
I'm happy and blessed that
the Lord has granted me
the opportunity to
have a role like this
It’s an honor to be part of
the adaptation of Project Loki
And this story is really beautiful
I’m nervous but also excited
because many people support
and read Project Loki.
I’m very excited to bring the
character of Stein Alberts to life
Hi, everyone!
I'm really, really excited
to play Rosetta…
and I hope my performance
gives justice to the character.
When we posted during the go-see,
I had a photo holding Rosetta’s script.
Someone messaged me
saying I really looked
like Rosetta,
and that’s when I realized
how big this project is.
It’s a mix of pressure and excitement.
I usually play demure role
but this time the character is
a bit playful, which excites me.
I'm really excited to do this
Until now, I still can’t believe
I got the role of Rhea.
Everything still feels surreal
This is only my second acting project
I’m used to performing—dancing and singing.
I’m a former girl group member,
so this is very new to me.
It’s exciting and nerve-wracking
at the same time.
I was nervous because Margarette
is a major character.
I got nervous and felt a bit pressured.
I started reading the book
to fully understand the story.
while I was reading,
I genuinely enjoyed reading it.
For the project Loki readers,
I am just excited as you guys are
We promise to give justice to
the characters you imagined.
Of course, I’m happy to
be part of a new project,
but I’m also nervous because
I know the Wattpad readers are super,
super invested in the characters.
All I'm hoping is that
we can all give a Justice
I can give a justice
I hope they’ll like what
we’ll do in the show.
I’m really excited
knowing that Project Loki
has such a huge fanbase,
and even more excited to be part of it!
I’ve read the book as well,
and honestly, it feels more like a
detective thriller than a love story.
And it feels really nice to
step out of the love team.
I'm really excited for this role.
This is going to be
my big break, somehow.
Because I'm going to meet a lot of people
and learn a lot of things from this role.
At first, I was really excited.
But right now it's finally syncing in.
I'm still nervous.
But I'm more excited.
I’m really excited to portray Bastien.
My character here is very interesting
and I can't wait to show it to you guys.
Actually I feel overwhelmed and nervous
because I read the book...
like a year ago or two years ago,
and I know how popular it is.
It’s the most popular mystery story
on Wattpad in the Philippines.
I want to give justice to the character
because if you don't,
it might give a bad impression
to the story and production.
It's overwhelming,
but at the same time exciting.
The character I'm playing,
Hershel Aguirre...
he is not like the front runner
who is solving the mystery.
He is more of the science guy
or the guy behind the QED 4 team.
He is actually plays a pivotal
and important role.
He is not recurring
but he is a fan favorite,
based on comments on Wattpad
as I've read the story.
And I think the Hershel
character is important
and pivotal for the timeline.
Hi!
Hello!
So there… left, left…
Yes, here.
Okay, so here.
Okay.
Behind the scenes.
She doesn’t know you, dude!
Just fix your hair.
You might have been sweaty
at that time, so you did this…
You’re that unbothered, I guess.
You have something to do
to him that disables him.
He’s like...
What am I gonna do? I can’t..
It’s not possible.
I don't want to pre-empt the scene,
but there's one thing that
I'm looking forward to is...
I'll just describe it.
To avoid spoiling the scene.
It would be the chair scene.
I’m really looking forward
to the chair scene,
as well as there's a scene involving Lori
and they drum.
And one more.
One last is the drinking tea.
So those are key moments that I think...
will be...
I'm really excited to shoot.
If there’s one thing I can promise,
especially when it comes to the actors…
Each director has their own sensibilities,
and some approach things differently.
The promise I make to my actors is this
I’ve gone through the grind,
and I’m still going through it on
this journey of becoming
and growing as an actor.
I promised the actors
we’ll figure this out together.
They don’t have to be scared
I know what it feels like to be on set.
Day 1, I already felt the pressure
of having to play the
character given to you
You have the fans’ expectations,
the producers’ expectations,
and of course,
your own expectations for yourself.
It’s just a challenge,
and I want them to embrace it.
That’s what I promise them
that we’re all holding hands
together in this project.
And we’re going to work
our way into making this
the best version it can be,
to really give it justice.
so as far as my journey as a director
It’s going to be a challenge to translate
the book into this adaptation.
I want the fans to feel at ease.
And I want them to know our promise
that we’re here to do our best
and deliver the best
version of Project Loki.
We can assure you that
it will remain faithful
to the structure of the source material.
So you don’t have to
worry about it deviating
from what you already know and love.
So rest assured—the story you loved
is the same story you will be watching.
For me, we just want to
give justice to the story
and stay true to
the source material.
We didn’t just take Project Loki
and change the story.
We will do our best to execute it
as closely as possible.
You will see your favorite characters
brought to life, in the flesh.
I thought I couldn’t be more excited
for this project than I already was.
But somehow, I became even more
motivated to do this project.
We truly feel your love and support.
So thank you so, so much.
We just want to give you a good show,
and I’m really excited.
I’m excited and nervous
at the same time,
and of course, happy to
be part of Project Loki.
I’m excited for you to
see Project Loki soon.
I hope you enjoy and appreciate
the scenes we worked on.
It’s a new genre—something to
look forward to, and very interesting.
It was the first time we had a meeting
like this after a press conference.
Where we actually got
to sit down with the writer.
And we were able to ask
all the questions we had.
It helped clear all our
doubts about the character.
I hope we do it well—it’s exciting.
Before we went out, I was already nervous.
I was extremely nervous,
I don’t know why.
But I’m happy because the
people welcomed us warmly.
Guys, please watch out
for me as Jamie Santiago.
I’ll give my best—
she’s a very complex character.
This is my first time
doing something like this.
I’m very grateful and
excited to start taping.
I’m very excited to work with Jada,
Marco, Dylan, and the rest of the cast.
Grateful and blessed.
To all Wattpad readers,
I won’t be fake with you.
I hope you give me a chance.
I know that at first, with
Calix,
some of you had doubts about
whether I could pull it off well.
I gave my all.
I hope this time in my new
project called, Project Loki.
It’s a new project that came in to my life.
I know this might be a very big,
important book for you guys.
I promise that I will give my best.
With the help of Viva,
with the help of Director Xian,
We’ll give it our all,
and we hope we can capture Luthor’s flair.
Hi readers.
I just want to tell you that
I’ll do my absolute best to
do justice for Jaimie Santiago.
I hope you’ll watch out for me as Jaimie.
I won’t let you down.
To all the readers of Project Loki,
I hope you’ll support us.
It will be a great, great series.
Stay tuned for us!
To all the Wattpad fans,
expect that we are going to do our best.
To the best of our ability,
All of that has already been taken care of.
So we will do whatever it takes to give
justice to all the characters you loved.
For all the scenes that really tugged
at your emotions,
That’s our promise.
We will give you a good one.
We promise to give you a good one.
I just want to thank to
all the Wattpad readers,
and to the fans of Project Loki,
for the warm reception
of the announcement
that there will be an
adaptation of my story.
To all the old time readers,
rest assured that what you have read
is what you will see on screen.
It will be faithful to the source material.
And for the new viewers or audience,
This is a nice change
for your watching habits.
I hope you support and you
will like the genre of mystery
because this genre is also very rich.
To all the PLayers of Project Loki,
I just want to say,
I hope we can make you proud
that you will love this series
as much as we do, as much I do.
Now I can already say that
this is something to look out for.
At the end of the day we just
want to give you a good show.
To bring this beloved story by AkoSiIbarra
to life, in the best way we can.
So I hope guys you enjoy this.
For the Wattpad readers who
are supporting Project Loki,
to all who read this book
and will start to read it,
we’re excited to finally
release Project Loki.
We promise to do our best, to give
our best to portray our characters,
and to give more life in our characters.
We hope that you enjoy.
We hope that you appreciate the art
we are doing for Project Loki.
We’ve been doing it together with lots
of great artist, director, and producers.
I’m also looking forward so
I hope you are looking forward.