Even if we are separated by fate, we will never stop loving each other.
We will never give up on our hearts.
We will only fight for the end in our hearts.
Until our fates are finally revealed, we will never stop.
Episode 15
Brother Chong.
What is it?
The knife you stabbed me with hurts so much.
Why are you here?
No.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I really didn't do it on purpose.
You rascal.
Mei Ran!
It's my fault.
Jiang Wu Huan.
Get up.
Help.
Xing Jia.
Brother Chong.
No.
Brother Jiang.
What are you doing?
A Yan.
A Shun.
Da Huang.
Brother Jiang.
What happened just now?
It feels like it's real.
There's something strange here.
We'd better leave here quickly.
It's not about this place.
Otherwise,
why didn't I and the guards
get the magical powers?
Then what's going on?
When we got the magical powers,
there was a drum sound.
The hand drum of Granny Su.
It must be
the magical powers
that were used by the drum sound.
It means that Granny Su
must be the successor of the Saint Maiden.
That drum sound is a magical power.
What did the little hand drum do?
It's so powerful.
It seems that
there's something wrong with the car.
Do you remember
the situation before we set off?
Young Master.
Aren't you looking for someone?
God knows where he is.
Then let's go quickly.
Wait.
Something is strange.
We've lost him.
You just gave us some clues.
You're still so cautious.
What's your good idea?
Tell us.
I've caught three ghosts and six demons today.
They're all evil.
So if we act rashly,
we'll be caught and be in trouble.
You're so stubborn.
But I never wake up.
Please take us to the mountain quickly.
Even if there's a little clue,
it's better than sitting here and crying.
You follow them secretly.
You can't let them go.
The ancient magic
has a sound.
What's the secret behind it?
Do you know?
Since we were ordered to find the medicine,
there's always a feeling of unease.
It seems that everything
from the East Road to Zhongli
is clearly connected.
For example, the ancient magic valley and the Ghost Clan.
Don't worry.
The Saintess's life
shouldn't be decided here.
Look over there.
That's Qingluan Mountain.
Yin Yang Cave is nearby.
Let's go.
Miss, wake up.
Don't sleep.
Everyone, wake up.
Wake up.
Don't come forward.
Hurry up and get up.
Come on.
Yeah.
Wake up.
Qingqing, I'm sorry.
You're awake.
I wanted to give you to His Majesty,
but now,
there's no need for that.
Qingqing, do you remember
the fate of the Saintess of the Yousu Clan?
I remember.
The Saintess of the Yousu Clan,
the Saintess of the Yousu Clan,
should be changed to protect the peace of Zhongli.
If you can't protect yourself,
what should you do?
If I can't protect myself,
I should be burned to ashes
and be buried in the ground.
Could it be...
this mask?
The punishment has been imposed.
The Saintess is the beauty.
Let me go!
Bear with it, little Saintess!
No one knows about this place.
You can't escape.
You...
The Saintess's fate
is to be the eyes of the Divine Valley.
The Divine Valley can be made,
and the Great Night can be made.
Don't run, little Saintess!
Qingqing!
There are... there are people from the tribe inside.
Okay.
What's wrong with your tribe?
They are possessed by the illusion.
The inner valley...
The inner valley is in trouble.
Today, I'll use your inner valley!
You can't let him see!
This valley looks good.
Where is the
Are you okay?
Shoujun!
The Saintess!
Send those women to the mountain to help the King.
We must ask the doctor to cure them.
The Saintess!
I want to go with them.
I'm really worried.
Maybe they are
my last people.
Be careful.
Take care of the Saintess.
Yes.
Then...
Don't worry.
The mountain is clear.
Let's go.
Today,
we'll make this mysterious place
clear.
Check it.
The inner valley is made by human's scalp.
And it's all women.
There's a missing one.
It's the size of a scalp.
I don't know why it's not complete.
The size of the head was peeled off.
It's very similar to the
clues in the underground city.
The head is very small.
But we don't know
the relationship.
So
it's very likely
to be related to the Celestial Immortals.
And
that person is from the Ghost House.
Ghost House?
It's the Ghost House again.
I don't know.
All the way here, from the Eastland to the Central Plains,
every
barricade
has the sound of the Ghost House.
I see.
But why do they
need to know this?
I think
it's very likely
to be related to the purpose of us coming to the Central Plains.
Celestial Immortals?
Do you have
any findings?
Come with me.
Look here.
This is a mechanism?
Let's not try it.
Since
the Celestial Immortals are related to the Celestial Immortals,
then what's hidden in this chamber
is the secret of the Celestial Immortals?
What are you waiting for?
Go and take a look.
Let's go.
Brother Jiang,
look at this.
Look at the surface.
Does it look like the skin of a wounded man?
Could this be...
That's right.
This is the source of the
Look.
This person has a set of
fake ashes.
It's a fake ashes.
There's a picture here too.
Have you seen this before?
These pictures,
what does it have to do with the Celestial Immortals?
What's wrong?
I think I know.
I want to know
why Uncle Lin and the others have become like this.
What is it?
Look.
The mark on your heart.
The eternal pain.
It's the Celestial Immortals' medicine?
That's right.
You said the Celestial Immortals' medicine
is a lie.
That's right, Brother Jiang.
You can't talk nonsense.
According to the painting,
the Nine-tailed Fox gave the Celestial Immortals' medicine to the Celestial Immortals.
The Celestial Immortals gave the medicine
to a mysterious family.
It's the Celestial Immortals' family from Yousu.
So the Ghost Wind took the escape from the Yousu people
to stop it.
It must be for the Celestial Immortals' medicine.
Everything is connected here.
No.
It's said that the Celestial Immortals' medicine
is the only way to unify the country.
If the Celestial Immortals' medicine is problematic,
how could it be...
It's to turn those who are alive
into living people.
Only in this way
can we establish a army
that won't be injured or die.
A army that won't be in danger
in the afternoon.
A army that won't be injured or die.
This army
is the real invincible.
It's better to live than to die.
This is what we call
the Celestial Immortals' medicine.
It's not the Celestial Immortals' medicine.
It's obviously a lie
that someone who doesn't have any intention
used to make war.
Who is it?
Catch her!
Bring her here.
Granny Su?
Brother Shoujun.
What's wrong with this granny?
Why are you treating her like this?
Miss Su, you don't know.
Today, this granny is pretending to be a ghost.
She almost killed the Crown Prince.
Su?
Your surname is Su?
What's your name?
My surname is Su.
My name is Qingqing.
Qingqing?
You are Qingqing?
You are Xiao Ying's daughter, Qingqing?
Heaven is far away.
We have a Su clan.
We have no ancestors.
Granny Su,
do you not know that Qingqing is still alive?
Back then,
those people from the other clans
were so cruel
to the common people of the other clans.
You and Kunwu
as the descendant of the Saintess,
were so naive and naive.
I thought,
how could I escape
their hands?
Later,
I accidentally
went to the other clans
and heard
that the King of Zhongli
would sacrifice you.
Someone
wanted the Saintess's skin
but it was the Valley of Gods.
I knew that you were still alive.
I tried my best
to escape from the village.
I wanted to find you.
It's okay, Granny.
But
what did you just say?
What kind of magical power
does the Valley of Gods have?
The Valley of Gods?
Yes.
What's that sound?
Someone is coming.
What's wrong, Granny?
What's wrong?
Hurry,
go into the Lulidang with them.
Is someone coming, Granny?
Listen to me. Hurry,
go with them.
Hurry.
The sound is getting closer. Hurry.
Everyone, leave.
Go with them.
Hurry.
Qingqing, take this.
It records everything
that happened in the Su Village.
You'll know what the clans
went through after you see it.
Take it with you.
Go.
Granny.
If it's really
what the wall said,
that the Longevity Deity Herb is problematic,
do we still have to bring this
harmful thing back to the capital?
No matter how good or bad
the Longevity Deity Herb is,
how it should be used,
it's none of our business.
If the Longevity Deity Herb is used by the evil,
then the people of my Shang Mountain
will be involved.
The people's business is the king's business.
You can't control it.
If the people of Shang Mountain
can't be controlled,
who's the leader of Shang Mountain?
Enough. Stop arguing.
We're just guessing.
What's the use of the Longevity Deity Herb?
We'll know after we find it.
What's going on?
Someone just flashed by.
Today is really unlucky.
Ju Li, did you see clearly
what he looks like?
No.
This person must be related to that drum.
It's that damn drum again.
I should have kicked it twice just now.
We were careless.
I didn't expect his accomplice
to come so soon.
A hidden,
hidden, and unshaken thing.
Someone came out to fight with you.
The evil spirit of the Longevity Deity Herb
is here.
What kind of hero is he?
Stop arguing.
It's so unlucky today.
Why don't you let me say more?
What are you doing?
Dig a hole and climb out.
You can dig a hole so hard?
I don't know which idiot
made this secret room.
Who made this kind of secret room?
No.
When did you two laugh?
I'm the only one who's afraid of
being stuck here, right?
These secret rooms and the cave outside
were made by the ancestors of the You Su clan.
Since they want to inherit the descendants of their ancestors,
they can't build a secret room
that's so quiet.
Then, the Dragon Stone at the door,
the stone door,
it's more like preventing the outsiders from coming in and going out.
The purpose
should be to protect something
from being taken out.
There's nothing to take out.
Look over there.
Aren't there just some decorated stone sculptures?
Look behind you.
Is there a light?
What's so special?
The whole secret room is closed.
But there's only one light.
Yes.
Why is that?
We'll know when we try.
This shadow is pointing at the valley.
Could this be the secret room?
This secret room is to protect her.
Look.
This should be the map of the secret room.
This position.
We should be able to find the exit.
There's really no way out.
I'll just say it.
I'm lucky.
How can I find the exit?
I'll just say it.
I'm lucky.
Let's go, Brother Chong.
Find the exit.
What's wrong?
This is the sign of the sacred temple.
Where's the girl?
I'm going to see Aunt Su.
If she's alright, she'll come to see us later.
If something happened to her,
what's the point of her going?
I can't leave her alone.
You can't go.
You can't leave her alone.
I'll go with you.
You can't go.
You can't leave her alone.
I can't leave him alone
Miss, there is a long story
How can we explain it to Lord Gu Xi
and the Crown Prince Zhu Wei?
I have no credit
and no effort these days
Please forgive me
Qingqing
You are back
Did you find any clues?
It's a long story
I have been working for the
Immortal Medicine of the Hu Hou Yi clan
and the Holy Valley
to pacify the chaos and build the Shangshan
Now the divine power is back
The mountain collapsed
and the people were angry
This is an ominous sign
In order to show my regret
I returned the divine power to the upper hall
From now on
the nine Hu Hou Yi tribes
are divided into the two tribes of the Tushan of Yousu
The Yusu clan preserves the holy valley
and the foreign country far away
The Tushan clan guards the immortal medicine
The two tribes have been inseparable
due to Ning Zhou
If the immortal medicine and the holy valley are together again
the nine states will be destroyed
and the world will be in chaos
The holy valley and the immortal medicine
The Tushan clan in the legend
actually came to the same place as us
If it is said by the will of God
the immortal medicine
should be managed by Tushan
But the change of Ning Zhou a few decades ago
Ning Bo Hou should not have got nothing
Or before this
someone has already found it
If the immortal medicine
is really as the painting says
will turn people into monsters
Then this immortal medicine
is likely to be in the middle of the age
a few years ago
and then there will be a change of Kun Fu
Then the ancient immortal medicine
is going to be in chaos
if it is held again
Today I met the mother of Su in the forest
In order to protect me
she led the people of the Ghost Clan away
and left this to me
It is the evil done by the Su family
over the years
The evil done by the Su family?
Cut off the skin
The Su family
has its roots
and is rooted in the holy temple
It is not the will of God
to change one's power and body
I was born as a Saintess
I didn't want to protect myself
I pretended to be a fool for many years
and then I was killed
But I was also killed
The Su family is forever in danger
I was ordered by the Saintess
to return to the Su family
to keep the promise of the Su family
to the immortal
The way Qui Fang set up an army
killed the mixture of the Monk and The equipment
and killed the chancellors
and the same killer
as the Du holla
the day I die
I will change myself
Be a member of the other clan
and dan Capital
So, other than the little girl,
Granny Su actually has the Holy Blood of the Saintess.
Granny Su, in order to save us,
is still in danger of death.
Her whereabouts are unknown.
Wait.
If, as you said, the ancient medicine of the gods is already in our hands,
we have already seen the ancient medicine today,
then where is the medicine?
Everyone, we seem to have overlooked one thing.
Qingqing said that Granny Su
knew that Qingqing wanted to escape from Qingluan Mountain
several times before she died.
She has been there. She is a member of the Su clan.
She is familiar with the terrain.
She asked me to open the Central Plains and guard the border.
The Gui Fang people are not familiar with the area.
They asked me to open the Central Plains and guard the border.
How did the Gui Fang people
enter Qingluan Mountain?
How did they stay in front of the Central Plains and guard the border for several years?
What you mean is...
First,
they know how to enter the secret passage of Qingluan Mountain.
Second,
behind them, there are extremely powerful Central Plains and guard the border.
Helping them to cover up.
Hiding here if they find out that the four spending men
joined the SecretToo 찍才一起来
The Fifth,
the right-hand person was toopieces and flighty.
What?
What did you think of now?
What is it?
The extremely powerful Central Plains
can't be Xian Xuanji, can it?
But it's not good for you.
Mr. Jiang.
The guards of Mount Jin are looking for people.
They've found the way.
You can go back to the city soon.
Don't make more troubles.
We'll solve the problem of the separation.
We won't bother you.
Okay.
We don't want to cause any trouble.
But the real man...
I have a message for you.
Don't believe the people around you.
My Lord.
Jiang Wenhuan and the others have found the valley.
Nonsense.
Nonsense?
We transferred the valley to them
before they were prepared.
We also caught the old living people who had been hiding for years.
I didn't expect that the saintess was hiding.
There are others.
Go to prepare.
Yes.
After so many years,
it's time to make a move.
So,
there's no trace of the man.
I've visited Guifang for many times.
I know he's the new noble
who rose up in Guifang's nobility.
His origin and whereabouts are very mysterious.
After the case of the Eastern Courtyard,
he didn't return to Guifang.
Instead,
he disappeared.
That means
the imperial guard was established in Donglu City.
The envoy of Guifang appeared.
The imperial guard went to the Zhongli for medicine.
The envoy of Guifang disappeared.
The imperial guard means
his target may be
the imperial guard?
Not the imperial guard.
The imperial guard is the immortal medicine
the princes are looking for.
Get a carriage.
I'm going out.
No, your highness.
You're just getting better.
You need to rest well.
You can't keep this little thing.
Little thing?
He's well-prepared.
He even dares not to underestimate me.
I must go there in person.
Zhongli?
No.
Mount Tu.
Mount Tu?
There must be
some clues that have been ignored.
Your time has come.
Young lady.
I'm sorry.
Your highness, you're in a good mood today.
Dream comes true.
Year comes true.
Who knows the past?
The stars in the world
are like the stars.
The white-haired man is like the red-haired man.
The young man meets the wind as the shadow of the moon.
He is not ashamed of the world and his love.
The hatred is deep.
The red-haired man is like the red-haired man.
The young man meets the wind as the shadow of the moon.
Your Massachusetts.
Your continuance.
Your tortilla Turns into an management system.
25 years is just an вз 살.
Words cannot be Tesla.
He doesn't even have a number.
My relationship with you is non-tailing.
What is it?
The moon's long 집.
This sword is so that you have to get it once before entering the harem.
Please make itидioper homosexual.
Happy Rain season.
I'm happy about the gourmet of this world.
I'm fine with that now.
I ate too much and I'm a little الأowski.
Thanks, Ninth God.
It's ok.