(All places, organizations, characters,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
Ultimately, I couldn't convey my true feelings,
and we missed each other.
(I like you.)
We were too far away from each other...
to undo the moment we missed each other.
(Lee Dong Ha)
(Junior Chun Choon Shik)
(Junior Bang Ho Dong)
(Bani's Birthday)
(Thursday, February 5, 2026)
(Delete event?)
(Yes)
(Thursday, February 5, 2026)
During that one year,
a gap that couldn't be closed...
formed in our hearts.
(1 year later)
- Bani!
Bani.
My sweetheart. Great work.
Good job out there.
You guys had it tough hanging out with my parents...
while I was gone.
No way. You had it tough coming back to Korea.
I didn't hit me until last night.
But you're really back.
Gosh, my sweetie.
You went through so much in such a faraway country.
I'm sure living without us in a foreign country...
- was a challenge.
- Goodness.
- Look at all your tears.
- Gosh.
Stop crying.
Some might think I'm leaving and not returning.
She's right, Mr. Ban. We should hold her welcome-back party.
Let's go. I'll make a huge feast.
- Come on.
- I'll do it.
- Let me.
- I'll push it.
- Goodness, it's been ages.
- Let's go.
Nice timing.
I was about to order dinner.
What's this?
Why are you still here at this hour?
Don't you have a date today?
I don't,
but it's not by choice.
How come?
Bo Bae is having dinner at Bani's...
You see...
Bani came back to Korea today.
She's returning to school this semester.
It was only for a year.
But seeing Bani here still feels unreal.
Me too.
Me being here right now feels like a dream.
It'll be worse at school, right?
That'll be dreamy in a different way.
You're now the so-called bloody junior.
Stop it.
Didn't Won come back last week?
He did.
He wanted to have a get-together once I was back in Korea.
That's a given.
I will soon set a date for it.
What about you, Bo Bae? Are things okay with your boyfriend?
I guess.
Dong Ha must be in total bliss.
Of course.
He’s been on a roll since he started dating her.
Not long ago, he and Yeol...
They...
created something together.
It's already a big hit.
Bani.
You and Yeol never talked after you left for the US, right?
No.
You two will bump into each other at school.
Will you be okay?
We're not in the same department.
And I won't have time for other things...
while adjusting to school.
I applied for a work-study scholarship.
When did you do that?
Oh, right. I need to enrol in an elective.
Do you have any recommendations?
How about the elective I'm taking?
I heard it's an easy class.
- What is it?
- History of popular music.
But I wonder if it's still open.
(Class Enrolment)
(Class: History of Popular Music)
There's one spot left.
I got it.
Things are looking good already.
On that note, Bo and Bani. Let's toast again.
- Cheers!
Good thing we made the effort to come out here, right?
It's not cold either.
Is it because I'm with you?
No, because I've got heater packs.
I'm kidding.
Of course, it's not cold because you're with me.
Come here.
Bani came back to Korea today.
She's returning to school this semester.
(Episode 11: An Unexpected Reunion)
Hello, students.
This is YEBS' 60th batch announcer, Nam Kot Nim.
It's Kot Nim.
After a long winter, the warm spring has come...
along with the new semester.
What comes to mind when you think about...
the excitement of a new semester?
As for me, the campus couple,
the flower of college life, pops into my head.
Even now, some must be spending a lovey-dovey time...
with their loved one somewhere on campus.
What's with you?
One sweet honey mocha campus couple set, please.
All right.
My girlfriend, the prettiest in the world, will drink one of the mochas.
Please make it special.
- Okay.
- Can I get my stamp here?
No way.
But today must not be exciting and sweet to everyone.
If you meet your ex-campus lover...
by coincidence on campus,
today might be the worst day of your life.
Even so, I hope you have...
more heart-fluttering moments on your first day of the semester.
- Hyun Seung Min.
- Here.
- Kim Chae Yeon.
- Oh Yu Ri.
- Here.
- Jung Min Ju.
(Week 1)
Ban Hee Jin.
I'm here.
(Class Enrolment)
(Search Results)
You had it tough since morning, right, Bo Bae?
After all, the semester started today.
Where else hurts?
Your shoulders? Knees? Or feet?
No, I'm better now.
You must be tired too. Get some rest.
This is me taking a rest.
I'm recharging with my hands.
That's really cute.
You are too.
What? What is it?
I never thought you had that side in you.
I go all in on whatever I do.
You sure do.
By the way, what have you been looking at since earlier?
He needs to enrol in another elective.
What?
I feel like I've heard something similar last night.
Just enrol in whatever class you can.
But there isn't any, okay?
Gosh. Is it that full?
(Classes)
How can she do a full lecture on day one?
Exactly.
The so-called deadly junior year has really hit me now.
Hey. We, the seniors, have it worse, okay?
The graduation project and job hunting.
My future already looks pitch black.
It feels weird that we're already at the age of job searching.
By the way, what about Won? Is he not returning to school yet?
No. He's currently in Korea,
but he'll soon leave for the US.
- What a bummer.
- It is.
Putting that aside, how was it in the US?
Tell us about your study abroad.
I'd love to.
But my elective starts soon.
I'll give you the details next time.
Come on. It's a promise, okay?
I promise. I'm leaving first. See you later.
Hi. I'm reaching out...
from "University Today," a campus magazine.
I’m reaching out in hopes of...
interviewing you for our upcoming new semester special.
"University Today?"
(Your wait listed course is open.)
(Class: History of Popular Music)
(You have been enrolled.)
(Timetable)
I got in.
Bani.
- Hey.
- Hi.
(History of Popular Music)
- Did you eat?
- No.
The professor gave a full lecture.
I had to come right away.
I should've packed you a sandwich.
No, it's okay.
Dong Ha is also taking this class. Are you okay with it?
Of course. It's not like we're strangers.
- Bo Bae!
- Dong Ha!
I see. I didn't know Bani was here.
Lee Dong Ha.
Hey.
What brings you here?
(Lecture Room 8)
I got into this class just now.
What?
Let's go inside.
Jae Yeol.
What is it?
You see...
I heard from somewhere that this class was a mess.
The professor is super strict.
There are no breaks either.
Why don't we take a different class?
No way. I barely got this one.
Please.
Take this class, and you'll regret it for life.
Believe me. I beg you.
(History of Popular Music)
- Why isn't he coming inside?
- I know, right?
I'll get us a much better class.
One hundred times better?
No, 1,000 times better. Please?
If that's what you wish.
You can go alone.
(Lecture Room 8)
The lectures will be hands-on.
We will be listening to music.
(Evaluated with Reports)
We will be looking back on the history of popular music.
Let's wrap up here and I'll see you all in the regular class.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
It's not like I didn't expect it.
If he had been happy to see me, that would've been weird.
It's okay.
Do you like Solomon's seal tea by any chance?
Ji Won.
I feel so much better now.
I missed Korea so much because of this.
Who feels homesick because of cafeteria food?
It's not cafeteria food. It's special food.
Seeing you say that...
makes it feel like no time has passed at all.
I feel the same.
Until when are you going to stay in Korea?
I'll probably go back with Hye Won in a month.
That's sooner than I thought.
It seems Hye Won has been doing well.
I saw her having a party on social media.
She neglects her studies.
She's busy having fun.
Have you met Yeol?
Yes. I saw him,
but it seemed he'd already moved on.
I thought we might be able to go back to how it used to be...
once we saw each other again.
But it was my selfish desire.
Since I'm here, it'd be nice to see Bo Bae and Kot Nim.
Would they be busy?
I actually told them...
- that you were back.
- Oh, they're over there.
Ji Won.
- How have you been?
- Great.
Take a seat.
This drink I have at the start of the semester.
I go to college just for this.
By the way, why are you guys still in school?
Did you decide not to join the military?
Gosh, I was so happy until now.
- Dong Ha.
- What?
I'll join the military next semester.
Don't be sad when we're gone.
He doesn't understand you.
I know. He hasn't changed.
Yeol, is everything okay?
You look more sentimental now.
I agree.
Come on. People might think you bumped into your ex...
on the first day of the semester.
They're fated if he did.
No way.
You can't fool me.
You didn't, right?
Will you really be okay?
- With what?
- Taking the same class with Bani.
Oh, no.
I should just cancel it.
Both of us will feel uncomfortable.
Why would you feel uncomfortable?
You said he pretended he didn't see you.
You should just ignore him and not worry about it.
He might've acted like that because he was flustered.
It might be different when you guys meet next time.
As if she wasn't flustered.
Even so.
"It's been a while. How have you been?"
He could've greeted her like that at least.
Dong Ha said...
once he turns away, he never looks back.
And that he's cold and heartless.
He could feel that way.
Honestly,
I think I was selfish.
It's all in the past.
Why would I not be okay with it now?
But still, taking the same class with her...
is a completely different matter.
I don't care.
Let's put our hands together.
Hey.
Hey. You drank so much soju.
Did you drink it all at once?
Hey, where are you going?
A convenience store.
What?
I had no idea!
I didn't mean to do that.
It's not difficult to ask her how she has been.
- Okay!
- Oh, gosh.
I lost again.
You said you're bad at sports. Why are you so good at this?
I was on the basketball team until high school.
That's why you wanted to play basketball.
Oh, my gosh. I was scammed.
You lost anyway.
So you buy us drinks as you promised.
Okay. I'll have...
any carbonated drink.
I want something cold.
Okay. I'm going to play this again once I'm back.
So wait right here. Okay?
Yes!
Let's play one more time.
(50 percent discount when using convenience store pay)
Thank you.
Sure.
I guess you came to buy beverages.
Yes.
This is really good.
Yes. I thought so.
Yes.
Are you going to drink them all?
What? No. These are for my friends.
I see.
- Would you like to have one?
- No. I drank...
No.
I drank a lot of water.
Okay.
Bye then.
Jae Yeol.
Yes?
That drink...
Oh, I'm sorry.
You have your hands full. Let me open it for you.
No.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
I'll throw this away.
Bye then.
As expected.
I think it's a little salty. Try it.
What?
- It tastes good.
- It does?
Bani, eat a lot.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Did you say hi...
to your friends yesterday?
Yes.
Everyone must've been so happy to see you.
No.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
I'll throw this away.
Bye then.
Not everyone was.
- What?
- Sorry?
- It's nothing.
Oh, right. Is today your first day working at the library?
Yes.
It must be hectic as soon as you're back in school.
I was almost late.
Jae Yeol. You left this yesterday.
- Thanks.
- What happened yesterday?
You said you would go... to a convenience store,
but you went home without telling us.
I know.
Why do you ask?
He mustn't have been in the mood to drink.
Actually, taking the same class with Bani...
was bothering you too, right?
- No, it wasn't.
- Don't deny it.
Never mind. You won't see her anyway.
What?
What did you say?
Bo Bae said Bani might drop the class.
Honestly, it must be uncomfortable for her too.
Even I feel uncomfortable.
Jae Yeol, what's done is done.
Just let the past go...
and come with us to the group blind date.
- Finally?
- Yes.
Jae Yeol, I think the time has come.
You can just sit still.
We'll take care of everything.
Just give up everything, will you?
Do you think he's crazy enough to go on a group blind date?
Do you think he'll date someone else in the college?
Who cares? We're still young.
- Young, my foot.
- We're young and full of passion.
- Jae Yeol, just once.
- Just once.
Please.
I'm not going to date someone in the college anymore.
So don't you ever say that again.
Hey.
Are you holding hands?
Say hello to her.
This is my girlfriend.
Oh, my gosh.
Jae Yeol, are you not going to class?
- Why are you so clueless?
Did you not want to go on a group blind date?
Will you set us up?
You won't.
(Main Library)
I'll show you how to register the barcodes next time.
For today, please organize these books...
and set up the banners.
- Are you okay with that?
- Sure.
All right then.
Yes.
When my head is a mess, I'd better just get to work.
(List of Returned Books)
Sorry.
It's okay.
What is wrong with me?
Bani might drop the class.
Honestly, it must be uncomfortable for her too.
Even I feel uncomfortable.
(Yein University)
(Timetable)
(Class: History of Popular Music)
(Library Reading Stamp Tour)
(Arts University)
(It's on the Arts University Student Council!)
I...
must be broken.
must have feelings for you.
Thanks.
(Library Reading Stamp Tour)
Don't...
drop that class.
I'll drop it instead.
See you.
(Creative Work of Art by Youth)
(Class Enrolment)
(Class: History of Popular Music)
(Withdrawal from the class is final once processed.)
(Are you sure? No, Yes)
What did you foolishly expect?
(Now Open, Dino Fit)
I'm good.
I said I was good.
I'm already strong enough, so I don't need the gym.
What's your problem?
I already know you're quite strong.
What did you just say?
(University Today New Semester Interview Proposal)
(University Today, Kim Hui Jeong)
So, you want to interview me?
That's right.
The concept for this semester...
highlights cool college boys studying art or fitness.
I believe you're the student who best fits that concept.
Just so you know, we selected...
Jin Hyun Oh at Gaun University as the PE major student.
He is just as recognized,
and he has already agreed to the interview.
Hyeon?
Thanks.
Of course. He was Bani's first love.
It's been a while.
What...
What are you doing here?
I was helping out a friend who just opened a gym.
But then,
I came across someone who was gifted in this field.
It's been so long. How long has it been?
We haven't seen each other since you moved away,
so it's been six years.
Not for me.
She hasn't changed a bit.
What?
Can I get your Instagram?
Sure.
He must really be popular.
He's good-looking.
Why are you looking him up?
I got curious.
But you're better looking.
- Whatever.
- You're doing it, right?
No. I can't be bothered.
Opportunities like this don't come by often.
Take this chance to promote Handsome Dolphins.
Do it for the team as the leader.
Come on.
Seriously.
Hold on. I study art as well,
so why didn't they reach out to me?
Could it be because I look young for my age?
They must think I have a baby face.
Say something, will you?
It's been a while.
I guess.
Are you back in school now?
No, I just had some business at the department office.
Sure.
Get going, then.
Can we talk?
While I was in the US,
I wondered how you were doing.
I doubt we were close enough...
for us to be thinking about one another.
I guess you grew on me before I even realized it.
You see,
this had been weighing on my mind.
I was worried that I came between you.
But,
I no longer have feelings for Bani.
I moved on long ago,
and now we're nothing more than good friends.
Why are you going through...
this trouble of telling me that?
It's always been you for Bani.
When she was in Korea and in the US.
Excuse me.
Where's the Sculpture Department?
Oh, right.
Go straight this way and turn left.
Right.
No way.
Am I in the right place?
Hello?
Bani, I'm here.
What?
Spring sure smells nice.
- Why did you style your hair today?
- What?
- Are you dating someone?
- Because it's spring.
It's not a good look on you.
- Maybe he has a date.
- Guys, I'll get going.
Hey, it's Jin Hyun Oh.
Who?
He plays basketball at Gaun University.
He played competitively and has been popular since high school.
He often plays basketball on our court too.
Right. Jin Hyun Oh.
I think I heard his name recently.
Oh, it's him.
The PE major chosen by "University Today."
Yes, that's him.
Hold on.
Why is he with Yeol's ex-girlfriend?
- Why you...
- Shut it.
They seem friendly.
- What?
- Seriously?
- Come on.
- Where's your common sense?
Darn it.
(Something is going on between Bani and Hyun.)
Who is this?
A guy who lived next door.
He's not just a guy.
You look suspicious.
What? No.
Hey, why are you looking at it so closely?
Come on. It's more suspicious when you're trying to hide it.
Was he...
your first love or something like that?
No. It's not like that at all.
Her first love.
Her first love!
Is he still not over her?
- Shut it.
- Quiet!
What brings you to my school?
I had a basketball game with my friends.
I thought we could meet up since I was already here.
Do you come here often to play basketball?
Fairly often.
But I don't come here just to play basketball.
I come here for other reasons too.
I was here the year before last for the Art School Festival.
The year before last? I was here back then.
We could've bumped into each other.
I actually wrote something for you.
What was it?
A Confession Tree card.
(I want to enjoy the first snow with you.)
(I want to spend Christmas with you.)
(Bani, I want to spend Christmas with you.)
You're the one who wrote that?
Yes.
I never thought it could be you.
I remembered...
how our families used to celebrate Christmas together.
Well, I didn't get to spend Christmas with you that year.
By the way, you haven't changed a bit.
You haven't grown since you were a kid.
No way. I've grown at least a centimetre taller!
What are you doing this weekend?
Me?
I don't have anything planned. Why?
I've never been on a set like this before.
Seeing how you're doing a fancy interview like this,
you must be famous, indeed.
Hey, Bani.
What? What are you doing here?
One of my seniors asked me to help on the set at the last minute.
But what are you doing here?
Oh, him?
He used to be my next-door neighbour until middle school.
He said he was doing an interview, so I tagged along.
- Then he's your first crush?
- Hey!
You know what? I'll let you guys get acquainted.
Hello. I'm Bani's best friend. My name is Nam Kot Nim.
I look forward to working with you today.
I hope you and Bani have a good time today.
Thanks.
We'll start shooting now.
Wait. Where's the other guy?
I'm right here.
This is my better side.
What on earth has gotten into them?
(New Semester Interview)
All right. Jae Yeol, you're also a key member...
of a creative group, Handsome Dolphins.
We hear that you have already received...
many offers from prominent production companies.
How does it feel?
Our creative works were well-received by many people.
I'm grateful for that.
As you are already building a solid career,
we're curious to find out about your goal after graduation.
I will focus on growing my team for the time being.
I'd like to create something original...
instead of joining someone else's project.
My goal is to grow Handsome Dolphins...
into an independent production group,
not a mere creative group.
I see. This is the last question.
Are you guys...
Are you guys currently in a relationship?
Jae Yeol, could you answer that first?
No.
I'm sure you're quite popular on campus.
Why are you not dating anyone?
I just...
want to focus on my creative work now.
Then what about you, Hyun Oh?
I have never been in a relationship.
That's unexpected.
Nothing ever captured my heart the way sports did.
Nothing except for one person.
My first love.
- Your first love?
- Yes.
Great job today.
You can expect to be paid sometime this week.
- I see.
- Oh, right. Here you go.
It's a ticket to ride the hot air balloon...
over the Han River.
If there's someone special, you can take her there.
Thank you.
This is a ticket to ride the hot air balloon.
Do you want to ride it with me tomorrow?
Why not?
Nothing except for one person.
My first love.
This is a ticket to ride the hot air balloon.
Do you want to ride it with me tomorrow?
Why not?
Could you drop me off here?
Sure.
Thank you.
(Complimentary Voucher for 2, Hot Air Balloon at Han River)
It's always been you for Bani.
When she was in Korea and in the US.
Dong Ha, can you come with me...
I'm sorry. I'm going hiking tomorrow with Bo Bae.
Hey, the movie is starting. I'll talk to you later.
(Cha Ji Won)
Hello?
Do you like...
hot air balloons?
I didn't know this place was still operational.
It's been ages since we came here.
You used to come here all the time.
Stopping by this place was your after-school routine.
This was practically my staple.
- Here you go. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Let's dig in.
You still eat it the same way as before.
This is the best way to enjoy the food here.
Try it now.
It tastes exactly the same.
- It tastes the same, right?
- Yes, totally.
Right. Was the guy from yesterday your ex?
How did you know?
Are you guys currently in a relationship?
Jae Yeol, could you answer that first?
No.
Are you still hung up on him?
Did your taste in guys change?
What?
He's the polar opposite of me.
Your ideal type used to be me.
How did you know that?
It was obvious that you had feelings for me back then.
Gosh, I was only a kid back then.
Slow down.
Hey.
Why must I do this with you on a weekend?
I thought I told you. We're riding the hot air balloon.
I didn't know you were serious.
Who knew you meant it when you said we'd be riding that together?
That's enough.
Since you decided to come, stop complaining and take this.
It's tasty, at least.
I knew it.
You had an ulterior motive for coming here.
Is he Bani's first love?
Jae Yeol.
What are you still doing here?
You're not going to do anything?
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Jae Yeol.
Don't get on it.
What's your problem?
(Crushology 101)
We didn't even have a chance to talk after you came back.
We broke up a long time ago.
But why does it feel like it just ended?
Bani. You're never supposed...
to go back to your ex.
I waited a long time for you. What's on your mind?
Bani. What I wanted...
to tell you was...
I'm sure he's out there.
Someone who will see you for who you are.
Then are you not interested in me?
What do you think about me?
Remember my first love I mentioned?
It was you.
Dramaday.me