Feeling better today?
After resting for two days, I'm much better.
I feel like
I'm pretty useless.
Always needing your help with everything.
Everyone needs help from others sometimes.
What about you?
You Capricorns,
do you ever need help from others?
I don't know about others.
I'm just
used to relying on myself.
Doesn't it get tiring after a while?
Do you have close friends or...
Sure.
Good friends, I have some.
But not the kind you're talking about.
What kind am I talking about?
Hey, do Capricorns
refuse to admit when they're being nice to someone?
What else?
What else? What else is there...?
What other traits do Capricorns have?
Says one thing but means another.
Slow to warm up, cold and aloof.
Don't forget your medicine.
Cheng Hai.
Cheng Hai, I made breakfast.
Let's eat together.
Made specially for me?
No...
Not specially, just made some extra while I was at it.
Quite convenient.
I'm heading to work.
You're in such a rush today?
I saw you working until 4:30 AM last night.
If you keep this up, you'll ruin your health.
There's a difficult project at work recently.
Once this busy period is over, I'll be fine. Don't worry.
Wait, let's go out together.
I'll go in early
to catch up on my work.
Okay.
Cheng Hai.
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm fine.
The cup just accidentally fell.
It's okay, go back to your room.
Cheng Hai, if something's wrong
or if you're not feeling well,
you can tell me.
I said I'm fine.
Leave me alone.
Talk to me about it.
Maybe I can help.
You're so annoying!
I said leave me alone!
Sorry.
It's the company project.
Our team has been working overtime for a month straight.
The contract was about to be signed,
but then the client's entire project got cancelled.
At work,
these things are sometimes hard to avoid.
It's not just your fault.
But I was the one leading this project.
And the company invested a lot in development costs.
No one can be perfect all the time.
Try to let it go.
Even if
you get fired,
when you come home,
I'll still be here.
Try it.
Might be a bit sweet.
It's fine.
Cheng Hai.
From now on, whatever happens,
let's face it together.
Okay?
Maybe for life matters.
But for work,
I can only rely on myself.
I understand.
But sometimes,
if you try to open up a bit more,
many things might become easier.
You mean I need to depend on others?
Not depend, but share.
You can try talking about anything.
Don't bear it all alone.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Whether it's sharing or depending,
as long as it makes you happy,
it's all good.
Mm.
I'm back.
Cheng Hai, who is this person?
Your friend?
An old friend.
Not important.
This person must be
important to you.
Past things
aren't worth mentioning.
Still thinking about the photo?
No, just wanted some time alone.
It's okay.
If you want to ask, just ask.
Don't keep it bottled up.
That person...
Left you a long time ago?
Yes.
Why didn't you
stay together?
Some people
are destined to be just passing through.
Past wounds
just become memories.
But he
still left traces.
The past is the past.
People have to move forward, don't they?
So have you made peace
with the past?
Of course.
I'm already looking forward to my future.
Mm.
Hey,
you Capricorns
are really hard to get close to.
Not really.
I always feel like
there's a wall in your heart.
It keeps people at a distance
and you won't easily express your thoughts.
Come on.
You're overthinking.
Besides,
saying it or not saying it,
is it really that important?
Then what's most important?
Feelings.
Feelings are what matter most.
Words from others might be lies,
but your own feelings
are definitely the most real.
Let's drink to that.