=Roses and Guns=
=Episode 13=
(Several days ago)
(Song Yu'er)
Madam,
don't blame me.
I'm just paid to do this.
You have to die tonight.
Before death,
do you have any words?
Was it Lu Xiangxue that made you do this?
Does it matter?
You're gonna die anyway.
What's the point of asking this?
I don't wanna die.
I have money.
I hid it in a place.
If you let me go,
I'll give you all my money.
After that,
I won't stay in Qin City.
I heard
you were not favored in the Qin family.
How much money do you possibly have?
I wanted to divorce Qin Boyang long before,
so I saved a large sum of money.
Right,
I also have a jade pendant.
Qin Boyang valued it
very much.
It must be worth a lot.
Where is it?
Tell me.
You let me go,
and I'll take you there.
Stop! Come back!
Stop!
- Yunong?
- Stop!
Don't run!
Come back!
What are you doing?
None of your business!
Help me.
It's not over!
We'll see!
Yunong,
great.
I finally found you.
Do you know
that I've cut all ties with my father,
and run away from home?
He can't force me
even if he is the Premier.
Yunong,
we can get married.
what's wrong with you?
Your injury...
(The Premier's stupid son
got the wrong person.)
(But he came just in time.)
I had my head hit,
and can't remember anything now.
Who am I?
Who are you?
Doesn't matter, Yunong.
You probably just can't remember
for the moment.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here,
and I'll be always with you.
Even if you lose your memory,
we can still
fall in love with each other once again.
(Now that I have the Premier's stupid son,)
(I don't have to sell you.)
(Now I'm having such a good life.)
(I really should thank)
(the gangster that kidnapped me
away from the Qin family.)
(But for him,)
(I would never have met Shuyi.)
(He regards me as Wen Yunong
who lost memory,)
(and is so nice to me.)
(I don't wanna go back
to the Qin family ever.)
Shuyi,
what are you doing?
I met the gangster,
and he told me about you.
What did he say?
You are not Wen Yunong,
but Qin Boyang's wife,
Song Yu'er.
I'm not Song Yu'er.
I am Wen Yunong.
You're not!
What are you doing?
Yunong doesn't have this mole.
And she doesn't squander wantonly
and indulge herself in pleasure
like you do!
Song Yu'er,
you've been deceiving me
from the beginning.
I'll never forgive you!
Shuyi!
You go see the doctor
and get the medicine for the fake abortion.
It's really not easy to pretend
to be pregnant.
I was always afraid of being exposed.
Now it's gonna be over.
You can finally rest assured.
Anyway,
thank you.
Go.
Madam, your soup is ready.
(So you're Wen Yunong.)
(Since you became Song Yu'er,)
(why can't I be Wen Yunong?)
(And that Lu Xiangxue...)
(Lu Xiangxue,)
(you frequently found faults with me
in the Qin family.)
Wedding photo?
- Don't!
- Xiangxue.
Song Yu'er!
Boyang!
What happened?
Boyang,
I just
saw her smashing your wedding photo,
and wanted to blame her,
but she pushed me over on the ground!
(And you also had me kidnapped.)
(I'll never spare you.)
Sir,
Lu Xiangxue came to me for help,
but she hesitated to promise me
to incite defection of Qin Boyang.
She is useless.
What do you...
I sent her to Qin Boyang.
Now she grew strong enough
to disobey me.
Then
give her a lesson.
Yes, Sir.
Wise decision.
Remember,
you must make Lu Xiangxue
show her real colors.
What a coincidence.
I'm just about to teach her a lesson.
You just wait at the gate of Qin's house.
When she is dispelled from the Qin family,
she will be at your mercy.
Ask your men
to take her to the Riverside Lane,
right in the run-down house
behind the old locust tree.
Okay.
As you want.
Okay. I'm going.
Doctor,
how is my little grandchild?
Madam, till now,
I don't wanna deceive you anymore.
I've been guilty over these months,
and sleepless over night,
being afraid this is gonna be exposed.
What do you mean?
It's all my fault.
I was so stupid
that I took her money.
In fact,
she wasn't pregnant.
What?
You're lying. I didn't do it.
- Mom, don't believe him!
- She'll find out eventually.
You'd better confess to Madam.
Stop lying again.
Mom, he lied.
- Don't listen to his nonsense!
- You bad woman!
- How dare you deceive me?
- Mom!
Somebody!
- Drive her away!
- Mom!
Mom, I didn't deceive you.
I didn't. Don't listen to him!
Don't listen to him!
Mom, let me explain!
Mom!
Who are you?
You can't be Qin Boyang's wife.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is
whether you wanna live.
I know nothing!
Nothing!
I'll tell you.
Who asked you to do that to Lu Xiangxue?
I don't know who she is,
because she wore a mask.
Where is she now?
In the broken house
behind the old locust tree.
Bring me there.
I've never expected
to get a big fish.
Tell me.
Who are you?
Why would you pretend to be Song Yu'er,
being around Qin Boyang?
Tell me.
You wretch!
Tell me who you are!
Doesn't matter.
You are so tough, aren't you?
I have many ways
to make you talk.
Wait!
Kewen,
what are you doing here?
(Qin Kewen?)
(How come he colludes with the Japanese?)
I'm here to save a person.
Save a person?
Is it her?
If you wanna take Qin City without blood,
you'll have to kill Qin Boyang
and his father.
And to do this,
you'll need my help.
I've accepted your condition.
It's not over the line
to ask you for a person, is it?
Kewen,
who is this woman?
You seem to care about her very much.
She is my woman.