=Roses and Guns=
=Episode 7=
Master,
I've sent Li Shuyi away
at your orders.
Keep searching for Wen Yunong.
Remember,
I want her alive.
Yes.
Please
bless my husband Qin Huai'an
with good health
and safety in battles.
Stop!
Kneel down.
Didn't you hear me?
Have you been out?
I brought meals to Boyang.
Brought meals?
Now that you've married into our family,
you should
stay at home,
wait upon you parents-in-law,
and bear children.
But now,
you're still childless after three years.
Worse still,
you ran away from home again and again.
I should have made Boyang divorce you.
Mom,
I'm sorry.
Stay here on your knees.
If you break your legs kneeling,
maybe
I would spare you this time.
(She suddenly gave me a hard time,)
(which is unusual.)
(Who told on me?)
(And this evil mother-in-law)
(must have repeatedly made things difficult
for Song Yu'er.)
(I gotta do something.)
Evil woman!
You dared to curse me, and even beat me!
Go to hell!
Not only did I tell on you to Madam Li,
I'll also let everyone know who you are,
and ruin your face.
Evil woman!
Go to hell.
It's really you.
Madam, I was wrong!
I'll never do that again.
Please don't beat me!
Your childish tricks
are really disgraceful.
Yes.
It's disgraceful indeed.
Madam,
I won't do that again.
Please forgive me.
It really hurts when you beat me!
(Song Yu'er)
You little good-for-nothing,
let me teach you
how to play some brilliant tricks.
Okay.
Now you can go tell on me.
What?
Mom,
look at Song Yu'er.
You made her on her knees last time,
she didn't obey you
but slipped away secretly.
You must teach her a real lesson this time.
Song Yu'er.
Mom!
I'm sending for the doctor.
You hang on there.
Mom,
are you alright?
It hurts!
You should have been careful.
Let me check it.
Don't worry.
I've learned bone setting.
It hurts even more!
Mom,
it looks
serious.
I'll send for the doctor.
You...
You bad woman!
It's gonna be 100 days to recover
from a foot injury.
Now Li Weiwei is unable to control her.
Nice trick!
Should we let Qin Boyang know the truth?
This is between me and her.
Obviously you still have feelings for her.
Sir,
what are we gonna do now?
Qin Huai'an has been out for battles.
He must have been carrying
the military seal with him.
We can't get it.
No hurry.
He'll be back one day,
then he will find
his men
are working for a new boss.
How much coptis did you put in?
Do you know how bitter it is?
Mom,
the doctor said
you had too much liver-fire,
so you need more coptis to reduce it.
You did it deliberately!
- Mom!
- It hurts so bad!
Get out!
Xiangxue,
take good care of Mom.
She is in poor health, after all.
If she scolds you,
or punish you,
just take it,
don't talk back to her.
If you ever dare to talk back,
I won't spare you.
Mom,
I'm leaving.
Look at those affectations.
What an evil woman!
What are you doing in my room?
Did I give you my permission?
I was gonna ask you the other day.
A rising movie star back then
(Alive with the Wind)
now becomes a nameless concubine.
Are you really happy?
Even you come to mock me?
I'm not mocking you,
I feel sorry for you.
You were in movies
as a star.
Do you know how hard it is
to have a career for a woman?
Why did you give it up?
I couldn't be popular forever,
so I had to marry a man for a decent life.
Don't I?
A decent life?
Pretending to be pregnant,
and scheming and plotting against
another woman,
is it your decent life?
Think about your past.
Are you really happy now?
Of course, I'm not.
But what can I do?
I can't go back anymore.
Please be honest and tell me
if you got involved in
the disappearance of Song Yu'er.
I know nothing.
Qin Boyang won't change your fate.
You should think carefully about
who you can really count on.
Is that you?
It's yourself.
Of course,
I can help you,
and you can help me too.
How about this?
You do me a little favor first.
What have you got in your hand?
Why are you asking this?
Come over.
Give me your hand.
Why do you always give me a hard time?
You made me take off my clothes
when you first met me,
and now you wanna check
what I've got in my hand.
Can't you just let me go?
Let you go?
Of course, I can,
as long as you let me check
if there is the tattoo on your chest.
What a rogue!
See? Now I'm a rogue.
Where is it?
I had nothing in my hand,
but you didn't believe me.