(OTHER'S LOVE)
(IT'S)
(JUST)
(OUR LOVE)
(These brave men's)
(true love)
(Their romantic love)
(that others can't have)
(even if they want to)
(Hyeok-jun)
(Chan-gyu)
(Jeong-hyeon)
(Chang-min)
(Eun-chan)
(Seon-yul)
(Hyeon)
(Jeong-ho)
(His Man)
(The day to make the final choices)
(The last morning the men are together)
(What kind of changes may have happened to the men's feelings over the night?)
(Wriggling)
(Chang-min, who gets up early even on the last day)
(And Hyeon, who's still in his dreams)
(Hyeok-jun and Jeong-ho, who talked for a long time last night)
(Gets up)
(Half asleep)
(Wakes up with Hyeok-jun)
(A glance)
(Did you sleep well?)
Did you sleep well?
M-hm.
(Did you sleep well?)
(M-hm)
M-hm.
(Did you sleep well?)
(M-hm)
Do you want to sleep or wash up?
(Knock)
(The two get along more naturally and become closer after yesterday.)
(Gets into bed again)
(Smiles)
(Jeong-hyeon sleeps in the sweater borrowed from Chang-min.)
(Puffs)
(Returns after washing up)
Brother, are you not getting up?
(Eun-chan)
What time is it?
(is ironing clothes)
(Doing makeup)
(The reason why Jeong-hyeon hurries to do makeup is...)
(Fast steps)
(Arrives at Chang-min's trailer)
(Sweater borrowed from Chang-min)
Hello.
(Give it to me.)
(Sweater borrowed from Chang-min)
Brother, you're wearing your prettiest clothes today.
(Checking)
Me?
(Me?)
(Checking)
Aren't you? Or is it because you're pretty anyway?
You're being mischievous again.
(Frightened)
You've had a long night.
You too.
Yeah, I've had a long night.
(Pats himself)
You didn't sleep well?
I slept splendidly.
Really? That's good.
(Sniffing)
(Ah, it's cold.)
Ah, it's cold.
(Passes him a hand warmer)
(Patting)
(Sit down)
Sit down.
We should have some breakfast.
(Do you have an appetite?)
Do you have an appetite?
You wanna eat this?
(You wanna eat this?)
Um.
(Um)
(You wanna eat this?)
You don't want some?
(Um)
(You don't want some?)
(Craning Craning)
(Having a simple breakfast)
What do the others have for breakfast?
(Gosh.)
Gosh.
(They don't eat.)
(Gosh.)
They don't eat.
(They don't eat.)
(Gosh.)
(Gosh! What should I do?)
They don't eat.
(They don't eat.)
(Gosh.)
Gosh! What should I do?
(Gosh! What should I do?)
What's wrong? Did you spill it?
(What's wrong? Did you spill it?)
(Yeah, it's messed up now.)
Yeah, it's messed up now.
(What's wrong? Did you spill it?)
(Yeah, it's messed up now.)
It couldn't be more messed up.
(Jeong-ho has been taking care of Hyeok-jun who keeps making blunders.)
Ah, it's hilarious.
(Embarrassed)
No, let me do it.
I was wondering why there was no accident today.
Exactly. Nothing has changed.
(Time to make the final choices)
(In what way will the men become couples?)
I want to see it too.
(Message to the men)
(Now it's the time for the final choice. Please check the final task outside the trailers.)
Now it's the time for the final choice.
Please confirm the final task outside the trailers.
(Now it's the time for the final choice. Please check the final task outside the trailers.)
(Oh, my god. There seems to be a task.)
Oh, my god. There seems to be a task.
Wait, is there anything outside the trailers?
(Mailboxes with the men's names on and letter paper inside)
Let's go.
What task will it be?
It's about to end now.
Shall we meet every day after we leave here?
Sure. Why are you even asking?
Where is the task?
Ah, over there.
Brother.
Come here.
Did you read the message?
Brother, it said this is the final choice.
It asked us to confirm the last task.
Please write down your real phone number
and put it in the mailbox of the man you want to be a couple with.
(Only those who eventually become couples will know each other's number.)
Only those who eventually become couples
will know each other's number.
(Only those who eventually become couples will know each other's number.)
(The task of the final choices
Please write down your real phone number and put it in the mailbox of the man you want to be a couple with.)
(Only those who eventually become couples will know each other's number.)
If we want to know everyone's number,
couldn't we just put our numbers in every mailbox?
What if you get many other opportunities?
I have no idea. I don't know yet.
(Hyeok-jun and Jeong-ho come out a little late.)
(A glance)
Write a random number like 112.
I feel regretful that I didn't get the chance.
I'll take the paper to write a letter.
What's on one's mind is only known to himself.
(Hesitating)
I think there's nothing more disturbing than that.
I don't know.
What if I put it in the mailbox of someone else?
I thought a lot and I was so distressed.
My heat hurt a little.
Our real phone numbers?
I'm still not sure about your feelings.
But I really mean it.
I worried for a long time last night.
I must express all my feelings.
That's what I thought.
(Time to express feelings to the men they want to be a couple with.)
(Who do the eight men have in their hearts?)
I didn't regret any single moment.
I don't regret my choice.
I don't know who to choose between the two.
I felt a little uneasy.
What if he doesn't give me his number?
I was thinking, "Who shall I choose?"
I want to talk more with him.
From the very beginning...
Shall I give it to the friend who I want to get his number?
It isn't over yet.
Who knows?
The feeling of attachment
will only become stronger other than change.
(What are the men's choices?)
(Grips)
(The last moment of the eight days and seven nights)
(The only man in the men's hearts)
(Steps forward to convey his real feelings)
(Prudent)
(Time to make sincere choices)
(Will the man I'm yearning for feel the same about me?)
(Time to reveal the final results)
(Who did the men leave their phone numbers to?)
(Rule of the final choices
The men who become couples have each other's real numbers in their mailboxes. The men who fail to make couples have wrong numbers.)
Call the number on the letter in your mailbox. If the man at the other end answers it, you'll become a couple.)
(Will the men's numbers be sent to each other?)
(The eight special yet ordinary men who are looking for true love)
I'm so nervous.
(Their final choices are?)
Do we really have to make the final choices now?
I feel uneasy about it.
Oh, my heart is trembling with tension.
What should I do?
I'm so nervous.
(The men look more nervous than ever.)
(The time to check their mailboxes finally comes.)
(The first to check the mailbox is Chan-gyu.)
What to do?
(Opens the mailbox carefully.)
(The letter in Chan-gyu's mailbox)
He's making the call.
Just make the call like that?
(Makes the call nervously)
(Who did Chan-gyu leave his number to?)
(Chan-gyu is attracted to Seon-yul after the one-on-one dating.)
It doesn't look like Pikachu.
I'll take one and let's share the other one.
You and me?
(Patting)
(Liking to fight in jest, Seon-yul responds actively to Chan-gyu's jokes.)
I'm here to sleep with you.
Let's sleep.
(The two become close quickly.)
Sleep? Come over.
(Seon-yul often amuses introverted Chan-gyu.)
(But)
No, I only flirt with someone because I like him.
How could I flirt with someone I don't like?
(Seon-yul's feeling for Chan-gyu is friendship rather than love.)
(After that, Jeong-ho moved into Men's House.)
Could you come and have a look?
Do I look better with my bangs being put down like this
(Since they became roommates in the quad room, Chan-gyu and Jeong-ho have spent a lot of time together.)
or kept up like this?
You look great even without bangs.
(You look great even without bangs.)
The quad room is the only room where we can sleep together
in one bed.
(Right?)
Right?
(Nodding Nodding)
(Right?)
We sleep in the same bed.
Who do you like best?
You're the one I like best.
Do you know I like another man?
I know.
(I know.)
(Chan-gyu is turned down again.)
(In the end, who's the man remaining in Chan-gyu's heart?)
(Which man will Chan-gyu leave his number to?)
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.
(The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.)
(It looks like he failed.)
What should I do?
(Regretful)
I left my number to Jeong-ho.
(But Chan-gyu didn't receive Jeong-ho's number.)
OK. It's just...
Though I don't know who it will be,
I hope he'll leave with a good man.
(Jeong-ho who cares about Chan-gyu all the time.)
(Chan-gyu, your mailbox is empty.)
(Chan-gyu fails to find a match in the end.)
(Bitter)
(The men become more nervous seeing depressed Chan-gyu who didn't get through.)
I'm so nervous.
No, but what should we do?
(The second one, Hyeon)
I'm so nervous.
(Hyeon checks his mailbox.)
(Who did Hyeon leave his number to?)
Hello.
He's a little shy.
(The two men in Hyeon's heart)
Really?
Get up quickly.
It's time to get ready.
(Sometimes they are like lovers; sometimes close friends.)
Let's go on a date later.
(Let's go on a date later.)
Who do you want to chat with next time?
The man I'm chatting with now.
No, no.
(Hyeok-jun who went on the first date with him)
(And)
(Hyeon who expressed his feelings to Chang-min by letter)
(Can't you tell the Cupid arrow between us?)
It's exactly like this, this, and this.
(Close Intimate)
(Can't you tell the Cupid arrow between us?)
But as I grow older...
(Close Intimate)
(Can't you tell the Cupid arrow between us?)
(Hyeon and Chang-min become closer and closer as they spend more time together.)
We're going to stay in one room.
You guys do whatever you want.
(Please hug me.)
Please hug me.
Can you just hug me?
(Please hug me.)
Cuddle and sleep?
No, I'm shy.
(No, I'm shy.)
(It's hard to tell who Hyeon will leave his number to.)
(Will the man respond to Hyeon's affection?)
(Makes the call nervously)
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.
(The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.)
(Q. Who did you give your number to?)
Me? I gave it to Hyeok-jun.
And why is that?
At the campfire party,
when we talked about what our most memorable date was,
I figured my most memorable date was with Hyeok-jun.
It was the most fun one as well.
That's what I think.
Can you do it?
(The most memorable moment for Hyeon is his first date with Hyeok-jun.)
You look a bit troubled.
No, I can do it. Everything's good.
(The most memorable moment for Hyeon is his first date with Hyeok-jun.)
I seriously doubt it.
All is good.
(The most memorable moment for Hyeon is his first date with Hyeok-jun.)
(Wow)
Wow. It's so amazing.
(Hyeon & Hyeok-jun who have shared unforgettable moments)
If we didn't have that talk about the most memorable date,
I'd probably choose Chang-min.
But after we talked about it,
I felt like I have more feelings for Hyeok-jun.
(Hyeon Your inbox is empty.)
This is a little cruel.
(The third one Chang-min)
(Checking his inbox nervously)
People's mind is just like flipping hands.
It just keeps changing.
So I was worried that what if there's no call for me.
(The two have had countless memories together within the week.)
You need to press harder here.
We got to get this thing up.
(Sometimes caring, other times naughty)
It looks swollen here. It swelled up.
(Jeong-hyeon who always makes others want to look after him)
Yes.
(The two who understand each other better than anyone else)
Looking good.
You must be so happy, right?
(You must be so happy.)
What?
You must be so happy.
(You must be so happy.)
(Did Chang-min choose Jeong-hyeon?)
(Hyeon and Chang-min who somehow got close)
Let's go check out the room.
(Let's go check out the room.)
I'll help you with this.
(Chang-min who is always very amiable with Hyeon)
Do you need help?
It's okay. I can do it.
I wanted to help you.
(I wanted to help you.)
What do you think of…
(A workaholic like me?)
A workaholic like me?
I'm fine with it.
Yeah?
You can always find the time if you like each other.
You can create the place to be together as well.
(You can create the place to be together as well.)
(Was this when he started to consider Hyeon?)
Yeah.
(Will Chang-min choose Jeong-hyeon?)
(Or will he make a couple with Hyeon?)
(The call went through.)
(Startled)
Do I need to answer it?
(Hello?)
Hello?
(Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon who gave their numbers to each other)
Let's go.
(Let's go.)
(The two have now confirmed each other's feelings.)
So shy.
It even got me shy.
(Bye-bye)
Bye bye.
Let's go.
(Now they can hold hands all they want.)
I feel so shy.
The others might have left a fake number.
They won't answer even if you call.
Ah, really?
Only I got shy?
The weather is so nice.
Hello, everyone.
(His Man The first couple Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon)
The weather is great.
Yeah.
(His Man The first couple Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon)
When can we even take a walk like this again?
Yeah.
(His Man The first couple Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon)
I want to have a date with Chang-min first.
It's not super great, but still not bad.
My favorite guy called me.
I'm so happy today.
Now my affection for Chang-min is probably at 80%.
I don't want to get separated from him.
90%... Or 100%?
I have zero doubt about it. It will never change.
Chang-min is the only one I can see now.
(Jeong-hyeon who grew more and more fond of Chang-min)
This is where you should go in weather like this.
So beautiful.
Have you brought food?
(Rapport)
Yeah. Let's eat together.
I got the food.
(Rapport)
Stuffed Fried Tofu Pockets?
Yeah.
Wonderful.
Is there meat in it?
In Stuffed Fried Tofu Pockets?
You are eating way too much meat.
I made only vegetable-stuffed ones.
(Unhappy)
Then I don't want it.
Don't be picky about your food.
You can make Stuffed Fried Tofu Pockets?
I'm a great cook.
Very good at cooking.
True.
Let's keep the same pace.
Let's walk back to Seoul like this.
Cute.
(What's Chang-min's alias in your contacts?)
I've already saved him in my contacts.
As puppy.
He's really like one of those big dogs.
(What's Jeong-hyeon's alias in your contacts?)
Lee Jeong-hyeon. I already saved it.
There might be pet names after we start dating.
I'll just change it then.
(What kind of pet name will you have for Jeong-hyeon?)
What pet name can I give him?
Wicked Witch of the West. She gets melted by water.
She gets cursed when touching the water.
(His Man Couple number 1 Jeong-hyeon Chang-min.)
(The fourth one Eun-chan)
(Checking his inbox nervously)
(The man who has entered Eun-chan's heart since the first day)
I have special feelings for someone.
(Eun-chan who always expresses his feelings honestly)
Thank you. Where did he go?
Why didn't you just call?
(Hyeon-jun has always been one of his options.)
We could talk for 30 seconds yesterday.
Brother.
Yeah.
There's still time. Can you say something more?
What do you want to hear?
I just want to hear…
Hyeok-jun must have someone he likes too.
But I was too selfish and put pressure on him.
(He's worried that his affection might seem selfish.)
(Eun-chan didn't get a response for his affection.)
But I was too selfish and put pressure on him.
I've tried to put an end to it since yesterday.
You are always very honest about your feelings.
That's enough.
(Seon-yul who supported Eun-chan when he was in pain)
You are here to help me?
Yeah.
(Seon-yul who supported Eun-chan when he was in pain)
You haven't eaten much, right?
I ate a lot.
Go have some.
I'm already full.
But after thinking about it.
I think the first date is the most memorable.
I would remember that moment forever.
Very cute.
(Who did this straightforward guy Eun-chan give his number to?)
(Did he also give his number to Eun-chan?)
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.
(The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.)
(Eun-chan goes back to his position with a bitter feeling.)
(Eun-chan Your inbox is empty.)
I got the message saying "your inbox is empty".
My goodness. It's so brutal…
And miserable… No, I have become the miserable heroine.
I already knew
that he wouldn't respond anymore.
I gave my number to Seon-yul.
(Why did Eun-chan choose Seon-yul?)
It's not like Seon-yul and I have to become a couple.
You need a successful match to know his real contact information
and social media account.
I still want to stay in contact with Seon-yul.
So I chose him.
(Eun-chan didn't find his partner in the end.)
(The interweaved hearts of the men)
(The fifth one Seon-yul)
(Is the number in Seon-yul's inbox real?)
There is a phone number.
(There is a phone number.)
(Seon-yul had feelings for Chang-min on the first day.)
I have a very good first impression of you.
Do you want to go for a walk, Chan-gyu?
Chang-min is going to sleep.
(But he gave it up after missing his chance.)
I can have it back in four weeks.
Really?
(But he gave it up after missing his chance.)
Not trying very hard to dress up.
(He had a connection with his same-aged roommate Hyeok-jun on the first day.)
Even a bit old-fashioned.
No way.
(He had a connection with his same-aged roommate Hyeok-jun on the first day.)
(They did not realize the importance of each other from the trivial things in daily life.)
(Watching)
They went again?
(Pay attention)
(Seon-yul was a little late to have a crush on Hyeok-jun.)
I want to hold your hand.
(I want to hold your hand.)
Do you want to try?
Like this.
Like this?
Yes.
(Can Seon-yul and Hyeok-jun's hearts connect?)
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.
(The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.)
Did I talk to Hyeok-jun too late?
Was I too late to see Hyeok-jun?
So it's a pity for me.
Here you are.
(The last choice Seon-yul gave the phone number to Hyeok-jun.)
(Hyeok-jun Eun-chan)
If only I had realized earlier,
and experienced this earlier,
Then maybe Hyeok-jun would have seen me
as someone more important than a friend. It is a pity.
(Seon-yul and Hyeok-jun missed each other in the end.)
(Seon-yul You have a letter from Eun-chan in your mailbox.)
(Seon-yul had no partner in the end.)
(Seon-yul's heart is still in chaos until the end.)
(The sixth one Hyeok-jun)
(Who did Hyeok-jun give his phone number to? Did he also choose Hyeok-jun?)
(The exciting first date Chang-min)
-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
(The exciting first date Chang-min)
Me too.
It is hot today.
(The exciting first date Chang-min)
It's fine for me.
I'm so happy to talk with you today.
(Hyeok-jun called Chang-min twice before.)
We haven't talked much.
Hyeok-jun?
(Hyeok-jun called Chang-min twice before.)
I seem to like Jeong-hyeon more.
So I always choose him.
So actually I was sad,
(So actually I was sad,)
(like there was a hole in my heart.)
like there was a hole in my heart.
(So actually I was sad,)
(like there was a hole in my heart.)
Jeong-ho…
(Jeong-ho chose Hyeok-jun when he was sad.)
Jeong-ho is completely out of my expectation.
I haven't expected that he would write to me.
I think you're a little sloppy.
-I think this part of you is cute.
-Really?
It makes me want to take care of you.
Is there anyone you like in the Men's House?
It's you.
(It's you.)
(Hee hee)
After today,
(I think I've changed my mind after today.)
I think I've changed my mind.
(The distance between them shortened rapidly.)
Are you riding close to me on purpose?
That's a pretty dangerous distance.
(The distance between them shortened rapidly.)
I want to stay next to you but it's dangerous to get too close.
So we need to keep a distance.
(The distance between them shortened rapidly.)
I like you.
(Jeong-ho actively showed his love to Hyeok-jun.)
(You are really really attractive to me.)
You are really really attractive to me.
I'd like to change the order of my call.
I was just worried.
When I was asked to choose who I liked in the beginning,
(I like you right from the start.)
-I chose you.
-Really?
(I like you right from the start.)
(Jeong-ho fell in love with Hyeok-jun without others knowing.)
We are so close now.
If you don't choose me in the end, I would really...
You would really?
I don't know, but it would be so terrible.
Brother, you won't do that, right?
(Can Hyeok-jun and Jeong-ho end up as a couple?)
(A phone call that isn't answered.)
(Surprised)
Hello.
Let's go?
Let's go.
Holding hands.
(Holding hands)
(Hyeok-jun and Jeong-ho gave each other the phone number.)
So embarrassing.
I know.
(Hyeok-jun and Jeong-ho gave each other the phone number.)
With Jeong-ho,
I can feel my heart fluttering.
Thank you for making me feel this way.
So I called you.
I was 100% sure that I wanted to give my phone number to Hyeok-jun.
It isn't that he has to give me his because I gave him mine.
I hope he gave me his because he likes me.
Why are you laughing?
Because you are handsome.
What? I mean it.
It's a lovely day!
Yes.
I want to ride bikes and kayaks.
(What is Hyeok-Jun's contact name?)
I'm going to save it as his full name.
For now, I want to save it as Gwon Hyeok-jun.
Note it in Gwon Hyeok-jun.
Because I want to call his name more.
(What is Jeong-ho's contact name?)
Note it in Jeong-ho first.
What are you doing? How are you?
(What will the first message be?)
Or how was your sleep?
Let's meet someday.
(What will the first message be?)
Can we hang out today? Something like these.
(Chang-min Jeong-hyeon)
(Oh, what happened?)
Oh, what happened?
What？
(Oh, what happened?)
(Ah)
(Wow)
Crazy!
What? When did they get together?
I have no idea.
When did you two start the relationship?
Congratulations!
But you guys look so good together.
-Really?
-Very good indeed.
You guys are more eye-catching.
Not at all.
(The second couple in His Men Hyeok-jun Jeong-ho)
Congratulations, kids!
(No congratulations, kids)
-So the four of us are couples?
-Yeah.
(So the four of us are couples?)
-So the four of us are couples?
-Yeah.
(So the four of us are couples?)
Can I tear this?
(Can I tear this?)
I hope they all fall into the river.
(I hope they all fall into the river.)
I hope you all fall into the river.
I hope they all fall into the river.
(I hope you all fall into the river.)
I hope you all fall into the river.
I'm gonna go push them down.
(I'm gonna go push them down.)
(Just go down.)
I'm gonna go push them down.
(I'm gonna go push them down.)
(Just go down.)
The message is so hurtful.
I guess you all got the message?
Yes, yes.
I got the message.
(Message received)
I am moved.
You have a letter from Eun-chan in your mailbox.
I will always remember that you chose me.
(Thanks)
We can't see the content?
I really think it's a pity.
It is the rule that we cannot know the phone number, and I can accept that.
But I sincerely hope that
Seon-yul can see the content of the letter I gave him.
But in the end, he didn't get to read it.
That's what hurts me most.
I thought for a long time.
I also thought about giving it to someone other than Hyeok-jun.
But if it does make a match,
it's like there's no connection between us.
So it is just a match.
I don't think it is good.
And it's impolite as well.
But Eun-Chan was a real comfort to me.
I hope we can keep our friendship in the future.
It's OK.
I'm pretty anyway.
(I'm pretty anyway.)
(Bye-bye)
Bye-bye.
(Wave wave)
Let's go.
Let's go, there is no need to stay here.
(Let's go, there is no need to stay here.)
Is it over?
We need to meet someone new.
(We need to meet someone new.)
Is it the end?
I also need to date someone.
(I also need to date someone.)
It is really "other's love" now.
(It is really "other's love" now.)
Send them to date.
It is really "other's love" now.
(Send them to date.)
Send them to date.
Bye.
Let's go, we can go find a partner by ourselves.
I want to go find my love.
I'm tired of witnessing other people's love.
(I'm tired of witnessing other people's love.)
(Thank all the audience for watching His Man during this period.)
(His Man)
(Are you happy in the Men's House?)
The eight of us are all friends.
Everyone is nice. I'm glad to meet them.
Though it's not easy to gather us all,
we might get together from time to time in the future.
When we talked about whether we would cry on the last day,
I was like, "Come on,
why would we cry?"
But it turned out I shed tears first.
I said in tears that I didn't want to leave.
I did that first.
Now I understand why people cry
after the wrap of a film, a drama or a variety.
In this process,
I know myself better.
This is a very good experience.
(This is a very good experience.)
I don't think a successful pairing here
can make them a real couple.
One of them may end up as my boyfriend.
(One of them may end up as my boyfriend.)
Anyway, I just didn't find my Mr. Right here.
I'll find him after I get back to my life.
(What do you want to say to the other seven men?)
You must come to watch my performance.
I'll go to visit you, too.
(I'll go to visit you, too.)
I learned a lot about love
instead of getting love.
I learned about new love styles I was unfamiliar with before.
I felt many times that I did some improper things.
I learned to do self-reflection.
After this program ends,
I'll get back to my normal life.
It feels like waking up
(It feels like waking up from a long dream.)
from a long dream.
Everything is like a dream.
(Sobbing)
(Eun-chan can't speak.)
(Gave all his heart away but ended up with pity)
(What is the meaning of Eun-chan's tears?)
(Swollen)
This is a very precious experience.
The memory and experience
only belong to the eight of us,
or the nine of us?
(Or the nine of us?)
Jeong-hyeon sometimes can split.
or the nine of us?
(Jeong-hyeon sometimes can split. That confused me.)
Jeong-hyeon sometimes can split.
That confused me.
(Jeong-hyeon sometimes can split. That confused me.)
There are only eight of us.
I can't believe that it ends just like this.
I don't want to go back to my old life.
That's why I cried.
Everyone is nice.
If I want to write my life story
related to youth,
this show may be my best memory.
In the past, I valued friendship over love.
After meeting Chang-min here,
I might think differently.
I'm looking forward to the future.
(Excited)
I met many nice people here.
I will remember them
for the rest of my life.
I want to watch this show together with them.
This may be the grandest date
I've ever had
in my lifetime.
Also the grandest blind date and encounter.
I don't think I'll have
a more exciting encounter in my life
than I had in this program.
I've changed greatly here.
I'm very grateful for that.
And,
to be honest, this is not easy,
both physically and mentally.
I feel relaxed now that it's finished.
And I have some regrets.
(What kind of memory did the past week leave to you?)
It should be
a beautiful memory.
(Moist eyes)
I didn't want to come at first.
(Finally burst out in tears)
(Hyeok-jun still felt troubled after he decided to attend the show.)
Now I don't know what I was thinking.
I still felt a little burdened after I decided to attend the show.
And,
I was worried that people who know me would watch it.
So I felt a little uncomfortable.
When I first got here,
I didn't get along well with others.
So I kind of regretted it.
But after living together for a period,
I found that everyone is nice.
I don't know if I can still see them in the future.
But I'm grateful for meeting these nice guys.
I'm grateful and happy.
To be honest,
I don't know what will happen to my life,
but I'm not afraid anymore.
(But I'm not afraid anymore.)
I didn't have any gay friends before.
So I wasn't sure
that I like these brothers
because I never had this experience before
or because they were nice people.
This bothered me for a long time.
After talking with them,
I realized that they do these sweet things to their lover.
I'm happy that I learned a lot here.
I got to know myself better after I came here.
People like us
usually hide our nature.
So we often don't know
what our true self is like.
That's what I did.
What is my character?
(What on earth is my true self like?)
What is my real personality and state?
I couldn't figure them out.
(What on earth is my true self like?)
But after I came here, I saw people of my kind.
We went through a lot together.
These experiences made me know myself better and find the true self.
(Find my true self.)
Of course, I also harvested love and friendship.
I gained a lot here.
(Letters to the men)
I don't think I can read this.
Thank you.
Oh, I got two.
(Um)
It turned out Chan-gyu also wrote me a letter.
Chan-gyu just put his number on it.
I wrote a short letter to Hyeok-jun.
I'm happy because of you.
This is a great experience.
(I'm happy because of you.)
This is my letter to Hyeok-jun.
I'll read it in front of you.
(I wrote this as they asked me to. Let's not keep in touch.)
I wrote this as they asked me to. Let's not keep in touch.
Thank you, but
you're not my type, boy.
(You're not my type.)
(Hee-hee)
His phone number is on it.
Heart shape. I really like you.
(I really like you. From Jeong-ho.)
That is what the letter says.
He is pretty cute sometimes.
(010 I really like you)
Hello, thank you for letting my heart flutter
(Hello, thank you for letting my heart flutter
in this short period. From Hyeok-jun.)
Hello, thank you for letting my heart flutter
in this short period.
(Hello, thank you for letting my heart flutter
in this short period. From Hyeok-jun.)
That is what the letter says.
We suit each other.
He said I made his heart flutter.
I did those things out of sincerity.
I appreciate it that he got moved.
I wrote a letter to Seon-yul.
(Wish you happiness and no more suffering.)
(Moved)
Wish you happiness and no more suffering.
(Wish you happiness and no more suffering. From Eun-chan.)
This letter swept away all my suffering
in the past eight days and seven nights.
Oh, I expected too much.
Please help me with my makeup, room chief.
(Please help me with my makeup, room chief. From Chang-min.)
What is this?
(Please help me with my makeup, room chief)
(Please help me with my makeup, room chief. From Chang-min.)
I wrote it in a cute way.
(Ha-ha)
(I want to contact you. From Jeong-hyeon.)
I want to contact you. From Jeong-hyeon.
(I want to contact you.)