(OTHER'S LOVE?)
(IT'S)
(JUST)
(OUR LOVE)
(These brave men's)
(true love)
(Their romantic love)
(that others can't have)
(even if they want to)
(Hyeok-jun)
(Chan-gyu)
(Jeong-hyeon)
(Chang-min)
(Eun-chan)
(Seon-yul)
(His Man)
(The men expressed their feelings over the phone in the last episode.)
The first night was of constant excitement and anxiety.
The men conveyed their feelings over the phone.
(Eun-chan was the first to make a call.)
(Eun-chan called Hyeok-jun.)
It hung up.
(30 seconds is too short to convey all their feelings.)
30 seconds is too short to convey all their feelings.
(Jeong-hyeon called Seon-yul.)
Hello?
I called you because I wanted to be closer to you.
(And...)
I just want to say, we can look after each other in the week to come.
You made a favorable first impression on me.
I had a good time talking with you today.
(Chan-gyu, Seon-yul, and Hyeok-jun all chose Chang-min.)
Yeah.
After knowing we have to make the call,
I've been thinking about who I'm going to call.
I feel like calling someone
means you have feelings for him.
(Dialing after so much pondering)
(His first date Hyeok-jun?)
-I have two suitcases.
-Two?
(His first date Hyeok-jun?)
(Seon-yul or Chan-gyu who called him?)
(Roommate Jeong-hyeon?)
(Or to everyone's surprise, Eun-chan?)
After getting three calls himself,
(Where does Chang-min's heart go?)
which man would Chang-min call?
(Nervous)
Hello?
I call to tell you that I had a great time at dinner today.
Right, thank you.
I hope you have a wonderful evening. Good night.
(Who received Chang-min's call?)
(Whose phone is ringing?)
(Chang-min called Hyeok-jun.)
Hello?
I call to tell you that I had a great time at dinner today.
Right, thank you.
(Surprised-I hope you have a wonderful evening. Good night.)
I hope you have a wonderful evening. Good night.
Yeah, thank you. Rest well.
(Surprised-I hope you have a wonderful evening. Good night.)
(Hahaha)
(Shy)
Who do you think that was?
I've no idea.
I can't even guess.
(Envies in secret
Seon-yul: So you have two votes now?)
So you have two votes now?
(Envies in secret
Seon-yul: So you have two votes now?)
(Can't help smiling)
(Hyeok-jun got two calls.)
This is fun though, isn't it?
(Hyeok-jun: I think it's very fun. Hahaha)
I think it's very fun.
(Shy. Chang-min: I thought I should tell Hyeok-jun, my date today.)
I thought I should tell Hyeok-jun, my date today,
that I had a great time with him.
(Shy. Chang-min: I thought I should tell Hyeok-jun, my date today.)
That's why I called him.
(A trembling voice full of sincerity)
(The phone call time ended with Chang-min's call.)
Don't sleep, brother.
Brother, it's not bedtime yet.
Anyone called you, brother?
-What?
-You got any calls?
You can have a guess.
Nobody called me.
Nobody called me either.
(Hahaha. The two people with complicated feelings who got '0 vote')
Is this just my fate?
I'm hurt by the reality.
(Jeong-hyeon: Someone (Chang-min) got three calls.)
Someone got three calls.
And I got none.
(Jeong-hyeon: And I got none.)
I wouldn't be able to get any match. That's what made me upset.
But I still have loads of time to win someone over.
(Jeong-hyeon: But I still have loads of time to win someone over.)
What I was thinking is that at least I need to win one person.
(I don't want to cry my way home!)
I don't want to cry my way home. Something like that.
(Chan-gyu: I never had much expectation from the beginning.)
I never had much expectation from the beginning,
so it wasn't hard to accept the reality.
(Chan-gyu: I never had much expectation from the beginning.)
(The gloomy single room on the other side...)
so it wasn't hard to accept the reality.
I thought I would get at least one call.
That was a heavy blow to my self-esteem.
(Frustrated)
(Stares. Eun-chan: Things I want to say? Too many.)
Things I want to say? Too many.
((What do I do~ QAQ))
What went wrong?
(Really curious. Eun-chan: Am I too tough? Do I look too tough?)
Am I too tough?
Do I look too tough?
(Really curious. Eun-chan: Am I too tough? Do I look too tough?)
(Hahaha. Please answer me, give me an answer!)
Please answer me.
Don't just ask questions. Give me an answer.
(Hahaha. Please answer me, give me an answer!)
(Don't just ask questions!)
Don't just ask questions. Give me an answer.
(Headaches. Eun-chan: I think I can hand in my phone now.)
I think I can hand in my phone now.
I don't seem to need it.
(Eun-chan: 0 vote)
(Chan-gyu: 0 vote. Jeong-hyeon: 0 vote)
(Hyeok-jun: 2 votes)
Who do you want to match with?
(Seon-yul: 1 vote)
(Chang-min: 3 votes)
(Results of phone calls
Eun-chan Jeong-hyeon Hyeok-jun
Chan-gyu Chang-min Seon-yul)
(Today's phone call couple: Hyeok-jun&Chang-min)
(Chang-min gets back from the call...)
Oh, I forgot to press it.
((I'm back.))
-What?
-My bad.
((I'm back.))
-What?
-My bad.
(Immersed in darts game)
-What?
-My bad.
(Immersed in darts game)
(Awkward)
Playing darts again?
(The two people pretend to ignore Chang-min.)
(Chang-min feels embarrassed...)
(The atmosphere in the triple room became awkward.)
I should have taken a shower just now.
Anyone wants to shower first?
Anyone?
Me.
(Jeong-hyeon: Then you go first.)
-Then you go first.
-If that's alright.
(Jeong-hyeon: Then you go first.)
-Then you go first.
-If that's alright.
(Chang-min: Can I take a shower first?)
-Then you go first.
-If that's alright.
(Chang-min: Can I take a shower first?)
-Can I take a shower first?
-Yeah.
(Chang-min: Can I take a shower first?)
-Can I take a shower first?
-Yeah.
(Okay.)
-Can I take a shower first?
-Yeah.
I won't be long.
(The men's house where the atmosphere got weird)
I'll be out in a minute.
(The first morning in the men's house)
(The alarm clock is breaking the silence.)
(Turns over. Eight in the morning)
(Chang-min got up first.)
(Is he going to clean up the messy table?)
(He starts to quietly exercise.)
(A man with self-discipline)
(Getting up)
(Jeong-hyeon also gets out of bed soon afterwards.)
(Halts)
Did you sleep well?
Ah, wait.
(Jeong-hyeon feels shy about his looks without make-up.)
(He's covering his whole face. Why?)
((What's the matter?) Jeong-hyeon wants to talk to Chang-min but he is unwilling to reveal his face without make-up.)
(Jeong-hyeon runs away finally.)
(Bang!)
(Jeong-hyeon stubbed his foot on the door frame. (Ouch QAQ))
((Painful)? (Occupied))
(8:05 AM, Seon-yul gets up.)
(Straight to the dressing room after he got up!)
(Checks his face in the mirror. Haggard)
(Single room. Eun-chan gets up, too.)
(Puffy)
(Creaks)
(Creaks- (What's the noise?))
(Startled)
(Hyeok-jun also gets up!)
(Half-awake)
(Not a trace of Seon-yul)
(Chang-min enjoys the leisurely morning hours after exercise.)
(#morning sunshine #coffee #handsome guy)
(Rustle)
(Methodically)
(Clipping his hair in place)
(Jeong-hyeon starts putting on make-up.)
(Zzz... A man is still in bed without the slightest movement...)
(Zzz...)
Brother.
Time to get up.
What? What time is it?
Already past nine.
(Surprised. Really?)
-Really?
-Yeah.
(Surprised. Really?)
(Goodness. Jeong-hyeon: Everybody is washing up.)
Everybody is washing up.
Brother, everyone's dressing up except you.
(Chan-gyu finally gets out of bed.)
(Half-awake)
((Is it really past nine…?))
(Checks time)
It's not nine yet.
-What?
-It's not nine yet. It's not.
(It's not nine yet~)
-What?
-It's not nine yet. It's not.
(At the same time in the single room, Eun-chan got up early and is dressing up now.)
(Make-up is done. He starts fixing his hair.)
(Fascinatedly. Chang-min is watching Jeong-hyeon very closely.)
Can you do my lips for me?
Do your make-up, brother?
Just make me look livelier.
It's morning after all.
Sit up.
(Getting closer)
(Jeong-hyeon puts lipstick on Chang-min.)
(Bright red- Done!)
Done.
His lips look good, right?
Suit you perfectly.
I'll have a look.
Put some on me too.
(Let me get my hair done first. Haha)
Let me get my hair done first.
Wow. It seems to red?
Brother, come here.
I'll wipe it off a little if it's too much.
No, it looks pretty nice.
It's not too much.
(Nods. Chang-min: You think so?)
You think so?
-It's pretty good.
-Thanks.
I look much livelier.
(Piapia- Hyeok-jun finished washing up)
(The men are all dressed and ready in a blink of an eye.)
(Handsome. Fetching. The men are all dressed and ready in a blink of an eye.)
(Diligent. Chang-min arrived at the living room first waiting for the others.)
(Eun-chan and Seon-yul notice something as they go down the stairs.)
What's this? When did they put the cards here?
-Read it.
-Read it for us.
(Eun-chan: Read it.)
-Read it.
-Read it for us.
(Plop. Eun-chan: Today we'll have one-on-one dates.)
-Read it.
-Read it for us.
(Plop. Eun-chan: Today we'll have one-on-one dates.)
Today we'll have one-on-one dates.
Those who draw an arrow card
can apply for a date with someone who draws a heart card.
A person who draws the arrow card can choose his date.
Then if someone I like…
(Today we'll have one-on-one dates.
Those who draw an arrow card can apply for a date with someone who draws a heart card.
The matching time lasts one hour from now.
Only those who possess both bravery and efficiency will find love!
Go express your feelings now.)
Then if someone I like…
(Today we'll have one-on-one dates.
Those who draw an arrow card can apply for a date with someone who draws a heart card.
The matching time lasts one hour from now.
Only those who possess both bravery and efficiency will find love!
Go express your feelings now.)
If I draw an arrow card,
(Today we'll have one-on-one dates.
Those who draw an arrow card can apply for a date with someone who draws a heart card.
The matching time lasts one hour from now.
Only those who possess both bravery and efficiency will find love!
Go express your feelings now.)
If I draw an arrow card,
(Eun-chan: Then if someone I like...)
and the person I fancy draw the same card,
(Eun-chan: If I draw the arrow card,)
(Eun-chan: and the person I fancy draw the same card,)
and the person I fancy draw the same card,
-we won't be able to choose each other, right?
-No, you can't date each other then.
(Eun-chan: and the person I fancy draw the same card,)
-we won't be able to choose each other, right?
-No, you can't date each other then.
(Eun-chan: we won't be able to choose each other, right?)
-we won't be able to choose each other, right?
-No, you can't date each other then.
(Understood)
-we won't be able to choose each other, right?
-No, you can't date each other then.
They can't choose each other if they both draw the heart card.
(Understood)
-we won't be able to choose each other, right?
-No, you can't date each other then.
They can't choose each other if they both draw the heart card.
-So you fancy someone.
-I don't know.
You have an hour from now to match your date.
Only those who possess both bravery and efficiency will find love.
(Jeong-hyeon: So we draw the cards now?)
So we draw the cards now?
-Yeah.
-Geez.
(Jeong-hyeon: So we draw the cards now?)
(Go express your feelings now.)
-Yeah.
-Geez.
(Jeong-hyeon: So we draw the cards now?)
(Go express your feelings now.)
Go express your feelings now.
You always like the middle.
(Quietly)
I'll draw one too.
(Eun-chan: I'll still do it last this time.)
I'll still do it last this time.
Oh no.
Pick one for me. No, no.
Let me do it for you.
(Eun-chan: No, I'll do it myself.)
-No, I'll do it myself.
-Okay.
(Eun-chan: No, I'll do it myself.)
-No, I'll do it myself.
-Okay.
(The looks on their face are subtle after they drew the cards.)
-No, I'll do it myself.
-Okay.
(The looks on their face are subtle after they drew the cards.)
(What cards did they draw?)
Should we show our cards first, then have breakfast?
Yeah?
Good idea.
-Who first?
-Start from Eun-chan.
((Me?))
(Awkward)
Why is it always me?
Mine is...
(What kind of card did Eun-chan draw?)
(Eun-chan shows it. An arrow card)
Arrow card.
Mine is...
To be honest, I was praying secretly
that Hyeok-jun didn't draw the arrow.
(Hyeok-jun drew a heart card.)
-The heart card.
-It's the heart card.
(Hyeok-jun drew a heart card.)
((Fortunately))
It's the heart card.
Mine is also the heart card.
(Jeong-hyeon drew a heart card which means he's to be chosen.)
Actually I wanted the arrow card more.
Because with the heart card, I'll have to wait for someone to choose me.
(Jeong-hyeon: With the heart card, I'll have to wait for someone to choose me.)
Mine is the arrow card.
(Seon-yul drew an arrow card.)
(Chan-gyu and Chang-min show their cards next.)
I got the heart card.
Arrow card.
(Chan-gyu and Chang-min show their cards next.)
(Chan-gyu got a heart card. Chang-min got an arrow card.)
Arrow card.
(An arrow card as same as Chang-min's. Seon-yul: I was a little disappointed.)
I was a little disappointed.
I wanted to have a date with Chang-min for at least once.
I wanted that.
I was hoping that we hadn't picked the same card.
That's a pity.
Chang-min and Seon-yul.
(Chan-gyu: I wanted to have a date with Chang-min or Seon-yul.)
I wanted to have a date with one of them.
Now should we leave them some privacy?
Now we should have breakfast.
I'm so hungry.
Have some chat while I make breakfast.
Thank you very much.
(Eun-chan will be preparing the meal today.)
How many eggs should I cook?
-Twelve.
-Twelve?
(Jeong-hyeon: Everyone can eat at least two eggs. Eun-chan: Right.)
-Twelve.
-Twelve?
(Jeong-hyeon: Everyone can eat at least two eggs. Eun-chan: Right.)
-Two for each.
-Right.
(Jeong-hyeon: Everyone can eat at least two eggs. Eun-chan: Right.)
-Two for each.
-Right.
(Eun-chan alone is busy cooking.)
Where's the cereal bowl?
Hire an assistant.
I can manage perfectly on my own.
We can help set the table.
(Hyeok-jun: Pick someone (to help you).)
Pick someone.
I can pick one? Then come help me, Hyeok-jun.
(Eun-chan: Then come help me, Hyeok-jun?)
(Just kidding. I shouldn't have said that. Aha.)
I shouldn't have said that.
(Eun-chan: Is this cooking oil?)
Is this cooking oil? It looks like it.
(Smelling)
Cooking oil has no smell.
It has no smell.
Can I break the eggs here?
(Hyeok-jun: Can I break the eggs here?)
(Eun-chan: Yeah! You can do that.)
-Yeah, you can do that.
-I got it.
(Eun-chan: Yeah! You can do that.)
-Yeah, you can do that.
-I got it.
(Peek)
-Yeah, you can do that.
-I got it.
(The oil isn't heated up yet.)
Is the pan heated up?
The eggs are not whisked yet.
(Laughter... Jeong-hyeon: You're frying eggs without whisking?)
-You don't whisk that?
-You are frying eggs without whisking?
(Laughter... Jeong-hyeon: You're frying eggs without whisking?)
What happened?
(Eun-chan panics: I can whisk the eggs in there, right?)
(Laughter... Jeong-hyeon: You're frying eggs without whisking?)
-I can whisk the eggs in there, right?
-Yeah.
(Eun-chan panics: I can whisk the eggs in there, right?)
-I can whisk the eggs in there, right?
-Yeah.
(Whisking the eggs hurriedly, Jeong-hyeon: Yeah!)
-I can whisk the eggs in there, right?
-Yeah.
((Cute))
(Eun-chan looks at others: Should I add salt to fried eggs?)
Should I add salt to fried eggs?
-A little bit.
-Just a little.
(A lot of salt)
(Panic)
Oh no.
((What happened?))
I forgot about it after I lit the fire.
(Will we be able to enjoy the breakfast?)
Brother, the eggs are getting burnt.
(He's way too busy.)
(He's finally finishing up.)
(Chan-gyu: What should we do with only five minutes to choose (our date)?)
What should we do with only five minutes to choose our date?
Oh really.
(Men look at each other and defer making a choice.)
How about putting one slice of bacon on the plate
of the one you want to date?
-Good idea!
-Right?
(Eun-chan: Good idea!)
-Good idea!
-Right?
(Good idea. Chang-min: Declare your affection with a slice of bacon.)
Declare your affection with a slice of bacon.
Oh, that's good.
(It's a little embarrassing to say it out loud...)
It's a little embarrassing to say it out loud.
(Eun-chan: Put bacon here for the one you want to ask out?)
Put bacon here for the one you want to ask out?
Privilege.
The cook today has the privilege to choose first.
Is that necessary?
(Plating the food carefully)
-He's really serious.
-Look at how he does the plating.
(Plating the food carefully)
-He's really serious.
-Look at how he does the plating.
(Look at how he does the plating. Aha.)
-He's really serious.
-Look at how he does the plating.
(Pacing)
This way or that way?
(Eun-chan, the cook, has the privilege to choose first.)
Wait.
((Shy) Running away quickly)
What? Take your time.
(Eun-chan: Should I just have the cheek to go for it when I apply?)
Should I just have the cheek to go for it when I apply?
I'm so nervous.
(Everyone else is watching where Eun-chan is heading for.)
Who has the arrow card?
(Seon-yul, Chang-min, Eun-chan)
-The arrow card.
-Him.
(Seon-yul, Chang-min, Eun-chan)
I have it.
Him, him, you.
(Seon-yul, Chang-min, Eun-chan)
I feel so embarrassed doing this.
-We are even more nervous.
-Yeah, we are even more embarrassed.
(Who will Eun-chan give the food to?)
(Eun-chan chose Hyeok-jun.)
Thank you. Where did he go?
The rules didn't say you can't say no, right?
((Frustrated))
(Kidding. Just kidding. Ha-ha.)
Just kidding.
I was so happy.
I see.
I was really happy.
It must be delicious.
It should taste pretty good.
Please enjoy the food.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
Arrow card holder, make your choice quickly.
(These two men have the arrow cards with which they can choose their date.)
(Seon-yul chose Chan-gyu decisively.)
(Kidding)
I wasn't the last guy to be chosen.
When someone chose me,
I felt quite happy.
(Now the people left are Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon)
-Date me, then.
-I have to.
Because I hesitated,
it seemed as if I were made to date Jeong-hyeon.
I could date no one, but him.
I felt like he asked me out only because he had no other choice.
It didn't make me happy, actually.
(Final results of one-on-one dates: Eun-chan→Hyeok-jun, Seon-yul→Chan-gyu, Chang-min→Jeong-hyeon)
(Getting ready to go out for one-on-one dates)
Thank you for drying my hair.
(Men are busy dressing themselves up.)
(Getting ready to go out for one-on-one dates)
(Excitement for the date, Making themselves tidy and handsome)
(What emotional changes will they have through today's date?)
It's a lovely day, isn't it?
It is. Flowers are in full bloom.
(Hyeok-jun: Flowers are in full bloom, right?)
Coming out is the right thing to do.
(The weather is as bright as their moods.)
I haven't been out for a long time.
So many flowers.
(The weather is as bright as their moods.)
That's right. They look beautiful.
Where are we heading for?
(Eun-chan and Hyeok-jun reached where they would have the date.)
(A small but exquisite candle workshop)
(Different kinds of candles caught their eyes.)
Is this a handicraft workshop?
(Eun-chan: Look at these. Hyeok-jun: What's in them (candles)?)
(Different kinds of candles caught their eyes.)
Look at these.
(Eun-chan: Look at these. Hyeok-jun: What's in them (candles)?)
What's in them?
Will we make this kind of handicraft?
(Mentor: Hello.)
Hello.
-Hello.
We'll use small and exquisite accessories
to make a night light.
It's a night light?
Yes. There's a bulb in the candle.
It can be used as a lamp on the bedside table.
Great!
We have to sleep with the light on tonight.
Yeah, right in our dorms.
(They'll make night lights that can faintly glow on their bedside tables.)
Make an aquarium candle?
What colors will you use?
-I like discordant colors.
-Discordant?
Dissonant colors, I mean.
(Hyeok-jun: Are you making the rainbow colors?)
Are you making the rainbow colors?
They're quite consonant. Something like this.
They look good.
Totally dissonant colors.
I love this kind of inharmony.
I like white.
Do you usually like this kind of date?
A date like this?
It's good.
But you know,
it's nice if it's something where you have to move around.
(Eun-chan: Like things with activities?)
-Like things with activities?
-Yes.
(Eun-chan: Like things with activities?)
(Hyeok-jun: This kind of things with activities are good. So are such quiet activities.)
This kind of things with activities are good. So are such quiet activities.
But I do want to climb the mountain.
(Hyeok-jun: This kind of things with activities are good. So are such quiet activities.)
I've never climbed a mountain before.
(Eun-chan: I do want to climb a mountain.)
Neither have I.
But I've always wanted to.
I want to climb the mountain on a Sunday morning.
-Sunday morning?
-Yes.
Shall we go climb the mountain?
Why not?
(Smiling, Hyeok-jun: We can carry a backpack...)
We can carry a backpack.
Yeah. We can carry one.
(So, they've already made a next date?)
Let me mix the colors.
(With a glance, Eun-chan: No offense, but last night, who did you call?)
No offense, but last night,
who did you call?
(With a glance, Eun-chan: No offense, but last night, who did you call?)
(In panic, Hyeok-jun: Who did I call?)
Who did I call?
(Hyeok-jun: Umm...)
To tell the truth,
(Nervous)
I called Chang-min who was a couple with me.
Who did you call, then?
Did... Did you ask because you really don't know?
Yes, of course.
Last night, someone called me.
I've thought about if it was you.
It was me.
Really?
But last night, you...
I said hello, but the caller didn't say anything.
You said you could barely hear me.
I asked who you were.
But you hung up.
I didn't hang up. There was a time limit.
So we were disconnected automatically?
(Hyeok-jun: So we were disconnected...?)
I had planned to have a chat with you.
But just as I started to talk, the line was cut.
Then I held the receiver and I was like...
Because the line was cut.
You planned to say something?
Of course, I did.
(Got it.)
Last night, I was quite unlucky and suffered a lot.
Of course, I did.
I really didn't know that.
When I could decide whom to date today,
I thought fate was playing a joke on me.
Why? Why?
Did you wish to get the heart card?
I wished I could get the arrow card.
Really?
I prefer to make the choice.
But why...?
You got the arrow card.
Yeah.
Why didn't you make your choice immediately?
(Hyeok-jun: Why didn't you make your choice immediately?)
(Twitch)
(Wriggle)
Do you mean choosing my date?
Yes.
(Curious. Hyeok-jun thinks Eun-chan didn't make a choice quickly because he wanted to date no one.)
I thought if it was because you didn't want to choose anyone.
It's because I was too nervous.
Actually, last night,
I thought you knew I called you.
I really didn't know that.
I thought you did.
But you didn't call me.
I confessed my feelings, but you didn't.
That's what I thought.
I thought you rejected me.
Is that so?
(Eun-chan: Date application. I just decided to 'do it first and then regret', anyway.)
I just decided to 'do it first and then regret', anyway.
(Nodding)
-But I have a question.
-Go ahead.
If you got the arrow card,
who would you pick?
(Hyeok-jun: Umm... Me?)
Me?
If I got the arrow card...
(Nervous)
Tell the truth, please.
Honestly speaking, yesterday I...
(Q. Who do you want to date tomorrow?)
Tomorrow, I want to date Eun-chan who I didn't talk too much with.
Yesterday, I said I wanted to talk with you.
(Feeling happy, Eun-chan: Why?)
Why?
Because we didn't talk too much.
It was always three or four of us together.
(Eun-chan asks abruptly: Then why didn't you call me?)
Then why didn't you call me?
If you wanted to talk, you should have called me.
We could have talked privately for 30 seconds last night.
That makes sense. I never thought of that.
Then I just called Chang-min who was a couple with me.
What a pity!
My bad.
(When they talk about what they care for,)
(they seem to get closer.)
What shall I put in the bottle?
Pick something for me.
How about this?
OK.
(Eun-chan picked a little dinosaur.)
Sounds like you don't want it. You don't like it?
I'll put this in it.
(Whiz)
What are you going to write?
(Shell)
What shall I write?
How about writing something to each other and exchanging the shells?
What do you think?
Good idea.
Let's write something simple. One or two sentences.
What shall I write?
(Wholeheartedly)
(Writing something to each other)
OK.
I'm done.
Let's exchange them.
I'm quite nervous.
(Pfft)
(Burst out laughing)
(Careful)
-Oh, that's how you put it.
-Then no one can see it, but me.
(Chatting nicely and making night lights carefully)
(What have they written to each other?)
(Hyeok-jun: Will you sleep with the light on tonight?)
Will you sleep with the light on tonight?
I will.
So will I.
(It's what Eun-chan wrote to Hyeok-jun.)
(It's what Hyeok-jun wrote to Eun-chan.)
(Nice to meet you! It's what Hyeok-jun wrote to Eun-chan.)
(Where Seon-yul and Chan-gyu are dating)
(Date in the bakery They're going to make popsicles.)
I chose to date Chan-gyu because I wanted to communicate with him.
I didn't worry if he was my best choice.
Instead, I thought this date would be fun.
What are these?
Ice creams, right?
More likely chocolate.
(Chan-gyu: Yeah.)
Chocolate on an ice cream stick, right?
(Chan-gyu: Chocolate on an ice cream stick.)
This is the raw material.
(Oh, I see.)
Which pattern would you like to make for me?
What suits me?
Suits you?
(Peep)
(Another peep)
This.
Don't you think it perfectly matches what you're wearing?
-Colors?
-Gray and white on your clothes.
(Angel, Seon-yul: It's gray and white. The angle is as kind as you, too.)
-Colors?
-Gray and white on your clothes.
(Angel, Seon-yul: It's gray and white. The angle is as kind as you, too.)
The angel is as kind as you, too.
Kind? That's all? Only kind?
Chocolate... It's also delicious, isn't it?
(Shy)
What would you like to make for me, then?
(Mm.)
Which suits me?
Bee. The bee suits you.
(Cute, lovely)
Why?
Because it looks cute. As cute as you.
(Satisfied? Shy?)
What do you think? Do you like bees?
(Seon-yul: I hate bees.)
I hate bees.
((A touch of panic))
Then what shall I make for you?
Make a puppy for me, please.
(In panic, Chan-gyu: Puppy? What kind of puppy?)
Puppy? What kind of puppy?
Like this.
You've even got a puppy on you.
A puppy like that?
Yes, a puppy like this.
(Woof)
((A puppy like that...))
I'll try to make a similar one.
-Let me go get the material.
-OK.
(Seon-yul is going to get the ice cream sticks.)
-Let me go get the material.
-OK.
(Seon-yul is going to get the ice cream sticks.)
I felt so good because, oh my, he agreed to make it for me.
-So small.
-How cute!
-We're supposed to coat the back first.
-All right.
(Small)
-We're supposed to coat the back first.
-All right.
Let me make the weird puppy first.
Don't say that. It's a cute puppy.
-Let's get started.
-OK.
(White chocolate)
-Let's get started.
-OK.
-We should first melt this.
-I think it would taste great.
(Seon-yul: I think it would taste great.)
-We should first melt this.
-I think it would taste great.
Have a taste then.
May I?
Do you find it difficult to feed me?
(In panic, Chan-gyu: Don't be silly.)
Don't be silly.
(Seon-yul: We should coat the back first.)
-We should coat the back first.
-OK.
(Seon-yul: We should coat the back first.)
-We should coat the back first.
-OK.
((Belated laughter))
-We should coat the back first.
-OK.
Like this.
I feel like I'm gifted.
-Are you doing fine?
-Yes.
-Am I doing a better job?
-I'm just still shaping it.
-You are? Got it. I'll wait for you.
-OK.
(Seon-yul: Got it. I'll wait for you. Chan-gyu: Good.)
-You are? Got it. I'll wait for you.
-OK.
(Focused)
-You are? Got it. I'll wait for you.
-OK.
(Focused)
My chocolate is no longer dripping.
(Seon-yul: Oh? I'm in big trouble.)
I'm in big trouble.
-Sir, help me, please.
-Wait a minute.
(Anxious)
-Sir, help me, please.
-Wait a minute.
(Oh, no. Oops.)
-It hasn't solidified yet, right?
-I guess so.
I had planned to start with this one.
-Look at the puppy when you make it.
-Got it.
(Look at the puppy when you make the ice cream.)
-Look at the puppy when you make it.
-Got it.
-Let me get a better view.
-Do you need me to hold this position?
(Staring, Seon-yul: Let me get a better view.
Chan-gyu: Do you need me to hold this position?)
-Let me get a better view.
-Do you need me to hold this position?
(Glance)
-Let me get a better view.
-Do you need me to hold this position?
I'm trying to stick the ears to the puppy's head.
(Knock knock)
It has a nose.
(Giggle)
What's it going to look like?
What do you think it is?
I'm making it attentively.
The shape looks a little bit weird. But I'm really looking forward to it.
Wow, so cute.
Finished.
(Finished already?)
Finished already?
Wait.
Where are its hands?
Hands are hiding like this.
(Hands hiding like this)
What about its legs?
Hands are hiding like this.
Legs are hiding like this.
-Are you a hedgehog?
-Yes
(Messy, cute puppy, making while thinking about Chan-gyu, finished(?))
-Are you a hedgehog?
-Yes
(Messy, cute puppy, making while thinking about Chan-gyu, finished(?))
((Check again))
But honestly, it's cute.
Identically!
Approved.
(Satisfied)
What do you think it looks like?
-Isn't this an alien?
- What alien?
It's your vest.
(Ah?)
Grey, the T-shirt inside, the stripes, the lines on the bottom.
It's kinda cute.
(Nods)
Knowing it's a vest, it's kinda cute, well done.
(Seon-yul made a puppy like Chan-gyu's Chan-gyu made a vest like Seon-yul's)
So interesting.
What am I going to make this time?
-I want to make bee.
-Bee?
(Cute)
(Knock knock)
-When you are making this, you would want to make it perfect.
-Yes.
(Popsicles that only belongs to them are gradually completed)
-When you are making this, you would want to make it perfect.
-Yes.
You would give me the vest, but who would you give the rest of them?
The first would be eaten by me.
We would need to share one to eat.
(Seon-yal: With the rest of the four?)
(Chan-gyu: No? Seon-yul: Then?)
The two of us?
The two of us.
(Slap)
I really like the way he is.
And I appreciate what he said.
I have never met someone as cute as a child.
Maybe this is what I am feeling right now.
(Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon's dating site)
Wow, ceramic studio.
(The two guys arrived at the dating site full of anticipation)
-This is the entrance.
-Here
(Chang-min: This is the entrance!)
-This is the entrance.
-Here
(You can make all sorts of bowls and trinkets)
-This is the entrance.
-Here
(You can make all sorts of bowls and trinkets)
This is so cute
(Ceramic studio for Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon's date)
(Swish-)
(Careful-)
(Chang-min: Do I look like an expert?)
-I don't look like an expert.
-Like a beginner.
(Chang-min: Do I look like an expert?)
-I don't look like an expert.
-Like a beginner.
(Joking
Chang-min: Do I look like an expert?
Jeong-hyeon: More like a beginner.)
-I don't look like an expert.
-Like a beginner.
Like a beginner.
(Mentor: Who will go first?)
Who will go first, is this your first time?
You should try first.
Yes, I will go first.
(Jeong-hyeon: I can try first, I am a beginner.)
-Is this your first time?
-Yes, my first time.
(Jeong-hyeon: I can try first, I am a beginner.)
Okay.
(Focus)
-Wet my hand first?
-Yes, wet your hand first.
(Focus)
-Wet my hand first?
-Yes, wet your hand first.
After wetting you hand, put them here.
(Teacher: Wet your hand first and put them here)
-Here?
-Yes.
(Wet)
-Here?
-Yes.
(Wet)
Put them there comfortably.
Feel kind of weird.
(Hehe)
Put them there comfortably.
(Jeong-hyeon concentrates his feeling on the spinning potter's wheel)
Hang in for a bit.
(Oh~)
I like handcraft, so it's fun and interesting.
-I have already learned how to do it.
-Yes.
(Jeong-hyeon: Brother, I know how to do it now, I can teach you.)
-I have already learned how to do it.
-Yes.
(Jeong-hyeon: Brother, I know how to do it now, I can teach you.)
-I will teach you now.
-Where should we start?
(Jeong-hyeon: Brother, I know how to do it now, I can teach you.)
-I will teach you now.
-Where should we start?
(Chang-min: Where do we start?)
-I will teach you now.
-Where should we start?
(Chang-min: Where do we start?)
-Wet your hand with water first.
-Put my hand into the water.
(Chang-min: Where do we start?)
-Wet your hand with water first.
-Put my hand into the water.
(Jeong-hyeon: Wet your hand with water first.)
-Wet your hand with water first.
-Put my hand into the water.
-Why are your hands so big?
-Yeah
(Huge
Jeong-hyeon: Why are your hands so huge?)
-Why are your hands so big?
-Yeah
They are wet already.
Put your hands here, hurry.
(Slightly)
Put your whole hands onto it.
(Jeong-hyeon: Put your hand on them like this.)
-Ah, all to it.
-Yes, steadily.
(Jeong-hyeon: Put your hand on them like this.)
-Ah, all to it.
-Yes, steadily.
(Listening carefully and doing exactly like Chang-min said)
-Ah, all to it.
-Yes, steadily.
(Not very good at it)
With your whole palm.
Like this, with your whole hand.
(Helpful)
-I'm making it.
-Yes.
(Chang-min is making it)
-I'm making it.
-Yes.
When it's like this, you should shape it now.
(The next step, shape the bowl)
Just shape it.
It already has the shape.
With one hand like this.
(Suddenly)
Put your thumb here.
Put a little more pressure here.
(Secretly)
(The two are getting closer without knowing)
Put a little more pressure here.
What happened? What does it look like now?
I can't see it with my hands in the way.
(The top collapsed)
-Great, I was going to make it like this.
-Really?
(Awkward)
(Chang-min is trying to shape the bowl again)
I think it should work this time.
(Nervous)
Hurry, hurry, it's going.
((Cute))
(Their hands are touching unconsciously)
(Started to get shy)
-It's done, so pretty.
-Yes.
(Tada. Chang-min's ceramic is finally shaped.)
-It's done, so pretty.
-Yes.
(Jeong-hyeon: It's so pretty.)
-It's done, so pretty.
-Yes.
Could you bake it for me, teacher?
(Jeong-hyeon: After it's baked, it will be sent to your place in 4 weeks.)
-After it's baked, it will be sent to your place in 4 weeks.
-Alright, noted.
(Jeong-hyeon: After it's baked, it will be sent to your place in 4 weeks.)
(Kidding, Jeong-hyeon: Just tell me your address.)
-After it's baked, it will be sent to your place in 4 weeks.
-Alright, noted.
(Jeong-hyeon: After it's baked, it will be sent to your place in 4 weeks.)
(Kidding, Jeong-hyeon: Just tell me your address.)
-Just tell me your address.
-Noted, thank you.
(Kidding, Jeong-hyeon: Just tell me your address.)
-Just tell me your address.
-Noted, thank you.
(Chang-min: Alright, thank you.)
-Just tell me your address.
-Noted, thank you.
I want to know Jeong-hyeon better before.
He seems completely different from me.
He seems outgoing and high-pitched.
Is this opposite attraction?
May I draw on it?
Yes, you could draw on it.
Why can't I get it right?
(Why can't I get it right...? Peek)
(You have to use the knife)
You have to use the knife, use the knife.
(Chang-min helped unconsciously)
-With this?
-Yes.
(Chang-min helped unconsciously)
What kind of soju cup are you making?
What kind of shape?
It should be just a regular one.
But I will draw on it.
Draw on it?
I am drawing on it right now.
What kind of drawing?
An animal that looks like brother.
(Jeong-hyeon: An animal that looks like brother Chang-min)
Really?
Yes? What is it? On the beer mug?
Yes, beer mug is tall, like you.
It would be more like you.
Really?
When I first met you, I thought you look like golden retriever.
So I'm making golden retriever right now.
I heard people said I looked like a puppy.
You looked exactly like one.
(Glance)
You look like a kitty.
(Jeong-hyeon's expression is inexplicable)
I heard that brother likes youthful boys.
I heard him like youthful boys with innocent and decent,
handsome look.
(Jeong-hyeon: (He said I looked like a cat so) I was upset.)
I am a little upset.
So of all the people you have dated...
Are they all your ideal type?
Yes, except for one.
Ideal type is just a saying.
So I have reached this age without much dating experience.
You don't have much dating experience?
Yes, I have just a few.
Do you have a lot of dating experience?
I think I had have my fair share.
I don't have much experience for my age.
Really?
Do you like experienced lover or?
I like someone with experience.
But not someone that's really good at it.
-Really?
-Yes.
Is it hard?
-Can't look like an expert?
-Yes.
It's hard.
What are you doing.
It's almost done.
I'm looking at the mug you made.
Really?
Are you watching like TV?
I'm appreciating it.
("I am looking at your cup with admiration.")
Honestly I wasn't too interested in making things in the studio.
(Chang-min: I wasn't too interested in making things in the studio.)
I just want to talk to him.
He didn't really seem to be interested in the studio.
And in me.
I was really into it.
But brother played while making it.
(Jeong-hyeon: We picked cards in the morning, right?)
-We picked cards this morning.
-Yes.
(Jeong-hyeon: We picked cards in the morning, right?)
-We picked cards this morning.
-Yes.
(Jeong-hyeon: Brother, do you want heart or?)
Did you want heart or arrow?
(Jeong-hyeon: Arrow?)
(Hum...)
I didn't think too much, what about you?
I don't want heart, I want arrow.
(Chang-min: The one that you get to choose?)
-The one you get to choose.
-Yes.
(Chang-min: The one that you get to choose?)
-The one you get to choose.
-Yes.
Isn't it easier to be chosen?
You don't have to do anything.
But I was thinking who would choose me?
I am more initiative anyway.
(Ah...You are the more initiative type.)
-More initiative.
-Yes.
(Ah...You are the more initiative type.)
I am more forward.
(Jeong-hyeon: Yeah, I am very initiative.)
And I have a lot of ideas.
So I am less proactive.
-And shy.
-Are you shy?
A little, a little.
I don't know.
So today...
(Paused. Jeong-hyeon: What about today?)
What about today?
I should have chosen when we were eating,
But instead, it looked like I was left there.
Like I was one of them.
I guess I should choose first.
Do you have someone in mind?
I was thinking about it,
and then someone got to him first before me.
(OMG)
Really?
(Chang-min: Correction! I mean the order of the choice, it's not about who.)
I mean the order of the choice, it's not about who
((Brain stopped working))
(Jeong-hyeon: Misunderstood. Why…? It must be a pity…)
How, it must be a pity.
(Chang-min: True feeling. No, I am happy right now.)
No, I am happy right now.
(Jeong-hyeon: Ah... I was thinking that...? What's going on? What's going on...)
I was thinking, what's going on?
Was he saying that he didn't like me in front of me?
(The air becomes awkward between misunderstanding and true feelings)
Is that so?
We had phone call yesterday.
Is there someone you like among them?
People who said they like you?
But I could only guess one of them,
(Chang-min: The people who called me yesterday.)
People who call me yesterday.
I didn't know who the rest of them are.
Really?
(Of course, I was right there. But... it was pleasant)
But it was pleasant.
-Right, it must be, I was right there.
-Awkward.
(Of course, I was right there. But... it was pleasant)
-It was a bit awkward.
-I was so embarrassed.
(Jeong-hyeon: I was so embarrassed. Why? Did I mute my phone?)
-It was a bit awkward.
-I was so embarrassed.
(Jeong-hyeon: I was so embarrassed. Why? Did I mute my phone?)
Why? Did I mute my phone?
I felt so awkward.
You called yesterday.
I did.
Can you tell me why you would call that guy?
Honestly, I was thinking it was more like I want to know you
instead of I like you.
I simply called the person with the looks I like the most.
But he was the person you like the most, right?
(Not really)
-Not really.
-Oh?
(Not really)
I am curious.
When I met him for the first time yesterday,
I thought he was just a kid who didn't know any better.
But now I feel like he wasn't someone frivolous.
I like him a little more than yesterday.
(The date of attraction and staggering back and forth is over)
(The Men's House Seon-yul: Let's put them in the fridge.)
Let's put it to the fridge.
(The guys' house Chan-gyu's fridge?)
(The Men's House Seon-yul: Let's put them in the fridge.)
-To the fridge?
-Yes.
(The guys' house Chan-gyu's fridge?)
It would be better in the freezer.
-In the freezer?
-Yes.
Then in the freezer.
Give them a surprise later.
I will put it in here.
They must wonder what it is.
What it is?
(Second to arrive are Hyeok-jun and Eun-chan)
What did they do?
But I'm sure ours are the cutest, right?
(The two are waiting for the rest of them)
(Suddenly)
Did you feel my sincerity during the date?
No.
What are you talking about?
(-Chan-gyu: Why didn't you accept my feelings?
-Seon-yul: We will see.)
Why didn't you accept my feelings?
(-Chan-gyu: Why didn't you accept my feelings?
-Seon-yul: We will see.)
I know. We will see.
(-Chan-gyu: Why didn't you accept my feelings?
-Seon-yul: We will see.)
I should join this, I should join this.
(Seon-yul dated Eun-chan on the first day and then Chan-gyu the next day)
-You have also went on a date with him, right?
-Yes.
(Seon-yul dated Eun-chan on the first day and then Chan-gyu the next day)
Who do you like more?
(Flash^)
(Chan-gyu's sudden provocation (?))
I'm so tired of this.
(Acting innocent)
-It's true.
-You are discussing some interesting topics here.
(Hyeok-jun: You are talking about some interesting topics?)
-It's true.
-You are discussing some interesting topics here.
(Hyeok-jun also joined the conversation)
I want to know, I want to know.
I want to know.
(Hyeok-jun also joined the conversation)
(Hyeok-jun: Who do you like more?)
I want to know.
(Hyeok-jun also joined the conversation)
(Hyeok-jun: Who do you like more?)
Who is it? Take your pick.
(Hyeok-jun: Take your pick)
Who do you like more?
(Glares)
((Upset...))
Who do you like more?
You can tell the truth, I really don't mind it.
So tired!
Come on! Say it.
To be honest, it's the first date with you.
So I felt kind of hurry-scurry, I can not feel anything else.
(Seon-yul: Kind of hurry-scurry, I can not feel a certain (feeling).)
(Seon-yul: But since this is a date a day after,)
But since this is a date a day after,
(Seon-yul: I could observe better.)
(Seon-yul: But since this is a date a day after,)
I could observe better.
(Seon-yul: I could observe better.)
What on earth did you observe?
(Seon-yul: Being with Chan-gyu is more comfortable.)
It's more comfortable.
-I am not so sure.
-Cry
am. not. sure.)
-I am not so sure.
-Cry
-He chose me instead.
-Just cry.
am. not. sure.)
-I am not so sure.
-Cry
-He chose me instead.
-Just cry.
Let's pretend to cry.
(Sobbing.)
(Where do the men's hearts lay?)
Let's pretend to cry.
(Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon arrived last)
They are here.
What a pity!
I am really curious what they did.
(Startled)
-You came back!
-What's going on?
(Startled)
-You came back!
-What's going on?
-Naturally give you the center place.
-What's going on here?
We've waited for you for a long time.
-Really?-Really?
What did you do?
(Curious, Seon-yul: What did you guys do?)
We made something.
What did you do?
(Jeong-hyeon: We made something. Seon-yul: Come in the middle, we are about to start the hearing.)
We made something.
Come in the middle, we are about to start the hearing.
(Jeong-hyeon: We made something. Seon-yul: Come in the middle, we are about to start the hearing.)
What did you make?
(Guys are curious about Chang-min and Jeong-hyeon's date.)
We waited for a while.
What did everybody make?
(Eun-chan: How about we bring over the things we made? )
-How about we bring over the things we made?
-Shall we?
(Eun-chan: How about we bring over the things we made? )
-How about we bring over the things we made?
-Shall we?
(What? Bring the things?)
-How about we bring over the things we made?
-Shall we?
(What? Bring the things?)
Bring the things?
What we made will only come in 4 weeks.
Really?
(What's it?)
We'll have to wait four weeks to get it back.
(Chang-min: That sounds like divorce papers.)
That sounds like divorce papers.
What did you make?
(Eun-chan: Then we bring ours (first)? Hyeok-jun: Go get it now.)
-Then we bring ours (first)?
-Go get it now.
(Eun-chan: Then we bring ours (first)? Hyeok-jun: Go get it now.)
-They have some nice things, I guess.
-Now we go and get ours?
(Chang-min: They have some nice things, I guess.)
-They have some nice things, I guess.
-Now we go and get ours?
(Seon-yul: We'll get it when they come back.)
We'll get it when they come back.
(Jeong-hyeon: What?! You guys all bring the things that can be kept (as achievement).)
What? Everyone has something can bring back.
So what you did was for yourself?
No, I made for all of us.
Really?
-Birthday related.
-Let me put it this way first.
(Observe their reactions, just put it this way first. )
-Birthday related.
-Let me put it this way first.
Just put it this way first.
Put it this way first and then just take yours.
( Confused, do not know why Seon-yul is not in a good mood.)
I called Chang-min yesterday.
("I really want to go on a date with Chang-min..." )
I really want to go on a date with Chang-min.
(I can't show it but it still feels like a pity. )
I can't show it but it still feels like a pity.
(Another miss...)
(I can't show it but it still feels like a pity. )
(Hyeok-jun and Eun-chan come down with a night light.)
(Assuming Chang-min: It is something that can be eaten.)
It's something that can be eaten.
What's this?
Delicate.
(Assumption 1 Jeong-hyeon: Is it not a soap?)
Is it not soap？
Cookie, muffin or something like that?
( Assumption 2 Chang-min: Something like cookie or muffin.)
Please open!
-Clang!
-Wow! What's this?
Isn't it cute?
It's a night light.
You did not buy it, you made it yourself?
Yes, we made on our own.
-So beautiful! -Such a night light.
(Satisfied with Eun-chan's night light.)
Please turn it on!
-So beautiful! -Such a night light.
(Blankly)
It must be fun!
Brother, what we did is fun as well, right?
(Ours are interesting as well!!)
(Sad...)
-It's so...
-Wow!
(Sad...)
-It's so...
-Wow!
(Woah)
-It's so...
-Wow!
(Woah)
You only made them for yourselves?
Of course it's ours.
(Sure! Seon-yul: Are these not for us?)
Are these not for us?
You are showing off.
-Surprised! We made this!
-Showing off! Showing off!
((Even with light))
-Surprised! We made this!
-Showing off! Showing off!
They are definitely showing off.
I want to see the others too.
(Hyeok-jun: I want to see (what the others) made as well.)
(Clay mark Chang-min: Leave a mark like this.)
I left a mark like this.
Did you make pottery?
Look at this.
(These two think night lights are amazing.)
-What's wrong? Not at all.
-The night owl even has light.
(These two think night lights are amazing.)
I think you made pottery.
We made a movie.
(Chang-min: It must be fun like making an atmosphere light.)
It must be fun like this.
What we did is fun as well, right?
It is interesting.
But it will be a different kind of fun.
What did you make?
Brother said he didn't like sentimental or useless things.
(Jeong-hyeon: Chang-min, you said you do not like sentimental and useless things.)
He did say so.
After looking this, he said, "Wow, this must've been fun."
(After seeing other's creation, he said "Wow, it must be fun" ...)
If you don't want to be with me, just say it, brother.
After looking this, he said, "Wow, this must've been fun."
What I am saying is because,
it's nice to have such immediate products.
There is no need to lie, brother, we did played for 30 minutes.
Hands up.
(Jeong-hyeon: But we did play for 30 minutes...)
We did played for 30 minutes, brother.
(Sad)
Like slime.
We prepared something for everyone to eat.
They said we could just give it to whoever wants it.
(Interested)
Wait! What does it look like?
(Chan-gyu: What does this look like?)
-Chocolate.
-Hold on a second.
(Chan-gyu: What does this look like?)
Wait! What does it look like?
-Chocolate.
-Hold on a second.
(Night owl? Addle almond?)
-Chocolate.
-Hold on a second.
(Night owl? Addle almond?)
Addle almond.
-Night owl.
-Night Owl.
(Night owl? Addle almond?)
-Night owl.
-Night Owl.
I told you.
-I can not see it.
-Isn't it a night owl?
(Sparrow?)
-I can not see it.
-Isn't it a night owl?
(Sparrow?)
Sparrow! Sparrow!
(All kinds of assumptions on Chan-gyu's great work.)
Is it a bird?
The first work is to make something for each other.
That one was supposedly made with me in mind.
May I see it?
Ah! Bird, it's bird.
(Bird? Want to capture?)
Trying to capture this feelings.
No, it's a vest.
(Bird? Want to capture?)
Trying to capture this feelings.
No, it's a vest.
(It looks like Seon-yul's vest. Chan-gyu's work turns out to be exactly the same. (?))
Really?
I made it with the stripes on them.
(It looks like Seon-yul's vest. Chan-gyu's work turns out to be exactly the same. (?))
I could see it, too, to be honest.
(It's a pity that everyone can not get Chan-gyu's sense of art.(?))
-How could this be? -Really?
-Ok. -But it indeed looks alike.
(Jeong-hyeon: But it looks indeed alike!)
I thought it was a bird.
-Ok. -But it indeed looks alike.
(I thought it was a bird... Haha, me too.)
I thought it was a bird.
I thought it was a bird as well.
(I thought it was a bird... Haha, me too.)
I don't think they can recognize it.
It turns out that they can not recognize it indeed.
Feel a little bitter.
(Chang-min: We came back from a presentation. (Did not bring the works))
-We came back from a presentation.
-Presentation?
(Chang-min: We came back from a presentation. (Did not bring the works))
Is it ceramic or something?
We made pottery wheel, soju mug and beer mug.
(Looks like Chang-min's(?) beer mug or soju mug Chang-min made just(?) a cup
(The afternoon of true feelings and misunderstanding.)
(What will happen to their feelings?)
I feel a little hungry now.
Talk too much?
What's for dinner?
-Ah, first we have meat.
-Meat.
It's beef.
-Beef, BBQ?
-Yes, grilled beef.
(Chang-min: Yes, it's grilled beef.)
-Beef, BBQ?
-Yes, grilled beef.
There are many bell peppers.
How about Vietnamese spring rolls?
-That's great.
-OK.
(Vietnamese spring rolls for dinner)
-That's great.
-OK.
(Vietnamese spring rolls for dinner)
-How about Vietnamese spring rolls?
-That's great.
(Vietnamese spring rolls for dinner)
-How about Vietnamese spring rolls?
-That's great!
(Vietnamese spring rolls for dinner)
Cool!
Someone can stir fry this with the sauce.
(Seon-yul: Someone can stir fry this (meat) with seasoning.)
(Jeong-hyeon snuck up on Seon-yul.)
I can deal with the ingredient.
(Seon-yul: Is there anyone good at cutting? )
(Jeong-hyeon snuck up on Seon-yul.)
Is there anyone good at cutting?
(Seon-yul: Is there anyone good at cutting? )
It's fine to just put the BBQ sauce to the beef?
(Secretly)
(Shy Busy cooking Seon-yul: Why... Like I'm taking the lead again?)
It's fine to just put the BBQ sauce to the beef?
Why... It's like I'm taking the lead again.
(Shy Busy cooking Seon-yul: Why... Like I'm taking the lead again?)
But I am really bad at using knife.
-Me too.
-Let me get the knife.
(Chang-min: Let me get the knife)
-Me too.
-Let me get the knife.
Then I will wash the ingredient.
Because I don't know how to cook.
-Let me do it.
-I was there to be the cheer leader then.
-Singing some labor songs.
-It's an important role.
Washing the dishes.
(Men who have fun finding their roles)
Wash the dishes again?
(First dinner last night)
What have you done that makes you so tired?
Do you need some help?
It's ok.
OK...
(One day ago The first dinner of men who didn't know each other)
Got refused immediately.
(Noisy Jeong-hyeon: Look like wasabi)
It looks like wasabi.
-I can not see it clearly. I have presbyopia.
-There is no remaining.
(Noisy Jeong-hyeon: Look like wasabi)
-I can not see it clearly. I have presbyopia.
-There is no remaining.
(Unlike the first night, the second night was lively)
-I can not see it clearly. I have presbyopia.
-There is no remaining.
(Unlike the first night, the second night was lively)
Do Vietnamese spring rolls need pork?
(Hyeok-jun is dealing with the meat)
It depends on what you like.
Is this enough?
It looks like it's been shredded.
Put it in the miscellaneous vegetables.
(Hmmm)
-I can open it for you.
-Thanks.
(Warm)
-I can open it for you.
-Thanks.
(Crack)
It's kind of like playing house in kindergarten.
(A peaceful dinnertime, everything is going well.)
(At the same time, a man driving toward the house)
(Chop chop chop)
(Chang-min and Hyeok-jun are standing side by side cooking)
(Peek)
Wow, it must be delicious.
Who wants to taste the meat?
Me.
(Peek)
It tastes good only when its hot.
(Wow)
Does it taste good?
(Yeah~)
Yes, perfect.
(Eun-chan's ears turn red quietly)
We have this, this!
-But I thought we had a terrace here.
-Yes.
(Chang-min: But I thought we had a terrace.)
-But I thought we had a terrace here.
-Yes.
The weather is good enough to eat there.
Yesterday or today, I was saying
that the wind on the terrace is cool,
so I want to have a date there.
-To be honest, I want to eat outside.
-That is to say!
All done?
Check it out above.
(Eun-chan: Let's go.)
-Let's go.
-To the roof.
(Eun-chan: Let's go.)
-Let's go.
-To the roof.
We can take one each to go up.
To the terrace!
(Six men moving their cooking to the terrace)
-Be careful with this.
-A few trips back and forth should do the trick.
(Six men moving their cooking to the terrace)
-Be careful with this.
-A few trips back and forth should do the trick.
(Eun-chan: What a beautiful day! Look at the sunset! )
It's a beautiful day. Look at the sunset.
Looks like we're going to start a fire here.
(Terrace dinner for a different vibe)
The wind is cool, too.
(And a strange man who radiate different feelings)
("A new man coming...?" )
(His Man)
How about playing darts?
-That's great!
-Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Game time! Two for a team.
(Chan-gyu: Two men a team.)
The losing team's penalty is to say who they called.
(Chan-gyu & Chang-min Team)
(Jeong-hyeon & Hyeok-jun Team)
Are you good at this?
Let's try.
(Jeong-hyeon & Hyeok-jun Team)
(Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team)
Let's try.
(Jeong-hyeon & Hyeok-jun Team)
(Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team)
Ok, we two are a team.
(Starting with Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team and throwing darts)
(Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team)
-Stand here.
(Starting with Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team and throwing darts)
I throw! 3 2 1!
This time I throw dart.
(Almost to the bullseye)
9 points.
(Eun-chan is good at defensing)
All right.
You have to make it 10, right to the bulls eye.
(Eun-chan is good at defensing)
(Teammate is satisfied)
You have to make it 10, right to the bulls eye.
What happened?
(Teammate is satisfied)
(Seon-yul, Eun-chan's teammate, also gets high scores)
What happened?
(End with Eun-chan hitting the bullseye)
-Great job!
-I hit it!
(End with Eun-chan hitting the bullseye)
-Great job!
-I hit it!
(Top score Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team 298)
-Great job!
-I hit it!
(Top score Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team 298)
(Next is Hyeok-jun & Jeong-hyeon Team)
(Be on Hyeok-jun's team)
(Serious)
-It's over.
-What's the score?
(Whoo Hyeok-jun&Jeong-hyeonTeam 282)
-It's over.
-What's the score?
(Whoo Hyeok-jun&Jeong-hyeonTeam 282)
All right.
(Haha)
This brother has a knack for being right in the bullseye.
(Jeong-hyeon: Brother Chang-min does well in hitting the bullseye.)
-Three hits straight in the bullseye yesterday.
-No.
(Jeong-hyeon: Brother Chang-min does well in hitting the bullseye.)
This brother has a knack for being right in the bullseye.
-Three hits straight in the bullseye yesterday.
-No.
(Jeong-hyeon: Three hits straight in the middle yesterday.)
-Three hits straight in the bullseye yesterday.
-No.
(The order of the Chang-min & Chan-gyu team, the spearhead in the center, as predicted by Jeong-hyeon, Chang-min who accumulates points)
Just make sure you don't miss.
(Nervous Chan-gyu also finished well)
Cool! Done！
(End with hitting the bullseye)
(Jeong-hyeon: Looks like we're the last team.)
Looks like we're the last team.
(Chang-min & Chan-gyu Team Score 298)
((Cool exit))
Great!
(Eun-chan & Seon-yul Team Score 298 Chang-min & Chan-gyu Team Score 298 Co-NO.1 Hyeok-jun & Jeong-hyeon Team Score 282 The last one)
-Co-No.1.
Look at the expressions on Jeong-hyeon's face.
(The penalty for disclosing the name of the phone call is Hyeok-jun & Jeong-hyeon)
You did a great job!
-Now say it.
-As much as I hate to admit it.
(Time to listen to Hyeok-jun's & Jeong-hyeon's inner thoughts)
-Now say it.
-As much as I hate to admit it.
I say first.
I called brother Seon-yul.
-Ah, brother Seon-yul.
- Don't you know?
(Chang-min: Seon-yu did not know?)
-Ah, brother Seon-yul.
- Don't you know?
I really don't know it.
(Chang-min: Seon-yu did not know?)
-Ah, brother Seon-yul.
- Don't you know?
I really don't know it.
Anyone would have known.
I really have no ideas at all.
Jeong-hyeon and brother Seon yul are giving us a surprise.
Jeong-hyeon is interested in Seon-yul.
Have no idea at all.
A little unexpected on the phone.
(Jeong-hyeon: (Hyeok-jun) It's your turn, brother.)
It's your turn, brother.
I called Chang-min.
(Surprised)
(Peek)
I don't know either.
(Jeong-hyeon: No, the sound...)
No, the voice is not very clear.
I could not hear clearly.
(Jeong-hyeon: No, the sound...)
-The voices are hard to distinguish.
-That is to say.
I thought he would know after hearing my voice.
But it turns out he did not.
-Interesting.
(What changes do unexpected confessions lead to? )