♫ Beautiful day, remember this season now ♫
♫ The streets where petals fluttered in the wind ♫
♫ Those moments when I first met you ♫
♫ Are racing through my mind one by one ♫
♫ The warmth in your eyes ♫
♫ The scent on the wind  ♫
♫ Back then, even in our wildest dreams,
we could never have imagined ♫
♫ That we wanted each other ♫
♫ I won't let you go again ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand ♫
♫ Beautiful day, remember this season now ♫
♫ The streets where petals fluttered in the wind ♫
♫ Beautiful day, remember this feeling now ♫
♫ My feelings are getting stronger, I'll confess
them to you today ♫
♫ You are the one in my life, you are the one in my life ♫
♫ You are the only one I'll be waiting for ♫
♫ You are the only one, I'll be waiting for you ♫
â„ï¸Cherry Blossoms After WinterðŸŒ¸
Hey, Haebom!
Let me borrow some money.
I forgot my wallet today.
Really?
What are you doing?
Dude, I need some money urgently, so I'm borrowing some.
I didn't bring any.
What's up with him today?
Haebom!
You brought all this just for me?
You're the man.
- Give it back.
- I'll make good use of it.
Please.
Are you crazy?
I said give it back!
Did you just shout at me?
Give it back!
Are you out of your mind?
What are you looking at?
What are you looking at?!
Mind your own business.
Hey!
Let's go and have some fun!
Oh, you surprised me.
Taesung!
Stop messing around and give it back.
You're not asking for this, are you?
I'll make the most of it.
Let's go. It's my treat.
- Okay.
- Cool.
Are you seriously letting this happen?
Shut the hell up!
[SWEET GAZE]
Taesung.
"I'll make the most of it." Oh my gosh!
Why did you do that? You never care about anyone else.
Even if he's not interested, he's a good person.
Are you going to give the money back to Haebom?
You guys used it to buy all that.
What?
What kind of asshole are you?
I guess he means it.
Ma'am,
I'm sorry.
Looks like he cried.
His eyes are puffy.
Look at him.
Give him the money back.
Or he won't be able to go home.
Haebom, pick what you want to eat.
You too, Taesung.
That's a big number.
[STRAWBERRY CAKE / 28,000 WON]
[CREAM BREAD / 1,000 WON]
Just this?
Yeah.
My little Haebom loves his cream bread.
I'll take all these cream buns, please.
Ma'am,
I'll eat every last crumb.
Should I ask Taesung if he wants to share?
But he doesn't like sweet stuff.
Ah… I…
Would you like some of this?
Do you want to share it?
You don't like it?
It's fine.
Hang on a second.
Wow! How did you…
It's yours.
Taesung, thank you so much.
I thought it was gone forever.
Haebom, I know I'm late but happy birthday.
Haebom?
How long has it been since Taesung said my name?
Why aren't you eating?
I'm just savoring it.
Should I go and buy another one?
No, you don't.
Haebom!
What?
How long are you going to put up with them?
Should I fight back?
You don't need to fight them.
But you've got to deal with it somehow.
Anyway, I'll never see them again after graduation.
Until then, I can take it.
Really?
You probably don't want my help, right?
Right.
So, please don't tell your mom.
I don't want her to worry.
Okay.
If that's what you want, I'll keep your secret.
Thanks.
It's the weekend but Haebom said he was going out to study.
Has he gone to the library again?
He left early this morning.
How's he doing at school?
We students are all the same.
Does he get along with the other kids?
Come to think of it,
he's never brought a friend home.
Seniors don't have time for friends.
Are you just robots?
You should hang out with friends and date as well as study.
Mom! Don't go around talking like that.
I hate it when you pretend to be cool.
Hey!
It's not pretense. I'm a caring person.
[HAPPY BIRTHDAY]
[MANY HAPPY RETURNS OF…]
Here you are.
It's much better if the giver writes it themselves.
It's more meaningful if it has a few lines straight from the heart.
They were probably nervous.
Even if you're nervous, it's cute if you write it from the heart.
A word-perfect confession of love lacks sincerity.
Taesung!
You're home late.
Yeah.
You weren't waiting for me, were you?
Just getting some fresh air.
Did you get a lot done at the library?
Well, you know…
Haebom!
Yes?
I hope I don't make you uncomfortable.
Let's go in.
Sure.
No, I don't want to…
Taesung, Haebom's your friend.
I hate it. I don't want him as my brother.
I don't want Haebom as my brother.
What was Taesung really thinking?
Hey! What's your relationship with Taesung?
Can I say that we're friends?
Hey!
Why aren't you answering?
I said we're friends.
Friends?
Oh my gosh!
So, "friend" in English?
That's what you mean?
Stop lying, asshole!
We are friends.
Really?
Let's say that that's true.
Then, would that bastard consider you a friend?
Answer me, you asshole!
Come on.
Enough with those questions.
But you've never talked to him all this time.
Would Haebom call you a friend, too?
Of course.
Why are you always so curious?
Hey!
I'm your best friend, so, of course, I'm curious.
Do you think I'd care if we weren't close?
This is between me and Haebom.
So just leave it. Okay?
But…
Is it wrong to care?
When did they even become friends?
What's got you upset?
He's not hanging out with us these days.
It's because of Haebom.
No wonder.
Hey! Don't you care at all?
Are you mad that he didn't mention it or are you mad that you lost him?
Neither, both, whatever!
There, there…
Let's go.
I left my English book at home.
Friends can borrow each other's textbooks, can't they?
So, this girl Andy, what kind of girl is she?
"I met some girl."
What kind of girl she is...
You can think of it as modifying the noun that precedes it.
Let's finish here for today.
I really hate English.
I'm beat.
Taesung!
May I ask you a favor?
Can I borrow your English book?
I was expecting something else.
Okay.
Really?
Thanks.
- What the hell are you doing?
- My bad.
My hand slipped.
You cowardly b.
What, you asshole?
You think Taesung will save you again?
Are you blind?
You little shit.
Just one hit?
Do it!
You're pathetic.
What?
You little shit…
I'm going to kill you.
What's wrong?
- Taesung!
- Stop it!
- You fucking son of a bitch.
- What are you doing?
- Hey!
- What's up?
- What's wrong?
- Stop, leave him alone.
Why are you like this?
Son of a bitch!
Taesung.
Haebom!
Eating cream buns makes you happy, right?
I'll buy you one every day.
Don't cry any more.
Okay.
Mommy said my grandma left for a trip with your parents.
A trip? Where?
Somewhere far, far away.
Far away? Where?
To the stars.
Stars?
Yeah.
And at nighttime, they're looking down at you.
Can't I go with them?
Nope.
If you leave, I'll be sad.
You don't want to be without me, do you?
No. I don't want to.
So don't go anywhere without me.
Pinky promise!
Promise.
You remember that.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thanks.
Would you like some?
No.
I'll have some.
Okay.
Here you go.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
â„ï¸ Our love blooms after winter ðŸŒ¸ Team @Viki.com
♫  I will put you safely in a box that's nothing special ♫
♫ So you don't lose your color and fade away ♫
♫ And leave you there until I'm no longer sad ♫
♫ And I have to open the box gently ♫
♫  So not to disturb the thick, thick dust on that plain, plain box ♫
♫ That box, which is filled with you ♫
♫ Where should I put it? ♫
♫ Where would be a good place to safely hide it away?  ♫
[CHERRY BLOSSOMS AFTER WINTER]
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
I'm too late.
[CON'GAY'TULATIONS!]
Everyone's going crazy.
Don't you care?
Don't worry about them.
Hey! Seo Haebom!
I'm right for sure.
Haebom must have drugged him with something.
I'll go with Taesung.
The girl who dated Taesung...
Was it Seri?
Yeah.
Someone who laughs a lot and is caring.
How should I put it?
Don't overthink it.
I know that but...
My feelings for Haebom aren't going away.
- What if he gets hurt...
- Whether he likes me or not...
I hope Haebom makes a decision.
You, I, and Taesung,
we're a family. Got it?
Yeah.
Taesung...
I thought you hated me.
I never hated you.
♫ That box, which is filled with you ♫
♫ Where should I put it? ♫