♫ Beautiful day, remember this season now ♫
♫ The streets where petals fluttered in the wind ♫
♫ Those moments when I first met you ♫
[SEO HAEBOM / OK JINUK]
♫ Are racing through my mind one by one ♫
[CHO TAESUNG / KANG HUI]
♫ The warmth in your eyes ♫
♫ The scent on the wind  ♫
♫ Back then, even in our wildest dreams,
we could never have imagined ♫
♫ That we wanted each other ♫
♫ I won't let you go again ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand ♫
♫ Beautiful day, remember this season now ♫
♫ The streets where petals fluttered in the wind ♫
♫ Beautiful day, remember this feeling now ♫
♫ My feelings are getting stronger, I'll confess
them to you today ♫
♫ You are the one in my life, you are the one in my life ♫
♫ You are the only one I'll be waiting for ♫
♫ You are the only one, I'll be waiting for you ♫
â„ï¸Cherry Blossoms After WinterðŸŒ¸
Taesung, I'm coming in.
He used to jump up as soon as I opened the door.
Now he doesn't even stir.
Has he gotten comfortable with me?
Taesung!
Wake up. It's time for breakfast.
Let's go!
Just five more minutes.
Then just five more minutes.
Is that the sound of my heart beating?
There must be something wrong with it.
It's been five minutes.
Not yet.
[THE START OF SOMETHING SPECIAL]
Haebom, what's your dream?
My dream?
For example, what you want to do for work,
or what kind of life you'll lead…
Have you thought about it?
I'm not sure.
Right now, like everyone else, I'll go to college.
I want to try supporting myself.
Alone?
Yes.
Will you be finding a place for yourself when you go to college?
Yes. That's what I'm thinking.
I get it.
I moved out as soon as I entered college.
I really don't remember why I wanted to get away from my parents so badly.
Ma'am!
Please don't be upset because I want to move out.
I'm not upset.
It totally makes sense.
I've always appreciated what you've done for me.
Thanks for saying that.
Haebom,
do you think that you could take those heavy words
and just save them for Mother's Day?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
When you talk so seriously, you come off like a stranger.
Okay.
Ma'am!
Can I ask why you took me in?
- I'll go first.
- No, I'll go first.
Follow me.
- I'm going first this time.
- Catch me.
I'm first!
- Wait for me.
- Eunseon!
I won't ever let Haebom grow up without a mom and dad.
Your mother always said she didn't want you to grow up…
without parents like she did.
I wanted to keep her word.
Haebom!
I hope that wherever you are, whatever you do,
you are happy.
Whenever you make a decision, don't think about me or Taesung.
Consider yourself first, and do what will make you happy.
I will.
Promise me.
Where have you been?
On a date with Haebom.
Next time, go with me.
Are you talking to me? Not your mom?
Yeah, you.
Where are you off to?
On a date.
Shall I bring you something back?
Something tasty.
Got it.
Don't treat me like a baby brother.
My birthday comes first! I'm older than you.
Really, sir?
Mr. Haebom!
That's more like it.
You'll be late. Better get a move on.
- Of course, we're watching a scary movie.
- I don't like horror!
Then go home.
- I'm scared.
- I can watch it with Taesung.
Taesung!
Oh, Cho Taesung!
Seri booked the tickets so pay her back.
Cool.
What's up?
I don't have my wallet.
Have you lost it?
I'm not sure. Wait a sec.
It's Taesung.
Hello.
Hey.
Can you check if my wallet's at home?
Okay.
There's one here, is this it?
- Don't touch it.
- Okay.
Now I've checked that it's at home, you can just leave it.
Okay.
It's lucky that it's at home.
I think I'll just go home.
I don't have my wallet.
What are you talking about? This is my first time out in ages.
Yeah, come on! I'll lend you some money.
Exactly! She's loaded.
Shut it.
Sorry.
Taesung!
Why are you home so early?
Where's my wallet?
Over there on the table.
You didn't open it, right?
Yeah, I didn't touch it.
Count your money.
I didn't mean it like that.
Here.
You forgot your wallet, how…
I borrowed some money.
What? You didn't have to do that.
Hello! My name is Haebom.
I see.
You're so polite.
You must be Taesung.
Nice to meet you.
You have to say hello, too, Haebom.
He's like this sometimes.
Taesung, you have to say hello.
From now on, we're friends.
At that time, I was acting out because my parents weren't getting along.
You were my first friend.
I've liked you since then, Haebom.
Taesung!
Time for dinner.
Did something happen?
Let me hold you for a moment.
Anything happen today?
Nah, everything was great today.
That's good.
Taesung! Haebom!
Hi!
Where are you two sneaking off to?
Are you ditching us again?
Of course not.
We're off on a date.
- Is that how it is?
- Barf!
Just the two of you are going to hang out.
We're running an errand at the supermarket.
See you tomorrow.
- Bye!
Later!
What a cute couple.
I think I've gotten too comfortable with you.
[BLOOMS/ FLOWER SHOP]
♫ A day like a painting and a night like a novel ♫
♫ I'll collect them all to give to you ♫
♫ The letter I wrote secretly ♫
♫ I'll write your name first ♫
[TAESUNG'S BIRTHDAY]
♫ Tell me what you want ♫
♫ I want to do everything for you ♫
A gift should be what the other person wants to get, not what you want to give.
Pardon me?
The older you get, the more you see.
Taesung!
What do you want for your birthday?
A present?
Yes.
You!
He definitely said me.
What did he mean?
Can I tell you what I want for my birthday?
Huh? Taesung!
What do you want?
You said you've decided. What is it?
What is it?
I'm the one getting a present, why are you more excited?
Am I?
So, what do you want?
Well..
Let's have a drink together.
Alcohol?
Just the two of us?
Yep.
You don't want to?
No. I'd love to.
Have you ever drank alcohol before?
Nope. It's my first time, too.
♫ In the dark night, I wonder about you ♫
Cheers.
♫ I think of you ♫
♫ Until the bright sunlight sticks out its head, goodnight ♫
♫ I'll protect you ♫
How is it?
I like it.
Me too.
But is this enough?
I really wanted to do what you wanted.
It's great.
It's the first thing we've done together since we've grown up.
Cheers!
♫ The deeper the love, the more I will love you ♫
♫ Trust me ♫
♫ I'll trust you a little more ♫
♫ Loving you ♫
♫ Forever baby, baby, baby for my life ♫
♫ I don't want anything ♫
♫ With love and hope just stay by my side like this ♫
♫ Forever baby, baby, baby for my life ♫
♫ This is different from other relationships ♫
♫ You're special to me ♫
♫ Now I like you more than myself ♫
♫ Falling in you ♫
Haebom!
Are you drunk?
I miss my mom and dad.
I'm sorry I'm the only one left alive.
Haebom.
Taesung!
You're not going to disappear, are you?
You'll stay by my side, won't you?
I'm sorry. It's your birthday.
I must be drunk. Talking about my mom and dad like this.
Sorry. I've ruined it.
Sorry.
I'd better stop drinking.
Just forget about it.
♫ Will I be able to see you again ♫
♫ before this winter passes? ♫
♫ Will you remember the white snow when it falls? ♫
I'll stay by your side.
Is that a promise?
Yeah. I promise.
♫ Will I be able to see you again ♫
♫ before the cherry blossoms fade? ♫
♫ Will the white petals fluttering in the wind remind me of you? ♫
♫ The time we spent together as exciting
as the first sign of spring ♫
♫ Will our love bloom again ♫
♫ Like the delicate flowers buried in the snow? ♫
♫ Will I be able to see you again ♫
♫ before the cherry blossoms fade? ♫
♫ Will the white petals fluttering in the wind remind me of you? ♫
♫ The time we spent together as exciting
as the first sign of spring ♫
[CHERRY BLOSSOMS AFTER WINTER]
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
â„ï¸ Our love blooms after winter ðŸŒ¸ Team @Viki.com
Oh, these kids…
Haebom!
Don't you remember what you said to me?
What did I say?
You're not going to believe me even if I tell you.
Haebom, shall I set you up on a blind date?
- Haebom!
- Yes?
Hasn't Taesung looked down lately?
Did something happen?
No.
I like you.
I've always been grateful.
I'm not talking about as friends.
I'm totally happy with the way things are.
Are you?
I don't want to disappoint your mom.
Don't lie!
You like me.
♫ Someone precious to me ♫
♫ To be together forever ♫