you
will expose
what
this
Chi An, it's me!
Father...
I just wanted to walk out, but I lost my way.
My hands... my hands hurt.
I know. I know. I'll take you to the doctor.
Li Zhi An is always in danger.
Even if he dies, he'll still be alive.
And... these safety services are problematic.
I don't know why Prince Qi believes in them.
Husband...
I'm afraid it hurts. Be gentle.
Okay.
You can't see.
I have to let Hua Mei with you.
I don't want to see her hurt.
Okay.
Why did you go in there?
I was near. I was so exhausted.
It's just that the guards are too nervous to do some work.
I see.
You're so considerate of the people.
You're also a good person.
You're busy with business every day.
You should take care of yourself.
Okay.
Zhi An, I'm busy with work today.
I have something to discuss with you.
Maybe I'll be too busy.
Husband said that as long as Zhi An can help,
he'll be fine.
There's a woman in the north who's not well.
She's a vice-president.
She's been working hard in the murder house.
Zhi An.
She's been working hard for ten years.
But later,
she finally found out the evidence of the murder.
What made me confused was that
she obviously had the chance to meet the murderer.
Why didn't she choose to take care of him?
Zhi An.
If...
If your family is in danger,
will you choose to just stay in the bloodbath or stay in the house?
If it were me,
I wouldn't have just asked for the murderer.
That would be a life-and-death situation.
The family's protection would have been meaningless.
I'll definitely push the murderer's whole plan
to make his true face public.
Only then can he experience the pain of the living.
I'll also give my family a full chance.
He's a justice.
Of course.
If you have a wife like him,
you'll definitely give your wife a justice.
What's wrong with him?
He's looking like a real criminal.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hua Mei! Hua Mei!
The palace's own emperor
is trying to meet the murderer.
It's not like he's not here.
He's just here to save himself.
Zhi An.
My husband.
You called me?
But you don't feel well?
It's okay.
I'm fine now.
That's good.
According to the time, the western emperor will be here soon.
I wonder what Zhu Huaiji will do with those letters.
Will he send Zhu Huai Chen to the court?
Commander Duan.
I heard that the prince was injured last night.
I think he's recovered.
Please don't worry.
I'm fine with the letter that my husband took care of last night.
The prince just got here.
He doesn't know the rules.
He'll be injured if he goes out of the palace.
I came here to tell you that
in the prince's mansion,
you need to be in the court.
You can't go out of the palace at night.
Commander Duan is a great man.
He doesn't look like a legend
but he's not good at making people's hands dirty.
Commander Duan.
You did pretend last night.
You can tell by your look.
So what?
That's just my feelings for my husband.
Instead of my husband's idea,
why don't you go and keep an eye on the prince?
Why are you so stubborn?
I was thinking for you.
Maybe you can make a name for yourself.
Why don't you say something?
Maybe the prince has rejected you.
Of course not.
I was in the trouble of the prince before.
I was the prince's savior.
I remember that it was Duan Yu Rou who saved him
while he was in the brothel.
You guys,
hurry up and take the prince to the palace.
The prince will take the prince to the temple in the afternoon.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
It turns out that the prince saved Duan Yu Rou
so he was the one who was killed.
So what will happen to the prince's heart
this time?
I don't know.