We are both confused
We can't only argue
We do understand what is going on
Let's look at that
So first we need to defeat her
Why?
Theoons are true
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure if I can do it.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Okay.
Take care.
Thank you, Mr. Bai.
Thank you.
I'm so tired.
Everyone is free now, right?
Yes, we are free!
Thank you, everyone!
No need!
I will have River King rules the whole world.
What a frical job!
What kind of job could a celebrity like this be?
You're deaf, but you have to handle the house.
What job?
Hard to handle?
Can I even handle this?
Noporoo from reason
Imperingly...
Separated from their dawn
I'm going to make a little bit of a
one
burger
chicken
Yunshen
Though short
You have like fire
With plenty of power
In next life
I'll do nothing
I want to be an ordinary person.
Fei,
I wish you to be a human.
To live in a normal world,
and to be loved by the world.
To get
the peace and prosperity of the world.
The dream is so hard to forget.
Who will stop me?
Time is so short.
It's hard to get used to it.
Every time I pass by, I'm so confused.
I'm so confused.
I've seen the world before.
I don't know what to do with me.
I'll stay here.
As long as I'm here,
this world
won't forget you.
Rice
trophies made of rice
just like the years.
I chose
Nihuang ...
A heart like a fairytale
leaps into him.
She tried and truly got executed
but at the opposite time she'd suffer great grief.
Even if I have a wish, I can always draw the land as old as I can.
Bai Jiu likes Ying Hong.
He should be happy now.
You like it too?
You are more powerful than the little girls in the world in the Golden Age.
The Golden Age is also the world's treasure.
But we don't care much about it.
As a demon, you can use magic to make a bigger fire than the one in the world.
Turn around.
Do you know that this kind of fire is cold?
Cold?
It looks dangerous, but it's not a problem.
The fire is so beautiful.
It's a pity that Xiao Zhu didn't see it.
He didn't eat the food for the whole day.
I'm starving.
Xiao Zhu.
Go to the hotel tomorrow.
I'll catch some rabbits for you.
Come on.
Don't be too greedy.
The three of us will be able to get through the competition.
We have to.
There is food and drink.
You don't have to be too polite.
Wenqiang.
Mingyue.
Taken several months cycle.
Have you taught me to overlap?
Have you Childe Liu?
Are you sure?
Yes.
This is your имityyl phase.
Wen'yi has finallyworld.
You should celebrate it tonight.
I'm not going to sing.
You sing?
Do you want to listen?
What are you looking at?
I heard that Master Zhuo
is a good dancer.
I'm so happy.
Come on.
This...
Brother Zhuo.
Come on.
Master Zhuo.
Brother Zhuo is good at dancing.
Good.
I think it's okay.
Master Zhuo is not good at dancing.
It's too hard for him
to dance.
You're here.
I can dance.
Zhao Yuzhao.
You're a good dancer.
You should get up
and have fun.
You're here too.
The song is called
The Song of Love.
Why?
Answer me.
Stop.
If it's difficult,
You have to say it first.
Also, I have different plans for my future life.
May I dream of adm ilkun to be another nightbreak.
I'll make it for you.
I promise.
Thank you.
I'll be back.
I'll see you in the next video.
I'm sorry.
Sister.
I'm not in danger.
Why are you here?
I'm here to sit with you.
Sister, you're not eating.
If you don't eat, I'll eat.
I'll eat.
Zhao Yunzhu, Zhao Yunzhu.
Zhao Yunzhu.
Jinx Barang.
Xiaojiu.
Wake up early tomorrow morning.
And you, Zhao Yunzhu.
Old!
Don't call themIDs.
Well, let's play the game now
OK
You have grass with a square삳
And there is the cuckoo
Why would I keep it?
Called Honestlyc
I can't let others be fooled up like us.
If someone lied to me,
I might be overjoyed and nauseous with all this.
I will know who Mazhu Blue LOL Cares was late.
Then, you start.
Let's start!
Okay.
thermal persuaded
ordinary
Sister Pei
You
Do you change your play composition?
Are you Chongying's spy?
What's going on?
What do you mean?
We received a letter from Mr. Situ.
Someone told Chongying about it.
That means we have a spy in Chongying.
Chongying knows very well about our actions.
That's why we're so busy.
The less we know about Kunlun,
the less Chongying can know about it.
So we have to keep it secret.
The law of Kunlun is to kill the villagers.
We should go to Kunlun Mountain.
Who affected the Eagle Teeth?
It caused us to come to Sinali Water Town.
Well...
Sorry.
When I was thinking about Kunlun Mountain,
I suddenly thought of Mr. Pei.
The Sinali Water Town in Kunlun Mountain.
It's so hot.
Who sent us here?
Let's find out.
Wait.
What?
We're not guilty?
Don't you think it's strange?
They took away Xiaojiu.
They want to take us there.
Mr. Zhuo and Zhao Yanzhou are gone.
They must be able to save Xiaojiu.
They went to the commandment.
They should wait here.
Wanhua,
why do you look down on us?
Are you hiding it at the ps cloudy?
Well...
No.
Many waiters come all the way to you.
I came here to Sachya.
I'm scared
Mr. Pei
Are you okay?
I'm scared, Pei Zui Xing
You
You are a little bit...
This is what you call a positive
I told you
There's no way that time can change the mind
The reason he went back to the Wanchu is because the grass didn't have a pig
It was Mr. Pei Zui who used the water-based ice tree I called him
to control the Wanchu of grass
Mr. Pei Zui is not a good man
I taught you the ability to get together with Wen Xiao to fool people
You want to try me?
Yes
After all, you are the most capable of us six
People in Wanchu will have a special English character
representing their identity
I have never recognized the commander of Wanchu
This is not a secret
But I have already been assigned to the command
and Wanchu is not a bad guy
Besides, I joined you because I was trying to sleep
It's not you, is it?
Besides, I was also hit by a plague in Lin Xi's wound
I might die
If I really did not play the role of a bad guy
I would be so happy
I think he makes sense
Since we have a role in it
then why can't this person be you?
Sister Pei, you are so noisy
I want to join the Chongying
I heard that they have a lot of precious intelligence
to deal with the plague
But my father did not let me go
I have never seen a person like you
Every time a white girl is very nice to a demon
I absolutely do not know
A good demon is a half of the demon
A demon
Why do you look at me?
How could I be a spy?
Not necessarily
If I were a spy
why would I have to help you fulfill your mission
I would be so tired to be a cow
You are so bitter
Anyway, you are so mean
I am a demon
I am a special killer
Moreover, they also want to steal my internal order
Chuo Xiaochen, please understand
Please take a good look
I remember someone said
in the J14, there was a threat to the capital
If we do not cooperate with you
you will go to the Chongying
The plan is all a plan
Do you all believe in the plan?
What's so interesting?
A woman who can be a great woman
The pain of the world
is so painful
Who is next?
Him
Me?
I am a chef
A chef is also suitable for the secret
Before I met you
I didn't know what I was doing in the J14
Moreover, without my mountain and countryside
we can't go back
our heads are on the ground
Yes
The little mountain god's plan
is not yet complete
Chongying can't see it
The pain of the world is so painful
Speaking of the mountain god's plan
we rushed back to J14
Who was it?
We went to the mountain god's plan
and almost got the ambush of Chongying
I am just a doctor
And I am going to the bank
Ask me
Chongying also has a doctor
I don't know kung fu
But you know how to take medicine
and how to take pills
and how to take needles
You are not a normal doctor
I am afraid of death, blood, and fever
I am just a doctor
because my mother is sick
I want to cure my mother's illness
Your mother's illness?
If your wish is to cure your mother's illness
Chongying has been in the hospital for more than a year
and collected many herbs and talents
Maybe one of them can help you realize your wish
Maybe
No need to say more
Chongying's people
have a female assassin every night
and have a smoke
Drink more
I am thirsty
I will have a drink
It's just a little bit
What's so good about it?
I will have a drink
Come on, Xiaojiu
Little boy
Baijiu
We have to see your hand
Actually, the person who is trying to kill you
has a hint
He hinted to us
that the person who is most likely to be a spy
is Baijiu
I am not a spy
Xiaozhu, believe me
It's not true
Then show your hand
I will show my hand
and see if you know
Even if there is a cloud
it can't be said that he is a spy
Is there another possibility?
So
you have seen Baijiu's hand
No
I just asked
Yinglei
You are so stupid
No, Xiaojiu is not a spy
Think about it
He is always in our treatment
If he is not there
he will die long ago
And
Don't say that
You are not a spy
You are a spy
So is there a spy or not?
I will show you
Xiaozhu
You are married
Baijiu
Xiaojiu
You are asleep
Xiao Bai Tu
We are too violent
I will compensate you
No
Xiao Bai Tu
We are too violent
I will compensate you
Xiaojiu
I will give you all the time to die
Don't be angry
Xiaojiu
Why did you tell them
about the spy and the spy?
You know my relationship with Baijiu
I really don't want her to risk it
But if I stop her
she will fight me
That's why I will do this
You
My lord
The spy found out
He will secretly show the secret of the spy
with a secret agent
in the dark
in the direction of Kunlun Mountain
Xiaojiu
Xiao Bai Tu
The chief sent the chicken to us
Xiaojiu
Come and eat
We will leave after eating
It seems that Xiao Bai Tu cares the most
is the hero in his heart
Lord Xiao Zhuo
You are too soft
Are you sure you don't have to mess with him?
Everyone is too soft
How can you let me be alone?
But he obviously
hates you the most
Zhao Yanzhou
Are you happy now?
I am happy
Finally someone surpassed you
and got the test
Everyone is fine
But Hong Xiao Hai
is too difficult
for our Lord Xiao Zhou
Hong Xiao Hai
It's easy
It's easy to make him
Give him candy
Just touch his head
Candy
Everyone is very brave
Please give a good look
The first is Kunlun Mountain
Shen Miao
Let's go
Come
Let go
Old man
It's time for the feast
Little Ying Lei is back
What?
Don't you have to
pursue your great ideal?
I still need to pursue
not because I found the Baizi order
I will come
to the feast
Lord Shen
This is my grandfather Ying Zhao
and the other is God of the Mountain
Greetings, Lord Shen
Thank you for taking back
the Baizi order
The God of the Mountain
will obey your order
Lord Zhuyin
I just got back to the Baizi order
Can you call me Lord?
I dare not say anything
I still need your advice
You brat
You really got back
I will hit you
You are lying
You are a coward
I said don't hit me
I will hit you
You are a coward
Come here
I will hit you
You are a coward
I will tell you
that you are a coward
You can't even get back to the Baizi order
You are a coward
I will hit you
You are the master of the legend
Lord Shen knows me
Legend says
you are the most mysterious dragon god
You can shine the darkest night
like a demon
I have served Zhuyin
for years
Now, Kunlun Mountain is about to be destroyed.
The Great Emperor has chosen a new route.
The 28 Star Cult has been destroyed.
We have no power to go back to the Heavens.
But now, the Goddess is back.
She only needs to start the Star Formation.
She can save the Great Emperor if she uses her power to save Bai Ze.
There is something very strange.
Grandpa Ying Zhao, you live well.
You should help me analyze it.
You are still so annoying.
You are so annoying.
What is it? Ask me.
Bai Ze Ling has been dead for so long.
I didn't expect that he is a child.
He has been left in Lu Wo and Wen Xiao.
But why can't he feel Bai Ze Ling's existence?
From the first generation,
to make peace,
Bai Ze Ling has to be divided into two groups.
One person, one demon, and one leader.
These two leaders are both kind and mutual.
They can start and develop power.
No.
It's too sudden.
Since the Goddess has regained her power,
I think you two have both trust each other.
We have both faith in each other.
You are so despicable.
Xiao Zhuo and Sister Wen have been together since childhood.
You are so ridiculous.
What's wrong with mutual love?
Friendship is love.
We are close friends.
We are together all the time.
Don't be so anxious.
You are so strict.
Don't talk about this.
Let's hurry up and open the magic.
But Kunlun Mountain's spiritual power has already failed.
The Star Formation needs a lot of spiritual power.
It's best to bring it to the 50th.
The heavenly power will be activated at the right time.
Let's wait until tomorrow.
Take them to the water town in Sinan.
Can you do it?
When do you want to take them?
You can't go and you can't be late.
I'm sorry.