I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
necessity
America
Episode 21
Prince No. 13,
no wonder you named her Classics King.
I didn't know that you
came so hastily to meet me,
what do you think?
How could you be with Prince Qi?
I didn't want to be with Prince Qi.
But since he's here, I'll be his witness.
Zhu Huai Chen bullied me.
He asked Prince Qi to pretend to be with me.
I can't bear to be humiliated like this.
Princess is old enough to be with me.
Please help me contact the Li family.
I want to be reasonable.
Prince Qi is making you witness.
He admitted this to you personally.
You finally grew up.
Since you all know that you're the Nanyang royal family,
you're indeed a perfect match.
Royal Consort, you're not a person's attitude.
I don't want to be a royal consort.
Don't be too naive.
I was still thinking about you before I was born.
I didn't expect you to be like this.
It seems that I really begged wrongly.
Do you always miss me?
Xiao Lang!
Your poison has already entered your heart.
It's fine.
There are always some things in life.
But Xiao Lang has been waiting for too long in heaven.
Please hurry and change me.
What are you saying?
Why is Princess poisoned?
Tell her.
You always want to protect her.
But she's trying to pursue the truth with her heart.
You don't have to hide it.
General Xiao is your uncle.
You should know how he died.
Ten years ago,
Nanyang found out that there was a Beijing spy in the palace.
Nanyang destroyed the alliance and two countries' war.
Uncle Xiao led soldiers to kill the general.
But if I tell you,
there's no such a Beijing spy.
I'm not a spy.
I'm a spy.
How do you remember the time when you were still alive?
I don't know.
He told me about this.
Under my investigation,
everything about Beijing's spy was just a lie.
I found out about this by the emperor.
He was afraid that I would attack the world.
So he poisoned me.
I'm so stupid.
If it wasn't for him,
what would Xiao Lang and I do?
So...
So everything was Nanyang's scheme.
He was to make a war with Beijing?
Yes.
Father is the one who can be a man who can be a man of wild ambition.
The two countries' war was a long-term battle.
Nanyang and Beijing were seriously injured.
People couldn't get along.
Later, the two countries' war was over.
Zhu Huaizhen went to Beijing to marry you.
It's getting worse.
It's just that father's illness.
Not only that,
he also wanted to take away your family's wealth.
So he wanted to kill himself
and hurt the people.
So Nanyang was the most guilty one.
He was the real enemy of my family.
Look.
Princess, I know it's true.
Could you help me contact Li's uncle
and help me get rid of the suspicion of the Yellow Hall?
I've contacted them.
I've tried.
But I've tried it before.
I've already tried Xiao Lang and Xiao Lang's relationship.
I'm afraid you'll have to do something else.
What are you talking about?
Xiao Lang!
Your Highness!
I'll handle it.
I'll get rid of you.
Princess, I have orders.
No one can get out of here.
Don't force me to kill.
Your Highness, you've made a mistake.
You dare to kill me?
Princess, I just want to see you.
I'm going to be made by these scoundrels.
Go back. I don't want to see you.
I can go back.
I'll hand Li Zhi An and Zhu Huai Jin out.
I know they're here.
You want to take someone back?
You thought he'd come to me
when you were doing it with him.
I'm going to stay with him.
I'll keep this person.
I'll report to the brother about the divorce.
You can go back.
Li Zhi An lied to me that
he wasn't here to see Long Yu.
He was here to see my aunt.
Is she here to kill me by his father?
You and Zhu Huai Jin
hid Li Zhi An here.
I'm afraid it's not simple.
You hid your Li family's old house.
What did you do?
To avenge the Li family who killed the whole of Beijing.
Now Li family's old house is in Beijing.
It's a traitor.
I won't protect them.
Who can avenge Li family?
Zhu Huai Jin is still in the big screen.
It's him who killed my Li family.
He even saved my Li family
and became a traitor to the whole of the Empire.
Now I can't contact Li family through Princess.
I can't let Zhu Huai Jin get away.
I have to go back.
Your eyes...
Li family...
I'm sorry.
Zhi An, I knew you were here.
Zhi An.
I don't know
what happened to Li family.
I'm sorry.
So,
you did all this
to avenge Li family.
I've been in love with you.
Everything is not important now.
As long as you can avenge Li family,
I'm willing to go back with you.
Long Yu,
I'm willing to leave it to you.
Are you sure?
Thank you for your help.
Take care.
Zhi An.
Go back to your mansion.
Your Highness, where is the prince?
Zhu Huai Jin is not well in my mansion.
Let him stay here.
Where is he?
He went back with Zhu Huai Jin.
Yes.
The third prince has ordered
that after the seven princes meet with the princess,
they will not be in the same boat.
They will fall into the cliff and die without a single drop.
Zhu Huai Jin,
you have a second heart.
The third prince will not stay here.
You want to kill me?
Just do it.
Kill!
I'm sorry.