The next day
Happy Holidays
Can you stop the camera?
Yes!
Hurry! Otherwise I'll break it!
I-I got it!
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
I'm asking you!
There's no time. Please be quiet.
Wake up.
I'm sorry.
Episode 3
Episode 4
The plan-9's mission is to get out of the captain's office.
Get ready.
It's not a joke!
There's so much monster there.
Should I go again?
You guys can't see it, so you can say that.
Kotou-san is so slow.
The new master is dead.
The hunter on the other side has defeated him.
He's dead?
Is that impossible?
The ability to use the master's power
wasn't just a shoukama-ho?
Bbyong!
I heard a voice.
The voice of the hunter who uses his own power.
Episode 4
I think I know who it was.
He was a warm person who was not under any control.
I can't use this power on TV.
It's a scary ability to get more power
if the intensity of the fight is lost.
But Min...
You're right, Hunter.
If you continue to fight as a hunter,
Bbyong's power will be valuable.
But he doesn't want to fight.
I don't want him to stand on the battlefield again.
It's the same as when I was in the Red Gate.
The back hunter caught my shoulder.
But this time, it's not an order.
It's a desperate request.
It's okay. I thought the same.
The concentration is gone.
Bbyong!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Why are they alive?
The Sun Hunter collided and defeated the new master.
I know if you see this.
Why are you in the island?
I didn't participate in the fight.
I don't know.
The magic power's reaction suddenly appeared.
What do you mean?
I told you that I lost the Sun Hunter in the 12th and 17th.
Captain, will you show me the Plan Q?
If the damage is more than 1 in the manga,
the power balance that the gate of the country is more than the master,
will be greatly reduced.
What will you do?
I'll retreat.
Retreat immediately.
Roger.
Why are they suddenly...
I don't know.
Didn't the queen defeat her?
I'm starting to get a little nervous.
Don't let them get away with it.
Wait a minute!
This is the place where the base team guild is!
Captain, boss!
Everyone, hurry up!
This is bad.
It seems that the people who are trying to escape from the island are heading towards the main road.
If they don't move, the road will be blocked here.
Let's retreat immediately.
Please let us out.
Where is the Sun Hunter?
He seems to be left behind and is about to die.
Unfortunately, we are now just a stone-tongue.
And I hope you can see the Char Hunters quickly in the medical field.
Even if you can get an experience from the egg before it is hatched, it's a happy thing.
It's a waste of time to let it get angry.
As expected of the devil's experience.
But I'll leave the rest to you.
Finally, level 100 has been reached.
This is the place where the dead man is flying.
Wake up!
What is this darkness?
I can't feel anything.
Something is really happening.
It's back.
I thought I was in a hurry.
Well then, let's go to the other side.
Did you talk to them?
Yes.
Why are you talking to them?
It's the first time I've seen a Shogun Kyu.
Is it because the level is different from the one you can talk to them?
Even so...
I killed you.
And you still want me to do it?
I was born not by death, but by the power of the king.
I am now in the state of being a king.
I will always be your servant.
Please give me your name.
Bell.
Your name is Bell.
Thank you, Shion.
Then, again...
Wake up.
The monster group has been defeated.
This is the final defense line.
Don't let them get close to the city.
What are you doing?
You can't get close to the city.
Stop the attack with your life.
What a great number.
The number of the four thousand is increasing.
It seems that the number is increasing.
Is it still that high?
Will you reduce the number?
Yes.
Please give me your name.
Go.
Good.
The enemy is strong.
I need to defeat them to a certain extent.
Find the enemy.
Mr. Mikazawa.
Are you all right?
What is this?
That light...
I don't know.
But did you help me?
Mr. Jingu.
No matter how many times the number increases,
it will never change.
It's impossible.
The enemy is falling.
It hurts.
You are so brave.
We will meet in the air.
I was saved by him until the end.
I can escape.
The people who escaped from the island
were caught by many hunters.
The crime was stopped.
And the victim was arrested at the very beginning.
The SQ hunters were safe.
The Chahunters were in a state of coma.
They were sent to the hospital.
They fought to pay for the sacrifice.
But they were forced to hide the fear
that was about to overflow in the island.
And the fourth Jets' raid
closed the door with our victory.
The SQ hunters were in the island
until the end of the war.
It was a good day.
The time has come.
The SQ hunters are on the move.
Get ready to attack.
Wait.
The heroes of our country
want to get rid of their bodies.
It's coming.
I have to move my body a little.
I will sink into the sea without leaving a single one.
The SQ hunters were in the island
until the end of the war.
If it was that dark,
not a kid like him,
I would have enjoyed it a little more.
But it's a pity.
A few days after the fourth Jets' raid,
a ghostly ghost was created.
Many people are coming to the island.
Look.
The SQ hunters are heading to the battlefield.
The raid this time
has a huge role in his activities.
They say that he was not successful without the SQ hunters.
Some of them are heroes and they are not good at expressing themselves.
And many of his companions are very suspicious.
If he was participating from the beginning,
he would have been able to survive without making any mistakes.
And he has a very negative voice.
Please put your chest down.
What the world says,
is that you are the one who sent the SQ hunters to this attack.
First of all,
I would like to thank you for your effort to attend
the fourth Jets' raid this time.
No.
If I could hurry up and get to the base,
I would have been able to survive without losing the SQ hunters.
But thanks to you,
the fact that I was able to save many lives
of the five hunters and the SQ hunters
is a fact.
This achievement is great.
Let's promise that we will do whatever we want
to the SQ hunters.
I understand.
So, what are you planning to do in the future?
In the future?
Yes.
You have been in the raid this time,
but you have not been able to show your power.
The world will not abandon you anymore.
There are people who will contact you.
Even as a church,
you will not be able to survive.
I would like to ask you again.
SQ hunters,
what will you do with your power from now on?
I would like to raise my own guild.
Why are you so desperate to join our master?
You can't be so desperate to join our master?
No.
I will not allow you to join our master.
It's a great job to take care of the enemy's death.
The last one who is left behind is a trusted master.
But...
And...
You will do something that will not be done on the road.
You are a true man.
I knew it!
What are you doing?
I am a forbidden hunter.
Why are you doing this?
You are a dangerous person.
You are dangerous.
What?
What are you doing?
I don't know what you are doing,
but I don't have the permission to join.
What are you doing?
What did you do?
I just fell asleep because I heard a sound.
By the way, did you confirm it?
Yes, I am sure it's his power.
It's a strange story.
I don't think that person can save humans.
His spirit has not started yet.
If you are interested, come to meet him.
If I have something to meet him,
I will live here.
I will pull you up.
You said that you are coming here alone.
I should leave this area to him.
You don't want to be involved?
He will start as planned.
There is no change.
I don't think you need to do anything.
Even so, it's smelly.
If that woman sees it, she will be shocked.
I don't need to go.
What about the sword of Guild?
Yes, I got permission from the 5th president.
Really?
Well then,
I will come to you.
You can't go.
I can't go.
Really?
Well then, I will hurry and find the office.
Hey, hey, hey.
I will not go.
I have a big story to tell you.
I don't want to go.
I really can't go.
Yes.
I'm a son hunter.
Did something happen in the Guild?
No, it's a different story.
Before this highway?
Yes, a B-class gate was created.
That's right.
I'm in the hands of the hunter now,
but it will take time to get to the end of the time.
If you don't mind, I will go to that gate.
Please go slowly.
Are you still there?
Can't you come with your body?
I'm in trouble.
Hey, hey.
I came to close the gate.
Yes.
The story is about to end,
but it seems that it will take a little more time for other hunters to arrive.
I have no problem with that.
But...
I went.
No, it's a B-class.
Huh?
This is...
No, this is definitely a red gate.
It's been an accident.
The exit is closed,
and where is this road going?
If it was like this, I should have told my mother.
Well, if it's this much, it won't take much time.
I will help you quickly.
He came.
I was reminded of this raid.
I'm still a monster.
I was just a person who could help me at that place.
But he was wrong.
I want to catch up with that person.
I want to stand by that person.
For that reason,
I want to be strong.
The hunter was born to hunt.
The dungeon is a weak meat-eating world.
It needs a certain determination to hunt.
That's right.
The world where the enemy doesn't know when to turn.
The world where the enemy always meets the enemy.
Even so, the hunter is trying to see the battle.
The enemy is trying to say how many enemies there are.
He is trying to use the power that makes the enemy feel very strong.
The purpose of their fighting is different.
To protect the family.
To overcome the trust.
To prove their existence.
To make them fight for their destiny.
The hunter is just hunting.
No one is going to stop hunting yet.
Translation by conceris
The next recently developed唉 civilization falls into their hands.
TH Means Python
How the amazing silicon was pplatified.
I'm not sure if I can do this.