♫  The blade dance causes ripples to spread across the lake  ♫
♫  Waving the banner admist the storm and rain  ♫
♫  The snow is not bothered by sadness or joy  ♫
♫  Blazing through the desert with the reins in hand  ♫
♫  Young and inexperienced, it is apparent  ♫
♫  Noble aspirations met with recklessness  ♫
♫  No fear of fate's intricate design  ♫
♫  Overcome all the obstacles that fate presents  ♫
♫  Through trials and hardship spawns vast courage  ♫
♫  The journey to seek glory and justice is not in vain  ♫
♫  With one smile there's understanding  ♫
♫  Singing about our journey  ♫
♫  Pursuing the dream of our youth  ♫
♫  We take everything as it comes  ♫
♫  The distant land might be dangerous  ♫
♫  But what's life without an adventure?  ♫
♫  The youth are supposed to dream big and be sharp  ♫
♫  Life teaches us with every struggle  ♫
♫  We must do what we can in the world  ♫
♫  Together, another journey awaits  ♫
I wasn't certain if I should agree.
I asked Marquis Lanyue, and he asked me to seek your opinion.
Who does he want you to treat?
According to him, it's a blind patient.
When he was young, he ate a snack he got from someone.
He lost his sight after that.
It's been 20 years. I'm uncertain if it can be cured.
Can you treat it?
If he hasn't been blind for long, I could remove the toxin with acupuncture.
But he's been blind for 20 years.
Maybe he'll need to get a new pair of eyes.
Wait. Divine Healer, are you kidding?
A new pair of eyes?
Just one word, yes or no.
You're the healer.
Saving lives is your duty.
Besides, this person is wealthy.
He can afford the medical fee for sure.
So yes, you can treat him.
Xiao Se.
But remember to say that it was I who asked you to treat him.
You're good-looking but not intelligent.
You came to Snowfall Mountain Villa at night.
- Yet you wore an all-white outfit.
- Vermilion Bird?
You, Dark River, like to give yourselves code names and call others' code names?
I'm White Tiger.
White Tiger?
This name doesn't sound...
Wait.
You're White Tiger?
What are you two doing?
Qianluo, stop.
Why didn't you ask her to stop first?
Well, Ji Xue, stop.
Are you giving me an order?
Both of you are very childish.
You're either surrounded by a silly child like Lei Wujie or an impulsive young lady like this.
Xiao Chuhe, is there no other ordinary guardian around you?
You could've come in through the front door.
Why must you sneak in here? You can't blame anyone for this.
Come in through the front door?
Do you know how many people in Tianqi City are having their eyes on this door?
As long as the misunderstanding is cleared up.
You must be the daughter of Bai Xiao Sect's head, Ji Ruofeng.
Finally, there's someone smart here.
Since you have a guest, we should leave first.
Her presence resembles that of an elegant soaring swan.
Gracefully, she moves like a dragon in flight.
Prettier than the autumn chrysanthemum. More vigorous than the pine in spring.
Mysterious as the moon covered by clouds.
Extraordinary as snow whirled by the driving wind.
What are you murmuring?
Miss, I'm the apprentice of Divine Healer Hua Jin, Mu Chunfeng.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I know.
I didn't know I was so famous.
But I don't know who you are.
Ji Xue.
I'm 21 years old.
How old are you? Are you married?
- I'm still single.
- See you around.
You should've inquired about her beforehand.
Qianluo.
Are those two close to each other?
It feels like she has an affinity for Xiao Se when she talks to him.
They've known each other since childhood.
Ji Xue's father is Xiao Se's master.
He is the closest person to Xiao Se in this world.
He's even closer to him than His Majesty is.
That's why it's different.
But he does act differently around you.
Does he?
Chunfeng, we should get going.
Master, let's stay a little longer.
Young Master Mu, is this Miss Ji Xue really that pretty?
Among the women in the world, I've never seen someone refined like her.
Her smile stands out among other ladies as if there's nothing.
Nothing?
Nothing.
- Let's go.
- Master, let's stay a little longer.
Just go.
How's the investigation going?
I've found the person you asked me to look for.
Where is he?
He's hiding in plain sight.
Long time no see, Boss Xiao.
You already knew that I'd come.
Bai Xiao Sect has been looking for me everywhere.
I can see that they're exhausted.
So I developed compassion and deliberately went downstairs to buy a vegetable bun.
This inn is a long street away from my Snowfall Mountain Villa.
Since you knew I sent someone for you, why didn't you come over sooner?
I would've like to try your royal banquet that contained 15 appetizers.
I would've also liked to see how commanding and majestic you were at Qianjin Gambling House.
Unfortunately, you hadn't entered the city before I went on the retreat.
You had already left when I finished the retreat.
Retreat?
Were you injured?
Yes.
I nearly became a cripple.
Who did that to you?
Head Eunuch Jinxuan.
What's wrong?
Every time when you're in danger, I would be there and save you.
But when I was in danger, you didn't show up.
So you feel guilty and want to avenge me?
You were injured by Jinxuan because you entered the palace.
So I was right.
You came to Tianqi for Consort Xuan.
You've changed, Boss Xiao.
You've become straightforward.
You knew that I didn't want to talk about this.
You should've pretended not to know about it.
You shouldn't have underestimated those skilled fighters in the palace, especially the Five Eunuchs.
None of them is easy to deal with.
And there are many Imperial Swordsmen.
Even I have never met them before.
I understand. I'll be careful next time.
Next time?
Wu Xin,
as you're eager to see Consort Xuan,
are you trying to ask her questions or get her out of there?
Will she leave with me?
She lives an extravagant life in the palace.
Unlike Tian Wai Tian, it's actually an infertile land.
Your Highness, it's getting late.
It's time to rest.
Your Highness.
Why did Yu'er suddenly
mention Shi'er today?
Did he have news from Shi'er?
Maybe it was just an innocent question.
Don't mind it, Your Highness.
Right.
It's been years.
Maybe Shi'er has already forgotten about me, his unfit mother.
What right do I have to see him again?
Actually, Consort Xuan is not what you thought she was.
She's an outcast in the palace.
She never attends any party,
and she doesn't interact with the people in the palace.
I remember when I was a child,
I once barged into her courtyard.
She gave me a piece of pastry and enjoyed the sky view with me all afternoon.
All afternoon?
She said it'd be nice if she could become a bird.
So that she could fly,
fly over the walls,
fly over the mountains,
and even fly to the far south.
South?
I didn't understand it when I was little.
I left after staying there all afternoon.
Until Imperial Uncle Langya told me about her story.
It made me wonder if the place Consort Xuan wanted to go
was the hut outside Gusu City.
After all, she and Ye Dingzhi have stayed there for a long time.
Also, it was where they gave birth to you.
You're saying that she actually has no choice?
I'm saying that this is your hardship.
You must take good care of yourself.
Everything I said is what I saw.
Forget it.
Actually, I also don't know why I want to see her.
Maybe I'm just wondering how she's doing now.
I'd like to ask her if she remembers that I'm her son.
Or maybe I just want to see her one last time
before I go back.
Then, she can stay in Beili as Consort Xuan.
I'll return to Tian Wai Tian and be the Young Master.
I can't believe there's something you don't know.
Everyone has their own worries.
If you just want to see Consort Xuan, maybe I can help you.
Or else, no one in Tianqi City can help you.
As expected, you care for me.
I just want you to solve your problems sooner.
And don't get me in trouble.
You speak with a forked tongue.
These are the fragrances I collected from everywhere.
You are welcome to take them if you like.
Sixth Prince, why are you being so generous?
I'm flustered.
Just get to the point.
All right.
Eunuch, whose side are you on in the current Tianqi City?
Must I pick a side?
In this war, only the winning side can survive.
It's impossible to stay neutral in this matter.
Your Highness, you must be well aware that no matter whose side we're on,
if His Majesty dies, the Five Eunuchs will have to guard the mausoleum.
Are you willing to do it?
To me, it doesn't make any difference.
Even now,
all I do is just chant, pray, and blend fragrances.
The Blizzard Sword Shen Jingzhou that I know is not like this.
He used to yearn for the martial arts world.
Though I can't go around the world, it's more liberal than staying in Tianqi City.
Eunuch Jade Deity, I won't beat around the bush.
I can assure you that you can go anywhere you like after leaving Tianqi City.
In the name of Lord Yong'an?
It's in the name of Xiao Se.
As long as you believe that I can do it.
Why me?
When you entered the martial arts world, you claimed yourself as Blizzard Sword.
Your integrity showed when you swung your sword.
I believe in my judgment.
Please have faith in me and give me a helping hand.
Every time I walk in here, this is the sound I dislike hearing the most.
This means that you're conscious
and by my footsteps, you can figure out who I am.
You really are a strong woman.
Just like your pretty face.
I couldn't forget about it ever since the first time I met you.
I won't let you have your way.
Do you know how I convinced Minghou to be the drug tester?
I told him if he resisted, you'd forever be locked in here.
With the stinky smell of blood, the bodies of rats,
and the insects' bites, your body will slowly rot.
You vile man!
No. You've misunderstood me.
I was just helping him.
Minghou won't listen to you.
You're wrong. He agreed without hesitation.
But he got a low adaptive capacity.
We were only halfway there.
Unlike you,
you're way better than him.
Yueji, you were born to be a killer.
But a killer can't have a heart!
I've found a perfect weapon.
Soon, he'll become just like you.
Yueji, you don't have much time left.
Stop!
Why are all of you entering the palace?
Eunuch Jade Deity wants to hold a Fragrance Ceremony for His Majesty.
These eunuchs will burn incense for each palace.
An assassin sneaked into the palace several days ago.
Those who enter the palace must undergo body searches.
How dare you!
Lingjun.
Eunuch.
This is His Majesty's decree.
Just let them check it.
- Thank you, Eunuch.
- Yes.
Wait.
Head Eunuch.
Why are you here so early today?
Old people need less sleep.
Sometimes, I can't sleep.
So I get up and walk around
in order to allow His Majesty to sleep peacefully.
Are they your new apprentices?
Yes.
They don't look familiar.
They just entered Hongqing Temple this year.
I think they're young but smart and agile.
They won't neglect their masters of each palace.
Is there any problem, Head Eunuch?
With you in charge, I'm at ease.
Go on.
Let's go.
Go to the palace you're assigned to.
Remember to be careful.
No mistake is allowed.
- Noted.
Consort Xuan's Jingtai Palace is at the northwest corner.
Thank you, Eunuch Jade Deity.
The palace gate will be closed at the hour of Xu.
(T/N: between 7 p.m. and 9 p.m.)
- Leave before that.
- Understood.
Also, remember that it's me who brings you here.
Don't do anything illegal in here.
Otherwise, I'll bring you to His Majesty.
I understand.
You're so nagging it's annoying.
I don't know if I'm helping him
or getting him killed.
Your Highnesses, please go back.
His Majesty is not feeling well.
When His Majesty wants to see you, he'll ask me to inform you.
We just want to see our father. I can't believe it'd be this hard.
Please mind your words, Your Highness.
I'll excuse myself first.
If imperial father wants to see us, please let us know, Captain Li.
No problem, Your Highness.
Her Highness always burns incense and chants here.
Prepare everything. I'll ask Her Highness over.
Thank you.
♫   The snow falls and colors the mortal world  ♫
♫   When will these dead trees bloom again?  ♫
♫   All that time wasted, just waiting for one person  ♫
♫   If we hadn't met, there wouldn't be this pain  ♫
♪ Unfortunately, the blades meet as weapons ♪
♪ It hurts me but I remain silent ♪
Greetings to Consort Xuan.
Since you're here to burn incense, I'll count on you.
Yes.
♫  Wandering around the world with you until the moon descends below the horizon  ♫
♫  Wish you spend the rest of your life with me  ♫
♫  My heart acts as a shield and protects you  ♫
Your Highness set up this prayer hall to eliminate karma
and accumulate good fortune for the person on the tablet?
How dare you!
Who gave you permission to ask this?
You're right.
You should put down the prayer beads and walk out of this hall.
Your Highness, this eunuch is getting outrageous.
Never mind.
Let him finish.
It's easy to chant.
The difficult part is to focus.
Staying focused is not as hard as forgoing the desire for love.
Your Highness is confused.
Why make things difficult for yourself?
You should let go of it sooner.
How do you know that I'm confused?
I knew it as soon as I entered the courtyard.
Was it because of the fallen leaves?
It was me who asked them not to clean it.
Leaf litter is a natural phenomenon.
It's unnecessary to dispose of them.
But why do you make this payer hall spotlessly clean?
What's the difference between the fallen leaves and the dirt?
What's your name?
Wu Xin.
Wu Xin?
Lift up your head.
Let me have a good look at you.
Your eyes look familiar.
It seems like fate brings us together.
You said your name is Wu Xin.
Who gave you that name?
My master did.
Master said one is clear-minded, selfless, and won't go astray
without a heart.
One will be free without a heart.
I guess you've got a good master.
He is the best master in the world.
Your Highness, Prince Chi is here to greet you.
You wait here.
Yes.
Mother.
Why are you here so early?
I made you upset that day.
I felt sorry when I went back.
After greeting imperial father today, I rushed over to see you.
I know you don't like Eight Treasures Tea.
I asked someone to bring new tea leaves over from the outside.
You can try it. See if it fits your taste.
- I...
- Go brew it.
Who is he?
He's a eunuch from Hongqing Temple. He's here to burn incense for your father.
He came here early in the morning.
The figure of this eunuch looks familiar.
You've seen many people.
Maybe they just look alike.
You're right.
Go clean up the prayer hall.
Yes.
Please, Mother.
The color looks nice.
I guess it'll taste good.
It's nice.
Does Prince Chi always come to visit Consort Xuan?
He only came here often the past two days.
Sometimes, he doesn't show up for two weeks.
Has Consort Xuan always been alone like this?
She wasn't alone at first.
Back then, His Majesty always came to visit her.
She was frequently rewarded.
Then, something happened.
His Majesty never came again.
She got no further reward.
Over time, others have stopped coming too.
Consort Xuan doesn't like troubling others.
As they didn't come, she didn't go out.
I haven't seen her talking so much with someone else for years.
Imperial father has been troubled by a matter lately.
Do you want to know what it is?
I'm not interested in something that doesn't concern me.
What if it is about your other son?
Why do you mention him again?
Don't do anything rash.
I didn't say anything.
Why did you scold me?
I just want to remind you that you can play any trick you like to get what you want.
But there's someone that you can't lay a hand on.
Play any trick I like?
Mother, if it wasn't for the trouble you made out there,
why would I have to play tricks?
You used to be imperial father's favorite consort.
I was imperial father's favorite son.
I could've gotten everything I wanted.
If it wasn't for you and Ye Dingzhi, I wouldn't have ended up like this.
Over the years, I've been ridiculed, left out, and mocked.
What about you? You lived isolated.
What would you know?
But judging from your look,
it seems like you're still deeply in love with Ye Dingzhi.
Even his son is more important than me.
Well, I'll wait and see what will happen to you two.
Your Highness, do you want to go back and get some rest?
You must've heard about my story outside the palace.
It's all an urban legend.
I won't take it seriously.
Take a seat.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Tell me about it.
Your Highness
was married to His Majesty when he was still Prince Jingyu.
Then, you were set up and abducted by Ye Dingzhi, the Head of Demon Sect.
In the end, Demon Sect lost, and you successfully escaped.
Then you got rescued and returned to the palace.
Pretty much what I had expected.
It has protected his reputation as the Emperor.
Isn't this a fact?
Are you curious?
If you knew it, it might get you killed.
Everything I heard here at Jingtai Palace will stay here for sure.
In fact,
the rumor out there is mostly true.
Except for one thing.
I left with Ye Dingzhi of my own free will.
We only parted as we were set up by the bad guys.
They lied to me that Yu'er was severely ill.
They got me back to Tianqi City
and made Ye Dingzhi think that I abandoned him for an extravagant life.
Before he died, I finally got to see him.
I told him that we should escape to Nanjue
and get away from the disputes.
He said he did many wrong things.
He couldn't leave just like that.
Only his death can protect his peers.
In the end,
he committed suicide.
So, what you wanted to say to him, in the end, was to leave with him?
But it was too late.
The wrong step I took was the reason that everything happened.
Then, why did you return to the palace?
I have two children.
One of them was trapped in the palace.
I couldn't leave him behind.
So you gave up on the other one.
Xiao Ruojin wouldn't make things difficult for my other son
only if I returned to the palace.
The imperial family always attaches great importance to their reputation.
If I came back, he would keep his promise.
Now, that son of mine has gone to the coldest land.
But I'll soon leave this place.
Unknowingly, I've told you a lot of things.
Maybe it's because you look a lot like him.
Ye Dingzhi, the Grand Master of Demon Sect?
His eyes looked as pretty as yours.
I suppose my child is about your age.
What is your child's name?
His name is Ye Anshi.
It's a good name.
I think those few years were the happiest in my life.
It was also the first time I found the world likable.
That's why I gave him this name.
I see.
Tell me about you.
What about you?
Wu Xin, tell me about you.
About me?
Yes.
Where are you from?
Where did you grow up?
How did you come to Tianqi City?
I lived in chaos before I met my master.
But I was happy.
In my memory, there were my mother, father,
and...
many uncles who loved me.
But then they passed away.
I was lucky to meet my master.
We lived together and relied on one another.
Then, my master also passed away.
After that, I've been through ups and downs.
Eventually, I came to Tianqi City.
I didn't expect you to experience so much at such a young age.
Your Highness, are you tired?
Don't call me that.
I don't like being called by this title.
Wu Xin, you may leave first.
Talk to me some other time.
But there's not much time left.
I'll leave here soon.
Consort Xuan?
Mother?
Xiao Yu, this jerk!
What are you thinking?
Wu Xin should be in the palace now.
Wu Xin?
You've found him?
He has entered the palace once before.
But he was injured by Jinxuan.
He's been recuperating lately.
I went to Jade Deity a few days ago.
I asked him to get Wu Xin into the palace.
Did he want to see his mother?
But this is too risky.
The Wu Xin I know is the smartest person I've ever met.
He won't do something silly.
Everyone would.
It's when they encounter the person and the matter they care about the most.
Keep an ear out for the news from the palace.
Sure.
Xiao Yu, why would you poison your own mother?
So what?
Anyway, the poison won't kill her.
Besides, you're here to remove the toxin from her body.
She'll be all right.
This is the Toxin-Reversing Technique of Medicine Valley.
When you mobilized qi to remove the toxin,
the toxin has already been transferred to your body.
Then, why did you do this?
It's all because of you, my dear brother.
You're a martial arts expert, and you're smart.
What kind of situation can make you let your guard down?
It's a great honor to have the Head of Bai Xiao Sect here
to deliver messages to me every time.
Many people are keeping an eye on Prince Yong'an's Residence.
Without martial arts, I wouldn't have gotten in here.
This is for you.
This is the name list you want.
The toxin-making experts who entered Tianqi City and haven't left in the course of the year.
As expected of the Bai Xiao Sect.
There are seven people from the Tang Clan, 13 people from the Wen family,
three people from the Five Poisons Clan, four people from Liusan Sect,
and some small sects.
I don't know which one you're looking for.
Ghost Physician, Night Crow?
I knew this name would catch your eye first.
Hasn't this person disappeared for a long time?
The three experts in Medicine Valley were Medicine King Xin Baicao,
Divine Healer Bian Suchen, and Ghost Physician Night Crow.
Ghost Physician Night Crow was the youngest among them.
But the medicine she used was the strangest among them.
And because of this, she studied secret techniques
and was evicted from the sect.
Then, it was said that the medicine backfired on her, and she died from it.
But Bai Xiao Sect found her whereabouts in Tianqi about six months ago.
Where is she now?
Do you know why her name is Night Crow?
Besides being a drug expert, her lightness technique is excellent as well.
We lost track of her.
So her current whereabouts are still unknown.
We must tell Hua Jin about this.
Are you sure it's her?
Medicine King Xin Baicao once said
that only an heir of Medicine Valley can render
another heir of Medicine Valley helpless.
Great.
I finally got my perfect creation.
♫  The temple is extremely quiet  ♫
♫  We still have a long way to go in the martial arts world  ♫
♫  Outside the snow is falling  ♫
♫  Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon  ♫
♫  The roaring fate  ♫
♫  Sweeping away the fog of time  ♫
♫  The past is desolate  ♫
♫  Waiting for the ride to the highest heaven  ♫
♫  The ethereal fog  ♫
♫  Fame and fortune do not matter to an enlightened person  ♫
♫  I face the sun  ♫
♫  To have a pristine soul in this polluted world  ♫
♫  Traveling far and overcoming challenges life throws my way  ♫
♫  I'm not wasting my youth away  ♫
♫  Like blade and sword, relying on each other  ♫
♫  With devoted friends and strong bonds  ♫
♫  No dream is small  ♫
♫  Despite conflicts and the feuds, we sing proudly  ♫
♫  Youths ought to be fearless  ♫
♫  Visiting all corners of the world with our youthful spirits  ♫
♫  Traveling freely with friends  ♫
♫  I won't be lonely if I have my confidants  ♫
♫  Traveling far and overcoming challenges life throws my way  ♫
♫  I'm not wasting my youth away  ♫
♫  Like blade and sword, relying on each other  ♫
♫  With devoted friends and strong bonds  ♫
♫  No dream is small  ♫
♫  Despite conflicts and the feuds, we sing proudly  ♫
♫  Youths ought to be fearless  ♫
♫  Visiting all corners of the world with our youthful spirits  ♫
♫  Traveling freely with friends  ♫
♫  I won't be lonely if I have my confidants  ♫