♫  The blade dance causes ripples to spread across the lake  ♫
♫  Waving the banner amidst the storm and rain  ♫
♫  The snow is not bothered by sadness or joy  ♫
♫  Blazing through the desert with the reins in hand  ♫
♫  Young and inexperienced, it is apparent  ♫
♫  Noble aspirations met with recklessness  ♫
♫  No fear of fate's intricate design  ♫
♫  Overcome all the obstacles that fate presents  ♫
♫  Through trials and hardship spawns vast courage  ♫
♫  The journey to seek glory and justice is not in vain  ♫
♫  With one smile there's understanding  ♫
♫  Singing about our journey  ♫
♫  Pursuing the dream of our youth  ♫
♫  We take everything as it comes  ♫
♫  The distant land might be dangerous  ♫
♫  But what's life without an adventure?  ♫
♫  The youth are supposed to dream big and be sharp  ♫
♫  Life teaches us with every struggle  ♫
♫  We must do what we can in the world  ♫
♫  Together, another journey awaits  ♫
I was so close.
Don't make it sound like I can't do anything right.
Do you know why you fail at the last step?
Why?
I'm the last step to success.
You only sent Bai Xiao Sect to intercept Prince Chi. How would that be enough?
Therefore, he came back way earlier than you expected.
If you had sent me, they wouldn't have made it back in time.
See, you can't answer it, can you?
Sister Ruoyi, what do you think?
Where is Lei Wujie?
I will find him for you.
Ruo...
You tell me.
Look at you. You scare people away every time.
Sit down.
I was thinking about it last night. Finally, I figured it out.
You didn't let me go because you were afraid I'd be in danger, right?
Yes. You've been in danger because you were afraid I'd be in danger, right?
Things in Tianqi City will be over soon.
Afterward, you can go back to Xueyue City without worries.
But you saw it too.
If it weren't for me, you'd all have been in danger.
If you leave me out again, I will really get mad.
You know what happens when I get mad.
You will be in even more danger then.
Xiao Se,
actually, even if I don't go back to Xueyue City, it's fine.
As long as I can stay in the same place as you,
anywhere is fine for me.
Xiao Se, do you hear me?
Yes.
What? The Leader is dead?
Near Prince Chi's Residence yesterday, the head of the Su family, Su Muyu, Lei Wujie,
Li Fansong and Feixuan of Mount Wangcheng, as well as Fairy Lady Rui of Xueyue City,
joined forces and ambushed the Leader.
The Leader was wounded by Pear Blossom Needle Cloudburst and died at the hands of Su Muyu
Useless!
They are all useless!
Calm down, Your Highness.
What about the rest of Dark River?
The other forces in Dark River have retreated, leaving only a few drugged subjects,
hidden in secret chambers, unawakened.
Darn it.
I want you to deliver two letters, one to Nanjue.
Since Xiao Chuhe dared to release the fake news that the envoy of Nanjue had entered Tianqi City,
it means he already knew that I was in contact with Ao Yu.
In that case, we have to speed things up.
Tell the one in Nanjue to make a move at the best time.
It's just that when is the best time?
The best time is the day my godfather enters the city.
So, the second letter will be sent to Muliang City.
Why did you call me back so urgently?
We received a letter from Leader Ji.
Father?
- Luo Qingyang left the city?
- Yes.
Luo Qingyang left Muliang City five days ago, heading in the direction of Tianqi.
Given his speed, won't he reach Tianqi soon?
Luo Qingyang is Prince Chi's godfather.
Prince Chi must've asked him to come.
Looks like Prince Chi wants to fall out completely, so he's asked Lone Sword Deity to attack the city.
Xiao Se, how strong is Lone Sword Deity among the Five Sword Deities?
Compared to Zhao Yuzhen, he is only stronger.
But Luo Qingyang is aloof and arrogant.
He won't obey Prince Chi easily.
Prince Chi must've asked him here to take someone away.
He will fight with all his might. This is the most troubling part.
Who is he taking away?
Consort Xuan.
There are rumors in the martial arts world that Luo Qingyang is deeply in love with his martial sister, Yi Wenjun.
Unfortunately, his feelings are unrequited.
Consort Xuan has married twice, but she never chose him.
Lone Sword Deity is halfway to the Mental Phase of the Unknown.
We are no match for him.
Why don't we write to my father?
Third City Lord can't leave Xueyue City.
Wushuang City is watching every move of Xueyue City.
With the two city lords gone, if one more city lord leaves,
the forces that are eyeing Xueyue City will make a move.
It seems we are on our own.
Inform Wushuang City,
this is my last chance and their best chance.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness, Lone Sword Deity has come to challenge Tianqi.
We have Rage Sword Deity, don't we?
Why are you still asking Wushuang for help?
Although Master and Lone Sword Deity are both among the Five Sword Deities,
if they really fight each other, it won't be easy for Master to beat him.
But if even Rage Sword Deity is no match,
it's even impossible for Wushuang City Lord to defeat Lone Sword Deity.
If he is wounded, won't you lose a major helper?
If the news is true and Wushuang can really manipulate Wushuang Sword Box completely,
then he still has a chance to defeat Lone Sword Deity.
I wonder what they will do.
They?
I'm sure Chuhe is trying to figure something out too.
Who dares to come to Xueyue City to cause trouble?
Are you that young city lord of Wushuang City?
Just City Lord. Why did you add the word "young"?
You really are Song Yanhui's darn disciple.
Take this!
This man's swordsmanship is superb. I can't believe he's as good as Master.
Is this the legendary Sword Wielding Arts?
I've only just learned the art of Liubo. I have yet to master it.
I am afraid I am no match for him.
Stop.
City Lord Wushuang, did you come to Xueyue City to seek a battle with me?
I've been looking forward to it.
Cloud Shuttle, Light Frost, Desolate Wind, Absolute Shadow, Slaughter, Ordeal Breaker,
Red Leaf, Butterfly, Thread, Jade Wish, go!
I'm afraid these ten flying swords are not enough.
What about two more?
Ash-Gray, Boundless.
City Lord Sikong, what do you think now?
You have a chance to fight, but no chance of victory.
I see.
Then I will fight first, then find a chance to win.
Thank you, City Lord Sikong.
Did you come to Xueyue City just to show me flying swords?
I have been ordered to go to Tianqi.
I don't know if I can return, so I want to fulfill some wishes.
I've come to Xueyue City to see you and learn about my current strength.
Second, I'm here to see Fairy Luoxia.
Me?
Why do you want to see me?
About this,
my master has given up the pursuit of the sword deity title.
He is living in seclusion in the sword cottage at the back of Mount Wushuang.
He said he had thought things through.
If you are willing to, he'd like to invite you to Wushuang City for a meeting.
A meeting your foot! You...
Calm down. Calm down.
Master, you can't agree to this.
That shameless guy obviously wants to get you back.
Master. You can't go, Master.
So what if I go with him?
I won't go with him.
What am I going to do if you leave?
You are not a child anymore. You can live without me.
It's exactly because I'm not a child anymore.
So...
So, whatever Song Yanhui can give you, I can give you as well.
What is he... What is he doing? What is he talking about?
What is he...
Are you confessing to her?
You are not a child anymore.
What the adult can offer, you can offer it too?
Why does that sound strange?
Did you hit your head?
No.
A beauty like you is around me every day.
If that didn't make me feel anything, I wouldn't be in my right mind then.
I am your master.
That's why people say first come, first served.
Keep the goodies within one's own people.
I have a poor memory, but I don't think this is the right scenario to apply that saying.
I knew something was off with you, you brat,
but I just didn't expect you had got the nerve to talk to the Fairy like this.
Do you know how many young talents confessed to the Fairy like this back then?
They were all beaten away by her.
But you do have a point.
What's wrong? Why can't a disciple be with his master together?
Shut up.
Tell him I'm not going.
One can only wait for some things once in a lifetime.
Since he gave it up last time, there is no more.
Master, well said!
- This is great!
- Brat.
Shut up.
It seems that swallows will return one day, but love won't.
I feel sorry for my master.
Farewell.
Sir.
Do you still serve food now?
Sorry, sir. The kitchen is closed.
That lady over there still has some food.
Please don't, sir. Please...
Sister, I'm feeling hungry from all the traveling.
Can you share some food with me?
You know, even my closest peers do not dare to eat with me.
Why?
Because I'm good at poisoning.
Every cup of liquor you drink could be a deadly poison.
It's fine.
Waiter.
Coming, Sir.
Here's your cup.
Interesting.
The moon is so beautiful tonight.
You're sitting here drinking alone.
Are you thinking about something sad?
You are interesting, Young City Lord of Wushuang City.
You know me?
I recognize your sword box.
Do you know who I am?
I have a poor memory.
Senior brother has probably told me, but I don't remember it.
I'm the head of the Dark River Mu family, Mu Yumo.
I see.
I've heard that there are many beautiful women in the Mu family of Dark River.
Looks like the rumors are true.
You are such a lovely child.
If I lean one inch closer to you, you will break my arms and legs, won't you?
- You can try.
- I'm not taking the risk.
Come on, Sister. Let's have a drink.
Let's talk about the man in your eyes.
The man in my eyes?
What kind of person is he that you can't forget him?
Have you ever heard of this poem?
As the music flows upon the moon reflected on the water's surface,
the breeze and the cloud are caught up.
In the Pipa City of Nine Rivers, he became famous for his three hidden weapons.
Tang Lianyue of the Tang Clan, a master swordsman on the Top-Rank List.
That's right. Back then, everyone knew who he was.
Even after years of retirement,
he is still the head of the Tang Clan after he entered the martial artists world.
Sister, I'd like to hear about how you met each other.
How we met each other...?
Our encounter began when I tried to kill him the first time.
The first time?
I tried to kill him three times.
The first time, he and I...
I kind of miss him now.
It's all over.
You can go see him anytime.
It's all over?
Changhe's body is in the carriage outside.
We will send him back to Dark River.
Then, we will dissolve Dark River.
After that, everyone can do what they want to do.
You are Su Muyu, the head of the Su family.
You recognize him, but not me.
Your 18 Swords Formation is incredible.
I'd like to see it.
Your swords are good, while mine is only a killing weapon.
It's not worth seeing.
Dark River has withdrawn from the fray.
This battle between me and you is unnecessary.
Yumo, let's go.
Xiao Wushuang, next time we meet, I hope to hear your story too.
Remember to visit me in Wushuang City then.
You're asking the head of a family of Dark River to go to visit you?
That's very cute, Xiao Wushuang.
Just like what this brother said, you won't be Dark River members any more soon.
Since you are not Dark River members, the killing weapon that he said will become a sword.
I look forward to fighting with you, Mr. Su.
You are going to Tianqi, aren't you?
Yes, Tianqi.
There are many good swords in Tianqi City.
This trip won't disappoint you.
You will even see the best sword in the world.
The best sword?
The City Lord of Wushuang City has gone to Xueyue City alone.
I've heard that the new young city lord has already mastered Wushuang Sword Box.
Rumors say that he's there to challenge Sikong Changfeng.
That's impossible.
Wushuang City has no reason to make a move on Xueyue City.
Those from the martial arts world think they know what the two city lords are thinking.
How preposterous.
Speaking of city lords, another city lord has left his city too.
He is going to Tianqi.
He is Prince Chi's godfather.
He's going to Tianqi to support Prince Chi.
As for Xueyue City, their Principal City Lord has yet to return.
Their Second City Lord is severely injured.
Their Third City Lord can't leave due to the tension in the martial arts world.
No one can go and help them.
Says who?
Tang Clan can go and help them.
Tang Clan?
We have no chance of making peace with Lei Fortress for now,
but the alliance with Xueyue City can't be given up so easily.
Besides, I am expecting big things from that young man named Xiao Se.
The moon is bright tonight. Let's depart.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say you would stay in your room to heal?
That's right. I was going to deliver breakfast to you.
It's just a minor injury. It's not a big deal.
Eat your food.
Why are you here too?
Because he has arrived.
What's wrong with this man?
He's been standing here for a long time.
- That's right.
- Leave it. Let's go. Come on.
Mind our own business.
Lone Sword Deity, Luo Qingyang, is a disciple of Tianqi's Shadow Sect,
secret bodyguards of the imperial family.
After the fall of Shadow Sect, there are only two Shadow disciples left in the world.
The other one is Consort Xuan?
That's right.
Luo Qingyang was the most brilliant disciple in Shadow Sect.
Later, he became the late Emperor's personal secret bodyguard.
He saved the late Emperor many times.
The late Emperor rewarded him with a city before his death in recognition of his merits.
Luo Qingyang chose Muliang City, the most desolate city in the west.
It is said that it was to practice his Desolate Sword.
Desolate Sword?
That's right. His life is pitiful.
He was born an orphan.
All of his martial siblings are dead.
The woman he loves married twice, but it has nothing to do with him.
Isn't his life pitiful?
What is going on?
You're saying that he chopped off the plaque of Tianqi City with his sword?
Yes. Captain Luo took the plaque down with his sword.
Then, he took it to Qianjin Gambling House.
Everyone in Qianjin Gambling House was so scared that they ran away.
Even Second Master Tu ran away.
The plaque of Tianqi City has been taken down three times.
The first time was when Xiao Yi, the first emperor of Beili, broke open the city gate.
As the true energy of his sword was too powerful, he struck it down at once.
The second time was 60 years ago when Sword Deity Baiyu saved the disciple who was being held hostage.
He struck it down as a warning to the people of Tianqi City.
This is the third time.
Why did he take the plaque to Qianjin Gambling House?
He did so because that place has people from all levels of society.
They will spread the news of his return to Tianqi.
What else did he say besides chopping down the plaque?
He didn't say anything at all.
In the end, he heaved the plaque into the ground
and said a few words.
Challenge Tianqi to sword fights.
My godfather only said these words?
Yes.
I wrote and asked him to come.
He really came, but he didn't tell me it would be this way.
Marquis, what should we do now?
You are the leader of the imperial guards.
When someone breaks Tianqi City's plaque, what do you think we should do?
We should behead him. Execute him.
Yes. Go and do it then.
Marquis, this is Lone Sword Deity, Luo Qingyang.
I've known him for ten years.
I know what kind of person he is...
He isn't a person. He's a monster.
I asked imperial guards and Tiger Soldiers to surround him with dozens of barrels.
So what?
If he enters this palace, will I be able to stop him?
If a swordsman could kill the ruler of Beili easily, the world would've been in chaos already.
Captain Li, you are looking down on me.
State Preceptor.
I'm so glad that you came.
Let me tell you, if he had really come to kill my royal brother,
he wouldn't have taken the plaque down
and yelled something about challenging Tianqi to sword fights.
He would've just killed his way into the palace.
"Challenge Tianqi to sword fights."
The meaning of this phrase is not simple.
One of the reasons Luo Qingyang came this time is to challenge swordsmen.
He was ranked as the best swordsman in the world,
but he hasn't fought in a long time.
Who knows if he is still the best swordsman in the world?
All the swordsmen in the world want to know that.
He himself also wants to find out.
Does he have another purpose then?
City Lord Luo.
Scholar Xie, I never thought you'd be the first person
I'd see at Qianjin Gambling House.
It's my pleasure.
Qingyang, have you mastered your Desolate Sword?
Almost there.
No wonder.
People wanted to challenge you before.
Now that you've made a little achievement, you want to challenge the world. There is nothing wrong with it.
I'm just curious as to who you will challenge.
The one I wanted to challenge the most
is dead.
You mean Tao Sword Deity, Zhao Yuzhen?
But you are still here.
Me?
I can't fight you. I'm just a scholar.
Look, my sword is called Ten Thousand Scrolls.
Reading ten thousand books is like traveling ten thousand li.
I respect you.
No need for this courtesy.
I'm flattered.
Brother Qingyang, are you just here to ask for a sword challenge?
Asking for a sword challenge is one of my wishes.
I will stay for three days, waiting for swordsmen of the world to come to challenge me.
Three days later, I will kill someone
and take someone away.
The one you're waiting for, Baili Dongjun, he's not coming.
Taking away the one you want to take away? It won't be easy.
As for the person you want to kill...
Who do you want to kill, if I may ask?
What a nice Nine-Song Sword.
Brother Qingyang, then, I should get going.
Are you in a hurry to leave?
I could have stayed a little longer,
but I'm afraid someone is losing his patience.
I'm even more afraid that he would misinterpret this and think that I'm competing with him.
This man is bad-tempered and very strong.
I need to go.
You see. I'm not wrong, aren't I?
Brother Zhantian, it's been a long time.
My sword is here. Let's fight!
What...
Young Master. What happened?
Young Master, the guards said they spotted an incredibly long flying sword coming at us,
and it struck our plaque to the ground.
It looks like it's coming at me.
Yes, Young Master.
- Put it away now.
- Yes.
- Hurry.
- Go now.
Someone has sent word that the first to challenge Luo Qingyang has appeared.
It must be the Rage Sword Deity.
Xiao Se...
You want to watch the show?
Let's go now.
Come on.
Lei Wujie, can you keep it quiet?
It's not like I let it do this on purpose.
Two sword deities are fighting here.
Of course the sword with the purest heart in the world will be a little excited.
Xiao Se, do you have the Hanghao I asked you to bring with you?
Why are you suddenly asking about this?
Then I am relieved.
You are the daughter of Spear Deity.
How can you place your faith in a good luck charm?
It took us an hour to get here.
We spent another hour chatting.
Why aren't they fighting yet?
Are they waiting for someone to come?
You think sword deities fight like you?
He strikes, you duck.
He strikes again, you duck again.
Then you turn around and stab...
Then I leap, raise my giant sword, and strike the gate open.
Thousands of sword deities step out the gate of Heaven, raising their swords, and stab!
The two of you together could be storytellers.
You all seem to be in a good mood.
Scholar Xie.
I just asked Luo Qingyang about the purpose of his visit to Tianqi City.
He said he would challenge Tianqi to sword fights for three days.
Three days later, he will take someone away and kill someone.
The one he wants to take away must be his younger martial sister, Consort Xuan.
As for the one he wants to kill...
I'm guessing that it's me.
What?
He wants to kill Xiao Se?
Is this show still fun to watch?
We will go back now. I will ask Ji Xue to send a letter to Xueyue City.
I will ask my father to come to help us.
Take it easy. We still have three days.
- Xiao Se!
- Xiao Se...
You've guessed it already, haven't you?
Let's watch the battle first.
Challenging Tianqi's swordsmen for three days is a ploy to put pressure on us,
proving that he is already invincible in the world.
After three days, whatever he wants to do, no one will be able to stop him or stand in his way.
Looks like Rage Sword Deity isn't just here to ask for a sword challenge.
He has also borne the expectations of Prince Bai.
If he can defeat Luo Qingyang, then Luo Qingyang's invincibility would be a joke.
He won't be able to take away the one he wants to take away and kill the one he wants to kill.
Master, why hasn't Yan Zhantian made his move?
Yan Zhantian's Rage Sword Technique has only three moves.
Draw the sword with rage, strike with rage, and withdraw it with rage.
He won't use the Rage Sword Technique easily against unnecessary opponents.
But for an opponent like Luo Qingyang, he has to use the Rage Sword Technique.
Since he can only use these three moves, he has to build up strength.
Here it comes.
Luo Qingyang wants to defeat Yan Zhantian without drawing his sword. How arrogant.
Draw your sword!
This is what Yan Zhantian looks like when his rage is at its peak.
What a great duel.
But who won?
Good question. Who won?
He has fought hundreds of battles and has fought with one sword against millions of soldiers.
It's tacky to judge this duel as victory or defeat.
Master!
Thank you, Master.
He's better than I.
Chong'er, I couldn't help you this time.
It's fine. I'm just glad you're not hurt.
Master, my men will take you back to rest.
- What about you?
- I will stay and watch.
Be careful.
After this battle, Prince Bai's Residence in Tianqi City will never be the same again.
I never thought Prince Bai would be the one to make the first move.
There are several reasons why he did that.
In the Imperial Court, the senior officials who were supporting Prince Bai
have begun to waver because of Xiao Chuhe's return.
His biggest helper in the court, Bearer of Records, has been killed by the Head Eunuch.
The Tang Clan no longer supports him in the martial arts world.
If Prince Bai had won this battle, then Prince Bai's Residence,
which has the strongest protector in the world, would've turned things around.
Didn't Prince Bai realize that?
Prince Bai is not a fool, but he is also a fool.
He actually began to care about his vain brotherhood with Xiao Chuhe.
He made the first move because he didn't want to give my godfather the chance to kill Xiao Chuhe.
Lei Wujie, don't be reckless.
I... My two sword deity masters aren't here.
I'll challenge Luo Qingyang on their behalf. What's wrong with that?
Besides, doesn't he want to kill Xiao Se? He can't be allowed to be that cocky.
It's not time for you to play the hero yet.
I'm Wushuang from Wushuang City. I have come to challenge you!
Brother Wushuang!
We met again. You have to fight well.
Don't worry. I will do my best.
I heard Wushuang City has a new city lord, who is young and talented.
I didn't expect he could be so young.
I didn't expect that even the City Lord of Wushuang has come to Tianqi City.
I invited him.
You asked Wushuang to enter the city because you think he can beat Luo Qingyang?
Wushuang City has been waiting for a chance.
I'm waiting for a chance too.
Please enlighten me, Elder.
It's an honor to see Wushuang Sword Box.
You know about Wushuang Sword Box too?
People say I was born to be a swordsman. Some people also say...
We will talk with swords.
Sure!
Twelve flying swords.
Wushuang City finally has a sword deity after a century.
I'm flattered, Elder. Go!
The Flying Sword Technique is indeed a wonderful sword art,
but as a swordsman, if you don't hold a sword in your hand,
you are still a bit short of the mark.
If you had borrowed your master's Water Breaking Sword,
you might have lasted longer.
I have a sword that I hold in my hand.
The Vermilion!
What is he doing?
The Vermilion and the twelve flying swords were made by the Ghost Swordsmith.
They need to be fed with blood. Therefore, the Vermilion has another name...
The Devil Sword.
It really is a good sword.
Kill Wushuang. I want this sword.
Oh no.
Wushuang failed to control the Vermilion. Instead, the sword has taken control.
There is no way that I would be controlled by a sword.
What do you think, Mr. Luo?
It's a good move. It's worth drawing my sword.
Look at Luo Qingyang!
This is... Martyr Sword Dance.
Why do I feel sad watching him draw his sword?
Martyr Sword, the best technique of Desolate Sword, is Luo Qingyang's strongest move.
What does Martyr mean?
Those who die without courage on the battlefield
are not allowed to be coffined and buried in the cemetery.
They are called ghosts without a master.
Do you know why Luo Qingyang chose Muliang City?
In the past, 100,000 soldiers were killed in Muliang City, which is the most powerful gate in the west.
Their country was defeated, and they retreated in a hurry,
leaving the bodies of those who had died in battle uncollected in the wilderness
until they turned into ashes 100 years later.
This is called Martyr.
What melancholy can be greater than the melancholy of a nation?
Is this the legendary sword tendency?
Then I will break the Nine-Song and the melancholy!
It's an honor for Wushuang City to have a disciple like you.
Your sword is not like a mortal sword. It was an eye-opener for me.
Is this a tie for them?
I still lost.
If you practice for another ten years,
perhaps your sword will really surpass mine.
It's a pity that you are going to die here today.
Luo Qingyang wants to kill him?
He actually took the bait so quickly? Kill him.
Wuji Staff?
I thought you were a man of extraordinary stature to have this kind of cultivation,
but when faced with such a talented young man,
City Lord Luo, why were you so determined to kill him?
I have my reasons.
But you can't kill this person today.
♫  The temple is extremely quiet  ♫
♫  We still have a long way to go in the martial arts world  ♫
♫  Outside the snow is falling  ♫
♫  Only clouds know the warmth of the cold moon  ♫
♫  The roaring fate  ♫
♫  Sweeping away the fog of time  ♫
♫  The past is desolate  ♫
♫  Waiting for the ride to the highest heaven  ♫
♫  The ethereal fog  ♫
♫  Fame and fortune do not matter to an enlightened person  ♫
♫  I face the sun  ♫
♫  To have a pristine soul in this polluted world  ♫
♫  Traveling far and overcoming challenges life throws my way  ♫
♫  I'm not wasting my youth away  ♫
♫  Like blade and sword, relying on each other  ♫
♫  With devoted friends and strong bonds  ♫
♫  No dream is small  ♫
♫  Despite conflicts and the feuds, we sing proudly  ♫
♫  Youths ought to be fearless  ♫
♫  Visiting all corners of the world with our youthful spirits  ♫
♫  Traveling freely with friends  ♫
♫  I won't be lonely if I have my confidants  ♫
♫  Traveling far and overcoming challenges life throws my way  ♫
♫  I'm not wasting my youth away  ♫
♫  With devoted friends and strong bonds  ♫
♫  No dream is small  ♫
♫  Despite conflicts and the feuds, we sing proudly  ♫
♫  Youths ought to be fearless  ♫
♫  Visiting all corners of the world with our youthful spirits  ♫
♫  Traveling freely with friends  ♫
♫  I won't be lonely if I have my confidants  ♫