It's over.
What's wrong?
You look decent
dressed like this.
Since we were little,
I've known your preferences best.
Do you remember?
In high school,
you said you liked metal models,
so I asked my dad to bring back
limited edition models from abroad
just for you.
As long as you like it,
I'll find a way to get it for you,
or...
turn myself
into what you like.
This is the first time you've been
with the same partner for so long.
Is he an exception?
Exception?
Rather than an exception,
I just like everything about him.
He's pure,
yet quirky;
honest,
yet so stubborn.
Why I like him...
I just like him.
There's no other reason.
Alright then,
since
you're so sure.
Have a good rest.
I'll come again.
OK.
See you.
Bye, Minwoo.
Did your
treatment go well?
Yeah,
it went well.
Then,
there's something I want to draw.
Would you be my model?
Um...
Give me a kiss.
Approved!
Let's go.
Your hand.
Dear master artist,
can I move now?
I'm tired.
Wait.
Just a bit longer.
Whining when you can endure it.
I'm done.
Done?
Yeah.
Have a look if you want.
Shall I?
Sure.
So impatient.
Ta-da.
Is this...
me?
That's you in my eyes.
You may think it isn't accurate,
but this is how you are in my eyes.
No.
It's too accurate.
It's like
you see the real me.
What are you doing?
Wait, let me give it a try.
Gosh, you're so bad at drawing.
Of course. I'm not an art major.
But now,
with my strokes,
the drawing belongs to me.
Nope.
Wow.
Has the sun risen from
the west?
You actually asked me out.
I don't feel like myself lately.
I want to drag him into my world,
but it's not as easy this time.
It was easy to control him before.
Put shackles on him,
be cruel,
and get violent.
But this is not
the method I want.
Being treated like this,
anyone would yield.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
But he's been trying to
outmaneuver me lately.
He doesn't listen to me at all.
Isn't that good?
Just tie him to you.
That'd be convenient.
But it's not what I want.
What I want is...
communication.
I guess it's communication.
Not shackles, abuse, and cruelty,
but sincerity that comes from here.
I bet you don't understand.
Wow.
You even did some soul-searching?
This is really unlike you.
You said
he's Kim Haejun,
right?
Don't worry.
I won't do anything to him.
But
sometimes,
I have other choices too.
You've gotten much better these days.
Continue the treatment
and you'll get better.
What is this?
Here too.
What are you doing?
Hey.
What happened to your neck?
I did it on purpose.
To understand you,
I had to do this.
Are you crazy?
Why did you do all that for me?
Do you think this is a joke?
This is just my preference.
Do you understand?
You don't even know anything.
Of course I had to.
If I want to help you,
to cure you,
I need to truly know you first.
Jaehun.
I know you better than anyone.
So,
can't you choose me?
I'm not afraid of you,
nor will I leave you.
I'll do anything
you want me to.
Instead of being with someone
who makes you walk on eggshells
and who may leave you anytime,
isn't it easier to be with me?
Yo, Santa's here again!
Hey, Minwoo.
Minwoo!
You're mistaken.
There's nothing between you and me.
Don't cross the line.
Yo, Santa's here again!
Hmm?
Where's Jaehun?
He's getting physical therapy upstairs.
Therapy?
Has it been effective?
Yeah,
I think so.
He says he's better,
and Minwoo is quite professional.
That's good.
Let's go in.
This is wine I treasure too.
Another bottle?
Yeah, I'm rich, remember?
Wow.
Jaehun is so nice to you.
I drew these recently.
The colors are all over the place.
The composition is decent,
but you didn't establish
a clear light source.
You need to figure out
the overall flow first.
Your talent is not outstanding,
but you have artistic sense.
The problem is
your weak foundation.
When you have many ideas,
you tend to go astray.
Or you could
just stay an amateur.
You're going to graduate soon, right?
This doesn't look good.
That's why I'm worried.
The professor said I need more practice.
How about this?
I'll come to tutor you every week.
For free.
Since Jaehun and I are friends.
Do you know how to draw?
You really don't know me.
I'm a Fine Arts graduate.
A graduation project is
a piece of cake to me.
Oh,
Yoon Minwoo!
Why are you here?
Soohyung is
really professional.
I think
he'll be of help to me.
If you think so, then sure.
Hey, manage the time well.
Don't get in Kim Haejun's way.
Of course.
Let's go, Yoon Minwoo.
I'll take you home.
Instead of being with someone
who makes you walk on eggshells
and who may leave you anytime,
isn't it easier to be with me?
Jaehun-hyung.
Something's bothering me.
Haejun.
Come here.
Kneel.
Jaehun-hyung.
Our relationship is contractual.
Without the contract,
would you still choose me?
Stop.
Tie your hands
and look at me.
I knew it.
This is the most comfortable way.
Already feeling it?
I haven't even started.
I...
can prove it.
You've gotten much better these days.
Continue the treatment
and you'll get better.
What now?
Nothing.
I just...
like it when we're alone.
There's only the two of us here.
You can do whatever you want.
And I'll do whatever you want.
I know you're thinking about Kim Haejun.
But...
I can
satisfy you better than him.
Then continue.
Try it.
Go on!
I know you're thinking about Kim Haejun!
But...
I can
satisfy you better than him.
How?
What do you even know?
You think you know
about me and Kim Haejun?
Answer me then!
What do you know?
Tell me!
I can do better than him!
What can you do?
Do it then!
You can't, can you?
Please give me a chance.
Please!
Hey.
A chance?
Chances are earned, not given!
Must I give you a chance
because we're friends?
Get lost.
Don't ever come back.
Minwoo.
It's over already?
Let's
eat together.
No.
He doesn't like eating
at someone else's house.
I'm craving pizza.
Can you buy me pizza?
I'll go buy it.
Minwoo.
If you're free,
can we talk?
Have you known Jaehun
for a long time?
Jaehun and I?
We were close since elementary school.
Including Kang Soohyung.
The three of us were
inseparable.
He seldom tells me about his past.
That's how he's like.
How long have you been seeing him?
About half a year.
Half a year?
Jaehun...
In the past,
he's slept with all sorts of people.
But
I guess he's into
the college student type now.
His taste has changed a lot.
With love, I think that
rather than the length of relationship
or personal tastes,
feelings are more important.
I think Jaehun thinks so too.
Jaehun and I are together
because we need each other.
Sure.
Of course.
But
in our community,
many things matter more than feelings.
Identity,
status,
and sexual compatibility.
Especially for people like Jaehun.
What he wants
is more than just a companion.
He needs someone
who understands his entire world,
including the darkness
in his heart.
Haejun.
You're too young.
You might not be able to handle
someone like Jaehun.
In other words,
he's not suitable for you.
I...
trust his choice.
I'll also be responsible for this choice.
Alright.
Good luck then.
Haejun, I bought pizza!
What's going on?
Why are you still here?
I just
talked about the past with him.
Let me do it.
Are you leaving?
I should.
It's late.
I can't spend the night at your place.
Coming.
Hey, hello!
Yoon Minwoo is here too.
Soohyung, what brings you here?
That's what I want to know to.
Why are you here?
There was some wine left at home.
Isn't it nice to drink together?
Hey.
It's not easy for us to get together.
How about a game?
A game?
What do you think, Yoon Minwoo?
Sounds good.
Truth or Dare.
OK?
Let's have a drink before we start.
Why the long face?
Don't be a killjoy.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Cheers!
Can I drink?
Yes, you can.
I'll get the ball rolling.
Soohyung.
Go ahead.
I have many secrets.
How many
people have you dated?
Zero.
Have you been single all your life?
Well,
dating doesn't have to be involved.
He's probably slept with
more people than Jaehun has.
Then...
are you a top?
If you're curious,
let's give it a go.
Are you drunk, Kang Soohyung?
You're drunk. That's enough.
Fine.
OK.
Since it was me, I'll spin it again.
Me?
I really have no secrets.
What if you don't get what you want?
I'll do whatever it takes
until I get it.
What if you destroy it in the process?
Even if it's destroyed,
what's mine is still mine.
OK, who's next?
Let's stop here.
It's boring.
Go home, you two.
We've played enough.
You should go back.
Let's go.
Jaehun.
How many people have you dated?
I've never dated anyone.
It was always contractual.
I've never been in a proper relationship.
Is there really nothing
between you and Yoon Minwoo?
I saw pictures of you two
on the canvas.
He seems to like you.
You seem to like him too.
Me?
Minwoo and I...
I can't believe I have to explain this,
but there's really nothing.
Don't change the subject.
Haejun.
Minwoo, Soohyung, and I
have been best friends since we were kids.
We know each other well,
so we know how to
treat each other
and make each other happy.
There's never been anything romantic.
I swear.
Have you slept with him?
Hey.
Who do you think I am?
Why'd I sleep with my buddy?
But Minwoo doesn't seem to think that way.
Kim Haejun.
Is that why you've been
coming on to me lately?
Because you see them as threats?
That's not what I mean.
It seems like I've come all this way...
just to
get to you.
I've finally arrived.
Now,
I want to accept everything about you.
[Tide of Love 2]