♫ My heart flutters like a startled deer ♫
♫ My face blushes ♫
♫ My flushed cheeks feel hot ♫
♫ I almost stop breathing ♫
♫ As you approach step by step ♫
♫ My heart speeds up, and I dare not look at ♫
♫ Your eyes ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them. Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them. ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
[Warm Meets You, Directed by Chu Dejian]
[Episode 6]
Zhao Ming Yang, you big fool!
Why give them all the project money you received?
Now you don't even have money for a cab.
Don't pretend to be a saint,
or you'll get struck by lightning.
No way.
I won't be as unlucky as Zhao Nuan Nuan,
who encounters rain on a clear night, right?
Never mind.
I'll go stay with Old Jin for the night.
[Old Jin: Boss, my girlfriend is here today.]
- I can't hang out with you tonight.
- Oh no!
Now you're all about your girlfriend.
Forget it.
As long as Zhao Nuan Nuan doesn't fight with her roommate
and is free from bad luck,
it's worth my sleeping in a garden.
Besides, I really don't want to see her roommate,
that she-devil!
What did you just call me?
What name did you call me?
Belle. Fairy. Queen.
Your sister seems to have no time to lecture you.
Today, I will teach this golden kitten a lesson on her behalf.
My clothes! My luggage!
Sir, on the latest mobile game project,
if we make it bigger, will there be a more—
Zheng Lin, I have to tell you something.
Mr. Dong.
- You may leave.
- Okay.
Ling Mei, next time you enter, knock first.
No, I was in a hurry.
Two sisters just called. They both said Yi Chen has a girlfriend.
Why are they so worried about him?
Aren't you worried? Anyway, I've pondered it a long time.
I think this matter is too strange.
Look, Yi Chen was back in China for years.
He never mentioned he had a girlfriend, did he?
How come he suddenly has a girlfriend,
and they seem to be very close?
However, their closeness is very odd.
- How's it going?
- Not very well.
Guess who came to talk to me today?
Mr. Dong from Meilin Investment.
"Meilin"?
Meilin Investment is owned by Gu Group.
It is controlled by your father.
Their approach to me shows your father wasn't joking with you.
If Meilin's big cash flow enters our market, next to UA and Hechuan,
there will be more trouble afterward.
If you don't want to miss this opportunity,
arrive on time with your girlfriend for the group's thirtieth anniversary party.
Zhao Ming Yang, you can stay here,
but you must pay a price.
Excuse me, Your Ladyship. Do you need anything else?
Please bring me two bowls of high-protein, low-fat, and plant-based drinks.
High-protein, low-fat, and plant-based?
Soy milk.
Wait a minute.
To make the soy milk I like, the beans must be fresh.
I don't want dry ones soaked overnight.
The liquid has to be freshly extracted.
I won't drink anything that's older than half an hour.
The temperature has to be 65 degrees.
If it's one degree lower or higher, I can't drink it.
Also, I want half sweetness,
and Nuan Nuan wants full sweetness.
All right, Your Ladyship.
Also, do not use ice to cool it down.
It will reduce the soy milk richness.
I will deduct you points for that.
All right.
Someone should have tamed Zhao Ming Yang long ago.
See if he dares disrespect me again.
I think he treats you quite well.
Do you?
That's because you haven't seen him betray me.
When we were small, he told me to soak all of mom's cosmetics in the bathtub.
Then he blamed me, claiming I wanted to bathe them.
Did your mother punish you?
She almost broke my legs.
So in my opinion, Zhao Ming Yang is not a puppy
but a wolf pup who bites.
Sister Xin Ran, are you no longer angry at me?
Of course not. Last time, you saved me in front of the boss.
Okay? Each person gets one time.
[Z.M.G. Tech.com]
Mi Mi, will you retake the college entrance exam?
No, I will not.
I want to conquer a man and let him fall under my wits,
having no reason to reject me.
Zhao Nuan Nuan, President Gu waits for you.
Mi Mi, don't do this.
Oh, no!
I forgot I had to tell Nuan Nuan something.
- What is it?
- Tomorrow seems to be Gu Group's anniversary.
President Gu is Chairman Gu's son so he'll likely attend, right?
My grandfather also got an invitation.
See.
Recently, many good things happened to me.
I don't stumble anymore. I no longer lose my wallet.
Even Ming Yang and Xin Ran's matter was resolved smoothly.
Am I really no longer super unlucky after meeting him?
That is right, the panda glasses.
Hello, President Gu.
[Office of the President]
President Gu, what are you doing?
Help her look prettier.
- All right, that can be arranged.
- Be fast.
♫ The blue summer sky outside the window ♫
Can you speed up a little? I'm in a hurry.
Yes, Mr. Gu.
- Make it quick. Mr. Gu is in a hurry.
- Okay.
♫ Of you every day ♫
♫ Flowers bloom all over the courtyard ♫
Bring your women's gowns for her to try on.
Okay.
♫ Every day, I think about ♫
♫ Your smiling face ♫
♫ Happiness unknowingly ♫
♫ Comes closer to me ♫
♫ Gazing at the future horizon ♫
♫ Discovering the halo of dreams ♫
♫ Collecting your love in my pocket ♫
♫ I just want to be doted on by you ♫
♫ Holding me in the palms of your hands ♫
♫ An inseparable dependency ♫
♫ I want to be doted on by you ♫
President Gu, didn't you like any gown?
You designed too much menswear the last two years.
President Gu, my apprentice designed these.
You may not like them.
Just this one, let her try it.
All right.
You look beautiful in it.
I didn't expect President Gu's excellent taste.
The dress you chose fits her perfectly.
This is barely acceptable.
Wait a second.
Turn around.
You didn't zip it up.
I can't reach it.
♫ Always secretly protecting me ♫
♫ White hair slowly shows up ♫
♫ Wrinkles at the corners of the eyes ♫
♫ Now it's my turn ♫
♫ To shield you from wind and rain ♫
♫ And to love you ♫
What's wrong?
The zipper…
is stuck.
That shouldn't happen.
I'm not that big, am I?
Manager.
Take care of this.
All right.
The mended clothes will be sent directly to the venue.
Now come with me to buy a pair of shoes.
Wait a minute. President Gu, can you explain first?
You took me to the beauty center, then you buy me clothes and shoes.
What exactly are you doing?
Tonight is Gu Group's thirtieth anniversary party.
Gu Group's chairman, Gu Zheng Lin, is my father.
I need you to act as my girlfriend and accompany me to the party.
I-Is Gu Group the super famous listed group
covering over a dozen industries?
Yes.
Zhao Nuan Nuan?
I'm sorry, President Gu. Maybe I can't fulfill your request.
You should find someone else.
Don't forget. We have a cooperation agreement.
Now you're a Z Mobile Games employee
and in a cooperation with me.
You should and must fulfill your obligations.
Even if I'm a Z Mobile Games employee,
I don't have to accompany you to such an event.
Gu Group is such a big famous company.
Their anniversary must be very grand.
Many celebrities and VIPs will be there.
You are Chairman Gu's son.
You're used to such events,
but I'm just a regular person.
I'm an ordinary, common girl who is often unlucky.
I've never worn such an expensive dress
nor attended a high-profile party.
I don't even know how to drink wine.
I want to stay by your side and borrow your good luck,
but I never thought of accompanying you to a grand event,
much less act as your girlfriend before so many strangers.
What are you saying?
In any case, I won't go.
Zhao Nuan Nuan.
I won't go.
I don't care if you fire me from Z Mobile Games or deduct my entire salary,
I just can't go!
Find someone else.
President Gu, your clothes.
Qiao Nan, come and pick me up immediately!
Zhao Nuan Nuan, you coward!
You always wanted luck and to attract good things.
Now a president asks you to pose as his girlfriend
and to be at a high-profile event,
yet you ran away?
You're such a coward!
But this is a big corporation.
I was never out all night in a nightclub.
How do I socialize there
and pose with the Chairman's only son?
That's too difficult.
Forget it. I won't go.
Where is he?
Over here.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yi Chen, don't worry about it.
Maybe this event is too sudden and imposing for a young girl.
You should at least give her time to think it over.
Okay, don't worry.
I'll call her in a while and coax her again.
Let's go.
Where to?
We'll go like this.
Are you sure?
If you go alone and your father sees you, won't that verify your problem?
You don't relate to him well as it is.
If this continues, it will be irreparable.
I shouldn't have lied to him.
I should admit my phobia to him.
Gu Yi Chen.
Whatever the consequences,
if he turns on me,
humiliates me at the party
or if Z Mobile Games sinks into an irreparable crisis,
all this is my fault.
I will take full responsibility.
Yi Chen! Yi Chen!
[Gu Group: 30 Years Party]
Miss, look here, please.
Over here.
Sir, you're here.
- Is everything ready?
- Don't worry. They arranged everything well.
Chairman,
tonight, other than major company executives and guests,
will Yi Chen be coming?
What does it matter if he comes or not?
It's like this. As stated in our last investment report,
besides Yi Chen's Z Mobile Games
and his old rivals, UA and Hechuan Technology....
Investing is a professional trade.
Which company is worthwhile,
which company to invest in,
and which investment will bring profits are all issues you need to consider.
Yes.
I hired you to run Meilin,
not to monitor my every move.
Do you understand?
I understand, Sir.
Sir, please come inside.
Nuan Nuan, why are you back?
Didn't Mi Mi say tonight is Gu Group's 30-year party?
She went with her grandfather.
Isn't President Gu going?
Whether he goes or not,
I don't know.
I have a headache. I'm going to my room.
He will go, won't he?
Or maybe he won't.
He won't go alone, will he?
If he goes alone,
won't our act of posing as a couple for his relatives a few days ago
be exposed?
No, no, he surely won't go.
But what if he does go?
If he goes or not,
I'm doomed.
How did this happen?
I just wanted to stay with him and share a little of his good luck.
I dislike being unlucky daily.
I just want to fulfill my dream of mobile games.
No, don't consider it anymore.
I need to focus on drawing.
If he's a lucky charm or Z Mobile Games' boss,
today I just want to draw.
[Mi's Video Call]
Hello, Mi Mi.
Sister Xin Ran, I'm at Gu Group's anniversary party.
Look!
So many people are here, and they are so beautiful!
You are the most beautiful.
You are so sweet.
By the way, Mi Mi, did President Gu and Assistant Sheng go today?
I don't think I saw them.
Will President Gu come tonight?
And Senior Qiao Nan?
I think I just saw them.
Chairman Gu is here.
- Sir.
This time, compared to other investment projects,
Yi Chen's Z Mobile Games has many advantages.
I am very optimistic about his project.
Zheng Lin, you're here.
I just saw Presidents Chen and Li.
- That auntie is here, too.
- They both brought their daughters.
I see.
Then I will tell them about Yi Chen.
Will Yi Chen come tonight?
Whether he comes is up to him.
Zheng Lin, after all, you are father and son.
Stop making your relationship so tense.
He said he would bring his girlfriend.
I'd like to see if he has the guts.
Zheng Lin.
Don't disrupt the celebration.
You can talk to your friends later over cocktails.
Okay, I understand.
Mr. Dong.
Let us continue to discuss our plan.
President Gu is here.
Mr. Gu.
But their relationship is not very good.
Really?
I heard it a long time ago.
Many people know about it.
His father's company still depends on him.
Exactly.
Currently, the mobile game project seems very competitive.
Okay, let's try this project first.
Father.
Okay, I'll leave you.
Don't worry.
Father.
I arrived on time as per your request.
My request?
Did I ask you to only be on time?
You are my son.
I know exactly what you plan to do.
You can't even put up a pretense.
Don't think of getting anything else in the future.
I've never thought of getting one thing.
When I studied abroad alone or started a business with Qiao Nan,
I always relied on my own strength and hard work.
Since you're so ambitious,
why do you need Meilin's investment?
I'd like to see how long you and your tofu-stall company
can remain standing!
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have come here today.
You can do what you want with the power you hold.
You'll see with your own eyes
that my company will go higher and further.
- Gu Yi Chen, stop there!
- Zheng Lin.
How can you argue with your son today on such an occasion?
Yi Chen! Yi Chen!
Don't come any closer.
Oh no, something happened.
What's wrong, Mi Mi?
I'm not quite sure.
It seems President Gu had a quarrel with his father's current wife.
"His father's current wife"?
Isn't that—
President. Gu is very angry.
Senior Nan is here, too.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have spoken to you like that.
But please don't interfere with my life anymore.
But Yi Chen, we are a family.
Since my mother died,
I have had no home.
Gu Yi Chen!
If you still remember how my mother died,
then please don't show up in front of me anymore.
I won't interfere with your and my father's life.
Please don't interfere with my life, either.
You and I were never a family.
Oh, no! Sister Xin Ran, something huge is about to happen.
Oh gosh…
Nuan Nuan.
Nuan Nuan, are you sure you're not going?
If you don't go, something is bound to happen.
Look.
- Mi Mi, do you have a dress I can borrow?
- You don't have to.
Just before I left work,
I saw Senior Qiao Nan leave the dress you tried on with Mr. Gu.
It's at the front desk.
There was also a pair of brand-new high heels at the front desk.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[South Tower]
- Yi Chen!
- How did it get that physical?
- They don't seem to get along.
- Yes.
This is too inappropriate. He shouldn't have done that.
So many people saw it.
- How could he do that?
- It's a disgrace to the family.
With this slap from you,
now, we are no longer father and son.
From now on, I am no longer your son.
Gu Yi Chen!
Yi Chen!
♫ Memories always inadvertently turn yellow ♫
♫ Good things always quietly fade away ♫
♫ I always feel sad for no reason ♫
♫ Even a helpless smile can't hide it ♫
I'm here.
I'm sorry I am late.
I caused you to misunderstand Yi Chen.
My name is Zhao Nuan Nuan, and I am Yi Chen's…
girlfriend.
♫ Is carved into my heart ♫
♫ As I hesitate, I am afraid that I will ♫
♫ Miss (fail to get) you ♫
♫ My heartbeat slowly falls from the sky ♫
♫ Whose breath is getting weaker and weaker? ♫
♫ I don't want to say who is at fault ♫
Were you and your father always on such bad terms?
My father and mother divorced when I was nine.
It's been like this ever since.
So the lady just now—
She is my father's second wife.
And your mother?
She passed away that same year.
Loving You by Tan Han
♫ When I'm unaware ♫
♫ He always quietly appears ♫
♫ Why is it always he who stirs my heart? ♫
♫ He's obviously a bit obnoxious ♫
♫ Why do I feel like my heart skips a beat? ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ It feels like we've been friends ♫
♫ But I really want to know if I'm in your heart ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ A bit tired and flustered, feeling annoyed ♫
♫ Love always makes me feel dejected ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to see the sunrise with you ♫
♫ Something simple and fulfilling ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫