♫ My heart flutters like a startled deer ♫
♫ My face blushes ♫
♫ My flushed cheeks feel hot ♫
♫ I almost stop breathing ♫
♫ As you approach step by step ♫
♫ My heart speeds up, and I dare not look at ♫
♫ Your eyes ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them. Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
[Warm Meets You, Directed by Chu Dejian]
[Episode 4]
Zhao Nuan Nuan is so messy.
I didn't expect her roommate to be even messier.
Mom always wants to arrange blind dates for her.
With them like this, it's rare if they find husbands.
Zhao Nuan Nuan, how could you?
Who is that?
Who? Who's in there?
Who is it? Exactly who is there?
Come out! Show yourself!
I'm going to hurt you.
If you don't come out,
I will really hurt you!
So it's you, Little Cat.
This really is too much.
I have to do this at Zhao Nuan Nuan's home.
What kind of punishment am I suffering?
No. I must get my studio done tomorrow.
I need to move. Move out.
Older Auntie, no, I mean Older Sister. It's not what you think.
Listen to me, Baby.
In the future, we mustn't play with the weird guy next door.
You're the weird one!
Hello, how can I help you?
I'm looking for Wu Xin Ran.
Xin Ran is off today. She seems to have gone home.
If you need to reach her, I can pass a message for you.
- What? Has she gone home?
- Yes.
That's bad. I wonder if Zhao Ming Yang is there or not.
- Zhao Nuan Nuan.
- Yes?
President Gu is waiting for you upstairs. Why aren't you going up?
- But...
- But what?
It's almost 3 p.m. Do you want to double the work?
Quickly, come with me.
Assistant Sheng, wait for me.
[Office of the President]
What are you waiting for? Go in.
G-Gu Yi…
President Gu, I'm here.
It's not 3 p.m. yet.
That's an improvement.
So my work is…
It's over there.
Will I work as a cleaner at Z Mobile Games?
To be precise, you will be an exclusive cleaner for my office.
It doesn't seem much different from a regular company cleaner.
The difference is huge.
You must sort the books according to the size, thickness,
category, and purchase year, and neatly put them in their place.
Also, pay attention to the color of the book covers and align them by color scheme.
For the sofas and coffee table, including the decorations and tea cups,
you need to wash them with very hot water daily.
Sanitize with the best disinfectant wipes.
Don't leave a single water stain on them.
When cleaning the office desk, besides daily cleaning and maintenance,
you must put all files back where they were.
If a file is lost or a single page goes missing,
you must take full responsibility.
Also, for the cleaning of the entire office,
besides the daily large-scale disinfection,
there's also a more thorough cleaning every three days.
Even the smallest corners of all sofas, carpets, and file cabinets
must all be cleaned until they are dust-free.
If I find a strand of hair
or a speck of dust,
you'll have to do it all over again.
Gu Yi Chen, you might as well kill me!
[Office of the President]
This is so hard.
But for Senior Nan,
I must persist.
Have you sent out all the administrative files today?
What are you doing? The packages are piling up.
Aren't you working today?
Oh... Xin Ran sent out all administrative files in the morning.
If you're in a hurry, we can send them for you first thing tomorrow. We—
No, these are all project copyright books.
They need to be expedited.
Forget it; I'll go myself.
Won't you stand up?
Do I have to personally pull you out,
Fang Mi?
Surprise, Senior Nan.
[President Gu Yi Chen]
I thought he called me back to Z Mobile Games out of real kindness
to give me a job as a concept artist.
I can't believe he is such a profiteer.
He called me back to torment me, right?
Thorough disinfection of the office?
He might as well soak himself in disinfectant.
If I keep working like this every day,
I'm afraid I'll die here before I reach 100 days in this office.
Wait. Since I met him at the hotel last time,
many good things have happened to me.
Now that I'm trapped in this office,
isn't it my perfect chance to get close to him
and change my life of almost 22 years of bad luck?
Maybe he really is like a lucky charm
and touching him could change my life.
The most awesome mobile game master in the industry, right?
Then let me…
I can't live this way anymore.
Even if I can't afford rent, must I hide?
I'm leaving right now.
U-Unbelievable.
It can't be that she has come back again?
Since we're roommates,
let me help you
expel the evil.
Chili, garlic, and vinegar?
Zhao Nuan Nuan!
- Qiao Nan…
- What did you call me?
Senior Nan.
What's going on?
Why did you suddenly return from America? Did you tell your parents?
How is it you've appeared at Z Mobile Games, even working as a receptionist?
Exactly what are you doing?
You're asking me so many questions. Which one should I answer first?
I just returned from America last week.
My parents don't know. I came back just for you.
I want to work at Z Mobile Games so I can be by your side.
I don't mind receptionist work.
As long as I can see you every day, I can do anything.
Stop playing around.
You rushed back without telling your parents?
They must be looking all over the world for you now!
What are you doing as a receptionist? It makes no sense.
Pack your bags right away and go back tomorrow.
No. Leave today. I'll book a ticket for you right now.
Don't drive me away.
Impossible.
Hello, book a flight to America for today.
- I won't go!
- This afternoon, as soon as possible.
I like you!
If there are no other questions, today's meeting can end right now.
[You should give it a try.]
[If this girl really can help you overcome your psychological problems]
and your troublesome pathological allergies, all the risks are worth it.
Hello? That's me.
You will come in person?
[Z.M.G. Tech.com]
President Gu.
Qiao Nan, the leader of Fei Xiang Investment contacted me today.
He wants to join our marketing operations.
I'm going out; come pick me up.
What do you want?
Nothing.
I just want to
borrow something from you, President Gu.
♫ My flushed cheeks feel hot ♫
So where should I touch him?
You should give it a try.
Maybe she can help you overcome your troublesome allergies.
♫ Your eyes ♫
Should I really try?
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
- This time, it's really good.
- True!
The moon is quite full tonight, right?
Yes, besides the moon, you can see Saturn.
- What's that one next to it?
- That next one?
It's Venus, twinkling and sparkling.
President Gu, good afternoon... good evening. Go home safely. Bye bye.
Why am I so unlucky?
I just wanted to touch the lucky charm for some good luck.
Why did I have to meet everyone getting off work?
You even managed to corner him.
Zhao Nuan Nuan, you're incurable.
Zhao Ming Yang? Zhao Ming Yang!
What happened to you? Who beat you up like this?
[Xin]
[Ran]
You met Sister Xin Ran?
She beat you up like this?
Okay, it seems the unluckiest person today... isn't me.
[Empress Mother]
Hello, Mom.
What? Again?
I'm only 22.
I won't go on a blind date.
Why aren't you driving?
Where are we going? I haven't had time to prepare.
What happened to you?
Me? What could happen to me?
Qiao Nan, whenever you lie, your eyes look right.
What about you, CEO Gu?
I just saw in the work group chat that you put on quite a show in the elevator.
Assistant Sheng, you just lost your performance bonus for this month.
Fine with me. After all, you're the one supporting me.
Enough of that. Let's get to business.
At Times Square, I'll meet the person in charge of Fei Xiang.
He seems very interested in our big data operation ideas for "Legend II."
I'll talk with him first. You can go back and sort out the data tonight.
If we can secure this investment, the marketing operations for our sequel will be stable.
All right, I'll get it ready as soon as I get home.
How have Hechuan Technology and UA been doing recently?
As you expected, those two companies initiated contacts.
From insider information, Hechuan has made many concessions to UA's demands.
I fear they probably want to reach an agreement no matter what.
If these two companies agree to collaborate, we will be their next target.
- Proceed as planned.
- Absolutely.
Mom, can't you just leave me alone?
Zhao Nuan Nuan, what's wrong with you?
Can't you understand my good intentions?
Nuan Nuan, we know you are only 22.
We're not in a hurry to marry you off,
but it's dangerous for a young girl like you to be out there alone
with no one taking care of you. Isn't that right?
We just want you to find a good boyfriend soon.
Even if he just brings you a meal when you're working overtime,
or gives you advice when you need it, we'll feel at ease.
Besides, if you start blind dates at 22,
then you have to date for two years.
One more year after you're engaged,
and buying a home, decorating it, buying furniture and other assets,
and preparing for the wedding will take another year, right?
By then, you won't be 22 anymore.
Mom, why are you thinking so far ahead?
We, as parents, have to think ahead, right?
Why aren't you asking Ming Yang to go on blind dates?
I'll deal with that brat after I marry you off.
I am only one minute older than him.
All right, enough.
I'll go, okay?
That's more like it.
That's my good girl.
Wait, I'll send you the address of the blind date.
Check it out.
I should have promoted Ming Yang
and let Mom focus on him.
Never mind. We'll wait and see.
Why your look?
I'm just concerned about our Nuan Nuan.
Children can find their own destiny.
What do you know?
If we wait for Nuan Nuan to take initiative,
all the good young men will be taken.
I'm just taking precautions, understand?
I don't understand.
Add water.
Okay, I will add it for you.
Boss, something happened.
Hechuan Technology just held a press conference,
to announce a cooperation agreement with UA.
More than ten investment company leaders
were directly invited to the press conference site.
- I see.
- What do we do now?
First, let's go back to the company.
Excuse me, where is room 208?
Over there.
By the way, which way is the restroom?
This way.
If you don't have anything to say, I'll leave now.
You failed to win the investment.
You didn't know you were facing your enemy's company.
With your business intellect,
don't tell anyone that you're my son when you leave here.
I don't want to be judged by my family name.
Cooperation depends not only on chance, but on strength.
I believe in my company.
[Haitian Mental Convalescence Home]
The Haitian Convalescence Home.,
You will handle the second phase of its development.
The group has many projects this year and can't spare any manpower.
You finish this project,
and all large, profitable items can be transferred to your company's name.
You need to meticulously prepare to compete against rival companies.
I don't have experience with big projects.
I'm afraid I'll disappoint you.
[The Haitian Convalescence Home]
No one gets experience out of nowhere.
If you don't start now, when will you have experience?
You are my son. The group will be handed over to you in the future.
You must start with these projects.
Besides, after additional construction is arranged,
you can stay in there for a while.
I've already notified Director Chen.
He's very experienced in mental rehabilitation.
You didn't come to give me negotiation tips.
This is your real purpose, right?
You've been making a fuss for over a decade. It's time to end it.
So you want to lock me in a convalescent home?
It's not locking you up. It's treatment.
An illness should be treated. What's wrong with that?
Aren't you clear about why I have this illness?
Didn't you help cause it?
Is locking your own son in a convalescent home
something a father should do?
What else do you want?
To make a fuss of it forever?
Ignore your family? Deny your parents?
Gu Yi Chen!
Let me make it clear to you.
This time, you must go, even if you don't want to.
You've acted on your own whims over a decade,
making up some kind of "gynophobia" (fear of women).
You've never had a relationship with a woman.
I'm not expecting you to manage and expand the group.
Your stepmother and I will watch you!
By end of this year, you must marry and start a family!
If you continue this,
your mobile game company is on a dead-end path.
[Haitian Mental Convalescence Home]
Mama! Mama, wake up! Mama!
Mama!
Mama, wake up.
- Yi Chen...
- Mama.
Mama.
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
What's going on?
Is this a little too much?
What is going on?
I've only gained ten pounds since high school.
Why can't I zip my dress?
I can definitely do it.
I just knew I didn't gain weight.
I'm still that slender girl from back then.
Okay, I admit it.
I gained 20 pounds!
I will definitely ruin this blind date.
Is it 208? It's 208.
[206 Shuyun]
Hello, are you here for a blind date?
I'm Zhao Nuan Nuan.
You're the son of Auntie Shen's younger brother
from Building 7 of Licheng Shuiyue Community, right?
What the heck?
Why am I meeting him everywhere today?
I-I-I'm sorry.
I dropped my glasses; I can't see where I'm going.
I…
- I'm sorry to disturb you.
- Zhao Nuan Nuan.
G-G-Gu…
G-G-Gu...
I'm sorry. I really walked in by accident.
I'll leave immediately.
Zhao Nuan Nuan,
let's get married.
["Loving You" by Tan Han]
♫ When I'm unaware ♫
♫ He always quietly appears ♫
♫ Why is it always he who stirs my heart? ♫
♫ He's obviously a bit obnoxious ♫
♫ Why do I feel like my heart skips a beat? ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ It feels like we've been friends ♫
♫ But I really want to know if I'm in your heart ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ A bit tired and flustered, feeling annoyed ♫
♫ Love always makes me feel dejected ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to see the sunrise with you ♫
♫ Something simple and fulfilling ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫