♫ My heart flutters like a startled deer ♫
♫ My face blushes ♫
♫ My flushed cheeks feel hot ♫
♫ I almost stop breathing ♫
♫ As you approach step by step ♫
♫ My heart speeds up, and I dare not look at ♫
♫ Your eyes ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them. Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
[Warm Meets You, Directed by Chu Dejian]
[Episode 10]
Take care of your sister.
[Mr. Ocean]
Oh no.
How did Dad know I was at Zhao Nuan Nuan's place?
But why is he always talking about Zhao Nuan Nuan?
Am I not his son?
Am I the extra one for free?
Dad…
[Z.M.G. Tech.com]
Everyone took a day off.
Their supervisor wrote this on the leave application:
"Due to the oppression of a certain high-level executive, we're under great mental stress."
"So everyone is taking a three-day vacation."
I think you should take a vacation, too.
Wait, Boss!
I'm on your side. Otherwise, I wouldn't have come to work.
- Redo.
- Okay.
Are you seriously asking me to sign this kind of thing?
All right.
Hurry, let's go.
[President Gu Yi Chen]
[Office of the President]
Yao Yao, take this back for me first.
I'll check on him.
Yi Chen, don't be too strict with them.
Everyone has been under much pressure recently.
What did you call me?
President Gu.
I heard you and the new receptionist, Fang Mi, are quite close.
Fang Mi and Zhao Nuan Nuan seem to be close, too.
I'm giving you three days.
No matter what method you use, or even go through Fang Mi,
you must secure Zhao Nuan Nuan's project.
This is your responsibility anyway.
Any questions?
No.
I'll leave it to you.
I should have told Zhao Nuan Nuan not to provoke him.
This guy is horrible when someone touches a nerve.
And he wants me to ask Zhao Nuan Nuan about the project through Fang Mi.
Why don't you just ask me to fly?
[Contacts]
A passionate classic,
Legend of the Mighty.
Zhao Ming Yang.
- What's going on?
- I want to ask about Zhao Nuan Nuan.
I don't know.
It's not Gu Yi Chen who asked me to come. I came to find Fang Mi.
Is she with your sister?
- You won't see them for the next few days.
- Why?
This morning, Zhao Nuan Nuan hit some lucky draw from a popular idol's re-tweet.
She won a two-day stay in a mountain hot spring hotel.
She took Wu Xin Ran and Fang Mi on the trip to the hot spring hotel.
What?
Big Sister Xin Ran, didn't you say that Nuan Nuan's nickname was "Unlucky Girl" at school?
Yes.
She seems quite lucky to me.
Her luck went through the roof (high) recently.
Yes, I didn't expect it, either.
She even won a lottery that selected only thirty out of tens of thousands.
Nuan Nuan, your luck has been defying the heavens recently.
Hello, how can I help you?
Hello, are you Zhao Nuan Nuan?
We are staff from the "I Love Idol" website.
You retweeted our lottery information on Weibo a few days ago.
Congratulations, you've won!
I won?
- Two days and one night?
- Yes.
Performance?
Isn't this what they call "fail in the workplace and succeed in the lottery?"
Mi Mi, you little ABC. ("American-born Chinese") Stop misusing idioms.
Wow, this room is amazing!
So big, so spacious!
I think it could fit a few more people with no problem.
Aren't we enough for you?
Whom else would you bring?
Please don't.
Let's make a deal.
No one is allowed to make a phone call while here.
Nuan Nuan, come over here.
Come here. Have a seat.
Nuan Nuan, don't be upset anymore.
Didn't you always wish to win the lottery by retweeting?
Now you've won, you're still unhappy.
What? Were you always the "denominator" (never wins) so you're used to it?
No, I was thinking,
how could I make my female protagonist look more beautiful?
If she is as beautiful as you, that would be enough.
Right. I saw your winning info on my way here.
They say a performance is tonight.
Really?
I prepared a secret weapon today.
"Secret weapon"?
Mi Mi, did you bring a portable makeup case?
Of course.
You have to learn to love yourself so others will love you.
How about I try it on you two?
I've called 28 times. Zhao Nuan Nuan and Xin Ran still don't answer.
Are they staging a rebellion?
It's worse for me. I called 29 times.
What should we do? Call the hotel?
There's no need. I have another idea.
What is it?
Over there, hurry.
Mi Mi, you can't abandon us.
Of course not.
You two go first. I'll be right there.
Senior Nan! You finally answered my call.
Where are you, and what are you doing?
We're at the hot spring hotel and super happy.
Look, isn't my makeup beautiful today?
- Do you like my dress?
- You…
Why are you dressed up like that for a vacation?
Because of a super party soon.
"Super party"?
Nuan Nuan's prize includes a special theme party.
When I was abroad, I never went to a special party like this.
Also, many stylish ladies arrived downstairs.
It is so much fun!
Look.
What?
Even Zhao Nuan Nuan and Xin Ran also—
Yes, I just heard them say the party has performances and stand-up comedy.
I'm really, really anticipating it.
Senior Nan, if that's all, please stop calling me.
I'm a little busy today so please don't bother me. They're here!
Senior Nan, you should get back to work. Goodbye.
Fang—
You won't dare to ignore me again.
- I'll ask the director for a leave.
- I'll get the car.
- See you in the parking lot.
Ming Yang, you wait at the elevator doors.
I'll check their room number at the front desk.
Do we need to tell Mr. Gu?
Some problems can only be resolved by the people involved.
Others can't help.
You'll understand when you grow up.
But I'm already an adult.
I really look forward to tonight's performance.
Many comedians have come, and it must be very interesting.
I'm also excited for the concert tonight.
I heard there are several famous bands.
Nuan Nuan, what are you looking forward to?
Only children make choices.
As adults, we will take all!
Mi Mi!
[President Gu Yi Chen]
Hello, is anyone in the assistant's office?
Ask Qiao Nan to come over.
President Gu, Assistant Sheng left. He may not return until tomorrow.
Do you need anything?
No.
Super party?
Sweet and funny?
Really looking forward to it?
Oh, no.
- It seems tonight will be doomed.
- Oh my.
I really want to see the performance.
My super stand-up comedy.
Just forget it.
Had I known, I wouldn't have taken Senior Nan's call.
Men are such a hassle!
But if they won't let us join the themed party, I have other fun stuff.
Mi Mi, you're like a Doraemon (robot cat's gadgets).
Of course,
coming for a vacation and still being bossed is so annoying.
Without a party or stand-up comedy,
let's drink as much as desired.
This alcohol is very strong.
What's there to fear? We have bodyguards.
Here, the first drink is to celebrate our happy vacation.
Nuan Nuan, you really can drink without getting drunk.
Nuan Nuan, this drink can get you drunk easily.
Take it slow.
Okay.
Second round: here's to Nuan Nuan's recent lucky streak.
Hey, that's not how you drink.
You can drink for me.
You girls will easily get drunk like this.
I'll order some juice for you.
Senior Nan, you also drink for me.
Why aren't you girls drinking?
Are you also looking down on me?
We are best friends; how could we?
♫ When I'm unaware ♫
♫ He always quietly appears ♫
It's not that Zhao Nuan Nuan's romance mobile game is so outstanding.
But the industry association made a compromise.
Nuan Nuan was just lucky.
Scum! Always hassling me,
belittling me, despising me,
saying I was incompetent from the start,
never giving me a chance,
and mocking my…
dream.
♫ I'm loving you ♫
[Annoying Guy]
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
Gu Yi Chen!
You arrogant jerk,
selfish, willful, harsh, unreasonable,
who bullies me,
chides and tortures me, you big jerk!
You've always felt contempt for me,
didn't believe in me,
always trampled my dreams underfoot.
I hate you, and I never, never want to see you again!
You big bad guy.
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
Well said.
- Gu… Gu jerk…
- Nuan Nuan.
♫ Something simple and fulfilling ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
That's why I'm standing in front of you now; scold me all you want.
Is that fine?
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
You…
Nuan Nuan.
What are you guys doing? Come help!
[Season's Greetings!]
I can't keep them here anymore.
Get up.
We'll always be together from now on.
Ignore them.
Don't be nice to him.
I just need my best girlfriends.
I don't need Senior Nan.
Stop this, Yi Chen. Nuan Nuan is a good girl.
Have a good talk with her later. She will come around.
Let's go home.
We should each go to our own home.
All right.
Good morning and have a smooth journey, Big Sister Xin Ran.
- Bye bye.
Have a smooth journey. I'm going to my new apartment.
What are you guys doing? Why aren't you coming to help?
I can't hold them back anymore!
Hey, you can't be serious.
At least say something!
Forget it.
Taxi.
Taxi!
This is more comfortable.
Fang Mi!
Who are you to tell me what to do?
Only my boyfriend has the right to tell me what to do.
♫ Even a helpless smile can't hide it ♫
Are you my boyfriend?
Do you like me?
I…
You can only tell me what to do if you say you like me.
♫ The look of your silly smile ♫
Say it.
I'm listening.
♫ As I hesitate, I am afraid that I will ♫
♫ Miss (fail to get) you ♫
♫ My heartbeat slowly falls from the sky ♫
♫ Whose breath is getting weaker and weaker? ♫
♫ I don't want to say who is at fault ♫
♫ Who really understands me? ♫
So... you don't like me.
Then leave me alone.
If I want to wear something, I will.
I'll take it off.
Fang Mi!
Surprise. I wore two pieces.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Let me go!
Xin Ran, wait for me!
Wait a minute.
Why are you running so fast?
I'm going back to my room.
- Wait for me to take you back.
- I can go back by myself.
So you're the type who hiccups when you overdrink.
Who says I hiccup?
You're too cute.
Get off!
Wait for me, Wu Xin Ran!
Be careful. It's slippery.
Xin Ran!
I told you to be careful.
Where did you get injured? Does it hurt?
It hurts.
Doesn't hurt.
♫ A pair of big, warm hands ♫
♫ Holding up the entire universe ♫
♫ Shoulders bearing heavy mountains ♫
Where are you hurt? Did you hit any bones?
Does it hurt here?
♫ Wrinkles at the corners of the eyes ♫
♫ Now it's my turn ♫
♫ To shield you from wind and rain ♫
♫ The evening breeze blows gently♫
♫ To whom can I give the pain of my longing?♫
♫ Tears gradually fill my eyes♫
♫ Memories rush into my heart♫
♫ Please walk slowly♫
♫ I seize every minute♫
♫ Want to repay you quickly♫
♫ To hold you in my arms ♫
♫ Love you ♫
President, the lady has been hanging on the wall for three years.
Has she admitted her mistake?
♫ My heart flutters like a startled deer ♫
♫ My face blushes ♫
On the third day, the lady flattened the wall in an excavator.
♫ I almost stop breathing ♫
Little Brother.
Will you carry me on your back?
♫ My heart speeds up, and I dare not look at ♫
Little Brother, why don't you say anything?
Little Brother, do you hate me?
Do you look down on me?
♫ I'm lost inside them. Oh, oh, oh ♫
Or do you also despise me?
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
Nuan Nuan.
♫ You're the koi ♫
♫ Who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
Where do you want to go? I'll take you.
Let's go to the mountaintop.
Let's go see the stars and moon.
Can we choose somewhere a little closer?
Then let's go to the seaside.
We can go fishing.
♫ When I'm unaware ♫
Not here, over there.
Okay.
President, the lady has been hanging on the wall for three years.
Really?
You say the next sentence. Say it.
So has she admitted her mistake?
Scum, you're dead!
Gu Yi Chen, Scum.
Jerk, you big bad guy!
You always bully me, belittle me,
and despise my dreams.
I've always, always worked hard for this dream.
I studied hard in university.
During graduation season, I stayed in for four months for this project.
I…
I just wanted to complete my project well.
I want to finish my mobile game.
But why did you have to treat me like this?
I don't want this kind of good luck.
I would rather be unlucky for a lifetime.
I don't want to hear you say
that I got first place
only due to good luck.
Gu Yi Chen, you're awful!
Jerk, you terrible guy!
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
I'm sorry.
I regret it, Nuan Nuan.
I didn't expect what I said unintentionally that day would hurt you this much.
I've never felt contempt for you nor despised your dreams.
I know how much you love art
and how much you love mobile games.
Even with our misunderstandings,
you've never left Z Mobile Games.
I was wrong to say those things that day.
When you put your heart and soul into the project, it should be respected.
Zhao Nuan Nuan, you're really awesome.
I apologize.
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
Gu Yi Chen.
I want to
shake hands with you.
touch your face.
I also want to...
share with you...
my good luck.
And...
I want to… do this... with you...
Hello, Doctor.
Yi Chen, I've carefully analyzed the disease case history in your email.
Between you and her, if we exclude smell, body temperature, life habits,
physical characteristics, and other common allergic reasons,
your non-allergic reaction to her may have only one possibility.
What is that?
Feelings.
Gu Yi Chen, do you… like her?
"Loving You" by Tan Han
♫ When I'm unaware ♫
♫ He always quietly appears ♫
♫ Why is it always he who stirs my heart? ♫
♫ He's obviously a bit obnoxious ♫
♫ Why do I feel like my heart skips a beat? ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ It feels like we've been friends ♫
♫ But I really want to know if I'm in your heart ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ A bit tired and flustered, feeling annoyed ♫
♫ Love always makes me feel dejected ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to see the sunrise with you ♫
♫ Something simple and fulfilling ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫