♫ My heart flutters like a startled deer ♫
♫ My face blushes ♫
♫ My flushed cheeks feel hot ♫
♫ I almost stop breathing ♫
♫ As you approach step by step ♫
♫ My heart speeds up, and I dare not look at ♫
♫ Your eyes ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them. Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
♫ The whole world keeps sparkling ♫
♫ My heart races as if under a spell ♫
♫ The whole galaxy is reflected in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm lost inside them ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh ♫
♫ You fill my mind ♫
♫ Hug me close in your embrace ♫
♫ You're the koi who brings me good luck ♫
♫ And courage ♫
[Warm Meets You, Directed by Chu Dejian]
[Episode 21]
Hello.
Do you want to meet me?
No.
Not for personal matters, for your Z Mobile Games.
What else do you want?
I want to be your guiding light.
Sign a cooperation agreement with me.
I can have UA give you the best treatment.
I can promise you all the conditions you want,
as long as you and your Z Mobile Games
join me.
Yi Chen, stop being so stubborn.
Z Mobile Games has developed very well under your authority,
but without strong backing,
and the experience of veteran mobile game manufacturers, you can't continue on.
If your so-called experience is to do everything possible to ruin competitors,
and take away all their projects and resources,
then sorry, I'm not interested in such a shameless experience!
Gu Yi Chen.
Although your cooperation agreement has long expired,
I tell you that I cooperate with only those who respect the project and the industry.
Yi Chen, think it over.
Now, only UA and I can save your company.
Yi Chen! Ming Yang, what did you do?
Let go of me. Today I want to teach President Gu a lesson.
He bullied my sister, Zhao Nuan Nuan.
Do you remember what I told you?
I will never let this go.
Ming Yang, use your words.
My sister was sent away by him. What can I say to such a person?
Your sister left? Where did she go?
Are you asking me? I want to ask you!
Are you happy now? Are you satisfied?
I tell you. Never let me see you again!
Ming Yang, Ming Yang!
[Meeting you]
[has exhausted all the luck in my life.]
I once thought this would be where my dreams become reality.
I once thought that I was lucky to meet you.
But dreams can only be achieved through hard work.
And finding my other half
will not last if it's based on luck alone.
Yi Chen,
meeting you
really has drained all the luck in my life.
I'm leaving.
♫ Memories always inadvertently turn yellow ♫
♫ Good things always quietly fade away ♫
♫ I always feel sad for no reason ♫
♫ Even a helpless smile can't hide it ♫
♫ I try hard to pretend, afraid the tears will fill ♫
♫ My eyes ♫
♫ The road to your heart is so long ♫
Yi Chen,
meeting you is the luckiest moment in my life.
meeting you has exhausted
all the luck in my life.
♫ Miss (fail to get) you ♫
♫ My heartbeat slowly falls from the sky ♫
♫ Whose breath is getting weaker and weaker? ♫
♫ I don't want to say who is at fault ♫
♫ Who really understands me? ♫
♫ Please forgive my persistence ♫
♫ The almost-forgotten promise ♫
[Good Luck]
♫ Is anything still worthy for me to watch over? ♫
[Find your other half and good luck.]
♫ My heartbeat slowly falls from the sky♫
♫ Whose breath is getting weaker and weaker? ♫
♫ I don't want to say who is at fault ♫
♫ Who really understands me? ♫
♫ Please forgive my persistence ♫
♫ The almost-forgotten promise ♫
♫ Is anything still worthy for me to watch over? ♫
Dear, this one.
Let me tell you. His family is so rich that two generations can enjoy the wealth.
What's so great about having money?
Our Nuan Nuan doesn't lack money.
Then this one, born to a family of doctors and has a doctorate degree.
Right, a family of doctors and nurses.
Future medical treatments and injections can be guaranteed.
Right.
My daughter isn't marrying to get medical treatment!
Dear, what do you think of that young man outside?
I don't think much of him.
He's so handsome, and you're still picky.
Our Nuan Nuan doesn't just value looks.
I'll tell you something.
When choosing a son-in-law, you must value his character.
He has to be good to my daughter, truly love my daughter,
and not hide anything from her.
He must be sincere to my daughter.
In short, if he sincerely loves my daughter,
I can be a satisfied mother-in-law.
If he openly or secretly bullies my daughter,
I will teach him a lesson as Mother-in-law.
What does he do?
He runs a seafood business at home.
Here's your water. Are you from out of town?
Uncle.
If you don't mind, would you join me for a drink later?
But I drove here.
What does it matter? If you get drunk, stay here.
Wait, I'll get the wine.
I prepared in a rush.
I haven't made any good dishes to serve you.
It's already very good.
No problem, there's more.
Children's mother (Dear).
I'm coming, coming.
What are you shouting for?
It's so cold, yet you're making him drink. So silly.
Drink if you want. Why do I have to serve you?
Here's your squirrel-shaped mandarin fish and salted duck.
My wife is the best. My wife is the best.
You dare to drink.
You're even drinking cold wine on a cold day.
Wait, I'll warm it for you.
- Thank you, Auntie.
- Okay, okay.
Don't mind what she said.
She's always like this. Her words are harsh, but her heart is soft.
She doesn't display affection,
but just keeps it in her heart for a lifetime.
Auntie is so nice.
Is that so?
Actually, let me tell you; all parents are the same.
At first, they hope their children will be successful.
Later on, they hope their children can have a better life.
In the end, they all hope their children can be happy.
Sometimes, when they blame you or don't understand you,
their love for you makes them emotional.
They're afraid that you'll make the same mistakes
that they did before.
So from the moment you were born,
they've been carefully protecting you.
When you grow up,
they hope you can have a better life than they did.
In this world, parents love their child.
No parents want to become enemies with their child.
When they hit or scold you,
the ones who hurt most are the parents.
I have two children about your age.
I won't discuss my son. That rascal does whatever he wants.
He would dare to do anything.
But my daughter…
Do you want to hear about my daughter?
I want to hear.
My daughter has been a very lovely child since childhood.
She was chubby, fair and charming.
But she always had bad luck.
However, no matter what misfortunes occur,
she is always optimistic and kind.
Actually, I never thought my daughter was unlucky.
Even though some setbacks and difficulties are in her life,
I believe she can use her wisdom, kindness, and innocence
to resolve these issues one by one.
In fact, no one in this world has everything go well.
Likewise, no one is always at the bottom of the heap.
What distinguishes people is how you respond to issues.
Some people pull themselves together
to have a better life.
But some people crumble.
For such people, none of us can help them, right?
So
I hope you can be like her. Pull yourself together and start over.
Here.
Here, eat.
Don't just chat.
Stay here tonight.
How does it taste?
[Honorary Credential]
[National (VHS)]
There are so many comic books.
She really didn't lie to me.
Why does it feel like I've seen her somewhere?
[Zhao Nuan Nuan, aged 9, commemoration of hospital discharge]
Nuan Nuan.
Why are you over here again?
Did you take your medicine and get your injection?
You're about to get your tonsillectomy in a few days. You can't catch a cold. Come on.
[Observation Room]
[Zhao Nuan Nuan, aged 9, commemoration of hospital discharge]
Back then,
could it really be her?
It's 38.5° Celsius (37 normal).
Mi Mi, we have to go to the hospital. Let's go.
No need, Big Sister Xin Ran.
I'll be fine after I take medicine and sleep.
You can't just take medicine for such a severe fever.
Mi Mi, listen to me,
or I'll call Senior Nan.
No.
Don't call him.
He won't want to see me.
After your fight,
you haven't talked to him or called him?
This won't do. You should talk to each other.
I know what he's thinking.
He must think that I did it on purpose,
and he must blame me.
He thought that I deliberately took him to the porridge shop to see his mother.
But I really didn't know about it.
I also didn't know he had so much pain in his past.
In fact, I don't blame him.
It's all my fault.
I've never tried to understand him.
I've never known what he truly wants.
All I knew was to pursue him desperately, forcing him to accept me.
If I had known our relationship was doomed to end,
then it would have been better not to start.
Mi Mi.
My mother called me.
I might…
I might have to return to USA soon.
So soon?
Just like Senior Nan said,
we will pretend we've never met.
But I really like him!
I really, really like Senior Nan.
I don't want to leave.
Don't cry.
I don't want to leave him.
I don't want to break up, and I don't want to leave.
I don't want…
Mom!
You're back.
How was your day?
It was okay.
Let me carry it.
Guess what dishes I made for you today.
- What dishes?
- Go look.
Okay.
[Office of the President]
Qiao Nan, I've decided I want to shut down
Z Mobile Games.
This is our start-up company.
Even if it faces the greatest difficulties,
I don't want to just hand it over to competitors.
So I would rather stop all the projects that we have developed over the years,
accept industry supervision and administrative review,
rather than give them
to UA for free.
I understand.
I will be away for a while.
I will leave the remaining things to you.
Don't worry.
We developed Z Mobile Games from scratch.
From now on, I will continue to protect it well.
Zhao Nuan Nuan!
Boss, I wasn't slacking off; I wasn't nodding off.
The shop was open for three hours, yet you didn't give out one flyer.
And you said you're not slacking off.
I gave the flyers out.
I gave out
three flyers.
Three flyers in three hours.
And you still say you're not slacking off?
Do you still want to get paid?
Do you want me to deduct it all?
No, no.
[Holy Taste]
Boss, I need this job to pay food and rent.
My dear boss,
my lovely boss, and the world's most beautiful boss, you are generous.
I'll get to work at once,
and distribute all the store's flyers
to double the store's customer traffic. How about that?
"Double"? Can you do it?
I'm sure I can do it.
I'll go right now.
[Holy Taste]
Boss. I-I'll help you.
Zhao Nuan Nuan!
You're a super unlucky person!
It can't be.
So unlucky.
I'm so unlucky.
I'm unlucky when I work and when I draw.
I want to start over.
But I'm still unlucky.
Who said I'm not unlucky anymore?
Clearly, I'm still unlucky.
I am so unlucky.
Heaven,
who has good luck?
Lend it to me.
Who would be willing to share their good luck with others?
Who would be willing to meet someone like me?
I am daydreaming again.
Didn't I think it through long ago?
My life doesn't need any good luck.
I just need to rely on myself, my two hands, and my effort.
Zhao Nuan Nuan.
Didn't you say you would start over?
Didn't you say you will focus on drawing?
You can do it.
You can definitely do it!
What time is it already?
Zhao Nuan Nuan still isn't back.
After leaving home once, she's become fearless.
When she gets back…
Oh, no. I forgot my key.
I wonder if Big Sister Xin Ran and Ming Yang are home.
What do I do if they're not?
Nuan Nuan.
I want to turn you into a tiny pocket cat
and carry you in my pocket daily.
So anytime, anywhere,
I can see you whenever I want to.
Meow.
Yi Chen, I like you
very, very, very much.
Nuan Nuan.
No way.
Dior's
999 lipstick.
Is Nuan Nuan still not back? Give her a call.
S-Still not back.
What kind of posture is this?
Nothing.
What are you holding?
I'm holding nothing. There's nothing.
All right, go to bed early.
My face masks!
What on Earth is this?
What's that under your foot? And what are you hiding in your hand?
Hurry up. Take it out!
My 999 lipstick (most iconic).
Xin Ran, don't get upset. Isn't it just a lipstick?
I will buy lots of them for you.
I'll get you another 999 of them, okay?
This is a limited edition. You can't buy it even with money.
Who needs you to buy 999 of them? Get out of here!
Get out!
Go away!
Xin Ran, Xin Ran, open the door.
I really didn't do it on purpose. It really wasn't!
Let me explain!
Go far away!
Xin Ran, Xin Ran.
Nuan Nuan, wait a moment.
Can you stop following me?
- Nuan Nuan, let me explain.
- I don't want to listen.
Nuan Nuan.
- Nuan Nuan!
- Xin Ran!
Open the door. I really didn't do it on purpose. Let me explain.
I don't want to hear your explanation.
Get lost. Don't come back.
Nuan Nuan, give me a chance. I can explain clearly.
I can explain about Luo Yi. I–
I don't want to listen. Go away. Don't bother me.
- Xin Ran!
- Nuan Nuan!
- Nuan Nuan.
- Xin Ran.
Go away!
What happened?
Was there a thief?
How could a thief cook breakfast for us?
This is clearly…
Tastes good, right?
My queens.
I'm willing to serve you.
Nuan Nuan.
Wait a moment, Nuan Nuan.
Gu Yi Chen, are you crazy or am I?
Zhao Ming Yang is so unreliable.
You actually followed him and made a fuss.
You want to stay at my house and live with Ming Yang?
Gu Yi Chen, are you all right?
Yes.
I want to stay by your side.
I want to be with you.
I am sorry for what happened before.
I was wrong to hurt you.
Thus, I want to return to your side.
I want to be with you.
- We've already broken up.
- Then let's start over.
Gu Yi Chen, you're crazy.
You can think I'm crazy.
Zhao Nuan Nuan.
I want to be with you.
No matter how you push me away, I want to be with you.
No matter what, I want to be by your side.
It's impossible.
Impossible.
We can't return to the past.
Nuan Nuan.
"Loving You" by Tan Han
♫ When I'm unaware ♫
♫ He always quietly appears ♫
♫ Why is it always he who stirs my heart? ♫
♫ He's obviously a bit obnoxious ♫
♫ Why do I feel like my heart skips a beat? ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ It feels like we've been friends ♫
♫ But I really want to know if I'm in your heart ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to get closer to you ♫
♫ Love should be cherished ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫
♫ A bit tired and flustered, feeling annoyed ♫
♫ Love always makes me feel dejected ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ I really do ♫
♫ I want to see the sunrise with you ♫
♫ Something simple and fulfilling ♫
♫ I'm loving you ♫
♫ If you want me, too ♫
♫ Don't just stand there in silence ♫