Why do you want to become the emperor?
If it is to protect you,
will you believe it?
Yes, I do.
Your Majesty.
It's time to go to court.
Come with me.
You're the Right Minister.
You are supposed to discuss state affairs.
Do you want me to ride into the palace
In this case, I will avoid being known
that I went out of the palace in the middle of the night.
This is vixen.
The sinister.
Shouldn't you be
shouldn't you have just come out
In the bed with him?
Why is it raining today?
It's so boring
from Your Highness
I heard that your brother has been
you have been punished to kneel by your brother for two consecutive times.
What do you mean?
I bet that
after the imperial court meeting today,
you have to kneel
In the Imperial Study.
Commander Xue.
What's the situation today?
Why can an evil minister enter the palace on a carriage?
Because His Majesty is in the carriage.
High Priest.
These days,
always appear in my mind.
When I was little,
I didn't teach him to practice sword either.
He was the one who taught me.
Brother Xiaoqi.
You finally come to see Yi'er.
My son.
From today on,
you'll join the Dark Pavilion.
On your own.
I hope in two years,
I can see a brand new South Yi
yi'er.
Congratulations on your becoming married.
This is the first task I've given you.
Go undercover in Qin's State Uncle's Mansion
to search for evidence of his crime.
I have arranged it properly.
From now on,
you are Miss Qin Yi who has been wandering around
who was just found.
Yes
but Brother Xiaoqi,
I've inherited the throne,
from now on,
call me Your Majesty.
For some reason,
since the first time I saw Cang Hanyu
I have had
this kind of
and kind.
Even the entire court
are in awe of him,
everyone remained silent in front of him.
But I always
this feeling
do you know about previous lives?
Two stars are gathering.
The wheel of fate has begun to turn.
Don't be anxious.
To find a solution
to your doubts.