Your Majesty.
This year,
there were frequent floods in Jiangnan this year,
causing crop failures.
Your Majesty, please open a warehouse for disaster relief
to relieve the people's plight.
My son is the best.
Your Majesty.
You
brother Emperor,
I made this soup myself.
Try it.
Is it good?
Your Majesty.
I poisoned this soup with hibernate medicine.
Is it yours
or not?
As long as it's made by you,
that you made.
Brother Emperor,
what did you say
what poison?
It's you.
Your Majesty.
You'd better take a rest.
She won't come.
No, she won't.
I need to wait for Yi'er.
Someone tried to assassinate His Majesty.
The Emperor was assassinated?
Come. His Majesty is assassinated.
My Lord.
How come you're free now?
You were the fourth lady of the Qin family.
And went shopping with me.
Right?
That's right.
And he used you.
Then
when I was fighting with the man in black,
I hit the stone
that flew over your head.
So you brought me
because my martial arts skills are weak.
So that you can be taken away naturally.
Yes
were you injured when you left
after leaving with the man in black?
Look at me now.
I'm fine now.
That's good.
Don't you hate me?
I know I have a poor foundation.
Even if I train every day,
I still can't compare to Su Yi.
I just want to know
beside my master,
that I'm still useful,
I'm already very happy.
As for resentment,
I hate that I'm not strong enough.
Otherwise,
you don't have to risk yourself.
If you're not strong enough,
I will train more every day
two hours
for extra training.
Alright.
Master.
My lord.
His Majesty has an accident.
Trash!
A group of rubbish!
If something bad happens to His Majesty,
If His Majesty dies.
Die with us.
Kill them all.
His Majesty is not dead yet.
And Her Majesty couldn't wait for him to be buried alive.
What
what his intention is.
What do you mean?
Guards!
Get everyone out of here
get everyone out of here!
Nan Yi, how dare you!
Before me, can you
It's your turn to speak!
Your Majesty.
Do I have any credibility?
The words of Prime Minister Nan
Is me.
Your Majesty.
Not for the second time.
What are you doing as an Imperial Guard?
I'm the Empress Dowager,
but also harm His Majesty.
But this villain
If he tries to harm the emperor,
who will bear the consequences?
If I really wanted to harm His Majesty,
Isn't that just what you want?
From the South?
Who gave you the courage to talk to me like that?
Who on earth will be in power
who's going to be in charge
anyway,
you won't have the right to
leave all this to me,
If he is involved today,
I want you all to die with him.
How dare you?
If you don't believe it,
you can have a try.
I don't know.
Guard the palace gate well.
No one can come in
without my permission.
Bring me the wound ointment.
Deputy South.
If she draws the dagger,
his Majesty will
that's why
just plug it in.
Or
you want to see the posthumous edict announced now?
Yi'er,
shut up!
I'll pull out a dagger for you.
And everything will be fine.
This is unacceptable.
His Majesty is in mortal danger.
How dare you stop me?
You just let Prime Minister Nan do what you want?
How dare you!
Guard!
The Princess Royal is here.