♪In the pursuit of a dream♪
♪Starting late matters not♪
♪No one is flawless♪
♪Take off against the wind♪
♪Loud cheers wait at the finish line♪
♪But sweat is the cost♪
♪Raise head toward the starlight♪
♪Look up together♪
♪My sky♪
♪Is so different♪
♪In my dream♪
♪There is always your smile♪
♪The freezing wind♪
♪Is warmed by the sun♪
♪Ordinary but glorious♪
♪Be your hero♪
♪In my sky♪
♪There is a hidden rainbow♪
♪Protect the star of dream♪
♪One day we will arrive♪
♪Guard the dream in the heart♪
♪Give you a firm answer♪
♪I will fly beyond the limit♪
♪Run for the lightning♪
♪Fight fight fight♪
♪The other side of the sky♪
=Here We Meet Again=
=Episode 12=
Do you know
you nearly fainted?
You just got out of the hospital.
Don't you know
your own health condition?
Why did you stand out
for everything?
Take the coffee.
Sorry.
I got mad.
I forgive you.
Can you get out of my way?
How to deal with
the thing about Li Chi?
Tell everyone the truth.
That the maintenance man is the one
who did that.
Li Chi shouldn't be the scapegoat.
(Meeting Room)
Everyone, attention please.
The one who installed the camera
has been found.
It's a maintenance man from outside.
It has nothing to do with Li Chi.
Rest assured.
We'll send an e-mail
inside the company.
Stop your acting.
You guys pretended to
clear my name.
Actually, you want me to leave here now.
Listen.
I've had enough
in this place!
Li Chi.
Sorry.
I suspected you
of installing the camera.
I apologize.
I wronged you.
I'm so sorry.
You come out
just to tell me this?
And
please delete
Chen Shu's photo.
Why?
Because she's my girlfriend.
I won't delete them.
So?
Besides,
do you think Chen Shu
really likes you?
What are people like you?
Oh.
Right.
Gigolos.
You haven't married her
yet.
Even if you get married,
it won't last long.
I'll kill you!
Stop fighting!
Go and stop them.
I'll kill you!
Gao Leng. Stop!
Stop fighting!
Li Chi.
The fight has been shot.
Say it again!
Stop fighting!
Come with me.
Why did you call him away?
Did he flirt with you in private?
Could I get you away?
Didn't you say you could handle it?
Didn't you say you wouldn't be naive?
That's because he just said...
Forget it.
What do you mean?
We should break up.
Argue and then break up?
Is it so easy to say that out?
Why?
I got punished.
Why... Why could Li Chi
get out?
Look at you.
Why did you offend him?
He is Mr. Yang's people.
Yinyin.
Don't be so willful
and childish.
To be frank,
everyone knows
you are stupid and...
So, they don't mind it.
If someone intended
to harm you,
you could have been killed.
Honestly,
I don't know
his relationship
with Yang Pingshan either.
Yang Pingshan stepped in for him
this time.
It means no one here
can touch him.
No one can touch him…
No one can touch him.
Then I...
Uncle.
Do you mean
I'm not the one who has
the greatest background in Velin?
Am I no longer
the number one in the company?
I...
He hangs up on me so fast.
I'm nothing now.
No. No.
I'm done.
How is it possible?
I'm not the number one in the company.
Even the coffee is so bitter.
Are you looking for me?
Hey.
Here comes the Boxing Champion.
Yuan.
Do you tease me
too?
Mocha.
Thanks.
Did you bicker with her?
I'm so confused
about you girls.
What's this?
Look at it.
You are involved in it.
People naturally blacklisted you from it.
Don't you feel that
we no longer check Moments
in the office?
This thing gets so big.
Even the headquarters have known it.
How would she think about it?
Chen...
Has Chen Shu known it?
Of course she has known it.
She's been in Velin for years.
Nothing can escape her ears.
I... I was too furious.
It's said that
you were a Straight-A student too.
The study was hard, right?
Certainly.
All students have a hard time
during their school year.
But after working for so many years,
I finally understand
that study may be
a relatively fair way
for common people like us
to be successful.
But I would not go back
to that time
and study again.
I still remember my study life
In senior high school.
It was a nightmare.
Actually, everyone has a prism
in front of them.
From the prism, people can see
all sides of themselves.
As adults,
we should keep every side
clean, decent and glamorous.
But only you know
what you've experienced behind.
Take Chen Shu as an example.
She studied so hard that she could
get an opportunity to be educated
in Shanghai.
She worked so hard in the company,
in order to be transferred
to the headquarters
and stay in Shanghai.
But your punch
to Li Chi
broke her prism
into pieces.
From these pieces,
they negated
all her hard work,
and put them into the way
they could make fun of.
How would she think about it?
I just...
In society,
women are easier
to be reproached
and criticized
than men.
When you work hard,
they say you neglect the family.
When you are family-oriented,
they say you rely on men.
If you had considered more for her
in her position,
you wouldn't
have been so impulsive.
Don't break
anyone's prism at will.
Moreover,
Chen Shu values her dignity.
Think about it.
(Chen Shu)
(Honey,)
(I'm so sorry.)
(I got impulsive again.)
Good morning.
You are in good spirits.
I thought
you'd be in pain
for some time.
Then you'd realize
you don't match Chen Shu.
What did you say?
What?
Are you angry?
I am right.
Chen Shu dumped you.
I think
you should stop struggling.
Since she said to break up,
she wouldn't turn back.
People like her
are decisive
when leaving.
What did...
Hello, Shu.
What are you doing?
Li Chi, you come so early.
I thought
I was late.
Let me go.
Morning, Miss Xiang.
Morning.
Hello.
Could you tell me
when you can offer
the drawing of
the Cargo Link Navigation System?
There are only a few days left.
How is it going?
The time is tight
for the factories and us.
Please be sure to give us
before the deadline.
Alright?
OK. No problem.
Rest assured.
OK. OK. Thanks.
Thanks. Goodbye.
Come in.
What's the matter?
I bought too many cups of milky tea.
Try it.
Too sweet.
I only drink oolong tea.
Why do you come to me?
Only for milky tea?
I... I want to ask
when the drawing
of the Cargo Link Navigation System
will be finished.
Most of it is done.
But the function of
safety driving assist
needs to be improved.
What?
Are they urging?
Three days.
Tell them it'll be done in three days.
OK.
Go out with me tomorrow.
What?
Test the system of the vehicle terminal.
OK.
It tastes so bad.
(Velin)
Is the development
of Cargo Link Navigation System
almost finished?
Yes.
Our company pays great attention
to the car navigation market.
Now most of the power
is in my hands.
If it's successful this time,
Velin will divert
to cargo truck navigation market.
All the clients we have now
will desert us.
Xiang Yuan
is unpredictable.
She shouldn't get high above me.
I have an idea.
Say it.
I'll leave it to you.
♪Small points on the map♪
♪Unconsciously♪
♪We are connected into a line♪
♪Billions of light years away
in the universe♪
♪How many stars are waiting♪
♪Sometimes the system crashes♪
♪Finally setting off
I'm back to square one♪
♪What if I lose my passion♪
♪I can always start all over again♪
♪'Cause everything is OK♪
♪Never be afraid♪
♪And every day I pray♪
♪This is not a dream♪
♪Make it a better day♪
♪My world never rains♪
♪Everything is OK♪
♪Small points on the map♪
♪Unconsciously♪
♪We are connected into a line♪
♪Billions of light years away
in the universe♪
♪How many stars are waiting♪
♪Sometimes the system crashes♪
♪Finally setting off
I'm back to square one♪
♪What if I lose my passion♪
♪I can always start all over again♪
♪'Cause everything is OK♪
♪Never be afraid♪
♪And every day I pray♪
♪This is not a dream♪
♪Make it a better day♪
♪My world never rains♪
♪Everything is OK♪
(Anji Manju Shanqu B&B)
Have you booked rooms?
I don't think we need to.
What if there's only
one room?
The chances are slim.
Sorry.
I didn't have time to rebook for you.
(33 rooms available, 22 double rooms,
11 twin rooms)
Sir.
This is so cute.
That's the new version.
Hang it up after brushing your teeth.
It takes up little space
and is hygienic.
What's the use
of this kitty box?
It's an ultraviolet sterilization box.
It's like this.
Let me show you.
Come.
Open this cover.
Put the brush in.
It can be sterilized automatically.
I'll take one.
OK.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Sir.
Would you want this one?
They are designed
for couples.
OK.
Here.
Working like this, you will die.
I am alive and well. Right?
You were not like this in school.
Back then you could rank the first
easily.
When did you become so hard-working?
After you started to work?
The mission is
kind of different now.
What is it?
Because of you.
And Gao Leng.
Shi Tianyou and You Zhi.
You asked me
when I became like this.
I thought about it.
Maybe when I became the team leader.
Responsibility?
Not so sentimental.
I just think
it's fine if I starve alone.
But I don't want others
to starve with me.
What are you doing?
I can do it alone.
Don't forget. I am a team leader too.
We only have one day left.
Can we do it?
Yes, we can.
(Velin)
♪In the pursuit of a dream♪
♪Starting late matters not♪
♪No one is flawless♪
♪Take off against the wind♪
♪Loud cheers wait at the finish line♪
♪But sweat is the cost♪
Come. Have some food.
Come.
What is it?
I'll take this.
Thanks, Miss Xiang.
You're welcome.
♪My sky
is so different♪
These are left by them.
♪There is always your smile♪
♪The freezing wind
is warmed by the sun♪
♪Ordinary but glorious,
be your hero♪
♪In my sky,
there is a hidden rainbow♪
(South Zone,
Xi'an High-tech Industrial Park)
Li Chi.
Organize it the last time.
OK.
(Team Leader of Technical Group I)
Mr. Wang.
I'll send you the template in two days.
OK?
Please take a look.
I'm sure
you can try it.
Yes.
I promise
it's very convenient.
OK. OK. OK.
OK. Mr. Zhao.
Miss Xiang.
Please take a look first.
Please sign it.
Yes.
(Letter of Production Confirmation)
I'll send you right away.
Please wait a second.
OK.
Mr. Chen.
It can connect
human, goods and vehicles
together.
Scan a code before loading goods
to the vehicle.
Then the location of the goods
will be the location of the vehicle.
Miss. Xiang. Hurry up.
The factory is urging.
It's very convenient as a whole.
OK. OK. OK.
Please don't hang up.
Mr. Wang.
Miss Xiang.
I can send you
the contract now.
Right now...
(Person in charge: Xiang Yuan)
No problem.
OK.
Thanks.
Then please wait a moment.
(File scanning)
(Li Chi.
Xi'an Shunfa Electronics Factory)
(Letter of Production Confirmation)
(Person in charge: Xiang Yuan)
(Just in time.)
Xu Yanshi didn't find it out, did he?
Of course not.
I didn't send a copy to him.
He can't see the final version.
The production will begin
once the factory gets the drawing.
Xiang Yuan will be doomed
on this matter.
(Distance: 11 km, 20 min.)
So slow.
Didn't you drive today?
It's not safe after working all night.
I'll go home by taxi.
It's been hard for you these days.
The drawing
has been sent to the factory.
Everyone worked so hard these days.
How about resting tomorrow?
The drawing has been sent
to the factories?
But I didn't get the e-mail.
The e-mails that
the technical department sent
should all be copied to me.
Cancel the taxi you called.
Let's go back to check the file again.
(Scanning copy of Letter of Production
Confirmation Task Flow and Design)
It's wrong.
The drawing in the e-mail is wrong.
The version isn't right.
When was this sent?
About 3 PM.
It's not too late yet.
Contact the factory immediately.
I'll send the right drawing
to it.
Mr. Li.
I'm sorry.
We sent you
a wrong e-mail this afternoon.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to bother you with this.
(Letter of Production Confirmation)
(Send)
Luckily, we found it out early.
Didn't you
confirm it at last?
(Letter of Production Confirmation)
(Produce 1,000 devices
based on version 1.3 we provided)
Do you know it?
The design drawing given to
the factory yesterday
had a problem.
Luckily, Boss found it out in time.
The factory said
even one day would be too late.
Yeah. That was close.
Yeah.
But what was
the problem on earth?
We had checked it.
Yeah.
Explain it.
Explain what?
The final version we confirmed
was version 1.8.
Why did you send version 1.3?
I sent it according to the link
in the letter.
It was right.
OK.
You don't admit it.
All the files of
the technical department
should be copied to Xu Yanshi.
Why didn't he get it?
Oh.
I might've forgotten it.
Miss Xiang.
Something was wrong with the file.
It might be
my mistake.
But don't forget
you checked the file
and signed
before submitting it.
You don't know specialized knowledge
and don't understand the file,
so you didn't find the problem
in time.
In a word,
you rely on Xu Yanshi, don't you?
Miss Xiang.
Forget it.
If you keep investigating,
both of us will be punished.
Miss Xiang.
I can send you
the contract now.
Right now...
(Person in charge: Xiang Yuan)
(Version 1.8)
(Version 1.3)
(Start scanning)
(To Shunfa Electronics Factory
CC: Xiang Yuan. Xu Yanshi)
(To: Shunfa Electronics Factory
CC: Xiang Yuan)
(Send)
(Letter of Production Confirmation)
Are you looking for me?
Xiang Yuan doesn't understand it.
But you are a technician.
Don't you know the difference
between version 1.3 and version 1.8?
You get an excuse
for your girlfriend so fast.
Xiang Yuan signed it
in black and white.
Do you blame me?
What will you do to me?
Listen.
If there is any problem,
Xiang Yuan will be punished too.
You can try.
I'm so full.
(Version 1.3)
What are you gonna do?
I want Li Chi to leave our team.
Because of the drawing?
Look at the confirmation letter.
The number three
was obviously scrapped.
I suspect it was done by Li Chi.
But there is no evidence.
(Version 1.3)
I checked Li Chi's
work record.
He had not completed his work,
and his progress was slower than others.
And he didn't coordinate
with other teammates at all.
He isn't suitable
in the team.
It should be reported
to the headquarters.
Li Chi also has an unusual relationship
with Li Qin.
It's not easy
to transfer him away.
Li Qin?
Gao Leng told me
that you defended Li Chi
for what he did.
Even if I didn't do it,
Li Qin would defend him.
Li Qin owes me a favor
now.
(Has Xu Yanshi)
(become so diplomatic?)
What about this time?
I just want to remind you.
Don't tell others
about getting Li Chi away.
I'll handle it.
I'm not doing this
for myself,
or doing it emotionally.
I'm responsible
for all my teammates.
I hope they...
You'll understand after a long time.
Sometimes,
if you can't do anything,
then play along.
So, as for responsibility,
you were just saying.
(Hello. Welcome.)
(You covered up Li Chi.)
Ma'am. I...
Ma'am.
All the meat burgers, please.
Thanks.
OK.
Why do you like
eating these things?
Yuan.
Why did you buy the food
Boss likes?
Good morning, Mr. Li.
(General Manager)
Good morning.
Cao.
Mr. Li.
Remember to do what I told you
yesterday.
Mr. Li.
Got it?
OK. OK.
Well, Mr. Li.
I'm going to work.
OK. Go.
OK.
Remember it.
Miss Xiang.
Are you waiting for me so early?
As the leader, you are very busy.
I'm afraid you have no time to meet me.
You must have something to say.
Tell me.
I want to get Li Chi away
from our department.
Did Xu Yanshi ask you to come to me?
The logistics department is too idle,
not suitable for young men
like Li Chi.
You should understand it.
Did Xu Yanshi go to you?
He was earlier than you,
at the door of my house.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
Xu Yanshi.
What are you doing here?
I'm packing up for Boss.
He is leaving.
Will Li Qin fire Xu Yanshi
because of Li Chi?
What are you
talking about?
Come with me.
No matter he is Li Chi,
or Ms. Li's man,
I will kill him.
Calm... Calm down.
I'm preparing files
for Boss's business trip.
Business trip?
Yeah.
One week in Shanghai.
Sorry.
What's going on?
It's my decision to force you to leave.
Stay away from Xiang Yuan.
Boss.
Do you keep the best food
to the last
when you are eating?
Like eating a strawberry cake.
You eat the cake first
and keep the strawberry.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you
according to my experience.
If you keep the strawberry,
it'll be robbed away sooner or later.
No one can take my things away.
Wait and see.
Did Boss tell Li Yongbiao
to get Li Chi away?
Great.
Boss is so great.
Don't take it personally.
In my opinion,
it is because of you.
If you hadn't told
Boss
to get Li Chi away,
he wouldn't have offended others.
He got disappointed,
and has been tolerated all the time.
Why did he get disappointed?
When Boss just came,
he worked very hard with us,
even sleeping in the company every day.
He wished to perform well
and be transferred to the headquarters.
Why is he still there?
Because there were not
enough places for those
who have strong backgrounds
in the Beijing branch.
The places for Velin were canceled.
So, is he still suppressed
by those who have backgrounds?
You can check that list.
It's either the Lis
or the Zhaos.
And some Zhous.
All have backgrounds.
Does he
hate closely-related units?
Yes.
Anyway,
don't talk about getting Li Chi away
in front of him again.
If Boss is fired,
you'll suffer a lot.
Will... Will he resign?
No.
But I think
it's better if he leaves.
He won't have a good time
in the headquarters.
Li Qin might speak ill of him
to Mr. Yang.
Mr. Yang?
Yang Pingshan, vice president of Donghe?
Ms. Cao.
Miss Xiang.
What's the matter?
Please get me
Li Chi's KPI
and attendance record
in the past years.
Li Chi's?
OK. I'll get them for you.
(Attendance Record)
Yuan. What's the matter?
I miss you.
Stop.
You want my help again, right?
Do me a little favor.
The last time you talked
in this tongue
was when
you blew your school lab up.
My gosh.
Tell me.
I can bear with it.
I want to reorganize
the technical department.
What's your plan?
Do you know Li Chi in our department?
Who?
An engineer.
He's been here for three years,
but his performance is terrible.
He doesn't contribute much
to the company either.
The effort of the whole department
was almost ruined
due to his faults.
It came out on several occasions.
Li Qin's man?
I knew you know him.
So, what do you want to do?
Transfer him away.
He can't be in the technical department.
Go tell Li Qin.
Why do you tell me?
If it worked,
he wouldn't have been
in the company for so many years.
Grandpa.
I'm talking to you seriously.
OK. OK.
When I didn't enter the company,
I didn't know about employees' hardships.
I didn't know what they care about.
They work overtime
and stay up late
for KPI.
I don't know
what that means to them.
I didn't understand either.
Now I know.
The physical and psychological pressure
on them
may not knock them down.
What matter to them is
the results
that they have earned hard,
which are covered or even stolen.
I don't want
these things
in my department.
I want all my men
can be treated
fairly.
All their effort
can be paid back.
You said so much.
I see
what you mean.
Grandpa, I know you are
the kindest to me.
You know me best.
You agree then.
Then you'll only have one chance
asking for my help.
Forget it.
Miss Xiang.
Will you
transfer me away?
Aren't you happy about that?
You don't need to work anymore.
No one manages you.
Suddenly, I think
you are much more powerful
than Chen Shu.
When I was chased by a large dog
at the age of three,
I ran and yelled.
Then I knew I'm powerful.
Because dogs bark at me
when they see me.
I forgot to remind you.
I've been spoiled
since childhood.
I have a bad temper.
So, I warn you.
You are employed to work
in the company,
not to loaf around
and get paid without working.
Miss Xiang.
I might be begged off
but not be coerced.
If you beg me,
I'll be good.
You can invite me
to go to a movie
or have dinner.
And you'd better play cute.
Then I will promise anything.
But
you are so fierce.
I don't like that.
I am
very rebellious.
I like to do things
that you don't want me to do.
Xiang Yuan.
I'm telling you.
You are not
a qualified leader.
A picture was changed
but you didn't find it out, did you?
♪Wanna tell you♪
♪The most beautiful scene for me♪
♪That is your smiling eyes♪
♪Wanna travel♪
♪Where no one reaches♪
♪The world that only belongs to us♪
♪Thinking of♪
♪The time when we were innocent♪
♪Shared all my secrets with you♪
♪If life♪
♪Can be scored in rhythm♪
♪Then I would sing for you♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪The boring life turns interesting♪
♪Take a deep breath for fresh air♪
♪As if you were whispering♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪Everything will be fine♪
♪The wind at the window awakens me♪
♪It is meaningful with you there♪
♪Wanna tell you♪
♪The most beautiful scene for me♪
♪That is your smiling eyes♪
♪Wanna travel where no one reaches♪
♪The world that only belongs to us♪
♪Thinking of♪
♪The time when we were innocent♪
♪Shared all my secrets with you♪
♪If love♪
♪Can be scored in rhythm♪
♪Then I would sing for you♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪The boring life turns interesting♪
♪The summer wind and the spring rain♪
♪You put them all in my hand♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪Everything will be fine♪
♪The dark night and the broken heart♪
♪It's meaningful with you there♪