♪In the pursuit of a dream♪
♪Starting late matters not♪
♪No one is flawless♪
♪Take off against the wind♪
♪Loud cheers wait at the finish line♪
♪But sweat is the cost♪
♪Raise head toward the starlight♪
♪Look up together♪
♪My sky♪
♪Is so different♪
♪In my dream♪
♪There is always your smile♪
♪The freezing wind♪
♪Is warmed by the sun♪
♪Ordinary but glorious♪
♪Be your hero♪
♪In my sky♪
♪There is a hidden rainbow♪
♪Protect the star of dream♪
♪One day we will arrive♪
♪Guard the dream in the heart♪
♪Give you a firm answer♪
♪I will fly beyond the limit♪
♪Run for the lightning♪
♪Fight fight fight♪
♪The other side of the sky♪
=Here We Meet Again=
=Episode 15=
(Xingheng Cup Beidou+Innovation
and Entrepreneurship National Final)
and Entrepreneurship Competition)
(Shanghai Auto Exhibition Hall
Intelligent Dream)
This.
♪Small points on the map♪
Please look at this.
♪Unconsciously♪
♪We are connected into a line♪
This is good.
Please take a look.
♪Billions of light years away
in the universe♪
Here.
So many people!
Yeah.
The competition has attracted
many foreign IT companies.
We mustn't let down our guard.
♪Finally setting off♪
We're on TV.
(Come on. Just do it.)
That's embarrassing.
♪I can always start all over again♪
Here is a QR code.
Scan this code and
we can send bullet-screen comments
on the screen.
What do we scan this for?
Nothing serious.
You can announce your goal
and cheer yourself on.
Just have fun.
Don't waste time.
Let's get in.
This isn't wasting time.
We can say something casually.
If we don't get a place
in the competition,
at least we have left a mark.
I think what
Xiang Yuan said...
♪Finally setting off♪
Xu,
how can you apply double standards?
Cut the crap. Hurry up.
(I hope our efforts)
(will be rewarded)
(and we'll win the competition.)
(May the prize money)
(save my credit card!)
♪Never be afraid♪
(May Xu Yanshi's wish come true.)
All right. Let's go.
Let's go.
♪My world never rains♪
(Xiang Yuan,)
(may you achieve what you wish.)
Is he from the Well Technology
which won first place
in the preliminary?
Really?
Yeah. He's talented.
(Feng Lei)
You go first.
He's good-looking.
Yeah.
And talented, too.
Dad.
- Have you arrived at the venue?
- Impressive.
I'm at the entrance.
What's up?
This is your first competition
after you returned to China.
I hope you take it seriously.
You're going to take over
my business eventually.
Win the competition
and show me
what you've learned abroad.
Dad.
I will.
Back then,
it took me a lot of effort
to send you abroad.
I hope you'll
perform well this time.
My requirement for you
isn't just to win first place.
I care more about how much
you distance yourself
from the runner-up.
Yes. I see.
Bye.
Feng Jun.
Your pass.
(Feng Jun
America Well Technology Co., Ltd.)
Go.
Look.
There are so many people today.
Yeah.
Sir, please sign here.
Welcome.
- Thanks.
- This way, please.
Look.
Is this the team
sent by Well Technology?
That's what we are about to use.
One of the top eight IT companies
in the U.S.
Why do they have to compete for
the prize money with us?
They are not
aimed at the money.
They clearly want to
expand the Chinese market.
Really?
Look at the leader.
The young master of Wanxing Group.
But,
another team is said to
have tied for first place with Well
in the preliminary.
I know.
It seems to be a startup company,
with the name
"This Is A Serious Technology Company."
But it doesn't
sound like a serious company.
(Wang Qingyi
This Is A Serious Technology Company)
(Snack Bar)
Fortunately, we participate
in the competition under Qing's name.
Otherwise, I'll never
accept in my life that
my name would be
followed by
"This Is A Serious Technology Company."
It took him years
to come up with the name.
Don't mock him.
Why?
Why does he have to use the name?
The guy is...
(Old Man Situ)
I have to take this.
(Yuan)
What's up?
Young lady, where are you?
In the company.
Where do you think I am?
I just saw a person
in a picture of the Beidou+
Innovation and Entrepreneurship
Competition,
which looked like you.
I thought you were back in Shanghai.
That's unreal!
Isn't that competition
organized by Xingheng?
You hate them so much.
How could I participate
in their competition,
right?
Could you slow down a bit?
Slow down.
Well,
I'm glad you remember that.
Didn't we
lose miserably
in their competition last time?
I think Xingheng
is directed against us
deliberately. I'm telling you.
OK. I see.
Gotta hang up.
I'm busy.
(There seem to be)
(many reporters.)
(I'd better be careful.)
Who is it?
Feng Jun.
You're back!
Are you surprised?
Have you missed me?
You're an adult.
Don't you know
how to say hello properly?
Aren't you the same?
You hit me as hard as before.
Why did you stop contacting me
after high school?
You stopped contacting me, OK?
Are you here to compete?
Uh-huh.
(Feng Jun)
Well Technology.
Are you doing so well?
A piece of cake.
I got the job with ease.
Don't show off.
How long will you stay in China?
I don't know yet.
But my company plans to
expand its business in China.
So I'll come back regularly.
What about you?
Why are you here?
Do you also work for an IT company?
Any problem?
You did poorly in math.
Are you sure?
When Albert Einstein
discovered the photoelectric effect,
he only scored one point in math.
He was in German.
They applied a six-mark system.
Don't read those impractical articles.
Hasn't your company closed down yet?
I want to introduce you
a brainbox.
Who?
Even better than me?
You'll know.
Where is he?
He was here just now.
Let me call him.
OK.
(Mr. Xu)
Xiang Yuan,
do I know the person
you mentioned?
Guess.
Feng Jun.
It's really you.
It's been a long time.
Long time no see.
How are you doing?
Good.
How long have you been back?
It's been a while.
On the one hand,
I'm back for the competition.
On the other hand,
my company plans to
expand its business in China.
I act solely in the early stage.
So I've been busy lately.
Good for you.
What about you?
Are you here to compete?
Not exactly.
I came with a friend.
Which company
do you work for?
Is it Xingheng?
Velin.
Velin?
I've never heard of it.
What do they do?
Do you know?
I'm in Velin, too.
Are you in the same company?
Good for you.
How's your brother doing recently?
I haven't seen him for a long time.
I'd like to have dinner with him.
I barely keep in touch with him.
Seriously?
Is Jiamian still
busy with his flight base?
Does he have a girlfriend?
Don't worry about him.
I have to go, if you may excuse me.
You haven't changed much.
I have to go, too.
Xiang Yuan,
give me your WeChat.
Let me scan you.
Gotta go.
Bye-bye.
Give me one.
I'm a
participant.
You want these all?
Participant.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Do you want this?
No. Not that.
Give me this.
OK.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Participant.
Wow.
I was wondering
how a computer repairer
could qualify for the final.
It turns out
you've called in reinforcements.
Why?
Have you come to Shanghai because
you couldn't survive out there?
Look at you guys.
Now,
Zhang Yi lives off a woman.
Gui is seriously ill.
I've become outstanding in Shanghai.
Are you and Xu Yanshi
still holed up in your shells
like two turtles?
Lu Junliang,
you've repeated
your cut-and-dried speech
again and again
over the years.
Aren't you bored?
Yeah, I'm only a computer repairer.
But after all these years,
I've never seen a display screen
with such a low resolution as you.
You wander around
all day long with a
QR code-like face.
If I were you,
I would sink through the floor
instead of appearing publicly.
You're shameless.
And also,
when we're here to compete,
you can only get this at most.
Bye-bye.
Guess who I met just now.
We also ran into
an old friend.
Let me say first.
I ran into
Lu Junliang.
Who is he?
One of our seniors at college.
He always got second place.
He used to cheat
and play tricks
in various competitions.
But as long as Xu was there,
he could never get first place.
He
is now
a notorious
hacker.
Why did he come?
I'm curious, too.
That's why I think the Xingheng Cup
will be screwed.
Anyone can come and compete.
It has almost become a
garbage collection station.
No wonder the big shots
in the circle
don't come anymore.
Do you know
what that guy called us?
He called us turtles.
How could I...
Well, who did you say
you had met?
Feng Jun.
Feng Jun?
Where is he?
What's wrong?
Why are you so surprised?
Weren't you alumni?
Don't you know him?
Yeah, I know him too well.
Back then, I...
Wait in line.
What happened back then?
Never mind.
We used to hang out together
and Xu had to save his ass often.
(Well,)
(another thing they wouldn't tell me.)
(Xiang Yuan)
(When have these two)
(hooked up?)
Hello.
The team tied for first place with us
in the preliminary is called
"This Is A Serious Technology Company."
The leader is Wang Qingyi.
Qing?
Go on.
It's weird.
This man isn't
working for any company.
He runs a computer repair shop.
OK. I get it.
(Xingheng Cup Beidou+Competition)
The final will begin.
Everyone,
please pick up your racing vehicle
and get ready.
The auto drive competition
has a distance of six kilometers.
It requires speed
as well as accuracy.
Players must avoid obstacles
in the race.
And the distribution order
of all venues is confidential.
It is like a close-book exam,
which will be a big test
of our algorithm.
We've simulated it many times.
We'll be fine.
We must drive accurately and steadily.
(Data Loading)
(Loaded)
Awesome, Xu!
I've never seen any other person
more impressive than you.
You...
You're the most impressive.
You know what?
It took me
all my luck
to meet such a big shot.
Of course he's impressive.
Let me see
which page you are
on a fairy tale book?
You're good.
Speaking of that,
I think it's a shame that
there are only five awards
for Nobel Prize.
I told you if there was a Nobel Prize
for Computer Science,
he must be a candidate.
No.
There should be
a Nobel Prize for Flattering.
You're so good at it.
Nobel should award you a prize himself.
Ungrateful man.
Take it yourself.
To further stimulate the passion
for innovation and entrepreneurship,
create a new force,
utilize the role of
Beidou Navigation Application
as an engine,
and build a new highland for
innovative application of Beidou,
the final of the third Beidou+
Innovation and Entrepreneurship
Competition
is kicking off today.
- Good.
- Good! Good!
(This Is A Serious Technology Company)
(The Third Beidou+Competition)
Eight teams representing well-known
domestic and foreign enterprises
will give us a show
of speed and passion.
Everyone, are you ready?
Yes.
(Current Vehicle No.1)
The No.1 vehicle from Maosheng Technology
is slowly moving to
the starting line.
Three,
two,
one.
(Unmanned Vehicle System)
They're off.
We've set up
eight levels for the track,
including a U-turn,
traffic light recognition,
a bicycle barricade,
a fork, return positioning, etc.,
to comprehensively examine
the autonomous vehicle
from multiple aspects,
including the obstacle recognition
sensitivity,
the accuracy of
the driving trajectory control,
and the comfort of
the driving experience.
The first level, the U-turn,
is approaching.
Can they smoothly
pass it
and take the top spot?
They pressed the line
and turned the corner too fast.
As we know,
the ride comfort
from smooth driving
is an important indicator
for the final score.
What a shame!
The No.2 vehicle is from
Baitai Technology,
which is one of
our old friends.
Last time they finished
(Current Vehicle No.2)
seventh in the final.
Can they wipe out
the disgrace this time?
They've come to
the U-turn quickly.
Smooth driving and turning.
Its tires have drifted.
Once it presses the line,
- it will probably
- I told you.
end up like the No.1 vehicle.
Good.
No.2 has passed the level.
The next is a red light
to test the accurate recognition
of the signal light
by the auto drive system.
Wait!
Why doesn't No.2
show any signs of stopping?
How come?
If it keeps moving,
it may knock down a pedestrian.
Once it hits a pedestrian,
regardless of its performance,
it will be out
from the competition.
The pedestrian is slowly
moving to the middle of the road.
What a pity!
No.2 is out.
Seriously?
Don't panic.
We've simulated
all the problems they have.
We are definitely better than them.
But this level is indeed difficult.
The position of the dummy was tricky.
I think most of the players
can't pass it.
I wonder
what difficulties lie ahead.
You're being melodramatic.
Yeah.
I have confidence
in Xu's program.
This is mine.
I'll get you another one.
Next is the No.3 vehicle
from Well Technology.
(UVS Positioning Deviation
Duration Map Speed)
This is an international team
with top talents from China and abroad.
They've caught everyone's attention
at the beginning of the competition.
Now they're off.
(UVS Positioning Deviation
Duration Map Speed)
They made it.
Well done.
They avoided
the simulated pedestrian
crossing the zebra crossing
without hesitation.
(Current Vehicle No.3)
While traveling smoothly,
the speed of No.3
is the fastest so far.
They turned the wheel
a little sharply.
But still, they passed it.
Well done!
They deserve their reputation.
You know, the barrier we've set
is a stationary bicycle,
which equates to a
non-motor vehicle barrier.
It's a great challenge
for sensor recognition.
The auto drive system...
Big deal.
Is prone to
misjudging a stationary
non-motor vehicle.
They are fast...
But they didn't make any misjudgment.
And accurate.
And they've passed most of the barriers.
Well, dude,
why do you
take their side?
But they are not sensitive enough
to detect a non-motor vehicle.
They nearly hit the bike
just now.
They'll probably go wrong
if there are more
similar road conditions.
I hope so.
No.3 is the
first vehicle to enter
(Current Vehicle No.3)
the difficult track today.
Could it avoid
the stationary tricycle
with goods on it
and turn right smoothly?
What a shame!
It scraped the goods.
But it doesn't matter.
- You predicted it precisely.
- This is the only mistake
they've made so far.
No.3 seems
unaffected and is heading firmly
towards the finish line.
So far, it has only taken them
seven minutes and 15 seconds.
There's only one level left,
the fork in the road.
After going through this fork,
they'll become the first team
to finish the whole course.
(Current Vehicle No.3)
(FINISH)
Good. They made it.
They reached
the finish line
through precise route planning.
Team No.3, Well Technology,
made one mistake,
finished in 7'42",
scored 1,460 points,
and ranked first for now.
No.4 has been fast
and steady till now.
(Chongqing Hanyu Technology Co., Ltd)
The performance of No.5
is perfect, too.
As their company name suggests,
(Current Vehicle No.5)
No.5 is speeding along the way
like it's soaring.
It seems that
none of them should be underestimated.
(UVS Positioning Deviation
Duration Map Speed)
It slowed down at the fork.
If it makes a wrong judgment,
it won't be able to
return to the starting line.
Correct judgment.
But No.5 has fallen behind Well
in terms of speed and driving stability
(FINISH)
and has dropped out of
the championship race.
I'm so scared.
Second place again.
There are only three teams left.
We didn't make any
big mistakes.
I think we'll definitely
get first place.
So,
don't put on a long face,
OK?
Not necessarily.
What's wrong?
I know Team No.7.
They have real strength.
No.6 is off.
Really?
Let's see
- What should we do?
- the performance of this team.
It has gone through
the U-turn successfully,
- It doesn't matter.
- but it turned a little fast.
If you're sitting in it,
you must grip the handle tightly.
The next is the signal light recognition
(Current Vehicle No.6)
and auto emergency brake.
Could No.6 overtake
the third and fifth teams presently
ranking first and second, respectively?
Let's wait and see.
(Rest Area)
Long time no see.
It's you.
Get out of my way.
Have you seen Xu Yanshi?
I have a way
to get you first place.
What do you say?
Are you interested?
You used to keep in
with Xu Yanshi at college,
you should know what he is
capable of.
You've been abroad for years.
Do you still want to
live in his shadow?
You're living in the shadow,
not me.
I hear that
they've perfectly solved
the sensitivity of
non-motor vehicle recognition.
If you have a way,
why didn't you use it
in our race just now?
Because I didn't think
you were a dark horse.
Then you can use it
on yourself
during Xu Yanshi's race.
Since we can
no longer win first place,
why would I dirty my hands?
Don't you want to win first place?
(Assistant
This Is A Serious Technology Company)
Next,
(Current Vehicle No.7)
let's welcome the seventh team.
Team No.7
has a special name,
This Is
- Xu,
- A Serious Technology Company.
will we be fine?
- We've done everything we should.
- Let's see if
- Be confident.
- their car is as their name suggests
and will achieve
impressive results.
(UVS Positioning Deviation Duration)
Three, two, one.
Go.
(Current Vehicle No.7)
The next is the U-turn.
Let's look at
the performance of No.7.
In the middle, steady, and perfect.
No.7 travels very steadily,
as if someone
is driving it.
(Current Vehicle No.7)
Its signal light recognition
is accurate.
It seems that
the barriers can't defeat them.
They and Well are well matched.
This car is steady.
Yeah.
- So,
- And it has good performance.
let's find out
how No.7 performs
in predicting pedestrians.
No.7 parked steadily
before the zebra crossing.
After No.3,
it has become another vehicle
to go through the track perfectly.
It has taken No.7
3 minutes and 33 seconds so far.
It performs well in comfort
and recognition accuracy, too.
The next is the bicycle roadblock,
which is difficult to detect.
No.7 seems to
have predicted the location
of the bicycle in advance.
What follows is the avoidance
of a stationary roadblock.
Perfect!
No.7 passed smoothly as expected.
It has easily avoided
the spot where No.3
had scraped.
(My requirement for you)
(isn't just to win first place.)
(I care more)
(about how much you distance yourself)
(from the runner-up.)
If the vehicle
dodges when approaching
the non-motor vehicle,
it can't keep steady.
It is prone to accidents
and comfort compromise.
In that case,
it'll have its points deducted.
But in terms of
its two dodges,
No.7 predicted in advance,
changed its driving trajectory,
and maintained its stability,
further improving its speed,
preciseness, and accuracy.
The company deserves the name of
"A Serious Technology Company."
Now is the most difficult track
with a fork in the road.
The team of Soaring
made a mistake here
and missed the championship.
(Current Vehicle No.7)
- Could No.7 pass
- After this level,
- this final test
- we can nail it.
and compete with
Well Technology and Soaring?
This is
a really exciting time.
(Current Vehicle No.7)
What happened?
Why did the well-performed No.7
(Speed: 33km/h)
suddenly slow down?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
There is a problem with the signal.
If so,
will the navigation system be affected?
How would it pass
the fork ahead?
This is the fork track
with rigorous requirements
for the system.
Without a high-precision map
downloaded in advance,
the vehicle relies solely on
the Beidou system
(Unmanned Vehicle Systems)
for positioning and planning.
Its judgment on the fork ahead
will directly affect the results.
If it goes the wrong way,
it will get a zero.
Could No.7 pass
in such a state?
No, no, no.
It only has to pass the final level.
How did this happen?
(Current Vehicle No.7)
(Unmanned Vehicle Systems)
(Inertial System)
No.7 seems to
have changed.
Is the signal recovered?
Because we have Plan B.
What is Plan B?
We recompose and relocate
(Inertial System)
based on synchronous
positioning and mapping techniques.
When the navigation signal weakens,
the car automatically switches to
inertial navigation
to keep moving.
But with its speed
and accuracy decreasing,
it can do no more than finish the race.
It's about to turn the corner.
After what has happened,
could No.7 still make it?
This is a real technology company,
and also the only
rookie team to
advance to the final.
They made almost zero mistakes
in the previous tracks,
overtaking the large company, Soaring,
and rivaling the top foreign company,
Well Technology.
No.7, come on!
Come on! Come on!
The final level is right in front of it.
No.7 is making a final attempt.
Come on! Come on!
Well done!
Though it grazed the line,
it passed the fork
in the road smoothly.
♪I cross the horizon
to enjoy the sunset♪
(Current Vehicle No.7)
No.7 has made a recovery.
It didn't deviate from the track.
Keep steady!
The finishing line is ahead.
Could No.7 defeat
No.3 which holds
the top spot?
Come on! Come on!
No.7, come on!
Almost there!
Come on! Come on!
No.7, come on!
(Current Vehicle No.7)
No.7 arrived at the finishing line
in 7 minutes and 50 seconds.
Let's see
how many points
does No.7 score in total.
1,450 points!
Only 10 points less than No.3.
Congratulations!
This Is A Serious Technology Company
overtakes Roaring
and ranks second
after Well Technology.
Everyone, check your Weibo.
Boss has advanced
to the final of Beidou+.
Hurry up. Check it.
Beidou+?
Hurry.
I saw it. He competed in the final.
Really？
This programmer
is so cool!
(Xingheng Cup Beidou+Competition)
Qingqing. Qingqing.
Who took such a great photo
of him?
Yeah. So handsome!
He is a handsome guy anyway.
(This Is A Serious Technology Company)
Second place is not bad.
I checked the black box.
There was no problem with the car.
But something was wrong
with the satellite signal.
But how could
the satellite signal go wrong?
Normally,
there wouldn't be
such a stupid mistake
in a large-scale competition like this.
Do you think
anyone might have used
a signal jammer?
I have to take this.
See you at the entrance.
OK.
If someone really
used a jammer...
Lu Junliang!
It must be him.
I remember during the race
of our team,
I saw Feng Jun and Lu Junliang
go outside.
They seemed to
be passing something.
When Feng Jun was back,
the signal went bad.
In that case,
it must be him.
Him again!
Well, why again?
Hello.
Boss.
Why did you go to
the Beidou+ competition?
How did you know?
You were photographed.
They even call you
the most handsome programmer.
Oh.
Why are you so calm?
This is a big deal.
Durian Witch will definitely
make an issue of it.
She may make an issue of it,
but she won't be an issue.
Do you still
have the mood to joke?
Or what?
Boss, I'm telling you...
All right. I have to go.
Hello. Boss. Hello.
Did he hang up?
Yeah.
What did he say?
He said nothing.
Xu is too kindhearted,
otherwise, Feng Jun wouldn't be
where he is today.
So, what happened between them?
(Offer from Xingheng
Technology Co., Ltd.)
Good.
You are the only
undergraduate student
who has got an offer
from Xingheng in these years.
Xingheng is leading in
the national positioning system
industry.
You must cherish
this hard-earned opportunity.
I still remember
when I gave you the first lesson,
I asked about your ideals.
You were the first to stand up
and told me that
you would contribute to
China's navigation industry.
Now,
you can start
realizing your ideals.
Sir, if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have had
such a starting point.
But you must remember,
from now on,
you not only
have an extra honor
but also shoulder
responsibility to China's
navigation industry.
Yeah.
I get it.
(Notice on Clearing Nepotism from the Group)
Did you make it?
Sure.
Who do you think I am?
Enough. Enough.
I was
only two seconds behind you.
What about you, Qing?
I'm far behind you.
I just logged in.
I'm telling you,
you made it because
you used Xu's computer
and shared his strength.
Why don't you use your own computer
and compete with me again?
My computer is running a program, OK?
Anyway, the computer
doesn't make any difference.
Stop acting shamelessly.
Drink. Drink.
Drink.
Fine!
I'll admit defeat.
Come on.
(Offer from Xingheng Technology Co., Ltd.)
(Infringement Indictment)
Xu Yanshi, Wang Qingyi and Gao Sibo.
You illegally hacked into
the system of our company,
causing its breakdown.
We've suffered a significant loss.
This is our indictment,
including all relevant
evidence and data.
(Infringement Indictment)
(In total: RMB 10 million)
Feng Jun,
say something.
Say what?
Why don't you say?
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't you
say anything just now?
Let me ask you. Get up.
Does it have anything to do with Xu?
You hacked into their system
with Xu's computer.
Did I do it alone?
Didn't you hack into it?
We were probably possessed that day.
How can we pay
such a huge sum of money?
Yeah.
We're about to graduate.
My family wants me
to hunt for a good job.
Now it's terrible.
I'm finished.
Great!
Calm down, all of you.
It has already happened.
We should think about
how to solve it.
These are cases of compensation
for cyber intrusion
I collected online
and the compensation amount
I consulted with my lawyer.
(Cases of Compensation for Cyber Intrusion)
Many of the claims
in your indictment are beyond
our compensation scope.
The amount we have to pay
is two million yuan.
I'm sorry about this.
But everyone should be responsible
for the mistakes they've made.
If we appeal,
it would be difficult for you
to establish yourselves in the industry
in the future.
You should understand.
I got it.
To compensate for the loss
we have caused,
we can upgrade
the security system
of your company.
OK.
As long as the upgraded system
can meet our
latest requirements,
we'll accept two million yuan.
Actually,
I can offer you
a better choice.
If you agree to
work in Velin,
we'll give up suing you.
You don't have to
compensate for us.
I won't go.
Professor Liang told me that
you were the only
undergraduate this year
who had received
the offer from Xingheng.
But you should know,
Xingheng wouldn't accept you
if you couldn't solve this.
I'll definitely solve it.
OK.
Since you're so confident,
I'll give you two weeks.
How did it go?
I made a deal with Chen Shan.
Within two weeks,
we have to upgrade
the security system of
Velin Technology
and raise
two million yuan in compensation.
I'll raise the money.
Two million.
No problem.
Well,
we don't have
so much money now.
Could you please pay for us?
We'll pay you back
when we get the money.
Thanks, bro.
No problem.
We'll be responsible
for the system upgrade.
Let's begin.
I've finished it.
What about you?
I've finished it, too.
Done.
Great.
We have two days left.
There's still time.
I wonder if Feng Jun
has raised the money.
(Sorry, the subscriber you dialed)
(is busy now.)
(Please redial...)
- Hello.
May I speak to Feng Jun?
Feng Jun has gone abroad.
Abroad?
Could you tell me...
I'm telling you,
this has nothing to do
with Feng Jun.
Don't harass my son again.
Hello. Hello.
What should we do?
Let's raise the money separately.
How much do you need?
Tell me. Don't waste time.
I need
1.5 million.
I'll
see what I can do.
As for Xingheng,
I'll communicate with them.
Thank you, sir.
Xu,
don't worry.
We'll give the money
to Chen Shan
and finish this thing.
Gui and I will find a way
to pay back the money
Professor Liang lent us.
When I start to work in Xingheng,
I'll help you to pay back the money.
OK.
We have to
count on you.
You guys,
you look upset
even though you're smiling.
Cheer up.
We still have a bright future.
We should celebrate.
Let's drink.
I'll get some beer.
OK.
(Dad Calling)
Dad.
Yanshi,
I've got a very good
opportunity recently.
Lend Dad
your money
for emergency use.
When I make money,
I'll make it up to you.
Well, Xu,
is your dad out of his mind?
Does he know what impact
this will have on you?
It will affect your future.
Enough.
You're not
helping.
Listen to me.
Let's reason with him.
Or we can call the police.
What do you say?
We can't call the police.
That's his dad!
I don't care.
It's two million!
Are you going to let the police
catch his dad for the two million?
What else can I do?
You tell me!
Do what?
It only makes him more upset
if you keep yelling.
(Offer from Xingheng)
Why do you always argue with me?
Let's sit down and think it over, OK?
(Several days later,)
(when we received Chen Shan's notice)
(to withdraw the lawsuit,)
(Xu had already)
(joined Velin.)
Did Xu Yanshi give up
his life and career just like that?
Feng Jun has returned from abroad
and started over again.
Gui has a successful career
and love life in Shanghai.
It seems that the incident
hasn't changed
anyone's life trajectory
except Xu...
You go first.
Are you waiting for me?
Let's have a word.
(This Is A Serious Technology Company)
♪Wanna tell you♪
♪The most beautiful scene for me♪
♪That is your smiling eyes♪
♪Wanna travel♪
♪Where no one reaches♪
♪The world that only belongs to us♪
♪Thinking of♪
♪The time when we were innocent♪
♪Shared all my secrets with you♪
♪If life♪
♪Can be scored in rhythm♪
♪Then I would sing for you♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪The boring life turns interesting♪
♪Take a deep breath for fresh air♪
♪As if you were whispering♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪Everything will be fine♪
♪The wind at the window awakens me♪
♪It is meaningful with you there♪
♪Wanna tell you♪
♪The most beautiful scene for me♪
♪That is your smiling eyes♪
♪Wanna travel where no one reaches♪
♪The world that only belongs to us♪
♪Thinking of♪
♪The time when we were innocent♪
♪Shared all my secrets with you♪
♪If love♪
♪Can be scored in rhythm♪
♪Then I would sing for you♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪The boring life turns interesting♪
♪The summer wind and the spring rain♪
♪You put them all in my hand♪
♪The time when I am with you♪
♪Everything will be fine♪
♪The dark night and the broken heart♪
♪It's meaningful with you there♪