♪The stars in the sky shine bright♪
♪The rippling water reflects your face♪
♪No one knows the struggle in my mind♪
♪I act calm as I say hi♪
♪In two different worlds♪
♪we're both rushing ahead♪
♪Thinking the view at the top
would leave us breathless♪
♪As memories fade like shattered pieces♪
♪I still find myself drawn to you♪
♪In a crowd of people,
with nowhere to land♪
♪Your presence is my island,
my solid ground♪
♪I know where you are,
but act like I don't care♪
♪My heart beats for you,
yet I leave it unsaid♪
[This World Is Not Real]
[Load game]
[Episode 17]
[The Real World]
I'm sorry, Chairman Lin.
He Lanxue has gone missing.
Find her.
We're doing everything we can
to track her down.
Why did she harm Xian?
Who's behind her?
I checked her mother's bank account.
There were several large deposits,
totaling over three million yuan.
Who sent the money?
The new CEO of Stone Network,
He Fan.
Just an upstart with no real foundation,
and he dares to mess with my family
and hurt my grandson?
Mr. He, you can't go in.
Chairman Lin is in a meeting.
Chairman Lin and Mr. Kun, I'm so sorry.
I...
Sorry to barge in, Mr. Lin.
[He Fan]
I'm the new CEO of Stone Network.
So,
you're He Fan?
You've heard of me, Mr. Lin?
Just get to the point.
Mr. Lin,
I respect your position in the industry,
so I'll
cut to the chase.
I want to buy Xian Game.
You must be mistaken.
Xian Game's market value
is ten times that of your company.
Recently, Xian Game's biggest hit,
"Qing Wan's Forest",
[Scandals Engulf "Qing Wan's Forest"]
has been caught up in scandals.
Players across regions
have fallen into comas
after playing this dream-based game.
Rumor has it that even Xian Game's CEO
has fallen into a coma because of it.
The company has yet
to make an official statement.
Don't worry.
I've paid a lot to keep this report
from spreading widely.
But how much do you think
Xian Game's valuation will plummet
if this hits the trending topics?
I can offer you a fair price now,
but I can't give you
much time to consider.
Kid,
do you really think
a piece of news like this
is enough to bring down Xian Game?
You're too naive.
A day is all I need
to paralyze
your PR department
over at Stone.
At your age,
you spend more time with your grandson,
though I wonder
if he'll ever wake up.
Thanks for your concern.
He Lanxue
was working with you, wasn't she?
I already have
all the evidence
of your collusion with her.
Legal consequences aside,
how do you think the media would react
to a corporate espionage story
like this?
How can you
maintain any standing
in the gaming industry?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know anyone named He Lanxue.
You're still too young, boy.
Since you're refusing my generous offer,
don't blame me for what comes next.
Find He Lanxue.
Lin Xian!
Are you okay?
Are you sure this will work?
Only the fear of death
can awaken
the brain's survival instinct.
It might just
stimulate my nerves in the real world.
No matter how much I struggle,
you must hold me down.
Don't let me get up.
No, this is too dangerous.
It's worth a shot if it can get us out.
♪Your absence leaves me
lost and broken♪
You won't let me
die in your dream, right?
How will I know
if you've made it out or not?
If I make it out,
my body here should disappear.
♪Endless longing piling up
like missed calls♪
♪And you won't even bother to look...♪
Qing Wan,
I love you.
I've been waiting for you to wake up.
♪We're destined
to fall in love again...♪
I'm doing this for us.
♪Don't mumble if you mean it♪
♪The one who won't let go♪
♪Tosses and turns at night,
desperate because of you♪
♪Those wrongs in love's name,
how are you going to justify them?♪
♪The falling fireworks♪
♪That once lit up my life
are taking away all of my love♪
♪In your silence,
I begin to understand...♪
Lin Xian!
♪You're the fireworks I can never touch♪
♪Those wrongs in love's name,
how are you going to justify them?♪
♪The falling fireworks♪
♪That once lit up my life
are taking away all of my love♪
♪In your silence, I begin to understand♪
♪You're the fireworks I can never touch♪
♪You don't belong to me♪
Lin Xian,
I won't let you die in my dream.
♪The stars in the sky shine bright♪
♪The rippling water reflects your face♪
♪No one knows the struggle in my mind♪
♪I act calm as I say hi♪
♪In two different worlds,
we're both rushing ahead♪
♪Thinking the view at the top
would leave us breathless♪
♪As memories fade like shattered pieces♪
♪I still find myself drawn to you♪
♪In a crowd of people,
with nowhere to land♪
♪Your presence is my island,
my solid ground♪
♪I know where you are♪
♪But act like I don't care♪
♪My heart beats for you,
yet I leave it unsaid♪
♪Passion and loneliness
carve our memories♪
♪The moonlight by the lighthouse
leaves no trace♪
♪For you, I'd cross mountains and seas♪