♪The stars in the sky shine bright♪
♪The rippling water reflects your face♪
♪No one knows the struggle in my mind♪
♪I act calm as I say hi♪
♪In two different worlds♪
♪we're both rushing ahead♪
♪Thinking the view at the top
would leave us breathless♪
♪As memories fade like shattered pieces♪
♪I still find myself drawn to you♪
♪In a crowd of people,
with nowhere to land♪
♪Your presence is my island,
my solid ground♪
♪I know where you are,
but act like I don't care♪
♪My heart beats for you,
yet I leave it unsaid♪
[This World Is Not Real]
[Load game]
[Episode 18]
[The Real World]
Qing Wan!
Qing Wan.
Wake up, Qing Wan.
I will wait for you to wake up.
♪Your absence leaves me lost and broken♪
♪My lips are still warm
from our passion♪
♪But I can't recreate
every moment we've shared♪
♪My mind's gone blank,
like a kite cut loose in the sky♪
♪Your cold words
cut straight to my heart♪
♪Always smooth with words,
skilled at playing games...♪
Qing Wan?
♪And you won't even bother to look...♪
Qing Wan,
you're awake.
♪Though we're from two different worlds♪
♪We're destined
to fall in love again...♪
Where am I?
At home.
♪The one who won't let go
tosses and turns at night...♪
You're back.
We're at home?
Am I really back?
Yes, you are.
♪The falling fireworks♪
♪That once lit up my life
are taking away all of my love♪
♪In your silence,
I begin to understand♪
♪You're the fireworks I can never touch♪
♪You don't belong to me♪
Recently, Xian Game's biggest hit,
"Qing Wan's Forest",
[Scandals Engulf "Qing Wan's Forest"]
has been caught up in scandals.
I'm sorry, Chairman Lin.
We lost him.
Let's forget him for now.
Now,
what matters most
is that both Xian and Qing Wan
have woken up.
He Fan doesn't know that
Qing Wan and I are awake.
He's in the open,
and we're in the shadows.
Stone Network must have
tampered with Dreamscape.
They accessed
the computational power base
and destabilized the cloud components.
I'm not letting them
destroy "Qing Wan's Forest" like this.
But we don't
have any evidence now.
We need to find He Lanxue.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lin.
Was there anything off about her
before she went missing?
Miss He?
Mr. Lin.
There's a contract
that needs your signature.
I've just remembered something!
Track and locate its host.
This is your specialty.
Found it.
It must be her.
Deng!
Qing Wan!
I knew you'd wake up.
Yes, I'm finally awake.
Deng,
wait for me.
I have something
more important to do.
Let me help you.
Okay.
We're too late.
What do we do now?
We wait.
Wait?
His end goal is to buy Xian Game.
As long as he has
He Lanxue with him,
he'll think we lack proof,
and he'll come talk
to my grandfather again.
Will He Lanxue be in danger?
Don't come any closer.
One more step back,
and you'll fall.
If I die,
I'm dragging you down with me.
Let me offer you a way out.
Here's a plane ticket to South America.
If you promise never to come back,
I'll give you enough money
to live comfortably abroad
for the rest of your life.
I won't believe you anymore.
Do you really have a choice?
Would you rather jump down
and become a cold, lifeless body,
or take the money and leave?
Lanxue,
you're a smart girl.
What about Lin Xian?
Why do you still care about him?
You've been working devotedly for him
for three years,
but has he ever looked at you twice?
Come on.
Give me the recorder,
and the money and ticket will be yours.
Okay.
Give me your hand.
Publish the news report.
Now!
I said I didn't want to see you.
Why are you here?
Mr. Lin,
have you seen the news?
Xian Game's market value
has dropped by half.
If you agree to the acquisition,
I'll wake up your grandson.
How are you going to do that?
Lin Xian got trapped in Dreamscape
due to an accident, right?
Stone Network has a technology
that can implant
a fake memory into his mind
to help him regain mental strength.
[Acquisition Agreement]
Just sign this contract,
and I'll wake him up immediately.
What a great plan,
Mr. He.
You...
How is this possible?
He Lanxue,
you're not dead?
I'm not. You must be
very disappointed, Mr. He.
[Eighteen hours ago]
Qing Tian, here's what you asked for.
Thanks, Deng.
This
is the product of an AAA project
I developed at Xian Game.
Qing Tian,
with your talent,
you should've joined
Stone Network long ago.
I'm not going anywhere.
I must find out
who harmed my sister.
Fan,
you'll help us, right?
Don't worry.
Qing Wan will definitely wake up.
The memory implant technology Xian Game
developed for the medical field
has long been perfected.
I never imagined
our first real-world application
would be in a situation like this.
Qing Tian,
the experience is incredible!
If you bring the project to Stone,
it'll become a massive success.
It's time
to give Lin Changmin a push.
Have you found
where he's hiding He Lanxue?
Yes,
but can an artificial
memory implant work?
The memory implant technology
was developed using Dreamscape's
computational power,
but its use is strictly regulated.
Let's go find He Lanxue.
Let's go.
I'll leave the rest of the work
to you.
Fan,
can Stone Network's technology
really help wake Qing Wan up?
Once we bring down Xian Game,
Lin Xian won't be able
to control Qing Wan anymore.
Let's make this project a success.
It will be.
Tian, you're being too dramatic.
Don't overdo it.
Why did you hire Qing Tian too?
He Fan was right about one thing.
Qing Tian is just as capable as you are.
You tricked me.
Don't leave just yet, Mr. He.
Didn't you want
to discuss the acquisition?
I have other matters to attend to.
We'll talk another time.
He Fan,
why?
Why?
Don't act like you care.
You've never wanted to be with me.
We'll see who gets
the last laugh.
I'm impressed,
Tian.
I'll take that as a compliment.
I said
I'd make this project a success.
I also said
I'd find out
who hurt my sister.
Fan,
I can't believe
you'd do this to Qing Wan!
Mr. He, you're under arrest
for commercial fraud
and false imprisonment.
Please come with us.
Deng, Qing Tian.
He Lanxue, come with us.
There's one more thing.
I can't wait any longer.
It has to be done now.
What is it?
Xian,
good luck.
It's been with me for three years.
♪Belong to you completely whatever♪
Wow,
it's finally happening!
It's time to ask you
the most important question.
Qing Wan,
will you...?
Don't ever make me wait this long again.
♪Cool breeze of midsummer
blows away the heat♪
♪The dusk embraces the sky
for a fleeting moment♪
♪People grow restless
chasing their dreams♪
♪We only get to live our youth once♪
♪Watching grown-up movies as kids♪
♪We imagined what it's like to grow up♪
♪Longing for love,
wanting to make mistakes♪
♪But in the end,
it's a peaceful life we lead♪
Wan,
this is only the beginning of everything
I planned for you.
[DECODING]
[This World Is Not Real, Load game]
[COMPLETE]
♪The stars in the sky shine bright♪
♪The rippling water reflects your face♪
♪No one knows the struggle in my mind♪
♪I act calm as I say hi♪
♪In two different worlds,
we're both rushing ahead♪
♪Thinking the view at the top
would leave us breathless♪
♪As memories fade like shattered pieces♪
♪I still find myself drawn to you♪
♪In a crowd of people,
with nowhere to land♪
♪Your presence is my island,
my solid ground♪
♪I know where you are♪
♪But act like I don't care♪
♪My heart beats for you,
yet I leave it unsaid♪
♪Passion and loneliness
carve our memories♪
♪The moonlight by the lighthouse
leaves no trace♪
♪For you, I'd cross mountains and seas♪