♪The stars in the sky shine bright♪
♪The rippling water reflects your face♪
♪No one knows the struggle in my mind♪
♪I act calm as I say hi♪
♪In two different worlds♪
♪we're both rushing ahead♪
♪Thinking the view at the top
would leave us breathless♪
♪As memories fade like shattered pieces♪
♪I still find myself drawn to you♪
♪In a crowd of people,
with nowhere to land♪
♪Your presence is my island,
my solid ground♪
♪I know where you are,
but act like I don't care♪
♪My heart beats for you,
yet I leave it unsaid♪
[This World Is Not Real]
[Load game]
[Episode 5]
This trophy is the one thing
Mr. Lin values most.
Sorry, we didn't mean to.
Deng.
It was my fault.
It has nothing to do with Deng.
No pets allowed in the office,
but Miss Qing didn't know
since she was new.
Deng, you didn't know either?
I found it this morning,
and I didn't know it would
wander into Mr. Lin's office.
But the name on the trophy...
Does it matter whose name's on it
if it's broken?
Miss Qing.
I couldn't find anything about you.
There's no trace of your name
in the gaming industry.
I...
Do I need your approval to hire someone?
I'm sorry, Mr. Lin.
That's not what I meant.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Lin.
No worries.
I'll clean it up.
Mr. Lin.
Don't get upset.
Miss Qing didn't mean it.
I'll get someone from cleaning.
Everyone, out.
Let's go.
[Game Designer of the Year: Qing Wan]
Mr. Lin.
I really can't handle being VP.
I'm just a game designer.
Maybe you should put me back
in the dev team
or demote me.
They don't respect you
because they don't
know your potential yet.
How are you so sure
I even have potential?
Because I, Lin Xian, believe in you.
[Game Designer of the Year: Qing Wan]
Stop staring at it.
I have plenty of backups of that trophy.
Is there really a designer with my name?
No.
That designer is you.
Me?
How's that possible?
Mr. Lin, I've never even dreamed
of winning the Purple Pupil
Game Designer Award.
You've got the talent,
or you wouldn't be here.
You'll get what I mean eventually.
He's always saying things
I don't understand.
He shouldn't be Lin Xian.
Should call him Weirdo Lin.
Thanks for the compliment, Mr. Lin.
- Does it mean...?
- Take a walk with me.
But it's work hours.
We can
chat about Qing Wan's Forest on the way.
[The Real World]
Three years,
and they've always had this connection.
How am I supposed to know
that you can't break the firewall?
See that van over there?
Open the trunk.
Take out the box inside.
What's this?
A small program.
Connect it to
Qing Wan's Forest's database.
That's all you need to know.
Do you even know
what Qing Wan's Forest is?
No idea.
So why do you want in?
This might sound
a little full of myself,
but I feel like
I have a connection to it,
like I'm the one
who can finish it.
That does sound pretty full of yourself.
The usual. Two vanilla.
Didn't expect him
to like vanilla, too.
- Thank you.
- Both are for you.
I don't like vanilla.
How does he know
I always get two?
Want to try one?
It's really good.
♪Jump into the dead sea of love♪
♪My love is generous♪
♪Crossing time and space♪
♪It's a pity our love is bright♪
♪But disappears so fast♪
♪Like a child's hope for love♪
I thought you didn't want it?
I never said that.
Lady, would you like to request a song?
No, thanks.
Dust Moment by LEQI CLUB, please.
Alright.
Thanks.
You like this song too?
This band is my favorite.
Back in college,
I followed their tour everywhere.
Never mind.
Just a silly hobby.
Go on.
I want to hear about it.
I used to code nonstop
just to save up for concert tickets.
One time,
I argued with a scalper
outside a venue
and got knocked down.
Hit my head,
and my dad
had a heart attack on the way there
from the stress.
He almost...
I felt guilty for a long time
and couldn't listen to them again.
How's your dad now?
He's better after surgery,
resting at home.
But I'm worried about Qing Tian.
He's got the same heart problem
as my dad,
a septal defect.
He'll be alright.
Thanks for saying that.
I just booked you an appointment
with the top cardiologist
in the country, Dr. Xu.
Take Qing Tian to West China Hospital
next Tuesday for a check-up.
Really?
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
I'll work extra hard.
Mr. Lin.
Where'd he go?
[The Real World]
Mr. Lin.
Start testing
the interaction data interface.
Got it, Mr. Lin.
Because you're someone
I, Lin Xian, believe in.
Didn't even say goodbye before leaving.
♪The stars in the sky shine bright♪
♪The rippling water reflects your face♪
♪No one knows the struggle in my mind♪
♪I act calm as I say hi♪
♪In two different worlds,
we're both rushing ahead♪
♪Thinking the view at the top
would leave us breathless♪
♪As memories fade like shattered pieces♪
♪I still find myself drawn to you♪
♪In a crowd of people,
with nowhere to land♪
♪Your presence is my island,
my solid ground♪
♪I know where you are♪
♪But act like I don't care♪
♪My heart beats for you,
yet I leave it unsaid♪
♪Passion and loneliness
carve our memories♪
♪The moonlight by the lighthouse
leaves no trace♪
♪For you, I'd cross mountains and seas♪