There is someone inside my body.
Get her out!
The all-night talk last night was quite fruitful.
But
it's a pity.
What's a pity?
You had a beautiful night and a lovely lady,
but you ended up studying Wentongzi.
I feel sorry for you.
What's wrong?
What do you smell?
Someone is getting really jealous.
Stop being glib.
It seems last night
someone else was awake all night too.
I just don't know
if it was for keeping watch or spying.
Jianqin,
why don't you go back and rest?
I'd rather come out to investigate with you, Young Master,
than stay with Miss Tu
and listen to her scare me.
What are you doing?
We would like to ask
about Qu Dayou killing his mother.
Sir, what else do you remember?
Yes.
My son is the Plague Boy.
Of my perfectly good family,
I am the only one left alive.
What is the use of talking about this?
Just go back.
You can't help me.
Wait a minute.
Have you seen the Skeleton Grass on this?
Get out!
All of you, get out!
Young Master, are you alright?
I'm fine.
How can you be so barbaric?
What if you hurt my young master?
Old gentleman.
My Lord,
Something happened to the Madam of the Duke last night.
Director
Ji
How is my mother doing?
Your Highness.
The Madam of the Duke
is suffering from
an evil disease.
This, this is unprecedented.
Forgive
my ignorance.
I also have no clue at all.
Even if Hua Tuo were alive,
I'm afraid it would still be useless.
A bunch of losers.
What's the use of keeping you?
I might as well chop you up and feed you to the dogs.
Calm down, Your Highness.
Liu Chuan,
why are you here?
The virus has evolved to this extent.
Liu Chuan, what are you doing to my mother?
Emergency rescue, of course.
Can you save my mother?
Aren't you a coroner?
A coroner?
Doesn't a coroner just examine corpses?
I've never heard
that a coroner can also cure diseases.
Isn't this Young Master Liu?
You frequent brothels and casinos all year round.
When did you learn medicine?
You reek of alcohol and meat.
Don't choke the Duchess with the smell.
So you are the rumored
Young Master Liu.
I've heard so much about you.
In my opinion,
your diagnostic skills
are quite extraordinary.
You look at money,
smell alcohol,
ask about gambling debts,
and feel your reputation.
Someone who deals with the dead every day.
If you fail to cure the Duchess,
how can you take the responsibility?
Are you doctors?
If you can't cure her,
get out of the way.
You... How dare you insult us?
How vulgar.
Your Highness,
if you really let him treat the Duchess,
and something goes wrong,
I'm afraid we won't be able to help.
Preposterous.
Your hands touch dead bodies every day,
and you dare to save the Duchess?
Aren't you afraid of killing her?
What are your intentions?
Then tell me what to do.
All of you, shut up.
Liu Chuan,
can you really save my mother?
Right now,
I can't guarantee a complete cure.
I can only temporarily relieve the symptoms.
There's no better way right now.
You saw your uncle.
What was the result in the end?
This...
Liu Chuan,
if you can cure my mother,
I will give you whatever you want.
But if you can't,
I'll have your head.
Glad I made it in time.
I thought it was some miracle cure,
but it's just anesthetic powder.
What are you doing with the knife?
You...
Are not going to...
Exactly.
I need to make an incision and drain the blood.
Nonsense!
This is simply child's play.
Your Highness,
if you really let him treat the Duchess,
I fear she will die at his hands.
Yes.
The virus has already invaded the body through the bloodstream.
The only way is to make an incision, drain the blood, and remove the rotting flesh.
Although there are certain risks,
I will do my best.
Don't worry.
Stop!
Your Highness,
you absolutely must not let him mess around.
If we don't stop him,
the Duchess will die by his hands.
Your Highness.
You two, shut up.
If you can treat her, do it. If not, get out.
Mother.
Mother, wake up.
Why isn't my mother responding?
She is dead.
Dead, dead, dead.
Dead.
The Duchess is dead.
Shut up!
Mother!
The...
The Duchess.
Guards!
Drag these gossips out
and beat them to death.
We are innocent!
Princess, we are innocent!
Injustice.
Liu Chuan.
You saved my mother.
I will give you whatever you want.
Even if...
Even if you want this mansion,
I wouldn't hesitate.
Even...
even if you want...
If you really want to save your mother,
we must find the murderer
and trace the source of the virus.
I still need your cooperation.
How many times have I told you
not to pat me from behind?
The sound seems to come from inside.
I found similar powder on
the Princess's uncle's body before.
As expected, the Plague Boy is man-made.
This is the Princess's uncle,
the Princess,
the Duchess of Jiaguo,
and the workers.
Oh no.
Why does the watchman's drum today
seem half a quarter earlier than usual?
Water.
Stop.
He's the one
who killed my uncle
and wants to kill my mother.
Qu Dayou is still alive.
The reason he became a Plague Boy
was also man-made.
Right?
The debt the Medicine God Society owes my family
should be paid.
Watch out.