[English subtitles are available]
[Miss You Forever]
[Episode 20]
It turns out that from the beginning to the end,
you've been one of them.
It was you
who set up this well-designed trap.
And I
was just a chesspiece to you.
Why me?
[Complete the show till the end.]
I've said that I cherish and love
this chess game.
Back then, Dazhao was defeated in the battle.
Only by devising a plan
to arouse all the people's aspirations
can we get rid of the plight.
We are just a fake couple after all.
We were wearing masks when we first met.
I had thought that the false love between us
could be ignored totally.
But when our masks were removed,
everything became different.
It turns out that from the beginning to the end,
helping the Lihuo Sect to take the royal power
has been an excuse.
You guys are the ones
who want to benefit from the chaos
and enjoy the fruits acquired by others.
It was you
who pretended to be dead regardless of the cost,
framed Sagebrush on the Snow,
suspected Lu Xi'er,
and lured us to Pingzhou,
causing internal disputes between us.
No.
I don't care about the so-called
Sagebrush on the Snow.
Then what do you want?
A reason.
A reason to dispatch troops.
Now Beiman is in a weak state.
The Saintess had better die in Dazhao.
Is there a better time than this?
So,
you asked assassins to take action again and again.
After the Saintess dies,
the two armies will have a justified reason
to kill people.
You're so cruel.
Killing an innocent person
can bring peace to the world.
You talked about bringing peace to the world.
Then let me ask you.
What is the world?
Those people whom you're going to kill
constitute the world.
We used to be strangers to each other after all.
This is the best for
both him and me.
So,
you still remember your mission.
I've told you all the details
of his whereabouts.
I also want to know
the whereabouts of Sagebrush on the Snow.
Do you have to stir up the storm?
Not me.
Second Prince.
What? I don't look like that?
Or...
I can only be Mr. Yunshan?
[Rebellion]
How is it?
This calligraphy looks vivid like a flying bird,
and graceful like clouds.
Read it out.
It's not that you don't dare to do it.
You just don't want to do it.
For this word,
you've already done it.
I thought all the members of the Grim Reapers were desperadoes
and wouldn't have any love affairs.
I
won't see him again.
You two
will never meet again indeed.
Where on earth did you guys go?
Why was there an assassin?
It was all my fault.
I was late when I came.
He's resting now.
Even till now, I still don't dare to recall it.
For the so-called obsession in my mind,
I set up a trap,
and persisted in my own opinions stubbornly.
In the end,
I suffered a thorough defeat.
Xie Jingshu.
I still lost in the end.
Don't cry.
Don't talk about it openly.
Someone might eavesdrop on us.
Dear, please continue to act in this show with me.
Xie Jingshu was just a small lesson for you.
It was due to the face that
you didn't do your best.
You're such a cold-hearted man.
You're just a civilian from an uncivilized place.
It won't be a pity if you die.
This is fate.
I'd rather die on the battlefild
than accept fate.
Aren't you afraid of death?
Yes, I am.
Why would I not be afraid of death?
As long as you tell me
where the Saintess is...
It won't be a pity if I die alone.
Seeing you fail to achieve your goal in the end,
I feel so happy.
The second eldest prince planned the assassination.
Why don't you go to see His Majesty directly?
What a man with wild ambitions.
If you want to collude with the vassal states,
aren't you afraid that he'll tell His Majesty about it?
He doesn't dare to do it.
It's also impossible that he would do it.
Stop!
It's too late.
Give it to him now.
If he's tired of being Marquis Dingbei,
I don't mind depriving him of this title.
Known as the son of Marquis Dingbei,
actually, he is just a dog raised by my father.
His Majesty wanted to set up a flag for Beihuang,
and Dazhao needed
a young Beihuang general who could encourage the people,
so I gave him this chance.
I gave this chance to Xie Jingshu, who had no real power.
In this round,
just go to hell with him.
Go inside.
Thank you.
Thank you for helping me at my most difficult time.
Thank you for understanding my difficulties.
Thank you.
Xie Jingshu.
Do you know I feel so lucky that
God has let us meet each other?
I go on living
for the sake of you.
Only with you
can I have the meaning of life.
How did you know that it was just a temporary expedient
for me to go back to Du Shaoqing?
When you returned to the capital that day,
I thought of the fragrance powder on the way to Pingzhou.
Therefore, I could guess part of the reason why
you went to see Mr. Yunshan.
But Du Shaoqing and Mr. Yunshan were trying to provoke you.
You still felt angry in the end.
Yes.
I knew they were trying to provoke me,
but I couldn't help being suspicious.
That's human nature.
However, if others hit me or scold me,
I can bear it.
Only you, Li Mengjue,
hurt my heart
and made me unable to recover again.
Xie Jingshu.
You're a descendant of the royal family
and a marquis that rules many people.
How would I be the only one by your side?
It's enough to have you only.
I thought I could protect you,
but you were still put into prison because of me.
Now that you and I are trapped here,
I'm worried that I won't have a chance to tell you.
Li Mengjue.
Remember.
My...
My love for you
will last forever.
Xie Jingshu.
I'm here.
My love for you
will remain unchanged.