[The killer bride]
[Episode 10]
One month ago,
I received a secret message that Sui Feng was coming to Tingcheng.
So I came.
To ensure your safety,
I gave you the assassination order
so that you could come to Tingcheng
and me.
Yao.
How could I have forgotten all of this?
How could I have forgotten the murderer who killed my mother?
I deserve to die.
I really should die.
Yao, don't be like this.
You have tried.
You sought revenge against him.
You almost lost your life.
As long as we're both alive now,
we still have a chance for revenge.
No matter what happens,
I will always be by your side.
But...
I don't remember anything about us.
If I can't remember in the future,
will you resent me?
No,
I've thought about it.
If you don't remember me,
I will still seek revenge against Sui Feng.
Then,
I'll try again
to make you fall in love with me again.
This way,
we'll have new memories.
Thank you, He Yunxing.
So they have such deep feelings for each other.
No wonder He Yunxing would rather die than marry me.
However,
this also shows that I didn't misjudge him.
You're back.
I, a noble princess,
have never taken care of someone's daily needs.
That damn Gu Shaozhen,
making me personally apply medicine for him every time.
I'm exhausted to death.
Yueyao.
Yueyao!
Are you alright?
Changning.
I know you like He Yunxing very much.
But if I can't help you anymore,
you won't blame me, will you?
Hey, no one can really control
the matters of feelings.
I admit my attitude towards you wasn't good at first,
but later I saw how sincerely you helped me several times.
I know that.
It's okay.
If we can't be lovers, we can still be friends, right?
Besides,
this time I came,
I gained you as a good sister.
Changning is so open-hearted with me,
and He Yunxing's feelings for me are so deep.
What should I do now?
Yueyao,
what are you thinking about?
I'm also very happy to have you as such a good sister.
I didn't expect you to be so carefree.
But when I think of that damn Gu Shaozhen,
I can't be so carefree.
Yueyao, you don't know how annoying he is.
He sticks to me every day and I can't shake him off.
[Prison]
Tell me, Xu Yun'er,
what's your real purpose?
I'm just a vain woman,
who wants to be a general's wife,
living a glamorous life,
with endless money to spend.
Is that wrong?
You don't want to tell me the truth, do you?
I certainly have ways to make you talk.
Soul-controlling incense.
You should be quite familiar with it.
It's Sui Feng's secret drug.
I've heard
it can make people spill everything they know.
Today,
I'd like to give it a try
to see if it's really that effective.
Tell me,
did you kill General He
and frame Qiao Niang?
Yes,
it was me.
Let me go!
That day,
I originally intended to find He Yong
to force him to reveal the whereabouts of the border defense map.
I happened to see Qiao Niang stab He Yong.
Honey.
Save me, Honey!
What are you doing?
Honey.
Tell me,
where is the border defense map?
Honey.
I used too much soul-controlling incense,
causing He Yong to go insane
and tear out his own heart, leading to his death.
Then I took Qiao Niang's cloud gauze cloak,
copied her face,
created a disguise mask,
and framed Qiao Niang.
Are you Sui Feng?
Did you kill my mother?
Yao!
Yao, calm down, please calm down.
I've told you
everything I can.
Let...
Let me go, please.
Are you Sui Feng?
Tell me!
Yao,
she's not Sui Feng.
Calm down.
Tell us, where is Sui Feng?
I...
I don't know.
Jiu Feng!
Yes.
Take her away.
Don't let her die.
Yes.
Yao,
Yao, calm down, please calm down.
How could they torture my mother like this?
How much pain you must have been in, Mother.
Yao.
Take a moment to compose yourself.
Yao!
Brother Yunxing.
When I grow up, can I be your bride?
Of course.
This is for you.
Is it pretty?
It's beautiful.
From now on, I'll keep this sachet
with me always.
Mother!
Don't run!
What's wrong with you, Mother?
Yao.
You must
live well.
Mother.
Mother!
Mother, don't leave me!
Mother.
Mother!
Quick, protect the master!
-Go after them!
Yao.
Are you alright, Yao?
Brother Yunxing.
I swear
I must kill Sui Feng
to avenge my mother.
Alright.
Yao.
I promise you.
I will definitely avenge you.
Brother Yunxing!