But don't go
We will never know the truth
Miss Chunyu Mr. Gao Xuan
hello
Been waiting for a long time
you know us
Information about contracted players
I received it early in the morning
You two, please come with me
This way
Come here please
You two, please take a short rest here.
Drinks and desserts in the buffet area
Please enjoy
Please follow later
Guidance for staff
Enter the signing room to sign the contract
Thank you
You should have discovered it too, right?
Game content in the promotional video
The version we actually experienced
completely different
Like the version we played
Beautified version
And the general signing meeting
Usually it's done with great fanfare
This signing will be very low-key
Hello you two
Please take a look at our brochure first
Why did you come in anyway?
Hello
no real content
What's wrong, Chunyu?
It's OK
Hello you two
You two, please come with me
please
Because it involves company secrets
Before I ask you two to enter the cubicle,
put the phone
Put it in the small basket at the door
come please
Please take a seat, both of you
Two people in our game
Under comprehensive evaluation
The ranking is relatively high
I didn’t expect that we were still friends in private.
As a good friend in the game
In fact, it is very advantageous
I'm sorry
Let's make a long story short
let us come over
Is it to sign a contract?
Yes
How long have you been alive in the game?
more than twenty hours
got to be us
Opportunities to sign up as experience officers
As a contract experience officer
You can unlock it in the game
More exciting levels
One more thing is great
Players who cleared the level
can get a sum
generous bonus
Who wants your bullshit bonus?
I want my brother
Sir, don't be impulsive
We have something to discuss
It’s easy to discuss something
Does what you say work?
Call your leader over
I've already told our manager
The manager said he would be there soon
please calm down
back off
Manager Zhang
good good good
Mr. Zhang Tianqiang, right?
I'm the manager here
My name is Zhang Yunfeng
What are your demands?
You can tell me
Let me ask you something
What does your company do?
What a bullshit game
Dead in the game
Reality will also be comatose
right
Where did you hear this rumor?
You don’t care where I heard it
Besides, this is not a rumor.
Let me tell you
My request today is very simple
First put my brother
Hei Er, give it back to me
then take my brother
Wake up A Yong
Then give us three brothers
a compensation payment
You two can rest assured
we are one
A very disciplined company
If there is no problem with the agreement
Just two of you, please
Signed this player agreement
Let's go next
I have a question
please speak
People who died in the game
what will happen
There won't be anything
Just log out and exit
Disqualified as a player
Those players just now
This is also the case
It's just that they think
The game is very exciting
Still want to come
Trying to get a chance to play again
Then why do some people
die in game
in reality
I'll be unconscious forever
it never happened to us
this situation
Will it
is caused by other reasons
you know
If the game causes coma
We called it quits long ago
I won't continue testing at all.
What about Hei Er?
where is he
I tell you
You can't do this
Today you
telephone
Hello
Hey Brother Qiang
Black Er
Hello
you where have you been
Lost your phone in the hospital
You don’t want it anymore
Bought a new mobile phone
That crap is useless
I just threw it away
I knew it
Then where are you now
In Linshui
What are you doing in Linshui?
I've done something wrong recently
Come out and hide for a few days
I want to tell you
But when I left that day
Look at you two sleeping soundly
I can't wake up no matter how I scream.
What a bullshit emergency
You go out now
Don't even say hello to me anymore
Can't talk about this
and
You should also keep it a secret from my brother first.
I'll hide for a few more days
I'll talk to you in detail when I get back.
Your brother has fallen ill
He is now
I'm busy first
Bye bye bye bye
Hey Hey hey
This brat
This is so urgent every time
Mr. Zhang Tianqiang
Put the knife down first
Let's talk slowly, okay
You can't solve the problem like this
So does he
Lost player status
As for where he is
Just ask your friends
Zhang Tianqiang
That's Brother Qiang
He should know better
In the game at the same time as Hei Er
The person who died is
Him
He is our engineer Xiao Li
He is in all players
when the game starts
Play a role for only three seconds
The tragic character who just went offline
That is for everyone
It just increases the sense of crisis
By the way, he's outside
How about I ask him to come in?
Verify what I said
No, I've seen it
As for what you heard
That person is with our company
Somewhat festive
That's why he said that
In fact, this matter is very simple
Wait two days
As soon as A Yong wakes up
You can know it all
It has nothing to do with our game anymore
A Qiang
Lao Lin, why are you here?
Okay, you two
we can talk
Signing details are up
good
please follow me
be smart
Don't be so honest
Signed the contract
Wait a moment
Because it involves company secrets
please before entering
Put your phone in this little basket
Thank you for your cooperation
If there is no problem
Just two of you, please
Sign this
Sorry
I have a question
How did we get in?
of this game
Try on your helmet
at the beginning
The system records
your player status
Time to start the game
will automatically enter
Automatically enter
When we enter the game
not wearing a helmet
Yes
This is our latest technology
Let the players do it
Completely immersive experience
so
No need to wear a helmet after that
can
Entered the game smoothly
latest technology
What's the principle?
If according to what you just said
This technology is difficult to implement now
You said it's hard to do
but not impossible
this is us
What makes this game unique
Our R&D team
Overcame technical bottlenecks
completed this
Works that span the ages
As internal beta experience officers, you
He also witnessed it with us
The birth of this work
Of course
Specific technical methods
It’s our company’s patent
This is to be kept secret
But as a player
Just enjoy it
The game is exciting on it
What if we don't sign?
I sign
why not sign
don't think about it again
After all, this game is quite difficult.
I don't care about the difficulty of this game
I just want to know
When can I get this?
Do not worry
As long as you pass the level, you will be given a bonus
That's right. I told you earlier.
Just this contract
Then I don't have it
Yes, this is company policy
Then let me take another look at your contract.
good
Just look at it
That handsome guy
Go get me a glass of water
good
Of course
this is your right
But I still sincerely hope
Think about it again
I think you are usually
He must be playing games
Must know
what does this game mean
how wonderful it is
its experience
Are these
Can't it attract you?
our staff
Everyone has seen the video Chunyu
your reaction in the game
your sense of timing
your wit and courage
All proved
You are the best for this game
Don't you think
You are on the nineteenth floor
Can you realize your greater self?
Besides, you can still get it by clearing customs
a generous bonus
Thank you. I won’t sign.
I won't sign either
What about your gaming experience?
That's the end
Very sorry
Quiet
spring rain
why are you here
I'm here to sign a contract
you signed
Ms. Qingyou
Have you considered it?
To sign or not to sign
So the strong
Willing to be with stronger people
so what you mean is
I should become stronger
Rather than drag her down
I want to become stronger
to be her only one
best friend
No need to think about it
I sign
Walk
what are you doing
Bring back the agreement
This game is so dangerous
Don’t you know? You can’t sign
Let go
It's my own choice
I make the decision myself
The friendship between these women
Just so plastic
Can't say that
What's up
I sign
good
Come
This is a killing two birds with one stone
Can play games again
Can you still get a bonus?
I also sign
actually
You didn't need to sign just now
Then you don’t need to sign it.
I'm not doing it for Qingyou either
I just want to know
the truth behind
Me too
Who makes me curious?
It's raining
grandma
I wanted to ask when will you come back?
Prepared today
But it’s all what you like to eat
Let me show off to you
Look, look
This
Grandma, I'm sorry
I forgot
I have something going on here
I won’t go back now
You, what's going on?
Are you doing this for grandma again?
Whose car are you sitting in?
I'm in the taxi
Grandma, if I really have something to do, I will
Xiaoyu can’t do it anymore
No more, Xiaoyu
grandma
It's raining
Master, let's turn around
Shannan Road
master
How soon can we arrive?
Can be there in five minutes
grandma
Just tell me
Are you surprised?
Hello grandma
It's raining
You have such a short time
You have a boyfriend
It works
grandma
Just be fine with your health
good
If there's nothing else to do, we'll leave first
what did you say
What does it mean to come early?
It's better to come by chance
Grandma has just prepared the meal
You guys are here
What the Greedy Cat said
Just you two
Slow down, grandma
Come on, come on, sit down, sit down
Okay, come, sit, sit, sit
Even your grandma doesn’t know how to do it
What to cook
Just make do with it.
It looks delicious at first glance
Really good at talking
Everyone has come
Have a meal with your grandma
It won't take too long
You said you were standing there
What are you still doing?
Don't hurry up yet
Bring those bowls and chopsticks
Go, go
Really
Come, come, sit down
Come, come, come
good
Child, what is your name?
Grandma, my name is Gao Xuan
I'm in Chunyu's class
Substitute teacher for computer class
Just call me Xiao Gao
Senior Xiao Gao
Xiao Gao
That soup is almost ready
I'll go take a look
OK
You sit down first. You sit down first. Okay.
light rain light rain
Let me tell you
I'm looking at this kid so well
If you like it
Grandma, I will use both hands
support support support
What are you still dawdling about there?
You go there quickly
Waiting there
How embarrassing you say
It's been a few days
Lao Yang’s decoration style
I can't chase you back
You three brothers
Forget about getting paid
I said
Yang, let me tell you
No matter what happens today
Please pay me back the money
Did you hear that?
No, no
This old Yang is so scary
I was beaten out like that last time
It's so shameless
Come on, Hachijo
Hang up
Come on, whose turn is it?
Gojo
no
Take a long-term approach
get rich
Have you made a fortune?
Change one to seven cakes
bump
Quick, quick, wait a moment
Get a bottle of mineral water
three pieces
come across
Twenty thousand
dad
Your kid doesn't go to school
What are you doing in my store?
Dad, today is Sunday
Is it Sunday today?
yes
Really?
Sunday
You go home and play on Sunday
Don't hang around here
Let's go back
dad
Will you pay me my living expenses for this past week?
Eighty thousand
and
Card 80,000
I'm playing mahjong here
What money do you want?
You don’t know that playing mahjong costs money
Am I on target?
No, you are afraid of me
I won’t give you living expenses
and you
Go home and wait
I'll touch a few of them in a while
I'll go back
Go and disappear
It's actually his father
God help me
Don't be angry
The same to you
Transfer an account via WeChat and Alipay
Isn’t it over?
Let the kids run for a while
That's all nonsense.
I do not need
Yang Bawan
Big brother
why are you here
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Brother, slow down, slow down
How did you find this place?
There's no place I don't know
Slow down
What's up
I tell you
From now on you every night
will be dragged into one
In a game called Nineteenth Floor
Can't escape
Of course
I still want to see her
Who are you meeting?
No, what are you having fun with?
Don't you think it's dangerous?
Yes, yes, it's quite exciting.
Are you irritating?
What a fool
I'm afraid you don't know
You died in the game
What will happen to you in reality?
In reality, this is offline
will become a vegetative state
Lying in the hospital
I can't move, I can only breathe
You do not believe
Brother, let me lend you a photo.
Embarrass this silly Baitian
This money counts both of us
We want to come back together
look
This is my brother Ayong
He was on the previous level
He died in this game
Still lying in the hospital now
Comatose
If you don’t believe what I say
You can ask Chunyu
How could this happen?
they all know
No wonder
At that time they had been
remind me to be careful
I won't talk nonsense to you anymore
Your dad owes me money
I want you to help me
OK OK
He is at the mahjong parlor
Let me help you call him
I said I want your help
Do you want your help like this?
What if I can't help you?
Then I'm in the game
kill you
If you're done eating, then take it away.
Grandma will make you a pot of tea
Grandma, let me help you
No need, no need, iron it, iron it
hot
Grandma, I'm coming
sit down
good
grandma
When Chunyu was a child
Smiling so happily
do you think
Our family Xiaoyu
That character is a bit weird
No, Chunyu is pretty good.
That's good
That was what she called it when she was little
A good one
Enthusiastic and generous
So sensible
My name is Chunyu and you?
Laughing every day
i have seen her
what did you say
No I said
Chunyu is doing well now
Actually
She looks like this now
When she was eleven years old
It has something to do with the car accident
That car accident happened that year
She hurt her head
Plus during that car accident
Her mother is gone
This incident greatly stimulated her
since then
I never dare to follow her again
Mention things from childhood
Afraid of irritating her
So that's it
Also blames her father
This unsatisfactory thing
You said mom is gone?
Dad doesn't care about her yet
It won’t be another two or three months
No more living expenses
Even her college tuition
Not even given
What a shame
Right
I still have to call her dad.
good
You, sit down first, okay
When my daughter goes to college, no one shows up.
This dad did it
What's wrong, Chunyu?
Why is Tianji's pen here?
grandma
Where did this come from?
This is what I give you
I saw it when I was cleaning the room.
it's out of water
I feel useless
I just threw it away
Grandma, please sit down first
Is something wrong?
Someone has entered my room
who would do this
Why?
This one looks familiar
Except Tianji
Where else have I seen
It was Dr. Jia who took me there
He sat in his office for a while
Dr. Jia
My doctor during the car accident
He also has this pen with him
boss
not found
Information about him
come back
good
Your illness is not serious
The order has been opened
Remember to take medicine on time
Come here every month for a review
ok ok
Thank you Dr. Jia
Dr. Jia
Please come to the nurse's station with me
good
a neurosurgeon
What does it have to do with Tianji Neng?
Even if there is
But they
Why put a doctor?
Here it is
Could it be said
Player is unconscious
It really has something to do with Tianji
They need a doctor to help
Only then can we get over this matter
master
Don't stop yet
I've already opened the order
Take medicine on time
Every month
Come and review
i exposed
knew
Finish it as soon as possible
behind that
Do not worry
I have arrangements
You should rest for a while first
Classmate, what are you doing?
This is a girls dormitory
Aunt
I'm in a hurry
Looking for spring rain and tranquility
Can you call them for me?
Find someone
Why don't you call someone first?
I hit
She didn't answer anyone
One is turned off
Which room is it in?
which which
Which major
Security department?
There is a male classmate here
I want to force my way into the girls dormitory
No no no don't don't don't
Auntie, I was wrong. Wrong.
Wrong Wrong
I'm leaving I'm leaving
Play this game with me
You are still a little young
Mimi
So good
you know too
I'm good to you
Just be nice to me
If only I could be stronger
Will she
You can also be nice to me
Quiet
you are here
why are you here
I came to find you
long story short
Do you know who Doudou is?
Doudou in the game
Yes
do you know her
Is she from our school?
Don't know
What are you looking for her for?
Tell her she died in the game
In reality, I will fall into a coma.
who told you
look
You also know
you all know
You just won't tell me
Brother Qiang told me
His good brother Ayong
Isn't it because of this?
Still in the hospital now
Are you unconscious?
So I have to hurry now
Go tell Doudou
Stop playing this game
We should choose the weakest
died in the game
In reality, I will fall into a coma
let me out
You don't deserve to be with them
are you okay
Why do you look so bad?
I don't know Doudou
I have something else to do
I go first
No, don't, don't, don't go.
Does Chunyu know her?
Please help me ask
spring rain
so
Me and the injured kitten
Same
They can all be discarded, right?
No