Chun Yu Chun Yu, listen to me
You can do it
I trust you
spring rain
let's do it again
Mr. Yan
It's time to start the game
No
next level
Need to be remodeled
At this time
We can get straight to the point
Let's take a break tonight
good
Why
This would be dangerous
Actually I used to
Be a member of Micro Technology
Because I can't stand it
what they did
Just resigned and left
But if the secret
Know I'm helping you
I'm in danger
Understood
I'll keep it secret
Important equipment of microtechnology
It should be at device two
receive
Do you know Chun Yiming?
Does he have anything to do with all this?
Didn’t enter the game again last night
Yes
Why didn't you get in again?
Xu Wenya
wake up quickly
What are you doing?
Not in the game again
Yes
Why haven't you entered the game again?
no
I've put on my jeans
Why are you not in the game again?
Why
Will it be like last time?
Something went wrong with the system
Probably not
They have completed
Our information
that's why
Are you giving us a day off?
Dream on you
They all started yesterday
Following us
It's definitely not that simple
Are you holding back some big move?
no matter what
We still follow what we said yesterday
Business as usual, be careful
good
Right
Didn’t you say that we need to investigate carefully?
What progress have these two great masters made?
spring rain
Is there any progress?
nothing
Chunyu said there was no progress yet
I don't have it yet either
Senior
Just now Teacher Zhao
When introducing the Turing test
the movie mentioned
What's it called?
Ex Machina
Okay, I'll look at it another day
By the way, there's another one
A biographical film dedicated to Turing
called the imitation game
Quite good looking
Highly recommended to you
spring rain
Sorry
Is class over?
The library is newly opened
A good coffee shop
Do you want to go together?
I still have classes
Which building is it? I'll take you there.
No
You give it to your junior sister
Answer your questions
no
answer
Sorry
Let’s communicate next time
I have something else to do
Okay, senior
spring rain
Sorry, I got the wrong person.
It's OK
In the context of the new era
Spiritual culture of the elderly
and learning needs
Faster growth
Show differentiation and diversification
multi-level features
Facing the new situation
New requirements, new challenges
What about the traditional education model for the elderly?
completely unsatisfied
Personalization for seniors
Diverse learning needs
and higher quality requirements
We need more innovative
Elderly education model
Open a new model of education for the elderly
inspire seniors
Passion for active learning
Expand new forms of education for the elderly
to change their quality of life
develop their intellectual abilities
Enrich their spiritual world
Make it easier for older people to integrate
Rapidly developing technology
modern society
for them
able to engage in
Meet the requirements of the times
Facilitate social activities
At the same time
And in line with their age level
and physical characteristics
Where are you
Lao Lin
Let's take a moment
Going to the supermarket to buy something
Do you want to come together?
You go ahead
I will be with my wife and kids soon
Pass a video
That's OK
Anyway, you are alone in the dormitory
Just take care of hygiene
Clean it up
He said he had to check at noon
Didn't you go to the supermarket?
Forgot my cell phone
You're so sneaky
What good stuff are you looking at?
Not authentic anymore, Lao Lin
You good thing
Let's share it with everyone
you let go
you
I just said this
Do you want to video chat with your wife?
You're not going to pick it up when it comes
Wife
Lin
Who is that vixen?
What did you say?
Stop playing dumb with me
I ask you
Where did the money in the passbook go?
What passbook
I don’t have a bankbook with me
Our family’s bankbook
Card folded into one
The bankbook is here with me
The bank card is on you
If not for the day before yesterday
Transfer living expenses to my daughter
I didn’t know I was missing eight thousand yuan.
this money
I didn't spend it on myself
I just bought a computer
Come
Come to invoice
Did you see it?
invoice
What do you need a computer for?
For my daughter
I was thinking
Waiting for her birthday
Take it out again
give her a surprise
I can prove this, sister-in-law
This old Lin
hide the computer
No one will see this
Did you hear it?
Okay
We still have to go to the supermarket to do some shopping
Hang up
Finally I can watch blockbusters
Stop moving
Go, go, go
Aren't you going to the supermarket?
You go quickly
Mr. Yan
as you wish
New game level completed
Can be started immediately
Make sure nothing goes wrong
Fighting and killing is so boring.
Next
Let's try it out
People's hearts
Hello you are
My husband has been missing for three days
His name is Chen Jianzhang
He is the medical director of Guangming Hospital
This is my ID
This is proof of our relationship
Since he took leave two days ago
Just lost contact
No one answered the phone
He told me that he wanted to go back to his hometown
but not at all
His ticket purchase information
My family didn’t say anything either.
Didn't see him go back
OK please wait a moment
You said your husband
Which department is the medical director of?
neurosurgery
This way
your message
We have completed registration
As soon as there is any news
We will contact you promptly
You go back first
Still have to try hard
Get in touch with your husband
Thank you
Guangming Hospital
Or neurosurgery?
no
I have to inform the Leaf team immediately
The relationship between this hospital and Tianji
Not simple
Good morning
Hello, senior engineer
Right
There is one thing I want to trouble you with
Is there a map of the company?
Can you send it to me?
Our company has so many offices
I'm afraid I went wrong
OK
Already sent to your email
Pay attention to check
OK thank you
You are welcome
Understood
I'll keep it secret
Important equipment of microtechnology
It should be at device two
morning
Sure enough it's here
Gao Xuan
Nian Sulan
why are you here
We will meet each other wherever we are destined.
Right
What are you doing in Building 1?
new engineer
Shouldn't we be working in Building 2?
yes
I was just thinking
Come and visit the laboratory
I am also very interested in the laboratory
How about I go with you?
It's okay, no need
OK
If it doesn't take up your time
no delay
Okay, sorry to trouble you.
Manager Tang
miss nian
Come, come, come
welcome
Come
Please come inside
Unexpectedly, Miss Nian
Will you come to visit us?
I've heard it from my dad a long time ago
The laboratory is particularly interesting
I came here specially to take a look today
It’s not really a laboratory.
Just one
Device Management Center
It doesn’t matter
Right
Take me, senior, quickly
Look around
OK
I don’t know about senior engineers
Which part of our place
More interested
To be honest with you, Manager Tang
I'm interested in everything
I might have to trouble you
You are welcome
That's it
Our equipment center
The main job
Divided into three parts
One
Is the management of daily office equipment
Two
Is the management of R&D equipment
Three
It is the management of self-developed equipment
By the way, senior engineer
Look at what you have besides these
Anything else you want to know
You just said self-developed equipment
I quite want to
Learn more about it
This one
What about self-developed equipment?
involves some
company secrets
I'm afraid it's not very convenient
OK, I know very well
Then I'm sorry
This way
Take a look here
okay
OK
Manager Tang
You stay
Let's go first
good
That year the young lady walked slowly
Senior engineer walks slowly
Sorry to trouble you
good
good day
Because there are beautiful people around me
This sugar is so sprinkled
Likely
I'll kill you single guy
Nian Sulan
There is something
I want to say sorry to you
What's up
Today I was
I want to visit the equipment department
But because there is no reservation
So I can't get in
I took advantage of your identity
This shows
I'm valuable to you
I didn't mean that
I want to say
I won't use you again in the future
What's this
I don't mind
What I like is Chunyu
Sorry
sister
Sister, why are you here?
Is it still like that?
Don't you like music?
Xiao Xian
Did she force you to do so?
I was lazy as soon as I left
She is more talented than you
The tip of the sword must be accurate
move forward
good
sword tip
Pay attention to the rhythm
good
Back Back
Pay attention to the rhythm
Pay attention to the fast pace
Be more fierce. Be more fierce.
fierce
yes good
right
insist
Rest for ten minutes
what are you playing
I'm playing a game console
do you want to play
Look, this is us
let's avoid them
Hit them too
Click this Click this
Click this and we can move
Click four keys
Any key will do
See if it's moving
Let me tell you, this is really fun
Nan Xiaoqin
You've had enough rest
Isn’t it ten minutes?
enter
sword tip
Pay attention to the tip of the sword
retreat
enough
pick up the sword
continue
We are not your substitute
We are not here to make amends
your regret
This path is yours to choose
I'm just
I just don't want to disappoint you
so many years
i never have
past myself
All I have is you
I have already paid
It cost me a leg
I won't let you again
use your dreams
crush another youth
Xiao Xian
you tell her
What you want to pick up is not the foil sword
It's the guitar
Walk
sister
I don't want to disappoint my mother
The decision my mother made for me
Must be the best
in addition
if something happens
Make mom happy
I'm willing to try
She chose this path herself
After your father resigned
It's never been touched here
Haven't cleaned in months
The gray is a bit big
spring rain
Where is your father?
Is one of the founders of the company
So we kept
this office
It's also respect for him
after he left
Is there no news about him?
He left too suddenly
Didn't say the reason
But it's always been the same here
Take your time and watch
hope to find some
his clues
Thank you
spring rain
Keep an eye on your Gao Xuan
The alumni group has exploded
Everyone is spreading the word
Say they made it official
Take good care of your family, Gao Xuan.
Who?
Latest model
What happened to your brother last time
I went a little too far
It's a compensation
Don't look down on it
What about live broadcast?
you arrive
Senior sister
What do you want from me?
No one else in the dormitory is here
do you want me to
Keep an eye on her for you
If it's not troublesome
Just take it easy
I'm sorry
Chunyu is my friend
i can't help you
Don't, don't, don't
This is a small gift
Or you can give me something as well
We reciprocate politely
This won't work
this game it
game
Could it be Gao Xuan and Chun Yu?
The one we play with, right?
Yes
I'm in that game too
But this game
Okay, Okay
That's it
You keep the perfume
I took this
I
I also have this helmet
What's so great
Anyway, I reminded you
So angry
How is it
Isn't this better?
Xiaoqin
why are you so late
I've been waiting for you for a long time
what do you want to do
wrist braces
I gave it to you
what happened yesterday
I was wrong
I apologize to you
Don't be angry with me, okay?
never mind
Just want to stay by myself for a while
I'm going back to the dormitory first
You go
Xiaoqin
What are you talking about?
My own helmet is better
It turns out that Gao Xuan and Chunyu
Just playing this game
I am
Entered the game
spring rain
You must have many questions in your mind
Only continue
Only you can know the answer
spring rain
Lin Uncle Lin
you
Did you see anyone else?
No
just me
Did you hear that?
what's the sound
no
What does it smell like?
What a broken place
wet
Is anyone there?
Senior, are you there?
Senior Gao Xuan
who
Don't, don't, don't
it's me
Eighty thousand
Acting all day long
Are you annoyed?
No, I'm not pretending
I just walked out normally
shut up
don't want to talk to you
what is this place
nuclear bomb base
Xiaoqin
is it possible
The scene in this level
is the most anti-human
731 black sun
Sprained ankle
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
Can't leave
Can't leave, Xiaoqin
Sprained ankle
What's up
Are you okay?
It's okay
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
It hurts me so much. It hurts me so much.
It hurts so much. It's stuck.
Can't take it out
It hurts. It hurts.
It hurts so much. It hurts so much.
Does it still hurt?
It hurts
Look, it hurts so much that I'm sweating
It still hurts
Then cut it off
Don't
I
not me
Pulled out
Come out Come out
Don't, don't, don't
Don't be angry Don't be angry Don't be angry
I
Xiaoqin, I'm kidding you
This
right
you or else
Don't be angry with me, okay?
Ours
At once
All right
who
Senior sister
Xu Wenya
no
You really came in
I'll just come and experience it casually
Look at the games you are all playing
exactly how
Fine
Let's go then
Lead the way
Senior sister
This game is actually
Very average
Whether it is the environment or atmosphere
tell the truth
Than the games developed by my dad’s company
Far from it
Right
What about the rest
you say
Senior Gao and others
What are you anxious about?
Won't you see me later?
I didn't say I was in a hurry.
I'll ask my teammates what others are there?
All right
What sound?
No, I don’t know
Isn't it just a game?
As for being afraid?
You are too timid
Xiao Gao
What are you looking at?
Nothing, Uncle Lin
You are here
The two of us are at the front entrance
encountered
This
There's a conflict
Take the initiative
OK
They seem to be in front
I'll go find them
spring rain
are you right to me
Is there any misunderstanding?
Yesterday I went to Micro Technology
Something really happened
I also accidentally
Meet Nian Sulan
when she took photos
I have absolutely no idea
Everyone is an adult
you have your own business
I have my own business
Everyone is busy with their own things.
spring rain
Nian Sulan and I
Nothing really
Don't think too much
That's not what I care about
You really don't have anything else to do
Are you going to tell me?
what other things
Walk
Eighty thousand
Were you shouting just now?
no
I thought it was you
That
Where is Xu Wenya?
It’s Xu Wenya
elegant
Senior
Nian Sulan
Great to see you today
Those monsters just now were so scary
i feel myself
Almost dead
monster
What monster are you talking about?
and
Why are you in the game?
I didn't see any monster clearly.
As for games?
I heard this game is very good
you are all playing
So I looked for Wenya
Asked about the game
And this gaming helmet
I already have it
Xu Wenya
How can you be casual
Tell her about the game
That
Did she have to ask?
I wanted to remind her that she was in danger
She ran away without listening
It's OK
How can we call it a game if it's not dangerous?
Say it again
Senior, aren’t you a master?
I'm ready to hug your thigh
Just lie down and win
in this game
But there is no great god
You have to rely on yourself
no problem
I can protect myself
and
Dear fellow students,
You are all veterans
I'm a newbie
I need to trouble you to take care of me
OK OK
Everyone is here
Everyone
Today’s game is actually very simple
Game name
Guess who is lying
game rules
One question and one answer
if lie
severe punishment
Quiz game
sounds like
It's relatively simple
The simpler, the more dangerous it is
Have we suffered too many losses?
That's right
There's no way to escape anyway
Just face it bravely
That's all it can do
Game starts
please first player
Stand in front of the door and start answering
That
Which of us will go first?
Now they all have opinions about me
The situation must be reversed
Then I'll help you out.
Player confirmation
Nian Sulan
I found this
There is someone you hate the most
Please say her name
Of course there is no one I hate
Judgment
lie