[Old House, Beef Noodles 2F, Afternoon Tea,
Wine & Dishes, Private Kitchen]
The famous novelist Zhang Ailing once said
"Love is not complicated, it all
comes down to three words."
"It's either 'I love you', 'I hate you',
or 'let it be', 'how are you'.
'I'm sorry'"
Unfortunately, I can't write about love.
All that's left in life are
various forms of 'I'm sorry'.
[Episode 3 Another Form of Happiness]
♫ Oh, time is a kind thief ♫
♫ Stealing doubts and building up love ♫
♫ My dear, what do you want after dinner ♫
♫ Cake, fruit, or me ♫
♫ Only you can precisely capture ♫
♫ Sour and sweet, the elusive taste of love ♫
♫ Hey, what's on your mind, keeping you awake ♫
♫ Tomorrow's work, and the planned trip ♫
♫ How lucky I am that you've chosen me ♫
♫ To share your present and your future ♫
[VIP Only]
Hey, boss.
That person is here again.
Why does he get to have it and I don't?
Why are you so good to him?
This is from my Boss.
He asked me to prepare this
for your hangover.
I am so sorry
for the trouble I caused last night.
Yes.
Tell me.
Did you take a fancy to our boss?
Didn't you two kiss yesterday?
What exactly happened?
And why didn't he go home?
It seems I really was
a bit too drunk yesterday.
I don't remember anything.
You don't remember?
Are you sure?
May I ask,
has Boss Gu always run a restaurant?
Why are you suddenly asking that?
Do you also think our boss doesn't
seem like a shop owner?
Speaking of which,
actually, our boss doesn't run this shop
for money.
He does it to carry on
the taste of his grandmother
and to make every customer who comes here
feel like they're home.
He was once the leader
in the advertising industry.
Do you know how many people were offering money
for his creativity?
Who knew he would be
affected by rumors and slanders?
There were customers complaining
about him being undutiful to his mother
and the company offered compensation.
Blah blah, so he left in the end.
After leaving, it is as what you see now.
He opened this store.
But where did these rumors come from?
This is the key point.
If it wasn't for that woman…
Anyway.
What? Boss.
Why the big mouth?
I didn't say anything.
I'll go back to work.
Drink this first.
You will feel better.
It smells good.
What is this?
Morning Bell Soup
A sobering dish that has
the effect of relieving alcohol.
After all, you did throw up a lot.
I got you.
I'm so wet.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I embarrassed myself so much yesterday.
Just consider it as an extra experience.
But I also kissed…
If I cared,
I wouldn't be standing here talking to you.
Drink it quickly.
Thanks for that Morris's autograph
You should drink less in the future.
Not only were you randomly kissing people,
but you also brought up so much about yourself.
I, I am really not like this normally.
Why do you say you can't write the third book?
The first book was to commemorate a confession.
The second book was
to commemorate a heartbreak.
For the third book, it seems
there's nothing worthwhile to commemorate.
So, due to writer's block,
I can't write anymore.
Do you think I should change my pen name?
You'll find it.
♫ Oh, it turns out happiness
is also good at disguising ♫
♫ An ambush in the ordinary daily life ♫
♫ My dear, what do you want after dinner ♫
♫ Cake, fruit, or me ♫
♫ Only you can precisely capture ♫
♫ Sour and sweet, the elusive taste of love ♫
When he is working,
he rolls up his shirt sleeves to his elbows.
That will be a total of 1500.
Okay.
He doesn't need a calculator
when settling the bill.
He uses mental arithmetic.
He is accustomed to using a pencil
and his posture of holding a pen
is very good-looking.
Ren.
You should get these things first tomorrow.
Don't be lazy.
Can only buy from the few stores I designated.
Okay, no problem.
He has his own ideas about cooking.
But most of the time,
he only needs to tell others what to do.
By the way, he also likes taking photos.
I wonder what he sees
through that viewfinder.
[Old House, Beef Noodles 2F, Afternoon Tea,
Wine & Dishes, Private Kitchen]
Are you not writing anything today?
My previous draft got rejected.
have to find new inspiration,
I don't have any ideas right now.
Why was it rejected?
The editor said
the characters in my novels are too similar
and they lack innovation.
I don't know what to do either.
Do you want some advice?
Boss, are you helping him?
Do you know how many people were offering money
for our boss's advice?
Consider yourself lucky.
Offering money?
So, is there a charge?
Of course.
Of course not.
Does my boss look like someone
desperate for money?
There's no charge.
But you can treat me to a late-night snack.
[Original Fries]
You said the characters in your works
were very similar.
You were probably projecting someone
into your written characters.
If you can't get rid of that,
your characters will always be the same.
If your creative inspiration comes
from your personal experience,
you need to find another projection subject
to escape your current dilemma.
There are many ways to fold the bluebird.
If you've never seen it before,
you would think that the bluebird
only has one form.
Of course, you might also know how to fold it,
but you're scared to try
because of the difficulty.
Find another projection subject?
Where can I find that?
There are many ways to fold the bluebird.
If you've never seen it before,
you would think that the bluebird
only has one form.
Hello, Dad?
Hey, Li, how's your job hunt going?
I'm still writing novels.
Didn't I send books back for you to read?
Alright, we have received them.
Have you made any money from your novels?
Do you have enough?
I do. You don't need to worry.
The editor is rushing me
for drafts every day now,
and I've also received
quite a bit of royalties.
Alright, you should take good care of yourself.
Okay. I have to go. Bye-bye.
I've made the transfer.
This is the last time.
Don't call me again.
How is the first step folded exactly?
It's okay.
I will learn it once he teaches
me a few times more.
Could it be
that I was stagnating?
You need to find another projection subject
Thinking that nothing can be replaced,
but could it be
that I forgot to put the right person in place?
[The third Flavor]
Jin.
The story of the bluebird tells us
that happiness is often right beside us.
But only those who are willing to provide
without seeking rewards can see it.
If you blindly pursue distant happiness,
no matter what color that bird is,
it will be crushed to death in your hands.
You need to take it easy.
Don't be like your mother.
Just wait patiently.
The bluebird might have just gotten lost,
and it will come.
Luckily you guys weren't
thrown away from back then.
Boss.
What do you think?
I'm trying a new recipe
and let the customers do a blind taste test
Boss.
Haven't I always been a professional
for the taste-testing?
You call it a blind test,
but it must be served to Liu Li.
Is this the taste of home?
It is spot on.
This looks so delicious.
I'll dig in.
Do you like it?
I like it a lot.
You see, I'm so busy eating
that I don't have time to talk.
Every ingredient is exclusively special.
If the food is not finished,
the Chef will be very upset.
Alright.
Different vegetables for different people.
Next time, I'll make what you love to eat.
Happy birthday.
I don't celebrate birthdays. It's not my thing.
From now on, it can be your thing.
The birthday person is the most important.
Is there anything specific you want to do?
Would you be willing to be
the reference for my third book?
♫ I like ♫
♫ The simple life with you ♫
♫ A relationship without expectation ♫
♫ Occasional distance allows us to breathe ♫
♫ And occasionally more intimate than lovers ♫
♫ It's getting late ♫
♫ A couple of guests ♫
♫ Are gradually leaving ♫
♫ This dish is specially made for you ♫
♫ Try it while it's still hot ♫
♫ Stop talking, or the noodles will be cold ♫