The current me
seems to be deeply immersed
in the taste of love.
But I forgot
perhaps this was just a tasting.
[Episode 5 Immersed in the Taste of Love]
♫ Oh, time is a kind thief ♫
♫ Stealing doubts and building up love ♫
♫ My dear, what do you want after dinner ♫
♫ Cake, fruit, or me ♫
♫ Only you can precisely capture ♫
♫ Sour and sweet, the elusive taste of love ♫
♫ Hey, what's on your mind, keeping you awake ♫
♫ Tomorrow's work, and the planned trip ♫
♫ How lucky I am that you've chosen me ♫
♫ To share your present and your future ♫
[Reserved Seat VIP ONLY]
Attack.
Hello, I'm Little Yellow Bird.
Good morning, Mr. Gu.
Sorry.
I drank too much yesterday.
I think you're more approachable
after leaving Old House.
And you're more well-behaved after drinking.
Especially,
when you were sleeping in my bed.
Rest assured.
I won't eat you.
Don't be nervous.
How do you know
I won't be the one eating you?
I don't have much to eat here anyway.
Go ahead.
The best food after a hangover
is a bowl of instant noodles.
Give it a try.
Boss, let me ask you.
Do you still remember what happened
in your restaurant
last night?
Are you talking about
'Who do you like the most?'
'Do you like Boss Gu?'
Or
were they trying to offer me up?
Do you want to ask
that if I still want to be
the reference subject
for your third book?
When I get drunk, I don't lose
my memory like you do.
And I remember
you asked me that question at home,
not in the restaurant.
So, are you willing or not?
I knew you wouldn't change your mind.
Although I've never been
in an official relationship,
those scenes have played themselves
countless times in my mind.
I can certainly master it with ease.
As for the practical experience,
it will just take a few tries.
You sound confident.
Then do you know
what the first step of falling in love is?
What?
You want to gain more
real-life experience, right?
I'll teach you
when the plot requires it.
I'll clean up.
Brother.
You finally thought of me.
I thought you totally forgot about me
after falling in love with that Boss Gu.
Shut up already.
Tell me something.
In your opinion,
does Boss Gu have a lot of dating experience?
Why?
Are you afraid he'll find out
that you're new at this?
No, I'm not.
He is just
a reference for my third book.
It's not like we're in a real relationship.
Dating a lot is a good thing.
At least it'll help you give up
on that teaching assistant who went out
and who knows when he'll come back.
To be honest,
seize the opportunity when it comes.
Even if you've gained nothing in love,
at least achieve something in your career.
That way, your third novel
won't have a difficult birth.
Besides,
I think Gu Jin would make
a brilliant leading character.
Do you still like him?
The protagonist in the book?
I suppose.
I had three years of secret adoration
and two years of heartbreak.
How can there be heartbreak
when love didn't even start?
Everyone has been comforting me all along
telling me not to feel sad about losing it,
but no one has reminded me
that I never had it in the first place.
You must remember.
You are not someone who has been abandoned.
You are someone waiting to be cherished.
Is that so?
Perhaps, I may never see that day.
You must believe
that you are worth it.
No wonder Ren looks up to you so much.
What you've said made me
feel great about myself.
What else did he say to you?
He said that even the worst things
can be sold well when you talk about them.
That's really impressive.
Don't laugh and joke around over there.
Focus on your studies.
Alright, Mr. Gu.
I have a question.
How should I arrange a first date?
The first date?
Go to the movies.
Ren.
What movies can enhance
the love between couples?
Boss, you've asked the right person.
Have you ever heard about
the misattribution of arousal?
The accelerated heartbeat caused
by the hanging bridge
is similar to the tension of a horror film.
So of course, it's a horror film.
But why would you suddenly ask that?
Boss.
You're not thinking of doing
something naughty, are you?
A horror movie.
[Scared stiff]
Why do you want to watch a horror movie?
This way, the relationship
between two people will become closer.
Let's go.
In the environment of a hanging bridge,
fear will cause the heart to beat faster,
giving people the illusion of arousal.
It creates distance,
and the opportunity to shorten it.
The last scene of the movie just now
was really quite scary.
Alright, we're here.
[Old House]
The horror movie we just watched
was really terrifying.
Can you stay with me tonight?
Let's go.
When it's mealtime,
if you can't cook,
should you order takeout or…
Make dumplings.
Making dumplings takes time
and there can be interaction.
Unintentionally,
it can also create
some amorous atmosphere.
This behavior can create a warmer contact.
When two people sit side by side,
it's the most natural contact
in a confined space.
Creating something together
produces a unanimous goal
in a common task.
We look at each other and smile.
Because we remember the next step.
Because we understand what each other wants.
And we have a common expectation.
How should we do it?
What should we do?
How can we wrap it?
Is it big enough?
Is it tight enough?
Your shape and my shape.
Arranged one by one,
they look the same yet different.
Wait for the water to boil
and throw them in.
We stand by the stove shrouded in smoke,
waiting for the moment
when the dumplings are cooked and float up.
Together we examine the fruits
of our combined efforts.
And then
eat them.
I see how it is.
You see, does this process
look a miniature of love?
Cooking dumplings.
Right?
I never knew that cooking dumplings
and falling in love
had such a huge connection.
It seems like I did the right thing
choosing you as a reference.
Please continue to guide me, Mr. Gu.
Okay, eat up quickly.
Aren't you going to answer it?
What?
I told you, that was the last time.
Boss.
Are you okay?
It's getting late. I should go.
Wait a moment.
I have another question.
If my love interest wants to leave in a hurry
and I want him to stay,
what should I do?
Boss.
You're too naive about people's feelings.
You can easily get bullied like this.
Who would bully me?
Don't trust people so easily.
Turns out, my heart can beat so fast
without working out.
♫ It's getting late ♫
♫ A couple of guests ♫
♫ Are gradually leaving ♫
♫ This dish is specially made for you ♫
♫ Try it while it's still hot ♫
If he smiles so happily,
it means he likes the person beside him.
Only when facing someone they love,
would one desire frequent physical contact.
They are constantly creating physical contact.
It's obvious that the man is in pursuit.
You're too naive to the wickedness
of human hearts.
You can easily get bullied like this.
♫ I like ♫
♫ The simple life with you ♫
♫ A relationship without expectation ♫
♫ Occasional distance allows us to breathe ♫
♫ And occasionally more intimate than lovers ♫
♫ It's getting late ♫
♫ A couple of guests ♫
♫ Are gradually leaving ♫
I'm back.
We should grab a meal someday.
[The Fifth Flavor, Ordinary Taste, Nothing Surprising]
♫ Try it while it's still hot ♫
Close relationship.
So if one wants to experience it,
what needs to be done?
They should partake in an activity together
and bring each other closer.
For example…
I know!
We could try hand-building pottery.
Just like that movie,
or like in 'Ghost'.
OH My…
Have you heard of this? You have, right?
Although it's a bit old-fashioned,
it's still a retro romance.
♫ Have you found the secret
hidden in these delicacies ♫
♫ All the sensitivities come from you ♫
♫ Eat it while it's still hot.
Let's continue tomorrow ♫
♫ Stop talking, or the noodles will be cold ♫
You won't have to face all that by yourself.
I'll be there with you.
Tell me honestly, are you truly
in love with that person upstairs?
If one person unconsciously remembers
the other's preferences,
it means that person really likes them.
Then what kind of relationship
do we have now?
♫ I like ♫
♫ The simple life with you ♫
♫ A relationship without expectation ♫
♫ Occasional distance allows us to breathe ♫
♫ And occasionally more intimate than lovers ♫
♫ It's getting late ♫
♫ A couple of guests ♫
♫ Are gradually leaving ♫
♫ This dish is specially made for you ♫
♫ Try it while it's still hot ♫
♫ Stop talking, or the noodles will be cold ♫