Looking for me?
Wanna go somewhere with me tomorrow morning?
Humans have the instinct to create illusions,
making the other person get used to, depend on,
and even fall in love with them.
But what's the next step?
[Episode 6]
♫ Oh, time is a kind thief ♫
♫ Stealing doubts and building up love ♫
♫ My dear, what do you want after dinner ♫
♫ Cake, fruit, or me ♫
♫ Only you can precisely capture ♫
♫ Sour and sweet, the elusive taste of love ♫
♫ Hey, what's on your mind, keeping you awake ♫
♫ Tomorrow's work, and the planned trip ♫
♫ How lucky I am that you've chosen me ♫
♫ To share your present and your future ♫
[Reserved Seat VIP ONLY]
How may I help you?
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
It's probably just an allergy.
It's been a while since I visited the market.
Do you always come this early?
Usually, yes.
- Hey.
- What are you looking for today?
One bell pepper.
Alright, just a moment, please.
And then two portions of lotus root.
Two portions of lotus root, got it.
And one lettuce.
Lettuce, got it.
No scallions today?
Some people don't like it.
Thank you.
Boss.
You're not buying only
what I like to eat, are you?
If one person unconsciously remembers
the other's preferences,
it means that person really likes them.
This sentence is awesome.
I need to write it down.
Don't you want to know my preferences?
When you said I needed a projection object,
I wrote down things
when you were working.
I'm sorry.
I wrote them down without your permission.
Is it very impolite?
I should probably…
It feels pretty good to be noticed.
Liu Li.
You can
do whatever you want with me.
Because I allow you to.
Do you know why?
It's so good.
Don't underestimate this braised dish.
It takes over five hours
from preparation to seasoning.
That's a long time.
Yes, it's like the steakhouses
where the steak sparkles as they pour wine.
If you want it to be flavorful,
you have to spend time simmering slowly.
One step at a time.
This way, the flavor will last long, right?
Do you like this simple taste?
You should have some.
I thought you liked steak.
Did your taste change?
[Old House, Beef Noodles 2F, Afternoon Tea,
Wine & Dishes, Private Kitchen]
Thank you for coming.
Tell me something.
What's with your boss's face recently?
He looks the same.
He has a handsome face, doesn't he?
It's not about the appearance.
He seems really joyful.
You mean that terrifying smile of his?
That's a love-filled smile.
I see, Secretary Yao's leisure activity
is observing other men.
No way.
In my eyes, there has always
been only you, Mr. Xia.
Here are your beef noodles.
Excuse me.
Enjoy your meal.
Use this.
Okay?
Tell me honestly.
Are you using this projection thing
as an excuse to pretend to hook up
with that person upstairs?
There's no excuse.
Or pretending.
Wait a moment.
If it's not pretending,
are you guys for real?
Take care of the place.
I'll go upstairs and take a look.
You're looking for him
only after one day apart.
Eat up.
Boss.
What are you doing here?
Lai gave me a spare key.
I thought you said it was just an allergy.
No.
I'll give you a cold as well.
It seems you really enjoyed
the experience of kissing.
I thought Lai was your friend.
Why didn't he come to take care of you?
Him?
He is busy dating.
He has never been successful yet.
But to have him take care of me?
I might as well be alone.
You don't have to face these
on your own anymore.
I'll be there.
If I cared
I wouldn't be standing here talking to you.
You'll find it.
Just consider it as an extra experience.
From now on,
it can be your thing.
Happy birthday.
How do you know
I won't be the one eating you?
Boss.
You're teaching me to observe love
and taking me to experience love.
Then what kind of relationship
do we have now?
When you get better,
I'll tell you the answer.
Anyway, that's it for the publishing house's
first-anniversary event.
Any problems, Morris?
Morris.
Liu Li?
I'm sorry, Miss Tsai.
What did you just say?
Are you still not over your cold?
Otherwise, why do you look so out of it today?
Miss Tsai, may I ask for your advice?
If someone takes meticulous care of you,
stays by your side when you're drunk,
and even does something foolish with you,
does that mean that person likes you?
Of course.
Why else would they waste their time?
Liu Li.
Are you having some new ideas?
Let me tell you.
The doting words you just mentioned
are much more attractive
than your previous works
of secret crushes or heartbreaks.
The market craves this kind of sweet,
pampering story.
It's healing to the soul.
So is this romance
truly happening
or fabricated?
♫ Sour and sweet, the elusive taste of love ♫
♫ Hey, what's on your mind, keeping you awake ♫
♫ Tomorrow's work, and the planned trip ♫
Is the slowly simmering fondness
easy to get attached to?
No matter how long it takes,
it never feels like a waste.
You're thinking what if time could slow down
or even stop at this moment.
How great would that be?
♫ Oh, time is a kind thief ♫
But there are no what-ifs
in love.
There are buts.
Thank you, Miss Tsai.
Yes, the event went smoothly today.
Also, Happy First Anniversary.
Okay, goodbye.
You're here.
Is there a private event today?
Yes.
Our store is closed to the public today.
The boss will be here soon.
Our shop is introducing beef noodles
French cuisine for the first time.
Just wait here.
When you get better,
I'll tell you the answer.
Boss, where are you?
Liu Li is here.
Gu Jin.
I called you, but you didn't answer.
I sent you a message,
but you read it and didn't reply.
Now that I'm here in person.
I wonder how long you are
going to keep avoiding me.
You've gone from being the advertising director
to Boss Gu now.
What? Have you become more arrogant?
You have money to open a shop
but no money for me?
I'm talking to you.
Look at me.
Do you want to be like your dad?
Leaving me behind
and enjoying yourself with the money, huh?
Every time you come to see me,
you're asking for money.
How much do you owe this time?
What do you mean how much?
I've just borrowed a little money
from the underground lender.
After I make money from my investments,
I'll pay you back with every penny.
Underground lender?
Did you borrow money
from an underground lender?
I only borrowed a hundred thousand or so.
Why are you yelling?
I'll wire the money to you.
But could you please
stop doing this in the future?
I knew my darling son
wouldn't abandon me.
I'll go now.
Bye bye.
It's been a long time.
How have you been?
There are many things that we think we forgot,
but in fact,
they are still there.
I have been following your social media.
Did you notice?
Or are you pretending not to see?
Boss, you're under attack.
That Teaching Assistant is here.
Hurry up. Your seat is taken.
You've changed.
No, I haven't.
I just haven't seen you for a long time,
Teaching Assistant,
so I feel a bit tense.
Teaching Assistant.
You're still calling me that after graduation.
Were you just close by or passing by?
What a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
It was intentional.
It's been two years.
Does this confession still count?
[A Hope Shaped Like a Rainbow]
♫ No need to respond. I understand everything ♫
♫ How I wish to hold you in my arms ♫
♫ To laugh with you and be crazy with you ♫
♫ I'd rather be left in pain ♫
♫ I smile and say, take care ♫
I want to start a new story,
but the old drama drags on.
The chapter I wanted to give up
suddenly continues…
♫ The plot moves forward to
the next section of happiness ♫
♫ Don't bother, don't turn around.
The past is worth talking about ♫
Sorry, Teaching Assistant.
What did you just say?
Let's start over.
This time, I'll chase you.
It was his place originally.
So I should return it.
If you let go now, you'll regret it later.
Do you have something to say to me?
♫ I like ♫
♫ The simple life with you ♫
♫ A relationship without expectation ♫
♫ Occasional distance allows us to breathe ♫
♫ And occasionally more intimate than lovers ♫
♫ It's getting late ♫
♫ A couple of guests ♫
♫ Afraid of leaving ♫
♫ This dish is specially made for you ♫
♫ Try it while it's still hot ♫
♫ Stop talking, or the noodles will be cold ♫