"Love Senior The Series Special EP."
If you knew that your trusted best friend
felt more than friendship for you,
What would you do?
Aof’s laptop is damaged from the impact.
The project files are all in this computer, right?
If we have to redo everything,
it’s impossible to finish in time.
Why wouldn’t it be?
Did you forget?
That you have friends in the same field as you
who can help?
Hi, Gorgeous! P'Lada is here to help!
(P'Warang)
Prang, are you okay?
I noticed Warang seems stressed.
I don’t want to be just friends with you, Warang.
The feelings I have for her,
it’s just friendship and goodwill.
That’s all.
P'Thida,
I have something I need your help with.
I knew you’d be here.
I forget something.
You don’t look okay.
Is it about Prang?
Warang.
These flowers...
The ones you gave me on our graduation day.
You’re still keeping them?
(I don’t want to be just friends, Warang.)
You’re probably wondering
why I never told you about this, right?
The truth is,
I thought of telling you during our first year.
But when I decided to,
you already liked Gyo.
So I figured
there was no point in saying it.
So all I could do was
accept the truth.
Just like I told you before.
That I had so many chances
but didn’t take them myself.
The way..Prang act differently,
because she found out about this.
If you knew that your trusted best friend
felt more than friendship,
What would you do?
I’m sorry.
I forgot about it in the recipe book I gave her.
And I’m sorry
that it’s my carelessness that caused this.
It made Prang feel bad.
You know what?
Prang kept apologizing to me over and over,
even though she did nothing wrong.
I’m the one
who’s at fault.
Thida.
Are you okay?
Of course.
Why wouldn’t I be?
Honestly, I don’t feel that way about you anymore.
After this, I just hope
you’ll be the reason she smile,
just like every day before.
I’ll be the reason,
just like she
is my smile and happiness.
Don’t worry.
Oh.
Also,
she sent some treats for you.
Oh, really?
Then I’ll be off.
Thanks so much.
Good luck.
If you need anything, just let me know, okay?
I don’t need anything
but you.
Yay!
You’re amazing!
Cheers!
Naow, you’re still up?
Is there a problem with work?
No.
I just want to review before presenting again.
If you’re tired, take a break.
P’Waris said everyone can come to work late tomorrow.
Careful, your face will get old.
If I gets old, will you not love me anymore?
Who’s going to let you get old?
Here.
Come on, let me apply this for you.
Aren’t you going to apply it, Gyo?
I will apply after you finishe.
Let me do it for you, then.
Naow!
That’s enough!
Let’s sleep.
Oh.
Where did all the staff go, Belle?
They're all leave.
I don't know why they all took leave at the same time.
Did you bake something and forget about it?
No.
You know I can’t bake.
But it smells like something’s burning, Belle.
P’Warang!
What did you do?
My kitchen is ruined!
It's obvious, right?
Don’t be mad at me, okay?
I’ll clean everything up, spotless, I promise.
And for anything ruined,
I’ll replace it.
As for this cake…
I think you shouldn’t eat it.
I think it’s…
Thank you.
I thought…
you’d forgotten.
How could I forget the birthday of someone I love?
I’m sorry.
For letting you overthink for so long.
P’Warang,
you knew?
Yes.
I found out from Thida.
And I also know
How bad that made my little sweetheart feel.
How much it hurt her.
Prang,
P’Thida and I
are just sincere friends.
No matter what happened in the past,
Thida doesn’t have those feelings anymore.
And now, Thida is genuinely happy
to see us in love.
There, there.
Don’t cry.
Here.
Chocolate cake.
It’ll cheer you up.
And finally make you Miss Overthinking Love.
I was actually going to make a smiley-face cake for you,
because I want you to smile more.
Like this, like this!
Smiling yet?
No more crying, okay?
Alright?
It’s okay.
I already have my smile.
Thank you.
My smile.
Happy birthday,
my love.
I love you, P’Warang.
I love you too.
(The shop is closed today.)
The shop is closed today...
Thank you for helping me last night.
Did you buy treats for the café owner?
If you don’t want it, that’s fine.
I’ll take it.
I was just teasing.
Thank you.
Actually,
that night, I didn’t mean to.
I know.
Even if I tell anyone,
no one would believe me.
It’s my fault.
I’m the one to blame.
I hurt others.
But I’m not evil enough to ruin someone lives.
I believe you.
I believe that you regret everything that happened.
I believe you didn’t mean to.
And I believes,
that P’Tarn isn’t that bad.
Everything you did
was because you loved P’Naow.
I understand.
I have been there,
at the point where you’d do anything
just to be loved by them.
Until you forget
that you need to love yourself too.
P’Tarn, can you try loving yourself again?
Try smiling,
like you used to.
Laugh, like you used to laugh.
Everything
has become just the past now.
Let the old Tarn inside you
come back to life again.
It’s okay.
It’s okay now.
Thank you.
Gyo, are you hungry?
Should I take you to grab food before the office?
Naow, good luck today.
I know you can do it.
If I succeed,
can I ask for a reward?
Alright, stop it, or we’ll be late.
The last day.
What is it?
Not telling.
When you finish presenting,
I’ll announce it to everyone.
Let’s go, or we’ll be late.
It’s the last day for me too.
-The pitching?
-Yes.
-Will they make it?
-They’ve been in there a while.
They worked all night, they’ll make it.
Of course.
Let’s hope it passes.
Hey, they’re coming.
They look so tense.
P’Waris, how was the project? Did it pass? You were in there so long.
I and P'Waris did ours best.
Like, Kirin and Kirin’s partner...
...approved it.
We did it! We did it!
And Kirin immediately approved the project.
Amazing!
Tonight, I’ll take you all to celebrate at Sweetness Café.
Wow!
Naow.
Before the party, let’s check the site first.
I want to wrap this up by the end of the week.
Okay.
Does the party have a theme, P’Waris?
How about a prom night theme?
It’ll fulfill P’Mujji’s childhood dream.
Oh!
Time to dress!
I need time for makeup and hair, so I’m leaving now.
Go, go. See you tonight.
-See you!
-Get ready.
Go, go.
See you at the café tonight.
Don’t forget my reward.
See you.
(You are my senior.)
(I can truly be myself when I’m with you.)
Gyo, look over there! There’s a rainbow!
Hey!
You’re right!
Did you know, Gyo?
If you make a wish on a rainbow, it’ll come true.
Really?
Wow, you took so long. What did you wish for?
I wished for my memories to come back.
I want to remember everything about us.
Good
or bad,
it’s still
The memories between us.
I don’t want them to disappear.
And you, Naow?
What did you wish for?
I’m not telling. If I tell, it won’t come true.
Hey!
That’s not fair!
Not fair!
What are you filming?
Nothing.
Stop!
Stop right now.
Turn it off!
You’re just too cute.
Of course, I am.
Get the camera from me.
Okay.
Gyo.
Gyo, do you still want to know?
What I wished for back then?
I wished to wake up to Gyo every morning.
I wished to fall asleep beside you every night.
I wished for us
to stay together like this forever.
These flowers,
I bought them for you on our anniversary.
I’ve never thrown them away.
I can’t change the past.
But I want these flowers
to symbolize a promise.
That I will love you forever.
Can I replace our bad memories
with good ones from today?
Will you marry me,
Gyo.
Yes.
Congratulations!
So sweet.
Congrats, Gyo!
P’Waris.
So,
about the rule...
Did you really believe it?
So, Naow, you knew?
P’Mujji told me.
Come on.
Want a tissue or my shoulder to cry on?
What’s this?
I happen to be P’Waris’ little junior,
so she invited me.
So, what will it be? Tissue or my shoulder?
About that night,
Tarn, I’m sorry, P’Gyo.
It’s okay, Tarn.
It’s in the past.
Let’s move on together.
Thank you.
For everything.
For all the love you’ve given me.
Thank you, Naow.
Let’s stay together like this until the very end.