We have an annual trip to the hot springs.
I've gotten super close to Ureshino-san
on this trip.
- I'll tell you more later.
- Sure, tell me.
Did you and Ureshino-san use to date?
I got the feeling you weren't just friends.
It's a relationship
you can't describe through words.
But if I said that,
Kusaka-kun would probably loathe me.
I won't hesitate to invite you out
from now on.
If only I could be true to these feelings,
things would be so much easier.
My desires are about to explode.
Huh?
Let me in.
Hey.
Why do you think I called for you?
- "Something" shochu?
- I don't know.
- Let's fix our makeup.
- Okay.
Mihono-san.
Oh. She's already asleep.
Seriously?
She must have been tired.
- Let her sleep.
- Yeah.
That's why I said no!
I wonder if Ureshino-san can drink a lot.
Who knows?
- I wonder what he's like drunk.
- Right?
Any predictions?
- Let's see...
- Hey!
I think he pretends to have a low tolerance,
but drinks a bunch.
- A bunch. I see it.
- Right?
I get that feeling, too.
- All right, I'm ready.
- Me too. Let's go.
All right.
We're drinking tonight!
Yeah!
That was dangerous.
You overreacted.
Unbelievable.
Your phone.
Ignore it.
That's more like it.
Morning, Kusaka-kun.
Good morning.
Sorry about yesterday.
I fell fast asleep.
No,
it's fine.
Um, is your foot okay?
Oh, yeah. I bought a Band-Aid
at the store earlier, so I'm fine.
Thanks.
I see. That's good then.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
- Ureshino-san!
- Oh, good morning, Yuri-chan.
Jeez, what happened yesterday?
Sorry, I fell asleep before I knew it.
We were waiting for you the whole time!
Really? Sorry, sorry.
Please sit.
♫ It's hard to resist the thing
that I've missed for so long ♫
♫ So long ♫
♫ Can't remember what it's like,
Just remember I need it ♫
♫ I need it ♫
♫ Even if I'm wrong,
the train of thoughts I'm always in the right ♫
♫ In the right ♫
♫ Gotta trust the guy,
yeah, no matter what happens ♫
♫ What happens ♫
♫ You're not what I thought you were ♫
♫ You were ♫
♫ To think I can't find a cure ♫
♫ Find a cure ♫
♫ Ooh, you're not what I thought ♫
♫ Thought, thought ♫
♫ Thought ♫
[If Only You Weren't the One]
[Episode 5]
The heat from that day
still hasn't cooled down.
Hey, aren't you staying over too much lately?
Can't I?
Right now, we're closer than
we've ever been.
- Get off me.
- No.
- I can't cook.
- Stir properly.
Hey... This is even harder.
Right.
Oh, this works.
That's why...
Don't look away.
all sorts of things
have become so clear.
You're finally awake?
Yeah. Morning.
Morning.
Your phone was ringing last night, too.
Huh?
Is everything okay?
What's okay?
Is it a girl?
Hmm.
It's nothing like that.
If you have time, eat before you go.
Whoa, looks good.
Huh?
Don't you prefer rice in the morning?
Yeah. I usually do, but sometimes it's fine.
Is that so?
Huh?
What about breakfast?
I can whip up some rice balls or miso soup.
Oh...
Nah, I'm more of a bread guy.
No, it's not like that.
I was in the mood for bread.
Oh?
Come on. I'm serious.
Well, either way is fine.
Let's eat.
Aw, man.
I wonder why we aren't dating.
If I fall for you seriously again...
I think I like you.
You're so cute, Miporin.
I wonder if we'll drift apart.
Hey, walk a bit further away.
What's this all of a sudden?
- Don't cling to me in the office.
- I'm not.
People will find out we came together.
So what? It's fine.
It's not fine.
Good morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Ureshino-san.
- Yes?
Regarding today's meeting with the client,
is the meeting in the lobby at 12 okay?
Sure. It should take about 10 minutes
by taxi, so that's fine.
Understood. I'll prepare the proposal
on my end.
Thank you.
I might be able to get a contract
from my old company.
- Huh?
- They said they're considering a company trip.
It's a pretty big company,
so it'd be a big deal.
Wow. Really? That's amazing.
It's not decided yet, though.
But for now, Kusaka-san and I
are in charge of selling to them.
The two of you?
Yeah.
We'll have to work together
and do our best.
So pyramids are the best for the first day, right?
[Travel Plan]
- Oh, really.
- Regarding the first day...
Well, the weather...
The Karnak Temple
is all the rage this year.
What's there?
- There's an obelisk.
- Oh?
Yes, it is.
You surprised me.
What's that face?
Ta-da! This Friday! Isn't this crazy?
[Dinner with Ureshino-san!]
Hm?
- What? You're having dinner?
- Exactly!
Isn't this awesome? It's crazy, right?
- Did you invite him?
- Yes.
I mustered up all my courage
and sent a message last night,
but he didn't read it.
I thought about erasing the message
a thousand times,
but he replied this morning!
- I see.
- Yes!
- That's great.
- Gosh, I did so well yesterday.
The best thing I've ever done
in the last 25 years!
Now that I think about it,
I bet girls like her are his real type.
With a cute smile, a bright personality,
straightforward, and open.
A pleasant girl.
Not tainted like I am.
A girl who doesn't
put on a hypocritical front.
The one who becomes Eisei's "real love"
is probably a girl like this.
No, I know.
This isn't worth reporting to you.
And Yuri-chan is a really sweet girl.
But Yuri-chan with Eisei Ureshino is a waste.
I'm worried, you know. Why that guy of all people?
But you know, I get it.
He's a handsome guy,
and his smile is to die for.
Yeah, I get it.
I really do,
but his communication skills are awful.
Why's he playing around
just because he's popular?
Well, calm down first.
Okay.
So, in the end, you like him, right?
Huh?
What?
You're scaring me.
Just admit it.
You want to be the main girl of
that playboy with bad communication skills.
To be his girlfriend, right?
Man, I see.
I haven't said anything.
No affirmation speaks more eloquently
than silence.
Sorry, what does that mean?
It's love, right?
- Okay, you admit it.
- No, I'm not admitting it.
I'm not admitting it.
Then, what? Are you playing around too?
No, but...
Well, I'm telling you, I don't know.
First of all,
handle your current relationship.
You know, for the last 10 years,
the same thing's been controlling you.
If you can't tell if it's play or not,
maybe you should distance yourself
from Eisei Ureshino
to figure out your own feelings.
[Eisei Ureshino]
Hello?
Not really.
I had lunch with a friend.
I have time, but...
The more I try to understand,
the more confused I get.
Here I am.
I'm losing...
my ability to think straight.
All right. It's Friday, so let's get drinks.
Yeah, let's go!
- But it's crowded everywhere today.
- True.
- What's for dinner?
- Barbecue!
Oh, yeah!
- It's a sheep.
- Sheep?
Your art's awful. That's so cute.
- But your drawing's worse, you know.
- You think so?
This one's way cuter.
- What about this?
- Maybe I replied.
I'm getting angry.
Really? It's true.
Stop it!
Angry?
No, no.
- I'll redraw it.
- Actually try.
Yeah, I'll be serious.
Onuma-san.
Oh, Kusaka-kun.
- Good work today.
What are you drinking?
Oh, it's coffee. To wake myself up.
I know that feeling.
Maybe I'll get the same.
Um, if you have time,
let's hang out sometime.
Not just a meal after work,
but a movie or something.
What?
I want to learn...
more about you, Onuma-san.
Sorry, that was sudden.
It doesn't have to be a movie, anything is fine.
Food-hopping, visiting an amusement park...
What else?
A cafe?
Oh, a fishing pond, too.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll check my schedule.
Okay.
Oh, it's the section chief.
Yes?
You know,
Kusaka-kun is surprisingly strong mentally.
What do you mean?
He doesn't give up even after that.
After what?
You really didn't notice?
I was seen...
going into your room.
Huh?
Miporin?
Hey!
Miporin!
- Miporin!
- You're too loud!
Just shut up and get in.
♫ We walked through the city at daybreak,
soaked by the rain ♫
♫ You and me in the rain ♫
Miporin, your phone.
Ignore it.
♫ I kept looking at you ♫
That's more like it.
[Kusaka-kun]
♫ Of my hand ♫
You're my partner in crime.
[Preview]
Don't talk to me.
Can't you choose Kusaka?
I've never once heard you say
what you like about Eisei Ureshino.
They say the one
who falls in love loses, don't they?
I wonder, what do I want with Kusaka-kun?
Looks like she got rejected.
Telling her the truth is true kindness.
With both work and love left half-hearted.
What if we actually started dating?
[This drama is fiction.]