We're kind of a special pair, aren't we?
Is it Eisei Ureshino?
You're friends-with-benefits!
If you're free,
maybe we could get dinner together.
If I could fall for someone
like Kusaka-kun, I'm sure...
I could be happy.
Instead of someone like Eisei Ureshino.
Instead of a man like him.
But I don't have plans tonight,
so if you want, how about a meal?
That's great.
I can clock out soon.
Wait for me downstairs.
Oh, it's a promise.
I'll be right there.
How about... a date tonight?
What? Out of the blue?
It's not out of the blue, isn't it?
We're special, after all.
I seriously can't believe you.
You were eavesdropping earlier,
weren't you?
You have a really
nasty personality, you know.
- I can't join you.
- Huh? Why not?
Because I have plans with Kusaka-kun.
Dinner, right?
- I knew it.
- Then, let's meet after.
What?
I'll be at your place, Miporin.
What are you talking about?
It's a promise.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's fine. Good work today.
You too.
- Should we go then?
- Yeah.
This is going to be a lot of fun.
Ureshino-san.
Are you still working?
Yeah. It's not a huge amount,
but I thought I'd try to finish it today.
You're doing great work.
Sorry, we'll be leaving first.
Have a good night.
- Goodbye.
♫ It's hard to resist the thing
that I've missed for so long ♫
♫ So long ♫
♫ Can't remember what it's like,
Just remember I need it ♫
♫ I need it ♫
♫ You're not what I thought you were ♫
♫ You were ♫
♫ To think I can't find a cure ♫
♫ Find a cure ♫
♫ Ooh, you're not what I thought ♫
[If Only You Weren't the One]
What a relief. We got in without a reservation.
[Episode 3]
Yeah, it's such a nice restaurant.
Do you come here often?
No, it's my second time.
I always wanted to come here.
So, before I invited you,
I came alone, just once.
That's so sweet.
I see.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
Not at all. I should be the one thanking you.
- Did I say something strange?
- Not at all.
I'm just so grateful, I couldn't keep it in.
What do you mean by that?
Thank you for waiting. Your appetizer.
Wow!
Wow, looks delicious.
This is incredibly tasty.
- You had it once, right?
- Once.
- Thank you. Let's eat.
- Let's eat.
During the meal, I was...
only thinking about Eisei Ureshino.
I'll be at your place, Miporin.
Eisei's slender yet large hands.
Those deep, dark eyes
that seem to pull you in...
His carefree smile and...
It's a promise.
the words he said earlier.
Sorry for making you pay.
It's fine. I invited you.
But still...
Then, next time.
Next time, let's dine together again.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right! It's a promise.
Ah.
It's raining tonight.
I didn't check the forecast at all.
Please wait here for a moment.
I'll buy an umbrella
at the convenience store.
- I'll go too.
- It's fine.
Please wait here, Onuma-san.
- Thank you.
- I'll be right back.
I'm back.
They were sold out, huh?
I can't take your umbrella.
It was intentional.
Intentional?
Oh, if it bothers you,
I'll go buy another.
I don't mind.
Then, let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
- It's really pouring, isn't it?
- Right.
Thank you.
It's really pouring, isn't it?
Right.
I didn't expect such a downpour.
- Thank you.
- It's my pleasure.
I'm glad.
Kusaka-kun, you said you take the bus, right?
I'm taking the train.
Oh, I'll walk you.
Huh?
Of course, I'll head home
after dropping you off.
Thank you.
But really, we can part ways here.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay, then. Please use this.
Thank you.
I'm sure the girl Kusaka-kun ends up dating...
will be happy.
[November 10, 10:07 p.m.]
Then, let's meet after.
What?
I'll be at your place, Miporin.
That was really fun today.
The food was delicious too.
Kusaka-kun is such a good guy.
Really, a good guy.
I wonder if he found an umbrella.
I hope he doesn't catch a cold.
He's not here. What a relief.
[Thank you for today. It was fun.
Did you get home safely?]
Coming.
Hey there!
Work dragged on longer than I thought...
Huh?
Hm? Miporin!
Miporin?
Miporin!
[Thank you for today.
I had a wonderful time.]
[Did you get home safely?
I hope we can get dinner again!]
Hey.
You're too loud.
Can I come in?
Thanks for having me.
I really hate this about him.
He's so pushy. And self-centered.
Don't yell so loudly outside my apartment.
But you wouldn't open the door.
Wow. I'm getting nostalgic.
I've been thinking about moving for a while,
but it's such a hassle, I keep putting it off.
I know the feeling. My place is the same.
Hmm. Is that so?
Well, I wouldn't know,
since I've never been there.
Oh, really?
Come over next time.
Wow, this bear brings back memories!
This is that bear, right? Non-chan.
The stuffed animal you treasured
since kindergarten, right?
I'm impressed you remember that.
Of course.
I brought cake.
Want some?
Hey, haven't we been eating cake at night
too much lately?
But it makes you happy, right?
Alcohol is fine too.
I figured I'd pick some up.
- Want one?
- Hmm...
I'll pass.
I'm full.
Oh?
What about you?
Did you eat something already?
Yeah.
But whatever.
You're all wet.
You ran back
because you missed me, huh?
Hey.
What did you two chat about?
What did you do with him?
Now, I get it.
Why you always seem
to be having so much fun.
This expression...
I'm sure I have it too.
So...
I won't tell you.
After all, this feels so good...
Morning.
Good morning.
Last night, Miporin,
you were different from usual.
What?
It was really good.
Stop it.
I love how your character switches like that.
Stop it!
Why?
Look this way.
If we were dating, would it be like this?
What about breakfast?
I can make some rice balls or miso soup.
Oh...
Nah, I'm more of a bread guy.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I can't help but laugh at myself.
I don't know anything
about this man, and yet...
Can I use your bathroom?
Oh, sure.
If we were dating, huh?
Hey, could you walk a little farther away?
Miporin, you changed clothes today, so it's fine.
It's not about that. I just don't like it.
You don't?
What? Did you start hating me?
Wow, we were so close until this morning!
You're going to make me really hate you.
So scary.
What I mean is, I hate acting
as if nothing happened,
putting on this phony face.
Oh, that's all that bothered you?
"That's all"?
What?
We're alone now.
Stop it.
Stop what?
Oh, good morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Looks like you had fun yesterday.
Huh?
Onuma-san was gushing about it.
Oh, but she wouldn't tell me the details.
Were you okay yesterday, with the rain?
Sorry, I fell asleep
and saw your text this morning.
It's totally fine.
Did you get home safely too?
Yes. Thanks to you.
That's good then.
Let's go together again
if I find another delicious restaurant.
Okay.
So direct, huh?
Not at all.
You two know each other
from college, right?
That's right.
So, if you're curious about her,
ask me anything.
Hey!
Oh, can I?
Of course.
Right?
You don't know anything about me.
Well, I have to go prepare
for my presentation, so excuse me.
♫ Hold me close, stay by my side ♫
He's so obvious.
Shut up. Stop saying weird things.
Who is?
♫ We wouldn't... ♫
Come on, are you gushing or conflicted?
Which is it?
I'm conflicted. I'm not gushing
even a micrometer.
Then, there's only one answer.
Kusaka-boy's the one.
Well, yeah, that's true.
I know, but that's exactly
why I'm conflicted, right?
Huh? I don't get it.
You're gushing, aren't you?
I'm sacrificing
my precious lunch break for this.
I'm sorry.
I'll treat you to those donuts
you wanted next time.
It's a promise. You have to wait
at least an hour for those.
Yes.
Well, to answer seriously,
it's up to you, Mihono.
I've told you this.
No one can decide this for you.
It's your choice.
Yeah, you're right.
Oh, Mihono-san, there you are!
Yuri-chan, what is it?
Mihono-san, I have a huge favor to ask!
What is this?
- Ureshino-san.
- Here.
- Kusaka-san.
- Onuma-san.
- Here.
- Everyone's here.
- Thank you.
We'll be departing shortly.
Enjoy the journey to Rinkai Hot Springs!
Yeah!
How did things turn out like this?
[Preview]
- Look.
- I had wanted to eat those strawberries.
I'm really getting sick of this.
I just wanted to do
something like this with you.
I won't hold back.
If only I could be true to these feelings,
things would be so much easier.
Why do you think I call you "Miporin"?
What is it that has such a hold over me?
The thrill?
The possessiveness?
[This drama is fiction.]
Or love?