♫ It's hard to resist the thing
that I've missed for so long ♫
♫ So long ♫
♫ Can't remember what it's like,
Just remember I need it ♫
♫ I need it ♫
♫ You're not what I thought you were ♫
You were ♫
♫ To think I can't find a cure ♫
♫ Find a cure ♫
♫ Ooh, you're not what I thought ♫
[If Only You Weren't the One]
[Final Episode]
I like you.
Me too.
The second round.
Let's skip out on it.
Wait, wait.
That's too steamy.
Let me sit properly.
So?
Well...
Hey! Where are you, phone?
Answer me!
Whoa, what are you two doing?
Oh, um...
Oh, so the rumors were true!
- I bet you both are skipping the party!
- No, that's...
What are you talking about?
We came to help you find your phone,
since you were so upset!
He's right.
- Oh, is that it?
- Yeah.
- You guys are so thoughtful.
- Right?
- That's amazing.
- I know, right?
I'll call it now.
I wonder where it is.
Oh, that's a good sign.
- It's over there!
- Here?
Right there!
Ouch...
I sat up for nothing.
So, what happened next?
- Karaoke until morning.
- Yep, that's annoying.
So now Miporin's greeting the new year
feeling frustrated.
It's as you say.
Well, that basically means...
it was always Eisei Ureshino.
Huh?
[Eisei Ureshino]
- Whoa!
- Huh?
Pick up! Pick up!
It's fine, you look cute.
I'll be right back.
Huh?
Can't you answer it here?
I already heard everything.
Happy New Year.
What were you up to just now?
Huh? Oh...
You remember Maki-chan? From college.
Oh! Yeah, I remember her.
Kind of vaguely, though.
She's at my place right now.
Oh, really? Sounds fun.
Why'd you call?
Oh, no, it's nothing really.
Are you going home for the new year?
Huh?
No, I'm planning to stay here.
Really? Then let's go somewhere.
Huh?
I'm so happy.
I thought I wouldn't get to see you
until work started again.
Well, I'll contact you again then.
It's cold, right? Go inside.
Hello?
Oh, sorry.
Thanks for calling.
Well, talk to you later.
Well, see you.
Maki-chan!
A happy new year!
Am I right?
Yeah!
Hey.
He looks so cool!
You're cute again this year, Miporin.
Stop joking around.
Alright then, shall we go on our date?
Let's go on our date.
Here.
This reminds me of the company trip.
Yeah, it does.
But back then,
you wouldn't take a bite of my crepe.
You ended up going to a different shop
with Kusaka-kun.
Back then, things felt a bit awkward.
I knew it! You actually wanted my food more.
Shut up.
Wow, this is so cute.
It is.
This would suit you.
You think?
Want me to buy it?
It's okay.
I probably wouldn't wear it much.
You could, though! It really suits you.
Nah...
I want to see it.
This one, please.
Thank you very much.
It looks cute.
- Was this on you before?
- Yeah, it was.
Hey.
Do you have a boyfriend?
- Huh?
What kind of question is that?
Huh?
If I said I did, what would you do?
Well, I'd probably be shocked.
I don't have one.
Of course, I don't.
Oh, good.
Don't ask something so obvious.
Why not?
You could be doing long distance.
Like, "I'm single for now."
Don't lump me in with you.
Huh? Wait, hold on. That's not fair.
I don't have one.
I told you this.
- No, you didn't. We never talked about this.
- No, I did tell you.
- No, you didn't.
- I did.
Fine.
I have someone, but not a girlfriend.
- I'm kidding! Don't make that face.
- Stop it.
Come on, Mipo-nyan*!
(*cute nickname referring to a cat's meow)
- Mipo-nyan.
- Hey, stop calling me that!
Alright.
You're so cute, Miporin.
There's no one else.
Of course not.
Whoa...
This is so pretty.
I was so curious when I saw the photos.
Whoa, the bathroom's huge.
What's wrong?
Hmm?
Should we order something?
Or we could go out for drinks?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Well? What is it?
Wait.
Before that, we need to talk.
Hmm?
What did you mean by "dating"?
Huh?
It's just what it sounds like.
So I'd be your girlfriend?
Isn't that obvious?
Can I trust you?
Huh?
Oh...
Why not?
Of course.
Why would I ask that after all this?
Huh?
After all, we're accomplices.
But...
I did like you.
My encounter with this guy
came at the right time.
Things with my boyfriend of six years
had gone stale.
My friend, who'd just fallen in love,
seemed so radiant.
So I went to a group date as a stand-in,
even though it's out of character.
Ah.
Sorry.
Let me hear more.
🚩 Channel Managers 🚩
shraddhasingh & lilgr84_544
🚩 Chief Segmenter 🚩
a_hauth_238
🚩 Chief Editor 🚩
trangstar888
🚩 Translation Editor 🚩
xylune
🚩 Special thanks to our language moderators and their teams 🚩
I knew it was wrong, but I couldn't resist.
What?
Why are you avoiding me?
Well, because...
You're so serious, Miho-chan.
Stop it.
Do you regret it?
Of course I do.
If it were just once,
I could've written it off as an accident.
And yet...
No.
I know it's wrong, but...
Miporin, you're so cute.
When I'm with this guy,
love becomes confusing.
Pleasure courses through my entire body,
overriding the guilt.
I like you...
I like you.
We should stop seeing each other.
You mean he found out?
I think so.
So let's stop now.
I see.
Okay.
You're right.
So?
What is it that you want?
Huh?
I told you.
What do you want to do?
What about you?
I...
will do whatever you want.
That's not fair.
This is the last time.
This is...
the last time.
One last time.
This feeling, this kiss...
It'll all end after this.
Although I really wanted
for this to last forever, with Eisei...
♫ We walked through the city at daybreak,
soaked by the rain ♫
♫ You and me in the rain ♫
♫ Rather than trusting others ♫
Hey.
What did you mean earlier?
♫ I kept looking at you ♫
What did I mean?
It's just what it sounds like.
♫ Don't let go... ♫
♫ Of my hand ♫
You want to date after all this?
That'd be such a waste.
♫ Need to think about tomorrow ♫
After all, this is the kind of relationship
we have, isn't it?
[If Only You Weren't the One]
♫ Bathed in acacia tones ♫
- Have a good day.
- You too.
You and Kusaka-san would make a great couple.
You're not going to date?
What? I told you before
that I'm not in the right mindset right now.
Oh?
Oh, how's your new place?
Yeah, it's comfortable. A nice, quiet place.
Oh, that's good to hear.
But you had your last place
for ten years after college, right?
Why now?
Well, I needed a change.
And to start fresh.
I see.
Well, I'm glad you like it.
Yeah.
Oh, I forgot I have a client call.
Mihono-san, please go ahead.
Okay. Thanks for your hard work.
♫ Need to think about tomorrow ♫
🚩 Thank you for watching 🚩
"If Only You Weren't the One"
[This drama is fiction.]