Which episode...
The King of Qin
Episode 1
Do you think this can really make the King of Qin feel better?
The King of Qin is a person with a high level of inner strength.
He fights with his sides and fights with his enemies.
In fact, his inner strength is soft and he can't overdo it.
As long as the words are correct, you can definitely understand him.
His Majesty ordered the King of Qin to close the door and think.
Didn't Prime Minister say that many people have read the memorials and said that the King of Qin is bad?
The wood-burning rain forest is closed and the wind is blowing.
It's because the King of Qin has worked hard this time, so he was replaced by others.
His Majesty is now at the top of his head.
If the King of Qin doesn't want to admit his mistakes,
I'm afraid that the father and son will be in danger.
It's a big sign that the King of Qin loves him.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Miss Gu, I'm going to visit Prime Minister of the Manor.
But I'm not going out now.
Please help me transfer the imperial edict after you return to the Manor.
You're welcome.
Actually, I didn't come today to ask for your permission.
I'm just doing my own business.
I have something to send to Your Highness.
You're welcome.
There's no need to be so courteous in the Manor.
You shouldn't have said that.
This is what I embroidered myself.
I'm a traditional Chinese.
I've seen many people who have seen the birth of the King of Qin.
I'll follow the image of Lady Liu's portrait
and show it to them.
After I finished the portrait,
I showed it to the people who know Lady Liu.
They all said that it looked like her.
Your Highness, our lady has been looking for a long time.
It's easy to find a few people who have seen Lady Liu.
She asked them for a long time and asked them very carefully.
She also embroidered the white, dark and white hair and embroidered the white hair.
Her eyes are red.
She finally got this portrait out.
Your Highness,
as a child, you can't have a mother like me.
Of course, you'll feel sad.
But Lady Liu is very spiritual in heaven.
She knows that you're a good person now.
You must be very happy.
Thank you, Miss Gu.
I'll take this portrait.
Your Highness, you're a good person.
You're a smart person.
Of course, you know that Lady Liu
won't be willing to give birth to you
for her sake.
Your Highness, look.
I used the gold and silver for this portrait.
I thought that if you put Lady Liu's portrait on the mark,
it wouldn't be too bright and red.
Miss Gu, you're too thoughtful.
I'm grateful to you.
You're welcome.
I know that you're not a good person.
I'll take my leave.
Miss, didn't you say that you'd persuade Prince Qin
to admit his mistake?
Why didn't you say it afterwards?
You're leaving so soon?
I thought I was wrong.
Prince Qin has been watching the birth mother closely.
I was watching Prince Qin's figure.
If I continue to persuade him,
he'll be unhappy.
Besides,
he took the portrait of Lady Liu.
Every time I see the portrait,
he'll feel something for me.
Since that's the case,
I'd better say goodbye.
Prince Qin really doesn't want to be Prince Qin anymore.
Then will His Majesty still punish him?
The Dragon Phoenix in the world
won't be as important as you.
A person like Prince Qin
can only disturb him for a lifetime.
It's impossible for him to disturb him for a lifetime.
Let's go.
We're back.
You're back.
Stop looking at it.
You didn't reply.
You didn't even reply to me.
I wasn't waiting for your reply.
But there's one thing I have to say.
Something is true about that Miss Cui.
He said
that this situation
should be like
First Surface of the wegen bandit's army as Head texture
should always be like,
well indeed
you probably can hold it out here.
But you never really have a hand in it.
What is this?
My mother 1965
said that
to the very first generation of those 502 soldiers
I never saw them.
That's a good embroidery.
It's just a good embroidery.
Yes.
Miss Gu sent it.
She said she embroidered it for a long time.
Miss Gu sent it?
It seems that Miss Gu is very interested in you.
It's true.
Does she have feelings for you?
I'm not the same type of person as her.
I'm more into my own eyes.
I like Miss Cui.
Miss Cui?
Miss Cui doesn't even look at me.
Is there any miracle in the poison?
The doctor has been trying to cure the poison for a long time.
The poison has been removed.
The poison is very dangerous.
Dadao.
I promised Prince Qin
that if he promises to protect the grandchild and protect the grandchild and the throne,
I will kill Sun Jing by myself.
I will sacrifice myself to save him.
But I didn't expect that I didn't kill him.
Anyway, I lost my faith
after he left the palace.
Your Highness, you've tried your best.
It's not a bad fate.
Prince Qin came to see you yesterday.
He said that Sun Jing is kind,
but he is still in danger.
He is still very cautious.
Write a letter to General Han
and tell him to not expose Sun Jing.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Consort Xiao is here.
How is mother?
Prince Qin told me that
there is no news from mother,
but she has been missing.
I'm worried that
something bad has happened to her.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Consort Xiao is fine.
She is in Qingyun Temple outside the capital.
She is safe now.
Now that the capital is full,
can we go back to the capital?
Your Highness.
Consort Xiao is here.
She is calling us to show her mercy.
Sun Jing is still in the capital.
Prince Qin is a kind person.
Prince Qin, Prince Qi,
and Prince Qin are also kind.
Your Highness,
let's keep it a secret.
I'm afraid that
you will be displeased
by all the other forces.
I know.
Prince Xin wants to lead the army to Changzhou?
Yes.
Father just told me to lead the army to Changzhou
in the court today.
He has been against Sun Jing for hundreds of days.
Prince Xin has already seen the army.
And several ministers of the imperial family
are telling us that
since I have seen the army,
I have been in charge of the general affairs of Prince Qin.
Now,
Prince Xin has been in charge of the army.
Isn't that nonsense?
How did he lose Luoyang?
He is the one who has been in charge of the army.
Isn't that why I have been in charge of the army?
Just withdraw.
And I am still with Prince Qi.
Prince Qi is brave and can help me.
In the end,
even His Majesty is going to be touched.
His Majesty has ordered?
He hasn't officially ordered yet.
But His Majesty is very clear about it now.
Prince Xin is the general of the army.
Prince Qi is the general.
I am the ex-convict.
I will send all of the army to Changzhou.
Prince Xin
Prince Xin wanted to be better in this situation.
He wants to stay in Changzhou
and improve the quality of court
so as to dispel our militarychw sexual kry Salvage.
дум
he wants to seize our haircut from Zhe Xi army.
Hmm?
Father said so.
Father also smash down
the three branches ofсck to the crown prince.
But the moment he was arson,
the Serping Guard couldn't compete with Cybercwolf.
So he took
To take the heartyt of Chang'Zhou.
Sun Jing is a army of big haul.
Thewords are used against them.
Fl personality.
their might is not over.
To lady Prince passaigati設
is ill.
King of Qi?
You are such a third-cold man.
Well.
As this is the second plight,
you can only win the battle.
You can fight both teams
in every battlefield given three rounds.
Come on, express it.
To yours first.
To yours first
Your Majesty,
what business do you have?
Prince Qin's son…
His Majesty...
And princess Qin's.
Your Majesty, pleaseborn her through the word of rank.
Didn't you ask him to close the door?
Do you know where you are?
You're like a memorial.
Do you want to see it?
Father,
you'd better take a look.
If Third Brother has any request,
you'd better go to the doctor.
Yes, Father.
It man-ducks my eyes.
I'm afraid I'llend my life with you.
Yisei is my personal bomber.
Is a man
who imitates your mind.
My love
is obviously yours,
so I can't
explain to you what happened to him.
denigrating the grandmother to think met smoother inauthentic.
To policy to equal basic law.
I dare not act recklessly.
But the royal decision of Grandfather cannot be easily challenged.
I have控utened Your Majesty.
Please solids the grandusi to him.
by the court debate.
Maybe it's the Been easiest
to get rid of him in the past few days.
Your Highness.
Please send her back to her manor
and tips her childhood.
Please make nem30
to assume Goddess Ji
diseases as soon as possible.
Do you agree, your Highness?
Only when the bow is the first thing
possessed in the Palace
will we become the crown prince this evening.
Don't be ridiculous,
I don't want to hear it from you.
I don't want to let Prince of Xin and Prince of Qi lead the army to Changzhou.
I understand.
I will tell my father about your business.
Father, what did Third Brother say in the memorial?
He said he didn't want to be a man.
He asked to be his mother.
He didn't want to be a man for Third Brother.
He even asked Father to be his mother.
Why did he suddenly admit his mistake?
So,
we must be careful.
Look.
He wants to know what he's been thinking about for a few days.
Third Brother may be just saying it out loud.
He still hates Father in his heart.
Since he's already admit his mistake,
I think it's better to pursue the trend and become a Consort Xian.
After all, you and Lai'er's mother have been pursuing the Empress.
Those ministers are also making sense.
I only have three sons.
Only his mother is being pursued as a Zhao Yi.
A Zhao Yi?
It's indeed inappropriate.
Third Brother, at this time,
I think he wants to take the army to Changzhou.
If he admits his mistake and Father takes the army,
it's too much for him to take.
How can he make him
feel the danger of taking the throne?
Don't worry.
Since he's been thinking about the future,
let him think about the future for a while.
Wei,
Prince Qin has been thinking about the future for so long.
Why did he suddenly think of that?
He asked the Emperor to pursue the mother as a Zhao Yi.
But he didn't become the Emperor's order.
In the end, he became Consort Xian.
This matter has been settled.
Prince Qin has already retired.
Shouldn't this matter have been settled?
We can settle the dispute.
But if we're hurt,
we can't just say it out loud.
I have to go see him.
Wei, we finally managed to get into the palace.
Prince Qin's mansion is so big.
Where is the palace?
Don't you have a fever?
Hurry and ask Er Dong to bring you in.
Yes.
Tao Zi, He Xiao Wei, why are you here?
Hurry and take our Xiao Wei to see Prince Qin.
Okay, follow me.
Let's go.
Bring me some wine.
Just put it down. I'll make some wine.
Don't I really need to make wine?
One person is alone, but the other is hurt.
I'll accompany you.
Why are you here?
I came to see if the Prince Qin's mansion
is surrounded by nine-leafed-beast forest.
What's the day when everyone is pregnant?
Nine-leafed-beast forest is not here.
No one is here.
It's indeed here.
It's time.
Shi Qi Lang, are you okay?
I'm fine.
My mother died for me.
Since I came to this world,
I've never had a life like this.
She was born in a humble family.
She was born in a mansion of Prince Liang.
She was like a wild grass.
No one asked her for money.
No one cared about her.
She died many years ago.
She didn't even have a name.
I thought about it on the court that day.
Even if I don't do it for Prince Qin,
I'll still help her.
Even if...
Even if it's just a name.
But it's just a name.
They wouldn't even give it to her.
Father.
They wouldn't give anything to her.
Since I knew my father didn't like me,
he blamed me for killing my mother.
I thought he was so selfish to care about my mother.
Now I've realized
that he doesn't care about my mother's death.
He's so despicable to her.
You know,
my mother is living for me.
Isn't it unknowable?
My mother ate a lot of bitter fruits for me.
It's said that the medicine she had before
was all for a little god.
But when my mother was alive,
she often said that
the most valuable thing in her life
was to give birth to me.
Shiqielang,
what evil, evil, and son are all nonsense.
Your mother has been trying to bring you to the world.
She doesn't want to see you being selfish now.
But she wants you to live a life of self-pity.
Self-pity?
There's no self-pity in life.
I thought
if I'm recovered from the Xichang Capital,
I can attain Complete Patience.
But now,
you see,
the imperial palace
will be filled with
ames and nå tw интests.
I beg you to paused and settle down.
I can't do anything.
I can't even do anything.
I can't even be a citizen
for my mother.
I can't do anything.
I don't know what else I can do.
I think
I'm useless.
I think I'm useless.
Father.
Actually, I'm very sad.
But I feel very sad.
I know it's a mistake.
Actually,
I'm very sorry for my mother.
Why?
Because she can always be with you.
I'm here to see you.
But you're leaving soon.
Okay.
I promise you.
I won't leave.
I won't leave tonight.
Really?
Really.
Taozi.
Why are you so anxious?
You left me alone.
Because I...
Because I went to get this for you.
What is this?
These are the herbs I picked for you.
Look.
This is yellow mushroom.
And this is the rose.
This is white wine.
And these.
I bought these herbs in the pharmacy.
After I went to the mountains,
I was so dry.
Actually,
I've never thought of you.
I want to pick up the herbs.
You pick them every time you miss me.
Then I'll see
if you miss me.
If you miss me,
I'll pick it up more than 30 times.
Then,
if you miss me,
you can come to see me.
You can write a letter
like a prince and a filial son.
Really?
Of course.
Then, Taozi,
have you ever
missed me?
Then you guess it.
I guess
you must have thought of me.
Why are you so stubborn?
Because if you don't miss me,
you won't call me to see you.
Nor will you call me
to write a letter to you
like a 17-year-old.
Really?
I'll say it.
It's okay.
It's late.
I should leave.
You don't have to leave.
It's late.
I'll let you go
if you need another poem.
As you wish,
the world
is your power.
Why do you need me?
I don't want the world.
I only want you.
You don't want the world.
But you want the people of the world,
but you won't let them go.
Then, let the world be theirs.
Don't want anything.
I only want you.
You don't want the world.
But you want the people of the world,
but you won't let them go.
I only want you.
You don't want the world.
But you want the people of the world,
but you won't let them go.
You don't want the world.
But you want the people of the world,
but you won't let them go.
You don't want the world.
But you want the people of the world,
but you won't let them go.
You don't want the world.
But you want the people of the world,
but you want the world.
Shi Qi Lang.
You're finally awake.
What time is it now?
It's already past five o'clock.
I remember.
I remember I drank a lot in the room last night.
And then I drank too much.
I had a beautiful dream.
What dream did you have?
A dream
that I was very happy about.
It's like real.
You must have dreamed of the Hexia Wei.
Where did the Hexia Wei come from?
I think you have a similar disease.
You're as ill as a tall man.
Last night,
you were here drinking wine.
I want to drink with you.
And you drove me away.
Yes.
Xiao Wei, have some.
You eat.
I don't have any appetite.
But you don't have any appetite.
You didn't sleep last night.
Shall we go to the front town to find a inn?
We'll be there in the evening.
No need.
Actually, I had a fight last night.
Tell me.
You're so polite.
You dare to meet Prince Qin in Pixing.
Why don't you stay for a few days?
You only said that to Prince Qin.
That's enough.
I just want to see him.
I'm relieved.
If someone else finds out,
I'll be able to give him a lot of advice.
But I don't know
how sad and guilty he is.
How long will it take to make him feel better?
I still think
it's better for the two of us
to stay together for a long time.
You only said such a harsh words.
That's not enough.
I think some people
want to be with him
for a long time.
Xiao Wei.
But don't say that.
I just left him for a while.
I really miss him.
What about you?
Do you miss Prince Qin?
Indeed.
I miss him all the time.
I miss him so much.
Indeed.
17.
What did you do?
Didn't Taozi come yesterday?
He said he wanted to eat dried fruit.
So I bought some in the morning.
I was going to find someone to send it to him.
Taozi came yesterday?
Yes.
He came with Xiao Wei.
I don't know where he is now.
Did he eat?
When did they leave?
They left without telling me.
Xiao Wei said it was hard to let the guards see it.
So they left without telling me.
I'm going to see him.
I have a lot to tell him.
17.
But His Majesty ordered you to close the door.
You can't do that.
What do you think?
The prince of Heaven is here.
I'm going to see him.
17.
Sir.
Please have a seat.
Do you want to try our new tea?
It's very delicious.
Okay.
Let's eat first.
Xiao Wei.
We can feel the sunset in the dark.
Your shop is quite elegant.
You can buy tea and flowers.
Enjoy yourselves.
Xiao Wei, try it.
It smells good.
How come there's more?
Can't you come out?
It's so crowded here.
Why are you here?
I just want to come and see you.
You didn't see enough last night?
Last night, I didn't see it clearly.
I'm so sorry.
I ran so far to see you.
I told you to stop.
I'm willing to do it.
I don't think it's hard.
I'll go see you in a few days.
You're so mean.
Aren't you afraid of being misunderstood?
You thought you'd bring the soldiers
to take back Luoyang?
My father has been thinking
to fight with Prince Qin
on the battlefield.
Do you want to give him such a chance?
If he sent you away,
my father would lose.
If he saves Qin,
it's a pity that he's a wolf.
You want to protect Luoyang?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
If you're in danger,
I'll help you out.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
But Prince Qin is too brave.
Don't give me such a chance.
I'll do my best.
Then you'll always owe me a favor.
I can't repay it.
I think Li Ni
is just a little bit too close.
She gave the letter to my father
to say she'd like to be his mother-in-law.
But my father
is just going to be his mother-in-law?
Li Ni is thinking about it.
She's always thinking about
how to re-enact the army.
Brother,
my father told you to stay
and hold the mother-in-law's memorial.
He told you to take over the general's position.
He told General Pei to lead the army alone in Changzhou.
We need to stop Li Ni's
from doing anything to protect Changzhou.
What's more,
he even took the military power from the Xi army.
Don't worry.
Since I'm the general of the army,
I won't give them a chance.
I only said that I'm in danger in Changzhou.
I only want Pei Yuan to bring
three-layered military force and two-storey immortal.
He'll think that
there's a big army in Changzhou.
He's just dreaming.
Didn't Pei Yuan only listen to Li Ni's instructions?
If this war is over,
I'll see
if Li Ni can still keep her.
Chief Zhao,
you've just been discharged from the army.
You should take a break.
Li Ni is a very old man.
I guess he's going to stop me
from returning to the army in Changzhou.
The news came from the capital.
Li Ni was dismissed from the general's office.
He ordered to close the door.
He probably used the trust of the king and the king.
It's too difficult.
He's so incompetent.
Three armies.
A small man like Lord Liang
can't be a emperor.
He's so weak.
He's so self-abuse.
Chief Zhao!
Chief Zhao,
send the people who are after Taicun back to the capital.
Taicun is hiding in the city of Yishu near the capital.
Send the order to ask Taicun to kill the rest of them.
Yes.
It's a great day.
I wish you a happy life.
Peiyuan sent a letter to the capital.
He said the army of the hundred-month army
has passed the flood.
He forced Changzhou to
urge the court to capture the army of Changzhou.
He urged the court to send troops.
Father,
according to my opinion,
the army of the hundred-month army
is not as good as the one in the faraway land.
And there are no supplementary supplies on the way to the capital.
Only a few thousands of people.
Peiyuan was born in the army of the five generals.
He's been in the army for many years.
He won't even be able to handle it now.
General Pei is a member of the court.
If the court doesn't know the truth,
I'm afraid Peiyuan will have a new idea.
Father, you're the woman.
Peiyuan is great.
That's also the father's son.
If he wants anything,
what will he give?
What's the problem with the father?
The court only sent three-layered troops.
There's not much to do.
Father,
Li Ni led the troops to the west.
The court never spread the provisions.
The west army is also in the long-term.
From the old manor,
they've been killed for two jin.
Now the court has sent the west army again.
It's spread three-layered provisions.
The so-called reinforcements
are just to eat and drink.
These are all the rules in the army.
Father,
don't be fooled by them.
You're the general of the army.
How can you
restore Peiyuan with your sword?
According to the court,
the court must order
Peiyuan to disobey the order.
He will immediately
send a letter from Changzhou
to destroy the Sun Bu rebels in the last 100 months.
You're still here?
You said you'd send the general of the west army
to the north.
When the war started,
the army only gave
three-layered provisions and two-layered provisions.
Now, they're not sending the reinforcements
to the north.
They're not sending reinforcements
Isn't that to make the soldiers
of the west army die?
Leave it to Taozi.
When did you
write the letter to the He Family?
The court refused to send reinforcements
to the north.
Instead, they want Peiyuan to leave the capital.
I can't leave the capital.
Now,
I have to ask the Cui Family to help
the Cui Family.
Okay. I'll go now.
Shiqing,
you asked the Cui Family to solve Changzhou's problem.
Can this be solved?
Anyway, I said it in my heart.
I was trapped in Changzhou.
He can't die.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at
the world's first white face.
What is it?
If you want to beg, you can beg.
You can't be too rich.
If you can use a letter to solve Changzhou's problem,
this soft meal is really
a waste of money.
I dare not.
You're so selfish.
I think Prince Qi is wrong.
What's wrong?
He must know
that if you're fine,
you'll be able to
get the magic wand.
But you have to use the herb to do this.
What if he gets it broken in three days?
He should
use wood to cast a spell.
That's how he'll accept it.
It's still a good idea.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't have thought of
making you a young man.
Why can't he get it broken?
It seems that
Prince Qin is really not a good man.
Wei.
Why did you say that Cao Cao is here?
It's a letter from the Qin.
Your Majesty.
The report from Changzhou.
How is it?
General Pei was ordered to attack.
He was shot to death two days later.
He was killed by the Sun Bu rebels.
The Zhan Xi army didn't survive.
General Pei was killed by the Shen Bu.
What about Changzhou?
General Pei and Cui Yi
took Cui's army to the capital.
They killed Sun Bu rebels.
General Pei took the Zhan Xi army to the river.
He should be in the city of Changzhou.
But Cui Yi took Cui's army
and entered Changzhou.
What?
Cui Yi took Changzhou?
Father.
Changzhou is a military camp.
No matter it's in Sun Jing's hands
or Cui Yi's hands,
it's all against us.
Father.
Cui Yi lost Changzhou.
He's the one to blame.
Brother.
Isn't it time to talk about the team?
Changzhou was lost by Pei Yuan.
Why can't he be the one to blame?
Father refused General Pei's request.
General Pei personally went to the palace
to ask for Father's help.
He sent the Zhan Xi army to help him.
But you said
General Pei was a military camp.
He was in a fight.
Then he sent three imperial decree to Changzhou.
Now Changzhou is lost.
If General Pei is the one to blame,
I'm afraid Pei's family won't agree.
Let's find a way.
Cui Yi killed Pei.
He took Dong Du last time.
Now he's in Changzhou.
Let's go down.
What's the point of being the emperor?
Father.
I want to protect someone.
If this person can lead the army to war,
I'll take over Changzhou.
Who is it?
I'll protect three brothers.
No.
Li Ni is in the door.
How can he lead the army?
Three brothers can fight well.
Besides, he fought with Sun Jing and Zhu Bu.
Cui's army fought with them.
They're all good friends.
Besides, in the Manchang Cultural and Dance,
only three brothers and Pei's family are close.
If three brothers lead the army to Changzhou,
they might be able to cancel Pei's army.
They'll be re-enact.
Li Ni is so arrogant.
You're so arrogant.
Is that how it is?
Who can lead the army to war at this moment?
Is it possible for you to fight with them?
You're the eldest son of father.
Even if you're the first one to fight,
it's impossible for the Manchang Cultural and Dance
to lead the army to war.
All right.
I'm right.
Go and wear the edict.
Prince Qin is very cautious.
He's very strict.
He's in a hurry to lead the army
to Changzhou.
Yes.