In the form of frost,Don't look back
See you at foreign countries soon.
Do you know what do you mean?
Make a date for tomorrow at foreign countries with a new record.
Something is wrong ing.
Not here at foreign countries.
No.
A'Ming,
I didn't expect to see you again.
Is this a dream?
This is not a dream.
I finally see you.
Do you blame me?
You blame me for not coming to save you.
You don't blame me.
But I always blame myself.
I'm sorry.
A'Ming.
Who are you?
Why am I here?
Why do you let me see my wife?
You can come in.
A'Ming.
General.
Why are you here?
Where is A'Ming?
General, your illness is cured.
Can you recognize us?
His Highness has been trying to cure you.
Father.
How are you?
A'Ying.
You're thin.
And you're chubby.
You've been worried about father for so many days.
Miss.
The doctor just came to see you.
He said he had a chest pain.
He was very clear.
He was fine.
I see.
I just think
you're almost lost.
But I'm scared to death.
I'm so worried about you.
A'Ming, you're fine.
Really.
These days,
you're like a dream.
Now you finally understand.
But father,
your hair
is all white.
You're lying.
Father is old.
Your hair will be white.
Father is going to be A'Weng's man.
Why is your hair not white?
Father.
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
Drink it.
Why didn't you tell me?
The doctor said it would be risky.
I'm afraid it will be a bad idea.
I'm worried about it.
What if it's a bad idea?
I shouldn't face you.
But I think
General Cui is a brave man.
If he knows,
he will be so angry.
So I asked Mu Qianhe
to make a trick.
He used his blood
to get the blood out.
He's so clear now.
It's a good time.
Thank you.
I've worked so hard.
Can you just say thank you?
How can I thank you?
I can't think of it now.
I might think about it
after a few more hours.
You said
you must thank me this time.
By the way,
I have something important to tell you.
I think Liu Chengfeng's death
is very strange.
After all, he didn't stop
when he was talking to Jie Shuo.
The leader of Jie Shuo
was the誤 at the top of the hall.
He was a businessman
and went to the Western Changjing.
I've sent someone to follow him for a while.
But the誤 is really cunning.
He lost it accidentally.
I think he must be
a bad guy.
He's not a good guy.
Jie Shuo is a bad guy.
He wants to get rid of
such a bold and bold person.
Maybe someone will be in the capital.
I'll ask Chang'an
to check the Wen Hall
for the two new regiments in two years.
See if we can clean up the snakes
and let them get out of the barge.
The first time I saw you,
I thought you were a good guy.
You invited someone here to take a look.
You said you didn't want to cross Liu Chengfeng's path
and go to the middle.
So you came to see me personally.
I did all Liu Chengfeng's things
before I promised you.
But Liu Chengfeng has a son.
If he gets his hands on you,
it will affect your big deal.
So I told Liu Chengfeng
to get your son back.
I told Liu Chengfeng
to help you.
So I came here
to make a promise.
As the official of Central Plain,
you're willing to see me personally.
Do you want us to do something for you?
It's just a small thing.
I hope you can help me.
If you can help me,
then the territory you want,
salt, iron, rice and grain,
I will do it for you secretly.
What is it?
Kill Crown Princess Cui Li.
She is Cui Yi's daughter.
I believe you will be very happy to know her.
You're the prime minister.
If you kill Crown Princess,
aren't you afraid of the consequences?
What?
ARRAM,
you won't go to fishing right?
I'm not a coward.
I'm just a woman.
There are two more
decisive candidates in my men's hands.
Although Cui Shi is the Crown Princess,
as long as I make my arrangement,
killing him is not a simple thing.
Good.
So from today,
you will be the Crown Princess.
I will be the Crown Princess.
So from today,
I will do my best
to make the arrangement.
But I also hope
that the arrangement will be done.
But I still don't understand
why you are like this.
In the eyes of the world,
the Manor is not as good as the human.
It's a good opportunity.
What about the former Manor?
After the war,
the two major matters were settled.
The war was over.
The war ended with a great defeat.
The Zicun family
took the chance to conquer the land.
The emperor is a confused emperor.
He is not capable of getting married.
Although I am a Prime Minister,
I am a landlady in the Eastern Palace.
I am the future emperor of the He family.
I can't
be so confused with the emperor.
Except for the Crown Princess,
what else do you want us to do?
Of course, I am in a relationship
with the court.
If something happens to the court,
I will inform you secretly
to send troops to the border.
If the general sent by the court is my man,
you will be defeated.
He will be the first to take the lead.
If the court is in danger,
I will think of a way
to defeat him.
Good.
You are very good.
As long as the war is over,
the soldiers and the soldiers
will be your men.
I am a civil servant
who is not in the service of the army.
If the general sent me troops,
I will think of another way.
You are not brave
and not ambitious.
But I like you.
Don't worry.
As long as you help us,
we will help you
with everything.
There is one more important thing.
Liu Chengfeng is a man
who is very good at hunting.
When you kill the crown princess,
you must lower the position of Liu Chengfeng
and be the commander.
These days,
the situation is very serious.
When the enemy is close to the river,
it is hard to keep the position.
Therefore, Liu Chengfeng
wants to kill the crown princess first.
He wants to kill the crown princess
and take the high position of the crown princess.
In this way,
you can kill Cui Lin
by killing him.
Since I returned to Central Plain,
I have never been so happy.
I can use the mule.
As long as I take Ying away,
I can go far away from him.
In the future,
I will leave everything behind.
Mr. Xing,
as you wish.
As you wish.
Shun Xing.
You can leave with me.
You were an orphan.
You were a nobody.
So I changed you to Shun Xing.
I am sorry.
I was too old to be your commander.
Actually,
I am the same.
I am an orphan without parents.
If you change my surname to Liu,
I will have a family.
Mr. Xing, you are so nice.
Liu Shu.
I am so nice.
Here.
Eat.
Okay.
Eat more.
I want to invite you to the Qingyun Temple.
It is quiet there.
There is a guard.
And the choice is also there.
If you come to the temple,
you can make a choice.
A child will be happy.
He will think about it.
He will be happy.
This idea is good.
I remember when I was a child,
when father taught me to dance,
I was so happy.
Okay.
Your Highness,
you can go to the court.
I have an important matter to tell you.
What is it?
We...
The jade bucket in the back hall is too small.
Change it to bigger one.
Okay.
I should go to the court.
No.
Those people.
What is the matter with that jade bucket?
Why are you here to disturb Yingzhou again?
Didn't we agree before?
What is the matter with Sanghe?
Your Majesty.
Since the liberation of Cui's army,
maybe it's a good chance to accept it.
So, I came to visit Yingzhou again.
Then send the crown prince to go.
He likes to fight.
But this time,
we must beat them up.
Let them remember the lesson.
Your Majesty,
as the crown prince,
you don't want to lead the army to rebel.
You should lead the army to the west.
Okay.
Then you go.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
I think General Pei has already had a spring and autumn.
Why not let Pei Yuan go with him?
There must be a Zhao Ying on the way.
Prime Minister Gu is right.
As a father,
I don't need to be a son to Zhao Ying.
I can't say it.
Now all the bones in the body are painful.
The royal family under the rain
is going to catch the crown prince.
Let's take care of it.
Yes.
You're back.
Why are you back so late?
You don't know that General Pei's going to war
with the general.
I don't know.
General Pei is going to war.
He has a lot of things to do.
Besides,
isn't it because of the wedding that he didn't go to the court?
My father
was so worried about him.
Now all the six books in the three provinces
have been deleted.
I've been busy with the work
and I'm only dealing with the bull and bull.
Did you use the bowl?
I want to eat the meat
that I ate with the bull.
Besides,
the bull
always has a good taste.
It's called bull ear.
You never call me bull.
You're so stubborn.
I'm going to prepare the kitchen now.
It's already three o'clock.
It's so late.
Let's go to bed.
No.
We should eat the meat first.
Let's go to bed.
You're the general of the boat?
I've heard many stories about you.
The snow night is over.
The war is over.
Who told you that?
General Han.
Every night when I can't sleep,
he tells me stories.
General Xu.
Your knife skills are so good.
General Han taught me some sword skills.
Can I learn it from you?
Of course.
Come.
Look at it.
I'm here.
I'm so happy to see you.
General Cui taught you well.
You taught Xuanze well.
So you've learned to play with this.
How could it be?
General Cui has Xuanze's true power.
Xuanze is so good at playing with General Cui.
He can learn a lot from him.
But he's not good at playing with two rings.
Yes.
You are right.
You can't always teach me.
You haven't taught me for a long time.
I just taught you yesterday.
It's not that.
You lost.
My talent.
A Yan.
I'm thinking
if we want to have two dolls first.
One is called A Zhen.
One is called Dao.
He's left.
We'll play together.
Who said I'll play with you?
You said you wanted to have four.
You can't have less.
When did you promise me?
You're so annoying.
I'll tell you the truth.
You set your own rules.
I didn't say that.
I don't care.
Just four.
No.
I didn't promise you.
Then six.
Eight.
Ten.
The meat of Feng Yinrong is so delicious.
Yesterday, you sent me to the chef
and cooked a new dish called roast snake.
I felt so fresh.
But today, you're eating the meat.
I don't want to eat it.
Mr. Mu, you're very concerned about your father's illness.
We're toast to you.
You're welcome.
By the way,
I heard that there's a big fish in Yingzhou.
It's very cold.
And it's very delicious every spring and summer.
The fish is very delicious.
But I've never eaten it in so many years.
You're so crisp.
You should eat it for me.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
That's settled.
You help me cook the fish.
I'll send you two a magic trick.
Really?
That's great.
I've been asking my father
what kind of magic trick he saw on Mr. Mu.
He wouldn't tell me no matter what.
People say that Mr. Mu is a magic trick.
He's like a fairy.
Then today,
he can open his eyes.
Do you like fireflies?
How do you know?
I don't know.
Mr. Mu
I'll use this little magic trick
to congratulate you two on your wedding.
Thank you, Mr. Mu.
Ladies and gentlemen,
how was your meal today?
I'm very satisfied.
Thank you, my guest.
There's a good fish here in the south.
Do you want to bring it home to cook fish?
Okay, I'll bring it.
The customer paid a lot last time
to buy a fish.
He gave us a lot of money today.
My boss said
this fish was for the customer.
He said there's no garlic in the family.
My boss said
this garlic
was also for the customer.
Thank you.
My boss told me
he knows how to do business.
He's the first in the western capital.
He's destined to have a new business.
Thank you, my guest.
Here's your fish.
Thank you.
You're really good at garlic.
Our family really doesn't have garlic.
Besides,
they sent it here.
If they don't take it,
it's not a big deal.
What are you going to do
with this garlic?
Why do you ask me?
Of course,
I'll be a non-sense.
Why are you a non-sense?
Of course I'm not a non-sense.
I'm afraid you're a non-sense.
Are you that cruel?
This is garlic.
Someone said
his wife
would let him taste garlic.
And the name of the online celebrity
is not as good as
the name of the famous couple.
I'm just kidding.
Miss.
Taozi.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Our Cui's army
has been taken over by the government.
They're just
leaving the money in Yingzhou.
It's just hundreds of people.
They're talking about the rebellion.
The court ordered General Pei
to take the people of the Zhengxi army
to Yingzhou
and make a strict order.
The number of soldiers of the Cui's army
is about to be taken down.
The Beizhou Water District.
It's said that
the Beizhou government is very strict.
It's very strict.
It's like a criminal
to treat our Cui's army.
Not only are they talking about the rebellion,
but also the movement.
They're also fighting for the country.
These people are really heartless.
So they're pushing your general.
From Beizhou,
they've been to the Western Changjing
to meet the general
or the lady.
Don't let father know about this.
Yes.
Where is the general now?
He escaped.
He has wounds on him.
After he arrived in Western Changjing,
he was always at our Cui's house
to comfort his father.
I would get something from him that day.
He recognized me.
He followed me for a long time.
He saw me with no one around him
and he dared to talk to me
in front of me.
I recognized him
as the general of the left wing.
It's just compared to the past.
The sales have really gone up.
I think he must have had a lot of hardships
during this journey.
He didn't have any problems
and didn't dare to stay in the palace.
He said that these days,
he could only be in the temple
outside the city.
Miss,
shall we tell your highness
about this matter?
No.
This matter
is about Cui Xia Jun.
Don't tell your highness
so that he can't suffer.
How about this?
You ask this Tan Fu Jiao
to go to Feng Ying House.
Then we two
pretend to go to eat and drink.
We'll meet him first.
Then we'll meet him first.
Then we'll ask him
what the situation is in Beizhou.
Okay.
It's been so many days
since we ate the garlic meat.
Your highness,
I've said that you can eat it every day.
You said that it's too late
and you can't eat it.
It's too late indeed.
I didn't eat garlic meat
for three and a half nights.
Today is a good day.
It's worth remembering.
Where's the drawing book?
Take the drawing book out
and draw the picture of the garlic meat.
Draw the picture.
I'll draw it myself.
It's not here.
It should be that way.
Where should I put it?
I knew it.
Give it to me.
No.
No wonder you don't want me to see it.
How can you draw it?
I didn't draw it for the garlic meat.
If you draw it like this,
our child will see it.
Then I won't be laughed at.
You don't have to draw it now.
It doesn't mean you won't be drawn.
I'm not good at drawing.
No.
You're a blackboard.
I'll have to tear it.
I can't.
I'm so bad at drawing.
I'll tear it.
Give it to me.
Your Highness.
It's been three hours.
Did you sleep in the military?
Do you want to sleep in the sun?
Let me sleep for a while.
Get up.
Don't let the superiors wait.
Come on.
I'll go get you.
Wait here.
Come on.
I'll go get you.
I really think it's a long day.
It feels like a year.
What about you?
You can't see me.
Is it a year too?
But you came back at night.
So it's not hard to see you in the daytime.
But it's hard to see you in the daytime.
All right.
Hurry up and finish those things.
You'll see me when you come back.
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to go to the seal restaurant with Taozi.
Don't go to the seal restaurant.
It's the best opportunity to send fish last time.
All right.
Get up and change.
When you catch up with those things,
you'll see me when you have a good time.
I'm sorry.
Greetings, Miss.
Greetings, Prime Minister.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Prime Minister,
how are you?
I'm fine.
I'm the leader of the army of the Yuan Cui family,
who is 400 yu-mings in Beizhou.
I came to ask for your help.
Prime Minister,
we're not in the same way.
Miss,
this is the serial blood of our 467 people.
Please take a look.
We're not afraid of being people
from the top and the bottom of Beizhou.
We're also people who can't bear to write this blood.
It's so tearful.
It's tearful.
Your Highness,
why are you so early today?
Are you going back to the palace?
Didn't you know that the Crown Princess and Taozi
went to Fengying House to eat?
I'm going to take the food and the storage
and take you to Fengying House.
Taozi is right.
He didn't tell me.
Let's go.
Let's give them a surprise.
All right.
I'm going to take the food and the storage
and take you to Fengying House.
Taozi is right.
He didn't tell me.
Let's go.
Let's give them a surprise.
All right.
Let's go.
Brother Yao,
how did you do this?
How did you deal with the younger brother and sister later?
Madam Sun really brought a female guest.
They met a guest today.
But they didn't order anything.
They sat in the room for a while
and then left.
They sat in the room for a while and then left?
Yes.
They didn't sit for long.
They probably stayed in the room for a while.
I went in and gave them a tea.
Then I found that they had left.
They even kept the money on the table.
Which room is that?
Take me to see it.
All right.
I'll take you upstairs.
Shiqing,
did the Crown Princess and Taozi
go back to the palace?
I'll go and see.
No.
Search this house.
Yes.
Shiqing.
Wang więcej.
Goar.
Wang
I'll go.
This is Cui Lin.
Cui Yi's daughter.
The crown princess consort of Linni.
Wu Yan.
We've already said it.
I used the talisman to lure Cui Lin out.
You'll help me bring Cui Lin here
to rest for now.
Then,
I'll take Cui Lin away.
When Li Ni finds out that Cui Lin is missing,
she'll find out the truth.
Whether you can get what you want
and kill Li Ni,
depends on your ability.
That's right. I promised you.
You promised me, too.
After the trial,
you'll give me the real talisman.
After I take it,
even if I don't take it anymore,
I won't die in the bones.
That's right. I promised you, too.
Give me the talisman now.
I'll take Cui Lin away.
What about her?
Just let it go.