Episode Jeff
The Long Ballad
Episode 1
Dong Dong.
Father, help me!
Get out of the way!
Father!
Jun'er, get up!
What... what's going on?
Qi Huotang killed me!
Your Majesty!
What?
The Prince of Qin is outside the palace.
Father, did you see that?
He didn't let Jun'er come to see me.
Father, please help me!
Help me!
No, no.
Don't let the Prince of Qin come in.
Let him kneel before him.
He doesn't have my order.
Don't get up!
Yes.
Thank you, Father.
Miss, the rumor that
General Pei really stopped the Prince of Qin.
But now the Prince of Qin still wants to get into the palace.
General Pei is trying to persuade him.
But fortunately,
General Pei has already brought people to the palace.
I think that no matter what,
the Prince of Qin can also stop him.
He can't just take the sword and enter the palace.
It seems that this time,
he is really sad.
Miss, how do you know that
if General Pei tells you that,
he will definitely persuade the Prince of Qin.
That person is very loyal to the Prince of Qin.
When he is in the capital,
he will not worry about his own things.
But Pei Yuan and Zhen Xi's army are in the same boat.
He will definitely worry about it.
As long as I tell him,
if he kills the Prince of Qin,
the emperor will definitely take Pei Yuan and Zhen Xi's army to the capital.
He will calm down.
Miss, you really are the most sensible person.
Now,
even if you know,
what can you do?
It turns out that you are not a sudden illness,
but a serious poison.
Prince of Qin is trying to poison the Prince of Qin.
He didn't expect that he would be in the house.
Oh my god.
When you fell down,
you were right in front of me.
You scared me.
Miss, you are so dangerous.
Didn't you just put poison in my liver?
You almost ate that poisonous bun.
Yes.
It's almost the same.
I might be poisoned by it.
Miss, this is too dangerous.
Don't see Prince of Qin again.
As the saying goes,
wealth is in the hands of the world.
How can I not see Prince of Qin again?
Well said.
You are indeed my daughter.
Father, please sit down.
You know everything?
I heard that Prince of Qin
took the witness and sent him to Prince of Qin's mansion.
Fortunately, when General Pei went,
he saw the palace.
This is where Prince of Qin was led.
It's also where he was punished.
The name of the dragon is Prince of Qin who poisoned him.
But His Majesty is partial to Prince of Qin.
Prince of Qin is a man of the world.
But he is partial to Prince of Qin.
He will protect Prince of Qin.
Prince of Qin is very ignorant.
Father, you mean...
Prince of Qin should be the one who knows the truth.
If I knew it long ago,
I would teach him.
I would get the witness and the witness first.
I would go to the palace and kneel in front of His Majesty.
He would say that he wouldn't believe
that Prince of Qin poisoned Prince of Qin
to get the witness.
But he couldn't believe it.
I only hope that His Majesty can see the father's will.
To avoid his death,
he sent the witness to the border to protect his life.
He would pursue Prince of Qin without mentioning the witness.
His Majesty will be very content.
The officials of the Manchukuo Empire,
I and Pei Xian,
including General Cui of the border,
will naturally help him.
They will surely kill Prince of Qin.
Prince of Qin will not do this.
Yes.
With this good plan,
he can beat the Great God of the Sky.
He can even defeat Prince of Qin.
But he is just a handsome man.
He is now a general.
What do you plan to do now?
We will be ministers.
Prince of Qin is being destroyed.
He can't be killed by the enemy.
Prince of Qin is very fond of his mother.
He is very sad.
You are the one who found his mother.
When he sees you,
he will be very happy.
You must take good care of him.
You must take good care of yourself.
Okay.
I understand.
My mother has prepared the skin care.
I will go to Prince of Qin's mansion later.
I didn't expect that
my brother is still not lucky enough.
He is just a single mother of Prince of Qin.
Your Highness,
our plan has already become half.
I have to go to advise
my brother who is not sure about his soul.
Let him work harder.
Miss Gu,
Prince of Qin is not in the mansion.
His Highness has gone to the palace.
He hasn't come back yet.
It's okay.
I am here to pick up my mother.
Your Highness,
since you are not in the palace,
let's go back to the mansion.
It's been a day.
Who taught you
the call in Prince of Qin's mansion?
I thought about it myself.
Miss Cui taught me this.
She said that only by saying this
can she stop you.
And she said that
she is not afraid of being in the mansion.
She said that she can stop you.
And I asked her
why she didn't tell you.
She said that you don't want to see her.
And she said that
you are not sure about it.
So I have to say it.
Shi Qi Lang,
at first,
I was very impressed by Miss Cui.
But after the day-to-day break,
I found that she really has a way of life.
She is thoughtful and
she always plans for you.
The most difficult thing is
that she doesn't pay the money to the palace.
Shi Qi Lang,
you two are in love.
It's a good match.
What?
You mean
to let the king go?
Right?
Your Majesty,
that's what I mean.
That's my son.
Even if
the so-called witness is true,
the king of Xin
is going to poison the king of Qin.
But Li Ni is not dead.
Why should the king of Xin
take the king's life?
And he is going to let it go?
Your Majesty,
the king of Qin is also your son.
Besides, the king of Qin
has taken two golds and
is in the palace to design.
And what about the king of Xin?
He killed the queen of Xin.
This is a court-court-based investigation.
But it hasn't been carried out.
It was just released by the government.
So he wanted to murder the chief.
The most vicious person
who killed the people.
Your Majesty,
do you still insist on
using the national law
to defend him?
Gu Qing,
it's not that serious.
It's not that serious.
It's just that
they are just making a scene.
Look,
the king of Qin
also used the sword
to kill the king of Xin?
Besides,
he is also out of the palace.
Why can't he let go of his brother?
That's his brother.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
why are you so generous?
the king of Qin
has taken two golds and
is in the palace to design.
But today,
the one who killed him
is in the palace to defend him.
Will anyone
in the future
be able to
kill the official?
In the army of Zhenxi,
the people are all in the same place.
They are all in the same place.
This is the fate of the army of Zhenxi.
Your Majesty,
the royal law of the dead
is a lie.
I will lead the army of Zhenxi
to avenge the king of Qin
and keep the king of Qin alive.
Your Majesty,
if you don't want to
let the king of Qin
rule the country,
I
will have to lead the imperial court
to give the order to the imperial court.
Gu Qing, Pei Qing,
why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this?
Can't you
let the king of Qin
live in the imperial court?
Your Majesty,
the king of Qin
is the one who killed the royal family
and the chief of the family.
He has committed
a grave crime.
Now,
the king of Xueju
has decided to let him live.
He has already let him live.
My Jun'er.
How can you bear
the suffering of Liu Fang?
I will leave.
Please wait,
please wait.
Please wait.
Liu Fang is fine.
But,
how far is Liu Fang?
According to my imperial law,
the king of Xueju
has left 3000 miles
to the north of the capital,
the place of the age.
Can't you be closer?
What?
It's the day after the emperor's death.
Can you let the king of Xin
go with me
to worship his mother?
If I let the king of Qin
go,
can you let the king of Xin
be his servant
and apologize to him?
Is that okay?
Can you
leave 1000 miles
to Qiongzhou?
Is that okay?
Your Majesty,
the queen of Dong
is not the birth mother of the king of Qin.
The birth mother of the king of Qin
is Consort Liu.
When she was chasing after the birth mother,
she has already wronged the king of Qin.
Now,
she is going to the temple again.
I'm afraid it's not right.
At that time,
I should also
chase after the king of Liu.
I shouldn't
be so angry at that moment.
How about this?
At that time,
I will first send the queen of Dong
and then send Consort Liu to death.
I will call the king of Xin
before Consort Liu's
death
to apologize to the king of Qin.
Is that okay?
If the king of Xin
can apologize
before Consort Liu's death,
then
the queen of Liu will go to Qiongzhou
for 1000 miles.
This is also
the heart of the emperor's love.
But this is the law.
We can't cut it off.
I understand
the meaning of the two love.
I know.
I know
that I can't
ever
protect her again.
I understand.
Miss,
the general's letter said
that the king of Jieshuo
sent a group of people
to follow Liu Chengfeng
to the middle of the land.
Then the general continued to search.
He found that the group of people
disappeared
after they entered the area near Jizhou.
I think they were hiding.
Where is the commander-in-chief?
He's not far from Jinzhou.
We will take a group of people
to the north to win the commander-in-chief.
We will secretly kill them.
Okay.
Father.
I was wronged.
I was still abandoned by Liu.
I was killed.
Father.
Jin'er.
I and Prime Minister
have discussed for a long time.
He's in the same place.
From Liu Fang's 3000 miles,
he took Liu Fang's 1000 miles.
The place in Qiongzhou
is also good.
It's to prevent the war.
Can't we not leave Liu Fang?
I...
I can't bear to leave you.
I'll go there.
I can't come back to Jianing again.
Jin'er.
Mother.
Father.
Jin'er.
I can't bear to leave you.
I have no other choice.
I'm going to kill the whole imperial clan
I can't.
Imperial Guard Aqua Question
You were so ».
She who she does routing
I do both
Yes
Father
I beg you
Come.
What are you looking for?
The carriage can't even get in.
It's not good to ride a horse.
Your Highness is planning
to take the throne.
How can you not
take the throne secretly?
Liu Chengfeng!
What are you talking about?
The one who bought the throne
and tried to take the throne
was my brother.
I'm not a man of the word.
As long as my two brothers die,
the throne will be mine.
Yes.
Your Highness just wants to make up for it.
It's a big deal.
But don't worry.
We will make you
realize your dream.
After all, we don't want to
let you
live.
Help me tell the Oulong.
As long as you can help me succeed,
I will make all the arrangements
for the throne
of the Crown Prince
in the north of Yan and Zhuo.
Mr. Shiqing.
As I said,
you will be the empress and my mother
if you lose your memory.
You will be punished
by my mother.
Don't worry.
I won't cause trouble.
Mr. Shiqing.
The Prince of Xie will be released soon.
This is the most important place.
Today is my grandmother's illness.
I will tell the old men
to pretend that I'm still in the army.
When the city is out,
I will send my grandmother to the hospital
and then go to the capital.
That's not a big deal.
If others know about it...
I will make the carriage in the city.
I will be in the carriage.
Who will know?
All right.
Go back.
Don't make your father worry.
Yes.
Brothers.
Take care.
OK.
The path isRecavation
that make it be than Placid on Ps annatus and aksu.
Enough.
One Spirit breaking
will kill both heroes.
In the charge of morale
he will see me.
lanternливо.
Era I took
the black céu
a pretty ghost
is over there
by the way
ca Lofi
lo wonder
you hundreds of hundred
any bowel
Former Li Zhongkang
Boys, please guess it is...
Help!
My looking should have been more advanced than usual.
Why didn't you tell me not to tell me?
Send her to the site!
The Coronavirus is all that's reasons.
Tell dön-senbe to get Ta-taikun out of Hujia.
I'll hide them.
Go back toNice County.
Too dark!
Thus, all of you come to see them.
Of course I don't bother to see you.
You absolutely aren't gonna be so assertive
even before I find you back in the back.
I was only thinking about the long distance to motorspr sucks.
It's not like you can get through this side.
The sentry-cube.
It's about time.
Yellow Anthony
Chief Mayor
You're afraid of my father.
Yes.
My father.
Who are you?
How dare you leave me here alone?
There was a
는데 til ken ngat map e
l el
total
running
Through you
you can bring your hope
Не depressed
We're all planned
Because you found all the этого
Hu Dian.
Your Majesty.
I am Hu Dian.
This bard is a Turks grandson!
At this fabled (?)
thisquote
why is this your highness' call doin'
Fu Huang.
If you are not bold-hearted
I'll take care of it.
Who told me to live in the Emperor's House?
These...
These assassins are all you've found.
I'm your own son.
How dare you leave me alone!
You're kind to me.
You're a good man.
You should live well.
Jun'er.
You...
Are you going to rebel?
The new emperor is going to rebel.
Protect the emperor!
You bastard.
I didn't expect you to be so brazen.
Kill the emperor.
You're going to rebel.
Jun'er.
You're going to kill your own brother.
Your Majesty, take it.
He's my brother.
Come on.
Elegant bastard.
No way, your enemy brother.
You...
Die.
Leave me alone...
I shall revenge you.
dealing with you.
Don't take offense.
StopIK
What's the point of Curry Cheeke?
Show your sufferer your have an end.
What unacceptable conditions.
You are vlogging.
That beautiful Consort is also
qualified as King Yu'sakah..
I'm so six years have changed
So,
I want to die.
Who let us live in the Emperor's House?
What's wrong?
How's it going?
I'm fine.
God.
Why is he such a big liar?
What are you doing?
knowing humans?
Peaceful humans aren't Halloes.
What did a little史 dominating Shaolin beatufen do to kidnap us?
We're 2003 and 7 vorpeg congratulations to you.
Looking for troops from I'll find some ones.
I'm good at human beings.
Didn't you hear that?
He married Su Yuzhoswong?
The trip was very impressive.
He didn't hurt others long enough.
We too were very happy.
Right.
The king and the king of Xin living together will be violent
to protect His Majesty.
Kill the king!
Come on.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Protect the kids.
Come on.
Go!
I will kill him!
Proof of attack, all of you retreat!
Shipping收dles
Shipped
You!
Brother!
Hey!
Cannon!
Software!
Search.
Go!
Go.
Alright.
Brother 40 Af會,
Brother.
I'm not pregnant.
紀u day dark.
практически disgusting.
Erge.
Brother Zheng!
Old Man!
Song Yuan!
You must leave first.
I'll take care of the emperor!
Brother Zheng!
Old Man!
The rain falls
The wind blows
The rain doesn't hurt
The third bowl is that golden sand
Golden sand
The golden sand of the girl
The girl is golden sand
The fourth bowl is that moon
Moon is the moon
Moon is the face of a good girl
I passed the girl's house
Old Man!
The water is so cold
The fifth bowl is that
The water doesn't hurt
The water is so cold
The water is the golden sand
Old Man!
The water is so cold
The sixth bowl is that
The蓋殺
The scatter
When will you景色
By Took the d hotels
By took the lorries
The gold papers
The action크
The quoted serpents
The newshing
The picturesque
The long love
Motion.
Yuan position.
Aishou!
No!
I am a hag.
What if she has been burned to death for really?
How will I find an old recommendation?
Why do I don't pay attention to you?
I give you the flities.
musstre
hé
returning home
ined
waiting for longer
getting ready
Go wait in your room.
If you forget the mutuallyizable years
When memories of a dream return
The moonlight fades away
If only I could渡 g 용
I'm afraid I'll be too tired to be with you.
I'm afraid that I'll become too tired to be with you and you.
I'm afraid that I'll be too tired to be with you.
I'm afraid I'll be too tired to be with you.
And I'll be too tired to be with you.
I will wait for you to come back to me
If love is a promise that I will keep for you
Don't let it go, I will love for you
I will wait for you to come back to me