(You know what?)
(I actually know someone really great.)
(I’d love to introduce you this time.)
(Just open your heart a little.)
(You won’t regret meeting them.)
(Date My Friend)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(The moment of selection starts on the second night.)
(Behind the closed door, )
(there is a piece of paper.)
(Open the door and check it.)
- What?
- Gosh...
(Sighing)
(Exclaiming)
I was so wrong.
(What is on the paper...)
(that surprised them?)
I am a doctor with 13 years of experience.
(Shin Dong Ha, 37, a doctor with 13 years of experience)
I currently work as a member of an investment strategy team,
and am a M and A strategist with five years of experience.
I am a producer in the planning division...
of my Lovebud Kang So Ra's agency.
(Choi Ji Eun, 28, producer)
I am a retired soccer player.
Now, I teach soccer to youth and adults.
(Kang Su Jin, 28, soccer coach)
I don't need to hesitate today.
Hyun Jin.
His manners and each of his actions made my heart flutter.
I think we connected a lot.
(She opens the door to her heart.)
Hyun Jin.
(She checks Hyun Jin's information.)
(Oh Hyun Jin is a 39-year-old stage and musical actor.)
For me,
six years is the maximum age gap that I can consider.
Gosh, 11 years won't be easy.
(Will they be able to overcome the age gap and get closer?)
My mind is heavy tonight.
How was the interview for you, Da Hye?
Was it shocking or not?
- It was shocking.
- What?
- Was it wrong?
- Me too.
What was it?
- But we opened this up.
- We did.
If it were today's date or another person.
Today's date.
- Yes.
- It's the same for all.
Why do you think I was shocked?
You were completely off?
I want to crawl into a hole.
When we were talking about that...
Then what should I do?
Do I stay still?
I really got into the details.
You were practically Detective Conan.
He must have thought you were really cute.
Right.
Thinking, "Let's see how well you can guess."
I know. This is so...
Then the question we asked earlier was,
other than your date today...
- If I'm curious about anyone else?
- Yes.
- I was very satisfied...
- I am.
With my date today.
It was different from yesterday.
Anyway, so I don't know what to do.
I'm the type that goes for it.
- Me too.
- That's why...
it's the same person for me.
(Did Sin Young really choose her date, Geon Wu?)
(Sin Young went on a yacht date with Geon Wu.)
(Sin Young picks Geon Wu.)
"Kim Geon Wu is..."
"a 29-year-old online fashion magazine project manager."
I am working as a PM, a project manager,
for an online fashion magazine.
I connect with different brands...
to identify the clients' requirements,
and plan and execute events.
(Kim Geon Wu, 29, online fashion magazine PM)
(Geon Wu is next for the Heart Room.)
"The person who knocked on the door of your heart."
(Geon Wu's choice is Da Hye.)
When we first met,
I was interested in Da Hye,
so I took the name tag with the same feelings from yesterday.
I didn't have to think much.
"Lee Da Hye is..."
"a 30-year-old model."
I'm a model with five years of experience.
I made my debut in 2021 through a video commercial...
and have appeared in various TV commercials for different brands.
Lately, I’ve also been modeling for print and digital content...
with domestic and international premium beauty brands.
(Lee Da Hye, 30, model with 5 years of experience)
It was really unexpected.
I thought she was probably about that age.
But with her clean short hairstyle,
fair skin,
and the aura of someone well-brought-up...
made me assume that she was in the medical line of work,
such as a physical therapist,
But it never crossed my mind that she would work in modeling.
So I wanted to talk with her.
I am very curious.
(Geon Wu became even more curious about Da Hye.)
Last week, when we heard the occupation and age...
of Gwan Hee's friend, we were shocked.
- Yes.
And also the occupation and age...
- Occupation and age.
- of the other friends.
Was there anyone who really surprised you?
For me, Su Jin.
- Yes.
- Su Jin is...
- so bright...
- Right.
And doesn't seem like she can teach or scold others,
- but she was a soccer coach.
- Yes.
- I didn't even imagine it.
- Because even with Dong Ha, - Right.
We all guessed other jobs,
but they were all outside of our predictions.
- Yes.
I'm also curious,
because my friend, Dong Ha, outright declared it at night...
that he's interested in Su Jin and Ji Eun.
- I think it will start today.
- Today will be the true start.
- Until now, it was just a preview.
- For today,
will Dong Ha see any big results?
- I know.
- Yes. I'm curious.
I think Jeong Geun could get hurt...
from Dong Ha's straightforward actions.
I came somewhat mentally prepared.
Dong Ha will go straight to it.
You reap what you sow.
So I don't think it will be easy today.
(Mi Joo's friend, Lee Da Hye)
(Gwan Hee's friend, Ha Jeong Geun)
(Ye Eun's friend, Kim Sin Young)
(Sae Ho's friend, Kim Geon Wu)
(Young Kwang's friend, Kang Su Jin)
(Nam Hee's friend, Oh Hyun Jin)
(So Ra's friend, Choi Ji Eun)
(Young Ji's friend, Shin Dong Ha)
(Episode 4. Timing)
(They wake up, holding the secret of their love interest.)
I didn't go this way yesterday.
Let's go here.
It's Jeong Geun. I knew it.
- Gosh, they met up separately.
- Around the dullegil.
(Ji Eun and Jeong Geun go for a walk, like promised.)
"Older?"
I’m suddenly feeling a bit upset.
(During Ji Eun and Jeong Geun's first date)
I guess you could be older than I am.
You could be right.
Are you older than me?
You never know.
- "You never know?" - You never know.
Don't regret it.
Whatever.
(Last night)
(Ji Eun opened Jeong Geun's door and checked his information.)
- Wait.
- They are four years apart.
He is older than her.
(Jeong Geun is 4 years older than Ji Eun.)
(Jeong Geun also opened Ji Eun's door...)
(and checked her information.)
- They now know each other's age...
- Yes.
- and occupation.
(Ji Eun and Jeong Geun know each other's age and occupation.)
Did you check it?
It seems like you checked it.
But it was really similar to what I had guessed.
Was it similar? What did you guess?
I mentioned the studio,
- and photo shoots.
- The photo shoots.
No, it's quite different from that.
- Let's sit here.
- I'm out of breath.
Catch your breath.
Catch your breath before speaking.
What was written as my occupation?
M and A...
(M and A strategist)
Somehow...
(They reveal their picks without hesitation.)
It wasn't that surprising.
- Really?
- Yes.
"Okay."
"That sounds possible."
- Really?
- Yes.
I guess you were curious, then?
Yes, well...
As soon as you see it,
you can see the age first.
It's on top.
"Older?"
(Jeong Geun had said that Ji Eun was older.)
- And I arrived late, right?
- Yes.
I joined later,
and I couldn't see any opportunity in my perspective.
During that short time.
I couldn't see any opportunity...
and you didn't seem to have the room either.
- I didn't have any room.
- Yes.
That's why I kept trying to carve out a chance.
Keep going, Jeong Geun.
Keep going.
The first day was very hard.
It was clear that...
you felt more relaxed...
with people who made you...
more comfortable,
and seeing that,
I didn't want to...
make you feel uncomfortable.
No matter what I did.
I wanted you to feel comfortable in every way.
I did feel comfortable. I was actually thankful.
- When we were talking, - Yes.
The way you asked questions...
You asked a lot of questions that I could comfortably answer.
That's right.
(Ji Eun was thankful that he made the conversation easy.)
Yesterday, I felt awkward about taking pictures...
next to someone.
I felt very awkward...
- having my pictures taken as well.
- Yes.
But those moments came to me...
- Stop it.
- as a really...
In 1, 2, 3.
Strong impression at night...
when I sat back and thought about...
- what I did during the day.
- Was it?
- When we took the pictures?
- Just...
When we took pictures and things.
So...
How did it leave such a strong impression?
You asked Geon Wu to take your picture first.
Is that still so...
You asked Geon Wu to take your picture.
You're a baby.
What do you mean, "baby?" I'm quite old.
You are, but you're still a baby compared to me.
Not exactly a baby.
Baby is...
- "You're a baby." - Wait a minute.
- What is it?
- I think it explains it all.
- With "baby?" - Yes.
What?
But isn't that something you can say only when you're dating?
- He just said, "You're a baby." - "You're a baby."
- "You're a baby." - Yes.
That's not too much.
For example, it's like this.
If we were eating with you,
- and you only ate sausages...
- Yes.
- or foods that are easy to eat, - Yes.
We'd say, "Ye Eun is a baby."
- That's what it's like, right?
- Sure.
What was that?
Or do you not like that?
For example, if you gave Gwan Hee water,
and he said, "Thank you, Ye Eun,"
and gave you a pat on the head.
- That will make your heart flutter.
- When you're not dating?
When he does that when you're not dating?
When you're starting to flirt with each other.
Then that's being fox-like.
It's being fox-like if you do that when you're not official.
Oh, really?
- I see.
- I'd like that.
- So Ra said it's okay.
- Yes.
Yes.
When you're not officially going out?
Getting a pat on the head is not bad for me.
- When you're not going out?
- Yes.
Is it not okay even if you're at the flirty stage?
Isn't that okay?
It's when you both know that you're interested.
But you need to make it official before you touch.
- All kinds of touching?
- Yes.
All kinds of touching...
needs to start after you make it official.
- You’re such a traditional girl.
- Completely.
- Really?
What kind of touching can you do before you make it official?
- Nothing.
- Not at all?
For anyone who’s going to start flirting with Ye Eun,
- don't touch her.
- Watch out.
You're very conservative, aren't you?
But it depends on...
- personal preference.
- Yes, it is.
Yes.
But those two are practically already a couple.
From what I've sensed...
from the conversations going on between the guys,
the guys will continue on...
with their bold moves until the end.
- So I really...
- Really?
It's...
This place...
might turn into a jungle.
- Really?
- That's what I think.
But,
I won't worry.
(I won't worry.)
Whatever.
- But...
- Should we go up?
I think I'll get eaten up by mosquitoes.
Let's go back up and get ready.
It doesn't matter if you change your mind.
Just don't have too much fun.
I hope you're not as comfortable as you were yesterday.
But listen.
Ji Eun changed the subject here.
Listen.
Jeong Geun said, "My mind won't change,"
- but Ji Eun didn't say...
- "Don't worry."
- She didn't say that.
- No.
- She didn't answer, but avoided it.
- Yes.
- This is the third day, right?
He should have stopped that on the second day,
but he kept going until the third day,
and I think it could have been...
- a bit burdensome for Ji Eun.
- Right.
Because Ji Eun didn't get to know the others yet.
- I really didn't notice that...
- Right.
- she had avoided the question.
- Yes.
Because if you're really into them,
it won't matter if you get eaten by mosquitoes.
You would want to stay longer to talk.
The hydrangea is so pretty. They must be in season.
Let's go down here.
It's the Eiffel Tower couple.
(It's the Eiffel Tower couple.)
- What should we do today?
- I know.
(Are they going on a run together?)
But yesterday,
since I know one person's occupation and age...
Yes.
It's so...
Why?
- Can I ask who it is?
- What?
We can ask who it is, right?
- The one I chose?
- Yes.
It's not that...
I'm curious about others' age and occupation.
I'm curious to know who you chose.
This is very clear.
I chose my date.
- Your date?
- Yes.
So...
I came on a run with you to ask that.
Really? That's touching.
The second day is over,
so I thought it could all end...
without me doing a thing.
(Dong Ha and Hyun Jin's conversation last night)
Sure. Because...
I'm interested in Su Jin and Ji Eun,
but I went on a date with another person.
Yes.
That's why I asked her to go on a run tomorrow morning.
So I can talk with Su Jin.
Su Jin is going on a run.
I like running,
but I do it at night, not in the morning.
I do it at night when the weather is nice.
- It's better when it's breezy.
- It's sunny in the morning.
(This morning)
(Dong Ha waited for Su Jin to come out.)
- Hello.
- Oh, gosh.
You scared me.
That really scared me.
What is it?
Don't you think they will let us choose now?
- The date partner?
- Yes.
Do you have anyone in mind who's different from yesterday?
- "Different from yesterday?" - Yes.
- If I get the chance...
- Yes.
- to choose myself today, - Yes.
Then you.
- Me too.
- Really?
- That openly?
- They're so cool.
This is so heart-fluttering.
My heart just stopped.
Okay. It's confirmed.
Okay.
Then let's say we go on a date. Where do you want to go?
Did you have a place in mind?
Where should we go?
For me, I prefer...
a cable car.
- Since we're here...
- That's good.
I love it.
They even finished talking about going on a date.
(Dong Ha expressed his true feelings to Su Jin.)
"I came out to run with you."
He told me everything.
"If I had the choice,"
"I really want to go on a date with you."
"I was curious about you."
I was like, "Really?"
I was grateful that he mustered up his courage to tell me.
I was glad that he expressed his feelings for me.
I really enjoyed our morning run.
We're done.
- Should we... Yes.
- Let's rest for a bit.
- It's so... Exactly.
- I want to go in the water.
- Would you like to?
- What?
(They headed to the beach without a camera.)
- Without a camera?
- What?
We'll get our clothes wet.
We're drenched in sweat anyway. Come here.
We're drenched in sweat anyway.
(The two of them swam in the sea without any interruption.)
It's so cool.
This will be a memorable experience.
(The two of them swam in the sea without any interruption.)
When I suggested we go into the sea...
As a woman,
she might not have been keen due to several reasons.
She'd put her sunscreen on,
and she couldn't get her hair wet. But...
she gladly said, "Sure, let's go in."
She joined me, which made my heart flutter.
- Dong Ha is very assertive.
- Yes.
He's heading straight for her and making it obvious.
- He's very assertive.
- He sure acts differently.
He's never shown that side of himself to me.
- That's cool.
- Yes.
He's turned over a new leaf overnight.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
My friend had said that he was interested in...
Ji Eun and Su Jin.
He knew Su Jin went for a run in the morning,
- Yes, he joined her on purpose.
- and he decided to get to know...
Su Jin first.
And he put it into action immediately.
I think Dong Ha had perfect timing.
Su Jin had feelings for Hyun Jin.
But yesterday night,
After she found out about his age and occupation.
- she saw the revealed information.
- Yes.
- She was a bit shocked.
- That's right.
She was very perplexed...
- about it herself.
- She was distraught.
With Dong Ha's sudden appearance,
she'll think, "How would it be like to date him?"
Now she has something else to look forward to.
- Yes.
- Now that he's set his mind to it,
Dong Ha flirts differently, doesn't he?
He's not curious about her age or job.
"I'm curious about who you chose." That's what he said.
- My heart skipped a beat at that.
- That...
"Who would you choose if you could choose a date?"
- "I'll choose you." - "I'll choose you."
"You."
I'm looking forward to how things will unfold.
Jeong Geun said...
- that it would turn into a jungle.
- Yes.
- I wonder what will happen next.
- It's fascinating.
- Shall we continue watching?
- Yes.
- Good job.
(The busy morning flirting is over.)
- Have a good rest. See you later.
- You too.
- See you later.
- Bye.
What?
- Why?
- Seriously...
(What did Dong Ha and Su Jin see?)
What is it?
- It just says you can use it today.
- You can use it.
(The infinity pool is available between 9am and 12pm today.)
- "The infinity pool?" - Swimming!
They're going to swim.
Jeong Geun, show them.
Show them.
(The infinity pool, soon to turn into a jungle, is now open!)
(What kind of charms will they show off in the pool?)
Is it a bit short?
No, it looks fine.
Your lower body is so fit.
- I have strong legs.
- They're no joke.
(Jeong Geun, who is proud of his upper body, walks in leisurely.)
(An investment strategist's strategy to show off in the pool)
(Pumping up his muscles)
He's doing push-ups now.
He wants to pump up his muscles.
(This time, he focuses on his arms.)
Look at those veins.
Isn't 6kg too easy for you?
- Sorry?
- Isn't 6kg too easy for you?
- No more than 6kg.
- Isn't it too light?
This is the most I can do.
Do men get sensitive at times like that?
Of course.
Dong Ha isn't even thinking of holding one.
He's already lost.
(What about the women's dorm?)
- Stay calm.
Choi Ji Eun, stay calm.
- Did she wear that?
- But this is too...
- What is it?
- I picked her swimsuit for her.
- I find it too cringey.
- I'm checking if she wore it.
It's not cringey at all.
- I should wear this on top.
- Yes, wear it on top.
That's it.
- Like this.
- Yes.
- It's good.
- Or...
(She's serious about styling her swimwear.)
No.
- Go with that.
- Like this.
Yes. If you're going to wear that, go with that one.
(She's so pretty!)
What a hot girl!
- It's "Too Hot to Handle." - She looks stunning.
Hot girl.
(Amazed)
- You look so cool.
- Look.
I did want to go to a swimming pool.
It'll be fun.
It gives off "Single's Inferno" vibe.
I told her to bring a swimsuit that would suit "Single's Inferno."
(It suddenly became "Single's Inferno.")
- Look at the weather.
- It's insane.
It's so nice.
(They walk confidently toward the swimming pool.)
- I can hear the water.
- It's so nice.
You can't resist going in.
As soon as I come up...
The water looks cold, doesn't it?
- Shall we go in?
- Should we go in first?
Shouldn't we warm up first?
Or you might have a heart attack.
- Not bad, isn't he?
- My gosh.
He's in great shape.
- Hold on.
- He's in great shape.
Rather than revealing strategically...
Goodness. What?
- That was so unexpected.
- You should know when to undress.
The water looks pretty deep.
- No?
- It's okay.
- My gosh.
- As expected.
Hyun Jin doesn't lose to him.
- He doesn't.
- Right?
(His upper body muscles are pumped up.)
It's not that cold.
Are you going in already?
(Staring)
My body isn't ready.
(Squeezing out)
Sunscreen. He's cute.
He's a dermatologist, you see.
He's a dermatologist.
- A dermatologist sure is different.
- He needs to have perfect skin.
(Blocking the UV comes before pumping up muscles.)
Well...
It wasn't easy for me.
So...
You guys are amazing.
- The best-looking one.
- An idol singer.
- The center member.
(Chatting)
You're the idol.
- Wasn't it embarrassing?
- It was.
- Right?
- Look at Sin Young.
- She's cool.
- So cool.
- Look at Su Jin.
- You look cool, Sin Young.
- They all look so good.
- They really keep themselves fit.
(The ladies arrive at the pool in their unique swimsuits!)
- My gosh.
- What is it?
They're shirtless.
Of course. It's a swimming pool.
I told her not to bring that windbreaker.
Really?
They're already in the pool.
(Everyone has gathered at the pool.)
- Are they already in?
- Be careful.
(Suddenly lying down)
- Who is that?
- Who's that?
Is that you, Hyun Jin? Hyun...
It's dangerous. You might fall.
It's tilted to this side.
Exactly. Be careful.
You're not there to have fun yourself, Hyun Jin.
Did you go all the way there to play in the pool?
(He is frustrated by his friend acting like a seal.)
By the way...
(Geon Wu, who is proud of his legs, takes off his shirt too.)
(She watches it happen right in front of her eyes.)
(Oh, my gosh.)
Look at his body.
(Geon Wu joins the muscular men.)
What's up with them all?
I didn't expect this.
Hyun Jin caught my eye.
I could tell that he worked out a lot.
They all seem to exercise a lot.
I'm sure they were waiting to show off.
(These muscular guys have been waiting to swim.)
Hold on. What's this?
(Her eyes are fixed on them.)
Jeong Geun always wore revealing clothes,
- so I knew about him.
- What are you talking about?
- He only showed his arms.
- I mean...
- It's so...
- You could expect that much...
- from Jeong Geun, but Hyun Jin...
- Exactly.
- was totally unexpected.
- Hyun Jin.
He had himself fully covered.
- His muscles are...
- Seriously.
- very angry.
- What a man.
- What a man he is.
- It's so...
He loves to exercise.
He's done crossfit and kickboxing for a long time.
- Really?
- That's impressive.
Yes, so...
I told him, "Don't show off..."
- "your muscles intentionally." - Intentionally.
He really didn't do it purposely.
It was natural.
I'll take it off later.
Are you going in with that on?
For now...
I'll take it off for now.
I'll run in quickly.
I...
This isn't it.
Sin Young stood out to me.
Her skin was tanned a healthy shade,
and she was overflowing with confidence.
Sin Young had a very firm body,
and I think she stood out the most to everyone.
The water isn't that cold.
(Sin Young's charms shine even more at the swimming pool.)
(Ji Eun enters the water slowly.)
Why is she wearing that top?
(She is upset about her friend's fashion.)
(Lastly, Su Jin gets ready to enter the water.)
(Su Jin chose a striking red swimsuit.)
She definitely works out a lot.
Look at her abs.
(Su Jin chose a striking red swimsuit.)
I saw Su Jin and could tell she kept herself fit.
It was a different side of her.
Su Jin. She wore a striking red swimsuit.
She looked cool.
- No, this...
- Here.
(This is a heart-pounding moment. They start playing in the water.)
It's war.
Let's play a game.
- Let's start here.
- The winners get to make a wish.
Sure.
- I like that.
- What did you say?
How are you going to split up?
Ladies, decide on a number each from 1 to 4.
We men will decide too.
- Play rock, paper, scissors.
- Yes.
Okay.
Two-on-two games?
Who you get paired up with is important too.
Don't let us hear you.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Who will they partner with?)
- Number 1, get going.
- Number 1, go.
Go, Number One.
(Who will become Sin Young's partner?)
Who is Number One?
(Male Number 1 quietly appears.)
(Couple Number 1, Sin Young and Dong Ha)
I wanted to become Dong Ha's partner.
It was a pity when I didn't.
(Who is Number 2 Su Jin's partner?)
Here comes Number Two.
(Submerging)
It's Hyun Jin.
Is it Hyun Jin?
(Couple Number 2, Su Jin and Hyun Jin)
(They were paired up both yesterday and today.)
"What is this?"
(Yesterday's Lovebud Matching Dates)
"Is this luck or fate or something like that at work?"
(Is it luck or fate or something like that at work?)
(The remaining men are Jeong Geun and Geon Wu.)
We played a game in pairs.
Honestly, in that situation, I feel most at ease with Jeong Geun.
Let's go.
- Number 3, go.
Number Three.
(Who will become Number 3 Da Hye's partner?)
Are you Number Three?
It's Jeong Geun.
- Jeong Geun.
- Jeong Geun and Da Hye.
Are we a pair?
Yes, this works.
Number Four.
(Couple Number 4, Ji Eun and Geon Wu)
Let's see...
- who runs faster.
- Okay.
(Warm-up game, the couple running)
Whether you carry one on the back or in your arms...
- Okay.
A piggyback, of course.
(The standard piggyback, Sin Young and Dong Ha)
I'll do that too.
(Submerging)
(A submerged piggyback, Su Jin and Hyun Jin)
Should we get ready?
(A light piggyback, Ji Eun and Geon Wu)
(Glancing)
- So I should sit down?
- Yes.
Go up there.
It's hot.
What stunt are you going to show us?
- Is this easier for you?
- Yes.
- I can hold onto you.
- It's okay.
No.
- I'm scared.
- Hurry up.
"What if I'm too heavy for him?"
I was a bit worried.
- No. I'm scared.
- Hurry up.
- She doesn't look happy.
She doesn't look happy.
Is carrying her on his shoulder...
- a big problem? Why?
- Yes.
It's an uncomfortable posture.
If he wins despite that, it's fine.
- No.
- He could never win.
That's not important.
- That's not important.
I think he'll win. Let's watch.
Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- Get ready.
- Hold me tight.
- Let's go.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
(For the warm-up game, the couple running starts.)
We can win!
- That's so much better.
- Push.
That's crazy.
- That's so much better.
- Push.
He's in the lead.
- I told you that he'd win!
- He's winning.
I told you that he'd win!
You're right. He's winning.
Wait.
(They win!)
Be careful.
How did you do that?
Good job.
(In 3rd place are Ji Eun and Geon Wu.)
(Submerging)
- I'm sorry. It's so slippery.
- It's okay.
(In 4th place are Su Jin and Hyun Jin)
The loser... I was the slowest.
You guys lost.
We lost.
I slipped there.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
It was so slippery that he almost tripped three times.
Frankly, I might've been faster if I had carried him instead.
(After the warm-up game)
- Should we do it in pairs?
- Yes.
(What will Jeong Geun and Da Hye, the couple in 1st place, wish for?)
Entrust the cooking to me.
I'm getting more confident...
in cooking since I came here.
Okay, you're the chef in charge.
Should I be the assistant chef, then?
As for the assistant chef,
can I choose myself?
Can I choose myself?
Sure, you can.
I want to cook with Ji Eun.
(I want to cook with Ji Eun.)
The two of them are set on each other.
- Let's play that.
- Chicken fight.
Yes, chicken fight.
(Team game, 4-on-4 chicken fight)
They're playing chicken fight too?
Should we have the losers cook breakfast tomorrow?
That sounds good.
- Here.
- We're one.
(Sin Young, Su Jin, Hyun Jin, and Dong Ha are in one team.)
- We're going to win.
- Yes.
Use this tactic.
Can Geon Wu carry me?
- I'm stronger than you think.
- Da Hye...
(Da Hye, Ji Eun, Geon Wu, and Jeong Geun are in one team.)
I'm very sure I won't lose to them.
Me too, actually.
- We're going to win anyway.
- We'll win.
- Me too, actually.
- I can hear you loud and clear.
That was so loud and clear.
There's not a chance that we'll lose to you.
- The match against Sin Young.
- Sin Young...
Just give up on winning that round.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- Who knows?
- She has the upper hand.
- She has long arms.
- She does have long arms.
Who will start?
(Who'll play the first round?)
Should we do this?
- Exactly. How...
- Take it slow.
You can do it. Show them, Sin Young.
- Get closer.
- Be careful.
(Sin Young versus Ji Eun)
You can do it, right?
I can't. What are you talking about?
She puts her hand only on him.
(Ji Eun naturally places her hand on Jeong Geun's shoulder.)
I could approach him more easily.
When I had to put my hand on one of them,
I chose Jeong Geun.
Let's go.
- You can do it.
- Let's go.
Try this. Let's go!
I'm not confident at all.
I'm so scared.
- Let's go.
- You guys come.
- Why?
- Wait.
- Wait. Calm down.
- Can I go?
- Let's go.
- I'm so scared.
She asked, "Can I go?"
Go.
(Initiating)
Show them what you've got.
It looks fun.
Watch your back.
Hold on.
I'm so scared. Hold on.
Go back!
- Okay.
- Be careful.
You won't lose to her. You can do it.
(Ji Eun starts to retaliate.)
Go on.
Go!
Sin Young, you must avoid her.
No, it...
- They might get hurt.
- She fights back.
Wait.
Okay, now is the time.
- Let's go!
- Go.
(Hyun Jin tries to support Sin Young who leans back.)
- She won.
- Yes!
(Unexpectedly, Ji Eun wins.)
Oh, my gosh.
- Good job.
- I...
I'm done for today.
(The paper doll announces that she's done for the day.)
- Good job.
- I'm done for today.
I saw the competitive side of her.
In that sense, she is very charming,
like a femme fatale.
That's what I thought.
If it concerns just me,
I'm not competitive in games at all.
But if I have someone on my team,
I believe that I have to do my best.
That was why I really did my best.
I really gave it my all.
It's okay.
(The next player gets ready.)
We're fine.
Right.
Look forward to it so that we don't get caught.
- No. Look at them.
- Does it hurt?
(Dong Ha puts Su Jin's hat on for her.)
Like this?
This way...
I couldn't hide my face.
- It bothered me too.
- This way...
- I see. Nice.
- It will be hidden.
- That's a good strategy.
- Nice one.
(Coming up with a plan for the game)
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
It's our strategy.
- What?
- What's wrong?
The hat will be hard to take off with that.
- It falls off like this.
- You can't do that.
I'll just untie my hair.
(Dong Ha kindly fixes Su Jin's hat.)
(Da Hye watches that happen.)
Shall we begin?
- Just like that.
- We can attack and retreat.
- Don't worry about us.
- Right.
It's getting hot in here.
- Here we go.
- Let's go!
Let's go!
- I'll use my lower body now.
- Right.
- Or...
- Just let go of your hands.
- This is a good balance.
- All right.
- Don't hold onto it.
- Okay.
- They keep running away.
- Come at me.
Gosh, that looks exciting.
- This is a good balance.
- All right.
Gosh.
- I'm sorry! I hit your eye.
- She hit her.
Gosh.
- I'm sorry! I hit your eye.
- She hit her.
- Gosh.
Her elbow got him.
- I'm okay.
- Are you okay? I'm really sorry.
Hold on.
What's wrong?
- Right.
- Are you okay?
- Bring her down.
- I'm okay.
- Did he get hit?
- Are you okay?
- Did he get hit too?
What's wrong?
(Jeong Geun got hit hard by Da Hye's elbow.)
Jeong Geun.
- What's wrong?
- Was it her elbow?
- Are you okay?
- Did he get hurt?
Was it my elbow?
- I think when she came down...
- Are you okay?
Where did you get hit? Your nose or your eye?
- Was it his nose?
- His nose got hit.
- Are you not bleeding?
- Let me take a look.
- Is your bone okay?
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- Are you okay?
- I don't think he will be okay.
- That must have made him dizzy.
- Are you bleeding?
- I'm okay.
I got really worried.
Don't force yourself.
I'm okay.
(Jeong Geun tries to carry on with the game...)
(while pretending to be okay.)
I felt very flustered at that moment,
and Da Hye got really worried about me.
After that moment had went by,
I was totally fine about it.
But I knew that Da Hye was a soft-hearted person.
I knew that she was someone who was sensitive to emotions.
I really didn't like the fact that someone got hurt because of me.
I kept feeling bad about...
not being able to apologize properly to Jeong Geun.
He got hurt too.
(The time at the pool ends.)
Is your eye okay?
(In the women's room after being at the pool...)
My eye is fine. I just feel...
I just feel bad that someone got hurt because of me.
- Right.
- I know nobody would care.
You just feel bad about it.
It would've been better if I was the one to get hurt.
Since I was the one to make someone get hurt...
- It wasn't done on purpose.
- Definitely not.
It just happened while playing the game.
- It just happened out of nowhere.
- Right.
We had to carry on as the mood can't go down too much.
Things would've been serious if we had taken some time off.
Da Hye feels worse as she was the one to hit him.
- Right.
I thought that we would take some time off.
- I think so.
- Yes.
(Da Hye feels bad as she was the one to hurt Jeong Geun.)
That was why I lost my mind.
And...
I didn't like how things became awkward.
It just...
(Da Hye keeps shedding tears.)
Knock, knock.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm coming in.
- Are you on the second floor?
- Yes.
I'm okay though.
- Is Da Hye in there?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- Were you talking?
- We were talking.
- Really?
- Who is it?
- Could I talk for a while?
- With Da Hye?
- Yes.
- I think...
- Who is it?
This is the only time I can talk to her.
- It's me, Hyun Jin.
- But...
- Is this a bad time?
- Turn back.
- Well...
Gosh, this is a bad time.
(This is not the time, Hyun Jin.)
Dating must be about luck.
(Gritting his teeth)
I think it'll be better if you come later.
What is it, Hyun Jin?
I just wanted to talk to you.
- Sounds good.
- That was why I came.
- I was just...
- Right. I got worried.
It's something that Hyun Jin can hear about.
- Just give me 5 minutes.
- Just 5 minutes?
- Just five minutes.
- Will you be okay with that?
You want to be just with me, right?
- Right.
- Okay.
Okay.
Hyun Jin suddenly appeared at that moment.
He said he wanted to talk to me...
at that moment.
I wondered if something happened...
or if he figured out that I cried.
- I needed some time.
- Right.
I'm fine now.
Did something happen?
No. It's just what happened in the pool.
Was it because of that moment?
Well...
I thought that I was the only one to get hurt.
Right. Jeong Geun.
I'm totally fine with what happened to me.
- But... You know, right?
- Right. I know what you mean.
(Hyun Jin understands Da Hye's heavy heart.)
I felt bad about that moment.
That was why...
- Would you like some candy?
- Sure.
- It will make you feel better.
- Right.
- I didn't eat too. Sure.
- Two pieces?
I'll take two. I did have a cookie.
It was something that I brought.
I was just talking about that moment.
- That was why I felt upset.
- Right.
Don't feel upset.
- I'm fine now.
- Do you need more water in that?
- I mean, let it out.
- Right.
- Forget about it.
Hyun Jin feels like an older brother.
He came to her as he wanted to talk.
Right now, all he can do is listen to Da Hye.
It seemed like a bad time to approach her at first,
- but it seemed to have worked out.
- It worked out?
(The timing was a blessing in disguise?)
It turned out to be a good time to approach her.
- He's hearing her heart?
- Right.
The two of us kept mentioning this.
We said that Hyun Jin felt very charming...
the more and more we saw him.
- Right?
- Yes. Seriously.
- We had our first 1-on-1 dates.
- Right.
That was when...
- I talked to Su Jin.
- Right.
- How was it for you?
- I confidently said...
that I was interested in two people.
- Right.
- I told her that...
when Su Jin asked me.
There definitely are people who you are more concerned about.
Right.
Am I one of those two?
You're asking me that straight up like that?
Since you mustered up your courage,
I think it will be better for me if I clearly know how things are.
I think I know who the other person is then.
Who do you think it is?
- It's Su Jin.
- Right.
Right?
- It's Su Jin.
- Right.
Right?
- Was I that easy to read?
- Right.
No. Just the timing of everything...
Well..
I'm right, aren't I?
Is there a hole around here I can hide myself in?
That's not something to be embarrassed about.
Even if...
I try to hide my heart and express myself carefully,
it will be obvious.
If that's the case,
there's no need to hide things.
I should just express myself while following my heart.
I thought,
"Does Da Hye find me to be uncomfortable?"
- These conversations are great.
- Right.
I didn't feel that before.
I'm not saying I was offended or anything,
but I was just curious.
- "Why is she like that to me?" - I'm not uncomfortable around you.
- "Is it awkward to be with me?" - No.
"Am I uncomfortable to be with?" I had these questions in mind.
There was this though.
During our first night, when we ate late at night,
we talked about marriage and family plans.
You were so detailed about it,
and you shared about your love toward your nephews and family.
To be honest, I couldn't really relate to what you said.
(First night)
This could be a sensitive topic.
It's the same with kids.
I really like kids.
I really do.
- That's understandable.
- I love my nephews too.
- You have nephews.
- I find them to be adorable.
Your nephews could make you feel that way.
My older brother had kids,
and it made me go crazy.
It made me think that life would feel so meaningful that way.
That was why I wanted to make my own family,
have kids,
and live that life.
He was a bit too honest from the first night.
(Hyun Jin went ahead of himself on the first night.)
- I was worried about that.
- That could've felt burdensome.
- Right.
Women would definitely find it burdensome...
to hear something like that during their first encounter.
Hyun Jin said that it was his goal...
to get married.
I understand why.
Regardless of his age,
Hyun Jin wanted to make his own family...
- ever since he was young.
- Right. That's understandable.
- Age doesn't matter.
- Right.
He wants to be settled down quickly too.
He wasn't able to make that happen...
and ended up coming this far.
(He ended up coming this far.)
Love is such a difficult thing.
I should've told him not to be like that.
- It's difficult, - Gosh.
- and the timing has to work out.
- I wasn't able to tell him.
No. It's okay. Let's keep going.
To be honest, I couldn't really relate to what you said.
That was why I thought...
you already had...
- marriage in your mind.
- Right.
That was why I felt that you were more of an elder.
- "Elder?" - Right.
I felt that from you.
It wasn't based on your looks or actions.
I felt that from your words.
- Elder isn't the right word.
- That's understandable.
I thought that you were more mature than me.
I'm someone...
who still finds my job and career...
to be important as of right now.
You seemed to be certain about your values, so...
Rather than calling it a barrier,
I thought that these things could become a problem...
if we got closer.
I think that was what was going through my mind...
- now that I think about it.
- Right.
I'm being completely honest right now.
- I see. That's understandable.
- Right.
Understood. I know what you mean.
Right. Anyway...
We still have...
Whether it is a lot or a short amount of time,
- but we still have time left.
- Right.
- Let's keep things open.
- Sounds good.
- We can spend more time together.
- Right.
- We started our conversation.
- He did well to talk to her.
- It felt as if...
he confessed his feelings to her and got dumped right away...
- in a calm manner.
- No. That's not true.
- That's not true.
- After having some coffee, - He did well.
It feels like the two of them are over now.
- No.
- She was just honest.
What do you think as the strategist?
In my opinion, it's safe to say it's over for them.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Right.
- I think the same way.
- I believe it's over...
for the two of them.
This was what I thought...
after listening to that conversation.
There was a misunderstanding,
and she just wanted to solve that misunderstanding.
Hyun Jin asked if...
she felt uncomfortable about him.
That conversation was to solve that misunderstanding.
It wasn't a conversation...
about wanting to learn more about each other.
I don't think they would work out.
Right. That was what I thought too.
Hey.
What are you drinking?
- Coffee.
- Alone?
- I was about to read.
- What?
- Alone?
Let's drink coffee together. I want some too.
(Dong Ha tries to spend time with Su Jin.)
He's so expressive.
Dong Ha is amazing with his timing.
Gosh, it's so nice. This place is really nice.
(Su Jin and Dong Ha spend a relaxed afternoon together.)
I have a question.
Why is the Eiffel Tower your phone wallpaper?
I think I already told you my reason.
The reason why the wallpaper is the Eiffel Tower?
I love Paris.
I went to Paris around five times.
You feel attached?
I love Paris the most.
That's amazing.
We have the same wallpaper.
Really? The Eiffel Tower?
Really? I got chills.
Should we show it to the camera?
(The two had the same wallpaper.)
Dong Ha was always by Su Jin.
But I'm okay today.
You're right.
(Su Jin showed Dong Ha her tattoo.)
Oh, I see.
Guess what it is.
Can I see it again?
No...
Right.
No... Is that your baptismal name?
What? How did you know?
- Noella?
- What?
- What is it? What did he say?
- Awesome!
Guess what this is.
(Dong Ha was the only one to understand her tattoo.)
- I have no idea.
- Guess what it is.
What? Matcha?
Ne...
What? Ne...
I asked him to guess, and he got it right away.
Really? What is it?
- It's her baptismal name.
- My baptismal name.
How did you know? Are you catholic?
Yes.
- They follow the same religion too.
- They follow the same religion.
They follow the same religion too.
I got goosebumps when you guessed my baptismal name.
Your baptismal name?
How did you know that this was "Noella?"
My older brother has "Noel" here just like me.
- "Noel?" - Noel and Noella.
"Noel and Noella."
I have this.
The pilgrim routes?
That's what it represents?
You recognized it right away.
It's because you're Catholic too.
- The Camino de Santiago.
- What?
- What is it between these two?
- Gosh.
- They have so much in common.
- This is a big connection.
- Right.
- After my first visit, - Yes.
I got baptized because I wanted to.
(They have tattoos on the same spot that represent their religion.)
This is amazing.
No one else understood what it was.
(Dong Ha and Su Jin find out that they have a lot in common...)
(as they learn about each other.)
We just clicked and understood each other right away.
We could talk about religion freely too.
It was great that...
we didn't have to explain things to each other...
in different aspects.
Do you take time to think?
What is your ideal type?
- My ideal type?
- Yes.
When I was asked about what I saw first,
I said it was height.
I like tall people.
When I first met you,
you were a tall person who came to pick me up.
- You came to pick me up.
- Right. I picked you up.
- I was the first person you met.
- Right.
That's it?
As I'm a bit extroverted,
I find it hard to be with people who prefer to stay at home.
Even when I'm alone and have nothing to do on a Sunday.
I go to a cafe.
I'm someone who gets sick if I stay at home.
You're just like me.
Is there someone else you wish to talk to other than me?
- Me?
- Yes.
Well...
I'm not sure.
I might get shaken if the other men make a move.
I've really left my heart open.
- What? Right.
- I've really left it open.
I think...
- That was a vague answer.
- What?
That was a vague answer.
(Su Jin's answer was vague.)
I can't even expect what will happen today.
(What are Su Jin and Dong Ha feeling right now?)
- She didn't answer him.
- What could that mean?
- She gave a vague answer.
(Su Jin didn't answer Dong Ha's question.)
So Dong Ha isn't interested in her, right?
- He was straightforward all along.
- Right.
He had an interest in Su Jin and Ji Eun,
so he wanted to learn more about them and talk to them.
He expressed that he wanted to go on dates with them too.
He said that last night,
so he's putting things into action.
I think he will go straight to Ji Eun...
after talking to her.
Really?
- Let's see.
- I felt this...
after listening to their conversation.
He did pick two women,
but he seemed to start this conversation...
- just to learn about who Su Jin is.
- Right.
The tone of the conversation...
- feels like...
- There's no feeling of love.
- he isn't really into her.
- You saw that?
That was a sharp analysis.
How would Dong Ha look when he's in love?
In my opinion,
he hasn't shown his true emotions yet.
What is it? Can we go inside?
- Come on!
- Hold on.
- It's torn off. It's a mess.
- I got a rush of dopamine.
Gosh, there's something on the wall again.
Oh, no.
(There's something on the board like it did on the second day.)
(The result of their second pick last night)
(This is what your hearts are saying.)
Again?
Da Hye got one vote.
Didn't Hyun Jin get a vote?
(Kim Sin Young)
It's okay.
You shine just on your own.
(You shine just on your own.)
Stop me from seeing this.
Please stop me from seeing this.
Okay. I got it.
And Geon Wu is there to check it too.
- I know.
- Okay. I got it.
(Geon Wu picked Da Hye after going on a date with Sin Young.)
(Sighing)
Honestly, I was a bit disappointed.
Is Sin Young the only one...
who doesn't get to disclose her age and job, then?
She is a mysterious woman.
- Until the end?
- Yes. She's mysterious.
(Welfare Center for People with Disabilities)
(This welfare center serves as a stepping stone...)
(to independence for people with disabilities.)
(Integrated Office)
Hello. I'm a social worker with eight years of experience.
(Ms. Kim is cute. I love you.)
- Five, six, - Five, six,
- seven. That's enough.
- seven, eight.
What I do is plan various programs for adults with disabilities...
so that they can enjoy cultural and leisure activities.
Two, three.
- Look up.
- Five.
- Raise your chin.
- Two.
(Counseling in session)
When the visitors come for the first time,
I introduce them to various programs,
including sports, arts and crafts, cooking, and excursions.
(Kim Sin Young, 30, a social worker with 8 years of experience)
I got it.
(Shin Dong Ha)
I think Da Hye picked me.
(After taking a break, )
(Jeong Geun comes to the common area.)
Yes. That's our memories.
- Look at that.
- You're here.
(Which name is at the end of Jeong Geun's gaze?)
(Choi Ji Eun)
(Ji Eun's name was taken by two people again.)
(Jeong Geun seems to have a lot on his mind.)
Only Ji Eun...
got two votes again.
In fact, I suspected that 1 of the 2 votes...
was cast by Dong Ha.
(Lastly, Hyun Jin and Da Hye join them.)
- I don't want to see it.
- I want to be alone,
so everyone leave.
(After getting 0 votes for the first impression, )
(Hyun Jin's name is finally taken.)
I assumed it was Su Jin.
Can I leave the door open?
- Yes.
- I don't have to close it, right?
Let's open it now.
It will be revealed now, won't it?
(They check the envelope on the board together.)
Please read it out loud.
- There's only 1 sheet.
- Only 1 sheet?
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- Those who got chosen last night...
- Those who got chosen...
Geon Wu, Dong Ha, Hyun Jin, and Jeong Geun.
Ask the person you want to know better on a date.
(Geon Wu, Dong Ha, Hyun Jin, and Jeong Geun.)
(Ask the person you want to know better on a date.)
- Since all four got a vote.
- That's right.
Ask the person you want to know better on a date.
- Now, we can clearly see...
- But...
- who they're into. Yes.
- it might overlap.
- They might choose the same person.
- In that case,
will they still go on a date?
- Will they?
- Please.
One might have a date with a group.
- That's possible.
- Yes.
- Just grab her hand and leave.
- Hurry.
Hurry and go for it.
They told the guys to ask out on a date.
But it sounded like it was on a first-come, first-served basis.
The one who makes the move first is the winner.
(After reading the announcement, a subtle tension is created.)
I didn't need time to think.
It was clear who I wanted to ask out on a date today.
I should go for it.
Good. Who should I go with?
I thought that when the opportunity presents itself, I should take it.
(Who will the guys ask out on a date?)
Don’t hesitate to express your feelings.
- Let's go.
- Okay. I'm going.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- It's Su Jin!
- He's cool.
He's cool.
"Hey, let's go."
- That was cool.
- He just went,
- "Let's go." - I was right, wasn't I?
- It's the Eiffel Tower couple.
- Gosh.
- I'll just say it.
- Okay.
- Ji Eun, let's go.
- Right away.
(Nodding)
(The second match is Ji Eun and Jeong Geun.)
I'll dash...
to the person I was curious about.
- I'll ask her out on a date.
- Say it.
Say it.
- Sin Young.
- Yes.
Nam Hee!
- "Sin Young." - Sin Young.
- Gosh. Really?
- Let's go out on a date.
- Really?
- Okay.
- Okay. Good.
- Let's go.
- Good.
- I...
The courageous ones go for it right away.
- Yes. Right away.
- Yes.
This is new. It's a new way of picking.
- Do you want to come?
- What? Yes.
(The last match is Da Hye and Geon Wu.)
I'll take this opportunity to talk more with Da Hye.
I didn't know Hyun Jin had a feeling toward Sin Young.
(What's with the two?)
- Ye Eun...
- I thought he'd pick Da Hye.
Made a dolphin sound for the first time on the show.
- Really?
- Ye Eun made the sound. Yes.
- I'm proud for some reason.
- This is fun.
(A date chosen by the men)
Gosh. It's sunny now.
(Su Jin and Dong Ha are the first to leave.)
- The trees are dense here.
- Yes.
We're going through a mountain.
I wanted to take her to an open space.
The guys have chosen the course for the date, right?
- That's right.
- Yes.
(Where is this open space Dong Ha has prepared for Su Jin?)
Good. When the sun sets, it will be crazy.
(Reaching)
Thank you.
(Sensitive Dong Ha noticed it right away.)
- Well...
- Yes.
We met for the first time two days ago.
- It feels like a long time ago.
I know.
I'm worried about one thing a little right now.
Yes? What is it?
The age difference between you and me.
- If there's a big age gap, - Yes.
It'll be hard for me to make a move.
It might be hard on you.
- It might look ugly.
- Well...
It would be a big burden.
- For the other person?
- Yes.
That's possible.
(Last night)
(She chose Hyun Jin...)
(and found out about his occupation and age.)
"Oh Hyun Jin is 39. He is a stage and musical actor."
"Thirty-nine years old."
I was shocked.
For me,
the maximum age difference is six years older or younger.
Seriously.
She has an age gap limit,
- which is 6 years.
- It's 6 years.
- The limit is six years?
- Su Jin.
It's okay to go over six years, Su Jin.
Since she's never dated before, she might be more careful.
Will they grow apart again?
But Su Jin is...
(Will she change her mind after knowing Dong Ha's age?)
- The smell of the sea?
- Yes.
(Ji Eun and Jeong Geun were the second to leave.)
They have women's clothes.
We can also check out fashion accessories...
- and jewelry.
- I see.
Let's take a look.
Ji Eun was wearing...
a beaded necklace.
I wanted to get her something that suited her.
That was what I wanted to do.
(Jeong Geun wanted to give her a meaningful gift.)
Do you not like plushies?
- I like them, - I see.
But I try to refrain myself.
- Really?
- Yes.
Do you collect them?
I used to buy them when I traveled overseas.
It will be great...
if it's something you can hang on your bag or suitcase.
- What about that one, then?
- Which one?
That one's cute.
What? Hold on.
- I can put it up here.
- Not me.
- No, not on me.
- It suits perfectly.
I just realized that you don't have a bag.
I don't carry bags around.
Really?
I can do something like this.
Isn't this adorable?
This is my type.
- Is that Jeong Geun's type?
- Yes.
I have nothing to say, then.
A card wallet.
(What would suit Ji Eun's taste?)
Let's buy something we can take away...
as souvenirs.
Should we get matching bracelets?
- What?
- "Matching bracelets?"
Ji Eun asked him to buy a pair.
Ji Eun brought it up first.
What? We can handle it.
Am I a feminine man?
You can wear it.
Why? Why not?
I was very flustered.
When it comes to cute little things,
I haven't tried them or even thought of trying them.
- Should we get matching bracelets?
- Still,
- Bracelets?
- Yes.
Deep down,
I was really happy.
He's obviously not the type of person...
who would wear something showy.
I was a bit excited.
Are they becoming an official couple?
If they wear matching bracelets while staying there,
- it's obvious.
- Yes.
It's like, "Don't bother us."
Aren't they like fetters?
- Fetters?
- That's right.
- But, as for me...
- Yes.
- personally, - Yes.
I think we're reading too much...
into wearing matching bracelets here.
- What?
- It's obvious.
- They can all see them.
- It's plain to see.
I'll read into it.
It's a done deal.
I think Ji Eun just casually asked...
- No.
- No?
- It's not casual.
- It isn't.
- No, they're matching...
- It's a couple's item.
They're literally the bracelets for couples.
In the early stages of dating,
when a woman asks to get a matching item,
- what should we think of it?
- That's surely...
- a way to ask...
- "Do you want to go out?"
- "Do you want to see each other?" - That's right.
Is it like, "Say you have feelings for me right now?"
Also, asking to get matching items...
is being flirty too.
She knows that he likes her,
so she asks, "Should we get matching items?"
To throw the ball into his court.
- To see how he reacts?
- Knowing he wouldn't refuse it.
- "He wouldn't refuse it." - Now,
- Jeong Geun is in Ji Eun's palm.
- You're right.
- The tables have turned.
- She has control over him.
He has become a feminine man from a masculine man.
You choose one for me.
Really?
- If you choose one, - You...
- I'll wear it.
- don't know what I'll pick.
In return, I'll choose yours.
(They pick bracelets for each other.)
I think this will look good on you.
Unlike how they look,
they are a masculine woman and a feminine man.
- In reverse.
- Right.
A very cool-headed investment strategist...
- has met a girl...
- Yes.
And has softened.
Do you like pink?
- No.
- No? Try this.
It looks good on you.
That's yours.
- Really?
- Yes.
(A white-pearl bracelet that suits Ji Eun well)
Can I pick one for you now?
Go ahead.
(Thinking hard)
No. That's not it, either.
Okay. Then...
You're careful.
Here.
- Okay. Let's get this one.
- Okay.
- I cut you some slack.
- Is this it? Okay.
- Yes.
Good. I'll wear it from now on.
- In Jeong Geun's life, - Yes.
- it's the only one.
- You're right.
(The first bracelet in his life was picked by Ji Eun.)
It has a smiley here too.
I'm not used to wearing this kind of bracelet at all.
I...
liked it.
I could tell...
that he was trying for me.
He was really cute.
(She adores Jeong Geun wearing the bracelet.)
Jeong Geun has mellowed out all of a sudden.
- I mean...
- He has become a softie.
When he wants to win her heart,
- he doesn't hesitate.
- He has softened.
But suddenly,
- This is what it feels like.
- he is softer.
When a man truly loves someone,
- he acts like Jeong Geun.
- You're right.
That's what a man does when he is in love.
When they're not fully in love, they act like Dong Ha.
When they're not as much in love, they act like Dong Ha.
- When he's totally in love, - Right.
- He's a player.
- he acts like Jeong Geun.
- I thought Jeong Geun would lead.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- I didn't expect he'd be led...
- especially by Ji Eun.
- He's led by her.
I didn't expect Ji Eun to act like that.
Ji Eun is dragging him around by his collar.
- He's been dragged around.
- Not by the collar.
- He's on the leash.
- He's like a puppy.
He's not a feminine man, but a puppy man.
- He's a puppy man.
- A puppy man.
He's become a puppy man, indeed.
(That evening)
You'll break the bracelet.
No one has noticed...
the bracelet I'm wearing, right?
It goes better with what you're wearing right now.
- With this?
- Yes, actually.
When would I wear an accessory like this?
- If not now, then when?
- Now.
Here's what we'll do.
(What is Jeong Geun about to say?)
Until Sunday,
no matter what happens,
we won't take them off.
Will you be able to do that?
(What?)
I was like, "What?"
Will you be able to do that?
I'm just asking.
- Let's do that.
- Okay.
(But later on, these bracelets...)
(sparks a misunderstanding.)
No. Don't get me wrong.
I wanted to turn back time.
- Really?
- Yes.
You won't put on in from now on.
I'll keep it.
I regretted it a little.
At that moment,
my face really went stiff.
This is driving me nuts. Seriously.
When I recall it now,
I still get extremely upset.
Should I run away?
(What will happen to these two?)
- What?
- Why?
- What is this all of a sudden?
She must have taken it off.
Wait. Wasn't the guy sitting in front of Ji Eun...
Dong Ha?
- Hold on.
- Wait.
Was it? Was it Dong Ha's clothes?
- Was it him?
- Hold on.
- Please rewind it a little.
- Wait a second.
- What's going on?
- This is getting interesting.
(This is getting interesting.)
(The dates picked by the men are not over yet.)
Is it okay if I don't answer it?
It wasn't consecutive, was it?
- Was it consecutive?
- Yes, it was.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Finding out about their true feelings)
(A date to reveal the feelings they couldn't express before)
I wish the others wouldn't come here.
Here? You want this place just for us?
Come. Come this way.
Come here.
Who is this person?
(A time that brings them closer together)
(Knocking on their hearts more without hesitation)
(While looking at them, he feels...)
Something between them is different from what I have with her.
Is this it?
It looks good on you.
It fits just the way I like it.
(And...)
(a confusing change in the atmosphere)
When I sat down,
her wrist was the first thing I saw.
(The bracelet is nowhere to be seen.)
I don't know. I just want to make sure.
Does she want to leave some room for someone else?
Do I have to suffer this badly?
It's overwhelming.
(At that moment, a new card arrives.)
Today, the women will pick their dates.
Who do you want to get to know more?
Ask the person out on a date after 30 minutes.
I was relieved.
I could do what I wanted to do more freely.
I'm nervous about this.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous in a different way. Do you get it?
Which way?
You can never know what's in someone's heart.
I wonder who Ji Eun will ask to go on a date.
(When the date begins, )
(the atmosphere shifts again.)
(You know what?)
(I actually know someone really great.)
(I’d love to introduce you this time.)
(Just open your heart a little.)
(You won’t regret meeting them.)
(Date My Friend)