Right!
-Ten seconds left.
-It's the last one.
Come on, hurry.
That thing, your bribe.
What? "Bribe"?
-What?
-A bribe?
The bribe you gave him.
-The bribe you gave to Peter Jason!
-Peter?
-Oh, the wine.
-What's it made from?
Grapes!
Yes!
Yes! I got it!
-Good job.
-That was amazing.
That was Gu Ae-jeong and Dokgo Jin's...
Mr. Dokgo, congratulations.
It's the first time anyone guessed
all ten words.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
Am I really the first one?
But Jin, what was that about your bribe?
You gave wine as a bribe
to Director Peter Jason?
You must bribe directors
with wine and whatnot.
-That must be the case.
-No, it wasn't a bribe.
It was just a small gift.
He must've really wanted to do the movie
to bribe the director.
We congratulate you again
for getting a part
in the film you wanted so much.
Thank you.
Finally, why don't you give Dokgo Jin
some words of encouragement
before he leaves for Hollywood, Ae-jeong?
-Words of encouragement?
-Yes.
Dokgo Jin, good luck filming at Hollywood!
Korea's national star actor
Dokgo Jin, good luck!
You can do it!
I can do it!
Wasn't that Quiz to Change the World?
A TV program?
Wait, but how did Peter come up?
Ae-jeong...
asked me about it.
Why did I take this call?
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you.
You hit the jackpot, Ae-jeong!
You’re part of Dokgo Jin’s circle now.
I should be okay, right?
-What if he's upset?
-Why would he be upset?
He kept bragging about going to Hollywood.
You spread the word for him.
He's not going anymore.
Peter told him not to come.
Really?
He was rejected?
That's so humiliating.
It's not like I stopped him from going.
I should be okay, right?
That's not your fault.
MR. ASSHOLE
What brings you here all of a sudden?
The shooting! How was it?
Yes, thanks so much to you.
You were really entertaining.
I see. You had fun.
You'll have fun watching it when it airs.
I don't know if I'll be able to watch it.
I guess you might be too busy.
Make sure to catch a re-run.
I won't be able to watch a re-run either.
-Why not?
-The quiz we did today
won't be aired.
-Why not?
-You, Gu Ae-jeong,
will tell them to edit that part out.
-Why would I do that?
-That's three "whys."
You still don't understand the situation?
Listen carefully.
I was going to announce
that I rejected Peter's offer.
You babbled that I bribed him.
Rejecting his offer
after bribing him with a gift
does not match up.
So that part can't be aired,
so it needs to be--
That's right.
Can't it be left in?
You're not even going to Hollywood.
Please let it go and help me out.
Where are you grabbing?
-Then you should just hit me, like this.
-Ouch.
I made a mistake.
I got really into the game
and just lost it for a moment.
-What are you doing?
-I’m really sorry!
Are you hitting your head with my fist?
Let go of me! I'm Dokgo Jin.
Since you’re Dokgo Jin
and loved by everyone,
you'll be forgiven
for anything you do, right?
So, please help me out.
If I ask them to edit it,
it'll be completely over for me.
Good. Stop presenting
your unlikeable, unforgivable self
and "clear and out."
It would be too obvious if I asked them,
so tell them you weren’t pleased
with the outcome,
and demand that they edit it.
And I don’t want anything to do
with someone like you,
so edit me out from your head.
Why are you still standing there?
Hey! “Clear and out”?
Is it that easy for you to tell someone
to end her career
just because you're embarrassed?
Have you lost it?
No wonder Peter rejected you.
You're so rude!
You have lost it.
Oh right, he rejected you
because your English stinks.
What? "Clear and out"? Nice try.
No wonder you got rejected
because of your English skills.
What did you say?
You, king of jerks. Okay?
Very much super dirty.
This much you can understand, right?
-Hello.
-Yes, hello.
-Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Nice to meet you, Dokgo Jin.
-You're really handsome.
-We're looking forward to the film.
Do you want his autograph?
Bye.
You said you don't want anything
to do with me, right?
Then, don’t call me
and don’t you dare follow me.
Where are you going?
Stop right there. Where are you going?
Get his autograph!
Oh, no.
Goodness, he’s following me.
He must be crazy.
Where do you think...
Hey!
Stop right there!
There's a car!
Stop!
Goodness.
Did he just hit my car?
Are you crazy?
How could you just run into my car?
Look here!
Hey, open your window!
-Hey!
-Gu Ae-jeong...
It's over for you now.
You're bleeding!
DOKGO JIN HOSPITALIZED
AFTER A CAR ACCIDENT!
Dokgo Jin!
-Dokgo Jin, how serious are your injuries?
-Dokgo Jin!
He hurt his leg.
We’ll provide you with the details later.
I heard it happened at the studio.
Who's the other person?
Well, it was another celebrity,
so we’re not at liberty
to disclose the name.
-One more question.
-Who was it?
DOKGO JIN SEVERLY HURT?
WHICH CELEBRITY IS RESPONSIBLE?
The car in front suddenly braked hard
and hit Dokgo Jin’s car.
I see. Then, who was in that car?
It looked like a celebrity’s car.
Why, thank you.
She’s a singer from a former girl group.
What was it...
National Treasure Girls, was it?
Gu Ae-jeong from there.
NATIONAL TREASURE GIRLS GU AE-JEONG
CAUSED DOKGO JIN'S ACCIDENT
She's here!
-How did the accident happen?
-Is Dokgo Jin okay?
Did you get into
an accident with Dokgo Jin?
Yes, I did.
We were both driving slowly in the garage,
so it was a light fender-bender.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
And Dokgo Jin should be fine, too.
DOKGO JIN IS HOSPITALIZED,
GU AE-JEONG IS FINE
-Dokgo Jin!
-What's going to happen with your film?
-Excuse me.
Due to his injury,
Dokgo Jin won't be starring in the film.
Unfortunately,
our plans for him to enter Hollywood...
have been canceled.
-Dokgo Jin!
-Are you really not going to Hollywood?
DOKGO JIN'S HOLLYWOOD PLANS
FALL THROUGH WITH INJURY
The interview can't be held in this state.
We'll take one question at a time.
Yes, Reporter Park.
Do you feel responsible
for Dokgo Jin's failed plans?
If you look into the matter,
you'll see that this isn't my fault.
Please comment on
the increase of your haters.
It's not my fault.
GU AE-JEONG CLAIMS "IT WASN'T HER FAULT"
What’s this?
They're calling her
the national Ankle Girl.
What's "Ankle Girl"?
A nationally acclaimed actor
prepares to enter Hollywood.
But Ae-jeong held him by the ankle
and now he can't go.
That's why she is the Ankle Girl.
How could he break his leg
in a parking lot accident?
And Dokgo Jin hit her from the rear.
The insurance company says
it's Dokgo Jin's fault.
Why does everyone blame Ae-jeong?
ANKLE GIRL GU AE-JEONG
For the past few days,
the top keyword has been
Ankle Girl Gu Ae-jeong.
Park Tae-hwan swims
in the 400 meter final,
in the Asian Games today.
but you’re the top search.
I didn’t know he was that hurt.
I should’ve held my anger back.
If it wasn't so negative,
this amount of attention is incredible.
People must recognize you
and curse you out on the streets!
I guess it's all over for me now.
But it's unfair that I'm responsible
for his not going to Hollywood.
Korea’s top actor, Dokgo Jin.
You can do it!
Play that again!
Good luck with Hollywood.
Korea’s top actor, Dokgo Jin!
You can do it!
-This is awesome.
-This shot is really awesome.
She said all this
and then caused the accident.
Gu Ae-jeong’s bad reputation
is going to last.
Seriously.
What do you think about someone like her
for this season of Couple Making?
She'll be hated from the onset,
and eliminated early on.
Isn't that an important role?
It would grab attention from the start.
Should we cast her?
What if I’m against casting Ae-jeong?
What?
I guess we’ll have to reconsider then.
Since I’m a professional,
I’ll put aside personal feelings
and consider if it'll help the show.
GWANGHYE MEDICAL CENTER
As long as he hasn't fainted
from the injury,
I should go talk to him, right?
But he didn't let you visit before.
And he won't take your calls.
He’s probably doing all that
because he’s upset.
So, as demeaning as it may be,
I need to get down on my knees
and beg.
-Let’s go.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
Just let us do a quick interview.
Dokgo Jin’s room is over there.
It’s surrounded by reporters,
nurses and even guards.
What time is it?
-Three o'clock.
-Let's wait a bit.
In a bit...
opportunity will come.
Hey, it's three o'clock!
Park Tae-hwan!
-Let's go.
-Over there!
-Is he on?
-Hurry!
Let's look at the athletes records
in the Olympics.
In the Asian Games of 2006...
You’ve been watching English shows nonstop
since you got here.
Be quiet. I'm studying English.
"Clear and out"? Nice try.
No wonder you got rejected
because of your English skills.
You, king of jerks. Okay?
Very much super dirty.
This much you can understand, right?
Jin.
Can we switch channels for a second?
Why?
Park Tae-hwan is swimming.
We should support him!
The competition is today?
-Isn't it an important race?
-Yes.
It's for the gold medal.
No, I mean my commercial depends on it.
If he wins the gold medal,
didn't you say he gets
my air conditional commercial?
There's talk about it--
Then he can't win the gold.
Come on, let’s see how it turns out.
You can watch it.
What about you?
You’ll be rooting for your commercial.
I’m going to root for him.
Good luck!
Whose side are you on?
Introducing the swimmers...
Sarit Tiewong from Thailand
in the first lane.
Korea's Park Tae-hwan is
in the second lane.
-Goodness.
-It's Park Tae-hwan!
Did it start?
-Really?
-Hurry up!
Get ready, okay?
Okay.
You have one shot, all right?
The competition will only last
a couple minutes.
I'll get past them then.
Good luck!
VIP SECTION KEEP NOISE TO MINIMUM
Park Tae-hwan! Swim faster!
Park Tae-hwan! Faster!
That's right.
-Hurry.
He's almost there.
Keep going.
You can do it!
-Just a bit more.
-You can do it Tae-hwan!
Park Tae-hwan! Faster!
VIP ROOM
DOKGO JIN
No!
Please, don’t get the first place!
Please don’t get first place!
My commercial!
Park Tae-hwan, please! My commercial!
Three, two... Park gets the gold medal!
-Yes!
He got the gold medal.
Damn it!
You’re fine.
You were jumping up and down.
-What’s this?
-Try jumping up and down again.
Weren’t you just using your leg?
Was it all a lie? It was a big, fat lie.
You used it as an excuse
for the Hollywood film.
Be quiet. Who are you to talk?
And here I was,
thinking you got hurt because of me.
People are cursing me
for being the reason
you couldn't go to Hollywood.
I knew for the longest time
that Peter rejected you,
but I didn’t say one word!
This is really unfair! Shame on you!
Quiet down! Someone might hear you!
I hope someone does!
There are a bunch of people
and reporters outside.
-Be quiet!
-Hey! He’s not hurt at all!
His leg is fine, too!
You jumped around hoping Park Tae-hwan
-wouldn’t win the gold, right?
-Be quiet!
I’m going to round everyone up.
And I’ll tell them everything!
Stop! Wait!
-Where are you going?
-Oh, my.
-My goodness. What are you doing?
-Stop right there!
-Stop--
-What are you doing!
Come here, you.
Park Tae-hwan won the gold!
Go to CEO Moon right now
and bring her here.
Okay.
You tried to kill me!
My heart rate hit 110...
because of you.
Just hold on.
I'll offer you a chance to negotiate.
ENDORSEMENT AGREEMENT
Wow.
Dokgo Jin must be really desperate
to offer all this
to someone like you.
Do you think I can trust him?
You have the upper hand in all of this.
Don’t let him get to you.
I guess his reputation really is huge,
considering how much he's paying
to preserve it.
He said he would hook you up.
I wonder what it is.
Isn’t your new show Couple Making
a program about matchmaking?
How bad would it look
if the host goes through a break-up?
-That--
-And if his US plans are canceled,
we don't need to announce the break-up.
So, that would work out for you as well.
Let's say I accept Ae-jeong.
Will the producers accept her?
I've already talked to them.
According to them,
they would audition her right now,
as long as you're okay with it.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
I’m here to see Ms. Moon in the VIP room.
Of course. A VIP guest has arrived.
I will show you to your room.
I don’t know very many people.
Finding a doctor to run the clinic
has been hard.
Who knew things could be hard for you?
I'm introducing to you
the most skilled doctor I know.
She was top of the class
at Kyung-in University.
I picked this place
so we could meet casually.
-Thanks.
-Don't mention it.
But since she’s competent and successful,
she'll want a lot of money.
If you like her, start high.
I’ve never done that before.
I don't know how I'll bring it up.
I’ll be right back.
You came!
Yes.
The others are here, so go on ahead.
I'll be back after a quick call.
The others?
I told you that I’d hook you up.
It’s a good opportunity, so impress him.
Okay.
I'm glad you found your way.
Yes, just continue walking.
Yes, you're right.
You're almost here.
I’ll be at the entrance,
so come down the stairs.
All right.
Excuse me...
Oh, you’re here.
We met outside,
but I was told to go in first.
I see. Have a seat.
Okay.
I’ve heard a lot about you.
You're known to be quite competent
and successful.
Me?
I wouldn't say successful.
You know where I stand right now, right?
Yes...
I don't know where to start.
Should we wait for my friend?
Yes, of course.
I want to tell you before we begin.
Please let me know how much money
you are looking for.
Money?
I heard you came here
because you need the money.
Rather than having me state a price,
you can state an offer
based on your value.
I need money?
-What do you mean--
-How much would you like?
The others are here, so go on ahead.
Remember I told you that I’d hook you up?
It’s a good opportunity, so impress him.
Is this one of those situations
that I’ve only heard about?
Are you
saying that you’re going to give me money?
Right. Because I’m going to employ you.
You want to buy me?
How much will you pay?
So, how much am I?
I'm sure you've been told this,
but I'm willing to match your price.
You're saying
that we're negotiating my price?
Can you give me a billion won?
-What?
-That must have shocked you.
As you should know,
I’m basically a national treasure.
-A billion--
-On second thought, a billion is too low.
I have lots of needs.
I have to buy a car, as well as a house.
I also need to open a golf
simulator facility for my dad and brother.
I'll probably need ten billion won
to do all that, right?
I'm worth ten billion won,
can you afford that?
Why? Do I seem crazy
for asking you for ten billion?
You told me to state my price!
You can’t give me ten billion?
You said to state any price!
Is ten billion too much?
Goodness.
How could you say such...
I think there was a misunderstanding!
Please have some water.
Excuse me, please drink this and calm--
You can't buy me at any price.
I’m a National Treasure Girl.
Don’t live like that!
You can’t buy or sell a national treasure.
Understood?
What should we do?
I feel sorry for her.
-Poor girl.
-What do we do?
Something really bad must've happened.
Why is she crying here?
Poor girl.
She's crying so hard.
Why is she crying in the bathroom though?
She's crying so much.
It's this room. Come in.
What happened to you?
What happened?
Did you stand under a storm?
Some woman claiming
that she's a national treasure
asked for ten billion won
then did this to me.
Being a national treasure
was my last pride.
How dare he think of me that way!
I can’t let this go.
Ae-jeong!
Why are you here? We've been waiting.
Did you confuse the rooms?
It’s this room.
Okay.
Please tell me how much you want.
I’ll try my best to match it.
I'd just want the same amount
from the hospital I used to work at.
Are there any other conditions?
No. That’ll be all.
You’re very straightforward.
Excuse me for a second.
Hi, Ae-jeong.
Long time no see.
Hi, Se-ri.
What brings you here?
Say hello.
The main producer of MBS' Couple Making.
Hello.
-The writer.
-Nice to meet you.
And the MC, Kang Se-ri.
Ae-jeong starring in a show
that Se-ri hosts
is going to be a big issue!
Of course.
They both became famous through me.
No, it’s because of their past history.
They were both National Treasure Girls.
Those National Treasure Sisters.
I can't stand them.
It’s National Treasure Girls.
Ae-jeong was way more popular back then.
And Se-ri was a nobody.
It should hurt Ae-jeong's pride.
Se-ri will probably enjoy being cocky
and mess around with her.
-No way.
-I know her too well.
Her personality is trash.
I guess you know since you’re alike.
What did you say?
-Jae-seok.
-Yes?
Don't just sit there.
Go check if the reporters are still here.
There aren’t any!
I sent them all away.
And I’ve been keeping watch.
So continue keeping watch outside.
Okay.
-Leave that here.
-Okay.
Are you unhappy or something?
Does it hurt your pride
to star in a show that I'm hosting?
If that's the case, don't do the show.
Honestly, I don't feel completely fine.
But I can’t refuse the show.
When we were in a group,
you would use your popularity
to stick me in shows.
Since we’ve switched places now,
just think of it
as me returning the favor.
Remember what you used to say to me?
“Don’t let your pride get hurt,
and do your best.”
Do your best, Ae-jeong.
Do you have any idea what you just did?
I told you that I was just joking around.
What did I do so wrong?
Se-ri, I'm...
What’s going on?
What happened?
Se-ri!
These all say
that Gu Ae-jeong is a bully.
GU AE-JEONG BECOMES ANKLE GIRL
AFTER CAUSING DOKGO JIN’S ACCIDENT
BANISH GU AE-JEONG FROM THE COUNTRY
IT'S WORSE THAT SHE'S UNSCRATCHED
KNEEL DOWN AND APOLOGIZE!
HOW CAN YOU EVEN EAT
AFTER WHAT YOU’VE DONE?
She’s getting a lot of hate for this.
JUST DIE
GU AE-JEONG BECOMES ANKLE GIRL
AFTER CAUSING DOKGO JIN’S ACCIDENT
All these hate comments
should be reported.
Who wrote this?
Username "Dokgo Enthusiast."
It's my fan.
Why did you want to see me?
Upload this.
I’ll publish an article confirming it.
"I just visited Dokgo Jin at the hospital.
I felt so bad seeing his leg
that broke because of me.
But he happily forgave me
and reassured me.
Thank you so much, Dokgo Jin.
Please pray for his speedy recovery."
I can't let people post terrible comments
about you because of me.
It's bad for my image.
That's the only reason why
I'm going to do this.
Are you really forgiving me?
What? Do you think I will?
Fine.
You don’t need to forgive me
on the inside.
At least on the outside, I'll be forgiven
and this situation should settle.
Then...
Can I make one more request?
What?
I need proof.
Could you take a photo with me?
A photo? With you?
Forget it.
I’m going to take it! One, two, three!
It came out well.
Let me see it.
Okay, post this one.
Go outside and do it.
Okay.
Dokgo Jin.
Thank you.
Tangerine?
Grapes!
If I post this,
maybe they’ll stop calling me cheeky
for not visiting him.
Am I smiling too hard?
Dokgo Jin.
I’m just visiting Dokgo Jin
at the hospital.
What's the news?
I got a call from Peter Jason.
He was shocked to hear about the injury.
So, what?
He wants to bring you back on board!
Wang Ryun must've been disappointing!
What?
I'm going to do Peter's film?
That’s right.
But you have to start next week.
No problem! Tell him I'll be there!
All right.
Since the press doesn’t know
about your cast yet,
take it off at once.
Okay!
Gu Ae-jeong.
I JUST VISITED DOKGO JIN AT THE HOSPITAL.
"But he happily forgave me
and reassured..."
"Reassured"? Huh.
No, Ae-jeong! The photo...
Your leg...
Goodness...
Not the photo...
VIP SECTION KEEP NOISE TO MINIMUM
HOSPITAL ELEVATOR
Gu Ae-jeong, please!
"Please pray for his speedy recovery."
Where are you, Gu Ae-jeong?
Upload.
UPLOADING YOUR POST
MY PAGE
LOADING
I JUST VISITED DOKGO JIN AT THE HOSPITAL.
Hey, Gu Ae-jeong!
It’s been uploaded!
Delete it! Hurry up and delete it!
Delete it!
I said, delete it!
People are already responding.
It’s been posted? You posted the photo?
Yes! Look at all the comments.
It's blowing up.
There's already an article about it!
DOKGO JIN FORGIVES GENEROUSLY
It didn’t work out.
He couldn’t delay the shoot.
He said he would have to go
with Wang Ryun,
and seemed so disappointed.
But it’s not like we can announce
that your injury was all a lie.
Let’s just assume you and Peter
weren’t meant to be this time around.
But honestly,
it’s not like I directly meddled
in his relationship with Peter.
But I feel like it’s my fault
for breaking them up.
Peter may not have come
to Dokgo Jin’s rescue,
but Dokgo Jin sure came to yours.
Your schedule is fully booked
for the entire week!
-Really?
-Ms. Gu!
-Hello!
Can you return next week
for another round of I Can Do It?
Of course! Thank you.
When is the recording?
COUPLE MAKING
WITH KANG SE-RI
Hello.
-Hello.
We have a meeting next week
with the entire cast.
-Okay.
-Let's do it well.
I'll do my best.
Did you sign the contract with Ae-jeong?
Yes.
And did she decide to do Se-ri’s show?
She must be happy.
And he...
Here...
Peter sent the wine back from LA
through Mr. Gong.
In the end, you’re the only one
who got really lucky.
Dokgo Jin is your knight in shining armor.
Peter Jason’s fickleness
is the biggest problem here!
Also, the fact that Se-ri
let you in her show
is a little fishy.
I know. Why did she do it?
Ae-jeong will grab some attention
and leave on the first round
of selections, right?
That decision will be up to the guy.
If our guy has peculiar taste,
she may stay on.
YUN PIL-JOO
Among all the male candidates...
...I like him the most. Who is he?
His name is Yun Pil-joo.
I knew him from high school.
He has an IQ of 160. He's brilliant.
Just look at him. He looks like a model!
A doctor of oriental medicine,
and comes from a good family.
He’s got it all.
But starring in a TV show
and going on dates
with female celebrities?
He won't want to do that.
If you can't persuade him,
I'll help you out.
If you meet him,
he might hurt your pride.
CHUNYEONG CLINIC
-Isn’t that Kang Se-ri?
-It is!
-It’s Kang Se-ri, right?
My goodness.
She has such a small face.
-She's so pretty.
-Aren’t you Kang Se-ri?
I’m here to see Dr. Yun Pil-joo.
Dr. Yun?
Of course. Please have a seat.
ORIENTAL MEDICINE TREATMENT
Kang Se-ri is here. Kang Se-ri!
Where is she?
Over there.
Eun-ho told me a lot about you.
I’m Yun Pil-joo.
I’m Kang Se-ri. I called you earlier.
It’s lunchtime, right?
Let’s talk over lunch.
I have 15 minutes left until lunchtime.
-Please have a seat and wait a bit.
-What?
-I’ll have carbonara.
-Okay.
-Just coffee for me.
You're not eating?
If you wanted me to eat,
you should've taken me to a private room.
People like me
can’t eat in open places like this.
Kang Se-ri, you’re so pretty!
You look like a doll.
Please give me your autograph!
Got it! Thank you.
Please give me your autograph.
I'm a fan. Please give me your autograph.
-Give me a second.
-Please sign here.
YUN PIL-JOO
Hello?
It's a method I use
to avoid annoying people.
If you stay on the phone,
they won't talk to you.
I see. Yes, I can talk.
Okay. Yes, it's fine.
I’m sorry. I have a call.
It's okay. You were saying?
Yes.
Right.
See? They just leave.
I guess it works.
I’m sorry.
I had no idea you'd be uncomfortable.
I’ve never eaten with a celebrity.
Why don’t you order now?
I'll find a better place for tea.
What’s good here?
Everything is pretty good.
But don't order the steak.
You can’t eat it while you're
on the phone.
Kang Se-ri was here?
She didn’t come for treatment.
I think she came
to cast Dr. Yun for a show.
Television? Which show?
For her show, Couple Making.
It’s a show where a successful bachelor
dates female celebrities.
A reality show?
That doesn’t suit my Pil-joo.
A medical documentary might.
Do you know Sungdam Skin Clinic?
The doctor there starred in a reality show
and his business hit the jackpot.
So many celebrities go there.
And he’s engaged to the anchor
he met on the show.
-Really?
-This show that recruited Dr. Yun
is even more popular than the other one!
As you can see,
I’m not suited for television.
Eun-ho forced me to at least meet you.
I have no wish to appear on the show.
At least take a look at our proposal.
Our previous bachelors
were also hesitant at first
and declined to do it.
But afterward,
they said that it was
a fun and exciting experience.
Wait.
Your nail color doesn’t look good.
And your palms are red.
-You drink a lot, right?
-What?
No, I mean...
Stick out your tongue.
What?
More than that, more.
You have coating, too.
You have bad breath in the morning, right?
Wait.
Am I sick?
You should stop by the hospital.
And cut back on drinking.
My lunch hour is nearly up.
I need to get going.
Since you came all the way here
to give me this,
I’ll take a look at it.
Goodbye.
I really didn’t think
he was going to pick up.
You look so pretty.
Look at my expression. I was so nervous.
He's not going to answer right away.
-I was so nervous right then.
-Hello?
-Isn’t it dramatic?
-It’s awesome.
AE-JEONG AND JIN CONNECTED
It's yellowish, and you peel it
and eat it. It's sour and sweet.
-A tangerine?
-Tangerine!
Didn't I describe it well?
-Yeah.
-The best. The perfect combo.
Move over, Dad!
-Just wait until you get old.
-I can't see.
You called Dokgo Jin with your phone
-and he took the quiz?
-Yeah, isn't that nice of him?
He's really good!
-Correct.
-There isn't much time left.
-Hurry up.
-It's red, and...
There's a seed in it.
-A plum?
-No, it's not that.
I wonder if he’s watching the show too.
It seems like she's stuck.
Time is ticking.
You say "lips like" this!
MR. ASSHOLE
Next.
It’s an erotic film. "Wild" something.
Strawberries?
-He got it.
-Correct!
-Hurry up.
-Yes.
-What you eat a lot in the summer.
-Melons.
No, not that.
-Peaches?
-No.
--It's red, and there are black seeds.
-Watermelon!
-The bribe you gave Peter Jason!
-Peter?
Oh, the wine.
-What's it made from?
-Grapes!
-Wow!
-He got it all right.
Yes!
Why did you do that?
Mr. Dokgo, congratulations.
You must bribe directors
with wine and whatnot.
No, it wasn't a bribe.
It was just a small gift.
COUPLE MAKING
He must've really wanted
to do the film to bribe the director.
We congratulate you for getting a part
in the film you wanted so much.
Wait.
This woman is the national treasure girl.
You know the National Treasure Girls.
-Pardon?
-It's her on television right now.
She's Gu Ae-jeong
from National Treasure Girls.
Ankle Girl, the hated celebrity.
Dokgo Jin, good luck!
It really is her.
GU AE-JEONG
Then why did she act like that?
I won't sit around like an idiot anymore.
Where are my car keys?
GU AE-JEONG
What do you want?
It’s yellow
and electricity comes out of its head.
What?
It starts with a “P” and ends with “chu.”
-Pikachu?
-Ding dong!
Who are you?
It’s a penguin with glasses.
It starts with “Po” and ends in “ro.”
It’s really cute.
-Pororo.
-Ding dong!
Hey, who are you?
Where's Ae-jeong?
It’s a train that huffs and puffs.
It starts with “Tho.”
Stop it! Who are you?
I said it starts with “Tho"!
Thomas! Satisfied?
-Get Ae-jeong on the phone!
-Ding dong!
Who are you talking to?
Hey! Did Ae-jeong make you call me?
Is she next to you?
Give her the phone now!
-What are you doing?
-The speed quiz.
Hey, Ding Dong!
Did Gu Ae-jeong tell you to mock me?
Answer me, Ding Dong!
Oh no, what do I do!
What do I do!
He must have copied
what he saw on television.
I’m really sorry.
You must've been surprised.
You should have just hung up sooner.
He kept going because you kept responding.
You answered three questions!
He gave me questions. I answered them.
Like how the phone rang and I answered it.
Why did you do that?
Yes. Why did I do that?
Forget it. Just go.
But I was wondering about something.
Why did you answer my call that time?
I didn’t think you would.
That's because I empathized with
your desperation just for a second.
Even though you getting rejected
from a quiz show
is completely different from me
getting rejected
from Peter Jason’s film.
Dokgo Jin.
Thank you so much.
I thought you did it out of annoyance
because I kept pestering you.
I'm so grateful
that you empathized with me.
You should be honored, not grateful.
By the way, why are you packing?
Are you going away?
I will no longer stay here like an idiot.
People are still outside.
Can you carry all your stuff on crutches?
DISABLED PARKING AREA
-I’ve loaded everything.
-All right. Go.
But...
Even if it's a fake cast,
don't you think it’s a little dangerous
to drive with it?
So you live in this neighborhood.
I live around here, too.
If we make a left, that would be my house.
I don’t want to know. Keep going straight.
Okay.
Drive slowly, safely and quickly.
-Oh, no.
-Seriously!
I'm sorry.
Goodness.
Sorry, I didn’t know
you were standing here.
Where should I put all this?
-Just leave it here.
-Okay.
Now I feel like I’ve been
some help to you.
This is not a big deal at all.
Ever since I met you,
good things keep happening to me.
My friend calls you
my knight in shining armor.
-"Knight"?
-Yes.
Gu Ae-jeong.
From now on, don’t act like you know me.
don’t talk about me to others,
and don't act like we're close.
That would be helping me out.
Understood?
Yes, I understand.
If that kid calls me again,
I’ll report you.
I didn’t make him--
Then erase my number from your phone.
All right.
Did you call me your knight?
You’re a demon to me,
so back off!
All right. I’ll back off.
I’ll get going now.
Good night.
Hey, Ae-hwan.
I’ll be right there.
Okay. See you.
It’s that song.
It bothers me in an odd way.
FIGHTER
Next customer please.
Goodness, hurry up.
DOKGO JIN’S MOVIE FIGHTER
A BOX OFFICE HIT!
FIGHTER SURPASSES THREE MILLION
NEARLY FOUR MILLION IN THE THIRD WEEK!
WE'RE TOGETHER UNTIL THE END!
Ms. Moon,
I think Jin not going to Hollywood
helped his film succeed.
I thought the movie would get bad reviews,
but it didn't because
people felt bad for him.
Anyway, it’s a relief
that he didn't get discouraged.
He’s got a schedule today, right?
He’s in such a good mood
that he decided to do all the interviews.
Today, he said he would drive himself
to the studio.
If he was always like this,
it wouldn't be so hard being his manager.
Who's the most handsome actor
in this country?
Jang Dong-geon? No, the one with style.
Cha Seung-won?
No, the actor who made it big
with his movie, Fighter!
Dokgo Jin! Ding dong.
This is Dokgo Jin’s world
Thank you for today.
You did a good job today.
Please call me again.
I heard you got a fixed show.
Yes, Couple Making.
We'll start recording soon.
That’s a big show.
After all you’ve gone through.
I’m worried. I have to do well.
I’m sure you will.
Thank you!
Goodbye.
Hi.
They greet you based on ratings.
I’ll get going.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Hey, girls!
You should greet people when you leave.
We did.
To everyone, not just me.
What’s up with her?
And you all came late today, right?
Did you or did you not apologize
for being late?
If you do well now,
you’ll reap the benefits later.
I’m telling you this out of affection
from my experience. Okay?
Bye.
-Hello.
-Hi.
She must be crazy! What’s up with her?
-She did that last time.
-What’s wrong?
-She keeps bothering us.
-It's annoying!
Ignore her!
You used to be her road manager, right?
I think that's why she looks down on us.
It's so annoying.
-Pil-joo!
-Hello.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
Let’s go.
You’re already at the studio?
I'm on my way.
Jae-seok,
I’ve been too nice to you lately, right?
Hurry up.
Darn it.
Dokgo Jin!
Right, he told me not to act
like I know him.
Okay!
She's acting like she knows me again.
Why are you calling?
I knew you would do this!
I told you to delete my number!
Why didn’t you erase it?
Erase it right now!
Seriously.
He doesn’t delete mine.
Why should I delete his?
Done.
Sir?
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to order my girls
to greet people
and make them apologize?
A nasty bum like you.
What could they possibly learn
from you and your advice?
From now on,
don't overstep your boundaries.
It looks pathetic.
Wait.
Girls,
you can't act like this.
You'll end up like me.
Do you want that?
Isn't it frightening?
From now on, when you see me,
don't be proud. Be scared.
Like this gaze right now.
Let's go.
Come one, let's go.
AE-HWAN
I want to meet this person.
Gu Ae-jeong?
Why do you let them slap you?
Wait, I don't think you should leave
right now.
What are you doing?
Thank you, Mom.
Eliminated in five minutes.
It'll create tension from the start.
Doesn't that sound good?
He might not recognize me
if I'm in full makeup.
Ms. Gu? Are you really Ms. Gu?
I’d rather leave the show.
So you're saying I can't be on the show?
I don't see my name in here.
Asshole?
They're all for you,
so choose anything you want.
Subtitle translation by Sunny Jeong