Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Please watch the movie by yourself.
I don't want to go in.
Coming here is the most I can do.
I've come to my senses
and want to go back now.
I've bought the cola and popcorn you wanted.
I even bought potatoes.
Why are you acting like this?
I'm really, really, really afraid
of that potato.
Are you avoiding me because you're afraid
I'll catch your chicken and torment you?
That's right, I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of myself
for not avoiding your torments.
In fact, I don't even find it tormenting.
I really want to live my life
with a cool attitude.
I went through so much pain
throughout the years before I learnt that.
I'm really afraid
that even at such an age, I'll be moved,
making me forget all that I've learnt.
Dok Go Jin, your anger towards me might
have blinded you and made you fearless.
But what will you do
if I told you to catch hold of me?
So please put a stop to it right now.
Because you are my man
Because you are my love
After sending you away and letting go,
you still remain and make me cry
Because you are my man
[Fighter]
It's because you are still my man
I can't hold back these foolish tears
Gu...
I cannot live without you
I am fine even if it's hard or painful
I can't stop my love for you
I've caught hold of you.
It will never change
even if the world ends
What are you going to do now?
My love
Will you let yourself be caught
or will you run away?
I cannot live without you
I feel ashamed,
so I won't catch hold of you again.
I am fine even if it's hard or painful
What do you want?
To let go of you?
Should I let go?
Even if I am out of breath,
even if my heart stops
Everyone is looking.
How can you hold onto me like this?
Only if you are by my side
I'll be dead if someone sees us.
Let go of me before we get recognized!
Let go!
I love you, I'm just right here
Dok Go Jin, what are you doing?
Can you see or hear me?
Don't move.
It will be your fault
if people recognize us.
I can't stop my love for you
I can't see.
Don't show your face,
so they can't see you either.
It will never change
even if the world ends
Where are we going?
Follow me quietly.
I've caught hold of you.
My love
Oh... hey, hey.
So he was really here.
Since there are two cups,
he must have been with someone.
Who is she?
Is she also an actress?
Is she someone more famous than me?
It seems when it's time
for rumors to spread, they'll spread.
Those rumors of them breaking up
must have some truth.
Will they announce their breakup
during the broadcast of our show?
Dok Go Jin has to consider many factors,
so I guess he'll keep it under wraps
for the time being.
But... who do you think he's with?
Probably a top star
of the same the level as Kang Se Ri?
If rumors of them dating spread
before the breakup with Se Ri is announced,
that woman will become
the third party who came between them.
Third party?
If they had already broken up,
she wouldn't be a third party.
The parties involved may see it that way,
but others will see her as the third party.
People think that Dok Go Jin
and Kang Se Ri are still lovers.
No one will recognize you
and misunderstand things.
I can't say for sure if it was Shin Min Ah
or Han Ye Seul sitting here.
But you're Gu Ae Jeong...
Thank goodness I'm not a top star.
If you want to get into a scandal with me,
you should at least dress better.
Am I someone who get into scandals
with people dressed like that?
Thank goodness that I'm dressed so shabbily.
For someone who's not a top star
and dresses so shabbily,
how can you make Dok Go Jin so distressed?
You're doing a good job.
Dok Go Jin...
Is it that distressful for you to like me?
I've never liked anyone other than myself.
To find myself
liking someone else is distressful.
For that someone to be you of all people
is extremely shameful.
How distressful it must be...
to have felt so ashamed
and then be rejected.
Don't bring that up again.
It reminds me of the shock
I received at that time.
Was it that big of a shock? It seems
you've never thought I'd reject you.
Of course I haven't.
It would be akin to you receiving
a rice cake from heaven.
Wouldn't you bite into it eagerly?
- And if I bit into it?
- I would have let you do that.
I would have sobered up
from the pain of the bite.
If I had bitten into it at that time, you'd
have sobered up and ended this promptly?
That's right.
If you had bitten it immediately and ended
this promptly, it would have been so easy.
Really.
Immediately and promptly?
Sounds quite easy, doesn't it?
Don't change the meaning of my words
with your expressions.
Dok Go Jin...
You said you've never liked anyone
other than yourself.
That means I'm your first love.
Why are you saying that?
You're making me feel ashamed.
Shall I make you feel even more ashamed?
The first love you finally have at this age
shall forever remain one-sided.
I will never, never like you.
Hey...
Hey, hey, hey, Gu Ae Jeong!
Gu Ae Jeong, Gu Ae Jeong!
Let go!
I'll take back my words.
Let's do this all over again.
Usually, under such circumstances, we
have to first get you some branded dresses,
turn you into a beautiful princess
and change you from inside out.
I skipped that step.
Let's do that
before we come here again, okay?
I'll arrange that for you.
Don't leave.
If you have money for that,
just give it to me instead.
What?
I'll then be able to end this
simply and quickly
according to the outcome you wished for.
I'll accept rice cake to make you sober up
immediately and end this promptly.
Do what I wished for?
Try doing it.
Dok Go Jin, you look really easy.
Do you want to sleep with me?
What?
You sobered up immediately, right?
I'll leave promptly then.
Hey, Gu Ae...
I was really cool up to
when I caught hold of her.
Maybe I shouldn't have gone for the wine.
Now that I've let her know
how I found her easy,
things have gotten really difficult.
[Fighter]
During the coming studio recording,
we'll assign the outdoor date locations
during the Mission Match segment.
Now, look over here.
Sweet Picnic, Refreshing Hike,
Romantic Cruise, Luxury Dinner...
Since we won't know which of the four
you'll be assigned to,
please arrange for a more flexible schedule
during the week.
It seems everyone hasn't established
a clear screen persona yet,
especially Ae Jeong unni.
An irritating persona is quite interesting,
why don't you try to play that role?
Aren't you being too concerned about
being called unattractive by the viewers?
I'll try my best to be up in your face,
but in reaturn,
as the show's MC,
play along with the jokes for me.
Just like Yoo Jae Suk and Kang Ho Dong*,
(*well-known TV hosts in Korea)
join in alongside the participants.
And we can make things
more exciting together.
There's a Chicken Fight* game planned.
(*contestants on one leg knock each other)
When I ask you to join the Chicken Fight,
please accept the invitation. Please do.
That's right, the Chicken Fight
would be great to watch.
Today's filming looks like a sports meet.
The atmosphere is really heated up.
If you emerge champion, choose the hike
and get him to teach you to ride a bicycle.
I think that's probably
the most popular option.
What kind of comedic act
should I make today?
Well...
Oh, wait a moment.
Isn't this helium gas?
Look here.
Ae Jeong, isn't this funny?
Try this.
This is so funny!
Oppa, see me try it.
Oppa...
Oppa, oppa.
- This is funny! This is hilarious!
- Let's do this during the show.
- Oppa, oppa... Wow, this is so funny.
- It will be a hit.
I'll go speak to the producer.
Oppa.
Gu Ae Jeong.
Yoon Pil Joo.
What's wrong with your voice?
I inhaled some helium gas.
That day at the cinema, you must
have been quite shocked because of me.
I acted that way
because I had to hide for a reason.
- You're not upset, right?
- I'm not.
You feel it, don't you?
Thanks for your help.
You're trembling, aren't you?
Although I'm being serious,
my voice sounds really funny.
How much longer
must I try to read your mind?
I need to adjust it a little.
Tell me how you feel.
It sounds okay now, right?
It sounds okay.
Don't pretend to be indifferent.
This is really fun.
I'll give it a try too.
You don't have to do anything funny, right?
Do what your heart wants you to.
Are you asking me
to let you take the idea I thought up?
Catch hold of my hand right now.
I just want to try it once.
Are you really going to do it
during the show?
Quickly catch hold of my hand.
I've got to do it if it makes people laugh.
I'm an entertainer now too.
You feel it, don't you?
Gu Ae Jeong, is it funny?
You're trembling, aren't you?
You're such a solemn character,
this will surely make everyone laugh!
How much longer
must I try to read your mind?
Oh, no... but I'm a doctor
at the Oriental Medicine Hospital.
Who are you?
Tell me how you feel.
Don't pretend to be indifferent.
- This is really funny, Yoon Pil Joo!
- Is it... is it? Is it?!
Do what your heart wants you to.
Those two have really grown close.
Catch hold of my hand right now.
It seems he won't eliminate her
from the show anytime soon.
Just catch hold of my hand.
But is it okay to inhale too much of this?
Catch hold of my hand right now.
Gu Ae Jeong...
I'm really worried.
Inhaling too much of this
gives you a headache, right?
Yeah, I'm really worried
that you'll be really hurt.
I hope you won't be.
But if something happens to hurt you,
come to me.
I'll treat you.
Okay.
You seem like a really great doctor.
Are you sure you didn't see the woman
with Dok Go?
Yeah, I didn't see her.
I'm sure such a person exists.
Who can she be?
Representative Moon, what if Dok Go-nim
dates a kind of poop standard celebrity,
What will you do?
Dok Go? Is he such a person?
Will he lower his level like that?
I'm saying what if.
What if?
If that happens,
I'll send Dok Go to work overseas.
And I'll make sure the other party won't be
able to step into showbiz ever again.
Do you think Dok Go-nim
will let you have your way?
I'll have to do it
without his knowledge of course.
Isn't that the job of a management company?
I've worked so hard
to protect Dok Go's image.
I can't let that scorned artiste
destroy all of that.
Se Ri and her production team
went to the cinema
to watch your movie last night.
Did you see her?
No.
I didn't see Jae Seok secretly tagging
behind me on your orders either.
I think Se Ri wants to let the team
know of your close relationship.
She asked me to send flowers and a cake
to the filming studio in your name.
Today is the anniversary of the
official announcement of your relationship.
So just let her have her way.
What filming studio?
Is it for Couple Making?
Yes.
I'll personally bring
the flowers and cake there.
- Really?
- Yes.
I need to go take look
if I don't want to be rejected so promptly.
That's right.
The effect will be better
if you went personally.
Representative Moon, am I really that nasty?
Why did you ask that out of the blue?
You never worried about that.
I didn't... But this personality
often creates problems for me.
Difficult problems.
Dok Go Jin, there are things
too difficult for you?
Yeah, it's gradually becoming
extremely difficult.
We'll start right away.
Get ready.
Ready, Start!
[Chicken Fight]
The match has started.
Gu Ae Jeong's leg seems weak to me.
[Gu Ae Jeong wins!]
Will she be able to reach first place?
She did it!
The champion for today is Gu Ae Jeong!
Gu Ae Jeong, please say a few words...
Gu Ae Jeong's persistence and passion
is really shocking.
She must have been
the National Treasure Chicken!
No, the National Treasure Chicken
from our group was Kang Se Ri, not me.
How can that be?
This is the first time I've heard of it.
Is it true?
She was the best when it came
to Chicken Fight games on TV shows.
Didn't we shoot a commercial
as the National treasure Chicken?
Se Ri, you remember that right?
Yes.
Since we've all forgotten, there's no reason
not to dig that out and have a look!
Let's look at the old records!
Go search for
National Treasure Girls' chicken commercial.
Okay, we've just watched it.
That was ten years ago. Ten years ago!
We were really young.
And we have no reason not to see them
in a chicken fight either!
If the MC allows me to,
I'll challenge her to that.
I'll do my best
if that's what everyone wants to see.
But it won't be interesting
if we just compete like that.
Shall we add an incentive?
Shall we?
If Gu Ae Jeong wins,
she'll get to go on two dates.
If I win,
I'll go on the date on her behalf.
I'll just have to win, right?
I can't lose then.
The match is about to start.
Which of the two will become
the Chicken Queen?
Okay.
I'm getting nervous myself.
We're starting.
Get ready.
Ready, start!
Gu Ae Jeong has exerted herself a lot today
so the situation
is quite unfavorable for her.
But as for Kang Se Ri,
she hasn't played this in a while either.
So, who will emerge winner in the end?
- We can't tell right now.
- Gu Ae Jeong, Gu Ae Jeong.
Gu Ae Jeong! Gu Ae Jeong!
That's right.
I used to be the National Treasure Chicken.
Despite that,
I didn't get to hold the chicken leg.
[Geudae Chicken]
Because of Geudae Chicken,
my heart goes "thump thump" forever.
I love only chicken,
my heart is filled with that rich taste.
Opening my arms widely,
I offer you this delicious chicken.
I will give you the greatest chicken.
Cut, cut!
Hey.
The chicken leg should be held by Ae Jeong.
Why is Se Ri holding it?
Se Ri, switch with Ae Jeong.
Se Ri, do you want to come to the front?
It's okay.
You're holding the chicken leg.
I'm holding the chicken wing
so I'll go to the back.
We're starting.
I offer you...
I will give you the greatest chicken.
- Kang Se Ri.
- Gu Ae Jeong.
Things are different now.
I am the MC while you're just nothing.
Gu Ae Jeong, Gu Ae Jeong, Gu Ae Jeong.
Gu Ae Jeong...
She's really strong.
Nice, nice.
[Muscle Pain Reliever]
[Refreshing Hike!]
Here.
Thanks.
You were really good
at the Chicken Fight game.
Was I?
It will affect a week's worth of screen time
so I tried hard like my life depended on it.
Are you good at riding the bicycle?
Actually, I can't ride bicycles.
I've got to practice.
Anyway, my screen persona
is one who is pushy and annoying.
So, even if I pestered you to teach me
how to ride, don't get upset.
Please react well to it.
Just do all you have to.
I'm an entertainer now too.
The Oriental Medicine physician
I respect most
is the Man of the Sun*, Doctor Lee Je Ma**.
(*drama about a **19th century doctor)
Why did I become an entertainer?
Lee Je Ma?
This line is really funny!
Can I bring this up in our conversation
during the show?
- Sure.
- I'll jolt this down.
Pen...
Here.
Let me share with you
an interesting tagline I thought of.
The Man of the Sun,
Doctor Lee Je Ma, helps patients.
But the entertainer, Yoon Pil Joo,
helps Gu Ae Jeong.
That punch line catches on even better.
Thanks.
This is that precious pen of yours?
Yes.
Please use it well and return it to me.
[Gu Ae Jeong]
I need to go look for Eun Ho hyung.
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
Yes.
He's really cool.
The Oriental Medicine physician,
Lee... Ma... Lee what?
Lee Je Ma.
You gave me a shock!
What are you doing?
Gu Ae Jeong, you're really good
at chicken fight.
You were just like a chicken.
Your chicken act was great.
Chicken act?
Is it that funny to see me
work hard to make a living?
Can't you say something more decent?
I am praising you.
I wanted to make a joke
out of the chicken analogy.
It's not funny at all.
You laughed so hard at the cold jokes
Yoon Pil Joo made.
Can't you just laugh along
for the chicken fight joke?
I laughed at Yoon Pil Joo's jokes
because they are funny.
That's true. You have to smile at him
to get into his good books. Work hard at it.
A pushy persona fits your image well too.
You've done a good job with the persona.
It will be a hit!
Are you saying
I have a pushy and easy image?
Are you mocking me?
I'm motivating you
and giving you some encouragement.
I don't feel encouraged by you at all.
If you're here to torment me again,
go over there. Over there!
I came to impress you.
I want to impress you so I did those
hard things to praise and encourage you.
I'm not taking you lightly,
insulting you or mocking you!
If you want to encourage me,
just watch the broadcast.
Oh, well...
Dok Go Jin's mouth is just like a butthole
so it's expected that whatever you say
turns out that way.
But still, just hold it in,
just hold it in a little.
When your real butthole
feels like letting it out,
you'll also hold it in
until you reach the bathroom, right?
So, when your mouth wants to let it out,
just hold it in a bit
and ask yourself if you should let it out.
Assess the situation before you let it out.
You're giving me an advice now, right?
When you give advice,
you ought to make it sound good.
Although I want to say
words coming from the messy Gu Ae Jeong
are expected to sound foul,
I'll surely hold it in and not say it out.
That's right. In any case,
thanks for the praise and encouragement.
I'll work hard
so as to survive till the end.
I'll surely end up as a couple
with Yoon Pil Joo.
What?
End up as a what with who?
Couple... a couple.
Isn't this show called Couple Making?
Oh, yeah...
The show is about that.
Well, I think I'll be able to make it.
Yoon Pil Joo seems to have
a good impression of me.
It will be great
if I could survive till the end.
Gu Ae Jeong...
This belongs to that
Oriental Medicine physician, right?
- Yes.
- Give it to me.
Doesn't it look nice?
He said that
it's a very precious gift from someone.
He'll be very angry with you
if you lost this.
I think so.
What are you doing?
Tell him you lost it
so that he'll be angry with you.
Why?
Because you have to like me.
Drop out of this show immediately.
Stop it!
Don't do that!
Dok Go Jin, you're really too much!
What should I do?
How can I find it?
How can I find it
when there are so many balls?
Is it a surprise for Se Ri?
Dok Go Jin is really as attentive
as portrayed by his image.
Yes, he always treats Kang Se Ri this way.
Se Ri is in a bad mood
and won't come out from her van.
What a great opportunity.
Since Dok Go Jin is here,
- it will be great if he helps cheer her up.
- That's right, that's right.
Hey, Kim Jae Seok, you punk...
- Hello.
Hello, hello.
They're in the middle of a meeting?
Mr. Jae Seok, shall we get going?
Excuse me, Dok Go Jin, please help us out.
Se Ri is in a really bad mood right now.
Can you think of some surprise event
to help cheer her up?
Yes, we need to continue filming.
Please save us.
Isn't this your first anniversary?
If you have a surprise event planned out,
please do it to your heart's content
in this room.
Yes, please help us.
- Please help us.
Se Ri is...
I guess I'll have to help you all then.
Let me prepare a special event.
- Thank you.
That's great!
I want to see what he's going to do!
What should I do?
It's not here!
Where's my sneaker?
My sneaker, my sneaker!
Dok Go Jin, I'll bury you under these balls.
[Refreshing Hike!]
This is Kim Jae Seok.
Where are you right now?
Dok Go-nim is waiting for her
in the dressing room!
Oh, the dressing room.
Oh, my, my.
Gu Ae Jeong?
What are you doing?
I'm in the midst of a surprise event.
- Leave, leave!
- Surprise event?
To impress me?
You seem very angry.
Just calm down
and let me explain the situation to you.
Shut your butthole!
Leave!
I wanted to be understanding
and just let it go,
but I don't think I can do that.
Gu Ae Jeong.
Praise and encouragement?
I don't need any of these.
What are you going to do
about the pen you made me lose?
Get it back for me.
Gu Ae Jeong.
- And please stop appearing in front of me.
- Leave, leave.
Just get lost!
I will never, never like you.
What are you doing?
Hey, please be careful with that.
You received a lot of scorn and hardship
because of me.
It seems you really harbor a lot of anger
towards me.
I'm trying to apologize
using praise and encouragement,
but you don't seem willing to accept it.
As for the fans* you lost because of me,
(*'Pen' and 'fan' sounds similar in Korean.)
you ought to hold fan meetings
or fan autograph sessions to win them back.
What do you expect me to do
by directing the issue towards me?
- Take this.
- Okay.
Regarding your declaration
that you'll never, never like me...
It's really a pity.
Leave quickly.
What is she doing?
Where are you going?
She's really strange.
How annoying.
Top Star, Mr. A, was preparing
a surprise event for his lover Ms. B
when he got humiliated by Ms. C
for no reason.
Ms. C, who had been bearing a grudge
towards Mr. A,
even took a studio prop
and swung it around threateningly,
astonishing the staff who were looking on.
Ms. C and Ms. B were previously
in the same girl group.
Ms. C is first on search rankings.
But the search term below that
is Gu Ae Jeong.
Netizens are really scary.
Anyone reading this
can tell that it's Ae Jeong.
Ae Jeong, you've got to eat.
I don't want to eat, Father.
[Camellia Flower]
It looks like she's really very angry.
[Gu Ae Jeong, I was in the wrong.
I'm sorry and... ]
and...
will repent...
I will never, never like you.
Who asked you to come say those things?
Why is this so difficult to handle?
I'm really sorry.
I've asked the prop master to contact me
when they start to clear the ball pit.
I'll find it for you then.
Let's look for it together when they clear
the pit. Didn't you lose your sneakers too?
I really don't know why I'm so unlucky.
My chest feels so tight,
I'm going to die from it.
Don't stop that,
please continue to press on that spot.
What?
There is an accupoint over here.
Pressing it helps to ease chest pain.
You're giving yourself treatment unknowingly
based on your instincts.
I don't know why but my hand
just presses here without me knowing.
People will all find a way
to keep themselves going.
Everything will turn out well.
Really?
Of course.
The most important thing
in a course of treatment is trust.
Somehow, I always feel
that I can trust what you say.
Send all of these to the props storage room.
Yes.
I'm feeling better now.
Ajusshi, Ajusshi!
Did you manage to find the pen?
What pen?
Didn't I ask you to help me out?
I asked you to call me
when you find a pen in the ball pit.
I got it, I got it.
Please contact me, okay?
- If she doesn't find the pen,
- I said I got it.
- she'll feel really guilty.
- You have my contact details right?
I'm Gu Ae Jeong, okay?
I got it, I got it.
Our status as a couple
is making things complicated.
I'll settle things through
my management company soon...
So take note of it.
Is it because of the report
on Mr. A and Ms. B?
Wasn't Ms. C the only one affected?
That's right.
Ms. C was the only one sacrificed.
Ae Jeong unni always has really bad timing.
Why did she pick that place to confront you?
She was also like that in the past.
When?
When we were part
of National Treasure Girls.
The day when she yelled at me
had to be that one day
with many reporters present.
- What did you do to provoke her that day?
- What?
Gu Ae Jeong must have acted that way
because you provoked her.
I didn't do anything.
Just like how she scolded you
although you didn't do anything to her...
I did do something.
What bad thing did you do?
It was just a small prank.
Do you hate Ae Jeong unni that much too?
What bad thing did you do?
A prank too?
Thinking that I did the same thing as you
makes me feel shameful.
Since Ae Jeong unni said
that she hates you as much too,
just avoid each other.
I didn't see her for ten years
after that incident too.
Ten years...
It's too long.
Let's settle things between us soon.
What?
Where are you going?
All right. Please enter, please enter.
- All right.
This is the place.
Thank you for opening the door for me.
Aigoo, you're Dok Go Jin.
I've got to open the door for you.
My wife is your fan.
Please give me an autograph when you leave.
Of course I will.
But this room is really big
so I'm not sure if you can find it.
- Please take your time then. Okay.
- All right.
Now, please search for it
like your life depended on it.
Okay.
[MBS Props Storage Room]
Dok Go Jin.
We've found them.
[For our son]
Thanks for the hard work.
Yes.
Is this what you're looking for?
That's right.
It's the same as the one I lost.
I'll take this.
[Top star Mr. A got humiliated]
Mr. A in this report is Dok Go Jin
[by troublesome Ms. C!]
And Ms. B is Kang Se Ri.
Ms. C must be that Gu Ae Jeong or something.
Aigoo, what can Ms. C do?
Someone as unpresentable as her will always
do things that are unpresentable.
Her nick name changed
from Ankle Girl to Commotion Girl.
Is it because
she brings trouble to everyone?
Yes.
This is really funny.
I have to tell Pil Joo
not to get too close to her.
Welcome.
Hi, can you tell Director Yoon Pil Joo...
That's Kang Se Ri's father.
Hello.
Aigoo, hello.
Yes.
My daughter has been feeling
quite depressed recently
so I came to discuss her condition
with Director Yoon.
He went out for a while.
I read the news report yesterday.
Mr. A, Ms. B and Ms. C...
It's because of that, right?
She must be really upset.
You look very downcast too.
Nurse Kim.
Yes?
Please bring some Kong Jin pills.
These are Kong Jin pills.
This...
Please take one.
Eating one each day
is really good for the health.
Aigoo, I just started chewing
and I already feel more energetic.
You should ask your daughter
to buy some for you.
Kang Se Ri makes a lot of money, right?
I'm giving this to you as a sample
because you're her father.
Each one costs two hundred thousand won.
Two hundred thousand won?
Then this sample...
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10.
It's worth two million won!
I'm giving this to you
since you're Kang Se Ri's father.
I'm not...
Actually, my daughter is...
Ae Jeong...
[200 thousand won]
[In total, 200 thousand won]
is really full of affection* for me.
(*Ae Jeong means "affection.")
Se Ri would be really thankful to you.
I'll accept this with thanks.
Hey, Ding Dong!
Come over here.
Hello.
Your aunt is not answering my calls.
Is she at home?
She said that she'll be home the whole day.
When you reach home,
tell your aunt to answer my call.
If she doesn't answer, you answer it
and then pass the phone to her.
Okay.
- Go.
- Goodbye.
Wanting to see Gu Ae Jeong is as difficult
as plucking a star from the sky.
She'll cheer up if I return this to her.
But I really don't want her to get friendly
with that Oriental Medicine doctor.
Who was that?
We shouldn't speak to strangers.
He's Dok Go Jin.
Dok Go Jin?
You're lying!
He's really Dok Go Jin.
You're lying.
It's not a lie!
I am Dok Go Jin.
And we know each other.
If you have a cell phone,
you can use it to take photos.
Really?
Yes, take some photos as proof.
And tell the whole neighborhood
how amazing this kid is.
Come on!
Got it, Aunt.
I told her to come pick me up
so she'll come over.
Okay, good job.
Your aunt is also an entertainer.
Don't your friends know about it?
I didn't tell them about it.
Aunt told me not to tell anyone.
That's true.
Entertainers who are disliked
will cause even their family to get scorned.
Hey, Ding Dong.
It's okay for you to tell everyone
that we're close.
I'll send you a 100 autographs
to distribute in class.
Thank you.
What is this?
A lie detector.
Let me have a look.
If you lie, a red light will flash
and it will say you're lying.
You're lying, huh?
You shouldn't lie.
So it's a lie detector
which lied about being a lie detector.
But saying we're close although we aren't
is lying, right?
Is it okay for me to lie?
Say that you're close to me.
We're close.
The red light didn't flash.
Since this isn't a lie, you can say that.
Answer me, Ding Dong.
Okay.
That's right, that's right.
Security is disarmed.
Where is Hyung Gyu?
Hyung Gyu.
Let's go. Get up.
What are you up to?
Did you make me come pick up the child
because I didn't answer your phone calls?
I didn't.
I met him on the street
and he insisted on following me,
so I had no choice but to bring him back.
Do you think I waited
in front of your nephew's school
and told him to make a phone call to you
just to get you to come over?
I am Dok Go Jin.
After you said you'll never...
never like me, do you expect
I'll do such things for you?
Never mind if you didn't.
That's right... I didn't.
I won't catch hold of you from now on.
Yeah, don't catch hold of me.
How great...
- You're disappointed, aren't you?
- What?
You're now at a loss because I said
I won't catch hold of you, right?
What are you talking about?
I am not.
Don't lie.
I'm not lying.
This is a lie detector.
If you lie,
it will beep and a red light will flash.
Speak the truth.
What are you doing with a toy?
Yeah, the child is precious to you,
isn't he?
Look at your Ding Dong while you speak.
If you lie, Ding Dong will grow up
with the same physique.
What?
If you want your Ding Dong
to possess a physique like mine,
don't lie and just speak the truth.
You're disappointed, aren't you?
You're disappointed because I said
I won't catch hold of you, right?
I am not.
You're lying huh?
- You shouldn't lie.
- It was a lie, wasn't it?
Take it away.
- It was a lie, right?
- Take it away!
Are you okay?
I got hit by *Pororo's head. (*Korean
cartoon character on the lie detector)
It's really painful.
It's swelling.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
My eyeball is swelling up.
Dok Go Jin was hit by Pororo.
That's better than saying
you got hit by Gu Ae Jeong.
At least Pororo is a top star.
But it's really a little red.
Did the small blood capillaries burst?
I need to attend some promotional events
in Japan tomorrow.
Let me take a look.
Look straight at me, look straight.
It looks okay.
Look at this side.
That side.
I think that side is fine too.
This side...
This side is red.
I think it seems okay on closer examination.
What a relief.
Gu Ae Jeong...
It's my turn to say something.
You be the lie detector.
I find... Gu Ae Jeong difficult.
She's not at all easy.
She's really difficult.
If I were to find that
Oriental Medicine doctor's pen...
Will you take back your comment
about never liking me?
If you find it, I'll forgive you.
Only forgive?
That's right.
You hate being seen as easy.
It will be shameful for you to take back
those words so easily.
I'll have to make it such that
you can take them back
without being embarrassed.
I'll be in Japan for Fighter's
movie promotion from tomorrow onwards.
There is something I hope you can do for me.
Come and feed them.
Why are you asking me to do that?
I'll activate the security system
before I leave.
You're the only person
who knows the code for disarming it.
You didn't change that 6090 code?
Yes, only you can come in.
I've never told anyone the security code.
If you don't come,
they'll all starve to death.
Don't hold me responsible
even if they starved to death.
Why should I go in and out
of Dok Go Jin's world?
Use the lie detector against your heart.
Then, you will come into my world.
I will never, never like Dok Go Jin.
You're lying huh?
You shouldn't lie.
She will find this
after feeding them a few times.
When she finds it,
she'll be able to forgive me and take back
her words without embarrassment.
Where should I say I found this
so that she won't see through my lie?
This is difficult.
She will only feel at ease
if we manage to recover it.
Hey. Hey, Hyung Gyu.
Did you really go to Dok Go Jin's house?
Yeah, we're really close!
I'm not asking you that.
Er... What did your aunt
and Dok Go Jin talk about?
I didn't hear their conversation.
You ought to listen!
Dok Go Jin is really popular in Japan.
If Dok Go Jin appears in your music video
for your new album,
maybe you can also ride on the Hallyu wave.
Manager Gu, don't count your chicken
before they are hatched.
Ae Jeong, don't think that I'm unaware.
The phone number stored under
"Camellia Flower" belongs to Dok Go Jin.
When will the flower bloom?
Thinking too far ahead
will make you lose grip on reality.
Unni.
Let's take a photo here for today's post on
Me2Day*.(*microblogging similar to Twitter)
Wait, wait a moment.
- Give me the eye drops from France.
- Okay.
Are you really going to announce
your breakup with Dok Go Jin soon?
Yeah... I need to make myself
look distressed before that
so that I can get more sympathy
and receive less censure.
Then what about
the one billion won commercial?
I don't know either.
Thinking about it makes me feel like crying.
It's upsetting.
Take the photo.
That will do, right?
It's upsetting.
The security system is disarmed.
Hello...
I just came to feed you all.
Your owner
lost a one billion won commercial.
He'll be so upset
if he sees you starved, won't he?
I feel really guilty
because it seems to be my fault, so I came.
Eat more.
Please help by looking after Ae Jeong.
She's going to release an album soon.
Please broadcast our music video
after your show.
Gu Ae Jeong is going to release an album?
As for her music video,
we're thinking of getting a top star...
someone on the level of Dok Go Jin
to appear in it.
Isn't their relationship very bad?
That's not true.
Did Manager Gu say that?
Representative Moon...
As someone who has been watching
Gu Ae Jeong since her debut,
I'll give you a piece of advice.
Please don't invest too much effort
into Gu Ae Jeong.
If you're referring to scandals around
Gu Ae Jeong, I'm well aware of them.
No.
Do you know the real reason
National Treasure Girls broke up?
When National Treasure Girls broke up,
other than the disharmony with Kang Se Ri,
were there other problems?
Things that happened between
me and Ae Jeong unni in the past?
Dok Go oppa also asked me that before.
Dok Go asked you about Gu Ae Jeong?
Are you trying to look into my past scandals
in order to settle the relationship for us?
Settle what?
Dok Go oppa said
he wants to settle things between us.
Haven't you heard about it from him?
When did he say that?
He said that when we hit the tabloids
because of Ae Jeong unni.
What exactly did Gu Ae Jeong
say to Dok Go at the studio?
She barged in and started yelling at him.
I heard her saying
that she will never, never like him.
Did she?
Was Dok Go referring to Gu Ae Jeong
when he said it was difficult?
How can that be?
That can't be...
[Gu Ae Jeong]
Children, your food is coming.
I'll fill this up before I go.
Thankfully, we came back
earlier than planned
So we didn't get delayed at the airport.
Are you feeling unwell?
I always feel unwell
after riding an airplane.
Do you want to go to the hospital?
It's okay, take me home.
The fish feed
should have decreased by a lot.
It didn't decrease at all.
What does this mean?
She didn't come at all?
And you all starved the entire time?
The sender is MBS's Prop Storage Room.
[Gu Ae Jeong]
And the receiver is Gu Ae Jeong, right?
Yes.
Courier delivery.
You feel it, don't you?
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Goodbye.
You're trembling, aren't you?
Yeah.
How much longer
must I try to read your mind?
Tell me how you feel.
Don't pretend to be indifferent.
Do what your heart wants you to.
This is Yoon Pil Joo's pen!
Catch hold of my hand right now.
They found it!
See, I was right.
Quickly catch hold of my hand.
Someone from the Prop Storage Room found it
and sent it to my house.
This is yours, right?
Every time I happen to turn my head around,
Wow, this is my pen.
Thank to you, I got it back.
Our eyes will meet.
It was because of me that you lost it.
I'm really sorry.
Since we've recovered it already,
you don't have to feel sorry anymore.
That scene keeps appearing in my dreams,
Does your heart feel more at ease now?
Bothering me all night.
I was really worried.
Isn't this very expensive?
Since I recovered it thanks to you,
I'll treat you to a meal.
You feel it, don't you?
You're trembling, aren't you?
I'll buy you the most delicious dish at the
restaurant you said your best friend runs.
How much longer
must I try to read your mind?
Can I accept the treat?
Isn't this a very expensive pen?
That's true.
Tell me how you feel.
Don't pretend to be indifferent.
[To our son]
Do I have to give this to her personally?
Dok Go Jin!
What are you doing here?
What are you doing here, Manager Gu?
What?
Aren't we in front of my house?
Are you here to see Ae Jeong?
I came to give her something.
Ae Jeong is at Jenny's restaurant right now.
Is that so?
Are you going over?
Yes, because
I have something to give to her.
Hey, hey, don't go.
Just go up and wait for her.
Ae Jeong is waiting for the
Oriental Medicine doctor right now.
Who?
The one who's participating
in the same TV show with her...
They aren't really close but Ae Jeong found
something of his which she previously lost.
So he's treating her to dinner.
Well, please go up.
I have something
to discuss with you too.
What discussion?
After a short while,
Ae Jeong will be releasing an album.
So, regarding the music video
and promotion events,
there are some things
I want to discuss with you.
Discuss that with Representative Moon.
Yoon Pil Joo is coming
so please serve a delicious pizza.
Add more toppings.
Don't worry.
I'm a "Pil-follower."
Pil-follower?
[Camellia Flower]
Oh.
Are you in Japan?
What are you doing?
I'm having dinner out.
With whom?
Yoon Pil Joo is treating me to dinner.
That Oriental Medicine doctor?
You lost that person's precious pen
yet he's treating you to dinner?
Because I recovered his pen.
- Did you really recover it?
- Yeah.
So, you asked him to treat you to dinner
because you recovered his pen?
Well, I found it.
It's very expensive.
You must have impressed him a lot
by helping him recover that expensive pen.
I have to impress him,
we're on the same show.
You really put in a lot of effort
just to impress him.
Keep it up.
He hung up?
In order to impress that man...
she lied?
Ae Jeong?
Yes, Oppa.
Did you meet Dok Go Jin?
Nope, isn't he in Japan?
What do you mean?
I met him in front of our house.
He said that he has something for you so
I told him you're there. Didn't he go there?
- He didn't come.
- Is that so?
Anyway, since he's going to meet you,
when you see him, bring up the issue
of the album and music video.
- You must, okay?
- Oppa, please stop it.
Goodbye.
Aigoo, seriously...
Did he come?
He knows that I am here.
Why did he just hang up like that?
He must have gotten angry upon hearing
that I was dining with Yoon Pil Joo.
I'm leaving right now.
- I'll get there in about 10 minutes.
- It's a relief that you're not out yet.
Can we eat together another time instead?
Oh, okay...
I'll treat you next time.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Okay.
Since I said I'll forgive you if I recover
the pen, I guess I'll have to forgive you.
Potatoes...
Since I fed the fish,
shall I also feed their owner?
She's being so difficult towards me,
but she can lie so easily
for that Oriental Medicine doctor.
I was too easily disarmed.
[Manager Gu]
What's the matter?
Dok Go Jin...
If you meet Ae Jeong later,
please give her a clear answer
regarding the music video and album
I mentioned to you earlier.
What?
Well... Ae Jeong seems to find it difficult
to broach the subject to you directly.
He hung up so quickly.
Dok Go Jin.
The security system is disarmed.
Hi, I'm here, Dok Go Jin.
You came? What about
the Oriental Medicine doctor?
The appointment was cancelled.
I heard that you came to our house?
My brother told me.
So?
Since you went all the way to the house,
I thought that it was something important,
so I came over.
I have nothing to see you about. Is there
anything you want to see me about?
You brother wanted to discuss
the music video and album with me.
Are you here to discuss it with me
personally?
Gu Ae Jeong, do I look that easy to you?
It's not about that.
I came to forgive you
and take back my words.
Because I recovered that pen.
Stop lying and...
cut to the chase about your requests.
- What's with you?
- Shall I put it in simpler terms?
Gu Ae Jeong...
I'll help you put out your album
and shoot the music video.
- So sleep here tonight.
- What?
I've come to find you easy too
so I'm asking you to sleep here tonight.
Let's just end it here, easily and quickly,
okay?
I guess I shouldn't have come here.
I had a great meal.
Was it delicious?
It was really delicious.
Please come again with Ae Jeong next time.
Okay.
I'll be going then.
- Goodbye.
Gu Ae Jeong.
Please just pretend that you didn't see me.
This is embarrassing.
I seem to have something in my eyes
What's wrong?
I'm just feeling a little unwell.
I'm feeling unwell so my tears just...
That's why my tears keep flowing
Pressing here doesn't work.
I have been hiding a part of my heart
Pressing here doesn't work either.
What would work when tears
just keep overflowing?
A certain person can't even sense it
thus bringing me to tears
Even if you cannot hear me
During times like this...
Even if you cannot hear my heart
The love my tears convey
Will you finally hear it someday?
Doing this should work.
Because you are my man
Because you are my love
After sending you away and letting go,
you still remain and make me cry
I feel so embarrassed.
Because you are my man
It's because you are still my man
I can't hold back these foolish tears
You seem unable to hear my heart
Why can't you hear?
Why can't you see me?
Turn around I'm here
What I'm saying is that I love you,
you fool
Don't watch.
You are Dok Go Jin.
Because you are my man
Because you are my love
Don't watch.
Don't cry anymore, I am sorry
that I can't let you go (I love you)
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator: karened
Spot Translators: fore, Beeni
Because you are my man
(You are my love)
Timers: em_ily<3, dizzybugs
I cannot give you up at all
Editor/QC: aaachec
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com
crunchyroll.com
I'm begging you to listen...